Yes, I was drinking Alkma Hall. It was a Kazi's birthday yesterday.
Shame for having a birthday.
We all got fucked up. We all got twisted, if you know what I'm saying.
That wasn't very Jehovah's Witness of you, having a birthday.
That's true. Having a birthday is the... yeah, yeah.
I have a bunch of Jehovah's Witnesses in my family.
My mom's side is a bunch of fucking... a bunch of fucking kooks and weirdos and crystal healers and Jehovah's Witnesses and shit.
Oh, God.
I know. I mean, famously, one of them, like a couple years ago at Christmas, I was drinking a diet soda and one of them came up to me and was like, you know that's rat poison, right?
I was like, yes, thank you, yes.
It says it on the wall. That's my favorite.
You know it's rat poison, right? What are you talking about?
Fucking old kook. You old fucking bitch.
Leave me alone.
I bet she's not vaccinated. I bet she's dead.
Oh, God, I know. It's probably true.
It's probably true.
Almost definitely true. Almost definitely. Who knows what's in it?
Yeah, who knows?
Nobody knows.
My mom was on a bit of an anti-vax arc for a while, but I spoke to her yesterday and she was like giving a bunch of pro vaccine arguments.
And I was like, oh, good.
Hmm. Okay. Yeah, that's good.
That's growth. That's character growth.
Childhood is, I don't know, not getting vaccinated.
Adulthood is getting vaccinated.
I don't know. I don't fucking know, whatever.
That's correct.
I can't wait for a booster shot.
I can't wait for my booster shot.
I can't wait to get another microchip.
I know. I already got the funny microchip once.
Yeah, it needs friends. It's lonely in there. It needs friends.
I have a friend who's unironically into that.
He believes a microchip is from Satan himself.
Are you serious?
Yeah, he found a video of a guy that kind of looks like Bill Gates giving a conference on, here's how we can chemically remove religion from the brain.
And, quote unquote, religion is just like fanaticism.
Apparently, they're running experiments that could reduce people's ability to blow themselves up.
Like suicide bomb.
I mean, that sounds kind of good, actually.
If we could actually do that with the microchip, I would kind of appreciate the microchip.
No, actually, no, that's not true.
Terrorism is good, actually. I learned that from Final Fantasy VII.
Yeah, that is an important lesson.
And then his other point of contention was there's a chemical in the vaccine Satan microchip called Luciferis.
Lucifer, oh no.
Is that true? Is there a chemical called Luciferis?
That is a chemical.
Well, that changes everything.
It's called, it has Lucifer in the name because it emits light and Lucifer in Latin means like light or some shit.
What, no, hold on, what are you talking about? Words can only mean one thing.
Yeah, words can only mean Satan.
Every, all words.
All words mean, it's Satan or get out.
Ugh.
Did they already complain how hungover I am while we were recording? Did I already do that?
I don't remember if you did.
I feel so shitty. I feel like complete dog shit right now. Holy fuck, this is the worst. This is the absolute worst.
Man.
I had a back, I have a back problem right now. I've developed a back problem, a consistent back problem.
I mean, God, hopefully not.
Since lifting, so they started lifting again. I developed a pain in my back and it got really bad the other day and I went to the doctor.
I went to fucking urgent care. I was like, because I didn't have a, well, I had to call my insurance and be like, hey, give me a doctor.
I don't have a doctor. Can I have one? And they were like, yes. Yes, you can have one. Here you go. Let's sign you up.
They gave me a doctor and I was like, can I go see him? And they were like, you can see them in three weeks.
I'm in pain now though. And they were like, well, you can go to an urgent care and we'll probably cover that.
So I went to one. I had to wait for two, not that urgent because I had to wait for two hours in the waiting room.
And then they, and I was like, hey doc, my side hurts. I'm afraid it's my kidney and I'm afraid it's a kidney infection.
And they were like, well, pee in this cup and we'll tell you. And I did. And they were like, no, it's not a kidney thing.
And I was like, okay, well.
It's just, the culprit is keto once again.
I think it's just, I pulled something or I strained something. Yesterday, yesterday, yesterday it felt great.
I couldn't even feel it. I was like, I'm recovered. It's over. It's gone.
Today, it sucks. I can't sit. I can't even sit comfortably. And I'm gonna cry.
I entered my back horrifically in like May.
Also, before I tell the story, is this staying in or we didn't even do an intro or are we waiting for people to come on?
We didn't do an intro, but oh, yeah, we didn't do an intro. Hi everyone, patreon.com.
Oblivionfall.
Oblivionfall is our guest today.
Yeah, the guest is patreon.com slash oblivionfall. Hello.
True, true.
I'm doing the thing now.
Yeah.
I'm just stolen it from you, Ben.
Every draw cast, I plug myself.
Do you actually?
That's so cringe. That's so cringe.
I know. It's so good.
Yeah.
Yeah, no intro.
No normal intro. Fuck it. Nobody else showed up. It's just me and you.
Epic. That's fucking funny.
Yeah, sure.
So I have a terrible back. It all started in 2013. Some of my animator friends, including the one who is telling me about the Lucifer chemical.
This is before he went off the rails, which is sad because he is one of the people I've known the longest on the internet.
That's a bummer.
I'm actually going to move, so I'm going to lie down. I'm actually going to lie down on my...
I'm going to move my mattress and lie down.
What is this? The sleepy cast? What are you doing?
God, I wish. God, I fucking wish.
Okay. Let me know when you're laid down.
I'm getting laid down.
Oh, jeez. I'm not. That's great.
If you know what I'm saying.
Damn.
I'm having sexual intercourse if you know what I'm fucking saying.
Oh, God.
So one day...
I've done this before. I remember I've done this before and people complained that my mattress was creaky.
So I hope that happens again and everyone hates it.
Everyone hates your creaky mattress during sexual intercourse.
Right. All these hot bitches are like, I love your dick, but I hate how creaky your mattress is. I'm afraid it's over.
It's over and I go, I don't care.
Go on. Get out of here. Go home and be with your own kind.
The row rocks at them and they go, ah, they run away.
Damn.
Yeah. Sorry to keep interrupting. Go on.
That's all right. I'll resume.
Please, please.
Back in my pivot animation days, I met a lot of cool people.
I was meeting up with some of them in 2013 because a few of them lived in Australia and I was still in New Zealand at this point.
What we did is we went to my fucking high school and we just fucking took pictures of us goofing around.
No one was there. I think it was a weekend.
I'll throw a couple random pictures in chat of us just being goofy.
I'll fucking stand up and walk over to my computer.
Oh, you see, you see.
No.
And so we goofed around the high school and then one of the pictures, this third one here, I just put it up on Facebook.
I wasn't thinking anything and someone just said like, what the fuck is wrong if you're back?
I was like, what do you mean? And then I looked and clearly God had used the circle tool in Microsoft Paint to cut a hole in my back.
Because I don't know what else the fuck is happening there.
I was so confused.
It looks like you're doing it on purpose.
Apparently, but then I noticed that like, huh, I guess my back is kind of fucked up and then it kind of got more fucked up over time.
And I started having like really bad back pain and I realized, oh shit, I need to like sort this out.
So for a while, what I did is I got a bouncy ball chair.
Well, what do we call it? It's not called a bouncy ball chair.
It's like a chair that is like an exercise ball like on wheels.
Apparently that's supposed to help with your back or some shit, which it actually did.
I was also doing a lot of exercise with my, I had a personal trainer like a few years ago who was helping me out.
So that was pretty neat.
But then Jim is expensive and the balls kept deflating every time.
I went for like four of those chairs because I kept just fucking deflating on me.
So I gave up and now my back's been in decline again.
And it's really bad.
So in May, I'm across the room, by the way, I went up to the wall and I d-dag zaggles on Twitter recommended that I get a tennis ball.
And I get a tennis ball and I like, and I like use it as a massage tool and I like, like, like something like back against the wall and I roll it around.
I'm doing that right now.
I've been told that too.
And I didn't do it.
It sometimes sort of helps a bit.
Sometimes I feel a little better after I do it.
A chiropractor told me to do that.
And being a chiropractor, I did the opposite.
Chiropractors aren't even real.
Exactly.
They're not even real scientists.
Yeah, they're not.
They don't watch freaking Morty.
It's a soft science like economics.
It's not real.
Yeah.
It's all made up.
They're just massage boys.
I mean, at the end of the day, it's true.
Well, in May, or I think maybe late April, I don't fucking remember exactly when it was.
I'd spent like a week with my feet on the desk.
I was like slouching on my chair, like at the Olympic level, dude.
And it was bad because it started really fucking on my back.
I'm like, you know, I should do those stretches that my personal trainer taught me.
I haven't done those in like a year.
What could happen?
And so one morning I was up like super early or something.
I was going to call off my friend and I just started doing one of the stretches.
And I did the hip bridge and something fucked up.
Like it wasn't like there was no, there wasn't like a click or there wasn't like a singular
moment where something fucked in my back.
But like I was doing it for like 10 seconds and I was like, oh, oh, this hurts.
This hurts more than it should.
And then I, you know, collapsed down and then I realized I couldn't move.
I was stuck on my back and I couldn't actually, I couldn't roll over.
I couldn't move.
I was in extreme pain.
Wait, you did that?
And you did that by doing the stretches that like the doctor recommended to you?
That my personal trainer did.
Well, yeah, the stretches are designed to help.
Yeah, they designed to help my back and they were really helpful back then.
But I guess I'd been out of it for so long that I wasn't ready for it or some shit.
And I couldn't move for like 15 minutes.
I was on the floor and I was, and my friend was just on discord because I had my headset on.
I was like trying to like, took me ages to like be able to get back up and talk to him.
And he was just like, oh, fucking jeez.
And it didn't get any better throughout the day.
And I couldn't even like, like sitting was the most painful thing.
I could keep my, keep my back straight was fine.
Standing up was fine.
Laying down was fine.
Anything else hurt so bad.
Like request, request.
Why can I speak?
What the fuck?
I had to get request.
I had to get.
I had to get two weeks off work where pretty much for a whole time I couldn't sit in a chair.
I had to like mainly lay like, I forget how it was.
There's like a specific position that was like really helpful, like laying on my side or something.
And oh yeah, I had to lay on my side with a fucking body pillow like between my knees.
It was like the ideal thing to recover because I don't have fucking health insurance.
So I googled like what to do and you injure your back and they're like, yeah, doctors just going to charge you money and just tell you to do this.
So just do it.
I'm like, okay.
So I did that and it worked and I've been worked on my back since then, but that was fucking.
That was a fucking time.
That sounds pretty fucking.
I was really scared I would become Tom.
Yeah, that's what we're all trying to avoid.
Next thing you know, you're writing for SaverSpark and then it's all over.
It's all fucking over for you.
Yeah, I was a bit, I was a little disappointed actually because on the one hand it would be bad to have a kidney infection.
But on the other hand, if I had gone and that she had told me like, yes, you have a kidney infection here or some antibiotics to take, it will go away.
I'd be like, cool.
And then I would do it and then the issue would go away.
But now she's just like, no, it's not a kidney infection.
It's just nothing.
It's just whatever.
It's nothing.
You just got to fucking deal with it.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
I love it when it's nothing.
Yeah, it's no the problem we're having.
It's nothing.
Just deal with it, loser.
My will, I suppose.
You know, back when there was health insurance in this household, I guess it was before we moved into this apartment.
Good times, good times.
Well, my partner used to have health insurance a few years ago and they were going through some kind of medical like catastrophe where they were basically throwing up like everything they ate for like a month.
Like even water, they would throw, they would vomit, food vomit.
Like one out of every 10 meals would stay down.
They were blacking out constantly.
They were losing weight.
They were in pain.
It was awful.
And multiple times we went to the emergency room and they would just, they're just like, sure, here's some fucking saline, I guess.
Yeah, nothing's wrong.
Go home.
Nothing's wrong, go home.
Also, give us 500 bucks.
Nothing's right, I'm torn.
And that happened multiple times and they just were fucking around being assholes.
And then eventually, they were like, oh, like five months later, they were like, oh, I guess we got to take your gallbladder out.
And it was like, oh cool, you couldn't have figured that out five months ago.
Yeah.
They just didn't even want to check.
Man, loving that health insurance is really worth the money.
Jesus.
Didn't Mage have her gallbladder out at some point?
Oh yeah.
Didn't she say that she had to go, it wasn't just like they did an operation and they took her gallbladder out.
She said she spent several months in Russia or something, or the Ukraine or something, in some sort of health camp, whatever that means.
Wait, I vaguely remember that, yeah.
It was like she did eventually just have surgery and have her gallbladder out.
But before that, yeah, she spent like, she went away to some health camp where they did alternative medicine shit of kinds I can only imagine.
This is just like, oh geez, Lois, this is just like that time in Golden Girls.
This is the reference I always go to when doctors are bad.
This is just like the time in Golden Girls when Dorothy has mysterious fatigue and doesn't know why and she keeps going to different doctors and they all go,
eh, have you considered that you're just like a stupid woman and you don't know what you're talking about?
And she's like, yes, doctor, I have considered that, but I still don't know what's wrong.
And they're like, well, I think we've cracked the case.
Get out of my office.
Oh yeah.
There was a bit of that, though, even from female doctors and nurses and shit.
They'd ask you about, you go in there because you got this pain and you're throwing up constantly.
And they're like, how's your sex life?
And my partner's like, I'm asexual.
I don't really, I don't do sex.
That's a phase.
You'll get over it, says the nurse.
Wait, that's totally irrelevant.
That's totally irrelevant to why I'm here to say that.
You'll want to have kids.
You better fucking breed, she said.
You gotta be fucking joking me.
Really?
They would just take the opportunity.
Let me take this opportunity to tell you, you should be having more sex and more babies.
Okay, cool.
It's pretty weird.
Well, the doctor didn't tell me that.
Well, that's because you're not a woman, Ben.
Yeah, it's true.
Yes, so who cares what I do?
So who cares?
Shit, I just remembered I left a portion of a Chipotle burrito down the street in Kazi's house.
Okay.
What do I gotta do?
Hold on, hold on, give me 10 minutes.
Give me a 10 minute hiatus as I walk down the street.
What do you say down the street?
I think you meant on a mailbox somewhere.
Yeah, it's a street burrito.
Street tacos.
That's what we in the biz call a street taco.
I've had some of those.
Can I switch to my phone?
Maybe you can switch to my phone and just record through Craig.
I walk over there, grab my burrito.
Eleazar is going to love you.
And walk back eating it.
Fuck Eleazar.
No, it's not true.
I'm sorry Eleazar, I love you.
I don't care that you're cheating on us with the gamer zone, it's fine.
It's okay.
Our draw cast editor is cheating on us with Nate and someone else.
Oh, is it no need?
It is no need, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What a slut.
I know, right?
What a fucking slut.
Oh, I think C.T.A.L. at everyone about a game of draw telephone for the draw cast.
And I didn't look, I was like, I'll look later and I think I may have missed it.
You can still get in.
I kind of wanted to.
We're not even halfway through the list.
We can just add people to the list and move them around who haven't done it yet.
So, you can easily still get in.
Well, maybe I should do that then.
Yeah, Teleperte is involved in that.
I know, I know.
I want to get in.
I want to be, I want to time it so I'm next to that guy.
That can be arranged.
I want to sneakily.
I can find a way to sneak you on to an episode of the draw cast with Teleperte if it means
that much to you.
No way.
You could actually get me on the draw cast.
In that no way.
I mean, you are a very, very unknown small artist, but it could happen.
That's true.
It's sad, but true.
Yeah, I think, yeah, yeah, I thought it was pretty neat.
I thought it was pretty neat that I was invited into that server.
I would be on a draw cast sometime.
I think Gib was talking about that she was on a draw cast.
Yeah, she was on the animation episode where we did an animation in 45 minutes, which was fucking crazy.
Which is, I mean, it's a bit of a cheat.
I mean, that's not even fair.
That's what Teleperte does is makes quick animations.
I know.
That's like his whole thing.
Is Teleperte a guy?
I think he's a guy, right?
He's a guy, yeah.
He destroyed us, but it was pretty cool.
Of course.
The deck was stacked.
Honestly, all of us did pretty fucking well.
Even C.T.O.L. who had never animated before did a pretty cool animation for that.
I mean, the theme was animating an amogus, killing itself.
Which, of course, they've got a very simple character design.
It's easy to draw.
We did a stick figure fighting one a bit later.
That should come out in a few weeks.
Teleperte was also on.
Oh, like a Zhao Zhao?
Yeah, Xio, Xio, whatever you call it, Zhao Zhao.
I don't know if I'm saying it right.
I mean, I was in the stick figure community for years.
I was deep in that shit.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Did you make any?
Oh, yeah.
I was legendary in my community.
You were legend?
Really?
Yeah, I think I mentioned before.
I didn't know this.
I got my start as a pivot animator, which is like...
Pivot is like this stick figure program that you...
If you've seen it, you probably saw some kids using it at school.
That's typically how...
People I know who've heard of it say they've seen it before.
It was specifically a stick figure animation program.
Yeah.
The way it works is really cool, actually.
Let me see if I can get a picture of it.
So it's kind of hard to explain without a visual aid.
Here we go.
This image should work.
Sorry about my creaky mattress.
I can't hear the creaky mattress.
But Pivot basically looks like this.
You have a stick figure and he has these little red joints.
You just click on them with the mouse and move them around.
Then you hit the next frame button and it saves the pose.
You can just position him.
There's no drawing required.
You can create custom figures and shit.
It's very simple.
It has less features than Microsoft Paint.
But it's really good for learning the basics.
There's no shortcuts.
There's no tweens.
There's no nothing like that.
Teleparter got his start doing that.
So did a lot of people I know.
It was cool.
Do you know what that is cool?
Most of the people I got on were people from the Hyun's Dojo server,
which is all about stick figure fighting.
Hyun's Dojo?
Yeah.
It's a discord server for stick figure animators
who are, I guess, fans or associated with an animator called Hyun,
who did some shit for League of Legends.
Bass.
I was a fan of that guy since 2009, even before League was a thing.
But yeah, basically we got a bunch of cool stick figure people on
to animate a stick fight for a draw cast.
And that was also cool.
And it's not even out yet.
But it will be soon, maybe.
Fucking neat.
Fucking neat as hell.
I haven't watched one yet.
I haven't watched a draw cast yet.
But I've seen the episodes you've been putting out.
I saw you guys got, did we talk about already,
that you guys got YouTube destroyed, but then they fixed it?
Oh yeah.
Your channel was Nukes or something, right?
Yeah, YouTube Nukes.
By accident?
Yeah.
You have a Nukes for spam and deception, like severe deception.
What does that mean?
Well, I had to look into it because I'm like spam.
Is it because we're uploading quickly?
No, YouTube wants us to upload quickly.
They want everyone to upload quickly.
If I can't fucking be the reason.
I had to look up YouTube's policy for deceptive practices
and spam and shit.
It turns out the bar you have to cross
is the lowest fucking bar in the world.
You know these YouTube channels that will upload?
Hello guys, it's BlackPant for 2017 4K.
Watch on YouTube for free.
Oh yeah.
I hate that guy.
And the video is just a fucking JPEG for an hour
and there's a virus in the video description.
It's basically that.
Wait, what?
Apparently that is what YouTube thought we were.
I actually don't know the thing you're describing.
Oh my god.
The video is, I've seen YouTube videos that are like,
if you're looking for a movie,
it will say that it's the movie
and then it will just be a still image
that's like look in the description
and the description is a link to a downloader site
that will give you a virus.
Yeah, that's basically what I'm talking about
is that kind of shit.
So that's what YouTube is like.
There's spam policy and deception policy
is mainly to stop people from doing that shit.
Or just like posting nefarious links in general
or trying to trick people into clicking on shit
that is fake to that degree.
So I was like, yeah, I'm pretty sure we didn't do that.
I'm pretty sure, yeah, I don't think so.
And we followed an appeal
and we heard fucking nothing for almost a week.
And then we just made a Twitter post
which nothing really happened.
Vintela Perte retweeted it
and it got solved within a couple hours.
Yeah, that's how it goes.
That's how it works.
That isn't that the way they say it goes.
Sad but true.
If only you'd had big famous friends
to save the PCP when it was under fire.
If only.
Well, we had a couple,
but maybe not Teleperte-sized.
So it did eventually get fixed.
It's not that fast.
Yeah, just a few months, you know.
Although, yeah.
I saw, is YMS still having the thing
with like his side channel got demonetized or something?
And for a while there, he kept tweeting about it
and it seemed like they weren't doing anything.
Oh yeah, didn't his game channel got nuked for terrorism?
Yeah, because, was it like a 9-11 joke or something?
Yeah, there was a 9-11 joke.
It was really messed up.
Hmm.
Did they fix it?
I don't know if they fixed it.
When a channel like YMS complains about something,
they always get what they want, because they're big.
You would think they would be like,
oh, sorry, sir, right away, sir.
I haven't seen a post about it in a while.
I mean, I could just look up that in plays
and see if it's there.
See if it exists, come on YouTube.
Well, it was always there.
It was demonetized, though, was the problem, right?
Was it? Hold on.
I'm trying to read the post,
because I found the post on Twitter from Adam.
This is him talking about YouTube claiming
that he supports violent criminal organizations.
Hell yeah.
Just lean into it.
Oh, yeah, okay, I see what happened.
He got a guideline strike, so it wasn't free strikes
and he's out, he just got a strike that was stupid.
Yeah, I don't know if I'd ever got resolved.
I see multiple tweets of back and forth between YouTube
where he's like, hey, YouTube, I'm not a terrorist,
and YouTube's been like, hi, after reviewing,
you are a terrorist.
Which is like, thanks.
You gotta be like...
Huh, what?
Oh, sorry, you go.
I'm gonna say you gotta be like, well, if YouTube
tells them, thinks I'm a terrorist,
then maybe I really will be a terrorist.
Maybe I'll show them what a terrorist I can be.
I'll show them how many funny 9-11 jokes
I can make and tell my audience that blowing up things
is cool, actually.
We'll see. We'll show them.
Okay, now you go.
I mean, you did say that terrorism was cool
at the beginning of this podcast.
I mean, I am a traitor of America.
You are.
Thanks, C-Tol.
Thanks, C-Tol, for getting me on the Traitors of America list.
That list probably doesn't exist anymore, huh?
That's a shame. I hope it still exists.
Maybe that guy, I think that guy deleted his Twitter account.
What's his name? Irate Gamer?
Wait, is it Irate Gamer or someone?
Pretty sure it's someone else.
Maybe...
Well, he had a name like that, though.
It was like One Angry Gamer or something.
Oh, yeah, One Angry Gamer sounds right.
I think Irate Gamer was like some ancient,
like, angry video game nerd knockoff.
Yeah, yeah, I think you're right.
So, sorry Irate Gamer if you're listening to this.
I didn't mean to impugn your character
by implying that it was One Angry Gamer.
Much completely different.
Irate Gamer's character has been impugned enough already.
Let's be fair.
That's true, that's true.
Is he the one that basically just completely stole
Angry Video Game Nerd's shtick?
I'm pretty sure.
God, I first heard of him
when I found my first Doug Walker video, I think.
There was a video I found on YouTube
fucking years ago of like...
It was called like the longest insult ever
and it was the nostalgia critic, like
calling someone a dirty, fucked up,
sadistic piece of shit for like two minutes.
Just a big string of ad-homs.
It was great and I was like,
wow, this is funny, who's the Irate Gamer?
And I had no idea.
Wait, why did you think...
Was he insulting the Irate Gamer?
I think so.
That's sort of what it was related to in some way.
Why was he insulting the Irate Gamer?
What did he do?
Why would he do this?
Hold on, I mean, I guess I could look it up.
Why would you so viciously attack one of...
Literally, one of your co-workers,
one of your contemporaries,
one of your peers?
Why would you attack them like this, Doug?
I don't know.
I mean, according to this,
that's just what the title says.
And unless the insult was from something else
and there was some Irate Gamer drama
and everyone was just putting this video at him saying,
hey, this is you, which I don't know.
Hey, this is you.
Hey, I bet Doug's talking about you right now
and he's like, I don't know about Doug.
Everyone was like, oh my god, Doug Walker
and talked for two minutes
about what a piece of shit someone is.
This makes me think of the Irate Gamer.
I gotta tell the Irate Gamer, okay, this is you.
Oh my god, there he is, it's young Doug.
It's young Doug in a more innocent...
A more innocent time.
You know, back when the wall was slightly beige.
Back before...
Oh, the wall behind him, not the wall review.
Oh god, no, not the wall review.
I've seen...
I've watched so many videos about the wall review.
I've...
The wall review is great.
It's actually a great video because it's inspired so many,
highly entertaining takedowns
and think pieces about why is this what it is,
why does this exist, why is this so terrible.
Why is Corey Taylor from Slipknot involved?
That's my big question.
There's so many things about it
that are like, why would you do this?
Why is this the form this project took?
Yeah, fucking Fena.
I knew about Fena already because one of my furry friends
was like introvert stuff
and I always thought it was creepy and weird
the way they move around.
Is Fena a girl?
I don't know if Fena's like the creator is a girl or boy.
I think the character might be a girl.
Maybe.
Is one of the characters named Fena?
Actually, maybe not.
I think Fena is the artist and the...
God, I don't know.
I'm just thinking of the creepy rat thing
with the sharp teeth and the rat thing on the side.
No, that thing's not named Fena.
That has a different name.
Lucy Lace Maker?
That sounds correct, actually.
I just thought all the characters were named Fena.
Maybe that's my mistake.
Every character is named Fena.
It was after I watched a Folding Ideas video
about the wall.
That was a pretty good video.
I love that video.
It's so good.
But he talks a little bit about Fena
and he sort of explained...
He says that it's bad, but it still made me curious.
I was like...
It's like a multi-media...
It's like an expansive universe.
It mixes animation and real-life actors.
That's kind of odd.
That's sort of unique, I guess.
I'll go and look at some.
I went and navigated over the channel
and I looked at it and it really is...
It is an interesting idea.
It's an interesting way of making a cartoon.
But it's...
It's like someone tried to interpret Vivzi Pop's style
into Uncanny 3D.
Uncanny 3D?
Like...
It's like...
It's like watching a high school or home movies
with just ad-libbed the dialogue.
When the actors are talking it all feels ad-libbed
and aimless.
I watched one that was like...
It was like a guy brings another guy to a field
and he's like...
Yeah, we own you now. You're my slave now.
We're gonna make you work in these fields
and do farm work for me because I own you.
Him and Lucy just like...
I don't know, they just ramble about it.
The guy goes...
I'm in a predicament and Lucy goes...
It's what you deserve, mate.
This is payback for what you've done.
What have you done, lad?
Why have you brought me to this field, son?
Why did you bring me to this field?
Because it's cheap to film in an outdoor location
as in the public field.
The crowd will never be yours.
Okay.
What do we have to work with for our video?
We have a camera
and we have a bunch of outdoor places that we could go.
Okay, so what story can we tell
in which it only involves our characters
like walking into a field,
talking to each other for a minute,
and then the video ends?
Okay, indentured servitude. Got it.
Okay, that's easy.
I guess when it comes to videos in fields,
Favre in the field is the best video of all time.
Favre in the field.
This is my favorite fucking video on YouTube, probably.
I save it about 10 different videos,
but this is one of the 10.
This is what FedEx should have spent their time doing.
Just animating JPEGs moving around
rather than really complicated 3D models.
The thing about FedEx is it is impressive
how much we're able to do,
but more movement does not equal better animation.
The characters are just constantly
moving up and down.
They're constantly wiggling.
It's weird.
It's not good character animation.
It's smooth, but that doesn't equal good animation.
They have some sort of tool set
that enables them to make the character
just constantly be wiggling around at all times
and be good for them.
Yeah, but it's very...
It looks like they're...
I don't know.
It looks like they're floating in liquid or something
and their fur is sort of anti-gravity.
It's all just kind of moving around.
The dialogue is the same.
They're constantly muttering something.
They're constantly mumbling
or just saying some off-topic stuff.
There can be no silence.
There has to be some...
They must overload your brain at all times.
Yeah, it's the same philosophy with the movement
as with the dialogue.
It's just constantly moving.
It doesn't matter if it's going anywhere,
but it's all moving.
Yeah, accurate.
What is this father in the field?
It's like Monty Python.
Oh, I skipped ahead a little bit.
Someone's getting stabbed.
Someone, definitely.
This is okay.
It seems good.
This seems like something Gib would like.
Yeah, probably.
This guy was like a video game review channel
or something, and then he just
didn't make a review in a long time
and then just made this.
And I'm like, yeah, you've peaked.
You can't peep.
Father in the field.
I feel like I wish I had...
If I could freeze time,
I would freeze time,
watch the whole thing, and come back.
But we're on a tight schedule.
We're on a tight schedule here.
We got to be in Cincinnati by sundown,
as Big Joel once said,
for no particular reason.
Joel's not that big.
He's not even named Joel.
What the fuck?
That's illegal.
You can't false advertise like that.
But it's not.
Okay.
My back feels a little better
from lying down.
Sorry about my creaky mattress.
Sorry if my throat sounds like
because I'm laying on my neck.
I have the mattress pressing.
It feels great, though.
Shut up, phone!
Telling me that it's 11.05 in the morning.
I don't want to know that.
Well...
I had my phone delivered to me by my husband.
I had to leave it with him
so it could wake him up
after I started recording this podcast.
And he delivered it to you?
I guess he delivered it to me.
He came out here a few minutes ago
and just put the phone on my desk and then left.
Why doesn't he get his own damn phone?
I don't know.
They'll wake me up at 9.30.
You know why I feel so bad this morning.
You know why I'm cranky.
It's because I didn't have my damn rain sounds.
I forgot to put my damn rain sounds on
for sleeping.
I forgot to put my favorite YouTube channel,
Dreamy Sound.
And I didn't have it.
So I'm not rested.
Dreamy Sound.
I love Dreamy Sound.
You know Minecraft, you tube a dream.
That's where he puts his music from.
Dreamy Sound?
The thing about Dreamy Sound,
this is a bit interesting.
There's actually a little bit interesting.
There are channels where they'll just post
10 hours of recording of rain or something.
Dreamy Sounds does not merely post
long sounds.
He posts that.
But for each sound,
he creates like a
fantasy landscape
to go with it.
He will make like...
Oh yeah, this is the sound of the ocean.
But in the video,
I will put together a little image that's like
a bed floating on like a platform
in the middle of like a
vast like placid ocean.
You can see all the way to the horizon.
Or like...
Placid, Placid.
Placid, okay.
Or he'll be like...
Or he'll composite an image of
like, oh, this is like my dream apartment.
And it's like, you know, it's got
like mood lighting and it's got, you know,
it's like a nice little cozy living room.
And there's like a big window
that looking out on like a city from
like a high rise building.
Or, you know, whatever.
He'll put together these little scenes.
It's like, this is the scene
where in the dreamy sound is occurring.
Oh, these are like...
These are like cool 3D renders.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's cool. It is cool.
I mean, I honestly don't care.
I don't really care about the visual.
I only care about the sound.
But he goes above and beyond and he makes
these little like...
These little scenarios for them.
That's kind of neat.
Wait, hold on. This is cozy rain.
I clicked on a video called dreamy sound
and then the next video
that I thought was the same channel
was actually a channel called cozy rain
doing the exact same thing.
That's just like when I'm watching
my favorite cooking YouTuber,
chocolate cacao.
And then I click on the next video
and I think it's another chocolate cacao video.
But no, it's some other freak.
It's some other freak stealing his bit
of making food that looks good.
And I can't fucking get off to that.
I can't get off to someone else
making a damn jelly tart
because they don't sprinkle the chocolate on it
at the end and they don't do the little
yada, like triumph pose at the end.
And what's even the fucking point
if you don't do the little yada triumph pose
at the end?
Honestly.
Why even live?
That's why I eat food so I can pose afterwards.
He does a little
he doesn't say yada
but he does a little like
fist pump thing.
Is he like
is he like a
Japaneseman?
I think so.
I think so, yeah.
He doesn't show his face.
You only ever see his face
in like dark, in like
shadowed silhouettes. Just for like one shot.
Just for one shot at the end of the video
you'll see his hands and you'll see his body
he's wearing an apron.
And then at the end they'll have a
other recipe and he'll put it on the table
and then you'll have one little shadowed
shot from the side where you see his face
only in silhouette and then he does
a little triumph and pose and then he
brings up a pinch of cocoa powder
and he starts to sprinkle it and then you see
the cocoa sprinkling onto whatever
it is he just made.
And that's all you get to see
of chocolate cacao.
That's cool, Gladdy.
It's so cool.
Mystery is fun.
He's not entirely faceless.
He's mostly faceless
but he gives you just a little bit.
Damn.
I mean, his
tarts are
works of art.
They're not even food.
They're masterpiece sculptures.
The only cooking YouTuber I've watched
is, I don't remember her name.
She's like an Australian
woman
who looks like my mom
kind of
and
Does she talk or is she silent?
She used to
just do regular cooking videos
and then she started doing a video series
where she debunks
fake cooking videos
where people are like, oh hey
pour some batter into a paper bag
microwave it, instant brownie
and they have all these recipes
that are literally impossible
or will actually kill you
and she'll basically explain how the videos are fake
and she'll
life hack.
No big cheesecake.
Put cheese in a bowl
and then put flour in it
and mix it up and yeah.
Cheesecake.
Yeah, I see.
It's pretty good videos
but then she made a lot of them
and I don't want to watch a lot of videos of this.
Yeah.
Speaking of
speaking of debunking
I had never seen
a Doctor Disillusion
No, a Captain Disillusion.
I finally watched
I think Gib mentioned
him in my discord
a couple days ago
and I just was like okay
and I went and looked up a video
and I watched a whole bunch of them
and they're so good, they're so cool.
Have you gone back
to his earliest video from 2007?
No.
Alright, I want you to do that now
and just watch the first few seconds
because it's freaky
Are you gonna post it?
Yeah.
Let me just link it.
I can't wait.
It's so...
This is from 2007.
It looks like Kramer.
Penguin slap debunk.
It looks the same.
Exactly, it looks the same.
He's been doing this shit
for so long
at such a high quality.
It's crazy.
I mean, it's a little less fancy
and he looks younger
and thinner.
So I mean, good for him.
But, yeah, other than that
kind of the same.
It's crazy like
how
good he was early on
and how unknown he was until recently.
I discovered him...
Is that true? Was he unknown until recently?
Well, I mean
recently on the scale of
doing this shit for 14 years,
I suppose.
I discovered him in 2015.
I saw the floating city
debunk video
because I saw that floating around
and people were saying, oh, it's a hologram
and I have a government
that's a mirage and I'm like, it can't be a mirage
because
the buildings are seen from a low angle
and if it was some kind of reflection
you'd see an upside down version
of them or some shit was what I was thinking.
I just found his video on it
and I was like, what the fuck?
What is this production value?
And he had 60k subscribers at that point.
And I checked his social
blade
and he had been sitting at 25k
for a very long time.
That's not even
even for like early YouTube
that's not even that much.
Yeah, and the 25k
had only been for like the past two years
because he had like one video blow up
before that he was like
around 10k
and he was like getting no subscribers for years, it seemed.
That's insane.
I mean, now he's gone big.
It was right after I discovered him
he started blowing up so clearly.
So something must have really hit.
Was it the
I remember the first time
I ever heard of Captain Disillusion
it was when
I don't remember who was talking about it
but some other video was talking about
his video debunking
the staircase.
The infinite staircase, you know what I'm talking about?
The Asherian stairwell.
Yeah, and someone
someone was criticizing him.
I think they said that
his video was
was like too cruel
to the
to the creator
of it because he was critical of that guy
for like, you know, basically turning
an art project into like a hoax.
I'm trying to think
it's perfectly fine to be critical of that.
Yeah, it was.
It is.
Dammit.
I don't remember who.
I don't remember whose video I watched
Captain Disillusion.
They criticized Captain Disillusion
for his take on it.
I don't remember where it was.
Oh well.
I mean
I don't know why you would criticize for that.
In hindsight, yeah, I don't either.
I don't
I wish I could remember because I'm like
yeah, why would you do that?
He did nothing wrong.
Because then
I watched
a bunch of
those Captain Disillusion videos
and I finally saw that one
the staircase one that I had only heard
about second hand
previously and I watched it and I was like
yeah, he is critical of that guy but like
it's kind of
only in the sense that
people who fall down the rabbit hole
of believing
UFO conspiracies
up until like
you know, COVID
denial stuff and all that
like weird fake videos
or like sort of what helped shape their world view
of everything being fake man
so like contributing to that is generally
not a good idea even if it is
for an art project it's good to like
be like hey, by the way, this is fake
just so you know.
Yeah.
See if this proves the lizard men are real.
My boy
Jack Saint made a video
one time
that I really liked. I really liked it
it was a
it was the story of like
a town
in
the US. I forget what the name of the town
was but it was like a
the story basically went
that there was like a telecommunications company
that set up like
a new like internet
service provider like hub
in the town and it like something went wrong
with it and it started to
like produce a noise
it started to produce a constant noise and like
the noise was like unsettling
to the residents and they started to
they you know a lot of them couldn't sleep
a lot of them started to become
like you know have like
mood problems and like a lot of them
they became irate and they started
having like you know it caused
all these all these all these
all the problems you would expect of everyone being constantly
assaulted with an unpleasant noise
that makes it hard to sleep all the time
until and and and and the telecommunications
company just like kept
basically just kept doing like PR
about it and being like
pretending the issue was solved even when it wasn't
and like you know it led to like
you know it led to like some shooting some accidental shooting
deaths in the neighborhood
it was not it turned out it was not a real
story I thought it was a real story
he he later said like
yeah this was like a work of fiction
that I wrote and like
it and like I was like
oh okay well I guess I liked it as a
story and it had like you know it was a
fable about you know capitalism
bad it was like yeah okay
but I think he apologized
because he was like yeah maybe I should
have made it more clear that this was like a
a work of fiction
I was like yeah
yeah I feel a little duped
I feel a little bit duped because I thought this was a real thing you were telling me
I watched the whole video and I
oh I felt I felt kind of stupid I felt like
um
he sort of implied that like you were supposed
to know that it was a fake story
I was like well I didn't I guess
I'm a rube
um
oops
yeah yeah
you gotta watch out
you can't be spreading
spreading fake shit
yeah like a lot of people have told captain
this illusion like oh why don't you make
your own fake UFO video and then reveal it
was you after it goes viral how'd that be
so funny and he's just like I mean I
could do that it would be funny
the people who are in on the joke would
find would be very you know entertained
but a lot of people
are gonna see that video without seeing
the correction and they're just gonna be like
yeah see man this is what the government's
hiding from us the aliens man
and he you know
it's not and that means it's not
worth it which I respect that's
in that's integrity I think
that's what integrity is I mean
is it
so
okay so I guess I guess the client the contention
there is that
if you if you make a if you make
a if you make something that looks
impossible and you put it out there
and then you debunk it
like it does more
it does more harm by
showing the fake
thing then then it does
good by like by debunking
something that's fake and showing
like this is how it can be faked
because
like debunking is good
like in the sense that like
people are putting out fake stuff
into the world
and you can like debunk it and like
you know
some people will be like oh okay that was fake but like
ultimately like
the fake thing would have convinced
a few people and then you can unconvince
a few of them but some of us people still got convinced
so like the net is still
in the bad direction
probably
maybe
I feel like
it's theoretically possible
that you might
debunk something
in such spectacular fashion
that the debunking
gets more
seen more than
the original thing itself
that's true
possibly
you might not be able to guarantee that that happens
so I guess I understand
why you might still not want to do it
it's probably like more of like a principle thing
than a like
I'm doing my utilitarian calculation
of how many people this will
bring which way or the other way
in any case captain D
probably
one of my favorite YouTubers ever
I binge his entire channel like twice a year
because the videos are just
very watchable
I was
binging the other day I didn't finish
I have more to binge
I have more captain D
than I haven't seen yet
it is all good shit
he did a long video
recently about
Flight of the Navigator
I skipped out on it
because I was like I kind of just want to see more
of the regular
the main videos
I mean
lowkey me too
but I still thought
the video was pretty cool
it was still good
it's interesting to talk about how the movie
was made like that's fine and all
but like you know
it's not as dense
it's not as densely interesting
as the D-Boom videos
I can't
I couldn't
I couldn't fucking believe
I don't know
I couldn't believe
he did the laminar flow
when he made the
I looked at his most popular video
I think his second most popular video was
the laminar flow
proof
and it's just like no it's just real
it's just real and like here it is
and then he just does it
oh okay
wow
that was so fucking
funny that video
the ending where like he's like
but if I did want to fake it and then he has
the fucking water flying all around the room
and doing all this crazy shit
yeah and he's touching it and like
he's just fucking
showing off his visual effects skills
because like to me
because I do
visual effects, animation, editing
sort of shit for a living
so the video of his
I mean I was watching him for like
two years before he even came out
the tape measure video was one of my favorite ones
I saw that one
it's not just that he like
you know explains how the video was faked
he will like
somehow like create
a version of the video where he has
removed the visual effects
and like given like the blank like raw
footage back which is so hard to do
we have to like erase the effects and like
paint the background back in
and match the camera movements and shit
and then he'll edit himself into the scene
like to be like look this is how I set up the effect
and you see him walking around in the video setting shit up
and it's like that is so much fucking
work that is like way more work than like
was actually put into the original thing
then they made to make the video in the first place
yeah
it's like if someone gave you a fucking Marvel movie
and you gave it to a guy
and he just turned it back into the green screen room
and like removed everything
that would be really fucking hard to do
I really liked
that one the
tape measure one
and also I think there's another one of like
they're throwing knives
like they're throwing knives at a girl and she like catches them
on ping pong paddles
that was the first one that like
bumped him up to 25k I think
with subscribers
that was the first big video he had
I mean not even
his
I mean his debunking is interesting but like
the reason it's so interesting is because it's like
wow they did this
but they didn't use like
fancy fucking
they didn't use like super technology software
to make like perfect 3D
effects they just
they did it with like
weird little practical tricks
that you're like you just kind of don't notice
when you see it and when you hear it explained
you're like like oh
she already had the knives sticking in the ping pong paddles
she was just holding them backwards
so you couldn't see them
and then she flips them around in one frame
and then it looks like they catch the knife on it but no
they were just already there
oh my god they tricked me
they tricked me
they got me so good
um
yeah the
the way that they cheated
and they like
you know they have the thing
like one shot
like someone must have just sat down and been like
hmm how can I
how can I make it look
like my tape measure
how can I make it look like my tape measure
is coming out of the little thing
and going to a
port-a-potty door and pulling the door open
if I drilled a hole and I put a wire through the door
so you could pull it
and then I cut the two shots together
it's like
it's very admirable
that someone sat down and figured all this out
in the
I guess they work for an ad agency
so they were like well I gotta make some
I gotta make some
video of some weird impossible looking shit
so um
what can I throw together
with some guys in like a lumber yard
um
oh yeah
yeah so good
very cool
um
duh
how you been
how's your life
how's your life going
my life is going cool
I should mention
the GoFundMe
yes the GoFundMe
I saw that
I think I mentioned earlier
in this very episode right now
whoa
I think in 2017
like
my girlfriend was harassed by a nurse
for being asexual
yeah
it turns out
that the reason they were asexual
is because
they were
they're trans
and they just didn't know it yet
that's crazy
having big honking titties
kinda sucks when
you're a boy
I guess so
it might yeah
it might possibly
maybe just a little bit
so
we're doing
they've been transitioning for about 3 years
about almost 2 years on hormones
um
so we're overdue
we could've, I think
most places will let you get top surgery after a year
so we've been doing it for nearly 2 years
with the hormone stuff
and
we need to raise the link
we need to raise like $10,000
because fucking health insurance
I believe I was the first donor
yeah I saw you sent a funny
you sent 20 funny bucks
sorry
sorry my American currency is so
so hilarious
American
American currency
the reason it's funny is because I sent you
like about 20 bucks like a week before
like a week before
oh that's right
oh yeah so it all
what goes around comes around
exactly
well basically you're just trading
your husband's tits
for a copy of Roger Radclon
that comic must be worth a lot then
damn
oh yeah that's
that's just called doing business
making deals
but
you know storytelling is
a donation to this cause
is a donation for gay sex
see I've been, we've been married
like 5 years
sex what even is that
they haven't been comfortable with their body
but this sort of shit is helping
since they started taking hormones
they were like oh hey, hey, sex maybe it's cool
so help me get like
this is what I'm saying
I
what more can I add
what more can I even say
I guess we'll probably
put the link down in the description to
support the
top top surgery
expense
you know it's good
good for them living
their best
life and making moves
yeah it is generally
awkward
like having
big booby in the way
cause I don't want to touch it cause they're not comfortable with it
but I want to like hug them
and tell them they're cool
and go jogging
they can't go jogging
I can't even look at them
I have to like avert my eyes
tell me more
I don't know
exercise sucks
a lot of things suck they get in the way
you know
these boobs were not meant for this world
they must go so help with that
and
it'll be epic
you know what's epic
the epic game store
yeah
what's epic Ben
I don't know I was gonna say
something about
how do I
concoct some sort of like
man it's good
when a person
gets to
be the most
authentically
realized version of their
their authentic self
and whatever
when they have the opportunity
to
make you know
the most liberated
liberation of their self
from the shackles
of flesh and blood existence
I don't know
do you ever have a dream where you
can do anything Ben
um
yeah
bro
lucid dreaming
it's like
you can
control it and shit
you can do anything
you can make it happen
I swear for a certain portion of my life
lucid dreaming was like an MMO
that sometimes if my brain
was lucky I would log in and I would retain
my skills from the last time I lucid dreamed
and I could like level up and shit
um and I save this
metaphorically it was more of it like
each time I lucid dreamed I had like
better control over what happened
I could fly easier
things we just generally
like
this is the plot of secret
in the basement
secret in the basement is that a book?
is that a game?
yeah that's the
spiritual sequel to
legend of the ten elemental masters
it's Ululilia's second book
Ulululu
yeah it's the second book
that's about
I guess
okay it's not actually about
like the kid does
he has RPG
adventures in his dreams
but like he first becomes
okay
it is while he's dreaming
but it's not a dream
it's a real place that he goes
when he dreams
and it's in his basement
so
you would think that he
would either go there in his dreams
or he would find a secret portal in his basement
but no it's both
in his dreams he can find
a secret portal in his basement that takes him to
a real place
that gives him superpowers
oh shit
secret in the basement
is such a funny book
it's okay
the thing that maybe makes it worse
than
ten elemental masters
one it's not about like funny
like fucking tiny
like colorful wizard people
aliens it's just about a kid
and that's boring
I hate children
and it's really long
it's a thick book
and it's kind of repetitive
and it probably didn't need to be as long as it did
but
it kind of flips back and forth between
have you read
ten elemental masters
I've
only heard the name
come from your mouth Ben
on the pcp
I see
I don't think I've really heard of it anywhere else
I don't know anything about it really
well I made a let's read video
I made a let's read video
with terrible video quality
I was really ashamed
that you were reading the book out loud
instead of reading it in your mind
how
but then I couldn't
I couldn't make a video
okay
you say that but like Gib
did her let's read series
years ago
and she didn't have to say anything
she sat down with the book
and she just opened it and then it was just like
ten minutes of just flicking pages
and then there was an N word
then that was it
yeah I should
I should take a page out of her book I guess
well
I kind of want to do
one of those but like with better
video quality and a better
shot
with Secret on the Basement
Secret on the Basement is funny because
in ten elemental
masters it's just about this
weird
sort of autistic
alien
who like just never
doesn't give a fuck about anything
and he can't relate to these humans at all
cause he's just like oh food
I just create
nutrient molecules in my body
I never need to eat
but here's some waffles
here's some breakfast waffles for you kids
oh light so you can see
oh I can see in every spectrum in the world
so I don't need light but like here
I'll just illuminate my
spectrums
he's like oh yeah
I live in a
concrete
a featureless
cubic concrete bunker
deep underground with no light
anywhere because I don't need light to see by
but I guess since these kids are visiting
I will
make my concrete bunker a little bigger
for them and I will
illuminate it with a light source
and I guess I will make
beds for them to sleep in
with fun patterns on the sheets
that look like
things they like
what a gentleman
he has a complete gentleman
secret in the basement is different
cause it's about a kid so like half of the book
is like the kid just like
living his normal life and going to school
and dealing with bullies
but it's funny dealing with
bullies
to the kid in secret in the basement
bullies means that like
one kid like calls him
like makes like a bad
pun in class
and the teacher gets mad and gives him
like 14 detentions
and like that like that's
bully like that's what a bully does
in Ululili's mind
is like be rude in class
and the teacher is like
that's one detention that's two detentions
that's ten more detentions
and then later on all the good
non-bully kids go wow
I can't believe Jessica got 14 detentions
that's gotta be a record
damn what a bully
that's epic
this is a place of learning
you shouldn't be making puns clearly
no like
sometimes
they'll make like a
shitty pun
about something the teacher says
and the teacher will go haha
good one but you shouldn't be making jokes
in class I'm gonna have to give you a detention
for that
like
the teacher will be impressed
but I have to I have to discipline you
for this
so we got the ten elements
earth, water, fire, air, detentions
one of the fundamental forces
and it's
it's a more fun book because
the kid starts out as normal
but then like in his
dream basement adventures
he levels up and he improves
his stats
but the stat increases carry over into
the real world so by the end of
the book
he's literally like stopping burglaries
by like casting ice spells
on like at camp
like at summer camp and stuff
and he's like
he's like tracking down like fellow
like kids that like
got possessed by demons and like went on
like got lost in the woods he's like tracking
them down and like exercising them with light
spells and shit
and
and it's very funny because
everyone around him is just like
wow where did you learn to cast
spells that's neat
oh well I won't ask
any further questions
it's normal
yeah everyone's like wow
I can't believe you I can't believe
you can do you know 19
pull-ups a second
and can like leap
like a hundred feet in the air
that sure is impressive anyway
what were we talking about
bye
god that's funny
it is funny it is funny
I feel like
I don't know if I
like
do you mind if I spoil the ending
spoil as much as you want
the spoilers for Seeker of the Basement
the ending in the end
when his
dream adventures have come to an end
he's got all these
fucking powers his stats are so high
he becomes
a movie star he becomes
like a superhero movie star
but like because
they don't use special effects
he acts in superhero movies
as
himself
because he just has superpowers in real life
why
and then he spends the rest of his life
like well I did that
so now I'll
he just like he becomes a gold medalist
in every Olympic event
he becomes a star
player in every sport
in every league he just wins every fucking trophy
in every league just because he can
they just let him in
they just let the superhuman in
well yeah they do
they just do
at least you're not a woman
if you're a woman we couldn't let you compete
where in the rulebook does it say us
you know
a level 10,000 wizard from
the dream realm can't be
a basketball player or whatever
there's no rule against it
if you were a trans woman that would be
an unfair advantage
but yeah
but no you leveled up
your stats legit you did it
like everyone else you went to the dream world
and you tapped on the little thing
and the wizard with like the barber pole
sign
like gave you
you bought your cosmos helm
from the store
with your igani
you collected igani like everyone else
it's just legit
why shouldn't it just worked harder
he picked himself up by his bootstraps
but the end
when he's finally done
when he's finally done just achieving
peak human accomplishment in every field
of endeavor that exists
what he decides to do with the rest of his life
is become a cop
he's just like well
yeah he's like well I've done everything there is
to do in the world I'm a champion of everything
all I can do now
now it's just like what am I gonna
how can I do the most good in the world
I'm gonna be a cop and I'll fucking
and I'll like fucking cast ice spells
on burglars and like petty
and petty criminals
and drug dealers and stuff
that's the best way to help the world
freezing burglars
nuts off
Ululilia loves cops
he thinks cops are the good guys
and criminals are bad guys
he should have just fucking like it was a mistake
like I can like
Ululilia
I made a mistake like one
like what did this kid
do to get good at acting first of all
why doesn't he just
why doesn't he just work for a VFX team
why doesn't he just like
why isn't he just like
the pyrotechnic guy except he just
shoots the flames out of his fucking asshole you know
instead of
he doesn't have to be the main character to do the elemental stuff
honestly honestly it's
I think in
in Ululilia's mind
he wrote this character to just be a kind of
idealized like good guy
who everyone likes
but
in actuality the character comes off
as an extremely off putting
like weirdo
who like responds
with complete deadpan appreciation
whenever anyone makes a shitty pun
he just goes like
haha that was a very funny joke
he just told
and he goes um
he likes to like he likes to correct people
he's a he's a big smart ass who likes to correct
people and he just likes to bring
up like like a trivia that nobody
cares about in in random situations
he will just he will just start like citing
Wikipedia pages
and be like I know I know a lot about
I know a lot about you know
constellations and astronomy
that that star that's the dog star
serious that's this constellation canis
major you know he's just like some like
obnoxious book nerd like I know all about
the launch dates for the James Webb space telescope
did you know the telescope was supposed to be
launched in 2017
yeah basically but but but you know
he
but in his mind this character he's just a nice
smart guy who everyone likes
and
so why why can't he also be a movie star
why can't he also be you know
the charismatic leading man
but how much how much sex
has had that's that's the real
measure I believe none
I believe I believe none
I don't think we are
he gets like a roommate he
moves in with like his female roommate
but I don't think they're dating
and I don't think he ever gets like a girlfriend
or anything he does he does
rescue a princess and the princess
like likes him but there's no
like there's no flirting or anything
they just he's just like
I've rescued you I just
just here to help you're welcome
okay bye
fight the final boss alright see ya
I feel like religious
huh I love is
really like a religious
do I love do I love Jesus
not to not to my knowledge
no not to my knowledge
I don't think so
there's no mention of like Jesus or
religion or anything and I guess I just
hate I guess I just hate sex
it's the only thing I can think of
I he might be I mean he could
be asexual I don't know
he never he never talks about like
romance or anything like you know I don't think
in any of his dream diaries he talks about
like attraction
or anything like that
not tonight
no he just loves you just loves video games
and he loves it when you
can go run really fast and jump really
high
that's what get that's what gets him off
those are admirable qualities for sure
I am
I think I might have mentioned this along
maybe months ago I talked to him again
and I asked him if he
I didn't I didn't ask him again about whether
he wanted me to make the audio book
for for legend of the 10 element masters
because it was he just seemed like so
uninterested in
discussing that I didn't even ask him
about that I just asked him like how he was doing
and he told me that he was
he told me about the game he was working on
he's making a new a new game
and he said he told me the name
of it and I mentioned it on the on the previous
episode I don't remember anymore what he called it
but it had a name
and he didn't even
he didn't share that much about it with me
but
platform masters
never came out it was never finished but like
the proof of concept for platform masters
basically was the game like it
I feel like we got a full idea of what it was
just from the trailers in which you are
just a little man's
and you run really fast and you jump really high
and there's extremely scientifically
accurate parallax scrolling in the background
that's what platform masters was
this one I don't know what it is
I hope it's something different
also I hope it gets done
I hope it becomes real one day
I mean having
scientifically accurate parallax is the most
important aspect of the video game
that was the thing that he was the most
interested about like in the videos where he talked
about the game he was making the thing that he
focused on the most was how he had calculated
the precise distances of the background
elements and he was like yes
they scroll at the precisely
scientifically accurate speeds
there was one where you were on Mars
and you could see Earth
in the sky and he was like
yeah Earth moves
at the accurate like
if you run like thousands
of miles an hour you will see the Earth move
in the sky like a tiny
like one pixel yeah
barely at all but it does move
I mean
like the people at NASA
who you know created
the big dome over the sky
they should have factored that in they should have used his math
because you know we can see through
their lies
we know the planets are fake
they're not real
there's um
have you played Lisa
um Lisa
the painful
I know of it I've seen
a video on it
there is a part
in Lisa
you know the game is set
in this town of Olaf
and it's like a
post apocalypse but it's not clear if like
the entire world
is in an apocalypse or if it's just
Olaf like if Olaf is just like
somehow separated
from the world because you never hear
anything from outside you can never leave it
um
there's a secret area in one
section
you have to jump down a
a cliff in a spot that you wouldn't
think you would want to jump down but it's a secret
and the hint
of how to do it the hint for where
it is is that in the sky there are clouds
and this one cloud
is like tilt it's like tilted at an angle
and if you and that's
where it's like I guess it's maybe
supposed to be like pointing down
but it also makes me think like
the edge of the world is this like
is this like the sky dome
that I'm seeing
it's heading towards the ground at like a 45
degree angle here and that's why the clouds
are like that are painted on clearly
yeah yeah yeah
and it's like
is this the dome
is this the dome of the sky
is this uh
is Olaf just under like
is it like a Truman show
I was about to say this is season 2 of the Truman show clearly
yeah I'm not sure
I'm not sure if that's the implication
of like the the angled cloud
or if it's just like
just a visual hint
about the video game and I shouldn't even
read more into it
it's it's it's uh it's possible
um
uh bup bup bup uh man Lisa's so fucking good
what a what a good ass video game
funnily I funnily I played
video games you know
wait I hope I didn't delete this image
um there's a
I think the other night um
my husband and a couple of my friends were
looking at a website that like
looks at how many hours you've spent on steam
and how much money you've spent on steam games
and
it was it was uh
I'll link it
if you want to fuck with that stuff
uh sure
let's see where I put the link
I don't I don't I don't spend that much money on
sometimes I will go on steam
every like one year or so
I might go on steam
and buy a bunch of like uh
a bunch of like the cheapest games
I can find things that are on sale
and stuff for like a few dollars each
so I probably haven't spent
more than maybe like a hundred or something
dollars on steam in like my entire life
maybe two hundred I don't know
I've really ever put money into steam
but like
what I'm uh proud of I think
I may not have put the correct link in there
um
it says private
yeah I took a screenshot of the important part
um so
well let me see it it's all private
yeah I mean you can you I linked it
mainly so that you could input your
your stuff if you want to
oh I see I see
I set my profile to private afterwards
but
yeah so apparently the total hours I've put into steam
in history is like
does that include like time spent playing games
I think that's I think that's just like
game time it just looks at all the game time
you have on all your games and adds it together
I have spent I have spent like eight hundred hours
playing Noida just just playing
Noida so
damn
I'm embarrassed to admit that
Noida is a good game though
it is a good game and I like it a lot
but when I think about like
what else could I have done with those
I mean I guess it would I mean I guess
it was 2020 quarantine like I think that's
part of why I put so much into it
I mean you could have played a Minecraft
of all those hours I could have been playing
Minecraft that whole time yeah
I could have been playing on the PCP Minecraft
server at patreon.com
the procrastinators to get access
to the Minecraft server which
we should do another we should do another shekels
for heckles this week we didn't do one last week
yeah
the thing I'm proud of with this
is in
2019 September so like about two years
ago they started calculating
hours per platform
so what this means
is it says the amount of time I spent in windows is
27 hours what that means is I've
only spent 27 hours playing games
in the last two years which is
cool I've been playing a lot less
games because I've been doing a lot more
work 27 hours and
that's nothing that's nothing at all
it is nothing and I think
you're not even a gamer
I think half of that is among us
no wonder you haven't been invited onto the gamer zone
exactly you know
having more subscribers than they
not good enough I have to be a gamer
oh yeah
you've
he's at like 100
he's 114
he's 114 I'm 116
congratulations
did you have like a recent bump
I had a bump
the come video last year but I talked on
when I was on the podcast one year ago
yeah yeah yeah
I was hoping to have a sequel out by now
but work's been fucking me up
I've had barely any time to animate anything
except for the last week where I've been
animating again including during this podcast
I have been
I have been tragically
tragically pulled away from my
work on my game
to do the lord of ghosts
a bonus comic
for the lord of ghosts book
and
it is
it's really big
frankly it's nine pages
I've spent the last two days just
drawing this one page
and it's like
I would say it qualifies as like slavery
wages
the amount I'm being paid to do it is frankly
I'm putting way more time into it
than I
have been compensated for
that's my choice
that was me when I was for
PCP editor basically
yeah it was
and you put
what am I trying to say
you went over and above
in terms of editing
so hard that you were like I can't do it anymore
and it's like well you don't have to
go so hard
you don't have to make every editing a masterpiece
and you were like no I have
I'm afraid there's no room to compromise on that
it will either be a masterpiece
or it will be nothing
goodbye
that's how I roll
I am incapable of like
it's passable
the PCP
this podcast
was very helpful for me
because I used to be even worse
if you can imagine
the thing about
PCP
in terms of my perfectionism
and not being able to let things go
and settle for good enough
because
my main skill is
I'm really really good at polishing things
making them really smooth
making them really shiny
the problem is sometimes I start out
with an idea that isn't that great
but I can polish it to where it looks shiny
and people like it
watching the PCPvo
it's like long before the PCP
I was watching
I was watching Tom's shit
in like 2013
like pony stuff
yeah your pony videos
actually recently 2013
yeah with the candlelight wedding video
that Tom did with
was that 2013
yeah the video that Tom did with Anthony C
for a candlelight wedding
I remember that video
wait what
couldn't it be in 2015
because season 4 was started
late 2013 I think you're about a year off Ben
Jesus
okay alright
I know your history better than you
it seems
yeah the first t-bap episode was December
wow okay
I thought it was like 2015
yeah okay
I remember it was in December
so okay
I guess you're right
damn yeah I for sure remember that
candlelight wedding video it's probably been deleted
right it's probably like not up anymore
because didn't Tom like scrub all his pony videos
coward
it's on Anthony C's channel
so it's still up
Anthony C
Anthony C is a cool guy
he commented on the last video
he commented on the last video wanting to see
Cassie's drawing
because someone had commissioned Cassie to draw
a bunch of brony
people
and he commented like where can I see it
and I don't know
I also have not seen it
someone
send Anthony C
that picture if you know
where it is I guess
I suppose
you suppose well you don't think so
you don't think they should
if they know where it is
the man wants to see the
damn drawing
save him
okay
I was watching all you guys
pretty early on
and you guys were the fucking best
in the analysis sphere
that was obvious
everyone was shit except you guys
I think that's true
I think that is true
I'm glad
a lot of very annoying
personalities in that community
I was looking at a time lapse video
I think this
it was for the art telephone thing in the draw cast
talking about how are we going to edit the time lapse footage
I'm so sorry
are you going to be editing at all
it's fine I've edited time lapses before
so I looked at an old time lapse I had done
to see how many hours it was
because I used to time lapse my pony animations
one of them
when you say time lapse
you mean like a show your work
kind of
it's a 7 minute video with
60 hours of OBS
recording my screen while I animate
gotcha
while I was looking this over
in the corner because I had one monitor
I was watching fucking t-bat videos
exactly what time stamp it is
I went into
I just talked about this
on my Patreon
my Q&A
I call it a Q&A
it is a Q&A people ask me questions
but it's more of just like a what have I been up to
in behind the scenes
just my personal stuff
talk about shit
podcasting on my
patreon.com I talked about this a bit
more
but I will just say I've been thinking about
I've been thinking about making a video
about Phantom Horn
called thoroughly analyzing Phantom Horn
I think I might make that video
after Phantom's Revenge is done
and just kind of
talk about
the character
and the ideas behind
the ideas he was supposed to embody
and how he succeeded
and how he failed at that and his whole arc
and like what
I don't know
I love Phantom Horn
for being racist
he's totally racist
it's really cool
he's so racist
but he's um
I don't
I don't know if I want to get into it
I have a lot to say
I have a lot to say about like
what his deal is
and what people might have
thought his deal
and what I thought his deal was
because I don't think I fully understood
some of the ideas
I was trying to communicate with Phantom Horn
in the beginning I think
now I can kind of look back and be like
this is what I was trying to do with him
but at the time I was like
kind of like didn't have the
vocabulary I think
because Phantom's flaw
Phantom's fatal flaw is not that he is like
an SJW
like a lot of the jokes about him
in his videos are like
he's such like a tumblerina SJW
but like really that's not
that's not really
the
that's over simplification
that's like the surface level
that's the most surface level
critique of Phantom where you could give and there's a lot more to it than that
I was watching
I rewatched
that one video
where we sing
where we did the cover of
and with
with Tommy
and Digi Brony
and An-Y Pony and all them
and I was like
you know An-Y?
I know An-Y I was on his podcast once
oh yeah
I haven't
heard from him in forever and ever
but that's okay
yeah anyway
I just watched that and I was like some of these
what was these jokes about Phantom Horn
are weird the whole
the whole joke here is like is bizarre
and I wouldn't write this today
um
anyway
he's a good boy
I wonder if I've seen that video
is it on the t-bap channel or is it on someone else's channel
yeah it's on the t-bap channel
I think it's um
I think it's part of the cutie mark kerfuffle
series there was gonna be
two there were gonna be
three parts
to the cutie mark kerfuffle
and it was a
it was
I think it was a
we just made a song parody
and then I think later we decided to turn it into a series
and then later we decided
I guess we'll call it the cutie mark kerfuffle series
and it's three videos
it's when we all got our fucking cutie marks
swapped around
and it's just each one is just a song parody
but the third one we kind of just didn't make
it's not like somebody made the song
and I think it's Jesse rapping
I think it's a Jesse like rap
and there's no like animation to
there's I drew one image that kind of
communicates the story of what's going on
it's it's when um
yeah I think it's Anthony C
and Jess and and starboard bow
become alicorn princesses
I think that's what happens in that one
uh
but it never got posted
no it got posted it just
there was just an image
uh the song is there
I think I think this I think that
video that I was just talking about the one where we sing
the song we sing a true true friend
I think it ends with a little teaser where
like Anthony C and Jesse become
alicorn princesses
I see it
wait no wait no everyone's an alicorn
were we
yeah I'm looking at it
everyone's an alicorn
except you because
it's a real horn
oh yeah
who says that the toilet paper
isn't a real horn it's as real as anyone
else's it can magically
wipe your ass that's the one thing it's good for
t-bap
the lost chapters and there's like
what is the secret of mana fucking like
text scroll
I don't even remember this why is it like this
I actually don't think I've seen this
I guess I sort of
the secret of mana text scroll
there's not that much to explain
I guess there is actually
I guess there is
I think I think the text
scroll is just like it explains
like what would have happened in between
like the last video
and this song
I think it's just like here's the context folks
enjoy
I forgot about this
um
this reminds me of
we were gonna we had we had one other song
we had another t-bap video we wanted to
make at the time it was gonna be
it was gonna be like it was gonna be a keg and phantom
sort of like backstory
video just like a song about
them and like what their family is like
and it was gonna be the introduction of
you see their parents
in briefly in the flashback
in phantom reviews heartswarming you
this was gonna be one where they
sing just kind of about their
themselves it would be set to raise
these barn raise this barn but it was
gonna be raise these bros and it was
gonna be about like how much
they annoy their dad
uh it was gonna be great
I think we I think
I
I think we recorded the song actually
I think Nate wrote the lyrics and I think
we recorded the song
but we never actually got around I drew
some some images for it
we just never made it
never finished I say I started
sketching it
that was that was gonna be a good video
that was gonna be a good video but at the time the time has passed
it's like there's there's no need
anymore but still sometimes I think
about it like I would have been good
you know what I mean
I suppose yeah I have
I've got a bunch of videos that like
I wanted to make when I was in
that community but I never got around to
honestly that that feeling
is kind of like dangerous
because it's what
prevented me from making a Five Nights
at Freddy's parody when that was like new
it's what prevented me from like jumping
on a bunch of stuff that was like
hot and fresh because I'm like no I gotta finish
this pony animation first
and then you know
I missed my chance
which
oh god
fuck my back
it's a little painful
wait which what what attitude
is dangerous what what do you mean
the the oh like
for me like I had
all these like pony ideas like ideas for
pony animations that I was like attached to and I wanted
to make all of them
and as a result I ended up like
turning away like opportunities
to do things that could have
been way more profitable and successful
because when a fandom is new
like making an animation
even if it is complete dog shit
quality it'll get like five million views
it doesn't matter
people will just watch it
and like it
and I should have like
you know when Five Nights at Freddy's
was a new thing I had a few ideas for
Five Nights at Freddy's animations but I want to finish
my pony animations first
which took like a year
which which sucks by the time I was
done like like Five Nights at Freddy's
was already so big and like it was
like too late they were already tons and tons
of fan animations exactly it was too late
to jump in and then the standard had risen
and it's not like I was going I was planning
on making like a lazy piece of shit
I would have still made it look good
but of course it's you
I
fucked up and there's been so many points
in my life where I had an opportunity
to do something and I just mucked around
finishing old things that ended up not
being successful and then missing
you know the train to something bigger
which is what I'm trying not to do now
by capitalizing on a meme
immediately when it's popular
instead of waiting around which is what
I'm doing right now
it's what I've been animating during this call
which I can't share
you can't
not with the public
I mean you can look at it and you can
ooh and ah oh yeah please
discord says
Ben St. has requested discord
block messages that
a robot seemed to be explicit Ben
you're a prude I didn't know
wait
well I don't
user settings
is it
language advanced
voice and video accessibility
it's
I forget the setting that like
prevents people from sending you porn
privacy and safety sounds right
allow access to
NSFW servers on iOS
no that's not it
use data to improve
discord
allow discord to screen
reader I want to see
oh it's at the very top
it's for keep me safe my friends are nice
and but do not scan thing
oh do not yeah do not scan
do not scan
send me this
oh Ben we're not friends on discord no wonder
what the fuck
there you go
that's what I've been animating by the way
wait
well I like it
I like what I'm seeing here
I don't know if I know who this
is
that's my character from the cum zone
video doing the
the Anka
Animal Crossing porn dance meme
thing
oh I'm not familiar with that
I know Anka
okay
there was zone did an animation
of Anka from Animal Crossing
doing a big sex
that was like inspired
by like an old minus 8 animation
and it's
people cropped the sex
and like so that way you couldn't see
the big dick going into her cat pussy
basically
and people thought oh she's dancing
and they turned it into a tiktok dance
not knowing that it was sex
which is fun I mean it's hardly
even a dance
it is hardly a dance
but it's an easy to animate loop
so I'm just fucking going for
a remix for song and everything
my patrons can see this shit
early but you guys
listening to a ptp you can't
I get it for free
yeah Ben gets it for free
as you know we charge all
of our guests to be on the show
so this will come out of
I will reduce your
appearance fee
by
I don't know
Ben saying the inventor of patreon
gets all patreon rewards for free
it's just one of the perks
of being an innovator
the
where you were just describing
alright I'm gonna air
my personal fear
my fear and terror and dread
what you were just describing
about like the
getting caught in like oh I gotta finish my thing
I gotta finish my thing
but then I can't do
some other thing that might be more
that's just like my whole life
that's just my whole life is just
I gotta finish this old thing
that's like
nobody cares I mean I've been working on this
fucking phantom horn game for almost a year
and I know that it's not
like
it's not attached
to anything
I know that it's
based on some old shit that I did
that is like
why are you still doing this
but like I can't that's what I like about it
it's like yeah it's got no
it's not
it's not gonna hit big or anything
it can't
but I just want to
I don't know
fuck it
but I
I guess the stallus I can take
is that I know that
I am wasting my time
doing some nonsense that
will not succeed
or benefit me in any way
will not pay dividends
but on the other hand
I'm not actually losing anything
because if I wasn't doing that
it's not like I would be making good choices
it's not like I would be doing something that was useful
I would just be wasting my time
even worse
I guess you can take comfort in that
absolutely
pass up some good ideas
like fuck
not me
I wanted to like in 2016
I was like you know I kind of want to make
story time like animator videos
I feel like I have a lot to say
like in that sort of style
story time like the
lightly animated like draw my life
kind of thing
like the jaden animations fjord ones out
domics if anyone remembers
that sort of thing
he was like
the og he was doing that shit like
in 2012 2011 or some shit
he was doing it real early
but like I had ideas for like
videos like that I could make
and I was like oh but I've got this project
and that project and this project and that project
and then I saw like a year later
the story time animator scene
blew up a bunch of channels
just like shut up into the millions of subscribers
and then I was like
oh it's too late now fuck
now the market saturated
should have
followed my gut instinct
perhaps I mean it's the
it's the
you know I've known people who were like
I was
this close to investing in bitcoin back in like
2010 like I almost
did it like I thought about doing it
it's kind of like
that I guess like
there was a thing that I thought about doing
I didn't do it
it turned out it would have made
it would have been a huge benefit for me
if I did but
but it didn't so
I was a fool
huh
it was foolish
sure sure
I'm not being a fool anymore
now I'm like I know porn
porn animations
pay very well
on patreon
and
like a lot of artists I follow
I've you know been drawing NSFW
art for like less than a year
now
I've been doing it for like 10 months on and off
and I don't have a whole
lot of followers but I know people with like
10 times my follower account who make less than
me on patreon
like you know you know cake they call
him cake big booby
I do I do know they call him cake
150 on patreon
really
but they're big on twitter
they're huge they've got hundreds of thousands of followers but
they only get like 150 on patreon
why is that
it's a combination of
not like
I think for one they don't draw like explicit stuff
really but also
they don't have
paywall content that I'm aware of
oh well yeah
I guess that makes sense
that does like
you know that does make a huge difference
and also
like people who do animations
like porn animations just make like double or
triple most artists anyway
on average
so whoa
what is this?
hi
are you recording?
did I be late?
yeah
wow
how interesting
are you recording?
okay
you're just in time we just started talking about boobs
like
sort of
drawing over that
drawing over that now
what?
hey guys welcome to the pro crest news podcast
show's over
goodbye
don't listen to Ben
he's a liar
I'm sorry I lost track of the conversation
you guys are gonna have to carry it for me
well I was just talking about
porn artists
and porn animators and how
being a porn animator makes you lots of money on patreon if you
do it right
I have a big old audience on my youtube channel
so what I need to do
is make
porn animations that are like
covered up in youtube
save and then have
the naughty versions on patreon
I've seen people do that
they've jumped from like
1,000 a month to like 10-20,000 a month
doing that
I've seen a few people do that
I mean that's what Mary does
or I don't know if he does it anymore
he probably does but he would have her
Mary weather
you know him
oh yeah yeah
the internet explorer
comics guy
he's also a vtuber now
yeah you have them on the pcpr number
yes they do
yeah they would have like a comic going
and then they would have you know
if you were a patreon supporter you could get the
the explicit version
not the explicit version
but like an extra panel sometimes
or just like official art
of the NSFW art of the character
they have only
90 patrons
interestingly
at the highest here
25 which
that would only be like 2,000 dollars
it's actually
it's probably a lot lower than that
wait Mary weather only has 90 patrons
yeah Mary weather comics only has 90 patrons
so assuming everyone's a 25 dollar patron
which is unlikely that they'd only be getting 2,000
that's less than I expected
wait a second I'm like
what
okay I was sure
I feel like
it was like 10,000 a month at some point
maybe
am I crazy hold on
maybe you're crazy
also
I just logged into patreon I have 18 notifications
this never happens
I usually have one or two what the fuck happened
why do I have it I'm scared is that everyone
on pledge or did I gain like 20 pledges
have you been putting stuff out
I've been putting stuff out
oh
someone went through and liked all of my posts
what an asshole
thank you
this could have been about money
okay so yeah I got 16 likes
on a bunch of patreon posts
and then two people pledged okay
alright
I was like today's
did something happen
okay that's cool
some
part of me thinks you should take
yourself all more seriously Gib
you should maybe try
to like
have a product that people can get excited for
on patreon.com
gib and take slash patreon
and I don't do it
but I could
the porn stuff I'm not really like good yet
at like
anatomy because that's the most important
well not really
not really the most important but it's very
very helpful for like actually
communicating
a specific look
I mean people can get away with like
drawing the same thing 100 million times
exactly the same every time
and if people like it
then that'll work
but I get bored
I get bored too easily
I have a couple
I have a couple that put patreon notifications
oh my god oh two people pledged to me
oh wow
three people pledged to me
I lost a few patreons at the beginning of the month
but a couple new ones too
so thank you Jacob and Airlock and Roger
I'll tell a few people that
unpatron okay
okay thank you yeah the balance
the balance must remain
the light
and the dark rises to meet it
there must always be a Sith for a Jedi
fuck oh okay
I gotta look at Merryweather's grafter on history
because I'm sure they were making more than that
I gotta look this up
okay
but yeah like my twitter
a big girl squish
which I've mentioned before
is like oh that's the porn one
where I post
not even that much porn
I have these characters
who are like oh cool
sex and stuff
but I've not really done anything with that twitter
I very occasionally have a drawing
and I put it there
and uh
it's really
it's like I'm treating it too much
like a hobby but maybe it is just a hobby
there's a lot of pressure
just from all sides and constantly
to make everything you do content
can't waste content
I can't waste it
what if I could make a
I don't know
some sort of an established following
of people who know what I do
and I could do commissions or something
ah jeez
sheesh
okay I can't find
Merryweather on grafteron
yeah I can't find them either
I'm finding a
someone who looks like a stripper
there's a deleted patreon
for someone called stormy merryweather
who is a porn star
um
I've never encountered this before
I just can't find their grafteron
weird
I use grafteron for the first time
yesterday so it's funny you bring it up
I use grafteron to watch Trixie's
patron, patreon collapse
month
I use it to
I use it to check over
a few like fellow porn
animators to see like
at what time their patron jumped up
I'm doing similar things
to some of them and I'm just trying to figure out
how beneficial
it'll be for me
I only need to earn like 2k
and I can quit my job and then like make
probably about five times as much porn
as I am now
that would be cool
I've seen behind the scenes bits
of you drawing stuff
and I've also seen the public stuff
it is good drawings
wait no
I make more than you on patreon
if you start
making porn animations
you might pass me
and I don't want that so
I have to stop you at any cost
we can't release this episode
but if I surpass you
you have to delete your patreon in shame
that's for rules
what if I
okay
what if I patron you now
but if you pass me in patreon
you have to patron me
I say this knowing that you definitely will
your plan is full proof
and it definitely will work
so I'm gonna have to like how can I negotiate you
into an unlinable deal
here's the thing Ben
that is actually the moral thing to do
if your friend is earning way more than you on patreon
it's foolish for you to pledge the same amount
to both pledge each other at the same time
because you're just exchanging the same coin
and patreon's taking a cut
only the bigger person should pledge to the smaller person
I feel like that is
what should happen also
even if I like someone's content
I generally don't pledge to them
if they make more than me
because like why
you're doing fine
I say that yet I still pledge teleperte on occasion
even though we're friends
I might
he does just give me his shit for free
yeah
who am I a patron of
I am a patron of
I think I pledged to you Gib
I think I pledged to
for a while I was a patron of Japanese emoticons.com
just because I used it all the time
I pledged them $1 a month
and then I was like why am I still doing this
my creators
literally where do I
find who I'm pledged to
I can't fucking find it
oh there's more tears on
Mary with this thing
oh there are more tears
oh there's five levels
oh I didn't see that
oh wait I still support DeVoo
I don't know why
okay DeVoo changed their thing
I pledged a dollar to DeVoo
but it was per game
now it has changed to per month
and I think I'm gonna unplug
cause I don't want to do that
oh live on the PCP Ben
I think I'm gonna unplug DeVoo
yeah I'm gonna do it
just stab in the back
well I mean it's
money you do what you want with it
I will
I usually like to
like for Autominus
the soundtrack was like the way
yeah
so I bought that and that was good
oh I'm a ShadOx
patron I'm a pledge to ShadOx
after the RFCK animation
I was like I didn't mean
I gotta pledge to that
gotta pluge
ShadOx is only
per episode
so like god I mean I could
for an episode of LoveWeb I feel like
it's worth more than $5
I might increase that
per month
I would be $5
but per episode I'm like I should be like
$100 per episode honestly
that shit
that shit is wild
I'm also pledged to
I'm pledged to Cheesy Manfredo
and I'm pledged to Gabriel the Starman
a few dollars a month
what's Gabriel's
is that a twitch thing
do you know them?
yeah Gabriel from RFCK
and also just in general
I saw them at Brighton
I mean they're an artist
although I can't
I don't know if they've posted anything
I'm not sure if they
they take their Patreon down
I mean I haven't
I haven't seen them draw in a while
but they have been like streaming with a funny
monkey vtuber
oh I haven't seen that
they made a Patreon a while ago and I pledged to it
that might be a secret
I haven't said that
oh dear
never mind
I didn't say exactly what it was
I think they may have
taken their Patreon page down
but I'm still pledged to them
maybe I should try
Patreon's just stealing it
stealing it all
that would be unfortunate
but that is something they would do
well this has been
a revelation
for me this has been
I've learned some things that I
feel damaged
to know
wow
a loveless episode of
the money cast
bonus next bonus
idea for the bonus episode
we just watch
the price of Bitcoin rise and fall in real time
and we go oh it went up like 30 cents
you have to modulate
the pitch of your voice to match the direction
it's going oh it's going up
oh no
oh no the candle's red
oh my god the hammer's green
oh there it goes
you know if we had someone
smart
because I know that data is archived
you could have someone run a literal
pitch changer
in real time that follows the graph
we send in our audio
and we run through the script
I have no doubt in my mind that crack could do that
I have no doubt in my mind
that he could create something that
dynamically reacts to the market
that would be like what makes it worth listening to
maybe
maybe if you could do it to just Ben's audio
and then I would just be there to sigh
every so often
in normal pitch
hey speaking of the bonus episodes
let me ask you something
what if
what if I were to call you
how would you feel
what if I said
hey you know what oblivion fall
you're a fucking gay wizard
not only that
but you're a bottom
you're a bottom gay wizard and you probably
either are or are friends with
at least one sorcerer
what would you say to that
choose your words carelessly
choose your words yes
if you have a big penis
put it in my ass
please
oh my god he admit it
it's just a hypothetical you didn't have to admit it
ergy ergy ergy
no this I'm using your platform to solicit sex
from the audience
well shit that's what we're supposed to do
you're not allowed to do that
well I gotta say
I gotta say
that's not
that's not what I was expecting
I was gonna
that's a hell of an answer
if you want to understand the ramifications of what just transpired
you're gonna have to be a patron
and watch the latest bonus episode
which should be out by now
for context into what the fuck I'm talking about
see I designed it like this so there'd be FOMO
so people wouldn't get the joke
if they don't know
FOMO is a moral good
I can't remember the joke I don't remember
I can't remember this
I can't like egg you on
with like specifics
I just know that there's a thing
and it's funny
I remember it but I don't know how to say it
if you want that's the only way to know
I'm gonna keep asking
guests until one of them gives the correct answer
the correct response
to that and see how long it takes
give can't egg you on
but perhaps give can most of an egg
you on
I'm just gonna say
things are not gonna go well
things are not gonna go well for you
if that's what you have to say
about the gay wizard thing
wrong answer
buzzer
that was a terrible attempt at a
buzzer sound
much better
okay do you guys have any
any more issues to raise
I got a thing
to talk about
so this is October
wow
clearly
oh my god it's spooky season
oh my god it's apple pumpkin
it's apple pumpkin spice time
oh my god
sweater weather
it's time to get all the cowboy paraphernalia out
cause it's wild west month
which is why
I'm getting
the Clarissa Gunsmoke comic
finally out into the public eye
all nice and dolled up
and polished
and I've been drawing
not really like draw
I've been like touching up a few panels here and there
where this line work is really sloppy
but mostly just
adding like tone
to the hair and some other things in the shading
so it's like the hot summer
sun of the wild west desert
beating down and it feels
way better than it was
before
and redoing a lot of the dialogue
cause it was cringe before and it sucked
of course
most importantly I'm reorienting it
reorienting it from
Japanese to western
left to right reading
which is harder than it
looked
harder than it feels
cause it's like you can't just
flip the page because then
the panel
the panels that you would read
would be the wrong way around
and like the characters would be looking in the wrong direction
if you want like the flow
of visual
stimulus and the speech bubbles
have to shift so that they actually
also within a panel
are left to right reading
but yeah
it's a whole lot of stuff
the first chapter is gonna be about 20 pages
gonna be posted on my website
gibandtake.site
so if you're gonna put it on twitter
it'll be buried in twitter
but people will see it and be like
oh I guess I go check out the website
and yeah
that Clarissa Gunsmoke Month
finally
are you gonna finish
the comic like is it gonna get
completed?
I don't expect that
I will have the time to finish
cause
there's a lot of stuff that happens
after the end of what I had already drawn
but there's 50 pages
there's enough for three
sort of medium-sized chapters
and
I'll think about
how I can finish it later
but I think as soon as I'm done with that
I'll be
more focused on the Lord of Ghost
Kickstarter backer reward
mailing stuff
and then after that I could probably start drawing
maybe even go back to
streaming the draw streams
with those
I mentioned this before
but I have spent
the last two days working on
this page
of the Lord of Ghosts
comic that I'm working on
it has been
I accidentally deleted
my sketch of it so I had to
recreate the sketch and then I have been
there's just a lot of layers
there's like
there's like 50 layers
on this
one page
on one page
there's a lot
happening in this one
it's good
I'm excited
you're gonna like it
maybe when you see it
you can guess which one
God I hope this is the page that takes me the longest
I'm hoping not the other pages don't take
so
I'm
a little sick of looking at it honestly
I've had enough but
it's almost done
this is page 4
this is page 4 of 9 that I am
holy shit
I know
the other ones weren't as bad
yeah
I'll get it done
pretty soon
we could go to voicemails
I wanted
I did want to mention one thing
about Clarissa
yeah
she is a tall sexy woman
which is good
something I never forgot
Gib
I don't know if this is when you first revealed her
it was like a post you did with her
a long time ago you said she'll root ya
to ya then shoot ya
which hell yeah
the way I imagine that
was like
moan bark fart but instead it's
because root means sex
wait
I don't know if that's it
what was the thing you said the moan
bark fart
you know moan bark fart
no
nates mentioned it on the podcast before
oh
moan boat
wait
that was a sound thing
okay I thought it was like a weird
moan bark fart
and then you bark
this is like a very specific
furry sex
fetish
order of operations
it's just an order of sound effects
cause root
is slang for sex
so I figured with calisher
it would be moan
moan
moan for
root to shoot
yeah I get it
I need to make an animation of that at some point
oh please do
that's technically fan art
and I love that
anyway
I pog all over the fan art
everyone's gonna love this conversation
cause the sound effects aren't gonna be in my
recording
oh so we can hear them
but your microphone can't
maybe
I'll make the sound effect for
Eleazar and he can put it in
moan boat
that I can't say
it's not boat
it's bark
what does moan boat
fart even mean
no it's like moan boat
I switched
some letters
to your own boat
and you're like
oh
I had to go
I was too hungry I had to go get some baby bells
but I'm back
baby bells
back and chatter than ever
oh cheese
yeah cheese
the little red
wax circles
oh the little wheels
I have had those
to go on crackers
you should get a greater bell
I'm happy to do voicemails
if you guys are
yeah I guess I didn't really have much to say
about the clear so just
be excited
you idiots and enjoy it
so it's going on your website
right it's going on gibbentake.site
it's gonna go on gibbentake.site
I guess I could maybe do a webtoon
or a tapas or both I don't know
I don't care about those sites they suck
I hate them
you know what I'll read it
I'll finally read it
oh yeah that's the point
that is the point
I hadn't read it because it was technically
complete but like no I'll read it
finally when it goes on the website
because otherwise I don't want to hunt it down
yes
that'll yeah
it'll be good
had you posted it anywhere before
it was up on the artstreet.com
which is the
medibang paint
like
artist area
like a deviant art kind of or a pixiv
where you can post comics and illustrations
and I put it there
uploaded for the contest
and then I put like a price tag on it
so people could
pay 7
no 420 yen
to see
like
I think the whole thing
and there was a preview of a few pages
but yeah it's been up
I think
but it's the one
that version is going to be
outdated it's going to be ruined
I'll leave it there
wait are you doing
are you remastering it
I'm only remastering it
in the sense that I'm
making it look good
because before
the contest was over
I was like oh shit I don't have time
to like make it
do shading and stuff
because I wanted that
and I started for the first 3 pages and I was like
nah I don't have time
I'm just going to post it
and then I just didn't get around to shading it
for an entire year and a month
I see
sure
okay sick
let's do
let's do a voicemail
here
let's do
shit where did I
it's the 3rd
of October
and the first
voicemail
why are these all out of order
what the fuck
oh I briefly should mention
I'm doing
a voicemail
I should mention
I'm doing
a whatever tober
which is a drawing challenge
is what you draw whatever
whenever
in October it's a really great system
because you can't fail
perfect
why didn't anyone think of this
I was trying to do prompts
prompts annoy me
everything is the same
oh was it chip chip
she was drawing
a character in a different status effect
affecting them
I thought that was fun
I like video games
it's neat enough
it's the sort of thing that
once I see other people doing it
why would I do it
why would I also do that
just do whatever
I mean sure
the first 3 voicemails
are not voicemails
which relate to me personally
in the form of the names of the voicemails
the voicemails are called
Ben Delta Rune
literally has the characters jump into
one out of question mark
and then the second voicemail is called
another world and use RPG mechanics
to fight enemies
2 out of question mark
and then the third voicemail is
they explain to Noelle
how RPG battles work
it's isekai
so those are the first 3 voicemails
they have no content other than the title
and I just gotta say
yeah I know Delta Rune isn't isekai
obviously Delta Rune is
like the most obvious isekai
veils are
isekai purity chart
which I will post here
that I retweeted on the twitter account
yeah that was a good one
it is a good one
Delta Rune is it's like most
I think it's most pure
isekai
that is not Japanese I guess
the super pure
is that it has to be from Japan
anime
it doesn't have to be from Japan
and then the lowest one is
it doesn't have to be from any medium in fact
or it can be from any medium
it doesn't need to be from the heart
medium again
colonialism isn't isekai
tripping on acid isn't isekai
true
there was this other isekai chart
that went up
the same day
as that PCP episode
but they didn't credit the PCP
if they ought to be
shot in the back of a head
they ought to be lambasted
they ought to be shot
wait was it you
I didn't say that
YouTube would not support terrorism
how did you fucking do this
I support terrorism
I once said 9-11 out loud
and they killed me for it
they shut down my channel
wait is this you
are you this vtuber
no that was just some person
no not you
wait I thought that
I'm not talking to you
who are you talking to
you you oblivion
I'm not this vtuber
this is just some guy
or girl I don't know
after the PCP episode went up
where you were talking about isekai alignment charts
like 10 hours after the episode went live
this person posted this chart
and didn't credit the PCP
how bad of them
this is
it's not even a good chart which is annoying
no I think it's a good chart
I think the moon landings is a good entry
moon landing is pretty good
but like I don't know
the way
just fails is better
the descriptions are better
the examples are better
I actually
I kind of think the examples are better in this one
I kind of like
like to me
there's not enough meaningful difference
in the medium rebel
row the haley's comment
colonialism and tripping on acid
are both questionably isekai
but they're all in the same way
they're all just like a real thing that happened
whereas
function radical on this one
your name kory in the house
and entering a taco bell
those are all not isekai
but they're not isekai in different ways
because one is an anime
it's just not about going to another world
really
kory in the house is also not about that
but it's a show and then entering a taco bell
is just a thing that you do in real life
so
wait is this like rotated 90 degrees
compared to
yeah no it is
in this one
all
the form
is in the column
but then it veils it's like the top row
the medium purist
I guess the axes are different
we could dissect this
scholars will debate
which of these two isekai alignment charts
is more
is more scientifically
accurate
I kind of prefer the bottom one
but I do hold
great malice towards them for not
crediting the pcp for the idea
you know
do you actually think that they got it from us
I assume
unless that
could it just be a weird coincidence
the discussion in the episode sounded
pretty like spontaneous
it didn't sound like you were referencing an existing meme
unless you were
I'm just wondering
do you think this person actually got the idea
or could it just be a weird coincidence
it was like 10 hours or so
after the episode
that would be a pretty big coincidence
I would say the myth of Plato's cave
in the top 10
that's a good one
that is a good one
that's a good example
Cory in the house
something about Cory in the house being
that's a tired meme
what is this 2012
what is this 2001
it works though
it does but I don't know
I like examples that are
not overdone
I mean they could have used
literally any show
about
well
any show whose premise is about someone goes
somewhere which is like most shows
Golden Girls
is an isekai because it's about
entering the metaphorically different world of being old
it doesn't exist
what
yes it does exist because Dorothy
had chronic fatigue and the doctors told her
she was just a dumb woman and she didn't understand what her body was saying
and then she told that doctor off in the restaurant
and she said he was bad at his job
and he should be ashamed of himself
being old was invented by like M. Night Shyamalan
like less than a month ago
it's like what
it's like
Carl Pilkington said why don't they just
invent a pill
that when you get old instead of dying
you just start aging in reverse again
until you become a baby and then you disappear
why don't they just invent that
why haven't they made this happen yet
the man's keeping us down
the man
makes a good point
I'm looking at the
second isekai, sorry I'm still on this
like the function
purest on the second one
isekai is to travel what is a clearly
a separate reality and then neutral
can be traveled to what can be
physically described as another world
but then radical is like can be
traveled to metaphorically different world
are they
very similar those
like how is the matrix
not a purest
I guess
I guess it's not magic
cause it's like
it's not exactly a world
it's a simulation
he's still in the real world
he's just experiencing a
yeah that one is
like that one is like
it is
in every functional way to the story
it is about like going between
from one world to another
it's just it's
yeah I think I agree with you that's like too close
and then the wizard of us
being like more pure
is strange cause that was a dream
oh yeah I guess it was a dream
was it even a physical different world
yeah you know what
you're right
they're the same in every meaningful way
wizard of us is the matrix
I think we need to
but just without computer it just is
it just is
it's just the same story
that's what we need to part of the world
let's listen to a voicemail
shall we?
let's do it
the first voicemail after that is called
clich
I won't
wait can I post it in the
okay it's called clich
three two one go
but I'm just of
more like
okay
I get it
hold on it's coming out my
negotiations is a word that I learned from watching
star wars for phantom menace as a kid
yeah
whenever I heard my parents say
the word negotiation
that's the star wars word
when do they say that
when the trade federation is talking to
we have to have our negotiations with the trade federation
we have to have the negotiations
we've got to negotiate a trade deal
to get the blockhead out of
fucking
Naboo
it's a funny story
you're really do
you're like negotiation
just like a Shakespeare
okay
setting default audio to
wireless headphones okay good
wait I don't mean
I don't mean to derail
go derail away
on the topic of George Lucas
have you seen the video
there's just a guy walking through the street talking about some shit
and George Lucas just appears
in the background
and just
making music plays
I have to
is it just someone was vlogging
and George Lucas just happened to be there
and he just walks into a building
that's great
I can't believe that George Lucas
actually walks around in the real world
that's so fucked up
it shouldn't be allowed
it's kind of nice
because I feel like George Lucas
lives in a real place
more so than other celebrities
which you only see them
never
only out of a limo
he's got that Skywalker ranch doesn't he
yeah they say that he lives on like his personal
little ranch
he's super rich
I've heard that he's kind of like a recluse
or I mean red letter media called him a recluse once
and I just assume they know what they're talking about
I thought he's been like seen just
eating salad in a food court
oh yeah enjoy your salad
yeah I remember the food court
thing
another thing red letter media made fun of him for
but like why
why make fun of him for eating the food court
what's wrong with that
let's react to this video
PCP of a reaction channel
where we react to voicemails and funny videos
okay here we go
three two one go
right
and they use something they call pyro processing
the interesting thing is
they call it pyro processing
it's a molten salt process
they're dissolving this thing
in a molten salt
and they're doing electro chemistry
it looks just like him
yeah I think it's him
because then it brings up another superior thing
molten salt
oh it is
it's
that's so similar to his face
I'm looking at his face
and now I'm not 100% sure
I wasn't sure until I full screened
it looks more like it than
well
oh no there's a frame where it looks
like someone else
who knows maybe it's just a
classic outfit
he just looks like a regular old man
so like
I really thought it was at first
but now I'm like it could be
just someone who kinda looks similar
and I think it's him
very funny
I don't know what the salt processing
molten, shut the fuck up
fucking egg head
get out of here
regardless of George Lucas
it's funny how he just sort of jumps
into frame like he's like supposed to be there
because he wanted to see this happening
and then he's like oh I guess he's filming
he didn't just walk by casually
he jumped into frame looking at the camera
like uh and then he just
walked all the way across the screen
but in a way that maximized his
screen time
he did it's like he's staying
maybe he had he like
maybe he like knew he had to walk by
and saw that the guy was filming
and he was like I kinda don't want to
walk through this line of film but like I have to
so he tried to like
I don't know it looked like he
he didn't like that he was on camera I think
he was trying to ignore it
he looks like a man who's seen a camera or two
you could say
you could proof perhaps
perhaps
the other smell which I have right here
is called heartfelt dondas
ready
three two one go
donda
I don't know if you have to listen to all 30 seconds of this
donda donda
donda donda donda
I don't know what it means
donda
I mean I believe it
I believe it too
donda
this is definitely George Lucas
this one I have no doubt about
this is George Lucas having sex dude
that's the noise in a minute
yeah
that's so heartfelt dondas
I was thinking of that fucking turtle
having sex video with the shoe
I was thinking of that
I said it's donda
next one is called
L2 bait
spot scrubs
three two one
go
yeah this whole
general strike thing
striking for one day
smells like bait
that's not how strikes
fucking work guys
I wasn't sure about it
but it's not the easiest bait to get a bunch of
dipshit baby leftists
fired
don't fall for it
I mean do you
I get that it doesn't seem like it's going to do anything
but like
is anyone really going to get fired over it
is anything even going to
if it seems like such a
you would never see the fruits
if your goal is like haha I will put out a plan
that will get a bunch of stupid baby leftists fired
that will get a few people fired
I have never met
but maybe vaguely have a sense that I don't like them
and in my heart I will know that haha
maybe a few of them got fired
because they fell for my trick
I guess that's something people would do
there are people in the world who are that cruel
I guess that's probably true
there are other Ben Saints out there
no no
I cornered the market
damn it well I need I guess I need a new
shtick cruelty is taken
next voicemail is called
will ben have cake
3 2 1 go
you will never have any cake
and then the delta rune logo appears
sounds like you answered your own question there
buddy
I'm sorry
I knew I said to the fucking voicemail
I forgot what it was
oh it was you
you fucker
I forgot about it
okay
okay cool
thanks
thanks man
good shit
you got that 5-4 groove going on
is that what that was
that was a fucking
time signature
is that doing like a disturbed
like
at the end
it was like you will never have any cake
you will never have any cake
it wasn't the drum line from
down with the sickness
no that's 4-4
5-4 is like 1 2 3 4 5
5-4 is real fun
most random sentences
if you just save them rhythmically
end up being 5-4 in my experience
you will never have any cake
yeah
sorry for your ears
that's okay
did I post it
the next one is called
it's called tiny facts number 1
a tiny fact
3 2 1 go
it's me
the muffin man
I like the way he cooks the dough
you're the muffin man
but you like the way he cooks
who's he
I don't know
there's so many holes in this
story I don't think I trust this guy
the next
it's a very tiny fact
it sure was
vanishingly small
the next one is called we did it boys
racism is no more
alright
1 go
on one of the recent episodes
Ben expressed his opinion that gender and race are fake
and we shouldn't treat people differently because of those characteristics
given croc disagreed
so Ben quickly folded as befitting of a spineless
beta cut
in relation to that I'd like to know your opinion on Asian
penalty in the US
Asian penalty
like football
like football penalty
kickoffs
like how Japan
a world cup
one time
I don't think that conversation
happened according to as this person
describes it I don't think I
I don't remember that either
what is Asian penalty
okay
do they mean like Chinese
I think they're talking about
what's the word
when you do something bad
and the government says points deducted
okay I think they're basically talking
about
the opposite of affirmative action
where colleges
won't take Asian people
because they have too many
I think that's what it is
weird
I think
I don't know I think it's neutral
I think it's neutral
I think affirmative action
is generally good
and
whatever those
Asian kids can just go to a different college
just like everybody else
big fucking deal
whatever
it's maybe not great but it's not
that big a deal
I don't think affirmative action should
negatively affect
Asian applicants
I thought the idea was like if two people
have equal qualifications
you give it to the person who probably
struggled harder to get there
well yeah
I mean yes
but it's not like Asians don't experience racism
or I guess it's a different kind of racism
I mean
you necessarily
if two people
have a thing and you have to give one
or the other
you're necessarily denying it to the other
that's just life
I mean
I don't know
it's a zero sum gain
I guess it's bad
I guess it's bad if like
an Asian person who
qualifies for something doesn't get it
and the reason is
in some part because they had to fill a quota
they had to give it to someone else to fill
some race quota or whatever
for anything right but like
the opposite would be just as bad
like if they gave it to the Asian kid
and not to the
someone is losing out either way
so it's not like an
ill has been inflicted on the world
a resource was moved from one person to another
which is just
happens all the time
and is normal
just go to a different college
the resource of my bullet has been moved
to the resource of your brain
true
I'm just trying to remember the
conversation
I just think racism is good actually
you know, sometimes racism is actually good
most of the time
we finally have a left at bits
you know what
I was kind of racist all along
we all were
I can't remember what that conversation was
I don't know anything
lol
I don't know if I listened to the episode that was referencing
gender
I don't think I would have said
it's fake like money
it's real because we make it real
yeah
whatever
okay
next voicemail
where did I put it
it's called
fuck I lost it
I lost it because that was one of those
those
vocaru messages
just get a fucking microphone
just get a microphone
okay
next one is called
where's the number
no sorry the next one is an image
the
I can't
there
posted
okay
so we have
whatever
defeated by
I assume this is mage
glowing
effulgent with power
can't believe defeated by a woman
and then it's me saying Nate we don't know their pronouns
I get it
I get it because
the joke is that I'm obnoxious
the joke is
true
but why are you on the right side of the screen
why is Nate to the left of you here
that's true
it's this
what we just said nice art
it is nice art
this guy
this guy kills it
this guy is really killing it in the voicemails
I gotta say
okay next one I posted up above
it's called hmm
it's the one we didn't listen to okay 3 2 1
go
I just wanted to test if
my mic works better
with socks on
or without socks
so now comes
the review
let's see if there is any difference
well viewers
well viewers what do you think
with socks or without socks vote down below
vote in the comments
I guess
my advice to the voicemailers
use your own ears
don't send it through
a service that like
purchases your audio and makes it probably worse
he can only tell if it's better
if he hears us listen to it on the PCP
a week later just so you know
listener a speak pipe
fucks with the audio that gets sent through
and makes it lower quality so
it's not a good way to test if something
sounds good
or is it
I have voicemails I've never sent because
I had a lot of advanced audio editing
and speak pipe just fucking like
tries to mute all of my sound effects
and then it just sounds like it's underwater
so it's just not like this
you gotta use vocru
vocru has a shitty bit rate is a problem
oh
that's when I put a link
to download and the thing
and then you complain
yeah I did
that's me
next voicemail is
this is another genes
here we go
3, 2, 1
wait
I'm stupid
the 35
35 is genes
3, 2, 1, go
with my high school friends was
Halo 3, Reach
and Halo 4
while those were fun multiplayer games
they didn't laugh with any interesting
conversations
and I didn't have any significant
recollection of those events
could you recommend
any similar comfy play foods
that I can cozy up and listen to
yeah if you're playing Halo
I mean you're like you're
you're engaged you're being like
or I'm gonna be shot
you're heavily engaged
cozy play throughs
do you mean like let's play videos
or do you mean like games that
can be like Ape Escape
in a cozy way
my cozy playthroughs
that I like so much
is I really really like
gdq speedruns of
Final Fantasy games and like
Chrono Trigger like 9 hour long
ones of like Final Fantasy 8
and stuff
that's the that's the
good content for me
I guess who excel
did a bunch that I like a lot
I guess this is sort of normal
but I like game grumps
there's a lot of good
old game grumps things but you probably already knew
that so I don't know
meaningful conversations
I don't think Ape Escape is specifically
like tailored for that sort of thing
I'm trying to figure out
what they mean
they missed out on playing
games that if played with
friends would result in
deep conversations
it just comes from having deep things to talk about
I think what she's saying is that
she didn't have
yeah cause they were all actively
playing Halo they were focused on the game
I think the thing about the
that playthrough and that game
is not that it was Ape Escape
it's that you were playing
and the rest of us were just kind of hanging out
yeah and like only sort of half
paying attention to the game
is me and Jesse passing it to each other
and then everyone was just hanging out
Davoo fell asleep
the best game
to just chill
and talk with your friends is Minecraft
that's a good one
yeah that's true
a lot of Minecraft is
just with your friends and just build some shit together
it's great
like you have your own little solo project that you're working on
and then occasionally
you invite them over to see your house
or you go to see theirs
and you just sort of hang out and stand around
and talk
it's nice
it's a good time
yeah I guess that answers the question
next one
yep
next one is called
drawcast idea
well good thing you're here for this oblivion
you've stolen our fucking thing
hey
3, 2, 1, go
it was silent
it was okay
is that the joke?
the joke is don't do the drawcast
well we weren't going to
don't worry
that's a lie you know me and Gibb
we're doing a drawcast later today
oh my god we are doing it later today
thank you for reminding me
hey we're going to draw
thank god
yeah
based alert
wait what's the theme for today
halloween girls
I hate halloween
boo I'm a halloween
rude
I'm going to draw scream
from scream with fat titties
underneath their cloak and their mask
it's not going to be a scream mask
we're going to be
cumin
it's going to be great
it's going to be cumin
like my curry
every drawcast episode my goal
is to draw a character with big tits or ass
so that can be the thumbnail
it's the only way
the only way
the only way to what I don't know
next next voicemail is called
sad wait no I think I already posted
I'm losing track yes I already posted it
next one is called sad
three two one go
I've experienced life
later what
a series
of humiliation
and defeats
what are you talking about
don't stop
I haven't got a
got a W
ever since I was born
oh gee I can't imagine
couldn't be me
are you okay
don't have the constitution
for suicide
as the guy says
I'm true detective
but other than that I see
no reason not to quit
your job
don't kill yourself
he's saying okay
I understand the point
what he's saying it's just he took so long
to say it with his like bizarre
like drawing like
took him like so long
he sounded like he's drunk
don't kill yourself
he's got the Eleazar accent
but it's not Eleazar
it's some kind of
South American accent
I can't place it more specifically than that
but
yeah don't kill yourself
is what I would say
dude here's the thing
W's
come after L's in the alphabet
I keep digging
keep going through those letters
yeah it's just
wow that's deep
W comes after L in the alphabet
by sex toys
it's like
it's like tomato anus
always says you guys ever watched tomato anus
no but I like that
he does speedrun explain videos
he'll walk through
a record breaking speedrun
and he'll just explain like what is the runner doing
here and here and here
every single video that he makes
he will at a completely random point
just insert a little
like 30 second bit where he's just like
and by the way I just want to say
the things will get better for you and if things are going well
if you feel bad now you won't always feel that way
and there's always hope and people that love you
and I just want you to know
that the things will get better
alright back to the run anyway
frame perfect inputs
so just go watch one of those
and just assume that
pretend that I said what he says
don't kill yourself
we love you
tomato anus
he's a wise man
I was just curious
has anyone personified
a tomato
as a girl
and drawn her with an ass
and they have
of course
it's a round
it's a fruit
these images are so bad
the only two images of like
tomato women
is an among us with a tomato
leaf and tits
and then one that's shitting catch up
and one that's farting and those are the only results
on rule 34
no one of them is an among us
I mean I guess this one's not explicit
I guess this one's technically
like technically won't get us
on youtube
the other ones will
because they involve anuses
but I did find
I found tomato anus just believe me
what did we get
that community guidelines strike for
it was for the
the link to the tails gets trolled
or jerry getting fucked by the dog
it's because it recognized the URL
of the website I think
we still have
we still have a strike
on the channel from the time that we
posted the
the shadbase link
in the description
even though we took it out
it was like a long time ago
but it's about to I think it expires this month
so that's exciting
but yeah we've had a strike on the channel
because of that link for like
a year
we didn't get the strike when we posted
it was retroactively applied
like much later
when I mentioned I was drawing
like boobs
booby in one of my voicemails
and I just linked the image
you linked the uncensored image
in the video description
maybe that should also be removed
or replaced with a censored version
in the one that you were on
I think it doesn't look at the image
I think it looks at the link
text
and if it matches with like
rule 34 that's a not allowed
site
I'm nervous about it because
they've retroactively applied them
the fact that it didn't trigger the thing
doesn't mean that it's safe
and that it won't be triggered in the future
if you tell me which episode it is
I can go and edit the description
I can try to figure it out
you weren't on the episode
I wasn't on it
it was a voicemail
all I know is it was one of the ones
with the gravestones
I don't know why
there's no particular reason why I'm bringing this up now
but I want to mention that last night
I drank a
see this is the price
this is the price of spooky season
nobody talks about the damage
it is inflicted on society
from the spooky season meme
I drank a pumpkin flavored
hard seltzer
it was so bad
I know it sounded awful and I was like
that sounds awful and I tried it
and it really was
it was terrible
it's not right
it's not the normal flavor
choice for such a thing
it didn't work but oh
it's so cozy
the meme
has to die
I'm going to be the one to kill it
the instagram girl version
of Halloween spooky season
is certainly
trite
it's just like shut up
I like chocolate
and I like punk
and ghosts and skeletons
I don't really like ghosts and skeletons
and pumpkin is okay
skeletons are funny
honestly
I like pumpkin stuff
the fact like when it's October
I like pumpkin stuff less
because I'm like I don't want to eat it
it's a meme it's a meme now
my enjoyment is not
my enjoyment is not authentic
get a big fucking turnip
get a big fucking tomato
I like pumpkin flavored eggnog
and ice cream
and all that shit it's great
but when it's being commodified
when capitalism has turned it into
a consumer
for the holiday
what everyone tell me about Halloween
is all about
the true meaning of Halloween
it's to get fucked
it's to get
wow
I guess I was wrong
it's to get fucked
sure
I mean Halloween stuff
is very much less commercialized
over here because it
even though we celebrate it
it has always felt like a big American thing
it's from America
I was shocked
I didn't realize when I lived in Poland
it was October
October came around and it was Halloween
and nobody did anything
I saw
I might have seen a couple
a handful of college students that were wearing a costume
but
it just kind of wasn't a thing
I thought everybody did Halloween
I didn't think it was just an American thing
and it's not just an American thing
but it's
most of
everybody does it over here
most of it comes from
not culturally
but my understanding of Halloween
comes from Halloween American movies
stuff that takes place in Halloween
spooky things
all the iconography and stuff
it's Hollywood
sure
it's our main export
we're civilizing the rest of you
next voicemail
is called
sex
I never had it
3, 2, 1
oh there's the tomato anise
the anise isn't visible
the anise was in a different anise I can't send
3, 2, 1, go
why does Kazi hate Nate?
they seem positive about everything else
but
it's like
Nate
is he real or is it ironic
and why
did he do something
how do you feel about
Michelle
how
sex
I never had it
true
I think Kazi doesn't like
the stuff that Nate says
in his videos and elsewhere
I don't know if there's anything else to it
next voicemail
by the way
is called
it is called
t.dash
space-xr
okay
3, 2, 1, go
what can I add
I stepped on and that's the story
next voicemail
is called
moving spaghetti around
they don't get it
they got that tomato anise
true
okay the next one
is an image but it's also
it's also a voicemail
so here's the image
no it's an album it's a whole album
hold on
posting it there
get Nate get $50
what is
what is Nate
is like a hit piece like bounty
get him
spend it anywhere Nate what is Nate
why would your company
just be a guy's name
why is he buying
what is it
well I'm selling
Ben's selling Nate's buying
is it a crypto currency called Nate
that'd be really funny
is it Nate.tech
yeah I found Nate.tech
it's like a payment
dude there's a fucking tomato
there's a fucking tomato on the website
does that have an anise
there is
it looks like an anise it looks pretty puckered up
it's a pretty puckered tomato
everything is linked together
universe
that tomato better be on screen
the world's only app
it's some fucking
it's some fucking payment processing app
it's garbage
solving a problem that
was invented specifically
for it to solve
it makes me mad
it makes me mad just looking at this
fuck this
stupid
oh look something
okay who cares
damn it
I think so pissed off at it
next
oh right
there's the tomato
okay well there's the voicemail
let's go
3, 2, 1, go
hey can you guys add episode
278 on Spotify
thanks
is that the latest one
Tom
put it on Spotify
I don't know how to do it
thanks Tom
I don't know how to do Spotify
okay I will go
to the PCP
thing and I will go
at Tom
someone
asked
for episode
278 to be
on spot
to find
yeah cool
next voicemail is called
3, 7, 4, 1
it is called
the
okay damn it
it's another image
it's a PNG
if that's exciting
the cycloneal is a socialist
masterpiece
immigration is a form of colonialism Abby
we need to hashtag build a wall
booba
that is what she think
this is a true image
this is very true
it rings very true yeah
I like that
I have 9 subscribers and I'm called
patreon.com
on youtube
should have unironically called my channel that
413 views
haha
413 views yes true
cycloneal is not a socialist
masterpiece
but the version of me
that made this video
it's a socialist-ish piece
it's a socialist-ish
it is
it's social-ish
it's so delish
we never
I never re-read
cycloneals for the cycloneals cast
we could always do it
but we could always do it
I still want to
I still wanted to do one about it
at this point I would have to re-read it
myself as well
okay I don't want to think about that
I got fucking shit to do
next voicemail is called
J
wait no here it is
there it is
wait do we listen to the last one
it's 0 seconds
there's no content
next one is called J
one go
what's your opinion on comics
drawn by people with no artistic
talent
do you think the story has to be funny
for terrible art to be justified
I am asking this
because I am a person with zero
artistic knowledge and I'm planning to make
a comic but it's supposed to have
a serious tone not a comical
tone
that's tough
comics and all
illustrations can look
raggedy
there's no correct way
the cleaner the lines are
doesn't mean it's better
if you can find a way
to communicate whatever ideas
you have
with the level of talent you have
because if it's a serious
story and you don't have
any artistic drawing talent
but you can write the dialogue
or whatever
you can basically make it text
there's no rules
you could also
get away with
even if you can't draw particularly well
if you're good at setting up a visual tone
for the use of color or something
that could also help
you ever read
you ever read Kate Wertz
comics
yes
though she's really good at drawing
she is good
there's sketchy there
there's a lot that goes into drawing anything
even
things that a layman might assume
is like oh that's lazy work
that's easy to draw
but I mean obviously not really
no
just work within your means I guess
if you know you can't really draw
very well but you really want to draw something
if you try to paint
a masterpiece thing
it's probably
not a good place to start
you can work towards it of course
you okay I think
it's tough if you have
a tone in mind
if you have a serious tone in mind
and it's like well
if you're a
bad artist
and you just kind of go with it
I mean it's going to draw attention to itself
like the bad artist is going to call attention to itself
and it might be tough
to make that work in a serious
story
well yeah I think if they're asking
because they said they don't want it to be a comedic
work and from
like tales gets trolled
some of the things there are like
not supposed to be funny
they're supposed to be intense and gory
and scary but they nonetheless
are hilarious because
of how badly they're drawn despite
how serious they're trying to be
for a number of reasons
like if I imagine like oh berserk
but drawn by a laserbot
it would not
work as well in conveying
guts and his like
struggle if it was drawn like that
but
there are ways
I think it's mostly because
like drawing a character from berserk
requires
knowledge of anatomy but if you draw
a character that deliberately is not supposed
to be anatomically correct
you sort of sidestep
the implication
that you are failing at doing something
if it may if it looks deliberate
if you know what I mean
I think if okay you can't
you say you can't draw okay
I think the only way
the only way is you're gonna have
you're gonna have to bust out the old tablet
or whatever and you're gonna have to like doodle
you're gonna have to like experiment with what you
can draw and just try and find
some balance
of something that you are able to do
and that like looks close enough
that it doesn't look like
distractingly different than like
what tone you're going for
you can't it's there probably is
some I can't think off the
top of my head of any like very
like I was thinking one punch man
one punch man was drawn very sketchily
but like that's a that's not
it's not exactly a comedy
it's partly a comedy it's also possible
to like go for a really simplified
style that just looks appealing
like appeal can also
be fine on its own
something like I mean yeah
you could just go for like a hyper minimalist
sort of thing and that could
like um
I don't know like like Paul
Paul who is a ghost I mean that's
that's a comedy a comedy it's partially a comedy
is that what is called Paul
who is a
uh
it's a yeah it's a comic
but it was from a website the website was
do you know
do you know what I'm talking about Paul who is a ghost
I think I can't find it on google
no it was a it was
a webcomic okay I don't know
oh pictures pictures for sad children
pictures for sad children is the
webcomic I'm thinking of it is
it is somewhat it is comedic but it is
it has a sort of
serious tone to it
and is hyper minimalist
yeah super hyper minimalist can
work I think the the the main thing
to remember is that
if it looks
if whatever style you're drawing looks
deliberately drawn that way
and it doesn't look like you've tried
and failed to do something that you can't do
then it would then it will come
across as less comedic
so if if you think of like
an artsy fartsy um student
film because I've seen a lot of those
artsy fartsy student films
and student film animation
things they're drawn
you know sometimes
the the the student can't draw
very well but they have a very serious
topic that they want to talk about in their
film and
they're sincere and they're earnest
and they're not trying
to go beyond you know the good ones
I mean they're not trying to do
what they can't do
and because of that you can sort of buy
this really shitty art
telling this sad story
so or not necessarily sad
but like non comedic
so it can work
yeah yeah
so you've got options
it's not it's not hopeless
but you gotta you gotta you're gonna have to experiment
you're gonna have to try different things
and strike upon something that you think
you can do and that works with the
story you're trying to tell
if possible
next voicemail is
it's number
43 here and it is
called
patreon.com
3 2 1 go
saw someone on twitter talking
about how
like they were upset that someone
on patreon had essentially pledged
just for a reward and then
immediately unplugged
like gave them the dollar got the thing
got out and their basis
for their argument was basically like
oh you don't pledge to patreon
for the reward so you pledge to support
a creator this is a
super dick move if you do something like this
psa guys don't
psa don't do this
give me psa
you care if people do that on your
patreon
like people you put a reward
at a dollar amount
it's so rude
it's so rude for you to pay the amount
that I asked you to pay in exchange for the thing
I said you could have
yeah
if they were talking about themselves
if they were talking about like someone just pledged
to my patreon and then unplugged
psa don't do this
this is a bad move
like that would be so gauche
you're just telling people not to pledge to you
that's money you're not getting
if you're not happy
the sort of person who
is not interested in pledging long term
which is a lot of people
even if they do like your work just because of
money issues they just need to
hop on and off and that's fine
the sort of person who would
pledge just for a reward is the sort of person
who would not have pledged had the reward
not been there
they would not have just become
a supporter
it's extra money you're getting
if you think that your reward is
not
it's
more than what they should be getting for
you know a single pledge
then like don't make it a patreon reward
like sell it on whatever you're offering
sell it on gumroad or something
or at least up your like
tiers to be more expensive or something
yeah up your tiers or do it some other way
like you're the one that put it on
the marketplace at that price
if you see like a guy on patreon
who's getting like 10,000 a month for some crazy shit
only like half that money
is probably going to be from like long time supporters
a lot of it's going to be people who pop in and out
but if there's enough of them that can still be
a consistent revenue source
there's nothing wrong with that
it's going to happen and it's going to make you money
so accept it
imagine complaining about
someone pledging to you wrong
that's so annoying
you're giving me money to think about
plus to us instead we
appreciate every patron
we did, we did
someone on twitter when I made the post
with the new bonus episodes
someone was like
I'm just going to pledge
they were being cheeky
they were like I'm just going to pledge
and get all the episodes and un-pledge
and I was like no don't give us $5
oh no please
don't do it
how will we ever recover
yeah
next
voicemail is called
oh it's another, it's just called
who designed the procrastinators podcast logo
there's no audio
the answer is divu
I forget
the reasoning for it
I guess I could scroll back in the
PCP chat and maybe find where divu said it
was there reasoning for it?
I think they had reasoning for it
but I don't remember
and it was such a long time ago
they just made it
and it's like okay how about this
and we were like yeah that sounds cool
we know what CDs are, we're old
it's funny
the background of the image
well I changed the icon
to be the gravestone one
but the old image in the background
it had some gray shit
and it was actually the vapors
it was a page of the vapors that was
partially scribbled over I think
that's what that is, interesting
why?
I'm pretty sure, yeah the old
maybe if I have the file
do I have the full size file on my
computer somewhere
yeah I think if you look at the
I want to
fuck where is it
D drive, PCP folder
wait it would be in the google drive
the full size
version
you can't see it on the small version
hold on I'm going to do it
I'm logging in
I remember doing some fucking stuff
if you're a logo when I did my
PCP theme way back
I was making an icon for it
and I didn't know what that sketchy stuff was
and I had to recreate something similar
yeah I'm almost
I just want to look and see
and just make absolutely sure that I'm not making
complete fool of myself
PCP components
theme
theme assets
I'm looking through the
no those are audio assets
images and logos, here we go
general
here we go
download this one
scanning for viruses
let's examine this
closely
there it goes
uploading
yeah it's the
vapors, it's the bush
it's bushes and trees
I don't know why
and there's another image
warped over it
it's like two pages of the vapors superimposed
on each other
I don't know
fascinating huh
sorry I was
for a second
there it is
sketchy vapors, sketchy vapors bushes
right I always had
the cutaway
PNG version
thumbnails and stuff
I wonder if I can find the image I created
for my
soundcloud thing because I also had to put some
scribbly lines in the background but there were different
scribbly lines
there's no real reason for it to be there
it's so strange
I thought it was like marble
never really looked at it
yeah I can see why you would think that
but no it's uh
it's that
just because
which voicemail
was that
that was
three
no that was uh
okay there's one more
voicemail
it is called I need it
here it is, found it
okay I need it
3, 2, 3, 2, 1
go
I need
breath mints
I need it
it does not
need to come
from a cis woman
it can come
from a man with
big mommy
milkers
Ben
give me your breast
milk
that's what they said
okay
I'm on it chief
my tradition of harassing Ben is being continued
by the people
you started something but can't
when the voicemails were brand new
once let out the genie can't be put back in the bottle
when the voicemails were brand new I remember Ben
I remember you saying
why is so many of these voicemails about me
it was me Ben
yeah true
that makes sense
I'm seeing this meme theme
I'm seeing this meme theme here
what did you just scribble
that stuff in the background
I think I just googled like sketch of
trees and just
so you knew it was trees
I mean it sort of looks like trees and bushes
I could sort of tell
clouds like it had to be one of those things
it's one of the shots
of the scenery from
Vincent's point of view in Vapors Chapter 2
I know exactly what it is
I didn't know it's from Vapors that is some cool trivia
and also Voice Smailer
if you like breast milk
well I've been animating a pair of flopping titties
this whole time I've gone
I've been looking at them this whole time I've had my dick in my hand
the entire show
by the way
you can go to patreon.com
the content on patreon.com
slash oblivionfall is
it's my seal of approval
right now if I had to plug a money thing
it would be the GoFundMe please
yes the GoFundMe
to remove boobs
it is a paradox
what is given can be taken away
it's not actually
it's not actually that confusing
what is that up to
how much do I talk about it
it's up to $600
and it's been one day
one day
actually slightly under 24 hours
as of our recording right now
I'm going to be doing
some live streams
to fundraise I'm going to be playing Undertale
for the first time
I've never played it
that's going to be a big live stream
I'm going to be doing a 12 hour variety stream
youtubers and stuff I know
and I'll be doing like a minecraft stream
where I try to speedrun the game
while my friends try to hunt down and kill me
that'll be fun but a few things planned
oh like dream
yeah like dream
just like that one guy
it is really fun except when we do it
it's not fake
I'm not going to say that dream fakes
those videos but there's a lot of
elements that are rehearsed
for sure
on twitch
stream on twitch or on youtube
it'll be on my oblivionfall youtube
the one with like
38,000 subscribers
not the really big one
I don't know what that audience is like
they scare me a little bit
the big one
are they there for the tits
they're there for the cumzone stuff
they'd be like a fundraiser to remove tits
I'm just going
I don't love you anymore
you'll be attacked
you'll be torn to shreds
you'll be hard and feathered
drawn and quartered
exactly
I don't want to risk
the demographics of those
freaking out those people
it can't hurt though right
maybe there's few people
well here's the thing
if it turns out that there's a bunch of people in there
who are like transphobic or something
which I don't know if that's true
I would rather
those people
support me for my animation
and then that money can go towards
my partner's bottom surgery later on
so that way they can unknowingly
aid in that endeavor
true
sneaky
but I mean
they're just there for the boobs which to be fair
that's reasonable
who can blame them
ugh
that's it that's the last voicemail
oh are you
I know
what else we got
did I complain about that terrible pumpkin seltzer
I did
I kicked a mouse the other day
you kicked a mouse
yeah there was a mouse
in my new shitty apartment
it got even shittier
there's a mouse running around in the kitchen
and I saw it on the table
and I saw it like climb down
I saw something at the corner of my eye
it was on the table and I see something
climbing down
the like rack that we keep our like
our pans on and it climbed down
to the floor and I see it
and I can see it start to run across the floor
it's right in front of me it's crossing right in front of me
I think
that I had
the ability in that moment
to kill it to put my foot out and
I saw its path I saw where it was going
I could have stopped it and killed it
I didn't have the courage
I was too squeamish
you thought about how it would feel to have your head crushed
I mean
that's the kind of thing that makes me squeamish
and makes me like I don't want to
I don't want to do that
so instead
I kicked it
I kicked it like a hacky sack
did it fly across the room
it did not fly across the room
it did not leave the ground it did not get air
but it did sort of go skidding
it kind of spun and skidded across the ground
and it sort of like
it wasn't even that hard
it didn't even hit that but it kind of thunked into
like the kitchen
sink cabinets
and then it like scurried between
the cabinet and the dishwasher
and I was like fuck
I should have why did I even bother
why did I even bother to do that
I could have killed it
now it just has a broken rib cage
maybe it'll just
saw it again later
it's literally better than ever
it was exhilarated
it got hit close to death
but it came back twice as strong
it just came back with a cool story to tell
that's all I gave it
I bought a bunch of traps
and set a bunch of traps in the kitchen
so maybe it will die soon
I guess we'll see
stomping a mouse to death is a bit
much for anyone I think
I one time in my old place
which at one time
did have mice in it we eventually killed all the
mice with traps but at one time it did
have a mouse problem and one time I
there was a mouse in the
near the trash can and I saw it
it like scurried and it stopped
and I froze and I was like
what do I do what do I do and I
dropped a pan on it and I killed it
by dropping like a metal pan and crushing it
it was not that gruesome
it wasn't like smushed
it was just you know
concussed and injured and bleeding
a little bit and it died
that's what you got to do I could have done it again
but I didn't want I don't want to feel its bones
crunching I don't feel its organs
squishing under my foot like
the thing with me is that
like I don't want to have to like
pick it up but I know no one else
will do it and it's
I don't want to leave it there
like a fucking towel
like get the blood off like
you when I moved
in my old
my old house the sanctity of life has nothing to do with it
it's just gross we had
we had a mouse problem for a while
at one time
a mouse was definitely running around
in my bedroom and I was like
this is fucking unacceptable this can't
fucking continue and there was a whole
my old room had a
it had sort of a little
like not a crawl space
it just had a weird like
it was a rectangular room
but on one side of it
between the far wall and the near wall there was just a gap
there was like a two foot wide little like
side space
that I just kept like a bookshelf in there
and in that
down that little side space
the inside corner of it at the very corner
underneath the radiator there was a little hole in the wall
and I was like
I saw a mouse one time crawling inside
the radiator
just going from one end of the radiator together
definitely coming from inside that hole
so I put glue traps
I put a glue trap in front of the hole
and I was like it can't come through here anymore
it'll step on the glue trap it'll die
I was clean so
fast forward like two years later I'm cleaning up my room
I'm packing up all my stuff I'm moving out
and I'm taking my bookshelf out of that hidey hole
space
and I see underneath it
it's kind of hidden underneath the radiator
I see the glue trap
there's something on it
I'm pretty sure
that there's just been a dead mouse
you know in the corner of my room
for like a year now and maybe
maybe it was the only mouse
and it got stuck in the glue trap and it died
maybe
it died there and other mice
would look at that hole
and think maybe I should come out into this room and then they would see
a corpse lying there and be like
no I don't want to go there actually
one way or another
it did stop mice from coming into my room
I never saw another one
so mission accomplished
didn't you smell dead mouse corpse?
no
I mean in terms of
like volume of
guts
mice don't have a lot
they're quite small they're very small
well this was Elton
I didn't look I didn't
I didn't want to look at it I didn't examine it closely
I'm pretty sure it was like a desiccated mouse
it was so
I couldn't even really tell what it was
when I saw it
but I think if I had looked closely I would have seen
like a withered mouse
remnants
I suspect
I mean how much does a mouse weigh
you could compare that to like leaving a bit of meat on the floor
right?
like one ounce
like nothing at all
house mouse like 0.68
mouse mouse one ounce
less than an ounce
waylord just like waylord
a mouse is lighter than air
by volume
it floats like a balloon
that's a fact
does that mean tiny
now that's a tiny fact
yeah it has
yeah it's volume
and it's mass
if you calculate it
it's literally lighter than air
and it's called the float whale
it's a float whale pokemon
it literally like floats like a balloon
alright so like a house mouse is like
0.04 pounds
that's like
a 25th of a pound
so if I take a pound of meat out of the freezer
it's less than an ounce
and take like
less than a 20th
take like 4% of it and leave it on the floor
that's not gonna smell
I don't think so
I have
one story
on the topic of being afraid to squish things
this is a
horror story from my real life
you know it's October
it's the season
for spookies
boo
no spookies allowed
so I was living
in Dunedin
which is at the bottom of the south
island of New Zealand
it's in
I'll post this image in chat
because I lived in the north island most of my life
but my family spent like
5 or 6 years living in Otago
specifically in Dunedin
and we're not supposed to get
a lot of bugs in that area
like most of the
New Zealand doesn't have many nasty bugs or animals
in fact it's one of the nicest places on earth
for avoiding that stuff
but we were in Dunedin
I was playing in the sand pit in the backyard
and I felt a scratch
scratch on my neck
and I'm like
I just kind of flicked at it
and then a few seconds later I feel it again
terrifying
and then I feel it really strongly
it's like on the side of my jaw
and I see something out of the corner of my eye
I swipe at it and a fucking
Avondale spider
drops into the sand in front of me
I put a picture
that's a big boy
they are fucking huge
these things are not supposed to be in the south island
they're supposedly not there
but there is one of these fucking things on my face
I was like 8 years old
I screamed
yeah I mean fair
I would
I was fucking crying
and my sister out to kill it
and my sister didn't want to squish it
I thought you can't squish it
it's so big it must have bones
I'm getting uncomfortable
get this fucking image out of here
no I guess I'll leave it it's fine
no I can bear it
the people can suffer
this was on my face Ben
I was like
oh what if it's more spiders on me and I took a shower
but my sister used up two whole cans of fly spray
on this thing
one time I found a caterpillar crawling on my shoulder
and I was like oh my god what if there are other caterpillars on me
what if they're just on me all the time
and I just don't even know what to throw on me right now
caterpillars are cute though
I hate caterpillars
they're wriggly and squishy usually
they're big and squishy
they're fat and they're gross
we have them
they're slow and not a spider
I'm gonna throw up just thinking about them
we have
a thing where I live
in other places too
we have these things called gypsy moths
I wonder if you're not supposed to call them that
anymore
but yeah that's what they're called
and that's what everyone calls them
and they have
part of the year in trees
they would
in the corner of trees
in the corner of branches
they would have these big white masses
of webs of nets or whatever
and they would lay their eggs in there
and then some years
there would just be a big harvest of them
and you would just find them
crawling up your house's walls
and garage doors
around
and then they would die
and then you'd find their corpses all over
the fucking place
the gypsy moths are
particularly disgusting
they're not cute at all
but even the so called cute ones
I think are pretty nasty
and disgusting and I don't want to think about them
oh the gypsy moth caterpillars
they're kind of gross looking actually
they really are, they're not pleasant
when I was at school we had like monarch
caterpillars
we just had a plant that had a bunch of ease
and we would watch them and then they'd go into a cocoon
and we would like wait for the butterfly to come out
and it was really cool
that's pretty cool
yeah I mean these are in like a
these are not
they're funny, he's reaching
he's halo reaching
I would be absolutely disgusted
if one were on me or if I had to touch one
like
I let them crawl on my fingers
not the spider though
having long hair
sometimes freaks me out
cause like you know it touches my neck
and I'm like well that's my hair
you know I know what that feels like
and then occasionally like I don't know
a bit will like fall
whereas it's been balanced and it falls onto my neck
and I feel like something is suddenly touching my neck
and I'm like oh my god
there's something touching my neck now
but it's just my hair again
and then sometimes there is a bug
and I don't know what to think
at any moment
any feeling I could feel
could be like death
you will die
I was walking
this is an old story now
this might have been pre-COVID even
but I was walking around with
Kazi and Munchie
and Munchie had like a
he was like he like
jerked or moved and he was like and there was like a beetle in his hair
there was just like a beetle crawling around
in his hair or I think it was a beetle
or it might have been
it might have been like a big
it was some kind of like fairly large insect
was just like in his hair and he was like what
ugh and he was grossed out
and then like an hour later
there just was another one
there's just two of these same like
I think they were beetles, these black beetles
and he was very disturbed by this
because it's like how many more are there gonna be
I came home from the movie theater
recently
we saw a movie I think
actually maybe it was I don't know
we came home from somewhere like a week ago
and I just felt something tugging on my arm
when I moved my arm I felt something like tugging
and it was like restricting my
movement and I realized like after like
a minute of fumbling around it was a spider web
but like a really really strong one
like just a single thread
that had like wrapped itself around my body
it was like near invisible and I could feel it
and I was trying to get it off me
and then my husband
was like trying to help me and then it got stuck to him
and he was like what the fuck this is strong
and I don't know where it came from
but it was like a single long thread
that was at least like three or four meters
long
I've never had a spider web
thread that's like so strong that I'm like
oh it's pulling on me like it's
yeah like and I tried to like pull it
to break but like I guess it was also like
it just kind of got taught
it was weird
was it like twisted around like a rope
it was sort of like on my arm
sort of wrapped around my arm a bit
and then like went around the back of my chest
and maybe like my shoulder
or something and it was also like
sucked in my hair in some aspect
I was trying to get it off for like
a good like five minutes with one long
thread
I don't know what kind of spider would make that
but I never found a spider
there was um
okay funny
funny exterminator story
I was talking to my
Brazilian roommate
about the mouse we had both seen the mouse
and uh
I was relaying to him a funny factoid
which was that someone I knew
once had an exterminator
I think it was like a store that they worked at
and like an exterminator came in to like
do pest control and there was like
there was like a crab there was an ocean crab
like living in their basement
or something the exterminator had to get rid of a crab
that just lived there
for reasons that nobody knows and
I told him this fact and he was like
uh crab like what's uh
what's what's what's that what's a crab
like he didn't know the word in English and I was like
uh
I'm like trying to think how do I explain what a crab is
I'm like well it's you know it's in the ocean
it's got a shell
and finally I had to do the little
like I had to do a little crab walk
I had to put my hands up in little pinchers and move
move side to side going like huh
and he was like oh yeah
like I got it
I did the I had to I pantomimed it
and it's the universal language
that that that gesture
means crab it's in in every language
across the globe actually you were a crab but were you
crab core
yeah for a moment yeah just for a moment
I think so
I think I did it I pulled it off
uh
shit that's all I got to say
about anything I'm just gonna
anyone in the audience who doesn't know
get the crab core reference
I don't get it
oh oh my god
alright so when uh
emo like metal music was going through
it's like
weird you're like well like when metal
core a lot of metal core
music is bad
some of it's really good but a lot of it's bad
um because
I guess I guess
I guess and at the time
people liked the metal core bands
where
but they're like the bands where the
singers were like like early
tooth like early
2010s vloggers
hmm
it's just a whole band of Onesians
yeah look at this power stance
it's the double
doing it together at the same time with the same
outfit and the same hair it's just so funny
alright yeah they all they do all look
is it literally the same guy just
playing four instruments no they're different guys
they look like the same guy
that white gate
that horse um
straddling like legs apart
is that the crab
stance that's the crab core it's the crab stance
wait what's the time stamp
oh um it's
throughout the whole thing but there is like one specific
time stamp that's
like 118
118 is legend
let me see the exactly
what you're talking
oh yeah he's like he's doing the
like moving from side to side
he does the little like
the lateral it's like the lower you stand
the cooler your your your riffs
the sicker your riffs
exactly
your riffs which are just
like because that's all you need
you just go do do do do
on the guitar
god i hate this band
i don't know
i think i found a new favorite
are we um god we're almost
almost four hours lol
yeah
uh are we are we
are we finished here are we
i think we're finished
i just don't want to end
give and take dot site clear us a gun smoke
yeah yeah yeah
yes check out it should be at the first chapter
should be out by the time this episode comes out alive
i'll make sure check out
check out oblivion's uh the kickstarter
for the govians
is yeah the go fund me right the go
my partners trans we need
their boobs to go in the bin um the doctors
won't let us give them to give unfortunately
they don't support organ trafficking
that should be that should be
illegal they should though just
this once yeah it should be illegal to
forbade organ trafficking it should
well i think it should be
illegal to make it illegal to forbid
organ trafficking actually
understand what that means
but yes that means
whatever but you but but i agree yeah
uh okay
i guess check check the check
that out uh and um
for me uh
fuck you uh become a patron
listen to bonus episode
find out
what you should do if i call you a gay
wizard bottom
it's that you you'll be glad you did
uh
is that it are we good end of the episode
goodbye
that's the end of the episode
mwah