I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It is me, Ben Saint, and Simsie.
No, it isn't.
It's me, Oblivionfall.
How's it going?
Okay, do it.
Do the Oblivionfall impression, but say something with a TH sound in it.
You can make it an F. No, I literally couldn't think of a single word that had a TH in it.
There aren't any.
It's a trick question.
Something.
I need to go do something.
Does he do that?
Does he do what?
Does he do the THF thing?
Yeah, a little bit.
Okay.
Subscribe to Oblivionfall's Patreon, everybody.
Sorry, Oblivionfall.
Everybody critique Oblivionfall while he isn't around.
Never do that.
Yeah.
The reason why I said, oh my god, and then went silent, and then said fuck softly before
we started recording.
That did alarm me.
That did make me quite frightened.
Well, I was tense because there's a fly in my room, and it is a particularly annoying
one that I have failed to kill for like an entire day now.
He will not land anywhere.
He just won't do it, and I keep losing track of him.
And usually it doesn't take me this long to kill one, but he landed on my gallon jug
with my excess slime in it, and I was like, oh my god, I was going to whack him while
he was on the cap, but he took off again.
Mal, maybe one day you'll find him.
He, he, this is the worst fly ever because he won't land, but he keeps like buzzing my
face.
He keeps buzzing like right across my face and in my ear, and like flies usually don't
do that.
Mosquitoes tend to do that more, but he is like aggressive and evasive, and he's big
too.
He's not even like a small one.
He's like a, he's like a good sized house fly.
He's one of the fat, juicy fuckers that buzz around.
He's not like the biggest, but he's, he's, he's big-ish.
He's house fly size.
He's not like one of the little ones.
I've mostly had moths recently, yeah, because of the heat wave means that I kept my window
open at night to try and actually cool down my room for once, and it would just meant
a million moths got in.
So there are about 40 dead moths on my windowsill, and then I think a bunch of spiders got
in as well.
So there's spiders in my corners.
There's one I can see right now just above my bed.
There's one in the lamp shade of my little desktop lamp who's built perfect spider web.
Yeah, I live in a spider hole.
Well now I don't feel quite so bad.
Oh yeah, that's all right.
I mentioned, I mentioned there were fruit flies in my kitchen.
There's have been reduced somewhat because I finally took my garbage out.
So you know, I'm thinking little, taking baby steps.
Mine was more of a migration more than an infestation, I think, because I just sort of left the way
open for them.
I haven't dealt with them yet.
Did I describe the most disgusting thing that I saw in my kitchen a while ago?
It was a...
Was it the coffee thing?
No, no, no.
It was more recent than that.
That was a while ago, like when I moved.
This was...
Okay, I mean someone had, you know, we had mice, so someone laid a mouse trap, a glue trap.
They laid it in the crevice between the fridge and the counter, which has like a couple,
like two inches of space there, which is just wide enough for it to set a glue trap.
And it did catch a mouse.
And you could see it like, you know, it wasn't really under anything.
You could pretty much see it just if you looked in between those.
It was easy to see.
The mouse got caught in the glue trap, laid there and died.
This fly is buzzing right in my face again.
I don't...
This one...
Why does he...
Most of them don't, like, come at me.
This one, like, comes at me and yet and never lands.
And I'm so angry.
I'm so fucking mad at him.
What did I do?
What did I do to be punished like this?
You do not have Febreze that you can use to murder him or something like that.
What do you mean Febreze?
Like a spray?
Well, it stuns them and then you can kill them.
Spraying at that...
Does it?
Yeah, usually.
Like, deodorant or something like that will usually, like, stun a creepy crawly and make
him able to be assaulted by a grown man.
I wonder if I have anything like that.
I have, like, a sprayable sunblock.
No, that's probably not.
I don't think I want to get that, like, all over my room.
It's more like aerosol kind of thing, yeah.
Shaving cream?
Probably won't do it.
It'll keep him in place.
If I hit him, yeah.
Yeah.
Um...
Okay, okay, but anyway, this mouse died on the glue trap and then before I noticed it,
he became infested with maggots and then the maggots crawled out of his body and also
got caught on the glue trap.
So the glue trap was covered not only with a dead mouse, but also with dead maggots.
Were there any maggots feeding on the corpse of the maggot?
Yeah, smaller maggots, based out of the...
It was very...
It was horrible.
Yeah, that was the sound.
It was very gross.
I don't think I've ever encountered a maggot in my life.
I don't think I've ever had to come to terms with the fact that those exist by seeing them.
Oh my god, I got it.
You got the fly?
I got the fly.
Did you get him or if you caught him?
No, I killed him.
He's dead.
He's dead, okay.
Seriously, he's been buzzing my face since last night.
I had to go to sleep knowing that he was around because I just couldn't catch him.
He was flying near my feet like on the floor.
He wasn't landing.
So I picked up my writing tablet, my soft paper notebook and I laid it out flat and I threw
it at the ground hoping to intercept the space between it and the floor and catch him in
it and it worked.
It worked.
I just hydraulic pressed that man.
I've done that.
This is not the first time that I've killed a fly not by like whacking it when it lands
but like by throwing something at it when it is in flight.
It happens.
It can work.
You know what's perfect?
A slipper smack.
Slippers, for some reason, some of the way the design have the perfect momentum and speed
to accelerate fast enough to destroy any fucking bug.
I have whacked a fly with a slipper before.
I have done that, yeah.
It's nothing that makes you feel more like a cartoon character than doing that.
First you feel like walking around in like a dressing counter to take off your slipper
and kill a bug with this slipper.
There is something that makes me feel more like a cartoon character than that and I did
it at my last house and that was no two houses ago.
Was it rolled up newspaper?
No.
I killed a mouse with a frying pan.
Yes, there we go.
I literally did that.
Rolled up newspaper would be pretty good.
Rolling panes is another good contender.
But again, just like this fly, I killed that mouse not by whacking it with a held frying
pan but by dropping a frying pan at it on the ground.
You killed that little motherfucker from above.
What the hell?
You killed that little motherfucker from above my fucker, yeah.
I didn't like it.
Mice are, I mean, mice are kind of cute.
Yeah, that's the...
It's kind of, yeah, it's a bit of a bug.
I mean, I don't like them living in my kitchen but they're kind of cute when you look at them
so it's not really fun to kill them.
They're just extra pets for me to keep them.
They like poop on the counter.
Ew.
Yeah, sometimes in the corners I find mouse poop and I'm like, well, that's not cute.
That cancels out any affinity I might have had.
It's pretty annoying how everything on this fucking planet needs to shit brown goo everywhere.
At least mouse poop is, it's almost hard to even spot, which kind of makes it worse because
it could be anywhere and I might not even notice it.
But it's very hard, dry, little like tiny little pellets, like smaller than a grain of rice.
Yeah, they look like tiny little black roses, don't they?
Yeah, they do.
And so they're kind of innocuous but like when I notice them and I realize what they are,
I'm like, god, fucking, god damn it.
Those mice have been shitting on my property again.
They've been eating my scraps and then pooping them back out at me.
And that's just disrespectful.
It's not the nicest thing.
No.
No, I'm going to disagree with you.
I think it's the nicest thing.
I think it's the coolest, sweetest thing is that mice leave you little presents all over the floor.
Yeah.
Haven't caught any more.
Only caught that one.
Only caught like two mice in these traps.
I know there still are some, but there are less than there were before, so that's good.
See, I can't even comprehend like killing a mouse because I've never had mouse infestation.
So if a mouse showed up in my room today, I would probably hide it from my family and keep it.
Put it in like a little cardboard box and feed it every night.
Yeah, at that other house two houses ago, they were a bit of an infestation in the kitchen.
They were really annoying and they are even worse one.
I would say they are a worse infestation here at this house.
So, yeah, I really, I never had mice as a kid.
I would see cartoons with a little mouse hole in the wall and be like, lol, what the fuck?
Oh, Jerry kind of actually based.
Garfield.
Garfield won't kill the mice.
That's funny. Garfield's lazy and fat.
I hate that.
Who wrote this unlikable fat character?
Was it J.K. Rowling? Right Garfield?
Trying to make me hate fat people?
By making them not kill mice?
Davis, I don't know.
J.K. Davis.
Blue's legend.
Blue's legend J.K. Fats Rowling or Davis, whatever.
Right, Garfield and Dobby and Hagrid.
I was thinking about that slavery thing in Harry Potter.
Yeah.
It's fun to think about, isn't it?
As a kid, I mean, I wanted to defend myself a little bit because I like those books a lot as a kid.
You were on the side of slavery as a kid, you will say.
Well, of course. I mean, they like it.
They like it. They do like it.
It's in the text. If you read the text you analyze it, it says that they enjoy it.
There's nothing wrong with it.
It literally is. And as a kid, I did not connect it to any real world thing.
I kind of just was like, I guess these slaves, I guess they like being slaves.
So that's weird. That's wacky, but okay.
Isn't that magical and whimsical?
It's magical and whimsical.
This is a magical fantasy world where slaves love their masters.
Okay, it's good.
It's literally Pokemon. We love Pokemon.
Everybody loves Pokemon because you enslave these sentient creatures and make them battleship.
But it's okay because they love it.
Oh, no, because it lets them reach their full potential.
It's literally the same thing.
Hippocrates.
Anybody who hates Harry Potter now because of the horrible things that J.K. Rowling has written and said
and likes Pokemon, you are a fraught and a faker.
Hippocrates. Shigeru Miyamoto.
Shigeru Miyamoto loves slavery and hates trans people just as much. Look at him.
Did you ever see like the leak from Nintendo?
I can't remember if it's like fake or not, but it was something like that.
Apparently whenever they would get people to work overtime at Nintendo, Miyamoto would walk in and say it's Mario time.
And then they would know that that meant they had to stay an extra four hours to crunch for a video game.
It's Mario time?
Yeah, apparently.
I don't remember where I saw that, but I don't think it's true, but I just thought it was funny.
I don't think I've ever heard that.
I think I did hear that he would like...
I think I did hear that he would just kind of like walk into people's cubicles and like fuck around with them.
Like he would just kind of wander in and out of the office at will and just like distract people.
Yeah.
I can't remember who it was.
There were some really early like Western developers that were working at Nintendo of Japan.
I saw it in like a documentary on Netflix about video games.
It wasn't very good, but it was narrated by Charles Martinet, so I watched the whole thing.
No.
There was a bit where they were just talking about the weird attitudes that Miyamoto had where he put them in like a tiny office on the other side of the building from all the Japanese workers.
And he would come in and just go like, you okay?
And they go, yeah, and then he wouldn't look at any of the work you're doing.
Just leave or something like that.
Oh, that's the dream.
It is.
I can't remember what they were working on, but...
Hmm.
Interesting.
Anyway, Harry Potter.
Yeah.
I said that in the worst way possible.
I was just thinking, I just want to say, I didn't love slavery as a kid.
Harry Potter didn't make me love slavery.
I just didn't think about it.
I just love slavery, but I love Harry Potter.
I swear, I swear, I didn't love slavery.
It didn't make me think, oh, slavery is based, actually.
Yeah.
I would say that I don't think Harry Potter has instilled any poor values on me.
I don't think so.
Not directly.
I am actually immune to propaganda.
So in my opinion, it just doesn't work on me.
It would simply not be influenced.
It's like you're a grass type being hit by a grass type move.
It just doesn't work because you always use propaganda yourself.
That's right.
You can't use stunts for.
At least not in generation.
I was going to say you can't get hurt by dragon type moves
because you use dragon type moves, but that's wrong, isn't it?
That's the opposite.
That's the opposite of what's true, yeah.
I don't fucking know Pokemon.
I know Hagrid.
I know who Hagrid is.
Are you not actually familiar with the source material?
With Harry Potter.
No, no, yeah. I've read them.
I've read them. I've watched them. I know.
I haven't watched them.
I've watched the first four movies, I think.
See, I'm a different generation than you.
So I started with the movies.
Yeah, yeah.
I think the first Harry Potter thing I saw was the beginning of the sixth movie.
I watched it with my dad.
No, I watched the whole sixth movie with no context from any of the previous ones.
And then we went to Citrus and saw the seventh.
Then I watched all the ones previous and then we went and saw the eighth.
That's so funny.
I know.
I saw the first movie in theater.
I think I saw the first two or three.
Yeah.
And I just got sick of them.
I just didn't care after a while.
I was scared of them as a kid, so I didn't watch any of them until
that's so funny.
Until I was like 13.
I was scared of fucking everything as a child.
At 13, really?
Yeah, I was fucking terrified.
I didn't fucking...
I think I was like year eight or year seven or something.
Must have been around then.
I mean, I was going to say, I was scared.
You probably never...
You probably did not have a Nintendo entertainment system.
You probably started with like the GameCube or some shit.
Like Spokes, even worse.
Yeah.
So, yeah, on the NES, there was a game called Star Tropics.
And there were caves, you know, to explore and battle in.
And some of the caves were like shaped like a skull.
And that scared the shit out of me.
The skull cave scared the shit out of me.
This was when I was like seven.
Six or seven or something.
So, I feel like I have an excuse.
Do you remember just like really bad like disc PC games?
That whole like early 2000s era of really bad ones.
We had the one that was like zoo vet.
And it was just like really weird like semi pixel art, semi like realistic painting things of animals.
And you just like dragged like needles into them and like sewed them up and stuff.
Like zoo vet.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like a zoological veterinarian.
That kind of thing.
I looked up screenshots of it.
Is that a game?
I don't remember what it was called, but it was something like that.
There are games called zoo vet that come up when you Google it.
There's a bunch.
So, I'm not sure which one.
I'm going to have a look even though I'm scared.
It looked pretty bad.
My sister used to play it and I would hide behind her and cry when the monkey was being sewed back together.
I mean, did it show like surgery?
Yeah, it showed like gooey bits.
I think it was this.
Hang on.
Here's a screenshot of a lion getting shit on his asshole.
What?
No.
It was this kind of thing.
It was like bad 3D renders.
Oh, that's gross.
Yeah, it is.
I know there was one where you opened the monkey's chest and that one really upset me.
Yeah, I could see how it would.
That one scared me.
That was an early video game scaring experience.
The whole vibe of Rayman 2 freaked me out even though I really liked it as well.
Of Rayman 2?
Yeah, that game's just weird and dark and strange.
Just the aesthetic of it really creeped me out.
I was a big, big pussy.
I don't think you understand.
Which one's Rayman 2?
Oh, the 3D one?
Yeah.
I'm not familiar with that one.
There was a level at the end where it has a place like a fucking scary horror movie that clips the audio and it freaked shit out me.
Everything was strange and French and I didn't like it.
I was terrified as good.
You know, when you say it like that, it makes sense.
I was scared of Hieronymus Bosch paintings as a child.
Those are meant to be creepy and scary and off-putting.
I guess it's probably not that weird.
What else scared me as a child?
To this day, I can't watch horror movies.
I don't like the emotions that they deliberately set out to evoke.
I was obsessively, massively squeamish when I was younger, which I've sort of overcome.
But it would even be things like in the Star Wars prequels at the end when Anakin gets burned in lava.
I would fucking scream and run away from the screen because I thought it was gross that his skin was coming off and was burning.
It is gross.
Yeah, but if you look at the effect, it's just a guy with black shit all over his face.
I mean, sure.
I was...
Oh fuck, I just had...
I didn't watch the Nightmare Before Christmas until I was in high school because I thought it looked creepy and scary.
I think I saw a clip from it, maybe from a commercial where the doctor pops his head open and rubs his brain.
And there's the part where the real-world kid opens the present that Jack left him and he pulls out a shrunken head.
And that scared the shit out of me.
Actually, I misremembered it.
I misremembered it as the kid pulls the head out of the box and the head starts screaming.
The head does not start screaming in the movie, but I imagined that it did and that thought terrified me.
Did you ever have something that creeped you out as a kid, like a movie where the whole general thing you found unsettling, but you couldn't stop watching it?
You were obsessed with it.
Something I was creeped and unsettled by.
But you really enjoyed it and wanted to keep revisiting it?
Maybe.
Think of an example off the top of my head at the moment.
There was a terrible live-action Pinocchio movie that we had on VHS.
And, you know, Pinocchio, it has weird shit in it like when the kids turn into donkeys and this had a particularly bad version of that.
Was it live-action?
Yeah.
I don't know when it was made, but there we go.
There's a screenshot of that moment.
Oh, dear.
Let's see it.
No good.
This was something I was obsessed with as a kid.
I just watched that movie over and over again.
It's pretty weird, but I can just about manage the scary bits.
Even Pinocchio himself was very fucked looking.
It looks like a puppet.
He really does look like a puppet.
Oh, I've seen this.
I mean, I haven't seen this movie.
No, yeah.
I've seen this character.
It was Martin Landau.
What's his face?
Gepetto?
Gepetto, yeah, that's the one.
It's like a bolo.
I was always annoyed when I watched the live-action version.
I was like, why isn't those two guys that try and kidnap him a fox and a cat?
Oh, were they in the Disney version?
Yeah.
I know I must have seen the Disney version at some point in the distant, distant past.
I barely remember it.
It's one of the ones that I watched a lot as a kid.
I guess I had a big Pinocchio phase.
I watched it in the early 2000.
I watched a lot of recorded episodes of Winnie the Pooh on VHS.
That adds up.
That makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
More so than any particular Disney movie.
That's good shit.
Wait, there was an episode of Winnie the Pooh that creeped me out, actually.
There was one.
It was a New Adventures episode.
It's the episode where Tigger breaks a mirror,
and so he thinks that he'll get seven years bad luck,
but he, through some sort of logical gymnastics,
convinces everyone that no, actually,
technically, Piglet gets the bad luck due to some technicality
in how the mirror-breaking rule works.
So they try to protect Piglet from bad luck,
and at one point,
it's Tigger's thoughtlessness and his carelessness
that keeps inflicting terrible things on Piglet.
He gets what Piglet, yeah.
But they don't realize this, so they keep convincing him,
oh, it's the curse.
It's the bad luck.
Tigger's right.
Piglet did get the bad luck after all.
So at one point, they build him a safe house
to wait out the bad luck in,
and it's like a towering, it's like a creepy tower of rocks
that's long and pointy,
and Tigger puts a lightning rod at the top,
and he thinks a lightning rod is just something that attracts lightning,
and that that's good, and that it's more safe, actually.
He understands that a lightning rod is meant to prevent lightning strikes,
but he doesn't understand how it works,
so he just put a metal rod at the top to attract lightning lights.
That's so stupid.
And therefore, lightning strikes the safe house and explodes it.
And kills Piglet.
And kills Piglet, yeah.
And he has to go to the zoo vet.
Well, it explodes the house,
and Piglet is left sitting at the bottom of it,
and he's completely traumatized by the fact that his house has exploded around him,
and so he's just sitting there, like catatonic,
like staring straight ahead with his mouth twitching,
just going like...
And there's a shot.
You see him after the explosion,
and he's just staring straight into the camera with his mouth twitching,
and then there's a match cut to another scene where Piglet is still sitting there,
staring straight into the camera, mouth twitching,
while poo and rabbit think ponder,
and they walk back and forth behind him,
like, what to do, what to do, what are we going to do about this bad luck curse?
And for like a full minute, Piglet just stares straight into the camera,
catatonic, mouth twitching, and I found it very unsettling.
Because he just looks really, I don't know, scared.
I love little things like that.
And sort of like his face is kind of twisted up in a sort of rictus expression of horror.
There is a lot of them in like cartoons,
like specific little things that probably wouldn't bother anything else,
but always bothered you, you know?
Me?
No, no, like the royal you, you know?
Everybody has one little thing from like a cartoon they loved as a kid that was like,
I didn't like that bit.
I feel like I spent a long time describing that one,
but there was another one, there was an episode of all that.
I don't know if you're familiar with all that.
Is it sitcom?
No, it was a sketch variety comedy show for kids.
It was on, not SNCC.
Yeah, SNCC was like the Saturday night like Nickelodeon block
for like marginally older kids, maybe.
It's the cooler, hipper one.
A little bit, yeah.
But all that, you know, it had like, it had Keenan and Kel in it,
and Amanda, Amanda Bynes.
Is it, you know, the all that diaspora is extensive.
The big names, you know.
The big names, yeah, yeah, the big names.
Lori, everyone, who could forget Lori Beth Dinberg?
I certainly didn't.
Yeah.
Whatever happened to her?
Anyway, there was an, I think it was a Halloween episode,
and there was a skit in which Amanda Bynes
brings her like monster pet to class for like show and tell,
and it's this big fucking like, it's this big fucking,
I don't know how to describe it, it's a big like furry like beast,
like horned beast that she keeps on like a leash,
and she brings it to class and she's like describing it for show and tell.
And she's, the camera sort of focuses on her as she's like show and tell,
describing things she does with her beast companion.
And meanwhile, the beast is like mauling and killing the other students.
And they, and like, they're like severed limbs are like flying like on screen
from off camera, from where it is dismembering people.
And they don't, there's no blood, they use like green slime for blood.
Like these limbs and stuff are like flying on camera,
and they're like, and they're like green on the stumps where they've been severed,
and they're like oozing like green goo.
Just have a significant impact on you.
And it just goes on, it just goes on and on,
like kind of the point of the scene is how it goes on for a really long time,
and everyone's like, hey, we're being mauled to death,
and the teacher's just like, don't be rude, don't interrupt,
and it just goes on and on until they've all been killed.
That seems like a forgotten like Treehouse of Horror Simpsons.
It's scary, you know?
And it's scared the fuck out of me as a kid.
Yeah, when I describe it.
But that's exactly what happened.
And it upset me a lot, I think.
I think my parents got kind of annoyed at it,
because like it really like disturbed us children at the time.
We were like, we don't want to go to sleep because we're afraid.
We're afraid that the big purple monster is going to kill us.
He was not purple.
He was brown.
I'm just imagining the big fucking thing from Foster's home for imaginary kids.
Yeah.
There's like a big purple guy with horns,
and that's all that's popped into my head.
He looks sort of like a cross between like beauty and the beast beast
and like the father-dook.
That's a good combo.
He was a horned monster of some kind.
He was a villain.
That's all we need to say.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, that was another time a children's media scared me, a child.
See, I was much easier to scare.
Remember the episode of Spongebob where they're looking after a caterpillar butterfly thing?
And then it shows a close-up of the butterfly's face.
I vaguely remember that episode.
That was enough to scare me as a kid when it cut the realistic live-action high-close-up footage of a bug's face.
Just like an actual video of a bug.
Yeah, it would just like cut and it would be filling like the entire screen,
and it would just be really loud.
They are gross.
Yeah, they are.
Bugs are gross.
They are gross when, like, yeah, butterflies look nice from a distance,
but you look at their face and they're just as disgusting as any other crawling insect.
They got that cute nose, though.
The proboscis.
Yeah, the big curly nose friend.
Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
Still.
That has good energy to it. I like that.
Yeah, sure.
The evil demon eyes.
So I still wouldn't...
Not so keen on them.
Demon eyes.
I still wouldn't...
I wouldn't want one to land on me.
It's still a little gross.
Yeah, I didn't think I would want any bug to land on me, and I don't know why.
No, I wouldn't either.
The wings are nice, but their body is still a nasty bug.
Maybe a dragonfly.
Oh, yeah, I mean...
I think dragonflies are cool-looking, but still.
They got that big, fat tail which makes them look less like a bug,
because most bugs just sort of end or go lumpy at the end, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It makes them a little...
I guess that's why they're called dragonflies.
It makes them a little bit more like other animal king to me.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Still.
Their head and body is buggy.
A nightmare.
Yeah, that's true.
A nightmare bug creature.
Yeah.
Wormpool.
Would you let a wormpool crawl up on your shoulder?
Here's the thing.
I am a genius, and therefore I'm psychic type, and therefore I'm weak to bugs.
Oh, okay.
So...
No, it would kill me.
It would kill me instantly.
No, I would die.
I would simply die, my friend.
No, I hate...
Actually, no, I hate caterpillars.
I hate caterpillars maybe the most of any bug.
Worms and caterpillars are the worst, and I like them.
So I think if a wormpool was real, it would make me throw up if I saw one in real life.
Yeah.
I'm not big on centipedes, but caterpillars and worms don't really bother me.
I don't like how squishy they are.
I kind of like that.
They're little guys.
They're little fatties, you know?
Yeah.
I have dreams with worms in them sometimes.
It's like a kind of a recurring...
It's kind of a recurring thing.
That sentence wasn't enough to make me laugh, then.
I have dreams with worms in them sometimes.
I do have worm dreams.
Occasionally, I'll have a worm dream.
And it's always...
I'm never as disgusted in the dream as like I should be, and I'll wake up and be like
retroactively disgusted like, oh, God.
No, yeah.
That's the way with dreams.
Your emotions are always like half of what they would be if this thing happened.
Sometimes I'll be really angry in a dream.
I'll be screaming, and then I'll wake up.
And it's just the next moment, but I'll just be like, huh, yeah.
I was really mad.
I find that dreamy has a lot of passivity to him.
I remember there was one dream where I can't remember how it happened.
For some reason, my entire genital area was gouged out and was just a big bleeding,
fucking gaping cannonball wound, basically.
And I was lying in hospital and talking to someone.
I was like, it is what it is.
Things happen.
What's the Japanese?
It is what it is.
I have no idea.
What the fuck do you think I am?
It's a common phrase you hear in anime and stuff.
Konnichiwa.
Shogunai.
It can't be helped.
That's so good.
Shogunai.
That's what I said.
You look down.
You've been bifurcated, bisected at the midst of Shogunai.
It is what it is.
These things happen, I guess.
It's always shit like that.
I had a dream in high school where I was in a zombie apocalypse
and I was with the girl I had a crush on.
And I was like, don't worry.
We'll make it through this.
We'll rebuild the world.
Stuff like that.
For some reason, dream me seems to be a wise, sage-ly, completely calm.
Just not sweating it that much.
Just not worried about it.
Yeah, basically.
In a situation like that, you got to step up.
You got to calmly analyze the situation.
And just like, all right, here's what we're going to do.
You're going to put the plow on the front of our Mack truck
and we're going to drive through this parking lot.
Well, you kill literally everyone you meet.
Be they human or Zomboni or whatever.
Sure.
Yeah.
Is that what happens in The Last of Us?
I don't remember.
I haven't played The Last of Us.
I played it for the first time recently.
There are bandits.
There are bandits that you do have to kill in The Last of Us.
Yes, that's true.
I believe the backstory of the main character is that
during the 20 years of the zombie apocalypse, he would do anything.
So he would just kill like everybody he came across.
Engaged in some light banditry.
And then he meets the girl and says,
oh, what if I can be daddy again?
And then he becomes daddy again.
What a beautiful story.
Beautiful.
Actually, I only know the story of it because I've seen
the action button review.
Yeah.
Oh, I haven't seen that one.
Now that I've played it, I could watch that one.
Oh, you have.
I've seen all the action button reviews.
What was it?
That's a pretty good one.
I was drawing and I had like Matthew Matosis and Noah Coldwell
in the background.
And I got all of their Last of Us videos in a row.
And I was like...
Were they just auto like recommended?
Yeah.
So I think I was watching like a Metroid one and then it went
to Matthew Matosis's Last of Us one, which came out in like 2014.
So it was like really weird and tearing him back then.
His old videos have held up really well, though.
Who? Matthew Matosis?
Yeah.
They're exactly the same except the mic quality is a bit different
and he's a bit higher pitch.
Yeah, but he said the N word that one time.
Oh yeah, he did.
Yeah, true.
We can't.
You can't condone him.
He said it in an Irish accent though, so it doesn't count.
Yeah, it's true.
That's true.
I mean, Irish people were also called that.
Yeah, I completely forgot about that.
I've never rewatched that review because I don't care about Bioshock.
I like that review because I hate Bioshock Infinite.
And he also hates it.
I mean, a lot of people hate it.
I played it and thought it was bad, but I don't particularly hate it.
But I have never played a single other Bioshock game.
I watched Nate play it and I thought, okay.
And then upon thinking about it more later and hearing more people talk about it,
I kind of realized that it's pretty despicable actually.
Yeah.
It do suck.
I would say it do suck as a game.
Yeah, I would say so.
As a game.
As a gamer.
It sucks as a game and it sucks as a piece of gaming culture.
It's like a regressive sort of damaging piece of media.
That game has such a huge fan, but that game specifically, Bioshock Infinite,
people fucking love that game.
I know so many people that stand by it.
I get what's appealing about it.
The setting is kind of cool.
It looks nice.
Yeah.
That's about it.
Yeah, everything else about it is bad.
It's kind of bad.
Like the gameplay even.
As a guy.
I didn't actually play it myself.
As somebody who likes a good shoot bang and playing that game.
That game came out 10 years after Halo 1 and it plays excrementally worse.
Excrementally is a good word.
Combined.
You've combined some concepts there.
I definitely did not fuck up and say the wrong thing.
Move on.
Bioshock Infinite suck.
Last of us pretty good.
Yeah.
Sure.
I mean, Tim likes last of us more than I would.
Yeah.
Tim finds some interesting things to appreciate.
I think Tim has a little bit of a sort of Gen X boomer sensibility.
And the things that he appreciates that I think I am a little.
He's a little bit, this is awesome.
He's, yeah, he's a little bit like, he's a little bit like, oh, 60 frames per second.
Like HD.
Like at high res, high res, high frame rate.
Like, oh, beautiful.
Yeah.
He's, he's impressed by that sort of thing.
I see.
Yeah, definitely.
It's like, I don't know, every single one of those fucking long form reviewers have
their thing.
I think.
Like Mathematosis seems to be mechanical complexity and solid, like actual design in
terms of going through the world and stuff.
No, we're called Weldovace is all about the experiential storytelling and things like
that.
And Tim Rogers is sort of this.
I don't know how I would describe like his like focus on when he talks about games.
He's very like tangential.
I guess that's the whole point, but you know, I don't know how I would boil it down.
Yeah, there's no way to boil it down.
You're like, maybe he's maybe focused on a game's like.
Reputation.
Yeah, it's like it's cultural.
It's cultural impact.
It's impact on the landscape.
It's it's he reviews games from the perspective of a gamer.
Looking at the landscape of games.
No, I don't know.
That's angry Joe.
Angry Joe does that.
Oh, angry Joe.
Oh, bless you, my friend.
I have not.
I'm not as familiar with his uvra.
He's very much.
That was fucking awesome.
Or this is fucking dog shit.
Where's the shooting?
I think I've seen.
Oh, you know what?
Which there's a there's a jar podcast where they compare.
I think they compare Doug Walker to angry Joe.
No, they did two separate episodes.
One was is the Nostalgia Criticist fringe, as they say, and is angry Joe as bad as they say?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yeah, it was two separate ones, but like they they they have a lot of like comparatively
positive things to say.
Oh, yeah.
They're very passionate people.
Yeah.
What was that thing?
What was that thing he did?
Like he like.
He said something like completely out of line to some like games journalist or like death or
reporter at the game.
But it made me stand up and clap.
He interviewed Jeff Keeley.
And I don't know what specific thing you're talking about, but he just made like a full
of himself basically by being completely unprepared.
No.
No, it wasn't that he.
I don't remember he.
I think he said you're appealing to the lowest common denominator.
Is that it?
Is that the one you're thinking of?
Your show appeals to the lowest common denominator after you've been invited.
He basically just told this guy like he sucks and like in so many words.
And I was like, cool.
I don't know.
I don't even know.
I don't even know who this guy is.
I didn't care.
But like if you think this guy sucks, it's nice that you'll just, you know, you're
not here to like play nice with someone that you hate.
Yeah.
If you hate someone, I respect the willingness to just tell them you fucking suck, dude.
Exactly.
You're an asshole.
God bless you.
Don't be a joke.
Keep it up.
Yeah.
I don't know what he's doing now, but whatever.
Probably reviewing video games.
Probably talking about is there any new video games have come out stray?
The cat game?
I saw stray.
I saw the, what do you call it?
Spyro mod.
It could be Spyro the Dragon.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
I was going to say what?
I saw that video.
I thought it looked pretty fun.
What is stray?
I'm pretty sure it's just like a short exploratory story game.
People were hyping it on Twitter.
It's a cute cat game.
So of course, you know.
But it's like a cat going through a post-pocalyptic world with robots and going through a story
and then you finish it.
I don't know.
Well, what more can you ask for?
From what I know, it's pretty short.
But I didn't play it because it would have made me sad because my cat died recently.
Yeah.
Crunchy.
I saw that.
It came out the day after Crunchy time.
Oh yeah.
Crunchy.
I saw, I'd seen pictures before.
Yeah.
I looked at the, just, Crunchy looked like a sweet cat.
He was a good, good, good boy.
Yeah.
But the heat wave genuinely killed him.
No.
It was horrible to say.
But he's always had like trouble with his breathing.
And he's had a thing with his nose where it leaks and stuff.
But the recent heat wave in the UK, he was just like lying on the ground gasping because
he couldn't get any breath in because it was so hot.
Oh no.
We took him to the vet and it was like, yeah, you can have a big expensive surgery, but
he is 17 and probably is suffering right now.
And we were like, yeah, it's time to say goodbye.
But it's all good.
Anyway, on a more positive note, Stray looks like a fun video game where you play as a
pretty cat.
It looked, I guess, I just, you know, just looked fun to like jump between ledges and
stuff and knock, knock shit over.
That's true.
Fuck around with humans who I guess are not in the game.
It seems like every human is like a robot.
Yeah.
I thought at first maybe that's like a stylistic thing.
Like the cat just sees humans as automatons.
But then I thought, no, maybe this is actually just said in like a post-singularity future
where robots are the dominant species.
Yes, maybe.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
I have no idea.
Speaking of short games, this guy on Twitter, Fulgadrum, he added me in a thread.
He shouted out my game, Phantom's Revenge.
I saw that.
Well, yeah.
Did you look at the thread?
No.
I didn't like it.
I saw the post of yours and it said equally unhinged webcomic.
I was like completely fair, absolutely fair.
When I do the Kickstarter, I should market it as unhinged.
I think that's a good angle.
You could put that as a quote, like a pull quote.
Equally unhinged web.
You know what?
Maybe I will.
The finale to the equally unhinged webcomic.
Just have that in text and then put like five asterisks below it instead of five stars
because you can get away with that.
It will trick people.
Now I'm, yeah, this guy didn't give any stars, but who's to say that the five stars that
I placed in quotations underneath his quote, I didn't say they were his stars.
I just put them there.
Those aren't stars.
Those are asterisks and they're there for an unrelated reason.
They're just decoration, bro.
That's part of the art.
Oh man, on that subject.
Well, I don't want to...
What was the thread?
Okay, yeah, on the subject of the thread.
The thread, it's the thread about short RPGs and some of them look super awesome.
They look better than your game.
I mean, I wasn't going to say it like that.
I mean, some of them do have like a very cool aesthetic to them.
I'm just scrolling through these and like, there were some that stood out to me like,
look at, okay, look at this shit.
This game, I guess, is called Strife of Cosmos.
I don't know what's going on here.
That's pretty cool.
I just think it looks awesome.
It's a little brain rot.
So many things on screen for me, but yeah.
Exactly.
I prefer to cut down on the aesthetic a little bit, but that does look like an RPG to me.
This one looks really cool.
I don't know, it's going through these threads.
Some of these are like two hours long.
I might actually go and play some of these.
That'd be fun.
Maybe on like a stream or something going through the rest of them.
That'd be cool.
Yeah, maybe.
Wait a minute.
Oh my God.
This one's called Slimes.
This one's called Phantom's Revenge, but it's also ugly.
Oh my God.
That sounds like an epic video game.
This one's called Slimes.
Well, I got to play that one.
Yeah.
On the subject of the book, since the Unhinged Webcomic, I have been, I worked like all week.
I basically spent like this entire week just doing shit, man.
Just like doing work on like the format.
Just like formatting files to fit the goddamn template this Chinese company wants me to fit
to have the stupid book printed.
I'm almost ready.
I'm almost ready to print a test print.
Man, I don't know.
It's really bummed me out.
I just felt like I worked like every day this week, and it feels like I'm barely closer
to having it done.
That's not true.
I am close to having it done.
The progress is slow and incremental, but you've done so much of it that you are actually
doing all right.
I'm almost there.
When I get it sent off and when I send her some money and she's like, okay, thanks.
You'll have the book in like three weeks.
I'll be like, thank God, but I'm not quite there yet.
It feels like I've worked and worked and accomplished nothing.
Yeah.
I seriously did nothing else this week.
I didn't get to play any more Mega Man legends.
I didn't get to work on that video project basically at all.
I have put that...
No, finish the next step of the book.
Finish the next fucking book thing.
Do I know what the video project is?
I don't think I do.
I don't think I have told you about it.
Do you want to know?
No, I don't.
Okay, good.
That's fine.
I want to surprise.
I need some surprises in my life.
I have told...
I think Gib might be the only person who I've straight up just told what it is.
I think maybe one or two other people have guessed it or no.
Okay.
Yeah.
I probably, if I thought about it, I might be able to guess it, but whatever.
Perhaps, maybe.
Yeah, if you're not an idiot, yeah.
Ellie is our bleep that out.
Oh, shit.
That's not exactly it, but it's kind of...
It's sort of on the...
It's too close.
Ellie is our bleep that out.
I can't believe you're reviewing this.
Bleep everything.
Oh, no!
No way.
No, that's not...
Okay, I was going to say.
Okay, Ellie is our get ready to bleep a lot of stuff.
No, I'm doing a lecture where I do...
I'm doing a lecture on...
Nice.
Right.
But no one can know.
It's a secret.
Okay.
Is it just like a straight video to audience lecture?
Are you going to...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cool.
There was a...
I was going to do it live.
I had a...
I had a studio books and everything.
Like, when Gib visited for...
Whoa!
Yeah, I had a whole thing set up and then Gib got COVID, so it all couldn't happen.
So, Ellie is our bleep most everything.
Cut that, cut that, cut that, cut that, cut that.
Don't let them know.
Wow, Ben, that project sounded interesting.
Thank you.
I can't believe I guessed it that easily.
You got it...
That's 75% right.
Okay.
Yeah.
You were close enough that I would call it correct.
Sure.
Anyway.
That's fun.
So, I think it's fun.
Although, I've been working on it.
I thought it was going to be kind of easy.
I have decided to make it hard on myself, but it's okay.
That's the way to do something like that.
Yeah.
My new goal with it...
My goal has expanded so that...
I think the video will just end up being longer and that's okay.
Long videos are good.
People like them and they do well on YouTube.
So, I don't even think that's a problem.
Exactly, yeah.
Yeah.
So, that's...
But I didn't get to do it because I have just been doing book stuff.
I hate it.
I hate the stupid fucking book.
It sucks.
It's not even that unhinged, to be honest.
Yeah, it's not unhinged enough.
No, not even close.
It's more unhinged by the context than actual what happens in it.
You know, speaking of context, I mean, I guess Chris Chan's going to trial now.
Yes.
I thought like, hmm, I wonder if I can like...
I wonder if I can use that for marketing purposes.
Ben...
What?
We've been down this rabbit hole before.
I'm in it.
I'm down it.
I'm at the bottom of it.
Ben, do I have to be one of the people in the comments who said,
oh, what ever happened to Prime Directive Chris Chan, Ben?
Well, she can't hurt anyone anymore.
That's true.
I suppose.
She's going away for a long time.
I don't know.
I saw Chris Chan trending because the announcement came out that the case is going to trial.
Did you rub your hands together and then look at all your formatted phantoms revenge comics on your computer?
I don't know.
If the trial was happening and there was like news coming out about it, I don't know.
Maybe it would...
Maybe I could use that.
How long has it been since Chris Chan was arrested?
Is it a year and a half now?
I don't think it's that long.
Wait.
I think it might be.
Wait, when did I put out Sonichi 102?
That would be good.
Because that was like right after...
11 months ago.
Yeah, so almost a year.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm overestimating time.
Did I have an exact date?
July?
On a wild ride, it's been...
Yeah, I put out that video on July 31st.
Wait, that was exactly a year ago today.
What?
Wow.
Well, that video came out exactly a year ago today.
That's amazing.
That's funny.
That was days afterwards.
It was a few days afterwards, yeah.
That's less than a week.
We're recording on things like...
That's funny.
Only a paltry 200,000 views.
Such a shame.
Deserves 10 times that many.
What's my biggest tweet got in terms of impressions?
Can I ratio with that?
I bet not.
Tweets don't get 200,000 likes.
Maybe impressions.
I got 418,000 impressions on one of them.
Wow.
Which one was that?
It was a drawing of a character from My Hero Academia
that was an unfinished sketch dog shit.
For some reason, it got 23,000 likes on Twitter.
I don't know.
Why did this one blow up?
A like on Twitter is better than a view on YouTube.
But an impression...
Yeah, because you have to click the button.
But an impression on Twitter is not as good as a view on YouTube
because you don't have to click anything
to make an impression.
I don't know.
My Twitter has gone nuts recently.
I saw you gained 10k followers this year.
I've gained 14.6k followers in this month.
And I don't know what happened.
I just put out two banger tweets at least.
Two drawings that just did really well.
Which ones were those?
It was the Nika Robin and that one I just sent you.
Oh.
Is it the My Hero Academia?
Yeah.
And then this one.
The most boring drawings ever.
What I would consider a pretty typical Simsie outfit.
Yeah.
There's nothing special about this.
I don't know why they went beast mode.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just because your account is bigger.
And so when you have a hit tweet, the hits get bigger.
Gross is exponential.
How can I monetize that?
Why can't I make it so that people have to pay me a dollar
to follow me?
Can you do that?
No.
You can do that stupid super follow thing.
I don't know what the fuck that is.
Okay, speaking of stupid Twitter features that I don't like,
do you ever see Twitter, I think they're called Twitter Spaces?
Yes.
It's like an audio call that you can join and listen to someone talk live if you want.
I saw someone was doing one.
This guy, Alex, I think it's pronounced Deegan.
Do you know who that is?
No, no idea.
He made a book called...
Oh fuck, what's the title?
He's done a couple comic, comic, graphic novels.
Soft x-ray mind hunters.
Soft x-ray mind.
Let me just post an image so you can get an impression of what sort of art this guy does.
Am I going to be overjoyed or disgusted?
No, it's joyful, it's joyful.
Okay, this is not the best image, but here's a sample.
The word soft has me concerned.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
There are some boobs, I guess, but whatever.
This is neat surrealism stuff.
He did this book called soft x-ray mind hunters.
My friend John lent me that book.
I read it and I thought it was cool and I followed this guy on Twitter.
He's not super big on Twitter or anything.
But he was doing a space the other day and I was like, oh, it's that guy.
I guess I'll join the space and see what's up.
There was like one other person in the space and I joined it.
And he was just playing some hip hop music.
And the text chat in the space just kept sending messages of the lyrics of the song.
And I think it was automated somehow.
And I was like, what's the fucking point of this?
He was just doing a karaoke stream.
He was not singing.
He was speech to text typing, auto typing, karaoke.
I don't know, that might just be a thing that spaces do on their own.
I bet you.
You started it and was like, you know, when you start a live stream and nobody's there and you're like, hello?
Is anyone there?
Is anyone in the chat yet?
I don't know.
That kind of thing where you're just sort of like waiting for someone to show up and then you got bored and started listening to music.
And then he was like, how can I turn this into a thing and then started spamming the audio?
I don't know.
Well, I mean, I joined it for like five minutes just to see what was going on.
Nothing was going on.
You were like, haha, that's crazy.
Bye.
I'll talk about this on my podcast.
I can mine this for content.
I have seen that was the only space I've ever joined.
I guess I would call it a bit of a disappointment, to be honest.
But maybe some other spaces are good sometimes.
I think I joined one from some artists.
I don't remember who it was, but I blocked them shortly afterwards because of something not okay.
They said on the space and I was like, I don't think I want to be aligned with that.
So you were in the space and he said something and you were like, oh no.
I joined the space and I was like just listening.
And then he said the F word that is offensive to the gay people and said that to the chat saying,
you guys are the F word that is offensive to the gay people to the chat.
I was like, yeah, I don't think I want to.
Have you seen, this is not entirely related, but have you seen the one thing that Neil Cisariga ever said to Jon Tron?
No.
Is it great?
Yeah, it is great.
I'll try to find the image, but basically Jon Tron, I think Neil made a tweet in a thread that Jon was tagged in or something.
And Jon replies like, hey man, like big fan, keep up the great work.
And Neil says like, thanks, all I know about you is you were a huge dick to someone that asked you not to say the R word.
And that's it.
I know Jon Tron was in an internet historian video recently.
Yeah, I deliberately did not go watch the video.
I like the internet historians like videos, but I don't want to see it.
I did watch that one and all I got from it was that his middle, Jon Tron's middle name is apparently Arian and I didn't know that before and that was funny.
And he called him out on that.
Is that his actual?
Apparently.
I think so.
Unless he just did the funny internet historian thing where he edits a Wikipedia article and shows it on screen.
It was not a good video.
Jon Tron is not funny.
He, yeah, I mean, some of his older videos seemed funny, but then like, I think the last one I watched was the one where he like fucks around in like fucking like Plymouth, Massachusetts, like doing like some sort of stupid historical cosplay.
Yeah.
Now it was not funny.
I know his latest video was like a parody of like Ted Talks and it was it was five minutes long of him like doing, you know, when like like a sketch comedy where it's like hard cutting between the like a guy pretending to be emotional speakers just saying weird things.
But you got to be motivated.
Time to move like shit like that, you know?
I don't really know.
Just like acting and pretending to be a funny motivational speaker who's embarrassing.
It's like that.
And it's like a six minute long video.
And at the very end, it's just like an advert for Rachel the legend to some shit or some or no, a dislike or whatever that is.
It's a motherfucking game.
I don't know what that is, but okay.
It was like, it was like an ad disguised as a comedy video.
And it wasn't even like where he put an ad in one of his normal videos.
It's just that I can see.
I mean, I can see how the premise could be funny.
Just opposing some kind of embarrassing motivational speaker with someone else's sort of like grim reality or whatever.
I'd like to confirm.
Not funny.
All right.
Yeah, I like the Internet historian.
I mean, going thinking back, I definitely get the sense that his politics, his personal politics are maybe not great.
But it doesn't really come into his videos much.
So I kind of just like if he's not going to make a big deal about it, then I guess I'm not going to complain about it.
Yeah.
So, you know, I like Internet story.
It's one of those channels that I will let play in the background, rewatch videos a lot.
Yeah, they go pretty.
I've rewatched them a few.
I've seen a couple of them a few times.
Yeah.
They're good.
Not interested in his secondary channel though.
I do like his secondary channel, actually.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It's just them rambling about life stories and stuff.
But I find that fairly entertaining.
I haven't checked it out.
The John Tron episode sucks though.
Yeah.
At some point, I think it was that old timey colonial video.
I think I just decided, you know what, I just don't think John Tron is funny.
Yeah.
I don't think I will ever watch another John Tron video.
Not because I don't like him, although that's true.
I'm simply not entertained.
I think I have watched a bunch of them recently.
I only watched that stupid advertising one because it was recommended to me.
I was like, what the fuck is this?
I wonder what that guy's up to.
I think the one you were talking about came out in like three years ago from looking at
this channel.
Yeah.
I think that was the first one that had come out in a while.
I was curious about it or something.
If you never have a public apology for things that you did, then it means that you don't
regret them.
No, he doesn't.
He's totally unrepentant.
I hate him.
He's so obnoxious.
It's obnoxious when people defend him.
The people that defend him are really obnoxious because he's clearly not apologetic about
anything.
So like, don't fucking tell me.
Yeah.
Don't tell me.
Don't lie to me, cowards.
Dude, back off.
Dude, come on.
Yeah.
Fight me.
Anyway, good YouTube interrogation videos of any kind based.
Interrogate.
You mean like...
Jim can't swim.
Yeah.
With us.
Things like that.
Didn't Jim can't swim?
Get like kicked off YouTube for a while?
They got nuked.
Loads of their videos got deleted like one around Christmas, I think it was.
I think most of them are still up, but like their latest one that they did is still gone.
Bummer.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
It sucks.
Yeah, why?
I don't know.
All they do is show things and talk about them.
There's nothing particularly offensive in there, especially when it's all taken from
that weird clinical perspective, which is what makes the videos good.
I mean, is it like the only thing I can think that like might be objectionable about it is
like that maybe it could be considered like murder bilia, like profiting off a crime almost.
Maybe.
Which is like, I don't know if I would make that argument.
I don't know because there's plenty of other channels that do the same thing, do a similar
or the same thing.
Yeah.
True.
Things that seem to have not had these issues.
I don't know why Jim can't swim was a single out.
I saw they were posting.
This was a while ago.
They were saying like they were considering like moving to a different platform or something.
Yeah.
And like, I mean, other platforms are terrible.
But like, yeah, I do really like those videos.
I might go watch something.
I might go watch a Jim can't swim video on to be or whatever.
Yeah.
There's another channel called explore with us, which pretty much does the same thing.
And but they're just a bit more long form and more detailed.
And that one's very good.
I don't.
I've not heard.
I've not heard of that one.
I think they they they think they've blown up more recently, but they're they're originally
their videos were a lot more like their videos are really click bait for what they are.
Like, you know how Jim can't swim is a little bit.
But like, you know, a good in like a cool way.
Yeah.
A little bit, a little bit click baby.
Like what what pretending to be crazy looks like.
That's like honest.
That is what the video is about.
But some of some of the explore with us thumbnails are a bit like, come on, man.
Look at this.
Let me see.
Explore with us.
I just sent a screenshot of the like recent ones.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, these look pretty similar.
They are basically the same thing.
Going to release my Bible.
Okay.
You pick out a really like.
Weird.
Coletious quote.
That one is a very good video.
I really enjoyed that.
Hmm.
Okay.
It's a.
It's a what is it?
It's a 15 year old girl.
Her 19 year old boyfriend.
And they're like 22 year old bipolar autistic friend.
Who murdered someone.
And it go and it like cuts between all the different interrogations in a way.
Where like reveals the information to you at the same time and stuff, even though the.
It's good.
It's well made.
You know what?
That sounds interesting.
The the narrator is not quite as silky smooth as.
Jim.
Jim can't swim one.
Yeah.
I assume his name is Jim.
I don't know.
No, he isn't.
He's a guy that they hired to do the narration.
I think.
If you look in the description of some of the Jim can't swim videos, it has a link to his
channel.
And it's mostly him going like, you know, the Republicans, they really fucked up this
time.
And I'm not.
I.
Oh, okay.
Very good.
Sure.
I'm glad he's getting getting work.
Yeah.
He's good.
He's a good guy.
He seems like it.
Yeah.
And he has videos.
He's got a pretty good voice.
I'm trying to discover what's going on in my life and trying to find myself.
You can see videos of him from like 12 years ago where he sounds exactly the same except
higher pitch.
You're making him sound like Kermit the Frog.
Yeah.
I always turn into that with really specific voices like that.
I always turn into Kermit the Frog.
Oh, I'm sorry.
George Lucas as well.
All right.
I might watch these.
But the explore with us guys.
Hello.
Welcome to our video.
This is one of those ones.
Is he more YouTuber?
Yeah.
He's definitely more tuberous.
She was stabbed and murdered.
That's not.
That's not my favorite.
No.
The following footage has been reviewed by a team of psychologists.
Cringe.
It's not too bad.
A team of psychologists gets involved.
And they inform random YouTuber what they think about crazy people.
Yeah.
Anyway, I don't know why I'm addicted to pro crime videos at the moment.
I, I like Jim can swim.
So how do we get on this topic?
I don't know.
We were talking about.
Where are we?
Right now.
And then a historian.
And then that's where the trail goes.
I don't remember anything before that.
Let's see.
Shit.
I don't really have any.
My, my PZP topic notes list was just how annoying and long and hard the work on the book is.
And I already complained about that.
So I was going to say, uh, I'm going to, yeah, I got to catch a train a little bit.
Cause I'm going home for my mom's birthday.
I made her another batch.
I made her another batch of gummy, gummy blocks.
This is a, this is better.
I have refined the recipe more.
This is, these are, these are better than the last ones.
Uh, they smell incredible.
It's been really hard not to eat them.
Have you not tasted one?
I did taste like, uh, I did, uh, eat a few of each like flavor that I made.
They were just really good and I just want to eat more of them.
Okay.
Uh, but I had, I had just, I had to stop.
It's like, no, I don't want to give her like a half empty container.
This is, this is, you've hit the limit.
It's a very nice present.
Something that you made yourself a big smile.
Yeah.
Unless there's shit in which case you fucked up.
I think they're good.
I think, I think they're good.
It would be a shame if like my parents think they're bad and don't actually like them,
but they're too polite to say it.
I don't know.
You know, I could have made, I, I considered, uh, since I know how to etch a glass now,
I could have, uh, oh yeah, I learned how to etch a glass.
With chemicals.
You can't just learn how to do that.
That's what computers do.
Nobody does that.
No, it's easy.
No, it's easy, bro.
They do that in big factories.
That doesn't happen in real life.
I was talking about this cause I, cause I made those, uh, those slime bottles and I etched
into the glass.
I etched the like product of New Los Angeles city, uh, into the slime bottles that I gave
out at RFC Kcon.
I was thinking I could maybe etch, uh, like a glass container or something, but I didn't
really have any appropriate, appropriately sized glass containers to present, uh, these,
this candy.
And so I thought, uh, maybe, maybe next time.
Ben's gummies.
When do you keep all your, your gummy chemicals?
Are they just like in a cupboard?
They're just in a cupboard cause like, I don't really, I, I did get some weird stuff, but
I ended up not using most of it.
I just use.
You got, you got like eggs, bread, milk, monosaccharides.
Yeah.
Well, now I use, uh, it's all I really use is sugar, sugar.
I don't really use the pectin anymore, uh, sugar, corn, fiber, corn syrup.
Actually, actually, no, I ordered a big bucket.
I have a big bucket of corn syrup, 50 pounds.
That's all you need.
Yeah.
Uh, I mean, it's cheaper to buy in bulk.
So, uh, sugar, corn, fiber, uh, corn, corn starch, uh, uh, water.
Uh, uh, citric acid.
And then I have a little box full of like flavors and colors.
And like, that's it.
There we go.
Did I forget, did I forget anything?
Wait a second.
Like, consult my notes.
Consult my master, my master list.
The weirdest thing I've ever known anyone to do is just know, just knows how to make
gummies.
Just household the ingredients anytime.
They're so easy.
It only took me like two years to figure it out.
Oh, gelatin.
Oh, of course gelatin.
You mastered it in two years.
I ran out.
I ran out of a gelatin.
I feel like I just bought like a big box of like 500 sheets.
I got the platinum.
I got the platinum sheets this time.
Oh, very nice.
The difference between platinum and like other grades, basically that's the highest grade.
The difference is basically just like one sheet, one sheet of platinum gelatin has as much
solidifying, gelling power as one sheet of, you know, gold or silver or bronze or whatever.
It's just, I think the other ones are like less pure.
Right.
And so there's like, there's more impurities in them.
It's condensed gelatin power, basically.
Yeah.
But like, it actually, it actually ends up that buying the platinum is like more, it's
like less expensive because like, because there's less impurities, it weighs less.
So you get more in the box that costs like, the box costs a little more, but you get more
sheets and therefore you get more gelling power and it's actually more cost effective to buy
the better stuff.
Right.
In addition to being pure and better.
And yummy.
So, so, but I'm out.
I ran out of, use the last of it, making this.
You need more platinum gelatin, my friend.
You need more platinum 240 bloom, baby.
Platinum.
Genatin sounds like a good band name.
Platinum gelatin does.
Damn.
That is good.
I've always had rules.
Do you have any band names in your head that I don't play musical instruments, but I have
like a band name in my head that if I ever through some circumstance needed to name a band,
I've always got one on the standby.
Do you have one of those?
I don't.
What's yours?
Radical gasket.
Come on.
That's perfect.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
It's pretty fucking perfect.
Would it be like a sounds like maybe a punk band or something?
Yeah.
Maybe also alternative rock, you know, anything, whatever.
Sure.
Yeah.
I am completely non musical in any way.
So I don't know why I came up with that.
Well, I guess mine is platinum gelatin now because I really like that.
Yeah.
It's good.
That rules.
That could be the name of like an outro song to an anime.
I can really easily see that.
I use the last of my, uh, my 600 sheets.
I made this, I made the stuff, you know, for my mom's birthday present and I had a little
bit left over and I was like, well, okay, I'll just use the last of it.
And I use the last of it.
And I decided, okay, well, I also have a little bit of cola flavor emulsion.
So I'll use the last of my cola flavor emulsion to flavor the last batch.
And I forgot that I hate the cola flavor emulsion.
It sucks.
It tastes bad.
So I just threw it out.
I wasted it.
But at least I, but at least I got rid of that bottle.
That goddamn emulsion.
God damn emulsion.
Just taking up, taking up so much space and it's little like one ounce bottle.
I'm finally free of it.
You need to start like a community in Boston of gummy makers.
Oh, wait, wait.
You know what?
That's great news though.
Gummy making convention.
They had, they had discontinued the worm molds, like the specific worm molds that I like.
They only had shitty ones that like were shaped weird for some reason.
And I don't know why they would make them stupid and bad like that.
But they did.
But now guess what?
They're back in stock.
They're back, baby.
We're back, baby.
They're back in stock and I'm debating, oh, should I, should I just buy like 10 of them?
Like, so I'll never run out.
Probably probably need to.
The fact that they came back once probably means that they would come back again.
If they get discontinued, maybe I'd buy like one more, one more set.
Oh, there's like the perfect gummy worm shape.
These are the perfect gummy worm shape.
They're, you know, they're, they're S curve.
They got that nice S curve.
What, do they get like worn out and stop working or something when you need to replace them?
I just want, I just wanted more.
I just wanted to be able to make more at once.
You were to make an absurd amount of gummies.
Wait, here.
Compare that, compare that to this garbage.
I mean, you could get this, which is like a good, a good shape.
Like this is a good shape, but it comes with all this bullshit.
Oh yeah.
Who the fuck wants to make gummy dolphins?
Gummy dolphins and starfish.
Oh, the gummy octopus is kind of cute.
Oh, the octopus, like whatever.
I eat the gummy octopus.
They're wormy.
Yeah, I mean, so that's all fine and whatever, but like just please, I'm here for the worms obviously.
I'm here for the worms.
We're ruining our gummy worm.
Please stop wasting my time.
And then this is the other ones you can get that are just worms look like this.
And I mean, I feel like this speaks for itself.
Yeah, no, not right.
They have heads, that's so stupid.
Those are gummy sperms, those are different.
What's going on with like the uneven curve?
I know.
Why do they like bend all, they have like a big like S-curve at the back and why?
And a really straight neck.
It's so weird.
I hate it.
Gummy snakes or sperms, those aren't gummy worms.
Frankly, frankly, these are no worms at all.
I can't stand it.
So I'm glad to see the good old modern gummy, 20 cavity candy kit back in stock.
Finally available.
Finally, finally, I might buy another one just as a treat.
Another set of two.
I treated myself to a Lego set recently just to have on my desk and you're treating yourself to gummy building.
I mean, I mean, I mean, same same same idea.
I think a little while ago, I was feeling kind of down.
And I think it was partially because I hadn't made any gummies in a while.
Like I I think I had like sort of been like just working on the book and not doing anything outside of that.
And I think I was just like, and then I don't know, you got to have you got to have a hobby.
You do.
So I think I, yeah, I don't know.
It brings me a small amount of joy in this dark, fucked up world.
Yeah, I've been playing a lot of multiverses recently because big product.
It's the Warner Brothers Smash Brothers fighting game thingy.
Have you not seen this?
No, it's a it's a big free to play.
Like Smash Brothers style game we can play as all the Warner Brothers characters.
My main is our Finn the human and Wonder Woman.
Finn the human is a Warner Brothers.
Yeah, because he's Carti Network and that's owned by Warner Brothers.
Oh, I didn't know that.
It's a it's good.
It's a really good little free fighting game.
And it's a it's going massive at the moment.
Have you not seen this?
No, I have.
Well, maybe maybe I did, but I didn't pay much attention.
Yeah, didn't like Nickelodeon make a like Smash like that?
Yes, they did, but it's been sort of killed now.
Oh, no one cares.
We added voice acting to that.
And that's good.
But the problem is that game just doesn't play great.
It's cool for what it is, you know, it's just like it's good, but it's not great.
Whereas multiverses feels really, really good.
Hmm.
And it's got lots of pretty solid lots of cool people in it.
And it's not just like Carti Network stuff.
There's tons of dog shit.
Hang on.
Let me send the Ross.
Multiverses.
I guess.
Yeah.
No, I think maybe I did see this somewhere.
I like playing as Finn, Jake and Wonder Woman.
Tasmanian devil versus Superman.
Sure.
Why not?
It's a it's really fun.
They recently added LeBron James.
Yeah.
Cool.
You shouldn't be surprised, but there's dog shit like that in it.
I don't know.
Shaggy.
Okay.
We got Shaggy, of course.
Shaggy is.
Do you remember there was memes of Shaggy if he was a Dragon Ball character?
Ultra.
I remember Ultra Instinct Shaggy.
Does he go Ultra Instinct?
Yeah.
He like powers up and starts glowing and stuff in multiverses.
That's I guess.
I guess that's kind of funny.
I guess.
I guess that's a little late.
Yeah.
Rick and Morty are being added soon, I think.
You can act out Scoob and Shag.
You can.
Because Bugs Bunny and Shaggy are both here.
And those are the only two characters in Scoob and Shaggy.
Arya Stark from Game of Thrones.
Really?
Yeah.
Voiced by the girl who played her in the TV show.
Oh, so like there's a lot that aren't on this image, I guess.
Oh, no.
She's there.
She's there on that image.
Wait, where?
Next to Velma.
Oh, like my eyes completely glossed over.
Yeah.
Arya Stark.
This is so fucking weird.
It is really weird.
But okay.
Who is Rain Dog?
I've never seen that one.
They seem to have like original characters that they're adding.
Just to fill out the roster of like.
Okay.
He's like a support thing where like if you get knocked off the stage,
he can pull you back in and things like that.
Hmm.
Oh, fine.
It feels like we need marketable dog type character for game.
It feels a little like that.
I feel like.
I don't know.
There's.
There's relatively few properties represented on this roster.
To be fair.
And some of them have multiple characters from them.
Yeah.
It's only an open beta at the moment.
Oh, okay.
It's not like the full release.
And I think they've said that they're going to keep adding characters as long as they can.
You know.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure Gandalf is datamined.
Okay.
I think Gandalf and Neo are definitely coming.
Oh my God.
Mad Max was leaked.
But I don't think.
I don't think that'll go through.
Something about.
I heard some rumors of Ben 10.
I hope Ben 10 gets in.
That'd be cool.
How recently did this game go to open beta?
The open beta started on the 26th.
So like a week ago.
Oh, okay.
And I see the there was an early alpha for it.
And then there was an early access to the open beta.
So if you got into the open into the closed alpha,
then you got early access to the beta.
So I played it a few weeks before it came out in open.
But yeah.
But it is really fun.
It looks really strange.
Yeah.
It is.
Who's your main?
Finn.
Finn Human.
Because he's kind of like.
If I was to compare him like a Smash Brothers character,
he's kind of like mass combined with a hero.
He's really weird.
He has like a shop mechanic where you collect gold as you damage people.
And then you can use his down special to buy things from the shop,
like a speed boost, a defense thing.
And then you can buy BMO,
which lets you do like a super attack,
which does tons of damage.
Very cool.
It sounds adorable.
It is great.
And they got all the voice actors for everybody,
apart from LeBron James.
LeBron James is the only person.
He doesn't.
They couldn't get him to voice himself?
No.
He's voiced by the guy who voices Barrett in Final Fantasy VII remake.
Cool.
They got Superman to voice Superman, you know,
the real Superman.
They actually got him, I can't believe it.
Oh, they got the real Clark Kent?
Yeah, they got him.
I don't know where they found him, but they got him.
My favorite thing about the game is that when Tom and Jerry get knocked off the screen,
it plays the scream, the Tom and Jerry scream.
Yeah, yeah.
Which is a...
What does Velma do?
What does Velma do in a battle against Batman?
Did you ever see Phoenix Wright in Marvel vs Capcom?
Not really.
Where he does like attacks where it makes like a speech bubble.
And that like is the hit box.
So like Velma is like sass, deduction and something like that.
And Jinkies it says in like speech bubbles and it hits you and stuff.
I see, I see, I see.
One of her attacks is based on like the little like charge up and run they always do in Scooby-Doo
when they're running away from throwing things.
And she like holds her hands completely straight and then her legs like wheel.
Oh, like Sonic the Hedgehog?
Yeah.
Legs whirlwind, gotcha.
If you like hit someone while they're in that, you like grab them and then throw them off the stage.
That...
Her main mechanic is really weird.
It's like you collect evidence around the stage and then when you collect enough it will summon a police car
and like grab the opponent and reveal that it was Mr. Jenkins all along.
It was old man Jenkins.
Like you pull the enemy, you pull your opponent's mask off?
Yeah, but it doesn't like show you pulling their mask off.
It like just puts them in a police car and then like it shows like a little icon of their character's face
and it flips over and it's old man Jenkins.
I see, I see.
And then it like throws them off the stage in the police car.
That...
That's so funny.
Oh my god.
It sounds pretty fun.
I'm just really...
I'm bad at fighting games though.
Oh, me too.
It's too late.
Yeah.
It's too late for me to get good at them.
I've always said to like fighting games you have to have liked fighting games for the past five years.
It feels, it feels that way.
You know what I mean?
It's impossible to catch up.
Yeah, I'll never do it at this point.
Oh well.
But I mean, I'm very, I'm, I'm you, I'm entertained by what I'm seeing.
Yeah.
I was very surprised by how much I liked playing as Garnet.
I'm not, I don't remember anything about Steven Universe.
I watched like half of it and I've completely forgotten it now.
But she's really good at this in multi-person.
I never finished Steven Universe.
I made it to like almost the end and then I stopped watching like literally like six episodes before the end.
And then I saw the movie, the one with the, with the...
The good drawings.
The clown girl, Harley Quinn.
What's your name?
I don't know.
I know who you're talking about.
Spinel, Spinal.
Oh, okay.
And then I never saw, and I think there was another movie.
I think there was a series afterwards, like a little like epilogue series.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was like a post-timeskip series.
Oh, I never saw the post-timeskip like post-series adventure time movie either.
Oh, there's four of those.
Really?
They're really good.
I like, I like adventure time a lot.
I don't know.
And I never watched, I never watched the movies.
There's four?
What the fuck?
They're hour-long specials and they all focus on like a different character.
The one criticism I have for them is they release them in the wrong order.
The third one definitely should have been the fourth one,
because the third one is the Finn and Jake one.
And that should have been last?
Yeah, that should have been the last one, because of the way it ends.
I don't want to spoil it, but it's pretty good.
Okay, yeah, don't spoil it.
I'll, I'll, I should watch it.
The first one's BMO.
The second one's Marceline and Princess Bubblegarden.
The third one's Finn and Jake.
And then the last one is Peppermint Butler, which should have been like,
come on, that should have been before the Finn and Jake one.
I mean, I don't know how that it ends.
Yeah.
It, it, it makes sense.
I get it.
I get why it's like a little joke.
Yeah.
It's funny.
It's cute.
Yeah, it is for cute.
Yeah.
But those are very good.
And everyone should watch them.
Yeah.
I forgot.
I forgot those existed until right now.
Finn and Jake one in particular might be one of my favorite,
like bits of adventure time.
I think it is just great and perfect.
I started a little while ago.
I did watch, I rewatched some of the beginning of Adventure Time.
And it's good.
And people say that it just makes me happy.
Bad.
People say, people say that it gets bad.
And I'll admit there are some underwhelming episodes, but like,
I remember even watching like late stage Adventure Time and knowing
that like it had a reputation that like, oh, it kind of,
it kind of gets bad.
It goes off the deep end.
It gets like up its own ass with its lore.
Yeah.
It's boring.
But I remember watching Ladder Day Adventure Time and knowing that.
People say that, but being like, nah, I'm entertained anyway.
I'm having a great time and it rules.
What I appreciate is they like commit to that lore.
Like they still reference things like that.
Like especially in the, in that last episode thingy that I was talking about,
they reference the fact that Finn is a reincarnated Comet and has like
tons of past lives and shit like that.
And all that weird shit that they came up with.
And, but they do it in like a cute little like nod way.
Like, yeah, it's kind of weird.
He accepts it because he's Finn.
So, you know, he doesn't give a shit.
The, the, um, they really, they really just,
they really just committed to all that weird shit and they ran with them.
They treated it completely seriously.
And I respect it.
I don't love the final villain of the actual series of Adventure Time
where it's just like some God guy that you see in one episode like earlier
that someone summons and is bad.
And I was like, that's kind of weird.
Wait, I don't even, I don't even remember.
It was a big red guy that, um, the bad bubblegum man summons or something.
I think it's called Grodd.
Oh.
Yeah, the one, oh God.
Yeah, it's called Gold.
The one that he sees like when he dies.
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, he's like a, some kind of force in nature or something.
Yeah, it's just like an Eldritch God thing, but I think that's, you know,
I either set it up a bit more or just make it a little bit more interesting.
I don't know.
Well, he's mysterious.
Yeah, I suppose so.
Uh, the, the, uh, fuck, I was going to say something about, um,
Early Adventure Time?
I do think it gets a little too invested in the sort of like, sometimes when it was
really going deep on like the, oh, there's a recurring cycle of fire and ice and candy
and slime and, and we will, we will, we will explore the like reincarnated versions of
these concepts over and over again.
Sometimes I thought like they could just left some of that out and it would have been fine.
I didn't really need like, oh, who was the previous, who was the previous ice person?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Where did the crown come from?
I mean, whatever.
I just assumed it was, you know, an evil crown.
Oh, an evil.
Oh, okay.
Now I know it was an evil crown that was made, made by a guy.
Made by an ice guy that was programmed to imprint his brain onto it or something.
And it turns anyone into him, into a crazy version of him.
I'm glad, I'm glad that I know that it was not just an evil crown.
That makes you a crazy ice man.
It's an evil crown with some other guy's personality.
That's like, that changes, changes everything.
Sure.
It's a bit, what does that, what does that remind me of a bit of like, I'm gonna, I'm
gonna explain this shit to you even if it really requires no further explanation.
The Master Sword in Zelda has that.
Yeah.
In Skyward Sword, that whole game is about explaining where the Master Sword came from and who's
in it.
Oh, maybe that is.
Yeah.
Maybe that is what I'm thinking of.
A fucking, it's got that like AI lady.
Yeah.
That's the first example that comes into my mind.
I didn't play Skyward Sword, but I know what you're talking about.
And that is a good example of like, did we really need the Master Sword need a backstory?
I mean, it's, it's worse in that case because they made a whole game.
Yeah.
And like, that's the kind of like, story of a whole game that you spend.
This is just like, there's a, there's a couple extraneous episodes in like a 75 episode show
or however many it is.
They're doing that with Dragon Ball a lot lately where they're like, oh, we need to show more
and more of Goku's dad.
It's like, he doesn't matter.
He doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Like if in one piece they did like an entire like flashback arc about Luffy's mom, like
no, I don't really, you know, I don't need that.
I haven't been, I haven't not been keeping up with one piece.
I assumed not.
I've been seeing a lot.
I feel like I've been seeing more one piece discussion.
Yeah.
On online than usual lately.
I see it.
I see it come up and people are talking about what happened in the latest chapter and maybe
I should, I don't know, kind of makes me want to maybe stay current so I can know what people
are talking about.
It's because the one walk is like over now, basically.
Yeah.
I think that everyone's like excited to see what comes next.
The discussions come up because there's lots of like hints at what's happening in the outside
world at the moment.
So there's a lot of stuff to talk about that.
That is, that is interesting.
Yeah.
Okay, I should catch up on that.
Maybe I'll catch up with it on the train.
Oh yeah, that's a good idea.
Actually, I probably won't have enough time on the train, but it's okay.
You can get like halfway there.
Yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
Some things are good.
Some media properties can be good sometimes.
Yeah.
Adventure time, really good.
I do love adventure time.
It makes me smile.
Overall, I would have to say it's really good.
I really like that stupid mini series with Finn's mom.
I don't know why I like that one a lot.
The one with like the islands with the humans on it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That series had a good tone.
I didn't want to watch any of Pendleton Ward's other shows.
No.
There's like that space one.
And then there's the space one, and there's the one on Netflix,
which is like a drug trip thing.
The space one about four guys in space or whatever.
Who look like adventure time guys.
Yeah.
And they have like a cute mascot.
I heard there was a new...
Yeah, I think I heard about the Netflix one.
I haven't seen it.
I don't even know what it looks like.
My friend really hates it, but it's definitely not his thing.
So I bet I would really love it.
Hmm.
Is it called Midnight Gospel?
That's the one.
Okay.
I saw one episode of that and I hated it.
I've heard it's good.
I've heard people tell me that it's good.
I think it's a Marmite situation where you love it or you hate it.
I think it's the...
I saw one episode of it and I thought it sucked.
But I don't know.
That's exactly what my friend said.
I've always been curious.
I might give it a go and see.
I...
No, don't.
I think...
I swear I tried to go into it with an open mind.
Okay.
Something about the premise of it...
irritates me.
And then...
But I was like...
I'm gonna...
But I've heard it's good.
So I swear I'm good.
I'm not gonna hold it against it.
I'm gonna just see what it has to offer me.
And I did not like what was served.
It's like he talks to people about stuff
and then they animate like a fantastical magical mystery space world
over that.
Right.
I don't know.
That blows.
I hate that.
I don't get what's cool about that at all.
What if you do the drug?
It make it entertaining.
I...
That better not be the argument for it.
The only...
I don't know.
The only thing that I think...
I mean...
I would want like does the world that it takes place
and does it have lore?
But like they're not talking about that stuff.
They're not talking about like some like fantasy world lore.
They're talking about like real shit in the real world.
So why is it set in a magical like drug trip space land?
Ben, it's a beautiful juxtaposition.
Don't you understand?
Is it?
Yes.
I mean, maybe.
No, I don't know.
Maybe, maybe.
Well, my initial impressions have been poor.
You can tell.
That reminds me of like how all the gorilla songs are just like about like living in L.A.
and being an artist.
And then like all the music videos is just like weird wacky like alien shit happening.
You know what?
That's fair.
Yeah.
I mean, some of them are about kind of abstract things.
That's true.
Yeah.
What is...
I just like...
What is Clint Eastwood about?
Yeah, that's true.
What's the one with the windmills?
Feel Good Ink.
What's Feel Good Ink about?
Corporate, uh...
Corporate.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the vibe I get.
Yeah.
Forced happiness, I don't know.
Uh, I haven't really, you know, I'm not like a...
I've listened to a bunch of gorillas.
I don't know all their songs.
Are a lot of their songs about being an artist living in L.A.?
Yeah, a lot of their more recent stuff have been about like...
To me, they've come off as just about the experience of being a musician and things like that.
Or...
Yeah.
And then there's the occasional abstract one where it's just nonsense.
They all sound really good.
Got to write what you know.
You got to have something to draw on to like what am I going to make a song about?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Interesting.
I still like gorillas a lot.
They did a whole album which was very clearly just a big criticism of the state of America.
Oh.
And that kind of thing.
Recently?
It was the 2017 one, I think it was.
Humans.
Which is good about like...
Thing bad.
This shit bad, yo.
Maybe there's...
Maybe once in a while, Midnight Gospel might sort of stumble into a conversation about some real world thing
that like thematically really matches and resonates with some sort of like trippy imagery that they animated for it.
I mean, I guess I could see that happen.
It obviously doesn't happen all the time.
Yeah.
But maybe there are some bangers.
I don't know.
Yeah, whatever.
Whatever.
Pendle some war.
Do what you want.
I don't give a shit.
I don't give a watch.
I actually didn't know he was involved in that one.
That's the only other thing that I know he's worked on.
Aside from that Space One, which I think was like a YouTube series.
I did not know that he had anything to do with that, actually.
I knew it was that guy, Alex Hirsch, was the guy who's like voice it is.
Ah.
And I thought it was maybe that guy Moynihan.
I know Moynihan is one of like the designers and animators on Adventure Time.
I can tell that Moynihan had like a hand in the art style on Midnight Gospel.
What does Pendleton Ward do?
Now.
On that.
What's.
Hmm.
I got to find out.
I mean, nobody writes for it.
Co-created.
What the fuck does that mean?
Co-created with a guy called Duncan Trussell.
Oh, wait.
Duncan Trussell.
That's the...
Wait, shit.
That's who I meant to say when I said Alex Hirsch.
So who the fuck is Alex Hirsch?
Maybe he's not involved.
Alex Hirsch is the Gravity Falls guy, and I didn't think he was involved with it.
Oh, yeah.
I was looking at his Wikipedia.
No, Duncan Trussell is the guy whose voice it is.
Yeah.
I saw Alex Hirsch tweeting out all the notes that he got from Disney when he was making
Gravity Falls, which was very funny.
Yeah, I saw some of that.
That was a good little insight into how fucking horrible this shit is.
Hmm.
They're just...
I don't remember...
Do you remember any details?
It was like, we're going to kick your butt, and it was like a note saying like, this phrase
is too similar to the phrase kick your ass, and we would prefer if they said something
else.
It was like really like minor shit like that.
They would change, and then of course...
You alluded to a swear word.
You didn't say a swear word, but it almost suggests one, and please...
And Alex Hirsch's response every time was just like, you're a fucking idiot.
Hmm.
Fascinating.
Yeah.
God, I would never want to work in television.
Yeah, I see he's created by Pendleton Ward and Duncan Tressel, so I assume that means
Pendleton Ward.
He made some phone calls to make it happen.
He's like, let's make a thing.
He met Duncan Tressel, was like, hey, Pendleton Ward, great to finally meet you.
I have a podcast, and I'd really like to make a cartoon about it, and Pendleton Ward was
like, yeah, okay, let me call...
Is that what it is?
Is it like a cartoon of a podcast?
Let me call Moynihan, and he'll do some sketches for you, and then we...
Okay, all right, I'll see you.
Okay, bye.
Yeah, it's...
The one that I saw was he was interviewing a...
What do you call it?
Not an undertaker.
A taxidermist, but like...
What do you call it when you do like a human taxidermy?
When you prepare a body for a funeral?
A mummification.
No.
I know what you mean, but I don't know the word.
Embarming?
Wait, no, that's part of mummification.
That's part of it.
Sorry, I've got mummies on the brain.
Okay, what...
Hang on.
What do you call someone who works at a funeral home?
Mortician.
Yes, mortician, that is the word, yes.
Anyway, he was interviewing a mortician, and...
I don't know, she was just describing fucking...
What you do as a mortician, and what it means to be a mortician,
and what her experiences at a mortician are like,
and some of the cultural history of...
I think she was going into civil war era funeral practices,
historical things that have been considered normal at certain times
that we would consider bizarre today, etc.
It's fine.
It's okay, I guess.
It's fine, but I just don't care.
But why was it animated as they're going through some sort of space maze
with monsters chasing them?
I don't know.
I didn't understand what the point of it was.
Hang on, here's the good Gravity Falls one.
Do you remember those two gay cops in Gravity Falls?
They would get notes every time they were next to each other and stuff.
Please revise the action of Blubbs putting his arm around Durland
as noted in previous concerns that their affectionate relationship
should remain comical versus flirtatious.
Ah!
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
No gayo.
There's the one of the...
This is not S&P approved, where it had some writing on a poster that they made them change,
and then they kept changing it and changing it and changing it,
and they kept refusing it every time,
and then they just put not S&P approved on the poster,
and then S&P replied,
not S&P approved has been approved.
Wait.
This bit is not standard and practices approved on the poster.
Oh, standard and practices.
So it was a poster on the wall?
Yeah, it was a poster on the wall.
Camera would have said originally, but they were made to change it,
and they changed it to something else,
and they wouldn't let them use that either,
so they just kept changing it,
and then eventually you just put not S&P approved on it,
and then there's the classic message,
not S&P approved has been approved by S&P.
I see.
Because they got away with that one.
I wonder if I can...
Can I Google image search the...
Yeah, if you just...
It's a party invitation.
Not S&P approved,
so photos better end up online.
Yeah, okay.
I can't remember what the original thing said.
It's in that video that you put out.
Yeah, that's what I want to know,
is like what...
They must have been some sort of
suggestion of saucy party activities.
It was Spin the Bottle.
Really? They can't mention Spin the Bottle?
It said Spin the Bottle and punch
at party or whatever.
And then they were like,
Spin the Bottle is alluding to kissing,
which is sexual, you can't put that in.
I think I...
You know what?
I think I have to vote Republican now.
I think cancel culture has gone too far,
and this is the fucking line.
This is the line that breaks me.
Yeah, but they wanted the cops to be gay then.
Which side are you on?
Ooh.
Wait, oh shit.
Damn it, should I hate them for being cops,
or should I love them and unconditionally
approve of everything they do because they're gay?
Ah, it's too...
Fucking Alex, her. She's a genius.
He's twisting our minds.
True.
You know what? I never finished
Gravity Falls either.
I watched a bunch of it.
I think...
It's one of the best. It's one of the best ones.
Well, there was a long hiatus,
and I never picked it up after the hiatus.
That's true.
Like, in between
Episode 10 of Season 2 and the rest,
I think it was.
Yeah, sounds about right.
I think I saw like two seasons of it.
But it was a...
Damn, it's the last 10 episodes.
Those are great.
The finale is the best episode.
It ends perfectly. It's great.
Yeah.
I think I maybe should have finished it.
Maybe I will at some point.
It's one of those...
It's like up there with Avatar,
in terms of just being like,
oh, it's planned out from the start.
It's only 40 episodes.
It's...
Damn.
It's exactly what it needs to be, you know?
I hope they never touch it again.
Don't fucking touch Gravity Falls.
Leave it as it was.
That's so funny.
That's so funny,
because it really doesn't look like that kind of show at all.
No.
It looks like...
It looks like something that would go on forever, you know?
Yeah.
And be like a...
Oh, it's SpongeBob.
Oh, they're at summer camp.
They work at a shop.
Yeah.
Crazy things happen.
It's a setup that could theoretically be stretched out
for Eternity.
Yeah.
It has a really good story and characters,
and a cool villain and things.
I like the episode with the mini-golf,
where they show the rich bitch girl
what's going on.
I did see that one.
There's a bit where the big buff golf ball
is carrying it through the poison gas
my new toys,
and they don't address it.
He just straight up does sacrifice himself
to get the ball to the end of the course.
Well,
gotta do.
I don't know how that got passed
standard of practices,
but spin the bottle didn't.
Did he do Owl House or something?
Did he do the other show?
Yeah, I think he did Owl House or the frog one.
Yeah, those are two that I'm aware of,
and I haven't seen.
Those are two of that genre of show.
Owl House and Amphibia are two
Gravity Falls likes,
and one, I guess, is about birds,
and the other is about frogs,
and that's all I know about them.
Okay, I don't think Amphibia has anything
to do with Amphibia.
Okay.
I think I saw a clip of them referencing
Gravity Falls in Amphibia,
and that's what I'm thinking of.
Okay, whatever.
There's like Owl House,
Infinity Train,
and Amphibia.
Oh, Infinity Train.
Didn't that get canceled?
Yeah, I think so.
There's all those shows that I lump together
in my mind and get them confused constantly.
And I feel bad about it.
Yeah, they're all kind of sort of a...
Happy,
mopey, you know.
I don't know how to describe them.
The sort of Steven Universe.
Yeah.
Like comedy, action,
but with emotions in them.
Emotional little girl's cartoon.
That's it.
I guess Adventure Time is like that, too.
Did Adventure Time just lay the groundwork
for all of these?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
And then Steven Universe refined it
in a way that people really liked,
and then these new ones
have taken up the torch.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I fell off to Steven Universe
right after the human zoo bit, I think.
That's pretty far in, I think.
Yeah.
And I was like,
I don't care anymore.
Isn't...
I mean, when I hear Infinity Train,
I think about that one episode of Adventure Time
that has the Infinity Train in it.
Well, Train Dungeon.
Yeah, that one's good.
Yeah, like that's what I thought
Infinity Train was about.
Is that...
I don't know what Infinity Train is about.
Dungeon Train.
I don't either.
I assume it's that.
Dungeon Train's cool, though.
Yeah.
I like the episode where Finn
falls into a pile of pillows
and lives out his entire life
with pillow people,
falls in love and has kids,
and then he comes back
and he's fine.
Yeah, and he sees Grubb.
Yeah.
He was set up.
That's true.
Oh, yeah.
That is where that one was set up.
You're right.
Yeah.
When he lives out his whole life
and then he dies of old age
in pillow world and his spirit
travels through dimensions past Grubb.
Yeah.
What's the in-between
between Adventure Time
and Steven Universe?
Because those were like a long time.
I would say probably Gravity Falls.
Gravity Falls was like 2012,
or 14 it started,
somewhere in between there.
That sounds about right.
I mean, I know Rebecca Sugar
worked on Adventure Time.
Yeah.
She did a lot of the hard-hitting ones.
And a lot of the ones with like the really good music in them.
Yeah.
Many of the hard-hitting ones were hard-hitting
because of the music,
but not all of them.
Everything I remember from Steven Universe
is the good music bits.
Those are the main things I remember from it.
I will say my main thing on Steven Universe
is it has the,
you know the idea of like a town cast?
Yeah.
The town is populated by wacky weird people
The town is populated by wacky weird characters.
Yeah.
I think Steven Universe
has the worst one of those I've ever seen
because I don't like any of them.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think.
Oh God.
I mean, yeah, there's like
Pizza Family and French Fry Family.
Everybody's favorite.
There's the Roberto guy.
I don't even remember who that is.
He was like the conspiracy theorist fat guy
with the noodle hair.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he's one of the Fry people, but yeah.
Yeah, there's conspiracy theorist guy.
There was the people who worked in the donut shop.
The girl was okay.
The boy was insufferable.
Lars and Sadie?
Yeah, that's them.
I mean, I would consider them a little bit more
than just like town-y side characters.
They kind of have their own little arc going on.
Yeah, they're the best ones.
But they're the best out of those, but I hate that fucking guy.
I hate that Lars guy.
I never saw the Res
I know he gets like a spaceship later.
What?
Yeah, Lars and the Stars.
Oh.
He becomes like the captain of like a renegades
fucking gem spaceship.
Geez.
Yeah.
Oops, spoilers.
Whatever.
Yeah, some runaway gems from Homeworld.
Like he becomes their leader.
Wow.
And I don't think I ever saw how that resolves, actually.
Okay.
Okay, Steven.
Adventure Time started in 2010.
Gravity Falls started in 2012.
And Steamiverse started in 2013.
They are just like all like writing it after each other.
Yeah, okay.
And what do we have now?
What's exciting that's coming out now?
The Owl House and Nymphobia, I guess.
Are those still happening?
I think so.
Or did they end?
Okay.
I feel like, I don't know.
I feel like one of them ended.
But Owl House?
Maybe?
What's that one?
Wait a minute.
What's the one that has the little, I think she's like Hispanic girl.
She's like stone tosses, like banner?
I don't know.
Stone tosses banner?
Yeah.
Or maybe it was someone else.
Is it the Owl House girl?
Because there's a little girl in that.
I don't know.
This one.
Maybe?
Who's a gay?
I know she's a big gay.
Her.
I swear she was like stone tosses banner.
Or maybe someone else.
I don't know.
Was it to make fun of the gays by having a lesbian character as his banner?
I wish I knew.
I wish I knew why.
Maybe it wasn't him.
But it was someone like that.
Okay.
When are we getting a kid's cartoon about gay men?
Done with lesbians, I'm sick of them.
Where's the gay men?
Stone toss, get his own cartoon network for adventure.
True.
Yeah, gay men erasure.
In fact, all men erasure.
There were no men in Steven Universe.
There was a start.
There were only women.
It's a big fact that.
No, they emasculated him.
They made him.
They force feminized him.
Sorry, that's why he had long hair.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
But.
His wife was taller than him.
So yeah, that's true.
What is, what did, what did fucking, his like, his like manager says to him that one time, like, fuck, what's the dad's name?
I have no idea.
I want to say.
It's something.
I mean, he was something universe.
I keep thinking it's, it's Steve.
I know.
The main character.
I keep wanting to say Steven Universe.
Because.
Steven's dad.
I've told you about this.
Greg, Greg Universe.
Okay.
Yeah.
I've told you about the stupid joke my friend has where he only refers to Steven Universe as Jared Universe for some reason.
Right.
No, maybe.
Me and my friend did that for a while.
So I literally just couldn't think of him as Steven Universe for ages.
It's like, it wouldn't look at him and say there's Jared from Jared Universe.
And then my brain went, his dad's called Steven.
Because he's called Jared.
His dad's called Steven.
So I had it like wrong.
That's the next, that's the next generation.
I don't understand.
But that, that his manager tells him like, like Greg, you know, why, why are you so focused?
Like you could have lots of little women, but instead your photo, you're too hyper focused on getting one big woman.
Base.
Absolutely base.
Maybe Steven Universe isn't so bad after all.
It's, it's got some, it's got, it's got some gems.
Yeah.
Get it.
Fucking get it.
True.
That's it.
End of the podcast.
It's time to go.
What do you, what do you think about voicemails?
Uh, no.
You know what?
I respect it.
If you, if you honestly, I wouldn't blame you if you want to leave and not do them and I'll just do them.
I think, I think we might be having dinner soon.
So it might make more sense to just not, me not hanging around because otherwise.
You know, you know what?
That's okay.
What, what would you, what do you even get out of them anyway?
I don't know.
Nothing.
The purpose of voicemails is to abuse me.
Yeah.
Okay.
I feel bad for abandoning you now, but.
No, I don't know.
It's honestly, I'll just, I'll just tear through them.
I'll just tear through them really fast.
Okay.
Everybody hate, the listeners hate the voicemails.
Nobody wins.
So.
Only the people who have submitted voicemails, like voicemails.
I think that's, I think that's true.
Yeah.
And then they go, oh my God, it's me.
My voice.
I hear it.
That's what I do.
That's, I only listened to the PCP episodes I was on.
The PCP.
And I go, oh my God, it was me.
The PCP is like a mirror for your voice.
If you put your voice on it, you can hear yourself instead of seeing yourself.
Wow.
Oblivion Fall is posting memes.
Oh no.
Is he?
He posted one meme.
He's right.
Yeah.
Something about animation.
Whatever.
Something about animation and how it's bad.
I studied animation and I decided I hated it.
Really?
Yeah.
I have a degree in animation.
Did you know that?
You do?
I didn't know that.
That's what I went to university for.
And I decided, yeah, I'm no good at this.
And it's too hard.
Yeah.
Still, still images are actually.
Just the way of the future, man.
Yeah.
I like animated 3D models, but I hate making them.
And I hate drawing animation as well.
I've never done anything with 3D models ever.
It's a, I don't know why I just got it.
I just sort of clicked with me and I was okay at it.
I did a little animation with Homer Simpson opening a box and then slamming it down and
he was pissed off.
And I was like, yeah, there we go.
One time, one time I applied for like a job.
I found out on Craigslist or something it was like an animator job for some furry porn
guy who I think just needed people to animate some like cartoon.
They were not public.
They were like for like, like subscriber only.
Like you had to like be subscribed to his like personal website.
And it was like, here, I'll give you, I'll give you flash puppets and like the application
when I submitted the application, they sent me a like a box.
They sent me a file of flash puppets and they were like, here, here's like a quick scene,
like a very brief little scene.
I take these flash puppets, animate the scene.
And I was like, okay, and I spent like a few days doing it like an idiot.
You know, I didn't know what I was doing.
So of course I was not accepted for the position and he was right not to let me do that, but
I did try it.
You could have made this furries personal NFTs for him.
Who probably who knows this was some this was some guy I'd never heard of sapphire
thing.
I don't know.
I don't even remember anywhere.
I can hear plates chinking and stuff downstairs.
I'm going to have to scram soon.
Well, that's okay.
It has been people trying to come in.
It's been lovely having you on.
Thanks for joining me.
Thanks for having me.
Thanks for filling time.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, have a good snack.
Have a good meal.
I will do.
I will stop recording now.
Good.
These are good things.
All right.
Well, I guess it's just me.
I guess it's just me here on the pro crass natives podcast.
Let's rapid fire.
These fucking voicemails.
I pre downloaded them.
Which I guess was kind of a waste of time since I'm listening to them by myself.
When it's just when it's just PCP members, we can just be logged in to the speak pipe thing and just listen to them in.
In whatever in the in browser.
But it's okay.
I'll post them in the chat just for Eleazar's convenience so I don't have to make a zip file of them later.
All right.
First one is called that face when the world kind of agreed with the Nazis.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
So Ben and Gabe, we're talking about the whole like Anne Frank have white privilege thing where like they're speculating like how did the Nazis treat queer and black people.
And the thing is that it's wack because they did not treat queer black people very well as you might.
That is wack.
You know, in my conf Hitler literally blamed Jews for bringing black people to Germany to destroy the white race.
I see.
Oh, I see.
And also like the Nazis destroyed like some way ahead of its time research into a lot of queer stuff going on in Germany.
I heard that that was the first book burning.
It was like a trans clinic.
And one really talks about that.
You're not taught about that at school, presumably because the Allied powers didn't really want the bad look of agreeing with the Nazis on something.
So they just like shrunk it down to being only about Jews.
Yeah.
That sounds right.
That that squares with everything that I know.
And I mean, yeah, it is it is kind of a bummer, but I mean, you know, an entire country was like composed, maybe not majority, but like largely of people that like pretty much were down with this ideology.
And you know, people haven't changed that much.
So like, yeah, a lot of people, a lot of people felt that way.
And it's just a numerical fact that like a lot of people still do and they probably will for a long, long time, maybe forever.
So that's a great that's that's nice.
Next one is called I can't get no satisfaction.
And you know what?
I just realized I don't actually have to count down to these because no one else is going to have to time these is just me.
Okay, here we go.
Ah.
Yes.
Excellent.
Wait, really?
Who you think you are?
Okay, until you next time.
Sayonara.
But no, that's that's fair.
Okay, next one is called furthermore.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Just got to do the best you can do.
Very, that's that's very big of you.
Very big of you samurai.
Okay, next one is called a song.
No, no, I won't count down.
Here we go.
What?
Wait, I got to listen to it again.
Turn my volume up.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I can't make it out.
Good.
Good one.
Next.
Happy birthday, Ben.
Yeah, thanks very much.
Better safe than sorry, Ben.
Okay.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Shit.
Fuck me, Ben.
You've been going to the toilet a lot during these podcasts.
Has something changed?
Are you and well, maybe you should go doctor and get this checked up.
I pee a lot.
You know what?
I just I drink a lot of fluids to stay hydrated.
I've always I've always peed a lot.
I think so.
I drink a lot of fluids to stay hydrated.
And that's on purpose because I think it will help to prevent kidney problems.
I think I may have been insufficiently hydrating back when I had those kidney issues a couple
years ago.
So to avoid that, you know, if peeing a lot is the price I got to pay, well, well worth
it.
Next one is called life.
Okay.
Here we go.
You know, when life gives you lemons, you make lemonade.
But life didn't give me any sugar.
So I go to life and I ask for some sugar.
And it says, yeah, it's in the mail.
Some sugar home.
And there it is my sugar.
But with an invoice, I go to life and I say, I can't afford this.
So anyway, I'm working for some sugar.
I didn't want for some lemons.
I didn't ask for life.
Life's a bitch.
Then why did you work for her?
You know, if you, if you, you know, if you don't, if you hate your, if you hate your
jobs, if you hate working for life so much, then why don't you just work for someone
else then?
Huh?
It's the free market.
Very drill.
Next one is called sucks that all the cool guests vanished and died in real life.
Yep.
MZ was the latest victim of that epidemic.
So, you know, so tragic.
Taken from us too early.
Three, two, one, go.
Fuck.
Where the fuck is Simzi and Cybert Shelling?
Gamer's Tavern?
What the fuck?
There was, they used to be on like all the, now what lies?
You know what?
I have not asked.
I only, I only asked.
I mean, people, guests are welcome to join whenever they want, but I was just talking
to Simzi for unrelated reasons this morning and I mentioned that I was going to start
the podcast and he was welcome to be on.
So that's why he joined today.
But I just have not reached out to those other guys.
I did a while back, I think I did ask Cybert Shelling if he wanted to be on and he was
like, I can't do it this week.
I'll do it another time.
And I was like, okay.
And then I never asked again.
And I don't know.
I guess I just, I haven't been very proactive about reaching out to guests to be on the
podcast because, and this is going to sound bad.
And I, I'm sorry to say, I almost feel like I'm insulting you, the listener, by saying
this, but I have just not had a lot to talk about.
And I feel like I've been focused on working on some stuff and getting some stuff done.
And I kind of feel like maybe I'll have more to say to guests when I have more stuff that's
been recently put out and maybe some more stuff that's going on, like say the Kickstarter,
for example, or that video that I'm working on.
I don't know if that's irrational.
That might be irrational.
But that's how I'm approaching it.
I just haven't been asking guests very much.
But I mean, hey, if you want someone on, tell them to come on the podcast.
And maybe they will.
They're any, anyone, any, basically anyone who's previously been on is welcome to come
on anytime.
I'm just too stupid.
End of sentence.
Okay.
This one is called, well, it's an Imgur link.
So let's see what's going on there.
Okay.
Ben and Nate, the guy who shows up every fucking episode.
Oh, it's a, oh, because Nate used to be the one that showed up every, every fucking episode
and now it's me.
Well, I was, I was always, there was, you know, there was, you know,
there was a stretch there.
There was a stretch there where I was not on as much, which was, I don't know if, I think
I've mentioned this before.
That was because I had a terrible girlfriend who was like really weird about it and would
like get angry at me if I did things at certain times.
And PCP was something that she would basically hated whenever I did it.
For some reason.
So for a while there, I was not as much on the, other than that though, I think I was
one of the more, one of the more regular people.
Other than Nate, who was genuinely on like basically every episode for the first, or
almost every episode for the first, like probably 200 episodes or something.
Who else was more consistent than me?
I don't think anyone.
But I mean, anyway, point, point taken, I guess.
I mean, I guess you're just right.
I agree with the meme.
Next one is, oh boy, it's another, it's another Son of a Glitch.
Let's fucking go.
My favorite show on the internet, Son of a Glitch.
Welcome to my favorite show on the internet, Son of a Glitch.
Today's glitch is my bag of chips.
My bag of chips is green, but yesterday my bag of chips was orange.
Who is to say that tomorrow my bag of chips might be blue or pink?
This would be much better to animate for, in a midnight gospel style than fucking, oh,
my job is an undertaker.
And in the Civil War, they used to stuff people with straw when they died.
Isn't that weird?
Just, that's what I have to say about that.
Next one is, oh, the next one is called Multiversus is pretty good.
You can beat up Steven Universe.
Alright, posting that.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
I realize I can send many messages at the same time instead of multiple messages.
Yeah, I mean, technically you can do that.
Make myself send something to make it funny.
So one, have you seen all the Lego movies?
Lego movie?
I saw the first one.
Lego movie.
Two, second part.
Batman.
No, just the first one.
It was good.
Lego Batman?
No.
Ninjago?
I think that's it.
They're all top tire animation things.
The first one looks really good.
Also, two, how do you draw?
I have a tablet thing, but it feels so weird comparing to actual paper and pencil.
What do I do?
Yeah.
I used to sketch in a sketchbook.
And then once I got my Wacom bamboo, I just used it all the time.
I just got myself accustomed to the bamboo by using it.
And then when I got a Cintiq, I didn't use the Cintiq for a long time because I was more accustomed to the bamboo.
So I would use the shitty bamboo instead, even though I had this much more sophisticated device.
But then at some point, I was like, I'm just going to start using it, just going to start practicing with it.
And pretty quickly, I was like, OK, this is actually way more convenient.
This is way more good.
So yeah, you just got to learn how to use it.
I mean, there's nothing wrong with drawing on paper.
It's a bit more inconvenient.
You've got to scan it and stuff to post it.
But just get a scanner if you like that sort of thing.
That's totally fine.
Next one is voice.
It's just called voicemail.
All right, here we go.
If you could instantly learn any language, what language would you choose?
I mean, I don't know, my answer is boring.
I'll probably just pick whichever one the most people speak, Cantonese.
I don't care.
I guess maybe Spanish.
I kind of, I speak a little Spanish.
I took it for years and years in high school.
So yeah, I'll probably just pick Cantonese.
More people speak that than Mandarin, right?
Yeah, whatever.
Just whatever lets me communicate with the most people.
I don't care.
Other than that, I have no particular proclivities.
Next one is called redash.
Sorry, that's such a boring answer.
I'm sorry, it's lame.
But that's me.
Next one is called redash.
Yo, Ben, you've been talking a lot about Mega Man and specifically like how many games there are in each sub-series of Mega Man and stuff like that.
And I'm surprised that in all of that, this one thing hasn't come up.
So I'm going to assume you don't know and probably break your heart live on air.
There was a Mega Man Legend 3 that was made almost to completion and then just never released for really dumb corporate reasons.
So I'll have fun with that.
PS, I thrash on your Ben Solo cast.
I thrash upon it.
Get punk perfect.
Pop pop.
Kind of true.
Park Boys is cringe.
Govate piss you.
Cop kiss her.
Kind of.
It is at this point a solo cast.
No, why would you think that I don't know that?
No, I am aware.
I didn't know it because I never played the Legends games before.
But now I played the first one and I was looking into the second one.
And yes, I am aware that there was a 3 that was cancelled way later.
And I was not sure why it was cancelled.
I assumed it was bullshit and apparently indeed it is.
And that's...
Yeah.
Seems terrible.
It seems like really awful and tragic and senseless.
But yes, I am aware and it's a bummer.
I will play 2 and then I will regret and then I will probably be sad that I don't have a
third one to play.
Maybe I'll do that this week if I get the chance.
Good voicemail.
The next one is called a very demanding voicemailer.
Where did I put that?
Here we go.
Okay.
3, 2, 1, go.
Fuck.
No Nate.
No Watch.
No Tom.
No Daboo.
No Watch.
You're gonna be not watching.
No Nate.
No Watch.
A Lot.
No Jesse.
No Watch.
No Munchie.