I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
It went from cold enough that I have to put on pants over my shorts to walk around outside
to it's hot and I need to install my air conditioner soon.
And I don't like that.
Yeah, how does that happen?
The planets flying through space and then all of a sudden it's like completely different.
We're really in like one damn.
It's just like just a little bit closer and suddenly it's much hotter.
And now it's gonna be 80 degrees for the next two weeks or whatever.
Something, air currents, equator, sun rays, blah, that's how it works.
Yeah, you see the sun is a mass of incandescent gas, a gigantic nuclear furnace.
Brilliant, dazzling.
Really fucking fat and should lose some weight.
You ever see, you know, what do they call it when the sun shoots out fucking photons?
Plasma jets and then they get trapped at the north and south pole.
The Aurora Borealis in this part of the country and this time of year.
Yes, at Astro Camp we would show videos about space to children and some of them showed, you know, the sun emitting,
I forget what it's called when the sun gives like a gust of like plasma out into space.
Solar flare?
I don't think it's a-
Coronal mass ejection, CME?
Yeah, I think that's it.
Yeah, not a flare, not a flare.
The mass ejection.
And we would show a video of like a 3D simulation of it like, ooh, the mass ejection is going through space.
Oh, but what's this?
The Earth's magnetic field traps it at the north and south poles.
How majestic.
And sometimes if the counselors are from like a religious school, they would say like,
you see kids, that weird magic thing that just happened, that was probably God.
That was probably God protecting the Earth, the magnetic fields.
Protecting the Earth from the gaze, that's right.
Right, first from the magnetic, first from the coronal mass ejection and then-
Wait, this is great, I'm a genius.
He's protecting Earth from the L, Bs, Ts, Qs and the Cs, M, Es.
All of the letters.
That's great, I'm great.
It's really cool seeing those videos showing like, because I don't think the Earth's been hit directly by a CME since like for about a, maybe not a hundred years or about that much.
I would imagine it's pretty rare.
Yeah, fucked up the Earth's magnetic field enough that like it started a few like fires and like electrical, not even electrical like stuff,
but like if you had like metal, like if you were holding a metal fork, you'd get like a little, little zap from it sort of thing.
Good fuck up computers, pretty bad.
If it happened now, which people think, people are like really worried, it would be like apocalyptic level if that happened,
but like, like, you know, all the electricity grids going out, but honestly, it'd be fine.
Because we have pretty good monitoring on the sun and like, I've looked into it and most places like, yeah, we'd have like a couple days warning.
We could, we'd just have to temporarily shut some, shut some stuff down and we'd be fine sort of deal.
Hmm.
So five whole seconds the internet didn't work the whole way around the world.
And that was it.
And see the YouTube video talking about it already.
All the nukes launch simultaneously.
Yeah, as, as, you know, the classic technology of needing electricity to not shoot the nukes as soon as the electricity fails, off they go.
Cause it's all, it's all linked, it's all hooked up to Facebook now.
You know, it all works on the app.
So it's a, instead of like two keys that like the president and the vice president have to insert in a big like desk and turn in at the same time,
they both just have to open up the app on their, on their, on their dang mobile phones and hit the okay button at the same time.
And it's just screws it all up.
It's a big mistake.
Yeah.
It's both butt dialed at the same time.
Cause they were doing a butt bounce and they had their phones in their pockets as they do.
Like you do.
Yeah.
Classic presidential butt bounce parties.
Those are very normal.
Welcome to the procrastinators podcast.
We're live and we're alive.
And what a time to be alive.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, did you, did any, either of you watch the Eurovision song contest?
No.
I doubt it, but maybe, maybe it's a big thing elsewhere.
I'm not sure.
Not for me.
It's a, if you don't know, it's a contest that held across Europe where each country in Europe and also Australia for some reason puts forth a song,
dance number, and they compete to see who's the best one.
Nice.
And it's often very political.
And for the last like 10 years, the UK has consistently been in like the last few spots during Brexit or just around that time.
We got zero points, which is like, they have like a two tiered points giving system where every country votes.
They give like the judges from each country.
They have like a delegation and they also have the public vote from that country.
And we got zero in one year.
I think it was last year.
No, nothing.
It was crazy, but completely expected because nobody likes us.
But this year, this year, first of all, Russia was banned because of obvious reasons.
And Ukraine got a big voter turnout.
Everyone was voting for Ukraine.
They had a pretty good song as well.
And that won.
But second place was the UK, which is completely insane.
Oh, you got robbed.
You got robbed by those dang Ukrainians just because they had a war or something.
Well, it's funny.
I think the reason we got second place was because we were like helping.
Really?
I think there's definitely politics involved.
Man, it used to be about the music, man.
No, it never was.
It was never about the music.
Well, maybe it was at some point back in peacetime where people just like ABBA came from Eurovision.
That was like Sweden, I think.
They became big.
And that's like, oh, ABBA, you know them?
They're pretty big.
I can't remember any others that came from Eurovision.
I don't remember it always being political, but it's often got a lot of politics in it.
But the English song, Sam Ryder, I think, he had a good song and he was really fun and energetic
and people seemed to enjoy his presence.
And then also politics.
So it was just sort of like, it worked out.
And now I'm a nationalist now.
I love the UK because we won a competition basically.
We got so many points, the number went up so high.
And now I feel proud to have been born in some arbitrary location.
And it feels great.
Finally, something had to do it.
You know who felt proud to be born in a location?
It's that guy who shot all those people on Saturday.
Yeah.
Did you hear about that?
I heard about it.
I haven't looked into it yet.
It's pretty bad.
It's about as bad as it gets.
Guys literally just like black people's existence in America is an act of violence against the white race
and they must die.
And that's it.
Supposedly.
I mean, I don't have this confirmed, but my friend told me about the shooting yesterday,
less than an hour after.
He livestreamed it on Twitch.
Supposedly this is the guy's Twitter account.
I mean, I don't have a source, but would be crazy if true.
No! No!
It's so true that...
What's that image?
Like the big brony in 2012 or whatever.
And there's like the two parts.
One is the nice castle, one is the evil castle.
On the left, it's like become trans on the right.
It's become white supremacist and there's no in between.
It's literally true.
There's no way.
It can't be true.
Ben, being a fence sitter once again, gotta pick one.
It can't.
Gotta pick Ben.
Possibly.
Never.
You look good with big titties, Ben.
That artist knew.
Damn good stuff.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
I might join in.
I might draw the both of you with big old boobas at some point.
No.
Please.
That would be...
That would be harassment, but maybe I like it.
That's harassment.
I think I'm gonna take it though.
Yeah.
It's not like I can do anything about it.
Ben, there's a subway sandwich confirmed.
Domino's Peach Subway Sandwich.
Fucking brands and sexual things combined.
I'm looking at this guy's Twitter banner.
No.
Oh god.
Nice.
Okay.
I'm over it.
All right.
Damn.
We were talking about space earlier.
I don't know if that's...
That was like before the intro, so I don't know if that's staying in or not, but...
Sure.
One of my topics is space related.
I don't remember if I've discussed this on the show before, maybe I have.
Big, funny fucking telescope, the James Webb Space Telescope is pretty cool.
It's the sequel to the Hubble Space Telescope.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
Crazy, crazy fucking piece of engineering.
I read about it on Wikipedia in like 2015 and even back then.
Wait, wait, wait.
Keep talking, but do a Tom Scott voice.
Tom Scott?
I've...
I can't fucking...
No, it's not too bad.
It's pretty close.
I don't know.
It's just this crazy fucking gigantic piece of shit in space that's really cool.
I like it.
Yeah, yeah.
And it started...
I'm in space and this crazy gigantic fucking piece of shit telescope.
It's so cool.
Yeah.
I saw a...
I saw a supercut of like Tom Scott saying like, I'm in blank location.
Yeah.
And it was...
And it was like...
The caption was like, this is like the level progression of a Kirby game.
And it's like, I'm here.
Like, I'm here in the rolling hills of Ireland.
I'm down here in the bowels of the CERN Large Hadron Collider.
I'm about to get shot with a gun.
I'm about to cross a street.
I'm here with John.
Say hi, John.
Yeah, I found it.
Yeah, the Kirby level with John.
Yeah, so we need Tom Scott.
I'm in space.
I'm about to fucking die.
I can't breathe.
But look at this funny fucking camera on this funny telescope.
All right, I'm curious.
This telescope looks like something that I saw...
Was it called again?
The James Webb Space Telescope.
So...
It looks like something I saw being talked about in a Smarter Every Day video.
Yeah.
But it might not be.
It was a...
Look at this honeycomb looking ass.
Destin from Smarter Every Day.
His dad worked on the telescope, which is really, really fucking cool.
Because this telescope's been in development for 20 years,
cost $20 billion or some shit to develop.
When I was reading the Wikipedia page for it in 2015,
when I first learned about it,
I was seeing all this shit about,
have I had to invent entire new camera technology
that was completely different from stuff that we had used before,
and then reinventing it again when they realized they could do it better.
This is the most fucked up looking device I've ever seen.
It has to look that way so that one,
they can fold it up and fit it inside of a rocket
because it's fucking gigantic.
I think the...
Yeah, the thing was like...
The things they need for it to be
is extremely lightweight and portable and compactable.
When you think of science fiction fantasy ships,
they're always a rigid structure.
People in science fiction are like,
well, in the future, you just take off and keep going
and gravity's not even really a big deal.
But in reality, things look so much weirder and more alien.
It's just really expensive to get something out of Earth's gravity well
and into orbit just because it just takes a lot of energy to do that.
Well, this isn't even in orbit.
This is at the Ville Grange point.
I think it's like a million miles away from Earth.
It's orbiting an empty patch of space
where the Earth's gravity and the Sun's gravity cancel out or something.
It's a weird thing,
but that giant metal diamond shape is a sun shield.
I think that's the thing that Destin, from Smarter Every Day,
his dad worked on the sun shield,
which is this huge complicated, unfolding sail that has five layers.
The gaps in between the layers have to be shaped perfectly
so that any radiation that is generated inside
will be directed outwards
so that way the telescope can be cold
because it has to be a couple degrees above absolute zero in order to work.
Because it's an infrared telescope
and if it has any heat, it'll start radiating itself
and it'll create noise.
Makes sense, yeah.
Yeah, so this launched in December.
I was fucking so hyped for it, everything went good,
and they've been setting it up,
unfolding it, unpacking it, aligning the mirrors.
And the first few images have started coming through
and they're fucking so good.
I'm going to post one of them here in a second.
This is actually a comparison
of an older radio telescope compared to this one,
so that's a little comparison video I made this morning.
The resolution on that is...
Dude, that res-
Pretty fucking crazy.
You can put that on the front cover of a video game about space.
Yeah, good.
And the video doesn't even...
When I made that video, I think the video was 1080p,
but I had to zoom the image out to only one third of a size
to even fit on 1080p.
It's very high resolution.
And you can see all these galaxies and stuff.
That's an extreme lens flare.
That's an interesting pattern.
Yeah, it's hexagonal, due to the shape of the mirrors.
That's why there's six.
And then the two smaller spokes are due to the arms holding up the mirror, I think.
Or something like that.
So that was from March.
And then more recently, there was another image I'm posting, a comparison.
It's just crazy how good the fucking camera on this is.
That looks so cool.
We're going to see so much fucking space.
We're going to be able to see galaxies we've never seen before,
because it's infrared.
It can see all the really far away early galaxies that have been redshifted.
It's just going to be really cool.
And I can't wait for them to start doing science with it,
because I'm a big fucking space head and a nerd and a piece of shit.
And I love this stuff.
I guess I didn't really know that about you until fairly recently.
What a nerd.
I'm a big space nerd.
You like large celestial bodies and large women.
Large celestial bodies.
Cool.
Funny voicemails last week.
Oh, with the Celestia, with fucking Ben St.
Yeah, that was great.
Right, yeah.
Perhaps the saga will continue.
Celestia's hot, though.
Phantom horn, I think so.
I agree with Phantom horn.
Phantom horn would be hotter if
he had big fucking tits though, let's be honest.
Sure, I mean, absolutely.
No argument here.
No arguments.
Speaking of large things,
was that image of the black hole that came not so long ago?
Was that from this, or is it from something else?
No, that was from...
I forget what the telescope's called.
The telescope is an amalgamation of the entire Earth being used as a telescope.
So yeah.
That was a picture of the black telescopes.
That was a picture of the black hole at the center of the Milky Way, right?
I feel like a couple years ago, I saw a very similar picture.
Yeah, okay, okay.
So there's two black hole images, the one from a couple years ago
and the one from a few days ago.
The first one I posted is from the Milky Way.
That black hole is about a thousand times smaller
than the one from a few years ago, but it's also a thousand times closer.
So they look about the same size.
I see.
But because it's smaller, the stuff orbiting it is moving way faster
relative to what we're looking at, which is why it looks blurrier.
Hmm.
But yeah.
Those three little things are moving around.
Yeah, those blobs.
That's the accretion disk that everyone's always talking about.
Yeah.
Yeah, and due to the gravitational distortion,
it pretty much always looks like a ring no matter what angle you look at it from,
which is wild.
But yeah, so the way that works is they have a bunch of radio telescopes
all over the world at different locations,
and they basically have all the telescopes look at the same patch at the same time.
As the Earth is like rotating over a period of like maybe six hours.
So basically each telescope across the world kind of traces a line through the sky
as the Earth rotates, and they kind of combine all of that information
to create the final image at the end.
So is that because if you look at a black hole, you'll see nothing?
Because it's a black hole?
Well, the reason they do take the image that way
is to get the resolution required, because it's so far away
that you need a telescope the size of the Earth in order to be able to see it.
Could the James Webb one take a picture like this?
The James Webb, I mean, earlier posted an image of the size of the mirror.
The mirror's not big enough to resolve something like that.
Oh, you mean like all of the telescopes on the surface of the Earth
like making up like together they like create a telescope
sort of that is the same like size as the Earth,
and that's like a big circle now using that?
Yeah, basically.
It is a really good Veritasium video recently that explained it.
This is our B-hole?
B-hole, exactly.
Very mature. Let's try to be serious about this, shall we?
Hmm, this is just like Spore.
You're just like Spore.
We have the greatest game ever made.
I can't believe Ben St was a Spore creation that got out of the machine.
It's fucked up that I did that.
It is fucked up.
What the fuck?
At 10 minutes 30 seconds you can see like each telescope for reasons can only really see like a band of lines on its own,
but when you combine the constructive interference of all those things together,
it like creates the image,
and at 1030 there's like a good visualization of that.
Is it just because like it's so faint that like a single telescope can't pick it up,
or is it that it's too small?
It's that it's like the angular size of it on the sky is like really tiny.
Yeah.
In terms of like how many like degrees and arc milliseconds and shit.
Gotcha.
Space.
Guys, the limit and space is the place.
Oh, yeah.
This is not exactly related, but I can pretend it is.
I saw that movie yesterday.
Everything everywhere all at once.
Oh, yeah.
I guess it was pretty good.
I liked it.
What is that?
I think I've heard one other person mention the word and I was like,
Haha, you saw everything?
Like what do you mean?
How to explain it without, it's about like,
it's about a woman who starts basically she gets in contact with like other versions
of like herself and like her husband from like other universes where like different.
Oh, so it's like home stuff where different possibilities happened.
It's like, it's like every, every different like way that her life could have gone.
All started like home stuck.
Yes, it's just like home stuck.
All right, I'll go.
Whoa, a picture of a black hole.
It's like home stuck.
Yeah.
A big mirror in space.
It's just like home stuck.
Yeah.
I remember.
Oh yeah, I remember.
It's pretty good.
Little green man turns into a big green man.
I've now seen like home stuck, but no, it's the Hulk.
I've now seen two movies this year, which is a lot for me.
So that's pretty good.
I'm proud of you, Ben.
Thanks.
I'm getting cultured.
I'm getting in.
No, wait, three because I also watched a fucking watch that one liberal movie.
Don't look up.
I watched.
Don't look up on things.
That one was all right.
I guess.
Yeah, I see.
It's three movies.
That's crazy.
It never happens.
The last movie I saw was episode five of Better Call Saul season six.
I think you're going to say Star Wars.
No.
It's funny.
Like almost all of my best friends have never seen Star Wars.
Like any of them at all.
Yeah, like just most of the people who become my friends are people who just haven't seen
Star Wars.
And it's just a coincidence, I guess.
When I was a kid, it was pretty ubiquitous.
Like I just saw Star Wars because like someone put it on somewhere.
Oh, yeah.
I basically had no choice.
I couldn't avoid it.
Growing up, everyone had seen Star Wars.
It's just all the friends that I have now haven't.
And I don't know how that happened.
That is odd.
Kai hasn't seen it.
Foras hasn't seen it.
Maid hasn't seen it.
I was never a big, huge fan.
I always thought that was fine.
C.T.O.L. had never seen it.
Wow.
Maybe it's creative people.
Maybe creative people don't see Star Wars.
Maybe there's a connection there.
I was cursed.
I was cursed by having seen Star Wars and I can never make anything good.
That explains it.
Yeah.
Oh.
I only make good things because I work so hard despite having seen Star Wars.
You've got to break through the conditioning.
It would be so much easier if only it had never happened but alas.
Oh, I'm looking at Bitcoin.
Oh, no.
It's fallen.
Well, we know that.
Let it fall forever.
It's doing real bad lately and I think that's pretty funny.
Let all those billions disappear.
Yeah.
Let everyone cry.
It's up.
I mean, it's up a bit from like two days ago but like overall it's way down.
So that's great.
I have like, I think I have like maybe $50 worth of Bitcoin in still in my wallet.
So, oops, whatever.
Whoops.
Yeah.
I guess it'll just stay there and dissolve, boil away like alcohol on a Bunsen burner.
Or alcohol.
And bringing it back in my stomach.
I drank some Everclear the other night and boy, was that a mistake.
What's Everclear?
Everclear is like, it's like pure grain alcohol.
Like nothing to it just entirely like ethanol.
You're just downing.
Yes.
Like 190 proof.
I mixed it really, really thin with seltzer water.
And I just tried sipping it and it's still, I had a terrible hangover the next day.
Why would you do this?
I don't know.
I just had some, I had some for cooking reasons, for candy reasons.
And I was like, what if I drank it?
Well, now I know.
I shouldn't have.
It's less than learned.
Less than learned.
All this talk is making me thirsty.
I'm gonna drink some water.
I'm gonna drink some Everclear.
No, Ben, you instantly forgot your lesson.
So tasty.
Gonna get all drunk like the Simsies friends who called in last episode.
I would hate to make a fool of myself like they did.
Making a voicemail for the progress in his podcast.
I mean, could you imagine?
Dude, terrible.
I would never do that.
All right, so I wrote this down.
Yesterday when I listened to that episode, I wanted to be caught up.
Someone mentioned something about Simsies penis being mentioned on the show or something.
I don't remember exactly what the context was, but I fucking swear.
And I have to confirm with someone else unless I'm hallucinating this memory.
Didn't Simsie post his dick on Twitter at some point?
Huh?
I mean, that's in my recollection.
I fucking swear he did.
I fucking swear I've seen Simsies penis on Twitter.
I have such a clear memory of this.
And if I'm wrong, that's really concerning.
I mean, the only funny one of those happenings I can think of is Mike Mate.
But I don't think it was his penis in the end.
I just remember the penis, the head of the dick was as bald as Simsie's head.
That's what I remember.
Well, maybe it was just Simsie's head.
Maybe you saw Simsie and you thought that that was the penis.
I just saw his dick and I'm like, wow, it looks so much like your face.
I don't know what to say.
It feels like a dream.
It feels like this didn't happen.
But I can't, I remember.
Yeah, I'm fine to think that you hallucinated this.
I swear.
Simsie and Simsie's like, yeah, I posted my dick on Twitter.
I want to see it.
I'm like, sure.
And he sent me a Twitter link.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe hallucinated the whole thing.
I guess everyone attacks Simsie.
I mean, I could message him, but no, I can't do that.
Well, now it's live on the podcast.
Now it's libel.
Yeah.
Wait, I have an image of Simsie that looks like a penis.
Why?
Because it looked funny and I saved it.
God, where is it?
Okay.
There it is.
I cut out his head.
But yeah, he posted that somewhere and I thought, ha, ha, you know.
At least I put that in the corner and keep it there the whole episode.
It looks like, oh, it looks like that when you fight that boss in Lisa the Painful, the
one that's just a sticky, but he's like a big like phallic, like a like pole, like sticking
out of the ground.
He's just huge.
I do not remember everything from Lisa, but that does sound legally familiar.
In like a dream sequence, you fight basically sticky, sticky, sticky's head.
Not his, not the dad.
You fight like either that one of the dad's friends, the one that he thinks has like kidnapped
and molested Lisa, or not Lisa, a buddy, yeah, his like huge head and it's a big spherical
cylindrical round on the top thing and that's, that's why that's right.
Amazing.
I'm downloading the voicemails, by the way, just so you know, I'm working on it.
Nice.
I've had some bullshit to deal with regarding getting to America.
Yeah.
Getting to America COVID thing.
You still have to have, like I said last time, I didn't know exactly, but it was indeed that
I have to like take a video call with a professional who watches me or directs me to use a specific
test, which I have to buy myself and have it sent to me, which I've done.
I have it.
I have to take the test no more than one day before the flight.
And so I had to, I had to book a consultation with the thing.
And then I, that they're going to call me on my phone or whatever.
I don't know how this is going to work.
I think they have a link that so I can do on my, on my computer and I think I have my
webcam, so it should all be fine.
But I had to pay money to do this test and have the consultation have them say, yes,
you took the test correctly.
Now please give us the results that you find on the test, give us a screenshot.
We'll verify it by comparing the screenshot evidence with the fact that you were with
the consultation and then we'll send you a thing that says you are guaranteed, have
taken a test.
And then I have to bring that along with a verify app thing, like an app thing.
I have to download, I need to download an app and then register so that that is verified
so I can just go up to them and say, okay, here's my passport, here's my ticket, here's
my verify app and also here's my fucking other thing and there we go.
And then they say, get on the ground and kill me anyway.
Get on the ground, because you're British, like, wait a minute, you're British, die.
You don't need any more of your kind, America.
We don't serve your kind, yeah.
Why do they have a British accent when they're doing that?
He's a trader.
No.
We don't serve my kind.
He puts a gun to his head.
That sounds like it sucks.
It was, honestly, as long as the video call isn't annoying, it'll be smooth enough.
But the websites, like the British Airways and the government website for the US and
the government website for the UK where I'm like, what do I need to do?
I Google it, I look like, please tell me what to do and they just don't really tell me.
So I had to go to a random YouTube video where a guy is just saying like a human person in
a way I can understand.
You need to book a thing with a third party company.
Obviously in a government website, for some reason they just can't say that.
They just say you need to have proof of this type of a test, no more than one day before
the flight.
They don't tell you, they don't give you any indication that there's like companies for
that.
I didn't know how to do it until I found a guy and he just said, use this service.
And I did.
And I assume because of how complicated it is, I assume that when I get to the airport,
there's going to be like the vast majority of people getting ready to fly are going to
be like blindsided by this because it's so obtuse, like they're going to be like, what?
What do I need?
I didn't know I needed that.
And then there's going to be like a very, very expensive in airport version of the thing
I did where they're going to be grumbling and being paying like a load of money for
this thing.
And then they take the test and then it gets verified and they're like, fucking stupid,
bullshit, COVID.
I hate everything.
And then they're going to be grumbling through the flight.
I feel like that's definitely going to happen.
So hopefully this is the least trouble version of the things that could have happened.
Oh, yeah, that's that's COVID.
Hopefully hopefully COVID goes away soon.
I yeah, you know, I'm looking at the numbers and they're going up and I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
That makes me upset, but I don't know what to do about it.
You got to get the mask gun.
You got to shoot masks onto people's faces when they're not wearing them.
Hold on.
Like a slingshot, like a sling, like you swing it around your head and then you throw it
and it's like the force of its spinning motion and it whaps onto their head and it ties itself
around the back of their head.
And then they're like, oh, I can't breathe and they die.
Other cases in the US are going up, not as dramatic.
They're going up more dramatically in Massachusetts specifically.
I think in New York as well.
That's bad.
Pretty bad.
I mean, is the vaccination rate high?
Yeah.
So it's just just one of those things.
Just one of those things.
Yeah.
The vaccination rate is quite high in Massachusetts.
Well, if the worst-case scenario happens, I mean, the worst-case scenario is I get COVID
before I fly and I can't even see anyone.
But other than that, if I land and then I catch COVID, at least I won't die.
I'm pretty happy to know that I'm just going to have a bit of a sniffle for a while and
that's about it.
Most likely.
I mean, you'll feel bad.
Yeah, it's going to hurt.
It's not unlike a fever, it's not unlike a terrible annoyance, and I'm going to feel
like shit.
But the threat of death being mostly gone, very, very much gone from catching COVID, is
alleviated a lot of fears I would have had.
If I catch it, eh, I'll just try to keep to myself.
And make sure no one else does.
My parents got the second booster.
I want the second booster, but I guess they're not, it's not available to just anyone yet.
So.
Ah.
Oh well.
What can I do?
You just got to boost jump into the hospital and steal it.
Oh.
Okay.
You got to clip through the wall.
I guess I will, then.
Thanks.
No problem.
It's my advice show.
Yeah.
Fucking.
On the topic of that, since I caught it the last time, my voice, I realized yesterday
that my voice is a little bit fucked.
You think?
I can't do high-pitched sounds anymore.
I noticed that when I was sick, I couldn't do the VemSnakes voice while I was on the
PCP for that big reveal episode.
I couldn't do the voice.
And I can do it again, but anything higher than VemSnakes, I can't do anymore.
And it sucks.
I notice sometimes I find myself not able to do a high-pitched noise that I feel like
I used to be able to do.
But I'll try it right now.
I'm doing it.
And now I can do it pretty fine.
That's pretty good.
Oh, that's completely not getting picked up by your mic.
You can't hear.
Oh, I heard the beginning of it.
That's the best I could do.
Oh, that's the best I could do.
And you drowned out.
It must be the noise.
It's probably getting picked up by the microphone.
It's just discord noise filter.
Maybe.
Funny.
This cord is pretty high.
It's discriminatory against people with squeaky voice.
Yes, die.
People discriminatory against TH versus F sounds, apparently, too.
Oh, yeah.
That one was Smailer who called me cute.
How dare they do that?
Did they call you cute at the same time?
This is making fun of your dialect.
My dialect?
I don't know.
It's not because of where I'm from, because people in New Zealand, once or twice, I had
a friend who would make fun of me.
They'd be like, oh, say thick, and I'm like, thick, and I'd say some word of letter F and
I'd say it.
And they'd be like, haha, what the fuck?
You say it wrong.
And I'm like, OK, how do you say it?
And then they make the same sound twice.
And I don't get it.
I know there's a difference between TH and F.
That's like when you sound the same when people try to correct me.
When someone tries to explain how to correctly pronounce Chinese and I literally can't hear
the difference between the two things, because Chinese just has sounds in it that I just
don't recognize as phonemes that a person can make when speaking.
I always felt like the TH is F thing was like a British thing.
If I say 43 instead of 43, I'd say 43.
I guess I do the E thing as well.
I'd leave out the T. 43 quid.
43 quid.
As I understand it, the difference, TH just has slightly more emphasis.
When I pronounce the sound, I kind of push my teeth a little closer together, maybe.
But the end result kind of sounds the same.
I just, TH is more slurred for me, at least.
Thrush.
I feel like it's interchangeable depending on, yeah, I feel like it's interchangeable
depending on how much emphasis I want to use.
If I'm calling someone fat, I'm going to really draw out that F sound and then maybe it sounds
more like a TH, I don't know.
Say thick fighters.
Thick fighters, thick fighters, thick fighters.
I have to deliberately press my teeth together if I'm trying to announce it correctly, but
if I'm just talking normally, I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a fuck about fat.
Yeah, now you're using the PH levels are high.
The PH levels are high, that reminds me of gummy worms and about pectin.
And everything I learned about pectin.
Did I talk last week about that?
You talked about gummies, I don't remember exactly.
You talked about gummies last week.
You talked about...
Did I talk about that YouTube channel, The Modernist Pantry?
No, I don't think so.
Well, I found a YouTube channel that is about...
There's a brand of ingredients you can buy on Amazon.
I see them all the time.
They're kind of expensive, but they're also the only people that sell certain things.
They're called The Modernist Pantry, and they have a YouTube channel that I found a video
on there that's like everything to do with gummies, and they talk about gelatin, they
talk about pectin.
They have other videos that are like specifically going into the details of different kinds
of pectin, and why some need sugar and acid, and others need calcium, and stuff like that.
And it's like this is exactly what I wanted to know.
And these videos are like new.
They were made like a couple months ago.
This information didn't exist online like two years ago when I was like first starting
my gummy journey.
Anyway, I have...
I keep...
Man, I tried to duplicate a recipe.
I made a batch a while ago, and I was like, that recipe came out good.
I'm going to make it again.
And I was like, okay, I'm going to do that exact same thing.
And I made that exact same recipe, and it came out different.
With different consistency.
And I'm so confused sometimes.
Sometimes I just don't know what's going on.
There's so many variables.
You've got to perfectly make the exact same things, the exact...
You've got to have like the room temperature the same.
So many variables, including like how long do I cook it for?
How hot do I let it get?
Like how much do I stir it and stuff?
It's like that.
Those are things that affect.
How toxic is your mind in that day?
How many VTubers have you yelled out to expel the toxins?
It was full of toxicity.
It seeped into my into the finished product.
By the way, I thought of a fun tongue twister.
Okay.
Thick fighters, thoroughfuckers.
I like it. I like it. There's a little new endless war. Yeah. Oops, we made another one.
It's a big boo-boo-boo Maui milkers. It's the branch that is obsessed with like fies
and just for technique. Sex. One is obsessed with fighting with their thighs and the other
one just fucks a lot. Yeah, they're both pure evil. Chaotic evil, sex. In the alignment
chart of like things. Sex is chaotic evil and then education is lawful evil. The opposite
of sex is education. Yeah, okay. What else could go on there? True neutral zoning out
getting high. Why not? I'm never educated. I don't want to be having sex. No. I should
I should I should have stayed in academia. I should have stayed a physics guy. I would
know things now. Now I don't know anything. Now I'm useless. Maybe I could have been on
that space telescope. Maybe I could have been launched into space. Wouldn't that and wouldn't
that be something? I don't know. I don't know. I feel like they say what's the cost-benefit
analysis of throwing Ben St. into space. I could have I could have made that so much
fuel. So much fuel I did. Yeah, I'll waste some fuel. Yeah, I'll waste some fuel for
NASA. What of it? It seems he's in chat right now and blue and four is hounding them. Yeah,
we got we got to know about that. I am on the side of it was a dream. It was a hallucination.
I think it was I think it was wishful thinking. I think it's gaslighting. You're trying to
convince Simzi that he already posted his dick. So he'll say, Oh, well, might as well
post it again. I guess. It's just for temper. It was another one of my friends. I don't
know. Simzi just looks the most like a dick and looks the most like a penis. That's a
compliment. I suppose. Do you think Simzi is a thick fighter or a thorough fucker? Oh,
geez. He's pretty large. So maybe he's a thick fighter. I don't know. And I've never seen him
fuck. So do I know that he'd be thorough? I can only I can only guess.
There you have it, ladies and gentlemen.
That's right.
Hmm. Hey, what else do I do this week? Nothing.
You guys seen that creator clash thing? Oh, I only just heard about it.
But I heard about it yesterday and I saw a video of was it the guy from like epic mealtime punching
ego raptor? Yeah, from Game Grumps, as well as a bunch of other YouTubers who are mostly
I don't care about them. But I dobs organized a fighting match because he wanted to fight
rice gum and rice gum chickened out because of course he would. I don't know who rice
gum is. I've rice gum. Thank God, you don't know. He did a content cop on him. I dobs did.
Okay, he's an annoying guy, but sure. He wanted to make it like an actual event with like boxing
coaches and to train for like months. And when rice gum didn't do it, he was like, OK,
well, I'm looking for other YouTube creators, other people. And then he just organized a
big old thing. And before you know it, there's a bunch of YouTubers gonna fight each other
to the death. And it was funny to see killed live on stream. It was funny to see ego raptor
getting punched. But the more I thought about it, the less surprising it was. I was like,
yeah, this is something he'd do. It does make this makes this makes a lot of sense for everyone
involved, actually. YouTubers boxing has become a thing. So I guess this was inevitable. Yeah,
although I dubs. I dubs really tried hard. I he made a video and I watched that I watched him
where he talks about like the pros and cons of like influencer boxing matches. And like how
things like Jake Paul, like he likes the mystery is the thing you said he likes the mystery of if
you go to see a boxing match, you know that the boxer is a boxer and they're gonna go be good
at boxing is just whether they're gonna win or not. Yeah, Jake Paul is an influencer boxer,
but he's done more than one boxing match. So the mystery is gone. You know that he can box
because he's already done it. And it's like less interesting. So the whole thing with this is
like, all of these weirdos, you have no idea if they even know what if they even know what
they're doing. Yeah. Yeah. And I dubs was I watched I dubs this match. And he was actually very
good. He trained very hard. It was impressive. It was a crazy event. I just, what do you know, huh?
My first reaction is to go and roll my eyes. But like, I guess there's no nothing wrong with it.
Like, why not? Why not box each other? It's fine. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't watch many of the other matches because I didn't know most of the other people.
I think I recognize Keith Apecari as like dad, who is like a character, you know,
Keith Apecari, the the balding like nerd looking guy. No, he does like, he does like a character
where he's like, oh, I'm a nerd and I will and he does like crazy pretfalls. He was on an angry
video game nerd episode where they were smashing through walls and stuff. And he's done some other
things. He's like a nutcase, I feel like, not like a real nutcase, but he could, he could, I feel like
he's dangerous. He's a dangerous guy. He's dangerous. Oh God. He's got he's got a dangerous,
he's got a dangerous aura to him. I want to watch that fight next. It's all finished though.
Yeah. Well, I probably won't watch any. I think that one clip of ego raptor getting punched
was plenty. Yeah, I doubt it's going to get any better than that. I only saw a clip of
iDubbbz with blood running down his face. iDubbbz took it so seriously. It was cool. It was actually
cool. Yeah, I maybe I'll look into it. I when I I enjoyed iDubbbz for a time back in 2016 2017,
but the more like removed we are from that era of YouTube, the more I don't want to look back on it.
I have I have never watched any iDubbbz. I mean, I know who he is more or less.
It was just a very sour time for YouTube.
If I had to like pick a word. Why? Because it was a lot of like
bickering and infighting and yeah, calling each other. I don't know what they called each other
back then cringe. So we still do that. Yeah.
I don't know. They were the kind of creators who were like prominent back then or just
I don't know just kind of unpleasant was is the general vibe, I feel. I mean, I feel like
most people are still around. I feel like iDubbbz is he's not. He's kind of like a like a, I don't
know, chaotic good. I'd fucking alignment shit. Like he's a good guy. And he has done edgy stuff
before. But like, I like him. I think he does. I mean, this event was like all of the proceeds
went to charity, which is a nice thing. And like everybody involved was like volunteered to be part
of it. And they enjoyed the he got like coaches for everyone. He seemed like a really like a serious
like mature like event thing, rather than just like, dude, let's get so fucking cranked up and punch
each other. And it's like a big YouTuber thing. Like it didn't feel like that. Yeah. I mean,
you kind of have to take it seriously. If you're like, planning it, even if even if the idea is
stupid, it's like, well, yeah, sure. But we got to like, if we actually want to make it happen,
we have to treat the concept with seriousness. So I guess, I guess it just
it makes sense that he was the one to organize it if he was the one taking it the most seriously.
Yeah. Yeah. His opponent was like a is like a doctor who boxes and has boxed for 10 years.
And he's like, like a very, very good boxer. So it was not like, I feel like if the rice
gun thing had happened, he would have killed him. Like rice is nothing. And he's like a real
he's a real Weasley type. And he probably wouldn't put any effort into actually training. So if he
did actually, he would have been like, he just knocked him out instantly. I feel like this was
going he went up against someone who was definitely better than him. And he held his own. It was great.
I wish I wish someone I wish someone would beat the shit out of Mr. Girl. That would be really
funny. But I'm also glad that Mr. Girl is too small time to go to something like this. So actually,
that would be bad if that happens. Who the fuck? Who the hell? You know what? Don't worry about it.
You know what? I'm glad you don't know. I'm glad you don't know.
Some fucking some some some some transphobe psychopath who are the dick show people really
like. Well, anyway, what do you think about the PCP boxing match? You want to fight Ben? You want
to fight when I throw down? Yes. Yes. I'll kill you. We'll do the same thing, but we'll use weapons
like in Dark Souls. It'll be an Elden Ring like in the ring. Cyber Shell tweeted he had a genius
idea. Elden Octagon. A creator clash but with guns. Yes, I saw that. That's why I thought like we get
Cyber Shell there. We got all the PCP guests and we'll kill each other. I think I think I think
Simsie might be the biggest guest we've had. He's very tall. I've heard. I don't know if it's
Cyber Shell tall. I have no idea. Cyber Shell is a sonic character. So quite short, I think.
How tall is Simsie again? Like eight foot, like nine, ten. I think he's he's got to be like six.
I think he's I mean, he's over six feet. I think he's like maybe like six six or something. I don't
know. I just six. I feel like I've heard that he's very tall. I don't actually know how tall.
I mean, I mean, I wouldn't be surprised if he was like six around six two or six three.
Yeah, maybe. I'm six one and a half ish. I don't consider myself that tall. But when I go out in
public, everyone's shorter than me and it's just weird. Why do I have to be tall? I mean,
I'm taller than all the women. That sucks. Does it get fucked a little bit?
Hmm. Actually, I'm sorry. Actually, there's a voice actress I'm in contact with who might
be voicing my character and some things and she's six four. So that's pretty cool.
I think you mentioned her. You you mentioned some voice actress for Falia at some point.
Maybe it's the same person. Might be. I mean, this is someone I met more recently.
I had. Wait, hang on. Hold that thought. Falia. Phallic.
Yes, that's how I only just got that. That's how I thought of the name. Wow.
Oh, I can eat it. I need a name. What phallic phallia? Oh, that works. It's
perfect. Five seconds. Oh, God. I just sorry. I just looked at
no, I just looked at the Twitter trending tab and I would know what are you seeing, Ben? What are
you? The buffalo shooting, grooming, replacement theory, white supremacy, Ukraine. Okay, Ukraine
drives back Russian forces. I guess that's not so bad. That's not so bad. That one's all right,
I guess. My Twitter feed is Japanese, so I don't have to worry about anything.
I was I never have a Twitter feed. They'll like if you if you want to go and eat the
slop in the trough, then have a feed, but you don't do want that. No, you don't need it.
You don't need that slop, Ben. I was just clicking through. I was just idly clicking
around artists just now, actually, just in case I found anyone who draws how I want.
And all the ones, they're all Japanese. I can't ask them. They don't speak English.
Some of them might, I guess. Did you really ask her? I don't know how to pronounce her
fucking name. Did you really just say I have a business inquiry and leave it at that?
Well, I said I said send me a DM because I couldn't send them one because their DMs were closed and
you should have waived the budget in front of them. So they're like money, maybe.
Really? You think I should? I mean, I guess I could do. I mean, I don't know. Like,
if I got a tweet saying I have a business inquiry, I'm just going to read that and be like,
you would the fuck? Okay. That's vague and ominous.
Didn't mean to be vague and ominous. I don't know. I just didn't think I should give all the details
right out in public. But yeah, I mean, true. If you mentioned like, I have this much money to
throw around, people might be like, um, um, what about me? Hot? Yeah. That all come busting in.
And I mean, would that be such a bad thing? Some of them might be good. It could happen.
Maybe, maybe. Yeah. Sure.
Uh, yeah, I guess it's worth another try because I didn't get, I didn't get an answer.
Um, yeah. And then you'll be known forever as Ben St. V. Annoying Pestering Man.
Yep. Well, I already am. Can't, can't be worse than what I've, I'm already known for on Twitter,
so only you can only, things can only improve. Okay. Okay. Well, I didn't do anything else this week.
I was going to go to Trader Joe's today, but I don't think I'm going. I don't need anything.
I have been animating a fat fucking pussy, um, this week, and I'm doing it right now
as I am in this podcast, moving lines back and forth.
How could you? I studied the blade. I know how to make a pussy look really fat.
I see. I see. Yeah, because the pen is mightier than the sword, so you studied the blade,
and you threw it out, and then I studied the pen. It was better.
Yeah, basically. Um, I guess I have some, some news that's good. Uh, Kai's top surgery is funded.
Based. Oh, good. Thanks to the, I think I mentioned last time I was on that we would be
able to afford it, and yeah, we did. We have a date scheduled for the surgery. Uh, six, nine,
Lamau. Lamau. Pretty good. Hmm. Um, what's the, what's the Japanese way to say congratulations?
Congratulations. Oh, yeah. Yeah, like an Ava. Hmm. That wasn't a dub. That's just how it was.
It's not itadakimasu. It's not gomennasai. It's ohayou gozaimasu. It's uh, sure. Probably.
It's a fukka. It's kawaii. Yes, yes. All these are ringing a lot of bells in my mind. Uh, got it.
Um, yeah, yeah. Well, that's pretty sick. Uh, good, good luck. It's probably gonna,
it's probably gonna hurt. It's probably gonna hurt a lot. That sucks. But uh, it'll be good,
I suppose. Uh, it'll be good. Pretty excited about that. Yeah. I'm excited. You go to the
top surgery and you have samurais there. He does like the iaii. Slice some right off. Hmm. Honestly.
I know, I know a lot of, I have a lot of people who are like donate the boobs to me and I'm like,
yeah, if only it worked that way. If only. Okay, so you're saying is it, it doesn't work that way?
No, it doesn't. Um, not legally. But if you want it to be criminal, have like illegal tits.
I mean, okay, I'm, I'm assume, if you can't do that, then I'm assuming it wouldn't work.
Because otherwise I feel like people genuinely would do that.
I guarantee it's possible to have a hormone that would just make boob go into overdrive.
Because I've seen it happen. Wow. I've seen it happen. There's a. You've seen it? What,
what have you seen happen? There's a woman who I found her through Twitter. Um, she goes by
Vatheverbeck. She has unbelievable gigantic natural boobage. Um, that just came out of nowhere,
like in her firties. Um, after she had. Vatheverbeck. Yeah, Vatheverbeck. She is a very well-chested
woman. Well-chested? Yes. Oh, I might have seen her. I mean, there's a, I mean, I know there's
a condition called Gigantomastia that makes that happen. Like usually, though, like most stories
I hear about with Vatheverbeck, like when it happens in, um, like, you know, I guess something
just went wrong during puberty or whatever, like they just kept growing and kept growing and kept
growing, so to deal. But like, she had like, like medium titties her whole life. And then
after miscarriage, they just went boom, uh, over. After a miscarriage. Yeah. So I guess something
hormonal must have gotten fucked up and triggered it. Um, so I don't know. It's, it's probably
possible to figure out if, if, if, if it weren't for ethics, uh, that could be figured out for
people. But I don't know, unlikely to happen. It's, yeah. I mean, it's, there's not a lot of
science annoyingly. There's not a lot of science on like that specifically. I've, I've seen the papers.
I've seen many papers because, you know, obviously I'm trying to grow my own. And a lot of it just
doesn't seem like there's enough evidence for, to say too much one way or the other.
It's just sort of like, yeah, some people just, it just happens. And then not a lot,
not a lot of people are really understand it. And the impetus, the, the, the, the, the, what would
you call it? The motivation? What do you call it when it's the, there's a thing to do something?
Is impetus the right word? Maybe. The impetus to like research it and figure it out. Isn't there?
Because it is cosmetic. It's not like medicinal. You don't need to have huge tits. Oh, well,
that's what they'd like you to think. I, I just, if it were, if it were possible to do,
to, to donate the breast tissue to someone else, I don't see why people wouldn't do it.
I mean, I know that it wouldn't, I know that just wouldn't fucking work because it would get rejected
and the body would just. I mean, science could improve, but right now it's not a thing, I don't
think. But, but I mean, they do that with other body parts. They just put it in and it doesn't,
you guess, they do. I mean, I mean, it's just like fat mostly, right? I guess so.
It's the memory glands, I think, is the, the strange part. Like, they need to connect to
something. And I don't know if the technology exists because there's no like, like, why would you
put money into like researching that? There's no technology doesn't exist to like connect
the memory glands of a foreign body onto your own such that they'll like, like the body will
accept it. It could be doable. I just, I don't think anyone would, which is annoying.
But you have memory glands already, so you just have like an extra pair of memory glands on top
of the old memory glands and that would just be. Well, that's the thing. Maybe you'd have to like
scoop out the ones that already exist. It's like weird. Put the bigger ones in.
I mean, they figured the shit out for cows to make them mega. Yeah, it's a lot less scary
and more epic to just take a bunch of funny pills and they'll explode
all on their own. Do they, do they, do they transplant utter material onto cows? No, no,
no with cows, it's just hormones. Oh, yeah. They found the mega milk hormones.
Yeah, but the, I mean, that's, I mean, milk, milk production and, and like
utter size or not. It's the same. I don't know.
Seem there some are related. Probably.
Well, I've learned that we don't know anything. We don't know enough.
Really, they're just, we just need to take all the money, all the money and put it into research
so that we can finally figure this out so that future generations can just say
huge tits please and they can have them. We don't have to worry about like it being impossible.
We need that money for, for border security. No, open them borders and give me some big fat
old titties please. It'll never, it might pass in the house, but it'll never pass the
Senate, the resolution. I'm sorry. The dream dies here. I'll run for prime minister and that'll
be my thing. Tits, that's what I'll say. I'll say tits, I'll say breasts. Tits or GTFO is
your fucking running slogan. The big booby mommy milker party. I mean, why not?
These days, they'll let anyone run. Yes, they will. That's what's called living in
some sort of a system. I know, I can hate it. It's nonsense.
Well, I mean, what do you think about voicemails around this time?
Well, are we too early for those? I have another little thing to say. Oh, sure. Yeah.
So I booted up Shia from, this is an MMO from years ago. Really bad. Shia. S-H-I, S-H-A-I-Y-A.
I've never heard of it. You wouldn't know. It's very obscure, but it was the sort of thing I saw
in the sidebar and it's like, MMO, but for free? You don't have to pay for World of Warcraft
subscription. You could just play this one. I'm like, oh my god, for free? I don't have a credit
card yet. So I played it. This looks like one of those things that you'd see with like, it's like,
if you are over 40 and have a computer, you must play this game.
I don't know what that means. That's an ad I see all the time. And there's a picture of a tree.
It's a picture. What are you looking at? I don't know. I've just seen an ad that says that.
Just on sites that have ads. Oh, yeah. It does look like one of those. I saw
a video of someone who played one of those like, you'll come in two seconds like games.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I mean, the sexy. It turned out it was just like,
it was like a whole just MMO that was just really shitty.
You see the thing? They'd come in two seconds. Yes. I mean, I came, but I didn't come every two
seconds. No, this, I remember that they had the advertising of like, there's the good elf goddess
who's sexy and the evil elf goddess who's also sexy and choose which one you follow.
So difficult. That did entice me when I was 13 or however old I was,
but I actually do remember playing the game a lot and the game was bad and it sucked,
but it was fine and it was good, but it was really bad and worse than World of Warcraft,
but I love it. And so I downloaded it the other day just to, you know,
fill time because I'm a loser. I don't do anything. And I realized that I really miss,
I made a tweet about this, I really miss polygonal, bad graphics with no dynamic lighting and
shadows and like shitty animations and terrible everything, but it's just got the right aesthetic.
I like it. I like being in like completely obviously fake locations that are charmingly
outdated with really blurry bad textures that are like
competent at like presenting a video game experience where you just walk around and you
kill things and you grab loot and yeah, it was good. I love, I love old stuff. I like old good,
new bad and I just really, I really just, I pine for a game that embraces like shit art direction,
well not art direction, but shit art like capabilities, technological capabilities
because it does have art direction. It's actually quite nice, some of the places,
but they just like, you can look into the distance and it's got like fog and you can see
things popping in, but like the hills have like three polygons. It's not smooth at all
and you walk up it like there's no change in your animation, like your feet don't change.
It's very static and there's like shitty particle effects.
No reverse kinematics on the character model's legs?
None, not even one reverse kinematic and it's just like, oh my god, I love that for them.
I see. And I don't know, I was just, I was pining for the fjords, those specific fjords.
I just, I like it and I don't like how every single game ever since like the invention of
fast and easy, no brain cells necessary lighting engine where like shadows and bloom and directional
light and stuff is like commonplace to the point of everything looking exactly the same
and it's soft and it's all the edges are anti-aliased and you can, and it's all like,
like made a play-doh and like it's a Pixar movie, every Pixar movie is exactly the same movie with
exactly the same character designs, exactly the same face and it's all exactly the same.
Where's my edge, where's my alias fucking cube with a shitty texture wrapped around it?
There's, they don't exist anymore. I have to go back. If I want something that looks like shit,
I can't find it anymore. It's not up, it's just unacceptable.
That's my, that's my video game brand.
Their art style for some of their recent movies and people Pixar, Pixar did have like a same
face sort of like approach for a while. Pixar has gotten better about it, but it's just sort of like,
like for a long time the Incredibles was like the only movie where like the humans like
like had like interesting designs and they like only started recently changing that up again.
Um, everyone complained, everyone complained, ew, Cal Arts and that.
Look at this fucking, hang on, sorry.
Oh my god, that boy's so sharp. He looks like he's friends with Genesis Valentine.
Look at this fucking font. The guard isn't even capitalized. It's so good. I love this font.
I mean,
I've had it with these fucking anti-aliasing overlords and their their claw grip on the
video game industry. They've got, they've got away, they've gotten away with too much.
It's, uh, it's very, uh, it's very angular. Important is what it is. It's very crisp.
It's, uh, it's, I mean, it makes me feel, it makes me feel like I'm playing with toys. It's
like it's just a cool epic action figure. Nowadays, I feel like I'm, I don't know, playing with a
shit action figure that's not a toy that's too real. I see, I see like a,
uh, a thing and I don't like it.
Oh, you know what it is? I also see a thing and don't like it.
You know when, like, I maybe don't, but like, there's, uh, I got, sometimes I go on my mobile
phone. I'm like, I want to have a game on here that I want to play. I feel like that's not too
much to ask. So I go on there and I look for something that's like, uh, medieval castle maybe,
some sort of a medieval castle game. I don't know, a tower defense. Maybe it's clash of
clowns even good. I look at it. I look at these sorts of things. They're like, I'll try one.
They're not that good and they're obviously very predatory with their microtransaction stuff,
but aside from all that, the graphics are way too cutesy. They're not edgy. They're not hard.
They don't look like castles. They look like, like duplo for plasticine babies. They're made of,
they're made of breast milk. They're nothing. They're like, if you pick up a little one of
these castles, if they're like a real thing, if they, you 3D print the video game art assets and
you have them, you wouldn't be able to choke on them. They'd be baby safe. They'd be, you wouldn't
be able to cut yourself with them. Where's the toys that if I grab them, it'd hurt and it cut me
and it'll draw blood. That's what I want. I want things that would hurt. I want to feel pain.
I want to feel anything. I don't know how to explain this feeling. I hope somebody in the
audience understands. I know what you mean. I want, I want literal edges on everything that I can slice
myself with. Edgy? Question mark? Edgehog? True. Need more edged weapons. Yeah. Yeah. All right.
It's a strange, it just overwhelmed me as I was playing it. I was like, oh my god,
I love this, but it's objectively unappealing in a lot of ways. Why do I want this? I don't know
why really. My rant is half observed and half off the cuff rambling nonsense, but I just,
yeah, you ever feel that? You ever get a big nostalgia hit and you're like, the good old days,
you just like scream it from the rooftops. You don't even know what you're doing.
You're just like, oh, the good old days. Stamp your fist. Sure. All the time. Ben,
you seem unconvinced. I'm convinced. I feel what you're saying a lot.
For me, okay, so like Age of Empires got this crazy flashy remake. They remade
all the first free games, I think, for Age of Empires.
Like the definitive edition or like a different version? I think it was definitive, wasn't it?
Actually, maybe it's definitive edition. It was like a year or two ago. Oh, 2018. Okay,
I guess more than a couple of years ago. But yeah, like they basically rebuilt the games
from the ground up and they work exactly the same, but the graphics are all shiny and whatever.
And like, I don't mind the graphical changes. I miss like the more pixely graphics of Age of
Empires one. But the thing that upsets me is that they changed for voices. They changed for
voices. They re-recorded them and they sound stupid now. And by stupid, I mean, they don't
sound stupid anymore. In the original Age of Empires one, if you click on a guy and tell
him to walk around, there's this funny fucking voice, but it's like, Rogan, Diploma, Sunks,
Irvine. Yeah, that's exactly it. He says some stupid shit and I love it. But in the new one,
they have like, it sounds like they grab like some guy out of like a magazine for like a hotel
resort. You know, you know, you see like the pictures of the guy like smiling by the pool,
looking at you. And you don't know what ethnicity he is because his skin's like
some weird like middle shade and he's Greek. Is he from Europe? Is he brown? I don't know what's
going on. It just sounds like, like, I don't know. The voices just sound like really friendly. Like,
it's like some infomercial for clean drinking water in Africa. Like, I don't know. It's,
they ruined it. Get these friendly voices away. Bring me back my Rogan. I need that.
Guy. I miss him. You remember the Joe Rogan experience? Rogan? Rogan?
They're asking where the new episode is. I remember chopper. That was my favorite one
from Average Urban Empires 2. When you click on a female villager and you send her to go chop wood,
so she'll say chopper if she's like British. She'll say other things if she's like
Spanish. They think they have like vaguely like true to some of the country's like language,
but not real language. It feels like Simlish almost. But like the Britons, you can always
understand vaguely what they're saying. Oh my god, I found it. Harbour Darkers. I remember
Habitacus. It's my favorite one. You're talking about, you're talking about Age of Empires, right?
You're talking about Age of Empires. I found the Voicelands. I just love this. I just miss this.
It's cool. It's janky. Duprema? Duprema? You're dying. It's just funny gibberish is good. Oh,
another thing that this conversation reminds me of is like sound effects in video games as well.
Like, so we played the Spyro Reignited trilogy a few years ago when it came out. I played through
most of it because I knew the game really well and Kai wasn't familiar with it, so I helped him with a
lot of sections. And like, the Reignited trilogy is really good. It's really solid. I think they
did a great job for the most part. There's a few things that look weird, but for the most part,
everything looks really great. But one of the things I missed that was common in old video games
that they don't do anymore is spamming the same like super like loud sound effect over and over
where it's like the exact same sound effect, like no change in pitch or whatever. Like,
if an enemy is like shooting a laser going, it's like the same like super just in-your-face sound.
But like in the remake, they'll have like six slightly different sound effects that are all
like not quite as loud. And I'm like, no, bring me back the spamming the same like wave font over
and over. I like that. It's like hard to like legitimately advocate for this sort of stuff.
But because it's like, what do you mean you want less quality? That doesn't make any sense. This
is the future. We can have more than one sound effect because we have more space to do it. You
know, technological limitations no longer a limit. And we can do whatever we want. And it's like,
yeah, but I don't like, I liked it when it sucked. Why is it good? It's hard to be that person,
but it's so true so often. I don't like things when they're good.
I mean, I feel when you had just one really like strong sound effect, but you just spam a bunch
of times, it's really impactful and memorable versus oh cool. Now it like it serves a purpose,
but it doesn't stick in my brain. It doesn't make me go, whoa, it doesn't give me chills like it did
when I was a fucking child, I guess. It's hard to know because you're dealing with
very specific types of memories with nostalgia. And it's like how accurately, how objectively can
you really analyze what you're looking at here? So I tend to just throw like the presumption of
knowing what I'm talking about out of the window and just be like, yeah, I agree that it's an
improvement, but I hate it. And you can't argue with that. Why is it? A lot of these things.
Maybe you could make an argument for some things like, well, it was better before and maybe I
would be right, but I don't know. I mean, there are definitely times where like the old thing is
better when it comes to like Apes Odyssey versus New and Tasty. New and Tasty did
genuinely just fuck up a lot of things. Yeah, it often happens. Yeah. It's not always just like
me liking the crappiness of things because it's charming and it's nice and makes me happy sometimes.
It's hard to talk about like that sort of thing where like
without discounting people's genuine experiences with it as their first version of a thing,
like people may have genuine connection to the later versions of a given product
and then not feel as good when they go to the other version. And in that situation,
you could say that the changes do not significantly impact the experience to a point
where it's so much worse one way or the other. It's just actually just a little different and
it's personal preference and there's not actually that much to talk about. But then it could be
like a legitimately big factor in like the enjoyment level. And if I feel like when
that's the case, it's quite obvious because a lot of people find it to be like worse.
I feel like when there's a large amount of people,
it's more likely that it's like, what am I talking about? I don't know what I'm saying.
I'm not a video game analyzer. I've never done this before.
No, never. Virgin Territory for sure.
The Virgin Territory versus the Chad.
Principality.
Prince. Yes. Region.
You know, one remake that was so terrible for one of my favorite games growing up
and it's getting another remake now, which is good, which actually looks a lot better.
But Clanoa, I fucking love Clanoa. It was like.
I'm vaguely familiar with Clanoa.
Clanoa is a really, really good game.
Is that Sonic Zero?
No.
What is that?
I'll get it. Hold on. Let me.
Oh, no. I'm thinking of that flying around thing.
That's Clanoa with tits. I mean, based, but not what I'm looking for.
Like the thing I was thinking of was the thing made by Sega.
There was like a purple magician flying around.
What's that called?
I know. It's this game.
Yeah.
So Clanoa was a game I grew up with.
The original game holds up really well, but simple graphics and everything still look really good.
They're very, very bright and very colorful.
And it got a remake that just the game ended up looking so much worse,
particularly in terms of like the color space.
There's a comparison somewhere.
I'm sure I can pull it up where you'll be able to like see just where is it?
Oh, yeah.
Okay. Okay. I found a comparison.
So like they increased like the polygons and everything,
but the colors are like super like muted and like washed out now.
Oh, wow. That's the downgrade.
Yeah.
That's that's that's art direction.
Oh, no.
Oh, sad.
So that's like one aspect.
But also the characters used to speak in gibberish
and each character sort of had like their own like gibberish language they spoke,
which was really cool.
And then for the remake, they gave English voice acting and they made
Clanoa who had this like cutesy like sort of high-pitched sort of cute voice.
They made them sound like fucking Sonic the Hedgehog.
Far out.
Grabbing crystals.
The villain.
The villain, Gaudius, who is this really tall, spooky looking bird guy in a cloak.
His voice in the original game is like this super like low-pitched distorted like
kind of like thing that's really cool.
And then in the remake, they made him be like, yes, I am British.
Look at that.
Yeah, they gave him the fucking Leviosa voice and they also made him look fucking stupid.
They fucking ruined his face.
Let me see this.
Oh, I'll show you a comparison.
He looks so terrible.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, I can see that that's like a mental hat now.
They gave him like HD.
Yeah.
The old, they made his eye like completely gone.
What is that?
It looks like a chess piece.
I know.
Like he looks more like a bird like in the original.
Like the front part of his face kind of hooks down like a beak.
And now it's like just a straight shot weird fucking thing.
I don't know.
The Wii remake was bad.
It was awful.
They ruined everything.
But it's getting another remake for the Switch that looks better.
And they're keeping the old voices.
You can still hear like the low fidelity-ness of them.
And it's good.
And I'm glad they're doing that.
And he doesn't look as stupid anymore.
There's something to be said for like, you know, you have a game.
It's on old hardware and the hardware is dying out.
You need to put it on new hardware.
Emulation works most of the time.
Sometimes it's hard.
So like remaking it, future-proofing it for like PC.
It's like, it's a smart thing to do.
It's good for money getting.
But like they always tend to like think, well,
since we're putting it on a thing and we have to remake some of the assets,
why not make them different?
And I feel like when you start doing that, it's very, very dangerous.
You're always, you're likely to ruin things.
I want things to be like preserved in a way that is just the same, usually.
Because like, maybe you could make an improvement here or there.
But like, it's, it's, it worked the first time.
If you make exactly the same, but it just is future-proofed.
That's good.
That can't go wrong.
Who would complain?
Unless you could.
You could.
There's no need for rebirth.
I shall imprison you in darkness and.
And then there's a Switch version, which is like somewhere in between,
but it's better because VI actually looks like it's part of his face again.
He's a very silly looking man.
His voice is fucking cool though.
He speaks distorted, like deep gibberish.
And he says a lot and it's good.
This is pretty good.
It's funny in the first one, their eye looks like it's too far forward.
In a way, like their chin is there and their eye is right above their lip.
Maybe it's, maybe it's just an angle thing, but the last one looks like it makes more sense.
Or at least the camera angle makes it look like it makes more sense.
Yeah, I saw it was like some gripes with it, but they're not as bad as like the middle one.
Oh, fucking, but do you see the problem?
The inherent problem with every three-dimensional thing ever made
post like 1992 or whatever is that there's bloom.
Look at that bloom.
It's bleeding into the, it's bleeding.
I like the flat color of the first one.
That deep black that is like, it's the blackest they could ever possibly be on screen.
No pixels.
The pixels are all gone.
They're turned off and the other one, it's gray because of like light bouncing off it.
I know.
I agree.
It's, it's, it's just, it's nice, you know, I can't complain too much
and it's hard to be like the anti-bloom advocate because like nobody really hates bloom,
except me.
Maybe, maybe, maybe more people hate bloom.
Bloom is fine in moderation, but people just, they just can't fucking help themselves.
It's just that it's-
They have to turn it up to 11 every time.
What annoys me the most is that it's a given.
Like there's no discussion about whether to include bloom for realism purposes
because that's how light works.
You just always have it because it's harder to not have bloom in current game systems.
You can turn it down, you can turn it off, but like I think it's just sort of taken as like
normal that yes, if a game can render anything, it has to have bloom in it and it doesn't.
Yeah, because before you would just have to pick the right color values.
So that they would always look good because the computer is not going to calculate it for you.
You have to like pick, the sky is this shade of blue and it's always going to be this exact
brightness because there's no weird calculations going on.
It just looks at the fucking P and G or whatever and just reads the color value directly from
there and you have to like pick your colors carefully.
Now it's like, oh just get close enough and we have all this lighting and blurring and
shit that's going to change everything and make it too saturated and
bleh. I don't like it.
It's not ideal. I understand that it's like, it's fine.
It works for most things like Mario games. Yeah, yeah, sure. I mean whatever.
I just, I just, I want, I want, I want more people to take an artistic design stance
where they actually make a decision to include it or not,
which is what I'm doing with Pumpkin Alley. There is no bloom in that game, I think.
I will not be, I will design the textures to look a certain way.
They will look that way whether they like it or not.
Like the only time bloom is necessary is for things that are like extremely bright that
would overwhelm the camera sensor. Like if you had like a fucking lighthouse,
you would probably have like a little bit of bloom around like where the light is being
emitted from or if you had like a bright fire, like you'd have some bloom around the fire,
but like pretty subtle and you wouldn't have it like obscuring like half a screen.
In Pumpkin Alley, the fire, I wanted it to, that was one of the first things. I was like,
I don't want it to be like a particle effect. I want it to be like a squishy looking 3D model
of a fire, the warps and wobbles. And then it like, and we made it work. It's like two objects
whippling and wobbling that responds to your movement and then swish left and right. And
it's like, yeah, that's a unique looking fucking thing. Nobody breathes fire like punk.
I still need to find the H Blizzard. Oh my god. You gotta do it. Your gamer crit is on the line.
I still haven't found it. Oh my god. You know, I recently became a gamer and I'm gonna have to
give it all up. I'm gonna have to. Yeah, sorry. You had your chance and you didn't pass. I'm sorry.
Oh no. Yeah, seven out of eight is just not gonna cut it. Our donors, our sponsors won't accept it.
Our sponsors, our donors, who are they? Going back to, you better get back to grinding a smooth
love potions and axes infinity. You get it back on the grind. What is that? You can graduate.
It's like crypto game. It's that crypto game that people from the Philippines were making money at
for a while and then it crashed. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that was on the line go up video. He did
mention it in the line. I've seen it mentioned other places too, but he talked about it. It was
like the most. I can't remember it. That's where I've heard of it. It's little creatures and you
battle them and you make crypto, I don't know. Oh, is it one of those like the player base
can earn money by playing? Yes, it's play to earn, play to earn stuff.
Voluntary indentured servitude. No, it's you make money because you it's like it's raising people
out of poverty. It's like having a job but much worse pay for much longer hours, but it's fun.
So it's fine. It's a video. It's just a video game. They're professional gamers. They go into
the office and they have to just play the video game and they get whipped. They get whipped into
shape with those little things battle. They love it. And then on the taxes, they can write
the occupation gamer like my roommate, Sean. Does your roommate Sean say occupation gamer?
He has like he does like video editing for a let's play channel at EA games. Yeah. And he's
like, I'm a video editor and the tax guy was like, you're a gamer. Just write that down. Really?
That's what I recommend. I always look like a career type as like being in arts and entertainment.
Yeah, something like that. Yeah. Oh, creative freelance work. It's usually
where I go. Creative. I bet you're trying to create new ways to dodge paying your taxes.
Yes, I am crafting the perfect potion to dazzle and confuse the tax man.
They'll come to my door, you know, like they do. They come to the door, say, Texas, please.
And I throw the potion at their feet and the gas goes into their nostrils and they forget all about
it and they leave. And then they I don't have a record of taxes and I still get in trouble.
I have my I have not been I have not been audited yet. Part of a plot of everything
everywhere is that she the ladies getting audited by the tax by the IRS. And it made me very nervous.
It's like, oh man, that doesn't happen to me. I don't have I don't have a good documentation
of anything. I couldn't I couldn't prove like that I bought such and such thing and such and such year.
Jesus. I mean, I don't even like would not like the the purchase history of your Amazon account
or whatever not count. Well, maybe. Yeah, maybe some things I would have an electronic record of.
I definitely don't list enough things. I definitely like undersell myself in terms of like business
expenses. A lot of this stuff is like, I didn't list like specific items, I kind of just like put a
general amount under like things like supplies and like, you know, postage and stuff. And I just
kind of had to like ballpark a number. I didn't really go through and be like, hmm, okay, I bought
this this pack of stamps for sending these letters. And I bought these envelopes. And I bought like
list list items one by one. I do actually do that. I don't write it all down. But I do check
like in a temporary. This is why I'm nervous. This is where I go. This plus this plus this plus
this plus this. And then it's the big money number. I kind of like doing that. I wish I was
chat enough. I wish I was chat enough to like, be like, hey, yeah, so like, all this NSFW art that
I like got off these people's patrons that I pledged to and saved to my reference folder to
reference for my art. That's a business expense, right? I wish I was VAT chat, but I'm not. I'm
a coward. I mean, like, the worry of like, claiming things that are like iffy is that somebody will
come and look at it and be like, um, explain. But like, when will they do that? Why would they do
that? That's like workouts that they had, they would have to spend, they would need a reason to
start doing that.
I just don't take risks. Like the only like things that like I'm certain I can be like
certain about are like, if I'm buying computer parts, because that's literally like, I cannot
do my work without computer parts, that's the only thing I can be like certain of.
Yeah.
Everything else is like, I mean, like it's there's a lot of things that sort of count. And I'm like,
I'm just not kind of, I'll just pay a little more taxes. Fuck it. I don't want to be a sneaky
boy. I think there's a there's a Simpsons episode with taxes where Ned is doing his taxes and he's
like, he has the joke is that he has legitimate excuses for like claiming things on his tax return
or whatever. And he's like, too, like nice. And he's like, Oh, but I can't do that. That would be,
you know, like he's making up reasons why he can't claim anything. And then what Meanwhile,
Homer is like trying to claim that like he has like 17 children and and all these other like
lies. Yeah, if the government asks Bart, you're a veteran, Lisa, you're a you're a nurse,
Maggie, you're a you're a you were wounded in a in a chemical accident. Yeah, stuff like that.
Yeah. It's chemical. So it turned you into a fucking baby on the job on the job worksite
accident. You're on a workman's comp. You returned to a baby by chemicals. Yeah. Sure, whatever.
So watching the Ned Flanders thing, I was like, Okay, I shouldn't be Ned. I certainly
shouldn't be Homer, but at least I know I shouldn't be that frugal, unfrugal. What's the opposite
of I don't know what part it is. A prodig prodigal. Or you're too giveable, you're too generous.
That's in in Dante's Inferno, the two twin the two twin sins in the greed circle of purgatory
are prodigality and parsimony. And parsimony is when you're like miserly, stingy, don't spend
enough money. prodigality is when you are, you know, too free with your money, spend recklessly.
Hence, the Bible story about the prodigal son is the the son that uses his dad's fortune and
goes off and runs off and spends everything and has to come back and be like, I fucked up dad.
I fucked it all. I fucked it all up. I was too poetical. And now I now my soul
burn my soul in hell. My soul will burn on the no, not in hell. No, not in hell. Oh,
prodigality and parsimony are the deadly in heaven. They're not they're not they're not so
bad that you go to hell for them, but they do have to be purged from you on Mount Mount Mount
whatever on your way. Yes, I think that's right. So now you know, now you know some new words.
You're welcome. What what if the Greek gods are like the Boomer gods and the Christian gods are
in there as like we're the new gods now. And the Greek gods are like, yeah, whatever kid.
So they're like, oh, nobody cares about Mount Olympus anymore.
Gods were just the HD remake. I think in I think in in Hades, you have the
there's the the the gun, there's the one gun, the form of the rail gun you have is like Lucifer's
gun. And I think they well, no, they imply that it happened that Lucifer was from the past.
But I mean, I guess that would have been like, pre like Christianity emerging, but like that's
like like the dawn of time or whatever, right? Like the creation of man. So I guess, of course,
that would be in the past. Never mind. That's not a that's not a valid historical record
that I'm citing there. There's no tax return for the beginning of time.
No, I don't think so. You can't audit it.
That's cool. Sure is a cool gun, though. That would be a cool book title. I audited God.
Yeah. And he was sweating. And it's just some sort of a some sort of a tax anime.
Okay, figure it out. That's the premise is the the the prompt for your book.
I'm looking at I'm looking at the Joe Rogan subreddit because I saw boy that this Joe Rogan
subreddit is mad at him because he basically called them all pussies or something for being mad
about Roe v. Wade being overturned. Pretty cool. Classic smooth move. Pretty smooth move, Joe.
They're all going Rogan. Wait, like question mark. How could you
do? Betrayal. Betrayed me.
Habadishery.
Okay. What's going on? What are we talking about?
I think I think that whatever we were saying is over. What do we think about voicemails?
Well, I don't really have a topic. Just a comment. I think I definitely have ADHD and I'm going to
look into going to a doctor and saying, can you just say that I have it? Can you just say it?
And then they'll say it maybe. What makes you think that?
Um, it's just been on my mind. A lot of things line up by watching some videos. I'm like, yep,
yep, yep. That's all true. That's all exactly the case. And it wasn't like YouTubers talking about
it. It was like they're like, um, well, it was a YouTube video, but it was like a psychologist
talking about ADHD and the things, the way you feel and why you end up feeling this way and how
it affects your self-esteem. And, you know, all these things are like, I feel these are normal,
or at least normal to me. And they say they're specifically ADHD related and they talk about
the frontal lobe. And I'm like, that seems sort of credible. I at least want to look into it a
little more because it's been on my mind for a while. I probably just do have it. I don't know
what will change if I know, but at least I won't be lying if I say I do have it.
I've seen ADHD Twitter make long threads about like the memory issues that come with ADHD.
Like in very, very precisely, lining up with issues I have with memory,
where like Kai will come out to the living room, have a whole conversation with me about like
what we're doing for dinner or going to the store or something. And I'll like respond to everything.
And then later, like, I don't remember the conversation and I have no recollection of it.
But like he and my roommates will be able to corroborate that it happened and I just don't
fucking have any memory of it because at the time I was like animating or something and
I guess somehow on autopilot, I managed to do a conversation without
remembering. And this sort of thing happens a lot. It happens way too fucking frequently and
it's scary, but a lot of people on ADHD Twitter were like describing similar experiences they had
and like that that's like part of it. And so I don't know. I mean, I don't have a diagnosis.
Sometimes when I am on a big ADHD moment, I think this people send me pictures of their penis
and they didn't do it. Oh my god. It's all coming together. This was the video. It's like Dr.
Tracy Marks Three Ways ADHD Makes You Think About Yourself. And I was like, oh, very,
very exactly the same as me. Self-esteem. I have good self-esteem though.
Yeah. Yeah. One, you rub it in. Oh, yeah. Rub my penis in. I'll do that too.
That's sexual harassment. That's too far. Jail time. No one, no one. Damn.
Voices. No, no, no, no. You're going to jail. It's a playground voice. I'm a cop. I'm a cop.
I'm a big old cop. I'm a cop. I'm a cop. And you go into jail. It's my favorite.
My favorite donkey. That is my favorite.
voicemail, voicemail. Yeah, voicemail, voicemail, voicemail, voicemail, voicemail,
trans rights, trans rights. What? What about them? Yeah, what about trans wrongs?
Nothing. Two trans wrongs makes a trans right. Oh. So as long as I keep making mistakes.
All right. Trans right angle triangle. Whenever you make a mistake, just do it again. Just do
the second time. Don't learn. Okay, first one is called PCP recommendations. Three, two, one, go.
Hello, Ben and Gibb and whoever else. I am listening to a lot of the PCP. I'm going back.
I'm listening to all sorts of episodes and you know, I'm just kind of picking them at random.
I'm going to go, I'll go and I'll click on them. Be like, oh, that one looks funny. So I'll click
on it and I'll listen to it. Or sometimes I'll look up a host that I like. I'll be like, oh,
what's an episode that monkey was on? What's an episode that Jeff did motherfucking somebody
else was on? I don't fucking know. I don't know why monkeys the only guy I could think of right now.
Anyway, you guys, you, Ben and Gibb and whomever should just help me shout out
episodes that you remember being good. There's too many of the PCP so I can go and listen to them.
The one where that's what you should do. The one help me
episodes. I prefer old stuff just because I like bigger casts. But
if there's anything in the new era that you remember being good and funny,
oh my God, I'm open to it because I'm still listening to current episodes.
Yeah, please. Okay, my recommendation. I don't remember what it's called, but the one with the
them snakes rap. Oh, that episode I can find our number. Jesse edited it. The image was everyone
as angels in the sky or some shit. Yeah, it sounds familiar. Wasn't there a
like a tier list, not a tier list, but like an image, I think tectonic improv did it?
Of like the top PCP episodes. I mean, I don't know if I would have would share his tastes
entirely, but I neither do I. I can't remember the things that happened. I just remember when
people say, Hey, remember when you said life is a cage and death is the key? And it's like,
Yeah, I guess that was a good line. I forget what one that was in though. I can't remember.
I don't. Yeah, I don't remember which episode was which like at all.
No, everyone quotes life is a cage and death is the key because I put that in
the come zone and people like just on rule 34, people will just quote them any image of my
character. I've not seen that before. I've seen it. I see it around. The Vemsnakes wrap episode,
I'm trying to find it the episode where Vemsnakes actually appeared like as a guest at the very end.
I believe that was episode 151. Isn't it the same one that I drew them snakes and put them in
there? That was the one with the wrap, right? Yeah. Yeah, so that was episode 151 of the PCP was
that one. What's it called? The wrap was a few episodes before that. That was episode 148.
Okay. Ben's Kidney Stone. My favorite episodes of the PCP are mostly,
most of them are in like the first hundred or so. I really liked memes that need to die was good.
I really liked the virginity episode. That was a very funny one. I've really listened to it a
bunch. I've shown that to my friends a bunch as well. I mean, everyone knows for yellow episode.
Is the yellow episode just called yellow? Things we can't get into. Things we can't get into.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And do crazy to think about for years, that was the longest episode.
What's it like three hours? Three hours, 43 minutes. Yeah. Recently, there's been a bunch
that have been longer than that. Yeah. The more the cast contracts, the more the episodes expand.
It's equal and opposite. It seems to mostly happen when there's a guest. Yeah. Like the last four
hour one, nearly five hour one was the last time I was on, then the last four hour one was when Simsie
was on. I guess that's, yeah. I think the, as far as I can remember, the ones where there's loads
of people is the energy level is so high and people like try so hard to get heard over the
cacophony that we all get tired out before we can really go for that long. And that's why they end
so much quicker than just chilling out and relaxed and talking outside the school about
like whatever. It's easier to go on longer when you have space to think and to make pauses in
between your own sentences and breaths. Probably also me only coming on every few weeks recently.
I have more to talk about because I don't come on every week. Yeah. So I tend to drag things out
probably. If I had, if I, if I were not on every week, I would have, you know, I'd have two weeks
worth of nonsense to complain about. There's also no Nate best man whipping everyone to stay on
topic and only talk about one thing so that you exhaust everything you have to say about it and
then the episode's over. Nate's like weird, Nate's weird insistence on like on topic discussion
baffles me to this day. I will never, I've never understood it and I never will.
I can't even remember what it feels like to have Nate on a progress in his podcast.
I've forgotten what our pussy feels like. Next voicemail is called death note fun fact
number one three two one go. Hey everybody, it's me the death note fun fact guy. Here's the death
note fun fact. Did you know that in episode two of death note light is using a PC and L is using
a Mac and that's a fun little Easter egg that shows how opposites they are? No. Yeah, that's the fun
fact. Tune in next week for another death note fun fact. That's a little bit more. That's a little
bit fun. I enjoyed it. I remember death note. Did you watch death note? Death note L using an
Apple and Apple Shinigami's love apples. It's all connected and light and L is eating an orange
in every scene. That's light saying I am eating your computer. Your data is mine. You'll never catch
me. It just means really makes you think and think and think until you can't think no more.
Okay. The next voicemail there's a note that says this dude is just a voicemail character.
Okay. Three, two, one, go. She makes me poop and I make her pee. Why? Because we're flipping
cycles. Finally, a good YouTube video. I'm just smiling because he's having fun. Yeah,
his enthusiasm is infectious. That was a good laugh. Great. Great stuff. Next one is called
Hello. It's short. Three, two, one, go. Do an impression of a former PCP member.
Hey, everybody, it's me, Monkey Jones here. Homie, did you eat all the eat the marshmallows
out of my s'mores, homie? You bitch. What do you think? That was pretty good. Thank you.
That's my Monkey Jones. What do people sound like? My impression of Trixie the Golden Witch is
I like to watch little girls getting fucked. Just say it matter of factly like that with no voice
at all. Just say it over and over again. That was my given impression. Oh, wait, you're still here.
No. Damn it. Wait, what? I can't do an impression of a former PCP member.
We're floundering. Let's go to voicemails. That's Nate. That was, we're floundering.
Hey, Nate. It's Nate. Welcome back. The difference now is that when we flounder,
we just keep floundering. Yeah. The flounder 100% completion rate.
I can do a pretty good mage impression, actually. Yeah. Oh, I get it. You're not talking.
Just, I mean, yeah, you just draw in instead of talking during the podcast. You basically
are the new mage. I kind of am. I'm animating yet somehow make the episodes long. I don't know.
The next one I think is just a text question. It asks, what do you think of the new Mary
Weather logo? And I do not know the Mary Weather logo. I have no opinion about it.
I saw discourse about Mary Weather last night on Twitter randomly and I don't follow Mary
Weather. I think I saw that discourse as well. It was something like they had a comic that was like,
I'm 14 and this is deep, sort of a message to it. It's like, how do you know you exist? Oh my
God, I don't know. And it's an anime girl saying, you know, presenting the idea. Oh, I know the one
you're talking about. It's like, eh, yeah. I mean, sure. In the comic, the guy says, well,
this person's weird, which kind of seems to be the message to me. Look at this weird girl. I don't
know. I don't really get dumb stuff. I don't really get what the point, I don't really get what the
joke is, but like, I don't know. It doesn't seem like there's no way to say that. Wouldn't it be
sexy if a hot anime girl was like having edgy 14 year old brain urizamas? That's probably...
Is that the point? I don't know what the point is. I'm looking at Mary Weather's Twitter. They've
made a follow up to this. They say, clearly I must have made a mistake while writing this because
everyone thinks it's about nihilism. It's just a strange girl talking about consciousness and
the point of view character thinks she's a weirdo. I'm not a nihilist and the girl isn't meant to be
either. All right. Okay. All right. I don't get it though. I think the interpretation I saw is
yeah, sometimes in the subway, you just meet fucking weird people who just talk at you too much
and say weird shit, but what if it was a hot anime woman this time? That seemed to be the
vibe that I... Wouldn't that be crazy? It would. I think it's just the fact that it comes across
totally sincere. I don't even see the punchline if there is one. Yeah. I don't...
If somebody actually thought this, they would draw this comic exactly the same.
Or they would write this comic exactly the same.
I just said there's no real punchline. I don't really know what I'm supposed to take away from it,
so I'm just kind of left shrugging. I don't know. I know. What do I think of the new...
I think you should... Oh, sorry. I was going to say the way you should make it more obvious
is have the guy say, what the fuck? And that'd be the last thing that said,
like, thinking his head. I still wouldn't get it.
Like, there's one little box where he says this girl is weird in his head.
I mean, he says, dot, dot, dot, okay. I mean, that's pretty much like, what the fuck?
But it's not like punchy enough. Gotta have a punch in a punchline.
I don't know if that would fix, would change anything. I don't know. It just has no punchline.
What the comic needs is a punchline, and it doesn't have one.
The punchline is very getting fucked. That's the problem for me.
If she was getting fucked while saying all this stuff, that would be really funny.
Getting groped on the subway by some... What's the word for...
How can you really tell if this person is real roping me? Am I really being groped?
Then it would be like, whole different.
I forget what the Japanese word is for the kind of pervert that gropes women on the subway.
There's a specific word for it. Chikon. Chikon. Yes.
Pikachu.
Is this Chikon really experiencing my supple breasts as he gropes me in the dark subway?
Or is he only a meat puppet?
I feel like that would push it over the edge and to be like, this is absurd.
What the fuck? This girl is crazy. Then it would be a punchline. It would also be
not suitable for work, as they say.
I mean, a lot of Maryweather stuff is a little itchy.
Maybe not on the main account.
I just realized, what we're describing is the character of Uwu Lilia,
C-Toll's, a bimbo character who gains brain cells the more it come she is in contact with.
I see. Gains brain cells? No thanks.
Uwu Lilia.
Yeah, the only way to make her smart is to fill her with coon, Dan Knight.
By the way, about the logo. I mean, I guess the new logo is just a new anime girl,
because I guess he used to use the Internet Explorer girl, but I guess they spun that off
into its own account. Now he made a new girl for Maryweather, and I don't care.
I don't care that that happened.
That's not a logo though. It's just a profile picture of a logo. You can see both of them in
this little video on his Twitter. That's the first one, and then there's a lightning bolt,
and then it turns into this one. There you go.
The logo.
So that's the logo update, those two images.
Oh yeah, that looks like a legit thing.
What does it remind me of? It reminds me of something very specific, and I don't know what it is.
It reminds me of Lion Webtoon. It also has a square speech bubble as its logo.
It's a little like Twitter, I guess. I don't know. I have no opinion about it.
It reminds me of the Sims 4.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
I fucking, there's a fucking giant gash on the other side of my foot, and I just
foot, and I just scratched it by accident.
Oh no, the demon came out.
I don't know how I got there. I just noticed it was very last night.
That was fucking touch sorts.
Sorry, that happened. Or happy for you.
This sword will fucking slice a baby in half.
Next voicemail is called, what is it? It is called, it's a search.
Here, it's this link.
Yu-Gi-Oh card.
Is it like a Yu-Gi-Oh card database?
Uh-huh. I'm going to search whatever it is.
Is there not a thing to go with it?
No result. No relevant data found. Ben, you're irrelevant.
To Yu-Gi-Oh? True.
The next one is a YouTube link with no elaboration, so I won't acknowledge it.
The next one is called, Bridge Burning Diatribe.
Oh, I can't wait.
It's a minute long. This should be good.
You're just not, you're just not looking hard enough.
Ben-Sane, no.
No.
I will forever douse my bridges in water. You'll never burn them. They'll be soaked.
All right, let's give this a lesson. Three, two, one, go.
During episode 312, in reference to Econ, Ben-Sane said,
I'm not burning this bridge. He's burning the bridge by making me annoyed,
which makes me wonder, how do you treat relationships in general?
Friends should be able to accidentally annoy friends without that turning the relationship
permanently hostile and salt in any attempts to make amends and working towards any middle ground.
For my parasocial relationship of consuming your content, I don't think you
go through most friendships in that way, so I don't know what's different about this case.
Is there some weird behind-the-scenes stuff we're missing?
But if there isn't, it really seems like you're burning a bridge.
You didn't seem open to reconciliation. A colleague just annoyed you and you
responded aggressively and started shit-talking them on the podcast,
after they tried making things up in the end.
You are an idiot.
At least bridge burning stuff does happen like this.
It isn't out of nowhere for no reason deciding to just unperson someone.
It's you to one or both parties being hard-headed and aggressive over some minor issue that crops up.
You are such a cringy lord. You are such a hand-ringing.
That's like sticking to their guns over their association, which ends up ending a friendship.
I feel like I know that you talked about this on the podcast, but this comes across as like,
I want to say this is none of your business, like what?
So scoldy.
So tell me what to do with my- Econ does nothing but annoy me, okay?
It's not that he annoyed me one time. It's that he does nothing but annoy me.
Yeah, I guess that's the simplest it is.
And I don't like it.
Yeah.
It's just the way this guy is approaching this.
Like I'm trying to psychoanalyze you.
Could you please like give me some more information?
Like that's annoying in itself.
Why does it matter to you?
Just seems like Ben is so irrational.
Just seems like Ben just cuts people off for absolutely no reason,
even though he explains that he doesn't do that.
Even though the whole point of what Ben said was that he doesn't do that.
Like I just kind of think that's what he's doing.
What's the deal?
Like a normal thing to do.
It definitely seems that way.
It's just to assume that, yes, there's information that you're missing
and why would you just ask about it?
That's just, I don't know, strange.
The perception is that Ben blows up at people and then when they're like,
wow, Ben, I'm done with your shit.
They're like, ah, see you burned it, even though I attacked you.
That's the perception of how it comes across.
But I don't know enough about the situations,
because I only like half pay attention to this shit when it goes on.
I don't know what shit they say to you.
I can appreciate that it might look like that,
but like the whole point of what I was saying last episode
or whatever episode it was in was that I don't blow up for no reason.
I do it for a reason.
I do it after I have been pushed to the brink.
Yeah.
The one time you definitely burned a bridge was with,
what's it even called, the fucking,
oh god, Team Fortress 2, Brony Analysis Anarchy.
TF2 Analysis Anarchy.
Yeah, yeah.
That's, I mean, that was the one.
It was still really a bridge.
It was just sort of like.
Wait, that was what?
That was so long ago.
I remember there being a section about that,
I think was it in a horseshoe finale or something,
where you told them to get fucked and it was epic.
I don't know if it was in a horseshoe finale.
I don't know.
It was so weird.
I just really didn't like those people.
They just were so, I remember I got pissed at them
and then like Josh Scorcher called me on Skype
and tried to like talk shit out with me.
And he was like so condescending.
And I was like, this guy sucks.
Like why do I even want to work things out?
I don't care that like he's like, I don't know,
relative to me or whatever he was like popular.
He had a bigger following.
Like I just, I don't like him.
I don't like Dr. Wolf.
I don't, I don't like this community.
I don't like their attitude.
I don't care that I got mad and upset them.
Like good.
Was it the Frog Fractions thing?
We did talk about it.
That was like additional.
There was definitely a Jesse video where
Jesse summarized like how he wall broke away from MLP.
And I swear, I swear it was horseshoe.
Was it in one of the footwear reviews
or whatever they were called?
The horseshoe reviews?
I mean, maybe like it.
Was it the time you did the moment with Dr. Horseshoes?
It was after.
Yeah, yeah.
It was around then because that was after
things had broken down between me and those other guys.
And I think it was like a parody we did later.
We got that same guy to animate it.
That was great.
I vaguely recall like, I know the people were in
like the Brony Analysis Skype group because,
you know, that was just the hip hopping place to be
for that sort of stuff.
But everyone left because it was sucked.
And I was in there still.
And I think you were in there for a bit.
And Nate was in there for a bit.
Jesse was in there for a bit.
Rift Cafe.
Yeah, that's what it was.
God, but like, did it happen in there?
Do you remember if you like had a like a,
all right, fuck everyone.
And then you left.
I think I made, you know, I think I made a post
on like a, I think I made like a YouTube comment
on one of the videos in the series,
on one of the TF2 analysis anarchists,
it's basically complaining about how weird it is
that like the plot of the, of the, of the series is
about Josh Scorcher and Ink Rose falling in love
when Josh Scorcher is like 26 and Ink Rose is like 16.
Yeah.
And I think that was what like,
finally it was like the last straw and they were like,
we want to, we don't like you,
but also we want to like talk to you and like,
and we haven't had Josh Scorcher be like,
hey buddy, like what's, what's, what's going,
what's going, what's going on with you, man?
Like, why are you, why are you burning this bridge?
Why are you burning this bridge, man?
Why are you being so, why are you being so irrational, huh?
Why, what are you going to just cut us out of it
as friends because we're just annoyed you just one time?
That's so weird.
Why would you do that?
It doesn't make any sense.
You only really happens.
I mean, those people do mostly suck.
So it's, it's fine.
I think so.
In hindsight, I don't, yeah.
It's, it's being, being away from that is good actually.
Yeah.
In my opinion.
I think that was my sense at the time
and I feel like it is born fruit.
I have been vindicated.
Is this from Horseshoe finale?
Yeah, that is from Horseshoe finale.
Yeah.
That's, that's why I forgot about that.
That's where I heard about it.
I mean, obviously it's very vague, but uh.
I think I, I was already kind of,
I was already kind of on the outs with them because,
and this is funny, I would argue with a guy called Brony Buck
who just was a homophobe.
Oh, fuck that guy.
I know that.
Brony Buck just was like a homophobe
and I would get pissed at him about it
and I would argue and people would get mad at me
for being like mean, for being argumentative.
That's, that's definitely the whole thing in the Rift Cafe
was somebody has a terrible shitty opinion
and somebody gets mad and people get mad.
But getting, but getting mad is the crime.
But getting, getting into an argument is such a heinous crime.
We're Bronies, we have to love and tolerate each other.
We can't tolerate, we can't fight.
Love and tolerate this bigot, please.
It's just like they, they couldn't look beyond the fact
that there was a disagreement happening.
And so they, they just started shaking and shitting
and crying and coming.
That, that was, that was what like led to my relationship
with that group souring.
And then the, the final straw I think was me
leaving that comment about like the age gap
with the Incros and Jeff.
And I was not the first person to point that out.
Other people were talking about it,
but I, I echoed the sentiment in the, in the comments.
Well, we're offended.
We're a sour pus and we don't like sours here.
I was being a big, I was being a big sour pus.
That's not all cops of that much for sure.
Really souring this bridge.
Now it doesn't taste very good.
You know, I mixed some gummies yesterday and I put,
and they came out really sour and I don't know why
because I didn't even add any, any acid.
All the acid that I added to them was from the Shergel.
And yet they came out sour anyway.
And I was like, so confused.
Was it good?
What the fuck was going?
No, it was a little too sour.
It was a little sourer than I wanted.
And I was baffled.
Maybe something went off.
I don't know.
All right.
I knew, I knew, I knew this would go back to gummies.
As soon as I said sour pus, I, I planned for it.
He fell right into my lap.
That was a good, that was a good fun trip down memory lane.
Next one is called, what is a GNU slash Linux?
Right there.
Wait, it's loading.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
In episode 306, Skip described Linux as a pair down version of Windows,
which is just really wrong.
Linux is its own thing created from scratch.
That's been like a public community project for decades.
Fundamentally, it's a bit more similar to macOS,
but it's different enough to pretty much be considered its own thing.
That's why you need to target it separately for games and shit.
I don't remember saying it was Windows.
I maybe used it as a, like likened it to Windows, but without like,
well, that's the way my brother, because my brother knows how to do Linux stuff.
And he explained it as, imagine if Windows wasn't like,
it didn't take an hour to load everything.
I mean, I mean, it is similar to Windows in that it is an operating system.
Yeah.
I mean, we don't have Mac, so that's how he described it.
It is similar to Windows.
I'm sorry to have made a technical error.
Yeah.
It's similar to Windows in that like, people who,
like the sort of crowd who uses Linux is more similar to like,
the crowds of people who do coding shit on Windows.
Like they're similar, like demographics.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know the code in the back.
It's just sort of like, Linux is for nerds.
Yeah.
And Windows is for people.
It's for the real tech heads.
And Windows is for nerds in training, and Mac is for different.
It's for normies.
Mac is for normies or like, artists who are like,
not technically minded, I guess.
Yeah.
Macs are good for music.
I think I've learned that at some point.
I have like, I've heard that.
I have never.
I've heard people who've switched to Mac who've said it's good.
And I'm like,
The only Macs I ever used were like the iMacs at my school,
like computer lab in high school.
Windows is starting to get so bad,
but I might have to consider another operating system in a few years.
Because I really don't like the look of Windows 11,
but Windows 10 isn't going to be supported forever.
I mean, I use a, yeah, I use like,
I think I use Windows 10,
but with like a shell that makes it look like Windows 7.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I like the look of Windows 10.
I'm just worried about the security updates eventually running out,
and then it being a security risk for me to keep using it after a certain point.
Yeah, that's, that's fair.
That's more forward thinking than I am.
Yeah.
My friends who switched to it,
I mean, aside from the tracking shit being even more annoying to disable,
it's also just slow.
It's just slow and buggy and bad is what I hear.
How do you make an,
how do you just make it worse?
I don't understand.
You hire people to do a job,
and then they just have to do something.
So I fuck it up for, for a while.
They just add code that fucks it up.
Good for them.
Glad I'm glad they're working.
Or YouTube's new like video description layout looking fucking terrible.
The views and the date and the first line of the description are all next to each other,
and it just fucks up my brain.
I can't see the date anymore.
Whenever I try to see when a video, a YouTube video was posted,
I find myself like, I can't find it.
The date is there, it's next to the view count,
and the same bold font with not enough,
with no like real differentiator between them.
You can see it on the screen.
Am I seeing an old thing then?
My YouTube has not changed recently.
Yeah, it updates for different people at different times.
It depends on when your cookies decide they want to refresh.
Mine changed like two days ago,
and I'm so fucking mad.
I can't fucking read anything.
And I don't even have dyslexia,
and this is like fucking up my eyeballs,
trying to like find the date, find the view count.
It's so hard now.
It was perfectly fine.
Why did they do this?
Yeah, I'm looking at this Brony screenshot,
and I don't know, mine doesn't look like that.
Yeah, it will soon.
No.
Oh, is that so?
It goes views, date, description, immediately.
No differentiation, no blinds.
It's ugly.
And also the button to click on the channel
is now at the bottom of the description.
So if you open the description,
I'll take a screenshot on this episode of the PCP.
The channel icon's at the bottom by the comments.
It's weird.
And also the font is different.
Like the font for the title of the video
is also different and harder to read.
I don't, I don't get it.
I could imagine it's for mobile stuff,
like you're scrolling down past the description.
I'm not.
By the way, would you like to subscribe?
I'm not on a fucking mobile phone.
Well, get with the program.
There's never ever going to be a desktop anymore.
It's all going to be in the palm of your hand.
Shorts, you can't rewind or like, you know,
find your way, click to a middle of a video.
You can only play.
It is no way to rewind or anything.
It's annoying.
Shorts are kind of unbearable to like use it,
like with the user interface.
I click on one, I'm like, oh, it moves.
It's clicked onto the next one in like the algorithm queue.
So I go back and then just replays the new one
that I was just trying to get away from.
And then I try to go back further than that.
And it's just, I just, I have to turn off the whole thing.
I close the entire tab out of frustration.
I can't believe how annoying YouTube shorts are on desktop.
I don't know why I would watch them on desktop.
I don't think I've ever clicked on a short and I never will.
They just sometimes appear where it's like, here's a video.
Here's a video.
Here's a YouTube short.
Click on this one.
And I sometimes do.
I know.
And then you're locked into like the shorts.
And then like, I try to like scroll.
And then it's like, oh, you're locked vertical.
And there's just a vertical strip of videos with all this empty space.
That part of it, the scrolling is so, because it's like they have the short
playing and then like underneath it is the short that's coming up.
And if you scroll, you skip to the second one.
I usually scroll when I click on a video to see the comments to see the description,
but there is none for YouTube shorts.
And simply by scrolling, the next video starts playing and the audio disappears.
And it's like, fuck off.
You're ruining my day.
It's like, what if we did it bad?
That's YouTube.
That's YouTube in a nutshell.
What if we did it bad?
You know, we had like a good like six years where like,
like the only complaints about YouTube were about like internal stuff.
So like the UI and layout was fine.
Because we remember like background like 2010 to 2014,
YouTube would update their layout every like year or two and everyone would be mad.
Like they kept it pretty good for a while and now they're fucking it again.
Yeah, they got to pay people to do nothing.
Did you see, okay, I'm sorry to change the subject, but I remembered something.
Did you see by any chance the latest stupid Peter Coffin take on Twitter?
Do you know who that is?
I don't follow it.
Peter Coffin walks out of his grave.
Get it back in there.
Peter, all right.
I won't explain who he is, but the point is he made a tweet about like,
he was like annoyed that people were like,
somebody wore a fursuit to like a pro unionized Starbucks thing.
Yes, I saw that.
And he's like, he said it was unserious.
And like, I mean, look, look, look at this.
Look at this guy.
A real, a real serious academic rooted in materialist dialectical theory.
What does he, what does he, what?
That's a, that's a good Papa Smurf beard, actually.
It's a very blue beard.
Sure.
Yeah, it looks all right.
It looks all right if that's what he's going for.
Is he's going for the Papa Smurf American?
Anyway, just, just, just scrolled by that and remembered that it gave me a chuckle.
A chuckle and a heckle.
The next one.
Okay.
Next one.
I posted it up a little while ago.
It's called Michael Jackson trans race.
Three, two, one, go.
In episode 307, you guys were talking about transracialism and ended up saying that like
Michael Jackson is transracial or maybe an example of being transracial,
which as far as I can tell, isn't true.
It seems like he just had a skin condition which turned parts of his skin white,
which was initially covering up with gloves and shit.
But eventually it got so bad that he decided to just bleach his entire body so that it
would all have a uniform color instead of having some blotches everywhere.
So it wasn't really done out of a change in racial identity,
but because of the skin condition.
Well, sounds like you, sounds like you know more about it than I do.
I know all about Ben's skin condition.
What does that mean?
My skin, I'm turning, I'm turning black.
Joe Biden sucked out, he said, you ain't black if you don't vote for me.
And he sucked out all the blackness from people and then he's giving it to me slowly.
Just to you.
We worked, we worked out a deal.
Yeah.
The next one is, okay, the next one is will the Switch 2 come soon and then the Nintendo
and then Switch 2 and then that's what I'm talking about.
I hope it does.
I'm hyped for it.
I don't know.
No, why would they make a Switch 2?
Everybody loves the Switch.
Didn't they already make like a version of the Switch that was like OLED?
Did they make like a light version or something?
Yeah, or like a version that doesn't have the disconnected controllers,
it's like entirely portable.
Yeah, I think that sounds familiar.
They probably did and good for them.
They call it the stationary because you don't change it.
You don't switch it.
I don't see why, I don't see why they would make a Switch replacement
while the Switch is still dominating.
So probably not anytime soon.
What would they even put on the Switch 2?
What would they do with a Switch 2 that they couldn't do with a Switch?
They could put it as a VR headset as well.
Now that, honestly, yeah, why wouldn't Nintendo make a VR console?
It's kind of, the technology has come a long way and it sort of works.
Yeah, it's strange.
Nintendo is, oh no, I think they have done something VR related
with like the cardboard thing.
What was that?
The Nintendo Labo?
I feel like there was like a VR, a cardboard thing that you put on your head
and like some of the games are in that.
Or maybe I'm just misremembering.
That sounds familiar.
I didn't know if it was a Nintendo thing.
No, no, no, you just put your phone,
you just put your phone into the little cardboard thing.
That's that thing.
No, the Nintendo Labo thing, I saw German make it and it's like a gun
or some sort of like shooty thing and it's like a visor.
And you put the Nintendo Switch screen and you put it up to your face
and then it's like you're shooting in VR kind of with the, I don't fucking remember.
Okay, sounds interesting.
It sounds like a Nintendo gimmick.
I feel like they would have, they should have,
not that they should have, but they would have done more with VR.
Seems like they're sort of wheelhouse.
I feel like they could do a VR console.
Yeah, maybe they're gun shy since the virtual boy.
They got to come back, they got to come back with the virtual
man.
The virtual non-binary.
The virtual baby.
Yeah.
Next one is called Notability, the downfall of Wikipedia.
Three, two, one, go.
In episode 312, y'all talked about an article getting removed from Wikipedia
for not being notable as if that meant it got too few page visits or something
and started saying stuff like, oh no, will this article get deleted
if no one looks at it 10 years from now?
But that's just not what notable means.
On Wikipedia, notable just means multiple news organizations,
published articles about this place person or thing.
So no, this isn't some slippery slope that'll destroy Wikipedia.
It's a policy that they've heard consistently for over a decade.
Okay, so maybe I didn't understand what the word
Notability meant in that context.
However, I remember we were talking about David Firth,
and David Firth is most definitely a notable animator
who should be, who should have a Wikipedia article.
So by that, if that's the standard, then it's a bad standard.
Like, yeah, he hasn't been published in a lot of major outlets or anything,
but that's fine.
He shouldn't have to be.
Yeah.
He's notable, dammit.
Like, I don't know.
I don't like the tone of this guy.
He's a little nitpicker.
He's going around trying to pick us with nits.
Yeah, a little bit, a little bit.
Like, isn't it clear from our discussion that it's these small technical foibles
and things are not the meat of the conversation clearly,
that the point is that David Firth, having his Wikipedia removed,
shouldn't have happened, and that's why we're talking about it in that way?
Like, you floated the idea of page visits, and then the conversation stared into you talking
about published media articles and stuff.
You did get to the correct conclusion eventually.
I remember, I listened to it yesterday.
Well, fuck.
So I don't get ways correcting you.
What does this guy want?
When you already said the correct thing afterwards.
I think this guy might have broken rule one and not listened to the whole episode
before he made his voicemails.
Maybe, like, I think it's a shame David Firth's thing got deleted,
because he is a very notable person.
And I'm sure this fucking article is mentioning salad fingers.
I swear, like, whoa, look at this creepy cartoon.
Like, that's probably happened.
Like, everybody knows salad fingers.
Yeah.
Um, it's ridiculous.
Like, the reason to complain is that, like, the definition of notable is flawed,
because there are plenty of things that are important that aren't necessarily mentioned
by mainstream media.
Exactly.
That are significant.
That's kind of the point.
Yeah.
Which, again, was discussed last week, so I don't get this voicemail.
I feel like there's something.
He's nitpicking.
If he's going to pit more nicks.
I'm the nitpick nerd.
You better have a good argument next time.
He's the, he's a new, new, new, new Nate fucker called the Nate Picker.
He's Nate.
He, he, he picks every episode, see if Nate's in it.
Next one is called, um, Tom upload the podcasts to Apple podcasts.
I, right, I have a feeling I know what this one's going to be about, but three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, you know, remember, uh, behind the bastards, uh, Robert Evans podcast from like a
year or so ago?
Yeah.
So anyway, I never listened to it.
He didn't, he did an episode or a two part episode on Christine Weston Chandler.
And I thought that you would find it interesting and funny and sad and shit.
Perhaps.
And yeah, now you and all the listeners know about it.
Bye.
Okay.
That's kind of funny.
I thought he did about like historical figures.
It's kind of funny.
He would do a Chris Chan episode.
Hey, who?
The, this, this podcast is about, uh, this behind, behind the bastards.
It's like telling the story of like villains from history.
I think that's what it's all about.
Dictate, like dictators and stuff.
Classic, classic villain of history.
Some idiot that got trolled online.
Dude, she like, I, she like curse you homie hard like so many people.
She did do some serious.
Did Hitler do that?
Don't think so.
Her kid.
Look at him.
Kersi, how me, huh?
Even a single.
If they, they better mention the bicarbonate rain holocaust.
Oh my God.
Honestly, many worlds.
She did carry out a Holocaust that she felt was a legitimate act of, you know,
but by her definition would be a legitimate act of genocide.
She did do that.
She believes she did it.
Yeah.
She believes that these characters are real people
and that she eliminated 70,000 of them with a artificial weather event.
With chemical weapons.
Chemical weapons, yes.
In violation of the Geneva Convention.
To quote, to quote Goose Goose from that, that half life commentary video.
I do not believe that Christian Western Chandler even read the Geneva
conventions much less ratified them.
Or Quickville, I guess I should say.
Ratified them.
Yeah, you have to rat, you have to vote, you have to ratify them.
Turn them into a rat.
In NATO or something like that.
To the king of the rats.
Next one is called, will Ben ever pay his taxes?
Three, two, one, go.
No, absolutely not.
I did pay my tax.
I already paid them.
Yeah, that's a good clip.
That's a good clip to use.
Absolutely not.
Laugh some a night.
I'm going to download that one.
That's pretty good.
All right, next one is a tweet from Drinking Moth.
So reincarnated Samurai Sama wasn't Mages but Maze, huh?
Okay, I'll draw American one too then.
Alexa, play Kill la Kill.
Opening two.
Oh, we've got a whole.
Look out those are the snakes.
In the fire.
Oh, they are Kawasaki clan of greatness.
Once protectors of voice jail were wiped out in one sentence by the traitor Tommy J.
He unleashed them snakes the serpent thousand times or Ruchi's worse.
Oh, it's a it's a poem.
Save the scroll.
Don't be ignorant.
Flew young boy full of remorse.
Even then Ben St.
What villain stole the Kawasaki scroll with no spirit or somebody Samurai Sama.
Samusama died all alone.
But the rage of Kawasaki yet still burns like flame them snakes.
His soul split like teriyaki to a tone for past mistake.
America was always a country of cowards.
Nobody is ready to take up arms and fight against oppression.
Latvia was never anything special in the grand scheme of things.
There's no one daring to make a statement of their existence.
I don't know what's what's that in the guitar like foam?
Yeah, it looks like styrofoam.
I will change it with the power of the Kawasaki scroll.
Do they mean Lithuania?
Because mage is from Lithuania.
I think they I think they mean to say Lithuania.
Oh, no.
Also, why is she missing an arm?
Oh, she's she's getting ready to cosplay.
A zooming.
Yeah, exactly.
One soul, two bodies, two dreams, one target.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Remind me to commission drinking moth for.
Yeah, I need some art when I do the League of Nightfuckers
compilation video.
I had I had had some art in my mind for like a year that I'm too tired to draw.
But drinking moth got the goods.
This is very this is very funny.
This is bowling ball on a club nun chuck.
I guess.
So I guess this is Ethan Ralph's daughter.
So Ethan Ralph's daughter, mage's daughter fighting over the Kawasaki scroll
for their own ends and fighting over it.
It was.
Yeah, I mean.
Why does she have a bowling ball on a chain?
Simple as could be.
I don't.
Oh, because she was born at or she was.
No, her parents were married at a bowling alley.
Oh my god.
Maybe she was also born in one as well.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Wait.
Born in a bowling alley, like in the alley, like with the bowling balls flying past drinking.
Drinking moth gave the the sword is based on the Latvian flag.
It's the wrong country.
No, it's okay.
But it looks so good, though.
Yeah.
It looks really good.
Thank thank you.
Thank you for these very.
I'm very I'm very chuck.
Chuckled.
I'm chuffed.
Chuffed was the word.
Chuffled.
Uh, next, next one is a Vokeru link.
I'll put it right here.
Okay, uh, in three, two, one, go.
Hi, this is drinking moth again.
Him, Twilight, can you switch my voice?
Sure.
I believe this is the button.
One, one, one, two, three.
Hmm, this isn't quite ideal yet.
So, see, you need to press twice and then rotate.
So, as you might have already guessed, I am the creator of Twilight Sparkle Saga.
Sorry for sending some red herring shittier voicemails.
Hey, if you have any questions about the whole thing, feel free to ask.
Now that narrative is over, I will answer them clearly.
Also, as a long time listener, I must say my thanks.
Ben, you were the reason I started making comics.
I just caught you once drawing vapors on stream.
Gib, your baby jail.
Jail babe.
Whatever.
Shown me that you don't need to have super pretty hyper realistic art
to tell an engaging story.
Oblivionfall, thanks for showing me voicemeter.
None of this would have happened if I had to register at every SFX site,
download every YouTube video and pay for every text to speech or deep fake server.
And of course, thanks to every guest and audience of PCP for listening.
Good night, space cowboy.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Ah, right.
I will fuck Nate.
Yes!
I'll fuck Nate.
Even I have you fuck Nate.
Oh yeah.
Fakayuri no sento sama and sayonara.
Thank you, drinking mom.
That was great.
Hell yeah.
You know, and right after I already was ready to commission them for some Nate fucker,
they just come out here with this.
Oh, perfect, perfect for the job.
I'll hit you up and maybe like a week or two and I'm ready to edit that.
I'll sketch up an image and if you're open, I'll give you money.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I tricked you into drawing comics like a fool.
I spread the curse.
The art's generally good.
I love how the snakes look.
The snakes are amazing.
I really love that.
Yeah, it looks really good.
But the pose for the Lithuanian girl, like the way like her like the like the line of action,
how her body is like slanted, leaning back.
Very, very nice pose.
Very nice.
It's very good stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
What can I say?
It's just great.
Shout outs.
Shout outs to Drinking Moth.
Shout out.
Thanks for everything.
Let's.
All right.
Next one is the, it's an image or link.
Let's see what we got.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I'm glad you enjoyed the ride.
I see.
Oh, it's, it's, yes, I get it.
I think.
They're all, they're all ready to fuck Nate.
That, that Twilight Sparkle does want to fuck Ben.
It's true.
We're Celestia to save you.
Why is Yahtzee?
I think Yahtzee was, was one of the voices right at the end.
Yeah, one of the Texas.
Oh, I'm not sure who some of these are.
Is that Linkara?
Linkara.
I don't know who that guy is between Yahtzee and Linkara.
That must be the grandpa.
That must be Twilight's grandpa.
Oh, they said to us for questions.
I have one question.
Could you put your voicemails in like a video in like order
so we can experience the whole thing?
Yeah.
In one big like, ah, go.
Oh, that would be nice.
That'd be nice.
Yeah.
So we can go back to it.
Is that, is it them snakes holding that green thing?
It looks too fuzzy to be them snakes.
It's got like hands and like wings.
Some kind of demon, some kind of shadow demon.
There was, there was some kind of like spooky shadowy voice
and one of the voicemails from them, so.
No, Nate.
Is that drinking moth in the middle?
Is that them?
I possibly.
With the sans eye?
I don't know who else it could be.
Yeah, it must, it must be.
I don't know who the woman on the front of the face,
but she sure is far left.
She's cute.
Yeah.
She's a, she's a, I don't know who, I don't know who it is either.
She's one of the good blondes.
Yes.
Next, next one, next voicemail is called.
Wait, I don't think I, yeah, I did.
Okay, here it's called.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Yep, I agree.
Good voicemail.
Next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder Play Delta Room Chapter Two.
Okay, next one is called,
If Nobody Threw Any Bricks Through Any Windows, What's The Po?
I don't know.
The next one is called Your Bugs.
Here, there we go.
Three, three, two, one, go.
And in a way, it's kind of a puzzle game, you know?
You're just, you're trying to figure out how to render each bug snack catchable.
And you can use anything at your disposal, you know?
You've got your tools and you can even like shoot different kinds of sauce all around to like,
you know, lead a bug snack one way or the other.
They hate some things.
They love some things.
You can use elements from the environment and you can even use other bug snacks,
you know, make a fight, make a hit each other, set them on fire, all sorts of stuff.
And it is really fun.
I don't understand.
What's the significance of the clip?
I think it's just Arlo saying funny things about bugs.
You're bugging me.
It's a game called Bug Snacks.
He's talking about where, where you like, it's like Pokemon Snap,
but with bug things kind of.
I don't know.
Cool.
Sounds good.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called your best and worst PCP episode ever or best and worst.
It's just a question.
I already said the best one is the them snakes rap.
Worst one is this one that you're listening to right now.
I'd say the worst one is the last one.
Oh, yeah.
Because we're only going up.
I don't have a favorite.
We already got a question about like good voicemail,
voicemail episode recommendations.
The virginity episode is still one of my favorites of all time.
Just because it's so, I've really listened to it so many times.
I do remember we all didn't, we all thought monsters was a terrible
topic and we all agreed that it sucked.
I mean, I listened to it and I thought it was fine.
And then afterwards when everyone hated it, I mean, like, I mean, it wasn't that bad.
It wasn't great, but it was just kind of.
Was I not on that one?
I keep thinking that I wasn't on it.
I'm not sure.
You're on Monsters Free because you shut up with a voice changer and it was funny.
Oh, yeah.
So I skipped the worst episode.
I just remember us all like not having anything to say about monsters.
Yeah, from the grapevine, it seemed like it was a topic episode that literally
nobody had any reason to talk about.
Mm-hmm.
But the the topic must go on, I guess.
Yeah, or something.
Next one is stop with all the YouTube links, please.
Yeah, although there haven't been that many.
There's been one.
I mean, if you explain what the video is, it's more likely to be included, right?
Yeah, if you, yeah.
Next one is a social blade link.
I don't know.
User is not found.
So it didn't work.
Thanks.
Thanks, dude.
Okay.
Next one is speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail.
And yes, that is where you can submit voicemail links.
Okay, good job.
Uh-huh.
Next one is called, okay, good advice.
No, no, good luck.
Thumbs up, adviceanimalsatreddit.com.
Posting right now.
Right.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Probably unsolicited advice, but as a person who had to shave his head at 24 years old,
it sucks.
It's fine when you do it like 30 onwards, but at 24 is the worst.
That being said, if you have hair that isn't like being obstructed, like destroyed by really,
really ugly bald spots, I would say keep your hair style better.
For example, there was like this Brazilian guy that like hosted a DND session at a public event
that I went to.
And he was like kind of an early looking guy.
And only after like two or three or four hours of DNDing, I finally noticed he was coming over
a bald spot.
But overall, he looked great.
So sorry for the long voicemail.
But I would advise this mantra, you can do a lot more with hair than you can do without.
Maybe, but like you did notice the bald spot at the end.
The comb over is such a bad look in my eyes.
Bald is just better.
I wonder if this guy's just down on his own look in that way that one is a harsher judge of
oneself than of others.
I did give myself a haircut and I decided afterwards that I was much happier with how
my hair looks now.
I cut it short in the back and the sides and left it longer on top.
And I think that's how I think that's how it looks best.
So I'm back to being like okay with it.
Yeah, so my crisis has been averted.
I feel like if you have the confidence to pull off an exceptionally not acceptable
weird hairstyle, like a fryer tuck where you're bald all over the top but you've got the end
of a bald cut all the way around, if you could pull that off, you would be so cool if you could
do it.
You'd need a lot of confidence.
You'd need to go around in a brown robe and just be a fryer tuck character.
So you're saying the coolest person you could imagine is just a monk.
Well, what I'm saying is going bald happens to a lot of people and people get it.
Like when I see a bald-ing person, I'm not disgusted.
It's just normal.
It's just like lots of people look like that in various stages.
But I feel like there's space to be having a bald spot or a bald-ing thing
and deliberately crafting it and making it look deliberate
with confidence that it could actually look cooler than if you just shaved it all off.
I don't know.
If you do a weird monk look or samurai shave the top of your head thing,
you just look like you're, it just looks like a joke.
It just looks like you're in a costume.
I guess I think jokes are cool.
I think joke people are like epic.
People should wear real clown makeup as normal clothing.
I would look at that and I would say that this guy is like doing a bit.
I wouldn't be like, damn, he's got the confidence to pull off an unconventional look.
I would think he's filming a YouTube video and I'm supposed to be,
and I'm going to be his next victim.
I guess I keep remembering this one guy I met while I'd meet.
I just saw him on the train once and he had like a bright green, like neon green suit
and like a punk hairstyle and he looked like he was like 75.
I'm like, dang, something about the way he's holding himself is like so cool.
I guess he's like an old school punk.
He was like trying to stay like on the edge.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, I appreciate the punk look.
It's like a true punk.
It's not an aesthetic in and of itself.
I think lifestyle choice to be strange.
I think long hair is more punk, but I just don't think I look very good with my hair long.
So I don't know.
You know, you can't necessarily just pull off any look you want to just because you believe
in yourself hard enough.
Maybe that's not true.
Maybe that's just my doubt.
Maybe that's just my own self-doubt talking.
Yeah, I don't think I could do it.
I feel like I would crumble under pressure and try to like fall into the background
so that people don't look at me.
But I know it's possible because I've seen people do it and I am impressed.
But maybe I'm only impressed because I have shy tendencies.
Who knows?
I'm not particularly bothered by like looking weird in public.
I don't really get embarrassed about that sort of thing.
So I maybe I could do it.
Next one is called, did I skip one?
Yes, next one is called You Dumb Yank.
And there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Listen here, Ben Shribatsky.
The reason why Shribatsky is the people united will never be defeated.
It's because it's a translation from a Chilean song called El Pueblo Unido Jamacer A Vencido.
It's a literal translation.
It's not a mistake.
The only reason why it's like that is because English is a garbage language.
Sorry.
And the people united will never be divided makes no fucking sense because as Gip said,
it's already implied that they are fucking united.
It doesn't make fucking sense.
Well, what the fuck?
I'm going to defend my statement.
I think that translation involves localization.
And I think that preserving the rhyme would be important.
And I think that no, it makes sense to say once they're united, they will not be divided
because if the goal is to unite, defeat and division are basically one and the same.
Exactly.
So it does make sense.
I think it, thank you.
It makes perfect sense.
You fucking Chilean bastard.
You South American.
Did you say English?
English.
Damn.
I heard that slip.
The people divided will never be multiplied.
Multiplied.
I still prefer Gibbs interpretation.
The people united will never be divided.
Will never be divided.
People will be so scared that they'll just conventionally to every demand.
Next, there's a follow-up called you dumb Yankee part two.
Three.
Actually, there's a part three as well.
This is part two.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, Ben Zelensky.
I'm sorry, man.
I was a little bit violent just now because I just got my third booster shot.
And I'm fucking, I am in fucking pain right now.
And it's fucking awful.
But I guess it beats breathing through a tube.
That's it.
Get your booster shot.
I did get my booster shot.
Fuck you, Ben.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, fuck Ben.
We're really good Ben fuckers.
Yeah, I thought for a second he was being kind and that was too far.
I did get my booster shot.
He had to say fuck Ben at the end to balance it out.
I got it.
When did I get it?
Probably in like late January, I think, or something.
So it's been a while.
I would like another one, please.
I'd like a boob or shot, please.
One in each.
Nice.
Very good.
There's one.
Okay, next one is part three.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, I know this is the third voicemail I sent.
I am sorry.
At least they're short.
I'm not going to send any more.
But before I forget, I want to thank Gib because the package arrived.
And I've been laughing like a dumbass to read my comics.
It's really funny.
I have not yet read The Lord of Ghosts.
I'm going to read it.
I have a lot of things to do first, but I will read it.
So thank you for the doodle.
Thank you for what you sent me and that's it.
That's it.
Have a good day.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for buying it.
That guy went through an arc.
He started off a villain and he became a hero.
Based gigachat move reading the Red Man comic first.
That's true.
I suspect that my package from you did arrive.
Something turned up at my mother-in-law's.
We're heading there today to go.
Oh, good.
Oh, I don't think I'm...
I don't know if I mentioned this on the last episode.
I meant to say it.
Oh, this is actually really important.
I wanted to say that I went to my PO box
and I discovered that my PO box had expired.
And so it's possible that some people
who I might have sent a package to and it did not arrive,
it might have been unable to be returned to me
and it was lost.
So I guess anyone listening,
if you have not gotten a package from me,
you should let me know and I will just send you another one
because that's my fault for letting the PO box expire.
Actually, there were like four...
There were like four packages.
I think there were three pleb in the wee Blu-rays
and there was one copy of Road to Radcon.
And these were like old copies.
I had sent them in February.
So anything after February that got returned is gone, I think.
So that's kind of sad.
Hopefully there's not that many.
But I have like four that I have
that I have to contact those people and send them out.
But there's probably some more that are missing.
And I hate to think that anyone bought something from me
and didn't get it.
So I will like...
Those people whose envelopes I do have,
I will try and reach out to them
if I can figure out who they were.
Yeah, that was a bit of bad news that I found today.
But I guess this does mean
that I can now get a new PO box closer to my house,
which is convenient.
That old one was like the other side of town.
It was very annoying.
Oh, yeah.
I guess I should mention briefly.
If anybody's gotten their Lord of Ghost package
but hasn't let me know,
I can't tell when things have arrived
because I didn't have tracking on a lot of these
for money purposes.
So I haven't received any returns.
So I assume most of them did arrive safely.
But if you have a Twitter account, tweet at me.
It's not just base and cool to see that you're enjoying it.
But it's helpful.
So I can just go on my spreadsheet and say,
that one's arrived.
Don't have to worry about that.
And yeah, some of them might be very stuck
and still in transit.
But I can't know right now.
Some of them end up, especially international packages,
sometimes end up getting stuck in shipping limbo
for a disappointingly long amount of time.
So if it hasn't arrived yet
and I haven't received a return,
it's probably on its way very, very slowly.
So that's that, I guess.
Just sorry.
Yeah, there's nothing you can really do about it.
The next voicemail is just a text question.
It says, is Tom still a member?
Yes, but he said he probably won't be on anytime soon.
He says he's busy with the channel
Nintendo 64, what was it called?
Saber Spark.
Yeah, Saber Spark 65.
Yeah, he's working on it.
100,000 subscribers.
Good for him.
Huh?
100,000 subscribers on that.
Good for him.
Good for them.
Vam.
Right.
Snakes.
No.
Good for them.
Snakes.
They've got us surpassed.
Soon enough they'll surpass Nate, just like I did.
True.
Yeah, good for them.
Tom said he's probably not going to be around anytime soon.
But he's not like officially quit or anything,
so that's what that's about.
Next one is called iPod Shuffle
Better Than Any Modern Day Portable Technology.
Let me post that.
Three, two, one, go.
So I've bought an iPod, it's like the MP3 player,
and I wanted to listen to this podcast.
I went to the link in the description,
and the MP3s were very hard to download in bulk.
I could download them individually,
but they're like a massive folder of thousands of hours of content.
So I know maybe I'll put like a zip to each one of them,
more money of like every single episode so far.
That'll be a touchy-poo life.
Okay, does this guy want to download all the PCP episodes?
At once, yeah.
In a zip.
In a zip file?
Well, I mean, I guess,
they're all hosted on Google Drive, right?
They're all downloadable from the PCP website.
Yeah, but not in bulk.
Not in bulk, you would have to download them one at a time,
which is annoying for sure.
Yeah, I mean, you know, it's a fair request.
It would just take some doing.
I would just have to put that together.
I might.
I mean, it's not a completely stupid idea.
Yeah.
Next one is called Happy Birth.
No, wait, no, sorry.
Sorry, I missed this one.
This one is called B321GO.
What kind of pornography do you like?
Sexy.
Yeah, I like it when it's sexy.
Did they say it was B?
It's just it's just the letter B.
The letter B, okay.
I like B porn.
Yeah.
Do you ever see a B woman and she has a big fucking what's it called?
Stinger.
Not the Stinger.
The thorax or no abdomen.
Yeah, the big or the big fuzz.
Wings and teni, mandibles.
There's an artist.
I've seen BOCs or if I give them like the big B but and I don't know what it is,
but it does something for me and it's good.
It's the B dump.
I found some good images, but they're all two NSFW to post.
Yeah, yeah, the abdomen is the big like the big bulgy part underneath the tiny little waist.
Like those giant ants in Elden Ring that I was saying.
I'm sure I can crop this to where it would be safe enough.
It's just two pixels.
I don't think I don't think it's insectoid.
Women really do it for me.
I just want to fuck everything.
Okay, I see where this is going and I get it.
There's a pretty large boob elsewhere on screen.
Obviously, you can't show that.
Yeah, yeah, I can see that.
I don't know if I like the thorax or if I like the sticking out of her butt there.
Little weird.
You grab it and pull it up like a, like a, like a, well,
psycho potatoes, what would it be like?
Like a giant bag of sand.
Like a thing.
Instead of a stinger, there's just another hole to put your penis in.
Ben is not bug fuck.
This is what we're learning today.
I don't think I am.
Yeah, I don't really think I'm much honest.
I mean, when it comes to-
Work's going to be so disappointed in you.
Yeah, she already is, don't worry.
When it comes to art, like this, this is like only tangentially bug.
Like it's basically just a woman.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, Ben wouldn't, Ben wouldn't fuck tangentially just a woman.
Terrible.
Come on, she's tangentially a woman.
What's, what's the problem?
Next one is called happy birthday Ben.
Oh my God.
And then the next one is, you're not going to believe the next one is called
you wouldn't fuck a bee?
There's, okay, there's, there's an image and an audio.
So I guess let's listen to the audio first.
Three, two, one, go.
I am not a horse.
I am a bee.
I am a funny fucking bee.
Oh yes, I have a big stinger.
Buzz, buzz, buzz.
Celestia, you're off your meds.
What?
She's really going for it.
Uh, there, there, there she is.
You know what?
I like this.
This is better.
Okay, okay.
But she's a tangential woman.
She's not a real woman, Ben.
Yeah, she's a horse.
I guess I like mammals.
No, no, no abdomen.
No chitin, please.
Mammal is good.
I'm very vanilla.
I only fuck mammals.
That is, uh.
No amphibians, no frog girls.
It's, it's like he knew.
It's like he knew that I would be upset
by his initial question.
And he anticipated my response.
But how did they know we were going to talk about bees?
I don't know.
Next, next one is another Imgir link.
They primed us by putting the letter B
in the voicemail, remember?
That's just a happy coincidence.
Um, okay.
Okay, so this is give Ben Saint.
Okay, it's this.
Yes, you, wait, is this an album?
Yeah, there's a bunch of, there's a bunch of images.
Oh, let me have a look at these.
Flights from England are now landing in Boston.
This is the truth.
This is, there I go.
There I am.
They gave you such a bubble butt.
Oh yeah, a little bit.
But hey, hey guy, no smoking in the airport.
Who me?
Yes, you with the, oh, it's a little cut off.
Yes, you with the smoke.
It's vaping.
It's vape.
I'm vaping, dude.
A man causing trouble just by standing in place,
not doing anything.
It must be none other than Ben Saint.
That's how I find you.
Just vibing.
I like that you got your guitar.
That's nice.
That's a nice detail.
I probably won't bring my guitar.
You have two guitars.
Do I have two guitars?
Well, there's the one on the, you're holding one,
and then there's another one in the baggage claim.
Oh, yeah, why?
What?
Am I dual wielding?
Maybe one's like a ukulele.
Maybe one, maybe it's the two guitars from the Rayman video,
or the hypocritical reviews, where like,
there was the one who talked,
and then there was the other guitar that the guitar played.
Remember that?
I like.
Yes, I do.
I was thinking about that character recently.
I was thinking, wow, hypocrite was a good channel.
Thanks.
I like how they drew my face here.
I think I look very cool.
It's vape.
I'm vaping, dude.
It's not even coming out of my mouth.
It's just seeping out of my skin.
Out of your pores, just like a mist.
Saturated with it.
It's losing out of my, my cloak.
This guy's so pissed.
Oh, he's a cop.
So, you know, of course he's mad.
He's going to go beat his wife.
Lamau.
Thank you.
I love, I love that.
That's very delightful.
Next one is called,
I, Ethan Ralph, am fixing what you did to him, Ben Saints.
Uh, there it is.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, mate.
Last week, I took the baby to the prayer gateway church camp.
I went to when I was a kid.
You know, I probably never told you, but I like dicks a lot.
But now I'm straight, mate.
And so will our baby be.
That's great.
When he's back, he'll be a completely different person.
Just like me, Ethan Ralph senior.
My son, Ethan Ralph junior will be a completely different person
by the time he comes back.
Who we?
Oh, wow.
Wow, wow.
Wow.
Wow, me too.
That's some shit.
Thank God, Ethan Ralph isn't gay.
I couldn't bear to share a demographic with him.
I know.
I'm glad he sort.
He got that sorted out at a young age before it could cause problems.
Now I can.
I don't have to feel bad about shitting all over him.
Absolutely.
What command is that?
Nothing really, nothing really happened in that voicemail.
What happens?
I, setting up the next scene.
It's a, it's a, it's a slow burn.
Next one.
Wow.
Pardon.
Next one is called Hades.
There it is.
Three, two, one.
There's only two left, by the way.
Three, two, one, go.
I started playing Hades, again, during my COVID adventure, which was hard
because the game makes you push a lot of buttons to do a lot of things.
But you, you, you talk to me into trying the gun.
I like the gun.
I think I'm bad though, but how do you pitch?
The gun, I had my first win with the rail, and I think I have the most wins with the rail.
It's not my favorite.
I think my favorite is actually, I really like the bow.
I really like the shields.
I don't know.
The, you fish by, when you see the little sparkling thing in the water,
you just go over to it and press the action button, and then you just pull out your little rod
and you'll fish.
And then when it flashes and makes a big blue sound, that's when you've got to reel it in.
I've never, I've never been too late on a fishing.
I've only ever failed fishing by like getting psyched out and hitting the, the, like,
reel it in button too early.
Damn.
That's it.
I gotta, I'm like so close to like 100%ing.
Hey, I only have like two achievements left, but they're like really tedious.
And I just, I don't know if I have, I freed, I finished the quest line to set Achilles free
and let him go back to see Patroclus.
But I have not played since then, so I have not visited Patroclus so I can see like,
what are they talking about now?
So that's, that's interesting.
Next one, and this might be the last one, unless someone gave us a last minute voicemail.
This one is called, Ben, I will release my manifesto saint.
Oh boy.
Three, two, one, go.
You've got some explaining to do.
Last week, you said you were going to deliver your manifesto last night or yesterday or
something, I don't know.
A young man in New York shot up a black supermarket and released a 100 page manifesto.
Memes?
Was this you, Ben?
Was he acting under your influence?
Jake, I know you didn't do it, baby.
Right, right, right, snake.
Did I say that?
Did I say I was going to release a manifesto?
I don't remember about.
I also don't remember.
I hope I didn't say that.
That's too bad.
No, I didn't know that guy.
No, he, obviously we, obviously we,
no, I don't even want to joke that like we agree on something that's terrible.
No, I don't know.
Fuck that.
Sad, I'm sad thinking about it.
Oh, the guy was, did I, do you remember me last week saying I was going to release my manifesto?
No, I also don't think this guy's making shit up.
I don't think that happened.
I think this guy might be making some shit up.
He was pulling a leg.
He's pulling my leg and I don't appreciate it.
I'm going to, I'm so annoyed that I'm going to burn my bridge with this guy and just call
him out and just say, what a piece of shit.
I hate him.
Not my friend anymore.
Just because this one time that I got mildly angry.
That's what I do.
Yeah.
Damn.
That's it.
That's the last voicemail.
Well, good timing because I think I have to head to the store pretty soon.
So I guess we can wrap up maybe.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's, let's wrap it up.
What are we at?
Like four hours, three, okay, three, three hours and 15.
Okay.
It's respectable.
Yes.
Anyone who didn't get a thing that they ordered from me, let me know it might have
been lost in my canceled PO box.
Please, please let me give you stuff.
That's it.
I guess next week we'll be, I'll be in America.
So I guess we'll record a live PCP.
I don't know.
I don't know if we're going to like film it with like a camera.
We will be in the same room though.
We'll, we'll, we'll do a PCP in the same room or something.
Do you want to do that?
I kind of thought we just maybe wouldn't do one that week.
I mean, we can if you want.
Um, figure, figure something out.
I mean, would it be that hard to like organize just sitting in a room for a couple hours?
No, probably not.
Sounds, sounds doable.
Yeah.
Uh, okay.
Sure.
Why not?
Okay.
Um, anything else before we
wrap?
Gentlemen, ladies.
Not much.
I am animating pussy.
You'll probably have a time this episode's out.
It'll be done at patreon.com.
Slash of William Fall.
Hooray.
That's it.
Cool.
Um, all right.
End of the episode.
See you next week, everyone.
And also give in real life.
Yeah.
In real life.
The real life.
Woo.
Bye.
I'm having like a lot of like right at the end.
Okay.