I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a-
That son of a-
Son of a-
Ah, hello, good morning!
Ah, good to morgan!
Good morning!
To an early morning,
PCP, I am up at five?
Well, actually I woke up at three.
I didn't mean to wake up until five, but I woke up early.
Oh, so you woke up, I was assuming you would stay up.
For such an early-
No, not this time, I woke up-
I had stayed up all night the previous night,
so I wanted to go to bed early last night,
and then wake up early this morning.
I appreciate you agreeing to move the episode earlier.
The reason why I wanted to record
early this morning
is because I want daylight.
I wanted to record early this morning,
because I want daylight.
I want daylight.
I wanted to record before daylight
and have daylight available.
Big day for me.
I'm gonna try and record that video
that I've been teasing
forever.
I think I'm gonna try and make today the day, yeah.
Yeah, alright.
That's good.
That's what I wanted the daylight for.
Yeah, I'm moving
two days from now,
so I
don't know if I'll be able to do anything tomorrow,
because there's been like guys
working in my house, like doing renovations
on the building,
and they come during the week,
and so on tomorrow's Monday, so they might be
all around making noise
and stuff.
They might, they might.
So I don't know if I will be able to
do anything today, but
or tomorrow.
So I'm gonna try and do it all today,
and just see how it goes, see how it works out.
I'm pretty nervous.
I'm scared. What if it's bad?
I don't know.
How many hours of recording do you think
it will take to get through?
I don't know.
I could see it.
It could take all day.
It could take multiple days.
I might not be able to finish.
But I'm not sure.
There's nothing wrong with like
having the second part
of the video, and you just say,
yeah, I'm somewhere else now. Okay, continuing.
Yeah, it wouldn't be,
it wouldn't be the worst thing
in the world.
I want to continue to be cagey about it.
I don't want to say exactly what it is
until it comes out.
But I have, let's just say
I had to make
a prop.
And the
prop will be used
during the video.
He's going to shove a dildo up his ass.
It will be, this is my only fans
announcement.
The prop will be used
and irrevocably altered during
the video. And so should I have to
re-record, I would need to make it
again, which would, I mean,
it would probably take me a day to
remake it, which would be annoying, but
it's fine.
I would do it.
Damn, what else
do I have to say about that?
Oh,
I bought a
man, I've been trying to get the
lighting right, and that's been
weird, because I have my
all right,
let me explain. I have my overhead
light, which is just,
you know,
regular, I think they're incandescent bulbs
in a lamp on the ceiling.
And I thought that would be fine.
But then when I tried to do some
test filming, things were
it's not the
thing, you could see everything, but
the colors were washed out. I think there wasn't
enough light.
I think my eyes are adjusted to it, but I
think the light is too dim for
the colors to be
visible. Yeah, the lighting
a set or whatever.
It's so much brighter
than you would imagine.
It's funny,
I
compared it with
that and an extra light, and
when I don't have the extra light,
the image looks just as
bright, but it's just more colorful
when the second light is
on it, is the only real
difference. And I think the colors
are important.
I had
considered ordering a ring light
or something, and I had put it off
and put it off and I never did it, because I thought
maybe I didn't need it. Turns out I did need it.
But it was too late,
it wouldn't get here in time, so I went to the
hardware store and I picked up
an LED work light,
which had a
it was one of the brighter ones they had, and it
had a nice middle of the road
temperature, like light
temperature.
So it's pretty good,
it works, it's what I'm using
to light the scene,
and it did make the colors pop, and it looked okay.
The problem is
that it was really bright, and it's
not bright enough that I could, but it's not
bright enough that I can put it a long distance away.
So I have to put it fairly
close to me to light the shot,
and it is
um,
it's bright that at that distance
it glares off of me, and it
casts a big shadow behind
me on the...
almost.
Yeah, and that's bad.
That's not good, it doesn't look good, so
I tried
Did you put a piece of paper
in front of it to diffuse it?
Yeah, I tried that,
it didn't really
it didn't really make a difference,
you know, to really diffuse light
you actually have to shine it
on like a big
on like a big piece of paper
or something.
Some of those, the lights
that I've seen, they have
like the light, and then like
an umbrella, like a big
cone that goes around it
and at the end of that is like...
The softbox sort of things.
Yeah.
I tried to sort of make an artificial one,
I tried to, I cut out some cardboard
and I made a thing to fix on the light
and I put aluminum foil
with the idea being
that it would sort of reflect
the extra light
that was going to the sides, reflect
and sort of keep it in this like sort of cone
that I built, and sort of direct it
straight forward, so that I could put
the light further back
but have more of the light
shine on me in a more narrow
direction
to light the scene just as well
from a further distance back
and it didn't really
make much of a difference, I think it was
kind of a waste of time.
I think...
Okay, the alternative
was leaving my window open because I do get
bright sunlight through my window.
The problems with that
is that, one, I have to record
during daylight hours.
Two,
it's variable if there's like cloud coverage
which is a little annoying.
Yeah.
Three, it's actually,
the sunlight is not directly
on me, but it's nevertheless
bright enough that there's sort of
it sort of glares off me, it sort of gives
me sort of white highlights on my forehead
and stuff if I leave the windows open
and that's not good.
So, before I try
anything today, I'm going to try
and I have some sort of like see-through
gauzy curtains, like a purple one
and a black one. I think
I'm going to try and just put up very
thin curtains and see if maybe that
diffuses or softens the light enough
that I don't get the glare while still
lighting the shot well enough with
like, you know, the sunlight
and I think that
might be the best.
I think that's going to be
probably how I do it
because I just want the shot to look
not ugly, right? It's not
anything fancy.
I just want it not, I want it not to be
glaring and I want it not to have
like a strong backshadow behind me which
would be distracting.
I want the light to look natural.
I just want a nice neutral
natural, bright
shot.
You know?
Surprisingly difficult to achieve sometimes.
Yeah, the very like default
nothing going on shot is very
hard to get happening.
I think in
when I did like all the stuff in my
hypocrite like skits
I didn't invest in a light.
I had like a lamp
and sometimes I would place it somewhere
and it would do.
It would be like very
very like DIY
and then I would only do a skit for like a few
seconds so it's
I changed camera angles.
I don't think any of my shots
looked like terrible except when they did.
Yeah.
But I did not have like a professional setup.
It's just about getting the right
amount of light mainly.
Yeah.
So if you have anything fancy like having like
ooh a nice little
what do you call
is it called an edge light?
You know when they try to be fancy and they have
a little like colored light behind
the subject that sort of gives them like a little
like you know colored sort of outline
on one side of them.
And if you're like a really fancy streamer you have
two of them you have nice bisexual
lighting so you've got one edge light
one pink edge light on one side of you
and one blue edge light on the other side of
it up pink on one side blue on the other.
Yes I've seen such things.
And you get on twitch you get on discord
you start.
I was wondering like
the lights
are always those colors
like why is there no like
green and orange streamer?
You know there's
when I think about edge lighting
the first example
that pops into my head
I know you've seen some
folding ideas Dan Olson videos
I've seen all of them yeah.
You've seen all of them okay so the one where
he talks about
not the flat earth documentary
no not in search of a flat earth
the other one
where he's talking about that other documentary
made by the Christian people
and they interviewed a bunch of physicists
and they didn't tell them what it was for
they had a hideous
green edge light
that they put on everyone
to make them look I don't know
sciency or something
sciency or sinister or slime core
I don't know
who knows what they were thinking
yeah
so
not doing anything like that
so I think I'm gonna have to
rely on the sun
which just means I have to
get everything recorded between
you know maybe like
7pm and probably like
7pm or 8pm
or something like that
the sun is like
I mean you have to be very lucky
to get a very long stretch
of the sun not being
interrupted by clouds
or anything
yeah
if you know it's a really nice day
then it will be alright but like
it's not gonna be like fully sunny
I think there probably will be some moments
when the clouds go overhead
and I think maybe I can just
either just deal with it
or maybe I can do a little bit
of adjustment in posts
to sort of brighten things
when it's dimmer
because the sun is extremely powerful
and like it fills the room
it makes everything so much brighter
the camera is like oh this is great
plenty of light as soon as the cloud comes up
all of that light goes really
like really far down on the camera
it's sort of like maybe it loses focus
as well if it's autofocus
you should definitely have
a light on you at all times
as well
I am going to have
I'm gonna use the LED work light
it looks pretty good
it's a good light
it's just too much at too close
and the back shadow
I need the sun to avoid
I need the work lights for it to be bright enough
that the colors aren't washed out
the back shadow from the work light
but the sun
the sun itself
gives sort of an uneven light
like you can see like I'm very much lit
more from one side than another
and that's not good
and I'll leave my room light on
just because why not
if you get a mirror in the room
you bounce that sunlight all over the place
oh you know what
that's what they do in like
to make a room like in
Victorian era or just
an old tiny room before lamps
and stuff
were that easy to use
get a huge mirror
brightens up a space
hmm I would have to adjust
the position of the mirror
as the day progress in order to
like continually move
but yeah I don't have a big mirror
but I mean I could
I have a cork board
in aluminum foil
and place it where the sun is shining
through the window
I don't think I actually
really get like direct sunlight
into my room
I'm not sure if I could really do that
well the thing with a mirror is like whatever light is in the room
will be bounced around
more
so it's not like you don't need to direct
some beam like in a video game
you just need it around so that
if the light is hitting it
somehow like bouncing off a wall
into the mirror it bounces back on to the wall
makes the wall brighter
you know what? I've got aluminum foil
I've got my cork board
I'm gonna do it
right now
just and I'll just see
we'll just see if it doesn't
you know I tried this with the artificial
the fake the DIY
softbox that didn't really
work out that's okay
that's fine
I'm just imagining
like your whole room is like
covered in foil
you're wearing like a mirror bowl suit
my whole room is covered in
bits of scrap paper
little pieces of tape
one corner is covered in
boxes
you know because I'm moving as well
as doing all this so I'm packing
nervous about moving
my current house
but the one thing that it does have
is that I do have privacy
I don't have to deal with
other people in this disgusting little
hole that I live in
is that not true for the
new place?
well it seems like the new place is gonna be a little more
like my old place where it's kind of
it's not it's like a house
you know
right now I live in an apartment
building
with you know everyone else lives on the
second floor
you live on a different floor and I hardly ever see them
I might sometimes pass them
in the kitchen and other than that we have nothing to do with each other
I might
have to see other people more
in my new place
and I don't know
I feel like that's probably good actually
but
it still makes me
anxious
what if I have to explain what I do
honestly yeah
I mean you remember
I told you I went to that birthday party
and mentioned being a
podcaster and I
felt so bad
I felt like I was a zoo animal
that has escaped from its
enclosure
I'm sorry is this tinfoil annoying?
I can't hear the tinfoil
I think discord
or something might be noise
removing it but you are
getting quieter because you're doing it
it's because I'm not facing
the microphone
well I will talk about something for a minute
you may have noticed
the RuneScape video I put up
on my pick and take
first comment
you liked it
you gave me a little like on that
yeah
yeah that's
I made it mostly for people
who like you who are like
what huh what's RuneScape
I don't know hardly nothing
about the mechanics of RuneScape
yeah it wasn't really mean to be
like here's how RuneScape works
but
I just wanted to like document this little thing
go watch the video if you're curious
it's a little challenge run
I'm doing on
old school RuneScape
are you gonna make follow up videos
is it gonna be like a series
if there's interesting things
to talk about I probably will
if I do like follow ups
I'll probably put them on Hippocrite
mostly because
on the off chance that
it blows up or is otherwise
just well received
I want it to be on the channel
that has monetization enabled
instead of the one that doesn't
take not have that
I remembered because
you know I made
9-11 jokes a couple times
in some videos
like a while ago
I think I may have talked about it already
but a while ago my channel was just like
super flagged saying oh you
your videos promote
terrorism
because you said 9-11 and you showed footage
in like a joke video
it's because you wrote in your diary
we're gonna shoot up the school that one time
they heard about your principal
called YouTube and said this kid
this kid's trouble
that's so true
we gotta get her on something
we gotta get
get them on the
the YouTube
9-11 jokes there
9-11 jokes
I think it's literally just because in those jokes
I have footage of the thing
happening on a green screen with a Kirby
plush or something
and they're like that's
that's
that's bad they didn't
think about it and now my channel
can't get monetized
and I think I repealed it
I said please give me money please
and they said no
I even took down the videos and they just
didn't do anything so
what's up with
your channel just has a black mark on it
I think it's just a black mark
and also like following up
it's like we'll get back to you in like
117,000 months
and it's like okay well
it's the give and take channel
I'm not missing out on that much
revenue so fuck it
I don't wanna bother
so if any future
RuneScape videos I make will go on Hippocrite
cause that's the video game channel anyway
and uh yeah
I don't know how I would make a series of it
Hippocrite's back baby
no no it is just an illusion
the ppt is back
I'm making a video you made a video
it's just like it's just like old times
it's just like old times
you were you were so known
for your video making
I mean
I mean I mean you say
you say that like a joke and yet I am almost
certainly better known for the videos that I made
than anything else
when I think of like classic like oh
the horseshoe crew and everyone in it
um you were like
the art guy of tbap
as well as the co-host
Nate was the edit guy of tbap
and then Nate went on to make videos
before you did
so I was always like oh Ben was the art guy
yeah I mean that's how I
kinda see myself
but uh I mean
I told you that the reason why I was
the reason why I resolved
that I should make another video
make another video
and show us what you got
remember that
you don't remember the cutie mark
kerfuffle episode 2
oh well I don't remember
that line from it
that's when
keg standard pushes give and take out
onto the dance floor
oh
no no
no it's not that
I remember that happening
he pushes anypony
in front of his computer
to make a shitty react video
oh yeah that's why I don't remember
because I don't care
oh yeah okay
make another video
okay
no no no no no
it's when
you say make another video
and show us what you got
and then it becomes a give and take video
and then the head pops out
of the edge of the screen
and goes like
hi everybody
it's me I'm back
I'm back and better than ever
oh my god it's so
the fans wanted it so much
and then the rest of us
all pop out from the sides and we go
Gibbon and you go ah god
yeah
I remember that bit
oh jesus christ
yeah
you don't know why you're there
but we really want you to continue
okay
that was a
how did I get on that
subject?
the reason why
I was
inspired to resolve to make a video
was because Maryweather
messaged me to tell me that he thought
that I should make more videos because he likes my other ones
and I said
well that's it
okay
this guy
I'll listen to Maryweather
Maryweather is no fool
I'm almost done
with my mirror
yes it's all coming together
oh god
what are you doing?
you're wrapping tinfoil around
like
stabbing it onto a cork board
no I'm just wrapping
I'm wrapping it around the edges
you know what I'll take a picture
it's complete
it's done
let me take a picture of a mirror
post-selfie
it's not a clear image
but you can kind of see my skin tone
reflected in it
that's disgusting
and you know what I feel about my skin tone
you know how I feel about my skin tone
we don't want to get my fucking
oh there's a
a secret prop that would give away the
video was almost in the
shot
that's fucking scary
you can see
actually this is funny
in
the in the shot
which I'm going to post in just a second
in the mirror
you can see some green reflected
and that's the
that's the jug of slime
that I made
that's my leftover slime
from when I made those bottles
for the rfck people
it's
in a jug and it's sitting on my
bookcase here which I put
in the middle of my room to stand
the light on because I didn't want it shining on me from the floor
I wanted it at
middle height
um
post in general
oh yeah
a rectangle
oh it's a rectangle alright
is that harmonica in the bottom right?
harmonica?
oh that's the role of aluminum foil
that is empty
oh this is a lot bigger than I thought
glancing at it yes
it's probably like 2 feet by
3 or 4 feet
alright you got a mirror
no I've got a mirror
oh my god I can't see your reflection are you a vampire
you a vampire or something
oh no I gave it away the video
it's a video where I show that I'm a vampire now
proof that I'm a vampire
I'm getting into
the occult
and the conspiracies
and magic and shit
startin
ever since I became a vampire I just find
stuff so interesting
so fascinating
you're really playing with fire
filming during the day
yeah I gotta use that
sunlight for visibility but if even a little bit
of it directly shines on me I will be obliterated
this is why vampires can't make videos
this is my dedication
do vampires
not show up on film
is that a
I think that might be a thing with them
actually
it's always a question
because like
obviously when vampire mythology was created
mirrors were the only way
you could do such a thing
you could draw a picture of them
yeah
but like
there was no such thing as film
but
I think
since you can see a vampire physically
when you're looking at them
I would say that a camera would be able to take a picture
of a
of a vampire
but by that logic a mirror should be able
to see it because it's just light reflecting off
the mirror
mirror special
it's the silver
wait but no
it's like silver oxide
is what is the
the compound
so you can't take it black and white
but you can't take a polaroid because it's a different chemical
if you do it
DSLR
single lens reflex is where they have the mirror
come out of the way
you can look through the viewfinder
you see nothing you take a picture
there was a vampire there
because you're looking
what you're seeing through the viewfinder is
the mirrored version
and then the mirror slides out the way to take the picture
that would be a cool scene
fascinating
it would be a cool movie if that happened
and then the whole movie is explaining
how that worked
and why
alright my mirror is done
I'm gonna put it over here on the side
lean it against the wall until such time
that's
that's good
that's exciting I wonder if that will help
achieve a
one issue is that
the
the shot is a bit
brighter on the side
with the window
and I
wasn't able to completely
fix that unfortunately
maybe this will help
hmm
well
that's what I've been doing
I just woke up
well not just woke up
I went on a dog walk
I came back
and I did my morning workout routine
I had breakfast
and I had a shower
and then I'm immediately podcasting
so it's a pretty
productive morning for me
yeah
my breakfast today
is
a box of almond milk
I'm trying to drink
every fluid
that I have in bottles and stuff
to maximize pee
to
so that I don't have to move it
in boxes and stuff
you know what I just finished the first
I'm gonna crack open another one
I'm gonna crack open another
almond milk right
you just you're gonna store your almond milk
in your stomach sack
sorry actually
this is not almond milk
this is an almond non-dairy beverage
from Kirkland
what the hell does that mean
I don't know
but it doesn't go bad
it doesn't expire
I found this out the hard way
almond milk will expire
whatever the hell this stuff is
as long as you don't open it
as long as it's sealed
it keeps forever
why does almonds make milk
I understand why mammals make milk
because it's like a protein thing
for a baby to easily
ingest
and almonds
but like why are they dairy
if they how do they expire why is it milk
is this a real question
I don't know I've never looked into what almond milk is
I just assume you squeeze the almond
and milk comes out
do you think that like the almond lactates
and that's where the almond milk comes from
I don't assume it has breasts
I just assume like why is there
milk inside like a coconut
like what is going on
a very funny
thing to even wonder about
honestly
they make almond milk they just soak the almonds
in water and it leeches
out some nutrients
and that makes the almond milk
okay why does it go bad though
I don't know
because it's freaking
it's got fat in it
it's got fat in it that would go rancid
I see
yeah
you know they had almond milk in the middle ages
like medieval people drank almond milk
how about that
you think about it as some alternative milks
new age soy
soy
but no
they had almond milk in
I know this from Max Miller's Tasting History
and I don't know it because I am stupid
that's right
that's right Gib
okay
almonds with tits
that's the new craze on the old
on the old art world
I liked your theory better
I never thought about it before
but when I was thinking
are they like tiny coconuts
is there milk inside
I understand not knowing
how almond milk is made
it's just funny to be like
wait
I know mammals make milk
but why do almonds make milk
not what is almond milk
made of where does it come from
how is it made but why do almonds make milk
as though it is a natural
thing that the almond does
that's what I think of milk
it's not like you soak a cow
in water to make milk
that's true
but you know coconut milk
you just crack open the coconut and it comes out
so it's more akin to that
it's more like blood
it's more like almond blood honestly
but we don't say that
for marketing reasons
almond blood would be cooler
I think also
what confused me
is that milk-ing is like a verb
you probably milk an almond
so it's like
you soak an almond
almond like
liquid residue
almond juice
would be
well you don't juice it either
you don't exactly juice it
almond runoff
it's almond runoff
it's more like a tea
almond stew
I'm gonna try
I have a number of verbal tics
that I want to avoid
when filming today
and one of them is
I don't want to not say um
I want to not say like
I want to not say um
I want to not go
after I laugh which I always do and I hate that
you go what after you laugh
what after you laugh
did you not
like I suck in air through my teeth
I don't know listen for it
I remember you talking about that before
I did talk about how much I hate it
yeah I just have
just make sure to blow instead of suck
I suck in air through my teeth
in an audible way
but um
like pausing and saying um
and ah is like the worst
and like like like
I should really avoid those
I mean I cannot
to some extent I can edit them out
later um
but
if they're all through
if they're peppered all through my speech then that's bad
you might have to do multiple tics then
because it's so natural
I think it's um
the
like uh
um
uh
or
beep boop
you're making space for yourself to think of the next word
so like if you have a sentence
in your brain
uh you can say it
yeah
uh I can I can I can always
just pause and think what am I going to say next
and then formulate
that and then say it and then edit out
the pause
uh
that's true that's true
um I want to
yeah
I want to sound a little more
considered
I don't want to sound completely like off the cuff
I don't have a script
but I do have notes
that I'm going to be referring to
I think I feel like I'm going into too much detail
you know what
uh nevermind
I don't want to talk about this anymore
people are going to guess what it is
I've got a small
story it's called
I forgot my steam
password and it sucks
hmm
but then I remembered it but here's the story
that was a great story
the story goes I forgot
my steam password I'm like okay
I do the steam recovery like oh I
can't remember my password
put in your email and
we'll send you an email about it
but first do this
capture
it says click on fire hydrants
I click all of them
I guess I missed one I click
the crosswalks I click the traffic lights
I click the buses
it just keeps giving me captures
and after I've done like eight
it says invalid response
you redo the capture
yeah
so I do another eight captures
and I do it again
I make sure to not make any mistakes
and it's not right
again
and then I do it again and again
and then I'm like you've done too many captures wrong
you're probably a robot
try again tomorrow try again later
and so I couldn't
I couldn't play my game
I couldn't play my games
and the capture
system is fucked
and I was like okay there's something
definitely wrong you failed the reverse
turning test I did
there's something wrong
I realized like
there was no reason it didn't work
there was no reason on my end that it didn't work
it just wasn't going through
and so I tried different browsers
for this capture thing
no browsers worked
I tried looking up like
what the fuck
what do I do about this
and the
you have a problem with capture so you go on google
and you type in what the fuck
what the fuck
well they're watching me at all times
they know what's going on
they probably do yeah
so
I look and there are like tutorials
like oh steen giving you this problem
from like
2017, 2019, 2020, 2021
this problem is still around
capture just sometimes doesn't work
and
there is no solution that
worked
okay there's no solution
I guess I have to go to steam
some other way and like ask them
for help but they don't have
customer support for steam
you go to their thing and it's like
okay I need help getting my account back
and they send me to the same page
where it's like input your email address
or your phone number and
do this capture and that's where it all breaks down
so I was like okay
I guess I gotta go to
twitter and at
steam hoping that they would respond
but like it's steam
it's valve they're not gonna fucking say anything
I did make a tweet
but then I remembered my password and I got in
so it's like
all for nothing
well I mean what it does
tell me is that if I do forget my password
there's no way I can
there's nothing I could do if I could call
a number if I could email somebody
that'd be something but if the
capture doesn't work and there's no way
for the capture to work
well I will forever be
locked out of my steam account and I don't know how
what about would do anything about it
what about some sort of do you have like
two factor authentication with like Authy
or something I do but like it
asked me to like if I want to
change my password I need to do the capture
hmm
I couldn't figure it out
maybe there's a way to do it
but it sucks because
so wait I don't understand
why did the captures fail
I don't know I did the capture
like it comes up with a little white box
so click on these things until there's
none left and then you say
next and then you do it again
a few times and then it's like
okay then the box disappears
and then on the page
where it says like I'm not
a robot and like
all that an error message comes up
saying you did not
the capture could not be completed
there's like a string of
like numbers and letters
like here's the ID
for this error
but it's a different every time so it's like
an individual case thing
um
I would have taken a picture of it
but I forgot
if it ever happens again
I will
scream about it
I've done the capture and I've seen
um
fire hydrants, traffic lights
crosswalks
pick out the bus
pick out the plane
pick out the sea plane
pick out the train
I saw a new one
the other day
recently I've been seeing
it's like pick out the giraffes
pick out the
horse made of clouds
was one
pick out the
horse facing right or horse facing left
uh
and then the creepiest one that I
really hate is pick out the lion
with its eyes open or the lions
with its eyes closed
and those are creepy because
the images that they show like they show lions
but
I think a lot of them are like they've been
digitally altered to have the lions
eyes like appear open or closed
and like they look weird they look almost
like their eyes have been sewn shut sometimes
these uncanny pictures of lions
uh
and I'm not a fan of them
why does AI need to know
whether a lion has its eyes open or not
what are they doing over there
because it's something that a robot
is bad at
identifying
in theory
but like I understand the road stuff
is like practical oh we can use all that data
from all the billions of people
finishing captures we collect that data
we can say okay robot
this is what a fire hydrant looks like
uh the humans have verified it
and the human the robot will be like
okay now I know what that looks like
I can drive a car now
but like what is the lion for
I know
I know how to like stare down a lion now
what what what purpose
wait a minute is that
is that why it's like fire hydrants
traffic lights crosswalks
it's to train AI to drive
it's to train AI to understand
and recognize things on the road
so it doesn't like drive wrong
and that's why the the images
are often like very hard to
determine for a robot but like like
they're blurry but a human can understand
through context like yeah that part is a crosswalk
wait a minute
okay hang on I don't understand
this because
it knows which
pictures are crosswalks
and fire hydrants like it knows
the answer and it knows
and that's it's using this to verify that
you are human so how is it learning
anything from having you pick out the answers
that it already knows
um probably because the images
were like screened
by a human first before they go into the
machine then it already
knows no no no I mean like
a person says okay this is
well
you know I've heard
that that is the why it does that
I don't know how it works that way
maybe maybe like cross
like maybe it's like a
like a um
the majority of people say this
therefore that's the correct
one
like it it calculates based on
all the inputs
I suppose maybe
something yeah it could be
it could be something like that
like there's it doesn't like it only
it decides what's a fire hydrant based
on consensus yeah that might be
true
that doesn't explain how
like the first person who sees
a capture
did they just get to decide
like they click
like nobody's clicked on this capture before
this person clicks on
this it says it's a fire hydrant
the computer doesn't have any other data
to cross reference it with to know
whether that is the consensus or not so it just says
yeah you're right yeah there would
either have to be one guy or some guy
who is picking out the images
in the first place and being like this is
a picture of a fire hydrant
or there would it would have to be
showing you images
that might have fire hydrants in them
and then letting like internet
consensus builds
the consensus about where they the fire hydrant
is
maybe it's like a computer
in like a self-driving car
is taking pictures and sending them off
like I don't know exactly
what this is can we verify it with humans
okay like this is
a traffic light
it's like the car is approaching a crosswalk
and there are kids walking across the crosswalk
and as it's driving it's like
hmm take a picture send it off to capture
I need to verify whether there are kids and I need
to swerve
I need to know right now
it's doing 70
or super computer
hang on
waiting for a consensus
waiting for a consensus to be reached
we just got to lock people out of their camps
so they do captures quick
make sure the capture doesn't work
so they can do it over and over again
uh
it doesn't work
the technology will never work
AI will never replace
artists
you know I had an idea
what if
the story of John Henry
but
it's about artists and
paint and art AI
you know
I don't know John Henry
John Henry was a
I think he was probably a real person
who has been mythologized somewhat
he's sort of an American folk
character who
his thing is that he was a railroad worker
and I guess they
invented a fricking machine
that was going to put all the railroad workers out of work
and he like
was so good at railroad
building that he proved that man could
beat the railroad machine
because he built better than the machine
I don't know whatever that's the story
these horses coming over here thinking they can pull our carts
better than I can
well so then
yeah
I think he died
I think the story is like
he drove those railroad sparks
so hard that yeah he beat the machine
but he fucking died doing it
but he proved something
god damn it
he proved that
if you grow a human for so many years
and then they die after one attempt
they can beat a robot but it's not very good
not very
sustainable
according to legend John Henry's prowess
as a steel driver was measured in a race
against a steam powered
rock drilling machine
a race that he won only to die in victory
with hammer in hand as his heart gave out from stress
okay
that's really just saying the robot
wins because it did die
I think the idea there
is not so much that
like oh he proved that man is
better than machine
it's not so much an applejack
at the end of the super speedy
cider squeezy episode I was right all along
you gotta make cider with love
you gotta drive those rail spikes with love
only a human can do that
robots don't know how to drive rail spikes
with love
it's more of just sort of mythologizing
or remembering
this guy
lived and died
history
the tide of progress
ended up making this guy irrelevant
but he won one
glorious symbolic victory
before he was
overtaken by the march of time
you know
it's not a practical victory
it's a
symbolic one
the whole discussion of AI art
it absolutely will replace
some kinds of artists
jobs
you can't replace art because it's like
an emotional
practice you do it because you feel good
or something you feel emotions
when you do it
the capital
you gain from having a job in the arts
that might
be in problem
that's a capitalism thing though
we gotta destroy capitalism
you see
and then we can do all the art we want
and then the computers can do the advertising
stuff
they can make the movie posters
and the illustrations on the books
and then we can go in there
and throw in the wall with our shit
and then they
and the computers
can use the algorithm to
advertise that
to steal everyone's data
and put the ads into their minds
so that our art can be
so everyone
so every little twitter artist
can have the AI
can maximize the algorithm so that
everyone's getting blasted with art ads all the time
everyone gets exposure
exposure's free now
no one has to work for it anymore
we've decommodified exposure
that's
space communism
fully automated luxury space communism for me
anyway
so much exposure
that nobody even
understands or knows anything
no one can separate
noise from signal anymore
so there's no point
there was already no point
true
I really do like
my mid-journey
avatar though
I really do like the
oblivionfall made some more
he made some more gorgeous ben saint
and slime city
AI mid-journey
images and he sent them to me and they look so good
mid-journey really is good at certain things
it really does
yeah it's good at like making a sci-fi
like sci-fi
sci-fi landscapes fantasy land it's good at
painting landscapes
it's good at like figures
but not faces
I mean
I could see it on like the front
cover of like a thriller
sci-fi book
where there's aliens
and slimes
and it's all fucked
yeah the man with the hood
and the face but he doesn't have a face
it's not it's not good at
depicting characters
expressions
people
you know what I have to
pee do you mind if I go do that
I gotta this is almond milk damn it
you know Matt in that
in that one episode of tasting
history max miller reads a
excerpt from like a medieval doctor
who is extolling the benefits
of almond milk and one of the things he says
about it is that it provoketh urine
it soothes
the belly and provoketh urine
that's what it's doing for me right now
alright be back in one
sec
one little second
so for the viewers at home
you may if I've
done a bad job of editing
my audio you may have heard
my mouse clicking
over and over and over again
and that's because I'm playing RuneScape
right now
I'm covertly gaining
lots and lots of iron ore
in RuneScape by clicking on it
it's very quiet so hopefully it's not
a problem
I'm gonna noise remove it I'm gonna click
remove it before I send it over to Eleazar
but if it's still there
that's why and I don't
I don't
apologize for it
it's my grind
it's my Sigma grind
you must respect me
and my stupid stupid ways
I've got
190,000
experience left until I'm level
83 mining
and let's see on my bank
how much iron ore I have
I have 68,981
iron ore
are you RuneScaping
I'm mining
I'm scaping
are you mining and crafting
in RuneScape?
not crafting yet
my crafting level is 35
okay
it's gotta get higher before you craft
I don't think I need to do crafting
crafting is like
it's an odd skill
because
it's just sort of
like a bits and bobs, knickknacks
a skill where
it doesn't have any specific
thing it's like you can have
a skill like wood cutting
and that makes sense you cut trees down
and it's how good you can cut trees
but crafting is like
you can make jewelry
you can make leather
items
you can craft
bow strings
you can have a look
you can weave
you can make pottery
pottery, glass, blowing
and it's like
they're all under one
that's true
remember that character from pop culture
okay sorry
so yeah it's like all of these different things
so in RuneScape you could
spin a bunch of clay pots
and somehow be very very good afterwards
at making
gold jewelry for no reason
because you didn't actually do
any of jewelry before
it's all in the same skill
I see
sorry to change the subject
but I did have a thought while I was peeing
and that is about the video
and that is that
if it goes on really long
if I'm recording it and it's getting
really long
there are some natural breakpoints
in it that I could decide
this is going to have to be in parts
so
I'll end the part here
and that would be a pretty natural place
if I move in between parts
who cares
I would still make the video
one big video because people love
seeing that long number
that's the plan
you would still cut it together into one
I would cut it together into one big
video file yes
they could be chapters but
people like seeing a big chunky video
so
this is something I was wondering
do you think that people prefer
one big
let's just say six hour video
two hour part one
part two part three videos
yes because
much less clicking is involved
and
the
if they want to rewatch it
they just have to do one click
and also it's just a fact
that part one of anything
will have more views than part two or three
that's
true the click through rate
that is true
so you might as well just put them all together
I think you're probably right
I guess the one thing
that's scary about that
is that like should the video ever become
flagged
or like be
decided that it violates something
it would be the whole thing would go
instead of just a part of it
but like
I mean flagged in what way
I don't know
like copyright I think there's ways you can cut
little bits out like audio
or like a tiny scene
that I don't know
I mean that's probably not going to be in
YouTube but it's not the best
better than it used to be
yeah
you know I've been noticing
stock
YouTube music
a lot
recently
just the first example
that comes to my head is like
the sad music that plays sometimes
in
the action button reviews
I've heard I've started hearing it in other
places and I think
it's like YouTube stock music
and that's
weird
I guess I had assumed that it was
a bespoke sort of like
picked out specifically
for this video but no
it's just what YouTube tells you
to use
yeah it is always a bit weird when
like one YouTube creator
has their intro music being this
song and you're like oh yeah
it's that creator and then
anyone can use it it's royalty free
it's a fucking Kevin MacLeod
it's like
that's the summoning salt videos
right there's like the Kevin
I think the summoning the iconic summoning
salt song is just a default
YouTube song
I don't know that that's
the case I feel like it's like a video
a song that's on
YouTube
maybe it's also part of the YouTube because like when you do
like
a library that you can access
through YouTube that they say
oh here's a bunch of things you can download and use
yeah and like the benefit
the benefit of that is that all the stuff that's
on there is stuff you know won't get flag
yeah
which is good which is like a big deal and pretty good
honestly
I can never be able to go
through that and like find anything
I just use like
very quiet video game soundtrack still
I totally understand
why that's useful and
and it makes perfect
sense however
when I the the sad music
from action button when I when I heard that somewhere
else and I realized that it was not
a like really
a personal choice
I it retroactively
was like cheap and I was like oh
he just picked it from a list and that's lame
thought it
was pretty effective in context but now
now I hate it
I feel less
I feel less about it
it's I don't know where that
royalty free music is from there's lots of
places you can get royalty free music
that work on YouTube that aren't from
YouTube
and
like
like red litter media huff in the bag
all those songs they use for that
you can find them there are playlists
people have found have made of like oh
this is the
little piano bit with the
huff in the bag
skit stuff
they use that all the time
but because it's like a relatively obscure
royalty free music
channel or whatever people don't tend to
find that when they're looking for royalty
free stuff
you can have a bit of an identity
as long as you're looking as long as
you're searching for something
you haven't heard before
no I think I do think that
the summoning salt one is just a default
but I mean he nevertheless
sort of made it his iconic
track
it's irrevocably linked
in people's minds with summoning salt
I guess there's room
for inspired choices
I guess
something I'm always
impressed when I
am watching a YouTube video and there's music
and at some point either they say it
or I realize by reading the description
like oh this guy made their own music
like the background
for this guy's videos
is like he's also a
musician and he made all his own
oh yeah like
Geo wizards the straight line
mission guy
all that 8 bit or
Commodore 64 sound and music
he made it himself
it's like wow cool
so iconic
yeah
a skill that I don't have and so I respect
it
I always thought I could make music but
like
I'm not like
I'm mostly good at guitar
and I don't really know how to like make a
whole big song
so I would do like acoustic guitar things
and I could do that but it's like
acoustic guitar is a certain
vibe you can't use it just
anywhere
you know I tried to make
I made a contest entry for the
um
that Homestuck music contest
the one that ended up being
it was like the troll
and all an ancestor
themed it was like two
two CDs
and each one had like each
one CD had a track for every troll
and then the other CD had a track for every
ancestor
that ended up being
but I made a track
as a contest entry for that contest
didn't win obviously didn't get into
the CD
how'd you make it
I used um
it wasn't Fruity Loops
it was shit it was some
free like you know
track editing
software I made it
and this is I made that
on my laptop as I was working
as like the cashier
at an ice cream store
parlor
huh that's some Ben St.
Law
yeah I've probably never mentioned that but yeah I
remember making that
track this was probably
shortly after I had graduated from
college
and I was working
for this one summer I didn't have anything
to do and so I
my mom like
she saw a hiring sign
in this one ice cream store
and I was like okay whatever and I went
and I worked there for a few months
and I remember
I would bring my laptop to work whenever there was
downtime I would fuck around on my laptop
and one of the things I fucked around at was
I don't remember what
music software it was but it was something
I could get for free and it wasn't Fruity Loops
and
I don't know
I tried to make my track
because the contest
prompt didn't specify
that this was going to be about trolls
it said that each of the entries would be
themed for a character
like
I tried to pick a different character
I tried to pick a character that probably
most people wouldn't make a track for
so I picked Typheus
the Denizen
and so I made my track
if I remember it I wish I could find it
I don't know where it would be
now maybe on an old laptop
I guess
it sort of was
I tried to make
I only used wind instruments
or I mostly used wind instruments because
he's the air
he's the breath guy
I sort of made an organ
I started it with
a bombastic
organ intro
and then I think I introduced a little
drum beat and I introduced
a little
melody over top of that
the background was
organs
wind organs and I think I had pan pipes
I think the melody was pan pipes over
organs and a drum beat
wind themed
because John plays
because John plays the wind organ
the pipe organ in the palace of
Typheus
I've heard
there's like the
I think Typheus does have a track
somewhere
in one of the albums
yeah I feel like they made an album
of like the denizens
and there's a bunch of songs
fan made songs for that
wouldn't it be funny if it turned out it was
my track
yeah I'm wondering what if they just
didn't credit you or didn't contact you
oh this is good
oh I think it was the land of
fans and music
that I think
yeah that could be it
that's about the
medium and the planets
which could also be about the denizens
I feel like I've seen
songs
based on them somewhere
if you can find
if there is an official
Homestuck song
for Typheus
I would like to hear it
if any thoughts on whether mine was better
okay well I can look in my folder
or if any if
this is to the listeners
if a listener knows
what album this was on
oh man I always really liked the denizens
I like them a lot
they're so mysterious
I still don't know anything really
they're very
mysterious the way they're
the way they're depicted with like you can't
they're sort of like
there's a very biblical angel
thing about how
you can't look at their faces
like the way they're depicted as
like
their face is just
this light that you can't
look at
it's like you can't comprehend
what it really is
until like
there was a
there was like a flash
where
Caliborn
was fighting his
I think it was a game over or something
y'all the bear
yeah he was fighting that in like a flash
maybe it was
it was one of the things in access I can't remember
but for a brief moment
you do see a little bit of a face
and I'm like oh
well I remember
hmm I remember there's a big um
it's not a flash
but it's a big animated page
where like you see
the whole body
of it reaching up and you see like
the head with just this light coming out
and Caliborn is like standing
really small in front of it
looking up at it with his gun out
that's when he like first
enters the chamber
yeah I think I remember that you do
see a little bit of face
you do see a little bit it's like um
Caliborn in his sprite form
is jumping around and hitting him with a crowbar
and stuff and then
Yalla Baoth does like a big beam
thing and you can see it sort of like
screaming like
hmm and the the beams
like rotate around like it's
a bullet hell
there's there's happens for a second
does it look like
you know
he in like in the in the browser
icon and in like the statues
he's just sort of got a sort of problem
sleuth like
non-descript face
no I think it was more like
like the detailed
hmm I can't
remember what it looked like I remember it feeling like
kind of gross
being like oh
hmm
now I'm
curious I don't remember
it could be game over
it could be
fucking
the one where everybody fights
collide it could be that
does he fight Yalla Baoth
and collide
I think that maybe
maybe that one and maybe another one where
Caliborn is depicted fighting
for like a few seconds
hmm and then it
goes back to whatever else is happening
I
this is just reminds me
how
disappointing it is
that like the actual like game
of spurb and like all the mythology
around it gets like so little
attention at the end of the game
or it's like towards the end of home
suck yeah
it's my favorite shit
and it's just it's just not
the priority
oh
oh you see
I think I see it
oh yeah it sucks
okay is this it
um
yeah
if this is it
I think this is it and it's bad
oh my god
yeah I saw that
what a head in my head
that blue bit wasn't there
I think it's mostly just the white
the black lines drawn
I guess it's a little bit
blue lit is like it flies
off really quick but yeah that's the face
I guess it's a little bit
it's it's like um
what do you call him what's the bad guy
from problem sleuth
mobster kingpin
mobster kingpin I think it's
meant to resemble that and like yeah
I right yeah
it's got a bit too much detail
it looks like a snake because it's a snake
it's just sort of makes it more
of a beast and less of a cool
like um
yeah like cool
I don't know magical
undecipherable energy
being much much cooler
when you didn't
know
you know what this looks like it looks like that
that fucking rick and morty joke
where the sun
is screaming all the time
oh yeah they go to a planet
and it's like oh this is great and then
the sun rises and it screams
yeah
you are right it does look like that
it's silly it makes me
I think it's meant to be silly
I think it
I think it's meant to be
dumb but I just
think it's a bad choice
I don't know if it's meant to be dumb because
like in the moment it's like a really hype
like oh Caliburn's fighting everyone's fighting
so much stuff is happening and it's like
I could imagine somebody
who just doesn't understand the importance
of mystery being like
oh but we've never seen like the face
of one of these guys
maybe this would be a good time
we could see the face at last
and now we can put that in a wiki
and now everybody knows how many teeth they
have
the tone of collide is
kind of comical though
so I think this face
is meant to be
a little bit goofy
I would make it goofier
I
if I was gonna do that
I would make it as goofy as a problem
sleuth face
oh I see yeah
yeah I
I think I
I'm pretty sure this is a mobster kingpin reference
which I get it
I get
the desire to do that
with your final boss monsters so you use
a callback to the other big
final boss monster from the other story
I get it
I get it but
it's bad for Yalda Bea
it's a very
it's if
the denizens... Yalda Gaoth
more like Yalda Gaoth
the denizens had so much like build up
and then like
I don't know if you're gonna like
subvert their build up by having them look
goofy yeah I think
to have it be like such a
fleeting throwaway moment
in the course of this one
it's very
if they wanted to reveal the face
if they wanted to really reveal the face
for some reason
it should be like a huge
impressive panel
it should be
it should be a
it should have been a moment
not a thing you could literally like
miss and not even notice
because it's like every depiction has been like
we don't see what's really
going on in the interaction between
the denizen and the kid
yeah
and earlier on we only hear about
what happens and you know John dies
because he goes to see Tytheus
mm-hmm
and we don't see any of that interaction
so fucking cool who know what what happened
why what was it like nobody
John doesn't remember because the version of him
that lived didn't do that
so mysterious
this this this this only this only takes away
this only takes away
some of the appeal I still
I still really like the denizens
I think they're a really cool element of the
story another another cool
part of spurb lore that
the homestuck that ladder
homestuck seems
almost obsessed with not
paying any attention to
yep yeah
yeah
but that is a conversation that has been had a billion
times I know I know
I'll never get over it
it's never it's never gonna be okay
it's never gonna be
okay what happens
well
uh speaking of
comics yeah I've been working
a little bit on Clarissa
oh um
there was a bit of there's a bit of a script
thing where I'm like I had
a few sketches
and I wanted to
something was off about the way
the story ended so I
I had to like go back and like rearrange
panels and add some new panels into
the sketches and do some script
stuff so that's
that's something not a lot yet
I'm not like really sitting down and like
okay
let's go let's draw
it's a lot of thinking and being like how do I
make the story like so
okay like
not bad this is what I'm
aiming for is that it's not stupid
that is the challenge
yeah
but I think I made a bit of
a not a breakthrough but just sort of like an
improvement so that's good
it is not going to be
too long now before I can sketch
the rest of
the pages and then I will have a page
count that I can tell people
and then I will draw it all
you have a
okay wait so this is chapter
two or three
of Clarissa
I don't remember let me go to giveandtake.site
yeah
.site to find out
you're going to definitely want to hit up
giveandtake.site
giveandtake.site there she is Clarissa
Gunsmoke and the bandit king
um also the top
of the page got my site sucked
so much um
come on
show me the show me the money oh no
it's so inefficient
I just want to I don't see the chapter
page how many chapters
do we got
was that button knocked over there okay forget
it one mile
um so we have this first chapter
and then the second chapter
we got three chapters
scrolling down
and I think it's three chapters
yes so this will be chapter four and onwards
I think I have more than a hundred pages
sketched
um more like 90 actually
but uh there's a lot still
to sketch
so who knows
I don't
I'm sorry wait
you see you already have 90
pages let me let me double
check it's probably not 90 it's probably like
50 but it's
sizeable amount sketched and then I still
need to like sketch the last
bit wait wait you've got
50 that are sketched but not
finished not finished
not public yet yes oh wow
that's a lot
yeah I'm not very efficient
with my writing how many are done
and published now
three chapters worth so that's
like how many pages like
20 pages a chapter
uh so yeah
something like that so you're gonna make
more than double it with all this
oh it's new possibly
possibly yeah sounds sounds
like it's headed that way
hmm interesting
hmm so I am
I'm feeling pretty good about
uh making some
progress on it pretty soon
did you ever finish those commissions
no
oh jeez okay
I still gotta do like three
alright so I have been working
on them it's just uh
I look at the commission thing and I'm like
please draw anything and I'm like but
but I can't
but I can't draw anything
not I understand
yeah I I should do those
first I will do those first
I've just been like
like the
I was talking to my therapist and being like
I don't know what I'm doing
and she said like what do you want to do
what do you need what do you want to
like I can't I
not gonna like remember exactly
what the conversation was but the
sure the result was
um I should start
things that I want to
get done rather than waiting for myself
to finish this one thing
I think it gets stuck
too often and I'm like I want to do things
linearly I had the commissions earlier
I said I would do all of the commissions
and then work on other things
so and because of
that I have just not done anything
and so like if I do the
Clarissa stuff at least
I'm getting something done and maybe
it'll just make it easier for me to
get into a working mood and
organize my life and get everything
else done I see so
like in the case that like
yeah
if you're not getting the commissions done
rather than not do anything else
until they're done you might as well
do something else yeah
I see that makes yeah I mean sure
that makes it make sense
not that like huge brain
thing that's just right it is
a consistent problem I love
doing things in order
and I love finishing things before moving on
because I feel like I'm gonna get overwhelmed
with like juggling too many different projects
it is good to do
if possible
it's a good instinct
to have in general
yeah I mean I was starting
to feel bad as well because
I had this idea to make a little video
about my RuneScape thing
and that was being like well
you should do the commissions first before you do that
right
but if you did that
but it would only be a little thing
but if you did that there would just be no video
you would never make it
I would never make the video yeah
so like I forced myself to make a video
because I wanted to do it
and I would feel bad about not
doing it and it wasn't gonna
take that long and it didn't because
I didn't make it a big
edited thing
it was just like a little explanation
few PNGs on the screen that's all you need
so that's done I feel good
that that is done
and now I will do the commissions
and work on Clarissa
at the same time
yeah
oh
oh yeah
yeah yeah
woo
I need to go toilet quick
I will be a moment
you know what me too
lol
I am back
ah boy
okay scared
scary
hey
you know
when you're waiting for a bus
and there's not been a bus in a while
and then suddenly
two buses come at the same time
that's what just happened
in the toilet
what?
because I had a shit
and then suddenly after I was done
it was followed by another shit
what?
you know what I mean
I
yeah you ever get that
I guess
it's like it was like one meal
comes down
and then a different meal
I mean I would probably describe that
as I
as one shit that I just had
I thought I was done
I guess that's exactly the same
as what I said
that's how I would phrase it
but I get what you're saying
I was gonna say that took a while
I was gonna say
my headphones fell out
I must grab
a spell suit
okay I can hear again
hooray
what were we talking about
jeez what were we talking about
we talked about Homestuck then
I talked about Clarissa
oh I think that was it
I think we were talking about Clarissa when you left
we talked about my video
that's my big thing for the day
my move
oh
frickin yeah I said last week
or something
that I had really screwed up
and by not getting a truck
and that's true
this blows
there was no
there was no truck available
in Boston like at all
anywhere I could not find one
my mom found one
in
a town that is closer to
where I grew up
and it's like an hour away
so I'm gonna have to take a train there
pick up a truck
like an hour away and then drive it back
here
fortunately I only have to drive it one way
because I can drop it off
at a different location
but yeah I have to drive this fucking moving
truck on a highway
for like an hour so that's gonna suck
and plus they charge you by the mile so that's a bit
it's gonna cost me like 50 bucks
for nothing
yeah but it's all
it's all I could get
maybe you should learn to live
smaller
less items
like the Buddha
I don't have that many items Gib
I called
U-Haul
and I was trying to get something more
nearby and I asked the guy
I was like
what if I just rented one on like before
he was like no we don't have anything on the 30th
I was like what if I rented one before
what if I got one on the 29th
and he was like well you'd have to have it back the next day
and I said what if I didn't
and the guy was like
well then some family
that needed a truck wouldn't have it
and I said yeah
but what would happen to me though
and he was like well
I guess we'd find you and I was like
hmm okay
how much?
honestly I mean
fine by me
kind of
decided it was easier to just
drive an hour that's fine
I wouldn't feel good about depriving
someone else of their rental
hmm
but I'd cope
yeah I'd be okay though
um
yeah so
that's what I gotta do
not tomorrow but the next day Tuesday
I'm gonna have to get up early on Tuesday
morning
because apparently
frickin my landlord asked me
when I'm gonna be out and I said
well the lease says the 30th so I guess
I'm gonna leave on the 30th
and she emailed me and said
like
the guys that I've been saying
have been doing renovations on my place
they're gonna be, she said they're gonna be here
on the 30th early in the morning
on the 30th they're gonna be like
drilling into my wall or something
so
I don't know I guess I'm gonna have to work
around them or something
that's gonna
be annoying
I don't
I don't know
I feel like she
I feel like she might be overstepping her bounds
a little bit lately sending dudes
to like
spend time in our rooms to like
do work on our walls and stuff
I feel like maybe she's not allowed to do that
while we're still living here
yeah
but whatever it's inconsiderate
at the very least
but whatever it's too late
I'm gonna leave now and I'll be gone soon
I
I think I successfully
hoodwinked her out of a month's rent though
I don't think I'm gonna have to pay
that last month's rent
nice
yeah so
pretty good honestly
that's
you should leave
like a
a calling card saying that you didn't do that
you didn't pay last month's rent
that's like haha you've been swindled
by the great Ben saying that's a great idea
there's no way that that
could be used against me in any kind of civil
settlement
leave a card
saying um
yeah I did cry
I stole here's some money that I stole from you
here's the exact amount here's how I did
it here's my new contact information
in case you want to reach me to talk
about it
bye
mm-hmm it's just like what a great criminal
does when they steal the priceless jewel
that's what they put their calling card
and they laugh in the face of the
authorities mm-hmm that's yeah
that that's why they're great criminals
criminal masterminds is because they make it
really easy to catch them
they put their alter ego they say Batman
was here except Batman is not a criminal
no if Batman were really good
he would just leave a card that says
the exact address
of the Batcave detailed instructions
for entering it his name
security number
etc etc that would be
if he was really the world's greatest detective
that's I think what would happen
man oh man
so that's gonna suck
I don't
they're like oh somebody stole the crown jewels
or like they opened the safe and like
oh it's gone
what's this and somebody's driver's license
with their face
and all their information
I have a
I have a mattress I have I replaced
my mattress at some point
because my old one was gross
so I still have it like
it's sort of like against a wall
I never I never got rid of it
so
I'm considering like
I'm not exactly sure how to dispose
of a mattress
there's probably a right way I don't think you can just
have the fucking trash guys pick it up
on the sidewalk
but
I have some
I think I might have to pay to get it
disposed of and alternatives
that I'm rolling around
in my mind are one
leave it on the sidewalk
anyway because
what are they gonna do
come and find me no
nobody's gonna know that it's my mattress
someone the landlord
will have to deal with it
to
maybe just leave it in
the room of one of the other guys that has already
moved out
just put it in there and put it on the floor
and leave and she won't know
that I left it
uh
what would they do
I think the second one
might be better
because maybe the person moving in
is like oh cool free mattress
yeah
possibly
yeah I might just do that
I don't really see any downside
and it means I don't have to deal with it
it's a bad
mattress and I don't think anyone would really want
this mattress that's why I replaced it
but
um
what's the right way
how
to dispose of a
mattress
you beat the shit out of it
discard literally
oh yeah discarded mattresses
and boxers can be notoriously difficult to
manage they're expensive to transport
so recycling
or use
okay mattresses and textiles are
banned from disposal or
transport for disposal
okay most mattress
and box spring components can be easily
disassembled and recycled
okay
so spring mattress
mattress recycling
incentive programs
I think it is a spring mattress
donate
you can donate to a charity
find a commercial mattress recycler
okay there there might be
there might be a municipal
program for like collecting mattresses
for recycling
I don't see my town on here though
where you live you go to eat
the mattress to get rid of it
I don't see
Alston or Brighton on here
so that's
hmmmm
Cambridge is not too far
whatever
I'll leave it in someone else's room
fuck it
uhhhh
I hate this landlady
I hope she has more problems in the future
I hope she has to deal with it
I consider that a
bonus is that it would be annoying for her
um
yeah
anyway those are my moving
concerns
I'm tired just thinking
about it
hmm I'm gonna have a nice long nap
on this mattress about it
because of how tired I am
I don't want to sleep on this mattress
it doesn't smell great
my new mattress is great
it's delightful
um
hey
what is
HD
resolution
high definition
that's HD
1920 by 1080
ok well my camera
will record in
uhhhh hang on
hang on hang on
my camera can record in
ok 2
560 by 14
which is not 4k
ok apparently 4k
is
3 by 2160
I assumed it would be 4000
yeah it's the 38
but it's close enough to 4 so I think
that's why
so my
my camera will it will not record in 4k
but it will record in like
in above HD
which is
fine I think I kind of wish I had
I kind of wish I could film in 4k
I think a little more resolution would be good
but I feel like
I feel like the expectation
is not that videos need to be
in 4k on youtube
I don't think anyone's going to be like
this isn't in 4k I can't watch this
um
yeah it's still like HD
is good enough
from most anything
yeah
I'm surprised
I could film in this
above HD resolution
and a minute of footage
is about 125
megabytes
so like
15 minutes of footage is like
1.8 gigs
and my phone is pretty empty
so it has like 40 gigs of storage on it
so I can store like
I can store like
uh
I think um
I think 30 minutes by
I can store like 300 minutes
I can store like 5 hours of
footage on that thing
that is quite a big
amount
my phone
I don't know how much my phone has actually
so I might have to like
set it to start recording
let it go and then I'll have
I have to
it will
I want to record it in chunks because
if anything happens I don't want to lose everything
the downside
to that is that
I can only tell it to restart recording
up to like 10 times
so if I'm recording like
15 minute segments
I can only record 10 of them
and also there's a little bit of a break
like it's not a smooth continue
I check this there's a little bit of a cut
each time it stops recording and starts again
so I will just have
to keep an eye on the time I'll like
I'll start it at exactly
a 30 minute point on the clock
and I'll just have to keep my eye on the time
and any time it's getting to be
an hour or half hour
I'll just have to know like there's going to be a cut here
I should like wait to start my next sentence
until
until the half hour mark
passes and then I can start again
mmm
that's my plan
I hope it works
okay thank you
I'm rambling
now
I have
been thinking a lot
about how this all works
it's very complicated
literally just to like
this is all just in service
of just like setting up a camera on a tripod
and telling it to record
I have had to consider
all of these things
it's so hard
being a content creator
being a successful content creator
like Ben St
it do be like that
yeah
well hey
we've been going for an hour 40
what do you think about going to the
Ask PCP questions
uh
sure
I can't think of anything
off the top of my head else that I need to
there's only one thing
and it's that I'm going to be doing
like Sunday assessments
of my work
there's another thing the therapist told me to start doing
Sunday assessments
assessment time
where I go over the previous week
and what I
accomplished
and it's not supposed to be like
an opinion piece
it's just sort of like
factual information what was done
and then make a plan
for the next week so what am I going to work on
next week and I feel like
having like a time
a thing happening an event
a Sunday assessment period
will help me to be like alright
let's actually like plan out the next week
so today is going to be my first one of those
and I hope it works
for productivity
makes sense
makes sense so
it's just like you write
a list of everything that was done
yeah I just sort of go over
the things that I accomplished
um
and not to like make it into like a
like a
talking down to or like a telling off
like oh you didn't meet the quota you motherfucker
it's not about
punishing myself it's just about like
keeping track I suppose of what
I was able to do
so that when I plan things
going forward I can adjust
plans to be like okay
uh
do less work because it was too much
or do more work because
uh you can
and you or whatever
I don't know how to do exactly
I'm gonna figure it out but like I like the idea
I like the idea of
of
getting a little document
little like clipboard and I like
writing down notes
ah yes
my life is
within my control because you see I wrote down
a lot of numbers
yeah makes
make sense to me checks out
uh oh fuck wait a minute
I need more caffeine it's been
four hours since I had any caffeine
and that's
just not gonna work for me
okay
alright
is that fine
that's that's fine but I'm drinking
caffeine right now I'm drinking a cup of tea
cup of cup of Yorkshire gold
a cup of
have a
have a cup of you
perver
huh
when people say cup of
I've heard like Hagrid and Harry Potter
he says have a cup of
is that just short for a cup of tea yeah
what do you think you meant
no I mean that's what I thought it meant
sounds dumb I don't like it
finish your damn sentence you freak
yeah no we're all about
conjugations or whatever
hideous
like uh saw right would be
it is alright
well I mean that's that's like pretty normal
Saul Goodman yeah
Saul Goodman sure
um that I mean that one
there's more extreme examples I can't
really think of them though it's the top of my head
but like yeah
shorten those words words suck
who cares just get that info
get that brain chemistry
longer words longer words for
longer content make the video
longer make it last
forever make the video never end
see this is a capitalism in action
you're elongating your vocabulary
170,000
hours of lo-fi
hip-hop beats to study and chill too
please make those longest
words we can think of in our
hip-hop beats um
return to monkey grunt
okay let's uh
let's look
at some there was actually some
some questions we missed
last week
yeah well did they come out
during recording or
they came out a little later
uh so it's not our fault
uh but I want to I do want to read
them actually one of them
is if you can believe it
it's I think it's a it's an art
post from new
so we'll have to here we go
oh my god
yeah it looks pretty
oh that's that it's so tall
substantial actually
let me zoom the fucking
wait a minute is it
this is a fucking
it's a whole damn manga
yeah
this oh it's a
yes okay I remember
art I remember meeting
r.r.a
last oh it's the last it's labeled
last art mail
no I I mentioned
that new said he was interested
in drawing um
a chapter of the manga right of the dojin
yeah
I appreciate so much
how
how I have my
uh giant forehead
my fucking five head but it's cute
it's cute here
uh
okay so
irari bonks the pig
yeah that was that was the last
art mail is is that's what happened
oh right like
previous art I I see
okay okay well that's not the last one
hopefully not
gotta find Nate
you fine look at these tits
oh god I'm looking at those tits
we're gonna sloshing out of the
of the of the gap there okay
you got a camel toe as well
yeah there's like the
gut the gut and the camel toe I
don't know if I appreciate that quite as
much
okay
it's so it's
so anatomical I don't like
it um I mean it's
like it but you know
huff huff this is so fucking
stupid one
uh how many more floors
uh
do we have to go
we literally just started running
since there's 10 episodes per floor
Nate should be 10 floors down
room
oh my god oh it's in
PCPHQ
PCPHQ just gets built
taller the more podcast episodes there are
PCPHQ 10 episodes per floor
PCPHQ infinitely tall
paid for by Trixie's big money
big money connections no
I think the HQ is infinitely tall
we're not building more we're just we're ascending
we're just going higher and higher
in the infinite PCPHQ
uh
Christ I can't keep up this
girl form
I can't keep up this girl form
for 10 more fucking floors wait am I like
transform transform
are you gonna transform
transform
looks like someone needs to lay off the gummies
that's me it's me it's my life
ah fine fine
looks like someone needs to
looks like someone needs to lay off the gummies
and hit the gym lol
and then
what's going on
I like how I'm just carrying my boobs cause they're so big
you just gotta carry them everywhere
floor 31
and
what's going on with this door
it's been it's being rattled
somebody's smashing
oh yeah yeah yeah I see
sounds like sniffing
Errorari says
this close up is so good
this close up is great
those expressions
yeah
you look looking like
you two look like you're solving some kind of
Mary Drew
Nancy Drew mystery
yeah
okay
what the hell are y'all standing around
for
I sense a strong adversary behind this
door do you wish to proceed
select options below yes no
fuck off bozo
fuck off bozo I did it
you did it
strong adversary
shut your cringe in
my forehead
there isn't even anything
down here
sniff sniff sniff oh no
what's sniffing
wait I know
that's a great nose
too woo
wait look how cute you are in this door frame
yeah
sniff
I love the fucking perspective stunts
like strongly
in the doorway
tiny little feet down there
tiny little feet
actually
you know actually look how tiny my feet are compared
to the door frame
it's exaggerated
why would he
exaggerate
perspective for
artistic effect why would he do that
I don't know it seems impossible
it seems impossible it's impossible
but true
snort
I was a snort
snort and then
my god we're collapsed
camel toe shot
that smell
oh this face on the next one
look at that so earthy delectable
pungent it smells just like
nay
oh my god
this is berserk all of a sudden
hideous
it's the sniffer
it's the I don't even remember
what he was called
does he even have a name
yeah it's hideous
fucking naked mole rat looking
teeth here
I'm gonna throw up
this is great
nay
yeah
there's rules oh my god
what do we do with these
they should be in a museum
they should be in a comic
that I could purchase with my money
yeah
yeah I'd buy this
if it were printed
this is so good I
love it
I'm glad that I was wrong but it's not
the last
the last art meal
how could this be the end
leave me hanging
in suspense
delightful
alright well I'm glad I almost missed it
because it was posted last week
but I found it
gonna save that image
yeah
next one is from rip dot
what is your favorite musical
do you ever listen to musical soundtracks
on their own or do you only enjoy seeing them
in person
funny if you assume that I see musicals
in person I don't think I've ever seen
a musical in person
I think I've seen
I've seen spam a lot in person
I've never seen that
yeah it's a Monty Python musical
yeah yeah
that's pretty good
I haven't really seen that many
I have seen
actual musicals that I've seen
and again I have never been to one live
I saw the Spongebob musical
of course which I thought was great
I've watched
I guess it wasn't really a musical
because I watched the
the 70s filmed version
of Jesus Christ Superstar
which is based on musical
yeah I
I guess I'd have to say the Spongebob musical
is the only actual musical
that I feel any
particular way about
is Peter and the Wolf
a musical
you know Peter and the Wolf
I know of it I've never seen it
it's set to
an orchestral score
yeah it's like an orchestral score
and it's an animation
the most famous one I think
is a stop motion animation thing
Peter and there's a cat and there's a wolf
I feel like a musical
as this guy means to say
is like
performed live on stage
sure because I went to see
like a live
like orchestrated
Peter and the Wolf but the animated
show was like on the screen
and then the orchestra was playing live
that was pretty good
interesting
um
mappa
mappashidepan
because why the fuck do you guys have so much lore
like I want to listen to your podcast
but every five minutes you're representing some person
who hates your channel
because some con that happened four years ago
or shit like that
I guess we've just been on the internet
long enough that we've collected
we've accrued
lore
through time
we've accrued relationships
and with people
that have
played out in various ways and now
that's all part of
the stuff that happened
see what we're doing
is we're making it
so long and confusing
that we can make a lecture about it
and rake in the big bucks
that's the plan
if only
if only someone had the idea
to make a lecture that explained
the origins of the horseshoe crew
and
the
formation of the pcp
that would have been a lecture that I think people would have wanted to watch
oh yeah
I didn't realize what you were referencing
I am of course referring
to the brony lecture much of which
was concerned with the
formation of the horseshoe crew and the pcp
but
I spilled some shit
okay
and it's wiped
next one is
from jade
how are you doing be honest I care about your well being
well
for me
I am feeling hopeful
about this video project
I feel
that makes me feel hopeful
that I think it will do well
I think it will
be nice to have done something
in a while
I'm feeling
stressed about the move but maybe not stressed enough
because I haven't packed
I mean I've packed somewhat but I have a lot more to do
so
there's that
and that's it
I feel
similar
I'm optimistic for projects
I feel
I mean it did kind of have a breakdown
like just the other day
but then by the end of the day I was okay
I think there's just a
talk about that
nah
it was mostly a gender dysphoria thing
but like
things like that happen from time to time
and it's just sort of
what changes is my ability
to deal with it and work through it
and then feel better afterwards
and I think that has improved
since having a therapist
and
yeah
I'm more capable
your therapist is a cis woman
I believe so
yeah okay
you should kill her
you should punish her
no she's great
is she
uh oh
bad news
I'm getting indoctrinated
yeah
but yeah
I think my life is
is alright
and I'm feeling okay
it's
things can come my way
and it'll be like oh that's bad that sucks
obviously the news is always depressing
but I'm more
capable of handling things
no not all news
actually
I think we did
you know what
I'm not gonna mention it
because there's a question
coming up but there was
some good news this week that was very funny
so
we'll get to that in a minute
yeah I'm alright
yeah
um
aboro asks
with infinite time money and access to
anything and anyone you want
what would you create artistically
so anything
you could do anything at all
what would you make
infinite time money
and access to anyone I want
also presuming they want
to work with me on this
yeah
I mean that's kind of like too many options
or you can pay
enough money that you can get anyone
you can get friggin
I don't know who's the
most expensive celebrity
in Hollywood right now
the no
doja cat
doja coin
I would
get
I get
Sergio Leone
and Ennio Morricone
the duo that made the movie
and music for
spaghetti westerns like the good the bad and the ugly
I'd get those two guys
and then I would have them make
the Clarissa Gunsmoke Wild West
movie
I don't know who would play Clarissa
maybe it would be even it
animated I get Quentin Tarantino
and
Sergio Leone
to co-direct
the movie
with Hayao Miyazaki's team
and
sure Hayao Miyazaki as well
and then Ennio Morricone for the film
and his Clarissa Gunsmoke the Wild West
feature big film
that's what I would do
so you would make
a western
yeah
okay westerns are so fucking cool
they're like pirates
but on the desert
a little bit
did you see the new red letter media
where they talk about the good the bad and the ugly
it did remind me of how much I love that
yeah
I went back and
I listened to the soundtrack
and I'm like
Ennio Morricone is like the Toby Fox
of
cinema
now there's a comparison
um
do you mean because he makes
his own soundtrack to his music
no no Ennio Morricone is the
musician he's the
orchestrator and Sergio Leone
is the director
but Ennio Morricone is just like
the songs he made for the westerns
and the films he worked on
are just so powerful
and cool and like perfect
and how could somebody be that good at making
music
and it's the sort of thing where you listen to it
and everything
the experience of watching the film comes back
and it's like
just like Toby Fox
yeah
I found
a disgusting thread on twitter that I hate
and I'm not going to look at it anymore
with infinite money time and resources
I would make angry posts
on twitter I would say fuck you
um
god
infinite
I could make anything I want
anything at all
and the Muppets would be there
the Muppets I would have curbed
the whole Muppets
troop yeah
it would be like a multimedia thing
it would be like there's live action stuff
with the Muppets but also
a Ghibli film animation
segments
with Clarissa Gunsmoke
and she shoots her gun
and she's so cool
when she does it
I
I don't know
I don't know if I can answer
I can't think of anything
would I make
like a cartoon
would I like make a whole studio cartoon
of something I don't know
what would it be
maybe I would
maybe I would get
some writers together
or something maybe I would just
workshop
with some writers
maybe I would get a team together
and we would just come up with something
we would come up with something we wanted to make
and maybe that's what I would
I would first invest in
getting people together to come up with something
that we wanted to make and maybe it would be
I'm thinking maybe a cartoon
or maybe a video game
you know I would probably make a video game
I think I would probably make a
I don't know what it would be but I think if I could
yeah if I could make any
piece of art or tell a story
in any medium and there were no limits
I think I would go with a video game
and
the details beyond
that are
I don't know
that's all I got
my answer sucks
alright
next
where
was I sorry I lost my
lost my place
Brody Pujas says
no voicemail no watch okay
oh and then some people commented
on the bonus episode which I'll remind
people I did release the
Bencast Ben commentary
bonus episode
oh yes I haven't seen that
it is about an hour long
as was the original
Bencast
and also
what was I gonna say
someone pointed out someone else on
Twitter pointed out that
why didn't I call
the calm Ben Terry
and I definitely should have
so that's my bad
well that would be like a comb
like a like a
like a honeycomb or a hair comb
comb Ben Terry
yeah I guess but like what's the
joke in Ben commentary
there's it's
yeah
combination
combination Ben Saint and Ben Saint
the next one
is
it's from Roxanne Kaiser
and it says check out this guy's work
and I think this is links to
more Vinny
more Vinny art
so I guess let's
Vinny has continued to
DM me on discord
and I have continued to not look
at them because I generally
look at them on
the podcast
okay this is
this is Saber spark so
that's not
a podcast member
Saber spark with Tom in a wheelchair
stand
God please you will just kill me now
wait are you that's not the first one
this is the second one I'm looking at
okay the first one gets heavier
the more clout his opponent has
his sword gets
Tom says God please just kill me now
so I was watching a children's cartoon
and making very artistic critics
and posting about it on twitter today
many many people retweeted my hot takes
on pause of fury and how the one cat
wears a thong my precious good boy persona
had to have many points of dialogue over
how there are always perverted images being
snuck into my otherwise wholesome children's media
furthermore my patreon has exploded
from mom
moms retweeting it and giving me money
to take down furry cartoons
with too many subliminal messages ruining
the innocent minds of their children
watching these shows
is that a thing?
I don't think he
does he have a patreon?
surely
I don't think he makes most of his money
through patreon
I guess he doesn't seem like the type
that would have patreon like fans
but he could get a lot of views
yeah
no I don't see a patreon
when I google
wait saberspray pink
no I'm wrong
I'm stupid yeah there is one
how much does he make on patreon
$17,000
he has
okay
$315 patrons so he's probably making
$1,000 or $2,000
that's not
I think he makes more money
through ad revenue and partnerships
and sponsorships and stuff
who cares
anyway
back to whatever we were looking at
shit I lost
the page
is
I think it's
some jojo things it's you
and then me with our jojo stands
oh
yes yes it's
it's the owoopity
is that my stand?
I guess so
gibbon takes stand platformer
they posted some
other images to me of this
that's like ray woman
because she's a platformer
I think that's jack
but female
from jack and dexter
I can see it
I don't know who the goblin
on the right is
goblin lady
yeah that's rayman
and
I don't
why do I always have the cat face
wait a minute
okay all these three are your stand
I guess so
yeah
gibbon takes stand platformer
cute ai girl gamer
can manifest a character based on
sony playstation platformer games
the manifestations have the powers of the game they came from
the limitations that it can only
be from
sony playstation exclusive titles
okay it's tauna
is that from crash bandicoot?
that's from spyro?
yeah
it's the lady from
I'm pretty sure
let me type that in
okay
no it's
it is crash bandicoot
I knew it
yeah it's the girlfriend
of crash
bandicoot in the first game
and she comes back and crash for
looking like a punk
right they gave her blue hair
and pronouns
same pronouns
she says I think
well they took her pronouns away and then they gave
them back to her unchanged
alright based
the next one is
simsy artist across the pond
no stand but he can
see stands with help from the
symbiote in his butt
okay sure
spoilers
simsy comes into the comic and the details
of it that aren't going into the
comic are the following
images
second
door on the right is the bathroom
is what ben said
there are pictures
of each row of images
not just individuals
the bathroom
get out of my room
oh sorry
wrong room I guess
I suppose that door
second to the first door
I checked
sure is simsy
pu this room smells
like a bathroom
yeah
yeah this looks like it'd be
an American toilet
pooping
huh
did I hear someone
crash oh my god 18 more images
I'm freed
oh this is
gotcha your body is
mine
full images for ben to
look at in one go this is a close
up okay close up row of
ben's room that I specifically wanted
feedback on
what
the trash one put a lot of effort into
what the mattress would look like
you have sat against a wall in your room
this guy remembers that I have a mattress
I don't know
the mattress leaning against a wall
it's between my bed
has it pushed up against
the mattress on the wall
it's like an image of simsy screaming
in pain as the guy touches
his shoulder lightly
oh yeah I didn't even notice the land
there I just think
I've been stuck in ben sains household
for too long together we can be free
simsy oh gee
who is that it's the symbiote
there's a symbiote
I guess I just had a symbiote
yeah in a tank
so ben sain has had
marvel's venom in his room
what's marvel's venom
I'm a slime based organism trying to live
symbiotically with a host body
that's venom okay
man so what are my superpowers
now I don't know we share
antibodies and T cells
you're immune to HIV
and that's it
alright mate your new name is
gumo gumo
haha I like it
he's just getting on with it
alright now let's watch this cool video
on YouTube I've tapped into your neural
synapses I'm learning
yeah learn how to do this cool anime
shit alright mate
the symbiote
has acquired the accent
alright mate this is monkey
this is monkey D. Luffy he stretches like rubber
alright mate
uh
and then
haha
I'm trying to zoom in on this
so it's gumo gumo pistol
gumo gumo
no hunter x hunter
I don't know hunter x hunter
I don't know what that is
gumo gumo no big booby mommy
milker oh frick my back is
giving out
ahhh
gumo no demon slayer
gumo gumo no
Fleur Delius
Fleur Delie
Fleur Delie like uh
Robin
oh it's gumo
oh it's gumo instead of
gumo gumo no
I understand
I understand the reference
and then
that's beautiful
is that what oblivion looks like
yeah canon
it's an image of him
oblivion fall does not
have a beard
you fucking unicycle a computer chair
with oblivion
hundreds and millions of big booby bucks
he's earned via art commissions
he can afford to order pranks and inconveniences
to send to ben saint on a daily
basis his only weakness
is to making mad cash
from all the boobies he has
how is that a weakness
and then
Nate the best guy ever
there he is
Nate bestman
stand
fluttershy
his iconic eyewear
were a focal point of his images
he manifested his abilities around that
the best anime ever
had an iconic pair of shades
Nate loved so much he further developed
that style around the shades in the anime
there's
Nate and me as our
ponies of course
but they're people
I imagine Nate dresses up Michelle
and bangs her dresses phantom horn
and he dresses keg sit oh
oh it's Michelle
wait I've seen some of these before
I think
there's me hitting the
the vape
me blowing some sick
skull clouds looking good
as always
dissolving somebody
melts a cop with the blue raspberry
these blue lives
matter something something
I fucked up the
cop hat oh
cop cruncher
cop crusher
cop cruncher Cerberus
it's a three pronged
demon dog vape cloud
attack
what did I do what did I do to deserve
all of this
lore elaboration
it's supposed to be that vape monsters
devouring cops yeah yeah I got that
don't you get it I'm a psychopath
and a killer Ben saint
a psychopath
a killer
when Ben talks about serial killer
this is great
okay these are so weird
very very amusing
though yeah
well that was fun
hilarious
yeah I like seeing these
for the first time on the show
okay good good stuff
let me find where's the where's the next
one here
the next one is from
happy birthday
Ben at birth da Ben saint
saying happy birthday
Ben
oh and then
birth da Ben saint also
has a vocaru link
so um
let's let's give that a listen
uh posting it right there
you ready yep okay
three two one go
there are a lot cheaper than like of course
unlimited or even first edition
even though they're much much newer
I want to shout out Derek H for selling me these
sold me these at a good price so that we could make a video
talking about Yu-Gi-Oh cards
because I always love opening these up
and these are the 2017 print
so if you don't know, Legend of the West has many many
different prints and originally came out in 2002
the first edition print
and then many prints after that
but these reaper packs started in
2010 out of the legendary collection
binder edition then they made the
game board edition in 2013 and 2017
so these packs have been around for
not as long but they're still
actually kind of over
okay good that's the
voicemail experience right there
yeah I miss it
no killer kauri says
what y'all think about the white house
dunking on republicans and biden being
based for once this was the news I mentioned
before uh yeah biden
did some student loan forgiveness
shockingly
some good news
actually did it
yeah I wish I hadn't paid my loans
off
but oh well
I got a little bit punked
yeah I got a little bit punked by that
should it just kept being delinquent
but
oh well
it's uh yeah it's like
I'm pretty sure it's like
they're pulling out like the big guns
for the midterms like
well now people think we're cool
and I'm like well uh I mean
it is student loan forgiveness so
fine that's pretty good
yeah I do like the way they've been
handling like
uh like
shitting on republicans for just being
anti everything good
I haven't really seen a lot of it I've
been hearing that the
the verbiage coming out of
the white house has been based lately but
it's I think it was a
twitter account like the white house twitter
account was like
quoting
republicans saying oh this forgiveness
is so bad and then
they're just pointing out like
that this person got like
subsidies from the government
to like repay loans
for stuff
you can do it you can always do it
everyone everyone who
bitches about it is some rich
asshole that
has some fucking stupid
business loans or ppp loans
that they've taken out and had forgiven
yeah good it's never about
it's never been about like fairness
no they always
talk about how it's not fair but like
it really has never been about it
no they don't actually care
they're just already
they're already on top and they want to stay
that way
every time
so yeah
killer cowrie I guess I would say
that it seems cool
I guess I wish he did it more often
but I'll take what I can get
Biden does some
some okay things sometimes
even though even though
he's like
even though he was like historically like anti
abortion
and I think he was also kind of a little bit of a
segregationist
that's bad but like the things he's
done
as president
he's been pretty like good about like
protecting trans rights
he's been pretty pro-abortion
I mean he has
but like
I don't know what
he can do to like
stop certain things
so it feels like he's not doing anything
and he is just saying
I have solidarity
and then Roe v. Wade is like
what can be done
for about that I don't know
yeah
can he do anything
he's at least
made his
stance clear I guess
stance is clear which is good
I don't think he can do anything
personally about
Roe v. Wade
that's a judicial
I guess wait
something something codified
is that something you do by executive order
or is that something you do in congress
I don't actually know how it works
I think
I don't trust Biden to be like
suddenly like
a super progressive
person
but if he does good things then that is good
right
like if it helps him stay in power
to be more socialist
and more progressive
then I guess that's good for everyone
yeah
next one
Kuzco asks
when will Ben continue his new adventures
of Winnie the Pooh retrospective
I'm craving for it for almost three years now
and I feel I'm going to explode
has it been three years
that sucks
Jesus
I do mean to finish it
I have always intended to finish
uh
I don't know exactly when
but definitely after this current video
is done
after that's done
I probably won't do it right away
but I do have
I think it's going to be
when I kind of don't really have anything else
that I'm like
actively working on
I'm going to be like okay now is the time
I can you know take a little
time and just finish that
series up because I
I do want to but it's not like a super high priority
there are other things that are more
pressing
so when the pressing things are
relieved
that will be
when I do that
um
number one
Ikutsuki Stan account
asks have you explored each other's bodies
Gabe do you want to
feel that one
uh well
not
from the inside
not from the inside
yeah that's a good
I would agree with that answer
um
Andrew Starkey asks
utopian fupor or future
or dystopian future
are you asking which one I would prefer
or which one
yeah dystopia please
dystopia please
I would I don't expect I don't think we're
actually headed for like a super dystopian
unless you think I mean we kind of already live in one
I don't think we do kind of already live
in one I mean depending on
your financial stability
uh living in
like a first world
country may feel like a third
world at the moment if you
don't have a lot that's
social safety nets have been
eh it's not good
it's not I don't think I don't feel
like it's it's necessarily
on like a
guaranteed track
like I think
the thing that's
potentially the most worrying is like
Russia doing a whole cold war
but then actually going through
with a nuke or two
but I don't know that that's any more
likely than it ever has been
yeah
oh god I forgot
about that
I mean he's always saying it
he's saying um
I still have a nukes guys
I could like blow you up
I should be scared of me
I guess if I had nukes I would probably
also do that so I get it
you know when when all you when all
you've got is a nuke everything looks
like a big red button
with a key behind it
yeah if you know what I mean
and then of course climate catastrophe
uh oh sure
sure it's like that's
definitely going to result in
thousands upon thousands of deaths
over the next hundred years
unless I mean even if
I mean changes are made immediately
it's gonna people are gonna be
displaced to the very least
so I don't know
I mean if climate
stuff gets
going I mean over the next hundred
years I mean I would say probably
millions and maybe billions even
depending on like how
severe
yeah I mean even just the heat
waves and like the coming
like cold wave
I guess of winter
like whether in
Europe at least is getting more extreme
so like the hotter times
are gonna be hotter the colder
times are gonna be colder so
if you don't have
the infrastructure you might
just die from
a heat stroke
or die from
being too cold then you can't turn
on your radiator
because it's way too expensive
because of the war
in Ukraine
so you know
I'm expecting
I mean people are predicting
like yeah people are just gonna
freeze to death today
this year there's just gonna be a thing
that will happen a lot
mostly older people
who like don't have people to
oh well okay then
but oh fine
I mean just like
just like covid right like
it's only gonna kill people that are like old
or people that have pre-existing conditions
and like you know so whatever
I mean it happens every year anyway
the older people you know
if they don't have family and they get
snowed in they just
they're just fucked
but like
everyone's
feeling
the energy increases
Vlad I'll never be old or dead
it's hard to be like
just blanketly
oh yeah we're not heading for a dystopia
we're not gonna it's not gonna be terrible
because it definitely is
I mean disasters happen
there's always been
disasters
I think what's gonna happen
is that we're going to just get more
used to whatever
dystopian things are happening
and just continue to not call it a dystopia
because it does feel like that
has already happened a bit
yeah I mean it's happened a lot
yeah
yeah and it'll probably
probably continue to happen
so what I'm saying is so yeah by the time
we get to what we consider a dystopia
now by that point we'll have been
acclimated to it and we'll feel like it's
alright so
so don't worry about it
you're gonna feel
yes I really like you're gonna feel like it's
normal when the time comes
and then you'll be able to like ignore it
and play video games and it'll be fine
that's right that's that's
correct
next one is from never paint
asks Ben are you already
or still awake right now
recording this episode I
answered that at the beginning
yes I woke up early this morning
I slept
woke up a little earlier than yeah I went
to sleep and I woke up very early in the morning
and now I'm awake
um the next one is from
dream man
beescapades conclusion when
I crave it
uh yeah I do want to finish
beescapades obviously it has been a while
since I did anything with it and I
would have to
kind of pick it up again and figure out
where I left it off
kind of the same as the Winnie the Pooh
retrospective that's something that I want
to pick up at some point but only after
like other more pressing
matters are dealt with
I would probably do the Winnie the Pooh
one first because that one is not
gonna take as long
because it's easier
so yeah at some point
in the not too distant future I hope to have
this video done
and the slime and punishment kick
starter underway
and then maybe after the kick
starter is over at that point maybe
I'll be like well nothing to do but
finish my Winnie the Pooh retrospective
and then when that's done well nothing
else but might as well finish
beescapades that's
kind of the plan
and then the next this is the last one we've got
is from CJ who says
when is the next oops all
guests
uh well it's never
any plan to do multiple
definitely there why would you
why would you want there to be another one
it was a
clusterfuck it was unbelievable
it took me all week to organize
that and I don't
yeah I don't want to do
another one it was really hard and the results
I mean it was fun I guess but the
results were not worth it
we're not worth how hard
it was to make it happen is what I'm saying
um so it was an experiment
and it was a successful experiment
and that I successfully obtained the information
that I needed and that information
was that I should not do another
one
yeah an experiment where
like is this a stupid idea
oh conclusive
yes
yes it was
if anyone could have told you
so beforehand but now we have proven it
with science
uh and that's it
that's the end
of the voice of well
end of the ask
things
I will
yeah after I move
I will try and set about
fixing fixing the voicemail
box among other things
I would also hope
to maybe have better internet in my new place
so maybe we could stream a little more successfully
after that
so that's sure yeah
so that's I like to try that again
when I'm in my new place with more rely
hopefully with more reliable internet
yeah I'm gonna be
slowly working
on the Clarissa and I'll get those
commissions done
um
potentially we'll go back
to streaming Elden Ring
I was reminded obviously
last time Never Paint wants to see it
I'm like yeah people did like it
I was just maybe streaming
too much
or like at
irregular times
but I feel like if I made an announcement
I'd be like yeah
a little stream
people come back have a look
I do want to
beat the game on stream
I feel like some amount of
completion would be fun
how far through it are you
I
have got
to
the
the capital city
but there are places beyond
that I've not seen yet
I think a snowy place
where you can eat whatever buses in the city
and then move towards that
and explore that
how much
of what you've played of it
have you done on stream versus off
from my
character everything has been
on stream
the only things I've done off stream
were like
doing buses that I've already done before
but like with
like being summoned by my brothers
so just be like
helping them with their character
which has been nice
should
part of me wants to play Elden Ring
and part of me
is a dozen I don't know
I was interested for a while and I said
I'll get around to playing it
now I'm a little more like should I
I don't know
it's gonna be there you just save it for when you're like
you know what I have a hankering for
of souls
like gameplay
and this one has
so much of it I'll get it
I'll play this one
just do it on a hunch
do it on a whim
okay
I guess that's a good advice
alright
any I mean
trying to think if there's
anything else I want to say
before we wrap up
what are we going for
2 hours and 30 minutes actually
feel good about that
I was afraid this might be a really short one
because no voicemails and so on
we can talk about
usually a voicemail
prompts a discussion so if a question
does the same thing it's about
it's gonna be about the same time spent
that's true
but we get more voicemails than we get
askpcp responses
I guess that's the truth
people should follow us on twitter
also I should remove the old
pinned post and
I'll make the
oh no I can't make the ben commentary
the pinned post because
I tweeted it from my account
you fool
I need to just make an identical tweet
yeah that's true
alright well I guess
if we're done I'm gonna
go open my curtains and see what sort of
seems like the light outside is a little dim
I'm wondering if it's a little cloudy at the moment
so
I'll just have to
try and set up, I think I'm just gonna try and
take what I've got and set up the best
shot I can manage to make
and then
if I get that
figured out and I feel like then I'm just
gonna go I'm just gonna start filming
that's my plan for the day
hell yeah
and I don't know how long it's gonna take me
you filmed that
content
content baby are you ready for
content oh my god what if it's
bad what if I film it and I'm like this was terrible
this was awful nobody wants to see this
no
what if I film it
then you
look at it and if you hate it you film it again
do a different
what if I film it
and then I
delete it and then I don't show
anyone and then I get pink pill
Biden pink pills me and I go trans
and then I'm like I'm rebranding my channel
and I'm gonna delete
this video instead of post it
what do we think
what do we think about that
I would support your every move
thank you
I was it that was a test
and you pass
um
I guess I yeah I guess
then I could I could I could
I could just record it I could just record it then there
would be no reason why I do that's why
it was yeah that's true that's actually true
because it's just you I feel
like I don't know part of me thinks
that like
if I re-recorded it
a second time
like it like if for some reason
I was not happy with how it came out the first time
and I recorded it again I wonder
if
like the sort of like
improvisational I haven't done
this before
quality would be lost and that
would be bad like it would be like more
flat and boring
in its delivery or
would it be better
because I'd be more practiced at it and I'd be more
confident in what I was saying
I think it would be better
I mean even if like you come up with
something off the cuff
that's pretty good
you can just say it again
you can deliver it
try to deliver the same way if that's
if that's easy to do
I think when it comes to like
off the cuff conversations
that's impossible to like properly recreate
because the reaction timing
with the other person
is hard to like pull off the same way
yeah
so you just have to do a different version of it
where everyone knows that it's been done before
but they're just saying it
damn well I mean
that raises a
I'll call it a paradox
that's like a Zeno's paradox
because then in theory
if I were to
record it once
it's not good enough
and then I re-recorded it again
and that improved it
like if that made it better
what if I then was like okay
but if I record it again
it'll be even better
I'll be even more confident
even more practiced
and then it's like okay
every time I record it
every time I redo it
it would get better and better and better
I don't think it necessarily gets better
next
yeah
they dissolve away
and you're left with
the refined metal
in theory I can just edit them out
my hope is that
in editing those things will be removed anyway
sure
um
I mean
it depends on if you have something
to cut to or if you're gonna do like a jump cut
or just go closer
what's the thing people do?
they cut
out like a pause
or a flub
move the camera closer
but like zoom in
it's the same shot
it's different enough visually
that you don't notice that there was a cut in time
hmm
yeah I see
I'm not a
particular practice editor
but I'm gonna do my best
my damn best
alright
but I guess we're done with the episode
yeah
and it's only
it's only 1.30pm for me
it is 8.30am
for me and the sun
the sun is out so
this is good
dammit I could have started even earlier
well I wouldn't have been awake
I wouldn't I only just
managed to get everything ready
I just kept the episode short
should have insisted on a 2 hour episode
oh well
yeah
patreon.com
the procrastinators
the bonus ben commentary
com ben terry
lol it's real for some reason
I really made it
the
okay that's it
follow the twitter
what was the thing
it's hashtag
askpcp
follow the twitter at tpcrastinators
if you want to be
updated about that
although I hope to
get voicemails fixed soon
nevertheless
you should follow us on twitter anyway because why not
okay
that's the end of the episode
see you next week
goodbye
okay
we'll have to edit this back in
to the end but we got a last
minute question just now
so the question was from white poop
misogynered
and I'm still recording
he said
after he detects them
I
I don't know
if
I mean it's a pretty simple answer
pretty simple answer to that maybe it wasn't clear
in reading it but
those buffs are
too strong
even though
disrupt can cancel more powerful
higher level magic than itself
like it's easier to disrupt magic
than it is to
do it
but this is like too much
Damian's like a pretty good wizard
but
and even though disrupt is a pretty simple spell
but even so
it's too far beyond
his ability
even to disrupt it
let alone to cast it
and that's it
thanks
thanks for the question
okay I didn't really have anything to say about it
okay
sorry I could have just done that myself