Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm drinking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I got a deadline.
Don't wanna do it.
We've been expecting your unwashed presence today.
Proud and noble vagrants and rabble-rousers.
It seems as though you've made a mistake.
A wrong turn, perhaps?
Fate remembers not such tribal details
as the catalyst for its inauguration.
For the fact rings as loud as ears would allow
sans rupture, and you have found yourself
in the Procrastinator's podcast.
And here alongside me are internet content creators
of most twisted and tortured tribe of artistic triumph
inconceivable to your noble and prissy class.
Yes, these cultural barbarians stand before you,
and their ceaseless advance will leave you
shocked, bruised, battered, and railed against
as we talk about that most lascivious of subjects.
Sexual intercourse!
Today I have with me Digibroider.
Yeah, get it in.
We have...
I will assume that was the best guy ever.
Let's talk about sex, baby.
Let's talk about you and me.
You guys remember the 90s?
Now it's the best guy ever.
An extremely goofy movie was My Sexual Awakening.
We have to hear...
Invisible in Cell and mythical MGTOW hypocrite
here reporting for duty.
Now it's all children of the world
and Santa Claus has ever wondered,
what is sex?
Well, I've gone to the highest power there is.
I've committed suicide and I've gone to heaven
just to get this one fact for you.
The top definition for sex on UrbanDationary.com is
sex is like math.
You add the bed, subtract the clothes,
divide the legs, and pray you don't multiply.
I love it.
Alright, let me kick back a cold one.
As I unwind here, as you see,
this is a pretty broad topic that could potentially
span the entirety of human reproduction
and as a human that's a pretty big deal.
But, as what I prepared for today
is the main crux here of what I want to spread
with you warped virtual vermin here.
The question that people have jeered and sneered
at my house for and made fun of me
for my completely legitimate beliefs.
Let's cut the chase here as all new listeners
will pitifully think as ironic or pretentious,
but longtime fans will know are all too real
and pretentious.
Is sex good or is sex bad?
Well, I have a question before I answer.
I've heard that when you have sex
you have to show the girl your penis.
And if that's true, I have to say it must be pretty bad.
Because that just sounds like a sex peepee.
That's not okay.
I thought sex was when the keyblades touch,
but I'm not sure about the dual keyblade.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Ben, so if it's when you show a girl your dick,
does that mean if there's two boys, then it's fine?
Well, yeah, guys can't see penises because they look away.
Like, guys reflexively look away from another penis.
Guys can't have sex.
I mean, maybe.
I have like a sixth sense dick detector
that if there's like dick nearby, I can avoid it.
Like, if I walk into a bathroom, I'm immediately aware
of like how in danger I am of seeing anyone's dick.
It's like when you come into a room
and you can hear that the TV is on, even if there's no volume.
Yeah, is that a question?
You can hear the presence of a visible dick.
Okay, so you have a special dick sense that most guys don't have.
So you have more relation to dick.
It allows me to avoid it.
I don't know that that's uncommon.
I feel like lots of guys are constantly in don't see dick mode.
It sounds like most men who go into the men's restroom
know that there are men in there who have penises.
I've spent a lot of time in changing rooms
and I've spent a lot of time looking at men's dicks.
And I just want to ask, is it gayer or not gayer
to have a specific dick aversion?
Because I just don't care.
I've looked at a lot of dicks, I look at a lot more as my tastes go on.
When I go to the men's room, I specifically try and find trick shots
and fucking sniper viewpoints where I can see that guy's fucking dick
without him realizing that I'm sneaking at him.
God damn it, look here exactly what I'm afraid of.
I'm afraid of this and the fucking bathroom.
Digi, it's not my fault your dicks looking like a fucking snack right about now.
It's not my fault.
You gotta cover that shit up.
Yo, wrap that shit like a quiche for me, baby.
I want to see that thing covered in smegma.
That's what I'm all about.
I want you to stick a fucking toothpick for that hors d'oeuvre
right through your fucking re-thrift.
I want to see a waiter walk out with a plate full of those snacks.
Just spread them around to the whole high-class crew that we've gathered to sample.
I will admit my flaccid cock looks exactly like one of those fucking little barbecue sausages.
Every time I eat one, I'm like, this is just a dick.
Smothered in barbecue sauce, just smothered.
The ones that you eat out of a can with a fucking toothpick.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, they know what that is.
Fucking order in the court.
Let's make the rounds here.
Let's get the general statements first.
What are your general thoughts on sex, Nate?
Is it all good or is it all bad, Nate?
It's all good or all bad.
He asked me, Ben, shut up.
Okay, my thoughts on sex are it is only acceptable in the missionary position
for the sole purpose of reproduction.
These are my thoughts.
I'm glad I picked you first.
Did you?
Is sex all good or is it all bad?
It's all good for me, baby.
Oh!
Look like a fucking snack from where I'm sitting.
Hippo, is sex all good or is it all bad?
Well, it depends on how far we define sex.
No, no, is it all good or is it all bad?
No, because I'm thinking you can make a baby without having sex.
True.
That's like what that guy tried to do in The Silence of the Lambs
when he just threw his jizz at that lady as she was walking by his cell.
That's like how you do it.
I think the way I see it is that making babies is pretty cool
because babies are cute, but then sex is like a hassle
and you don't want to have to do it.
It's indirect. It's not the most optimal prime position to have a baby.
The prime position is just, you know, lobbing jizz at random women.
The worst part about sex is the burned calories that interfere with my gains.
That is the biggest problem with sex, for sure.
It's just a lot of red tape you got to go through.
That's true. That's true.
Nate, in order to retain that protein, you should do a Nate of your own every time.
Yeah, you got to do a Nate right in your own mouth.
No, that's a fucking snack I'd like to eat if you were to fucking say it.
Glug, glug, glug.
Ben, is sex good or is it all bad?
Well, my interest is piqued. I'm very curious about the subject.
I'm very interested in learning more one day.
Perhaps one of the five gentlemen could show me a thing or two.
Yeah, but I'm prepared. I'm prepared for it to be bad,
but I still kind of want to find out if you know what I'm saying.
I'm risking the danger someday, but not yet because I'm a little baby boy.
I don't trust myself as a bad sexual or only attracted things that make me feel bad
to things that are consistent, like, consistency, considered bad things, like murder.
I'm only attracted things such as that.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Necrophilia? All right, all right.
Okay, to ask myself that thing, I have, legendarily, the controversial belief that sex is all bad.
And I have written, here, I posted in the chat,
something like, like, 1600 words ran out in my fucking notes.
Like, I have a fucking lawyer, I have like a prosecution lawyer for fucking sex
trial case right before me right now.
Okay, muchi, I got to ask.
To me, I feel as though, when I hear you say sex is all bad,
I just think you are objectively wrong because some people are having good sex right now in the world.
So, what is bad about their sex?
Like, is sex bad for like a higher reason than that it, you know,
like, you're not saying that all sex is bad to, like, it's not a bad time,
but you're saying it's like morally bad, right?
Maybe muchi's one of these guys who's saying that, like, you know, like,
sex can reproduce children and it's immoral to bring children into the world
because they will suffer to some degree.
I think the idea is that sex is not productive.
Like, it's not productive in a real way.
Like, it might make babies, but that's bad.
Well, that's what I want to know.
I mean, it's, it's like as literally productive as you can possibly do.
Not, not at all.
It could do anything.
Yeah, I think you're on a purpose that it's intentional for.
I want to know, yeah, which is bad?
Is it the recreational aspect that's bad?
Is it the productive aspect that's bad?
What's, yeah, tell us, tell us.
The problems with sex in two words are society and time.
In one word, pressure.
In a whole fucking bunch of words.
Again, one hundred, sixteen hundred words written down here.
I'm ready to fucking like Roman Senator go as hard as fucking Ken Ham
as a fucking mother bleeper here.
Okay, well.
Feel what's her screenplay at a moment's notice.
So, so.
Well, let's get into it.
Argument one, argument one.
What's, what's wrong?
Number one, society.
Sex is one of, if not directly, society's main measure of wealth and status.
It is the root.
The starting point.
What about wealth and status?
Yeah, what about those two?
Yeah, well, those are all.
I'm a bunch of here.
It is all in pursuit of sex, basically.
No one, well.
Okay, everyone in the world understands that Bill Gates is the richest man
and the most successful man in the world.
Jeff Bezos is Jeff Bezos now.
There is, okay, whatever.
There's never been a time that Bill Gates has had to be on TV with a hot chick
to prove to people that he's the richest and most successful man in the world.
Like, he's never, his wife is just some normal looking lady.
Like, he's never had to be like, oh, fucking, I'm banging a supermodel.
This is the ultimate show of wealth.
We all know he's the most wealthy because he has the most money.
So, money is by far the biggest show of like fucking status in the world.
Well, on a biological level.
And what do you attract when you have money and wealth?
You attract sex.
But you don't have to taste it.
Bill Gates doesn't have to fuck a bunch of random girls just because of that rich.
I mean, I think people, like, I think people admire if they think that, like, you could have sex.
Like, you don't have to actually do it.
Exactly.
But like, if they detect that, like, you couldn't even if you wanted to, then that's bad.
I don't think people look up to rich people because they think they get laid all the time
because you don't have to be rich to get laid all the time.
What you have to be rich to do is to fucking own the world.
Well, you're oversimplifying.
What does it mean to even owe the world?
Like, if you, okay, the whole point of this is what is the measure of a successful human being?
And from our origin, biologically speaking, what a successful human being was,
I mean, for guys, let's just say, a successful man was someone who impregnated lots of people
and passed along his genetic code.
That was success for that person.
I think that's not, like, that is not what we as a society,
like, we don't think, oh, the most successful guy is fucking Ron Jeremy
because he's fucked the most girls.
Well, he, subconsciously we do.
Subconsciously, if people with disabilities are represented, maybe you do.
Would you not say that sex is one of society's main measures of wealth and stash?
Because that's what my sentence was.
I thought you said it was the most.
That's what I heard.
Sex is one of, if not.
Oh, well, it's not. It is not. It is just one of.
One of, okay, sure.
Like, let's continue. That was the first sentence I said.
I would argue that the concepts of sex and death, like, are the root drivers of everything that human beings do.
Like, money is garbage, money is to have sex.
No, I agree that it's the drive of everything we do.
It's just not how we measure success.
Like, it's not the number one way that our society measures success.
Well, it's like the root thing. It's like saying that, like, yeah.
We're already in the weeds here.
We're already getting caught up on minutiae and pedantic fucking semantics here.
It's not pedantic. We're already there.
This is the meat. This is the real shit.
Okay, whatever. It's an important issue related to all this.
But, okay, bunch of go on. Go on. What else you got?
Again, again, I'm making it.
It's the starting point of major and vast social contracts.
It's the root of a whole...
Most of the shit we do is for sex.
To be bad at sex, or to be considered unattractive,
is synonymous with being undesirable, unwanted,
and you are literally losing life by not reproducing.
It is the subject of many key debate,
and it is, like, when it was sought after,
concept in all of life as we know it,
in all of, like, multi-cellular life,
is to fucking have sex. That's it.
That's the lens I'm dealing everything from.
That's the starting point from what it is.
I'd like to expand on the thing I said earlier
about making babies without sex.
This is sort of tying into that,
in that the need for society, in society,
to have had and be having sex all the time,
at least enough, is, like, a big pressure.
And if baby-making was entirely, like, scientific,
you just go to a place, you get a baby,
like, that would make that less of a problem.
I think...
I think babies should come out of the scientist place,
and sex should be not real.
Then you could do eugenics without having to be uncomfortable
to say that you like eugenics.
Well, here's what I think.
I think that, like, not the having of sex,
but the ability to have sex is, like, if you wanted it,
is, like, an indicator of power,
and, like, the ability to, like,
you know, the ability to, like, do what you want
and, like, not be impeded.
That is definitely true.
And so, like, yeah, like, I don't know,
if you see a guy and you're, like,
oh, man, I bet that guy could get laid,
that's, like, you know, like, that's one thing
that's, like, oh, well, he's got that,
like, he's powerful in that way.
It's, like, oh, this guy's got a lot of money.
Oh, he could afford a lot of stuff.
He's powerful in that other way.
I mean, there's no need to, like, look at,
look at it past the just, like, you know,
the frat level, just, like, like, don't you agree
that, like, when you see someone who fucks a lot,
that's, like, oh, wow, cool.
Do you not have that thought in your mind?
Do you not think, like, wow?
Yeah, we all do, I think.
That's what I'm saying here.
I'll set a level.
It has social currency.
Sex is social currency.
That's true.
Correct.
And as such, I think that it is undeserving
of this, what would I call it,
this stature, this status in the world.
I do not think it is deserving of this
for multiple reasons.
Number one is that, well, like, the main,
I guess, appeal of sex outside of making babies,
which is not really a main thing, like,
culturally, that's not the main thing
people have sex for.
Do you guys agree?
Yeah.
Mostly.
Wait, I'm sorry.
You're saying that it's not, say that again.
I'm trying to parse what you just said.
People have sex because it feels good, right?
Yes, correct.
Well, I think a lot of people have sex
for those social reasons, because, like,
having sex makes them cooler guys.
I think, I do.
I do.
I think that people have sex because they feel
an incredible tugging urge to do it at all times.
Yeah, that's exactly that.
I don't think people have, I don't think people
have sex as a consequence of knowing that it feels good.
Like, we know it is supposed to feel good,
but, like, you want to, like, you know,
until you have sex, if you're, you know,
like some of us who didn't have sex,
that we were well into our 20s and wanted it
since we were fucking 10, then, like,
you've spent a lot of time just obsessing over it,
not even knowing that it feels good
or how good it does feel or, like,
what it's going to be like.
It's just, like, this insatiable fucking urge
to have it drives you towards it, you know?
It's ingrained deep into your brain,
and I would argue we should surgically remove that.
Literally every human generation.
Okay, here's why you guys are all wrong,
especially you, Munchie, and it also gives.
Every generation of human being that has existed
up till now has obviously passed on the trait
of wanting to have sex because sex is good,
because that is how the human race has evolved.
And it is the desire to have sex that,
and, you know, and the fact that the human race
is divided into two sexes, male and female,
to promote genetic diversity that has allowed
the mutations that allows, you know,
like mammals to evolve into apes, into human beings.
Like, it all exists for the very specific purpose
of genetic mutation,
so that, or genetic diversity,
set the best of the best rise to the top.
And the problem right now is that we are no longer
living in a Darwinian system,
and now everything is just done, like, pure,
because humans are, like, so software driven,
as opposed to hardware driven out,
like society dictates how we do things like,
now you just fuck hot guys as opposed to,
you know, like the best fathers, just as, like, one example.
It's completely changed the way this whole thing works,
but we've still got these archaic things beat into us.
I personally think that we're better off
in a more Darwinian system than we are now.
I don't disagree with that.
I wasn't arguing against that at all.
Well, you were saying that it's wrong.
I actually think we might be getting,
hold on, I actually think we might be getting
better about, like, finding
better matches for people,
and this is why, like, online dating
is taken off so much.
Sponsored by eHarmony.com.
None of those have ever worked for me.
My method was get famous enough for people
to fucking message you, you know,
either way, it's still online dating,
and like,
I think that
the reason it's so popular is that
people are dissatisfied with, like,
finding, like, just whatever's
in their local, like,
I feel like we've expanded
the gene pool
in a way, where it's like some of us who are born
on this new generation are not
meant to fuck within our town, because we've
developed a system of beliefs
that only really exists
in the internet space, you know,
like, the kind of people that we are,
especially guys like us who spend
a lot of time online, like,
we need to have, like, a mate who understands
the internet, because, like, the kids
that we're gonna have are gonna be, like,
super fucking plugged into that,
and as technology, you know, improves,
I'm plugged in. Oh, yeah.
I'm just saying, like, for all we know
by the time we, like, all our kids are, like,
10, they might be rolling out, like,
oh, money microchips in your hands
and shit, and, like, we need to be able to, like,
I need a mate who's up and up on
technology so that when we have to teach
our kids about computers, you're not a fucking
retard about computers, because that's going to ruin our
kids' future. Every kid needs to grow up
learning coding, you know?
My kid's gonna know coding by the time they're 10.
You know?
Dude, do you plan on blocking websites
from your kid?
Um, I mean,
if he's, like, 5, I should put it on, like,
an adult mode, you know?
Like, most electronic devices have
some kind of, like, here, hit
this button and only kid-friendly stuff appears,
you know? So I'd probably do
that until I thought they were, like,
I mean, if they get old enough to figure out
the internet, there's nothing I can do to stop them.
Like, nothing stopped me
or any of you, you know, like, once
we got into the open wide internet,
we just found everything we wanted to find.
So, um,
you know, there's no stopping them, but you have to get to a certain
age before you even have, like, the cognitive capacity
to do that, you know?
I feel like...
This is, again, a topic,
but I feel like there might be
some duty as
parents to not let your
kid be a role-player.
Very personal
issue for you, I know.
We can't let another one fall to that.
Yeah, I feel like
there are some websites that I'm
torn on, on PossiblyBane,
but we can do an entire
topic on the child.
A good idea. Let's do a banned websites episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Websites we won't let our kids use.
YouTube.com
Yeah, yeah.
We'll wait until we are actually dads.
Then we can do some shit like that.
It'll be fun to do one before being a dad,
then after being a dad.
Oh, okay, okay.
You just said about how, like,
like, it's not like
you're choosing to get
horny. You never just, like,
think, okay, like, it's time for me
to get horny. Bone are happening now.
Well, sometimes, I mean,
if I'm bored, then that's literally
what I do. Well, most people I don't
think, that's their experience with
sexuality. It's your
decision to go look at things that will
make you horny. You can't turn it on
without any stimulus.
I mean, I can think about things that'll make me horny, but...
Well, that's you searching
for it still. Yeah.
The memory archive of the mind.
Yeah.
That vast mental fortress, they called
the Digi Cranium. Yes, yes.
Um, uh, fucking, yeah,
yeah. This is
a biological cancer
that is forced upon every
human. And just to
clarify, the, is sex all
good, is all sex bad?
Like, obviously, that is a mean point.
My more nuanced actual
thesis is that sex is
placed too highly status wise
in culture.
In culture, you're saying. In culture.
You know, I don't think the problem
is culture. I think the problem is that
it's got too, it just has too much
of a hold over our minds. Like, it's
just that our minds are, like,
are geared in such a way that, like, all
week, it's
weird, actually, because humans, their
reproduction cycle is super fucking slow.
It takes nine whole months to have a baby,
and after you've
had it, you can't, you would have another one
for, like, a couple more months. So, like,
the better part of, like, you could basically
have one kid a year. And so, it doesn't
really make sense that the dick gets hard,
like, eight times a day. Like,
you're not really meant to be out impregnating
fucking everyone, because you'll narrow the
gene pool if, like, one guy is having babies
with every fucking chick. So, it doesn't
make sense that we want to have sex
as often as we do. And then there's
some people who are like. Well, what did it
make a drive for, like, you know, early man
to want to have sex all the time, so it creates
a better... Yeah, let's talk about what
makes sense. I keep getting confused
if we're talking about early man, or if we're talking about, like, now
for society. No, it made
sense at a time, but it doesn't make
sense now, because, like,
we don't, like, you know,
women are not scarce the way
they were back then, probably.
You know, like, you didn't have to,
like, you didn't need a constant drive
to be seeking one out, or trying to,
like, capture and, like, you know,
fucking
inseminate one. Like, nowadays
it's like, most people just settle
down with one woman, and they've got,
like, she can have as many babies
with you as you want her to have, you know,
or as they, as you agree to have together.
As you agree to have.
I mean, you can probably convince her to have as many
as you want. Well, maybe.
It's real easy to convince a woman to have another baby.
If you, like, act like, if you can, like,
give her, like, a sob story as to why.
How many of you are so... I'm convinced to have a baby
with you.
None yet, but I know how easy it is.
How do you know that?
Why do you say that? Have you ever...
I don't get it.
All you gotta do is be, like,
Oh, but, like,
Please!
Let's say you've got eight, and she's, like, nine is too many.
I guess after, like, four at that point
you're just like, why not have more?
And they'd probably be like, yeah, I can't even keep track of them at this point anyway.
But, like, a woman has to go through, like, nine months
like, that's like, a horrifying ordeal for them.
I mean, at some point you just get used to
being pregnant most of the time.
What?!
You don't even know what a pregnant person is!
Think about that lady, the 18
and counting lady. Like, that bitch was pregnant
most of her life. That's one bitch!
That's one fucking piece of shit.
She seemed to be having a great time, though.
You know what I'm saying? I actually have no problem with her
whatsoever. I'm just memeing.
I'm also memeing, and I don't remember what the hell
I was actually talking about.
What a wonderful use of everyone's time this has been.
Why is sex bad?
Tell me more.
I keep trying, but did she come in
with non sequiturs that completely derail
discussion midway through
one sentence after one
sentence?
I was making a point and I just told a joke
and then everybody, like, latched onto the joke
and I expanded on it.
So, I lost track of what I was
actually saying.
I'm saying that sex will hijack your mind
in situations where you will not want this.
You could be in a funeral, you could be in a baby shower,
you could beat your own funeral
and you would still get a vote.
I think I've got a fundamental problem
with your arguments here.
I think your point is perfectly valid,
but here's where I just hit a stopping point.
Like, this is just how...
Starfleet.
Actually, this is kind of the opposite of Starfleet.
It's just like, this is just how humans are.
So, what good does it do
to talk about how mad we are
just how humans are?
We can get rid of it with robot splicing.
We can splice it right out.
We can splice that shit.
We can download a patch update
and get the DLC for our human consciousness.
I think actually it would help a lot
if we... I think part of the problem right now
is everyone's really overstimulated
in modern society that there is
such easy access to
pornography and you can watch...
I definitely think that I grew up
with way too much
access to, like, sex.
Because, like, I'm fucking...
I feel like I'm horny all the fucking time.
Like, just non-stop. And it's always been this way.
It's not just now, like,
I've always just been, like, wanting
to fucking jack my dick all day.
Everybody knew this!
Like, you listen to the pub crawl.
I used to talk about how much I jack off all the time.
I've listened to one episode
of the pub crawl made.
I thought you... I thought you listened to...
You told me you listened to, like, everything I'd ever done.
Yeah, I specifically said besides the pub crawl,
I specifically said that I don't like pub crawl.
Well, pub crawl is great, anyways.
I used to...
I, you know, I just feel like
I've always been over-sexed. It's mostly because
of overexposure, too.
Like, I'm fucking constantly surrounded
by, like, posters of sexy anime girls
and fucking I'm always on A
and they're always posting porn on A
and they're always... I'm just saying that, like,
the internet is just constantly inundating
you with, like, images of sex
and, like, society, if I watch
TV for long enough, I'm going to see, like, an ad
with some fucking hot chicken
and I'm going to be like, well, I've got a boner now.
Like, you know...
DJ, absolutely. I absolutely
see where you're coming from with this.
But where I immediately hit a brick wall for myself
is, what can possibly be done?
What could anyone do?
Why is it me? Shit.
Here is what I think I'm not communicating well.
The point is not to just stew
on the fact that, like, wow,
we are like this, isn't it bad?
And we need to abolish sex.
That's what I'm trying to say. I'm saying
that we place too much emphasis on sex
and I think it will do some good
to look at the negatives of sex
to kind of knock it down a notch in our minds
so we can better conquer it.
So, maybe you're talking about how, like,
right now, like, at college, it's, like, a big
meme that everyone goes to college and just, like, fucks, like, crazy.
Like, that's, like, a cultural phenomenon.
So you're saying that, like, it might be better
if we just, we don't emphasize that so much.
Maybe our, maybe our, like, our movies
stop, stop lionizing, like, these guys
who just fuck, like, crazy, like, in these
college movies, like, like, things of that sort.
Exactly. Exactly.
Okay, okay, I got it.
That it just stops become,
it stops being such a federal fucking issue
for all things related to sex.
If I can just plant a flag.
If I can just plant a flag, you know.
If I can plant a flag on it, in my sense,
I think nobody will be surprised by this.
But I personally, I have a lot of sex.
I do. I had a large amount of sex
yesterday and today, and it was great.
But I really am not
that interested.
You beat me to, like, doing that bit.
Like, I, I thought I was going to be the one, like, obnoxiously
bragging about having too much sex.
Well, I, I bring it up because it's relevant to my point,
goddammit, not because I'm just trying to brag.
That's why I thought it would come up.
And everyone's just like, oh, but if I had done it
that way, even if it was for my point,
everyone would have been like, oh, do you,
you are the boy, you are the boy
who cried, I had sex.
I am not that boy.
I am, I am a good boy.
Yeah, you, you're just not.
You fucking sat there, you sat there like the intro
of that Slipknot song that's like,
I felt the air rise up in me.
You're like, you're like sitting there, like,
peering from the bushes, waiting for a chance to get to you.
It's more like that, it's more like the intro to a song
that's like, duh-duh-duh-duh-duh, do you feel that?
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh, oh shit.
It's the next reaction point.
I care about this intellectually.
I care about this topic.
I want you to say what you were going to say.
Okay, what I was going to say was that
even though I have access to sex right now,
it's great, I do it a lot,
it does not provide any practical
benefit to the things I'm trying to
accomplish in my life other than kind of
just satiating my base level human needs.
And for that reason,
I totally understand, like I personally,
I went through a big dry spell for years
recently and that sucked.
But now, now that I have it, I no longer
give a shit.
I don't spend any time like, stewing on it.
It is just, I have a checkbox.
I had what was previously an unchecked box
that is now a checkbox for sex.
It's done. It is handled in my life.
And I can now move on
to all the other stuff that I want
to spend my time on and make progress on
every day. That's how I feel.
And I feel like culture should treat it that way.
It's just something you gotta deal with.
It's basic. It's like, it's like, yeah,
when people, you know, they say
that like sex is only a big deal if you're
not having any. Because if you're not having any,
you're gonna start to feel like, you know,
something's wrong and you're missing something
and oh god, oh god.
And then you get it. And it's like, well,
it wasn't that big a deal and there are more important
things, you know, it's just, it's just something
you gotta deal with. I don't know if I feel that way.
I always felt like, if I could,
if there was like a hypothetical
situation where I could have a partner
for life without worrying about
the sex aspect,
I probably would.
You mean just like you could not fuck?
If it wasn't real, okay. No, if it wasn't a
real thing and I could just like, I could
marry a person that I like to hang around
with. Because, you know,
nice people don't always have the big
sex parts. And if you don't
get a person that you like who also
has the big sex parts, then
I'm like a bitch with a big old
vagina. I'm talking people
who are down to their knees, my dude.
I want a girl with a curl. This is a volleyball.
That's what that's about.
I want to beat that thing around like a boxing bag.
I'm gonna throw it. I'm going to throw it.
I'm going to throw it.
Alright.
You know those boxing montages?
Like doing this thing,
like doing this spiral motion. That's me,
boy. That's me every time.
I want to chomp down on my girl like a
French dip. I'm gonna dip that Chinaz
and I'm going to take a huge old
biker. Real quote. Real quote from a friend
of my girlfriend. When I go down on
a girl, I want something to bite on to.
Referring to pubic hair.
Okay, this is real.
Settle down, children.
What I was saying is the...
What is it?
Get the fuck out.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
You were going on about beef curtains, I believe.
Yes.
Sex is like...
People either have the body they...
Usually, they just get a good sex body
that is sexually attractive.
It's either you die or you lose.
And if you marry that person,
you'll be like a baby boomer.
You'll be every old person ever.
You'll be unhappy and you won't like them.
Oh.
You're describing me, hippo.
A person with a great sex body
and a terrible personality that you don't like.
Exactly.
I would kind of...
If sex bodies weren't part of it,
or either...
If you could augment your body really easily,
but it's expensive.
If sex wasn't as big a deal,
you could just worry about getting
to it with a person that you like
and want to spend time with,
and then marriage makes a lot more sense.
And it's not even a big deal.
I would like to hug and cuddle people.
I just don't care about all the squishy shit.
Well, you can do that now, you know.
You can just not...
I know I can do that now.
It's just...
That's what the whole discussion is about.
It's societal pressure.
I would slightly object to the idea
that you are, and you have to be that way forever.
Because, you know, I'm a big self-improvement guy.
Unless you're born with a cataclysmically tiny dick,
or, you know...
Cataclysmically.
That's the right word for it.
Unless you have some actual physical defect.
If you're just a sensuality guy.
Under the weight of the tininess.
Of the absence of weight of this dick.
What I mean by that is that I just wish
I didn't feel certain ways about people
who were attractive or not.
Their personalities.
It's not possible because, you know,
a person is made up of everything about them.
Did you know?
My whole point is this...
My one point about this is just that
I understand all the frustration with sex.
It totally makes sense.
But life, I think it's appropriate
that has intense, extremely brutal
backbreaking struggles that we have to
overcome if we want to get where we're at.
That means life will be full of suffering.
But when you achieve it,
there's a better person for it.
That's how I think about life a lot.
It's the whole, don't wish for lighter burdens.
Wish for broader shoulders.
I think between hippo and munchy
we've touched on what I think
is a solution for how sex can be handled in culture.
Which is simply
to educate people better
on what
sex feels good.
Because I think there's...
You're talking about dating ed classes.
Pres proposed by Christian Western-Chandle.
That sounds dated.
That's his joke.
Not mine.
What about dating
ed with two D's, double D?
My favorite ed in any character.
I thought it was a girl who I had to crush on
because I thought it was a girl.
Ladies, get off your butts and date him.
Anyway,
I think there needs to be more education
because basically all we tell kids
is like, here's how to have safe sex.
Here's the problems with sex.
You don't have to have sex when you're young.
But you're going to...
So instead what we should tell them is like,
hey, guess what?
If you go to some random party
and get drunk and fuck some random guy
you're probably gonna regret it in the morning.
However, if you find someone
who you really genuinely care about
and is gonna take care of you
it might actually feel good.
Maybe you should go find sex that's good.
Forgive me for going full anarcho-capitalist here.
It is totally...
It's the problem. It's that
society, at least in America,
parents have abdicated
the responsibility of raising their kids
to schools and the state
in a huge degree.
In my life, not to shit on my dad,
but I really felt like there was a lot of things
about how to be a man that I just never knew
until I looked into pickup culture
in my late teens and 20s
and then I learned how to be a man.
The only reason I know anything about sex
is that I watched so much fucking porn
and I literally would ask women online
about their sex lives.
Hey, baby, did you order a sausage pizza?
It works every time.
I mean, if you watch fucking...
Try to watch the porn that doesn't feel fake
and then you'll feel like, oh, okay,
that's what actual sex looks like.
Gang bang, rape, abduction, dungeon.
I literally remember the first time
I ever saw an amateur porn
and was like, oh, real sex looks like that?
Oh. That's totally different
from what I thought it looked like.
No, that is good to know.
Not about brassers shit.
I would just find people online that I could talk to
and ask them questions about
what was it like the first time you had sex?
What is it like this time?
Just learn about it from asking people
because no one taught me the right information
that I wanted to know.
Everyone needs an American Pie-style
Kamina older brother guy
who they can ask what sex feels like
and how to do it.
Everyone needs a guy like that.
I'm definitely someone who passed that
kind of information on to
my...
I'm going to tell my brother,
turns out sex is great, you should go
trying to have sex with that girl
who you might want to have sex with.
I probably did tell him that
after the first time I had sex.
I was probably like, you got to try this for yourself.
Shade beat us both
through the punch.
That someone in the family
was fucking
I thought it was cool.
If Grace was a guy,
well, I don't know.
Our sister became
an independent person
before Ben or I either of us did.
She just
felt like she wanted to be out on her own
and then became an independent adult.
I don't know.
My little brother is the same.
Maybe it's
like he has
experience because I'm the older brother
and he just had a head start
in his life about
what I knew when I knew it.
Our sister always had more of
an adverse reaction to
like she didn't like
being in our parents...
She always resisted more
of our parents' control
and Ben and I weren't happy about it
but she had that desire, that urge
to be free on her own.
I hated living with our parents.
But we didn't have the spark to do anything about it.
Whereas Grace,
apparently she was so into
getting out of there as fast as she could
and then she did. But she's way tighter
with the parents at least
than I am.
She hangs out with them
which I don't get at all.
That's how you leave the house.
That's how you ease your way
out so your parents don't question it
because they'll just be like
if they see enough of you anyway
I think that's how I got away with
being fucking May away
because I just kind of showed up out of nowhere
and after like three weeks
moved into a place with her.
But like her parents are right there
like her work was next to like her dad's house
so it was like she'd go there all the time
for lunch and so it didn't feel like she's gone
like she's kidnapped by some internet guy
you know?
That'll ease the transition.
It's a good way to make them not
afraid.
Okay okay okay cease fire
give me like five minutes don't interrupt me
because here's the main thing I want to
get on.
I can talk all day about how
we should
sex is not like
that pressure but it's like a minimal
like fleeting high that you get
whatever the fuck. Here's the main thing.
Here's number two
time. Here's my main
problem with sex.
Sex takes up so much fucking
time.
That's my biggest problem with sex too.
Did you just hear
my words? Did you just hear
me say that I wanted
you to be quiet for maybe just
five minutes while you read
my script that I've been writing
all night that I could do for
this worst podcast?
Do you not think you can be quiet for five
minutes? Here we go.
Sex takes up it's not radical
to say that takes like maybe
like a fifth of your life.
It's not hard to talk about the sheer
genocidal amount of time
you're wasting thinking about sex.
Can I ask a question?
Are you talking about sex or like
pursuit of sex?
He'll explain.
You'll see.
Just wait.
I will understand.
No! No!
This is not over!
No!
I
on average have masturbated
two times a day for the past six months
or around 30 minutes each.
That's an hour every day. Assuming there's
three days in a month that is 30 hours
each month. That's 120
hours in six months. I have
wasted a work week of
my life in the past six months
obtaining the basic uninspired
bland boiler plate
cheap flaccid unremarkable thrills
that I've had a million times before.
That's not even talking about the real thing
which is way longer than 30 minutes.
And that's not even talking about
the immeasurably holocaustic
years we spend
attracting people to have sex with.
The hours we spend playing on make-up
by an uncomfortable clothes practicing our pickup skills.
Nate, Nate, how much time do you
spend in Japan practicing your womancraft?
Confidence increasing our life skills and this is
not true.
I call woman mancy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, woman mancy.
This is not like the whole shit thing.
I'm just saying.
You have spent thousands of hours of your life
dedicated to pursuing sex.
Is that inaccurate to say?
Well, that is
fairly accurate and the only thing I would say
is that I think that these skills are related
to lots of other valuable things that I discovered
in pursuit. But okay, but that is true.
Yeah, I just said
I don't think I spent like any time in my life
at all pursuing sex.
What about
masturbating? That counts, doesn't it?
Yeah, that counts.
You know what I spent thousands of hours
doing? Playing team
Fortress 2. I play
that game and get the most powerful
direct dopamine stimuli
in the moment and I can constantly
reflect fondly on this genius level design
and art style. Not only
that, but the fondest memory I have
are playing that game with my friends forging
unbreakable alliances.
That's a problem of sex, is that you
spend your time wasting away
literally end metaphorically
twiddling your clit, waiting to have
sex, or hours you could be playing
learning the skill doing your work. You are not trying to tell me that team Fortress 2
is better than sex.
I literally am, I literally am.
I literally am saying that. There's no
video game I enjoy as much as I like having sex.
I will put that down.
There's no, I can't think of
anything I'd rather be doing.
Believe me, I'm not saying this
slightly. I have had the conversation
in my head while having sex
is this actually better than Dark Souls?
And the answer is yes.
And I've read three different
tests. The skill
lore is so low for sex. It's incredible.
The skill ceiling is incredibly high.
That is a real thing.
Okay, the problem
with sex is the same problem with Mario Odyssey.
All the rewards are the same
level. You get a moon for everything.
You never get any higher rewards
than just a moon. It gets boring
after a while.
That's literally true.
Make it out like sex is just
go until you come and then you're done.
You can do other things.
It doesn't have to be about achieving the same
you don't have to just be trying to
get that same reward.
There's only so much you can get.
Keep trying, man. Keep finding new ways.
What do you tell me there's some sort of secret
alternate nuts?
There's a secret alternative come.
I feel like it's knowing.
Oh my god.
I want the butt.
Where am I going to get my butt?
How do I cheat that?
Tell me how.
I'm stimulating my butt a lot.
You just hold the podcast. I've been stimulating
my butt and I've yet to butt come.
Please help me. Please teach me.
There's a lot of ways that you can come
emotionally.
What about my butt?
What are you talking about?
We're talking about ultimate nuts, Ben.
Keep the fuck up.
I don't even know what a nut is.
I feel like
what Digi might be getting at
is knowing that someone
truly cares about you
is good.
Let's not nut.
I assume.
The intimacy involved with sex
can lead to
emotions that rush through your brain
other than just the one that you feel
when you come.
You can get these different reactions.
Your brain can spike with chemicals
from the intimacy
of it rather than actually
from your dick coming out.
Digi.
I understand
what you're saying.
I know that
feeling.
The thing about that is that much like
the physicality
of sex and coming.
That is fleeting.
Have sex and then just pop out
and wait a few moments.
Instantaneously, all the pleasure you have
is gone.
It is only directly when you're doing the thing
and when you come for like 5 seconds
afterward that there is anything to do with it.
What I consider
when I reflect
on sex
I do not see
a morass of the same sex being had all the time.
I think about different
outfits that were being worn
or what positions were used
or what furniture was involved
or
what bodily fluids were spewed.
What threats were made
to induce it.
Did you?
Whereas you see different positions
and different outfits
I see different time stamp
numbers.
I see different amount of
numbers that have been consumed.
That is what I see.
I just look at that stuff as an aesthetic experience.
The same reason
when I watch anime movies for instance
I don't watch anime movies
because of the incredible
richness of thematic depth
and narrative. I would read books for that
if that was my main thing.
I like the aesthetics of anime and so
there is always going to be the aesthetic
experience of it is just enjoyable for me
to see this thing.
It's like a movie you really love
and it just looks great
and you're like fuck every image of this looks amazing
and I feel that way about sex.
I wanted to have all these different aesthetic experiences
and this time
we're wearing fucking schoolgirl outfits
and pretending to be lesbians.
Oh god.
Yeah exactly.
That's like an aesthetic experience though.
I'm actually
sympathetic to what you're saying here.
That hasn't happened by the way yet.
I don't believe it.
I hadn't thought of it until this time
but it was beautiful.
Again, I do not think that sex
is all bad or all good.
I agree that
I am not above the biology
of myself. I am not above
wanting to have sex and then
feeling good during
when sex is presently currently
happening right now.
I'm not above that. That feels good
and when you lift your loved one
it feels even better.
I'm just saying that sex takes up
way more time than I get out of it.
It does not even
remotely as good
for the amount of time
investment I get from playing Team Fortress 2
rather than having sex.
The amount of joy to hours I spend
is holocaustic.
Here's one
point I would make to the contrary of this
and I normally wouldn't make an argument like this
but I do think it applies in this case
honestly the best thing about sex for me
is making the other person
feel good. That is what I get out of it.
I get to experience them
enjoying it.
I completely agree.
I don't disagree with that.
There's a lot of good that comes from
that. The sex act
is only one aspect.
Then there's the appreciation
that you get from the person and the bond
that you form doing this extremely
intimate act that you can't share with anybody else
like a little private joke between the two of you
because sex is a joke. We all know this.
On that level
that's not really a tangible thing
but it's kind of an indirect
tangible benefit.
You're working on building your relationship
to some degree.
Obviously all these points are kind of
retreaded from famous
Listen Buddy Episode 1. Since Listen Buddy Episode 1
I have had sex
and I have spent many more hours of my life
ruminating thinking about since then
and I've come up with way more
nuanced approaches but because we're in this
hellfire podcast
I have to condense all my real points
and condense mimetic
rage totem pole beliefs
that I have to spread out before it interrupts me
mid-sentence
like every single thing I say.
I'm trying to help you
because I agree with you
that sex takes too much time.
I think that is the biggest problem
I have with it is simply that
I mean it's not to say that I'd rather
be doing anything else. It's just that
the amount of time makes it feel
like I'm not spending enough time on other things.
I literally have cut out podcasts
from my life entirely.
I just don't have time to fuck as much as I do
and also listen to podcasts.
You can just fuck while you're doing podcasts.
It's not while you're listening
while you're recording.
It's like talking about
some libertarian politics
or something while you're trying to fuck.
I'd rather just put on some trap music, you know?
Because I'm fucking a trap.
Do you have sex
with trap music in the background?
Dude, Denzel Curry is like
my main fuck music.
I'm gonna
come out. I'm gonna out myself.
It's possibly a weirdo. I don't know how weird this is
but I do not like music.
I do not put on music for sex.
I find it distracting.
I can't go my life without music
so I have to have it.
That's not true.
I feel like a lot of people do.
I've never really been into it.
Just not if I'm in the office.
Ben, I honestly
haven't experimented with listening enough
to music to know whether I find it weird or not
but I generally just don't even think to bother doing it.
Yeah, that's what it is.
When I think about putting it on, I'm like,
wouldn't that be distracting?
Well, here's the thing.
I was throwing up.
Oh, I put on Big Crit the other day.
I grew up
always wanted.
I had so many songs that I had listed as
these are my sex songs.
I have a playlist of sexy songs.
I had songs that I've had in mind
since I first heard them when I was 14
that I'm like, I want to fuck to this song.
So immediately
the first time that I had sex
with May, I was like, put together this playlist
before we even started.
I need to hear these songs.
What's one song on there? I'm curious.
Come On Over Turned Me On by Mark Lannigan
and Isabelle Campbell was the first
thing on my list.
Prom Night by Anna Monoguchi was on there.
Oh yeah, that's a good one.
That one's more of a make out song though
than a fucking song, honestly.
There are two things
that I've wanted to do when I've gotten
a girlfriend.
I feel it coming by
that's a great one.
Fucking Christ, there have been
two things I've wanted to do when I get a girlfriend.
One of them did you that mean you have Bond Over.
Number one, play Kirby's Epic Yarn.
Co-op.
Because of Game Grumps.
Number two...
Is that when John and Aaron cemented their love?
Danny and Aaron?
Same, same.
And the second one
was from Raising Gazorpazorp
from Rick and Morty
when Morty rushes down and drinks an entire
carton of orange juice after coming.
I've always wanted to do those two things.
Doesn't he really? That's amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
And I can see you doing that too.
And then you run right back up
and the noise begins again.
Exactly, exactly.
I've not achieved, but I'll keep you
posted.
I feel bad, I feel bad.
All those people in the comments.
Just please post a single tweet with a single orange
in the body of the tweet.
We'll know.
I'm sorry to all of those people
who have broken the pack.
I'm still on your side.
In fact, this just strengthens my case.
This just makes me more a champion of the people.
You have to dab on the dark arts
to know how to defeat them.
You have to understand your enemy before you can take them down.
Just think about it that way.
I haven't turned.
I haven't flipped my heel upside down
and slipped my banana heel.
No, it's true.
When I think about this argument
the way you're presenting it,
if there was a magical switch before me
that would just turn off my need
for sex.
At this point in my life, I would absolutely do it.
And I would just be like, now I can just be productive
all the time, nothing to worry about.
Can you turn it on again?
Well, I don't know.
If I could turn it off and on, I would keep it off
most of the time.
This is a need for sex, not the capacity for sex.
This is a need for sex, not the capacity.
Okay, then yeah.
Honestly, it would have implications for my life.
I don't think it would change.
If I only turned off the need and not the capacity
I don't know if it would change enough.
Well, see, that's interesting.
Because most of the sex I have is because
I don't want to do anything else.
We live in a fucking frozen
nightmare world where there's nowhere to go.
So most of what we do is stay inside.
My life is like this.
I want every fucking second
I can have to work on my
extremely backed up catalog of
projects that I have in the pipe.
So for me, a single second
I can spend more on that.
That's how I feel.
I feel as though I wish I didn't have
to spend as much time on that as I do.
I already am spending so much time
working and trying to get through all these projects
and I wish that my projects were like
one of them had enough impact
that I didn't have to do them
all the fucking time.
But that's the world we're in.
Digi, do you think your life's going to
change at all when you're in a not
nightmare snow hellscape?
Do you think that's going to change anything?
Or do you think you're cemented in this?
We were going out a lot more
before winter started.
It's just a matter of
our house is a little out of the way
and
it snows almost constantly throughout the winter
so we have to dig out the car
out from under the snow every time you want to
so it's like
even taking a five minute drive to
McDonald's is a chilling effect.
Exactly.
I got the emotional nut
when I made the joke.
It only just like three days ago
finally stopped being snow every day
and now it's kind of getting normal
and we've gone out more
but it's just like
there's lots of things I like doing
but there's only so many that you can do
in the same day.
Gone out to eat, gone shopping
or something, like done something outside
that's fun, maybe gone for a walk
or something, you know
and then you get online, you do all your social media
shit, you checked Twitter, you checked your comments
you've caught up on whatever YouTube videos
are out, alright now it's time to work
alright I've worked to the exhaustion capacity
of my brain
so where do I fill in the other like
four hours that are there in the day
that normally I would just sit there
and listen to podcasts.
I don't want to fill that time with more work
because I don't think I work well
when I'm like forcing myself
I tend to
follow the flow of whatever I'm inspired
to work on at the moment
and if I'm not inspired to work on anything at the moment
I can't work
I don't get writer's block
I just do
go between
if I don't feel like
writing any anime videos
I'll make a song
or vice versa
Hey, I think Gib was going to say something
Yeah, okay, yeah
Here's my
sex music
I got to try that
actually
Do it immediately
Will you think of Sansa? Will you think of
Riska?
I'm disappointed
Disappointing in what's happened here today. I was bragging my stuff. I was smirking. I was smiling ear to shining ear
I was thinking about how I was going. This was gonna be my magnum opus
Everyone's gonna remember my performance here on this procrastinator's podcast episode, but but I floundered
I've just repeat what I've said in an attempt to to spit out my ideals in a completely un-nuanced
Unpragmatic fucking retarded way and now people will just remember me as the guy who just is repeating listen buddy topics
Even though and though I have thousands of words here
They they they were completely squandered and wasted and to go back and read them again would just be trained old
Again in this topic. So I'm disappointed and I'm upset. I think your main point. I I
Completely agree with I wish sex took up less time and I think that really is the ultimate point
You're trying to make here. That's that's a utilitarian point and I completely agree with it. I also have that exact same desire. I
Don't know
I
Turns out that when you're not when you're like arguing like and the people have like an actual defense lined up that they've been
Considering ever since here
You are you would be fucking banned from ever serving in a town council or any degree of
Citizenship you would be fucking exiled for your display here on this podcast for ruining my stone cold
defense
Do we want to bring up migtails at all
I kind of do what is it what is a migtail?
Dictionary can help a modern-day hero, but let's find out
Let's find out do you remember when me you and they got mad each other or me you and being a match other rad con too
But migtails, absolutely. We had a big argument. What video was that and that was in the
It was in a blue glow. Yeah, it's on it's on a blue glow some way
Here's the okay. Here's the definition of migtail top definition on her dictionary men going their own way
Migtail is a statement of self ownership where the modern man preserves and protects his own sovereignty. Okay, this guy's obviously a migtail
It is the manifestation of one word. No. Oh my god. I'm getting inspired now eject
Preconceptions and cultural definitions of what a man in quotations is looking to no one else for social cues
Refusing to bow serve and kneel for the opportunity to be the dream is like
According to his own best interest in a world, which would rather he didn't guys parents
Are you gonna get married and buy a house and start a family guy answers? No?
This is me I am the proudest migtail who's ever lived
Guy guy writing this nobody said you have to have a girlfriend. Okay, this guy
You know, he's drunk the Kool-Aid in a big way. That's fine
Okay, here. I'll break this down super easy migtails see the very real challenge that is presented in society
That is like a pressure to get a girlfriend and like judges you if you don't get one and they're just like this system is unfair
I like don't like it. I think it's not helpful. I choose to not engage in it
And then they just like sidestep it which which honestly morally there is no problem with that morally that that's completely
Unobjectionable people are allowed to do whatever they want. Yeah, but practically. I don't get why it's yeah
It's it's a weird label because it just gives people something to laugh at when they look at you
Now they're not laughing at the fact that you don't have sex. It's now that they're laughing at the fact that you're a crazy man
I don't think someone's deciding not to have sex is completely crazy to be militant about it
Like a lot of actually do a lot of migtails are into kind of like the pump and dump mentality
We're the like they'll fuck women like they there's still many want to have sex
But like they don't want to shackle themselves with like a wife or you know a girlfriend or whatever get out of town
I mean I again, I don't think being identitarian about it makes is like a healthy thing to do
But like there is definitely a real like a migtail is kind of like a feminist like they recognize
Some injustices in the world or what they perceive to be injustices and they choose to like specifically
Oppose those and like reject these certain things and this is just the label to indicate that in this case
These people are rejecting like society's pressure to like get a girlfriend and possibly have sex
just like you know, maybe they'll just want to be you know jack off all the time or whatever some some certainly do that and
It makes sense, but I just don't think it's productive
This is a very much a mentality of you know the opposite of what I say, you know
These person want lighter burdens as opposed to broader shoulders without a doubt. That's definitely what this means
They're like we were we reject this challenge of society and think it is unfair, which it is which it is not like a morally
Justifiable position for people to put on you because you have no obligation to marry or reproduce morally speaking
There is absolutely none, but in a practical sense there is an impetus to do so
Which is why I certainly can't agree with this well because if you don't reproduce
Yeah, because we want more humans. We want more people to do stuff and like
What if you're retarded?
Well, but I mean just a perfect utilitarian position to say ah my genes are bad
I'm not gonna reproduce that but if your genes are fine, then you should and
Definitely retarded so no okay reproducing is about more than just genes if you
Like even if you have fucking leukemia if you reproduce and you have a kid who also has leukemia
But you are just a badass like
Entrepreneurial motherfucker who like achieve so much you will instill those values in your kid to some degree and like that will be a
Better person than some like welfare, baby, you know like I don't know piece of shit asshole who just was like my life's somebody help me
You know so like there there's values outside of just genetics well that you can improve
I feel like like if if say if you want from a practical
practical
Perspective you want the people who are good at adding to society to reproduce
So that they will instill values in the children
Surely the people who are too weak to step up to the challenge don't we don't need them anyway? I
Hear what you're saying on that print the only way I even sort of disagree is just like I just don't think that like the
Getting the mig town message is actually a helpful thing because there's gonna be some people on the fence probably who could have gone
One way or another and then like maybe if this wasn't a movement
They would have gone the other way and then like yeah at themselves and risen to the challenge, you know
But I would also say that the opposite is like some people who don't who have like terrible
They they reproduced
Despite their flaws as character as like members of society that add to it
Like yeah, they just happen to be in a place where sex is easy to get because everyone's easy or whatever
Like like white trash play. Well, I just don't think that the MGTOW like identity or movement is actually the best for the people in it
I think what is best for them is to adopt an attitude where like self-improvement
They accept that that's their responsibility to obtain
Happiness and what they want in their life and then to work towards it as opposed to just like you know saying like oh society's fucked
I choose not to engage in it because like they're the ones who are gonna suffer ultimately for doing that. So
Yeah, I think it is
Irresponsible to just simply want more babies. I think we want more babies who have good parents
If we had the same amount of humans, but just all of them were smart
That would be that would be way better than just having like like, you know, 25% more population
But we can't actually control that though. I mean, I'd certainly like to
If we're yeah, there's definitely ways to improve that if we focus more of our efforts on making people better instead of just having
There be more people but you know like like like you know again not promoting just having babies
Okay, but you don't have to only do one of those things
It's not like one comes to the exclusion of the other and and on another level like practically speaking
Economies need growth in the population to grow
So like there is just an intrinsic good for an economy when there is population growth
You know, obviously to a saturation point, but that varies from place to place
You know America is nowhere near as crowded as India Japan like in the cities etc. Etc. There's plenty of room to grow
Population like economies need this sort of stuff, but God, I don't fucking care about this. Let's talk about something else
This is this is
I was interested in just talking about migtails in the context of like people who
Like there's the sexual it's the same stuff. We were talking about before like there is a sexual impetus on men like to go out and conquer and
You know like get sex because then they'll be thought of as cool guys and migtails like reject that and I
Morally speaking make sense what they say. I cannot refuse house. We're about having sex
But not all of them. There's there's there's subdivisions within the Migtail move. It's a fractured a fractured
Sad
divided
Why would you call yourself a migtail if you're not the one of the crazy ones?
Like it's like calling yourself a brony if you just watch the show people are going to assume you're a pedophile as well
Because it's fun to label. I mean, that's my argument about literally all labels like
Like why would like that's right? Like there's a lot of people who want to try to like reclaim labels
I think that's the problem is like the reclamation like people who
You know insist on calling themselves like like oh
I am a feminist because I'm I'm in favor of like, you know women having equal rights
And it's like well most people when they hear that word don't think that's what you're about
You know so like you might as well like move on to a new term, you know
Like that's how I feel about like pretty much any label is eventually it's gonna get diluted
And it's gonna seem like the the most extreme part of it is like what people associate with it, you know
Yeah, I think
Identitarianism of any type is the largest problem in humanity. I think it is the root cause of so many issues
I'm a big
By the way, well just well
Shout out. Yes. Here's a song that my girlfriend likes to sing
Welcome to my life as a female make towel. Welcome to my life. Yeah, thank you. I was laughing about it
But it was really funny. I like it. It's good though my female make towel life
Okay
And so I had
Inseminate it into that's right. I had to impregnate this podcast
The core make towel belief again is something that like like I I I do believe that it is not I again as I've been saying
I don't think I don't think society should pressure people into thinking that sex is just inherently like like as as you know
Important as we now think of it, you know, I think it's perfectly fine to not want to participate in it
But you know, I'll be like like obviously, you know
They have like a somewhat reasonable idea if you take the most mundane aspects of it
But you know, they're they're militant. They're warriors. They're SJW is in their own, right? And that is
You know in a sense in a sense
Yeah, I sense in a sex. I have zoned out. I
Think we're pretty much at the tail end here. Are there any final points to make? Yeah
Here are my testimonials for what I've said earlier today. Here's testimonials for what I've said
I'm on team munchie Ben St
I got to say munchies argument were a lot more convincing even though I've previously enjoyed sex in the past
I'm starting to reconsider its merits. Wait, wait, who's saying this?
Whose words are these high sex campaign? Did you Ben St said this? Wait, I did not say it's you
To me again
My name is about me then Ben you said I'm on this is on the the the
Collins I'm listening play episode one. I'm on team. Oh, then Digi bro says I gotta say munchies arguments were a lot more convincing
Even though I've previously enjoyed sex in the past. I'm starting to reconsider its merits
They consider joining munchies anti-sex campaign. Okay for what it's as you can see in that video
I'm tainted by recent insatiable lust for them dawn
Fibrom high heel penis
Drubbings your opinions have been laid bare if you were to go back on them now
You will be changing your mind and your credibility would be shot down instantaneously
Oh
Damn
Bro is so known for having consistent
Because he's totally not known for being a flip flopper on literally everything
Yeah, but the problem is that he talks with so much authority and that's a big problem
I
Will delete yourself from real life so so so you so you heard it from Digi bro sex is all bad you heard you heard it here
Yeah, there it is. We've settled the question all bad
You got my vote have a stronger argument in that podcast
Which is why why I said about a hashtag assassinate President Trump so that his son munchie J
Trump can rise to the throne and
And hence outlaw
Sex that's what I want. It's the only way we can make this happen. That's the only avenue available to us at this moment
That was a problem for me
Yeah, we need to upturn that apple cart and really go back to basics of you know
enslaving you know
Everyone that's what I want
I
Hope you still like us everyone. I hope you still enjoy us. I hope you still enjoy our company
I hope you haven't left. I hope you haven't thought that we've gone downhill and they've been jacking their little baby dicks this whole fucking time
This has been a dream come true for that. Yeah, this podcast has been great
Well, there you go. Are we are we reading comments? It's time for comments. It's time
The the moment has come
Okay, here we go at Lobotnist. Oh, wait, you know, this is a great question
Is there a death? Oh, right at Lobotnist
Is there a death pool for the IRL Radcon 3 arena and how did you bet explain that pool?
What is this man's talking about a dead death pool is when so so at fucking Radcon 3 funded happening
There will be the the fucking Radcon 3 arena IRL where we shoot each other with real
real
Deadly nerf bullets do we fire arms and and there has been no betting pool, but there should be stakes
He's right. There should be stakes to this event. Yeah, absolutely add some sort of you know
Loser doesn't get to eat the steak dinner
Stakes
The dinner has to make dinner
The losers to make dinner for the rest of the people but there's but everyone's a loser
All the losers have to make the most decadent dinner for the one winner
How about like at the dinner like like like how about everyone eats?
But like the winner like it arranged in order of like winner like the winner gets the most sumptuous banquet and the loser
Yeah, and we're like arranged at the table from like winner to loser. Yeah, I don't know
I think there should be some kind of hierarchy based on
On how to perform all just instantly like conclusion. Yes, they like the reward will be dinner related
Instantly I like it. I think it's a good
Like how about like um, I don't know maybe like they're become like for one day
There's like a chain of command or something and like like everyone has to like
Let's get let's get real sexy with it and be like the losers. The losers have to do whatever the winner
Emotional
Oh
Yeah, you just have to just shower me with compliments. You just have to shower me everyone gathers in the circle
It just jacks off their emotions onto my face. I want that. That's when I win. That's what I'm going to ask
Or maybe I don't know we could we could bet something like we could bet something not money
I want the loser to suffer and die
What about betting our
Subscriber
Everyone puts up everyone bets subscribers
Yeah, we've all got 10k I think or like around there and then we trans like we transfer them to the winner like based on some mysterious
Process we have yet to
That'd be great by the way, everybody just in case you hadn't noticed
I don't know if I said this before did we talk before about how fucking the we are max reviving t-bap
It fucking happened did that that get brought up last episode? No, because we didn't know no
But I got some related questions I can ask such as thalamus dred from our patreon
Exclusive discord group asking how do you feel about the Kickstarter doing as incredibly as it did even reaching there you go
You never thought I would make
It's unbelievable. That was literally a joke. It was literally a joke
$9,001 to max revive t-bap, but we thanks for the money guys
And we will use it how to make rad con as dope as fucking possible how I feel about it doing as incredibly as it did is that I
Probably fucked up really bad by not reading any of the discussion that happened around rad con 3 at all
Or what any of the stretch goals were and so therefore I did not at any point raise my voice and say hey
Let's make a stretch goal so that we just get paid
To do this like I'm like a stretch goal of like
$5,000 higher than what we need to make it possible and then that's the money that just goes to us
As a matter of fact that already is kind of in the thing like it's in the thing that yeah
Whatever money is just left over after the thing. It just gets given to us
I am gonna spend it on rad con as much as possible
Because yeah, yeah, I made the mistake of only saying and it would cost me a hundred dollars because I was travel cost
But because I decided I want to stay in a hotel instead
I will definitely be operating at a gigantic loss for rad con 3 if I had known that it was gonna make so much money
I would have just asked for more money to go
I would have been like oh I cost three hundred dollars down here or however
No, we have actually given you money for a hotel outside of rad con
I would have just told you that my travel cost was three hundred dollars and line and okay
Or like three hundred dollars for it to be worth it for me to come like well there you go
You know there you go, but I'm glad we can have you on board. I'm glad
You're a credit to the force
Okay, what else is going on?
No, that's bad what at Doombox 2 asks. What's the most underrated thing?
What's the most underrated thing?
Sex the the core of the earth under
Homestuck
Homestuck, yeah
I mean it's highly rated, but not nearly enough. It's definitely underrated compared to the cultural like force that it is
Like I think that's true. It should be recognized as being one of the greats
You know like the fans the fans love it, but nobody else. Yeah
Nobody who has like anybody who hasn't read Homestuck and is not a big fan thinks it is like literally they just be on their
Comprehension like that's really gonna watch our machine will we use right into it fucking check out arm retrieval
I'm retrieval con 3 was funded by the way guys. I'm sure the con 3 is definitely gonna happen
That's right, and Steve are gonna be there fucking dope as hell check out our retrieval
Incredible, okay. I got another question for y'all. This is from a horse power
He asks what's the biggest project you ever wanted to make but don't have the know-how yet or time?
Mmm the know-how or time and not the money or resources
Yeah, like you literally you don't know how to make this thing and that's why you haven't made it a
Musical I would like to make a musical that is what I know on the stage on the stage. Yep
That's it for me. It's an ARG. I
Is that gonna be the revival of Tbap? That's what yeah Tbap IRL is gonna be. I
I
Want to keep doing small Japanese Juggalo ARG so I can grind my skills to make an actually good real
That's a good idea. I want to make an actual real marble hornets
The only problem is like the one problem that I have with trying to do a marble hornet
Is that eventually like you know one day I will have the patreon and okay?
Here's my problem with marble hornets. I can't fucking wait hold on
Okay, but I can't like just be like here's my new series guys. It's my horror ARG
I can't get an ounce that it is an ARG. Yeah, that doesn't work
So it's you know
How am I going to let people know that I'm not doing nothing and let them know of my new content?
You gotta wait for that like you need that frog fractions word-of-mouth. It's the only way
It's the only way dude. What if what if this was like a like a secret hint and it's already out. Oh
Oh
Yeah, by the way my
No, I was gonna say I've also tried to launch ARGs a bunch of times or like tried to work on them
But it is like daunting to make it like big enough to be like noteworthy, you know
Yeah, especially because you're risking nobody giving a shit, right exactly like when I was working on one
Like what was it two years ago when I was trying like really trying to launch this ARG
And I made a whole ton of footage for it for all these different videos and stuff
And then I was just like the amount of time it will take to complete this like for a chance that no one
Finishes this like no one sees all this footage. It's just like I can't take that risk, you know
Did you you you helped create the Japanese juggle ARG the most successful ARG of all time?
Something to be celebrated for it there. I
I want to learn like you need to know how in the time to actually produce a good rock album
That isn't just a bunch of me fucking around with guitars and not knowing and or caring how to record properly
Mm-hmm, like I want to do it right. I want to actually have like songs
That's what I want hippo think about it
You have two unique skills and no other PCP PCP people do you have 2d?
Animation skills and you have music skills that those are two unique. Oh, I guess did you actually never mind never mind
I mean, he is a reviewer. He's not an animator. Yeah, okay, that's true
For Ben what about you? I think maybe like the ultimate magnum opus and I have no plans for this at the point
This is just off the top of my head
but some kind of like some kind of like big like
comprehensive like
Volume or tome kind of like like House of Leaves or something but like, you know, obviously there'd be illustrations
So I'm thinking something like Jimmy Corrigan the smartest kid on earth that has like, you know, a big like a big like
Dance like, you know world and characters and history. That's all kind of like, you know, just all all in one big
Volume that might be something
Someday thinking about my answer to this the problem is that like it's the biggest problem you've ever wanted to make
So that would just be some video game
I wanted to make as a kid because obviously that's like I think video games like the biggest
projects that are like in modern media probably yeah, but like as for
Currently like biggest project I want to make but don't have to know how yet would just be any masterpiece
Like I just want to know that I've made a masterpiece that people recognize as a masterpiece
And I just don't think I am good enough to do that yet, you know
But what would that masterpiece look like? I don't know like it could be a YouTube video
Yeah, it could be I don't know like what by what means I have it in me to create something that would be like recognized
The way like infinite jest is recognized, you know, like well
What what well digi your dream is a farce piece you already made a masterpiece measurement man on modal
On a tangent about infinite jest for a second, okay
Something okay, this is not like a new observation, but it's something that I've like come to terms with okay
Well, like when I first was introduced to infinite jest it was like oh
It's this big complicated work and everyone's like in awe of its like sheer size and scope and I was like whoa neat and
I mean the more I've thought about it
It took me like two years to read and I was like, okay, that was pretty neat
I get it but the more I've thought about it the more I think that really the reason it's famous is not
Because of what it is. I mean what it is is noteworthy and people probably would have taken note
But I really think that it's just because of the reputation the DFW had and like I think the fact
That he made it and the people knew him and that this was coming from him was probably was like a really big part of
Where it's like the recognition for it came from it's hard to I mean anything that fucking out there like you have to be known
You know like James Joyce's Ulysses would not be famous if James Joyce hadn't already been famous, you know
Yeah, which is it that's like it's it that's like I guess that's true of everything that like things get notorious like based on like
You know like the notoriety of their creator and that's just like an inherent thing like people are attached to be the names and identities and stuff, but
Is your is your point kind of that the book is a little bit less deserving of all the discussion in praise
I think there's a lot of legitimate
Criticism you could have with a book like the book is really like sure like it's known for its size and scope and those are undeniable
But like it's pretty fucking meandering a lot of the time and like messy and sloppy and paced really weird
Which is I guess is kind of inevitable with something that size
But like you know those are real problems
I think you could I think you could reasonably argue that it isn't the masterpiece that everyone says I don't know if I
Necessarily don't think that it is but I think there's an argument against it
To go on a tangent from your tangent the only thing that's made me want to read
Infant jest is is knowing that the author killed himself
It made me think like wow, he's not like a pussy like he's actually killed
He's like he like says he's like much or something and I didn't like whatever like author is say like oh
I'm depressed and they're believing but like he actually killed himself. He was actually depressed like wow
You gotta look into the Japanese author Mishima
I don't remember his first name
But he was a guy who like wrote about like the aesthetic beauty of like the human body and everything
He was like a big workout dude big like body improvement guy
But he was also radically anti-government and like he literally this is just an author
But he like like led an attack on like a military base
Like killed a bunch of people and like made demands that like they like shut down the government
And of course they didn't so he committed seppuku and
Chop his head off. This isn't like the 60s. Holy shit. Yeah
It's it's crazy when like people like people like go on to do real things
Yeah
Doing like they're these are just people that write stuff they write fiction like there was um
There's a one-hit wonderland about a beds are burning by some Australian band and like it turns out that it's like a political
It was like a very politically motivated band and like now that guy is like part of the Australian like parliament or some shit
And he's like people underestimate like how much like I think there is a lot of people who do music and stuff like that
Who might actually have more insight into what's going on?
And that's why they're doing art is that they're trying to let people in on like they're trying to fucking woke you
You know with you know what this is actually great. I'm glad we get on to this cuz like okay
Here's a problem. I have with guys like like fucking a nerd writer
Nerd writer will spend his whole life writing about how much you should feel like oh this thing is so special
It's so important
But like what the fuck is he gonna actually do to like achieve any of this shit?
He's talking about like I feel a pain every day that I am not a scientist or an engineer
Currently working to like make better rockets to get human beings into space it
It consumes me that I am like just a guy talking about anime and like I talk about the themes that like so I'm no better
I'm no better than this guy, but like with him because he's so popular
It's just he's just like giving people these emotions to like feel a certain way and to me
It's really cheap and but my core message behind everything I do is improve yourself
Fucking lift weights eat healthy be a better man
You know or women whatever and achieve something with your life and all I think about is is what I'm doing right now
Actually making the world a better place
Probably not and that really fucks me up and then you know, so like I'm thinking about like am I really?
Passing along the message. I actually really sincerely care about passing on to people about self-improvement and you know
whatever like I get out of stories like ghosts in the shell and
A gurren login like important themes. I think I want people to really hear I want them to actually think about what the fuck
I'm talking about
You know, I mean I mean I care I care that I'm not doing that pisses me off
I feel similarly, but I I look at my um
Cuz I constantly get messages from people that are like, you know
Oh, you were an inspiration for me to do whatever and like sometimes it's something. I'm like cool
I'm glad you were inspired to do that sometimes
I'm like maybe you shouldn't be inspired to make a YouTube channel if you're you know not gonna be dedicated to it and do a good job
He's probably my mortgage my house to be just like you exactly
If you do if you something like that, I'm like no be careful, you know
But like because I do inspire people and a lot of people have just told me things like you know
Your videos help me get through the day or like I don't want to kill myself anymore because your podcast came out
I'm like sick so to me. I'm like, okay
I'm clearly doing a service for humanity in that sense
But then I can also go into my watch time like my total watch time and it's like
100 years of human life or exactly
Exactly, and I'm just like, okay
Well, have I have I inspired enough people to like make up for how many have died just watching
Claimed an entire human life in a half. I've claimed like six. Hold on. I gotta go look at the actual number
It was something like please pull that number up
It was several human lives with the best comments
I get occasionally I'll get like tweets or whatever about people saying like dude you videos inspired me
I have lost like a hundred pounds because I took responsibility for my life. I have where I just got a message like that the other day
That like what a fucking hero that guy is and I am so happy that I actually made a fucking difference in the world
It actually meant something the shit that I say that is what actually matters
The people about making people feel good a little bit. That's fine. All I care about is actual results
Okay, they're being achieved by the shit. Yeah, what do you got? What's your number?
My total watch time for the Digi bro channel is 618 years
There you go. That's like six or seven lives. Maybe more depend. Yeah, I mean if we're the 75
What what's the current fucking like life? I don't know
That's like eight to nine ten lives. Whatever's ten lives. I think it's like high 70s seventy
74 are we doing another question?
Well, wait what I want to say was like the most important thing is it gives sometimes says this give has made videos about this very point
And I think it is so true
It's that like inspiration is fleeting
Inspiration is fleeting all that matters to me is that the people act on inspiration and actually start to make changes in their life
And do something if people watch my fucking galco video and like you're like a hot slut
Who's like, why is everyone so mean to me? Why is everyone, you know, like why can't people just appreciate that?
I'm a nice girl and then they watch my video and they're like yay someone like the hot girls can be nice like okay
Great, but how are you gonna change your life?
How are you gonna be a better person as a result of this?
That's what matters, but Gib here is completely right in his videos where he says like this is such a fleeting thing
You'll watch this video you'll forget about it like 99% of people it won't make any fucking difference in the world
And I feel like nerd writer shit captain Christian shit and and me and me
Well, that's that's like most of what it is disposable like positive feelings
But like guys like Elon Musk like Elon Musk founds SpaceX is like, okay, let's make rockets
I want to hire people to make rockets. Oh
No one exists in the world qualified to make the rockets. I want to like advance the human race
Okay, luckily I personally am willing to work to understand this
So he becomes the own lead engineer for SpaceX because no one in the world was good enough
So he did it and now we just had the Falcon Heavy launch that executed
fucking like land like upright landings of rockets that will allow the cost of like
Flight of space travel to go down by like 50% which means 50% more launches
Which means we're that much closer to colonizing like the moon actually having civilizations on Mars like actual real
Tangible benefits. That's what fucking matters in this world not this bullshit emotional shitty stuff that I do on YouTube
But how did the dark night rises make you feel?
Shit composition
All that stuff all that stuff is Huey's law
Which is good because it baits people in to actually like listen to your message
But if that message isn't good or isn't there then you've wasted everyone's time I could not shit
I don't think it's true at all. I think a lot. I know we disagree here
I think a lot of the point of aesthetics and of art in general is not just about like inspiring you to do better
But helping you to understand yourself
I think there's a lot of people because of the fact that no one educates us that well on like
Psychology or understanding our place in the world or like what the hell's going on because both our teachers and parents don't really understand that shit
Like we need art in order to show us like what the hell's going on in my mind
Like why do I feel this way? Are there other people who feel this way?
Do other people obviously like Gern Lagan was like a clarifying vision of like something important to me
So okay, and I think when you can package that in this in an aesthetic that like okay
Gern Lagan is the same story that's been told a thousand fucking times. It's a hero's
Narrative but like it's in an aesthetic that resonates with the specific type of person that is the two of us
You know like yeah guys who currently are in like their late 20s
Who were probably in their late teens when the show came out and it had like a massive impact because it's like this is the
Bombastic over-the-top epic thing like style and hyper masculine style that was big in the late 2000s fucking it came out like a year after
300 you know like this is what we wanted was like sloganeering
bare-chested like dudes fucking punching each other and
Yeah, so it was like the perfect fucking snacks what we want. Yeah, yeah
Exactly, so that was okay
Like the perfect delivery of this timeless message that everyone needs to hear in order to grow up
But like for us, this is the aesthetic that mattered the one that resonated with us because we're from that generation, you know
Yeah, okay, okay. I'm totally happy to like
Let's give everyone whatever aesthetic they personally need to become a better person
Whatever the delivery package needs to be for people to understand the message. I am all for
Figuring out what it is and exploring it and I think to your point
You're saying that like I mean we don't exactly we can't like identify this shit
Which is why we need people to go out there and make art so that people will feel that there's lots of stuff
They can resonate with and they can seek it out and enjoy it. Um, yeah, okay. That's a pretty reasonable point
I don't know. Sometimes I feel like art is just a big fucking scam
Sometimes I feel like I actually do anything and it's all just uh, you know
It's all just crap that makes you feel good in the moment and people are just being tricked into thinking it's important
What do you guys think about that? I see a break with you
But like it's it's all a matter of like how do we quantify it like how I can't fucking there's no stat sheet
That tells me like how many people I've inspired like, you know, I don't have the analytics for that, you know
I don't have the net good on the world analytics. It's in some way
Somebody making a living off of art. Mm-hmm is worth it for at least the people who know the artists and our friends with them
Yeah, and then that improves the making of art
I think it's like I mean at the very least I'm stimulating the economy in a way
I wouldn't be if I wasn't doing anything, you know, yeah, that's true only if only if you're putting it back
I
Agree with you so much in the fact that it is just appeal
It is just that you are appealing to people and they like what you have made. There's no inherent
You know responsibility for art to inspire to do any real work real world things
That is not intrinsic to art is that that is well
I would I would never say that artists have to do that
I would never say that but I would think like the most valuable art or perhaps even the only art that is actually valuable
Does do that. I guess would be my point
Well sure, I would you I would just say the where I where I disagree with you Ben is that I don't think it's just in the moment
I think if you make good art people will remember for a long time and as I've said before in the sex part of this
I think uh fleeting highs are the most despicable highs and if it can just last a long time then I think that's more valuable
Here's here's my problem. I think that generally okay art can inspire people
But I feel like in general what it mainly inspires people to do is to make more art
Which if if it's just like a big self self inflicting loop a big like
You know a self perpetuating cycle of art inspiring more art, but the art itself is not really getting us anywhere
I mean you can say that but like literally every scientist talks about how they were inspired by star trek
That's a reasonable point everybody. That's a reasonable point. I think there are some all the art that's out there is inspiring people to become
That's true, but like we gotta throw enough darts at the wall until somebody's thing sticks like that
How many sci-fi franchises existed before star trek like was the one that made everybody fucking want to do that?
Unpopular opinion when I hear like someone like I don't know fucking Neil deGrasse Tyson be like
Yeah, I was I love flash gordon so much as a kid that I went into physics and space and astronomy
I roll my eyes so fucking hard. What why because it's fake shit because that's like fake fictional shit and like
Real science is boring
I don't know. I just I don't quite get the like how can like how like like okay like flash gordon
Maybe make space look really cool, but then you grow up and you'll be just studying real space and it's not like flash gordon
I don't know how that I don't know how that could possibly inspire like a real lifelong interest and fascination enough to sustain like
A real career. I feel like you don't have to maintain the problem. We had the interest in it already
Like maybe they probably would have been inclined to do that
Anyway, and flash gordon just happened to be the thing I like at that moment got them to take notice of it
I don't know if I agree with that. Hold on. I gotta
Okay, sure
Just like I'm thinking about because um my friend ghost lightning got into tennis because he watched prince of tennis
Like that show like watching it marathoning it with his wife made them want to get into tennis
The thing is that once they got into tennis and they started watching real tennis
They quickly realized that that show is like utterly nonsense. Like it's ridiculous
But they ended up loving real tennis and it
What actually happened is they just thought that prince of tennis was dog shit, but they love the sport
Like now they just watch fucking baby steps and like and real actual tennis matches and like have fun with it
So like it's not that flash gordon was a good representation of science
It's that once they started doing science
They realized it was great and there's so many people who have the opposite
Like there's so many people who try to get into something because they liked this show and then they realize it's not like that
Like there was a huge boom and people trying to get into crime scene investigations after csi got popular
But like once you actually start up that course load it is not easy
Dude, did you hear did you see there's like a uh, there's a fucking uh, I think was the canadian government
Like posted a notice saying please stop applying for uh, like uh crime scene investigation degrees
We have too many people like you can't get a job. Please stop like the shows are just too popular
How okay, okay, let's let's take it fucking for granted that like
A show or something can inspire
By the way hippo really has to be given like can be credited as like the reason why someone gets into some
Important practical field like science or engineering. Let's just accept that as true
um
How okay, even if that's happening
How do we know that the number of those cases aren't far outnumbered by people who like maybe would have gone into a real field
But instead spent their life just fucking around on the internet just spent spent their life drawing some art and maybe entertaining some people
That's what I worry about thing. I I think we're being really fucking narrow-minded and what we view as I don't know the word just positive
Be okay. I'm somewhat being a devil's advocate right now by the way being alive is good and enjoying
Breathing and being good. Yeah
No, no incorrect
I
Of culture and
Having a heart and a soul and a dick and a brain
Okay, and enjoying
Living and talking to your fellow humans and feeling emotion and conversing muchy. This is all bullshit. I don't care about at all
No, no, I totally agree like I do think that just like enjoyment itself is like sufficient end in and of itself or a thing to be important
I agree
What literally what is the point of advancing human civilization if human civilization is just boring and nothing
Okay, I'm exaggerating a little bit. There's there's a distinction here
I do actually think there was an inherent good in human life and human like happiness and pleasure
I I I do believe that um, but I would say that there is I here's where I would
When rarely one of the rare times I would use the word objective
I would think it is objectively better if there is more happy like more people and more enjoyment and more happiness
And I like I think the way to get there is to constantly be progressing from lifetime to lifetime, you know generation to generation
To be working towards expanding the circle of how much happiness, you know, uh knowledge and pleasure
There is the world, you know, obviously every life should have not too much pleasure
I I don't understand how you think that that like like the like
Well, here much it's real simple here. Okay. Okay. Go. Okay. It's very simple
If you have one person just living a life
You know, normal level of happiness normal level of sadness
They live their life and they die as opposed to two people
Both have a normal level of happiness generally pretty happy lives. They both live and they both die
Which of those is objectively a better universe like where has more good happened? I have a
I don't agree with more people being happy is better. I'm saying, where do you think the happiness comes from?
Where do you think this happiness is?
It does it does come from the subjective experience of being alive. That is true. That is true
It comes from culture. It comes from being in a society and being in a civilization
Like like the point of progressing civilization is that there is more civilization and culture and humans
But here's what I don't like
I I would not be satisfied with the idea of like we keep the exact same number of human beings that are alive
Right now on the planet earth and we just like stay right here and everyone's like happy
I don't know where this idea. I don't know who you're responding to with this. I don't know
I think what Nate is trying to say is that if all we do is worry about art
Then everyone just becomes an artist. We're not worried about expanding the civilization going out to space and all that
This is not this is not is is sex all good or is sex all bad?
This is not do we only focus on culture or do we only focus on I just don't think there's any disagreement here
And I don't know why you're taking the attitude like we do disagree like what is your issue with what I have said
Not not with what you have said. I I I just thought that we were being like like Ben was talking about how like, you know
Oh, that's all fucking scam like like sure like I don't think we need to be discussing
Whether whether art has any like intrinsic like objective value here. Is that not a fair discussion to have?
But I just think it's it's it's it's narrow-minded. It's it's not
There's no sounds like it sounds like you're just taking a position in that discussion
Which is fine, which is having the discussion. Well, okay. I'm I'm okay sure that this is my opinion then in this discussion
This is what I'm presenting. Okay. Is that I think is I think that art is important and I think that it doesn't have
objective
Value do we want to answer another question? Yeah, let's go to another one
All right, let's do it. Um
Much has been disproved. He has been proved incorrect. So let's move on. I'm ready to move on
This is a question. I I'm gonna choose to interpret a certain way
The guy said the guy's name is lord legend of the galactic heroes sucks space dandy wins
That's okay
His question is what would your real life theme be and I've chosen to interpret this as in your theme like
As if you were a work of art. What is your theme? I think he means musical theme, but okay
Like the motif of your life. Yeah, yeah, what is what is your theme?
How much I can fuck how many sluts I can fuck
Uh, that is a that's a great question
The theme uh, the theme of my life would definitely be utilitarian progress. I know it's boring
I know it's obvious, but that's like what it is. So, you know, fuck you
Mine is some masculinity. I don't know whatever. Did you say did you say toxic masculinity? No, I said some themes
Oh, that's what it is. That's what it is. All right. All right. Hey. Hey is talk is toxic masculinity real
Let's talk. Okay. Toxic masculinity is just the idea that masculinity is inherently like bad. It is inherently
No, no, I don't think that that's not
masculinity is when someone is being toxic in a way that is related to their masculinity. I think
Yeah, uh, uh, I don't know. Well, okay. Let's see what urban dictionary. Let me just read the urban dictionary real quick
Why did we why are we talking about this?
Toxic masculinity a social term that describes narrow rep repressive type of ideas about the male gender role that defines
Masculinity as exaggerated masculine traits like being violent unemotional sexually aggressive and so forth
Also suggests that men who act too emotional maybe aren't violent enough or don't do all these what the fuck is this?
I don't understand this definition. This is terrible. Yeah, this is not helping me
um
Well, the theme of my life would probably be like, um, yeah trying to be understood
Like a desperation for like like a mutual understanding or something like that
Okay, the theme of my life would probably be like, I don't know, um
Freedom independence, I guess, you know living
Just living on my own terms. Yeah. Yeah, that sounds about right
Which is great by the way
I would say
irony
Retrospection
Fun
I feel like you're I mean, you're like the most sincere person I know so how is irony a theme of your life
He's pretty ironic too though. He's like post ironic though. Yeah, that's kind of true
Because the way that I express my my inner emotions is presenting them not as
You know the nuanced or or the most, you know
Gently put things in the world. I progress them to to an insane degree and make them appear foolish
Even though they they are how I feel
I don't know if I call it
I do want to express my sincere thoughts sincerely
By the way, I thought your theme was performance
Performance works too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's also good. I would probably I would probably say irony performance fun
I just want to
Do everything that I do I feel like I left that thread hanging
I just looked up the definition of toxic masculinity on wikipedia, which which is much clear
It's much clear
It's just the concept of toxic toxic masculinity used in psychology to describe a certain traditional male norms of behavior
In the united states and europe that are associated with harm to society and men themselves. So okay much clear
It's just saying some aspects of
Socially conceived masculinity masculinity is just the bad kinds
Yeah, but like who defines bad and good. Well, I mean, yeah, that's the kicker like you like I guess it would be up to the
Individuals like what is and is not toxic
And I I guess I'd say there's a problem in here
I don't know like masculinity is another form of
Identitarianism to like define yourself as like masculine. So I guess that's kind of I don't know
I don't really see a lot of value in doing that either, but whatever. It's just good to run your shit
We only got one more good question left. Okay. I found
Your boy Liam asks
Good remedies for the worst days
With a good question mark at the end. Good pussy, my dude
I like to draw
Drawing is good. Oh, I would literally say exercise
I would literally say exercise and here's why first of all exercise has a actual physiological
Positive stimulus once you're done with it
You just feel good and then also if your day is shit you probably feel like oh no
I fucked up everything everything's going bad to to obtain mastery over something in your life
Like to exercise and feel like I did it like I have control over this. I am good
It just makes you feel like better about your life. I was gonna say I was like for kind of the same reasons
I was gonna say just accomplishing something like yeah
For one you have to have a goal like you have to have something you're working towards
Like making making some progress even a little bit of progress on it like before better something
Will make you feel like your day wasn't completely wasted. That's so true. That is so true
Nate on exercise and in one specific thing that I don't do a lot
But I should do because every time I do it. I absolutely love it. I love jelking. You talk about jelking my dude. Oh, yeah
Okay, oh my god. Oh my god the secret we have we have to do the jelk cast next week, but I'll just
It's just
Dwarf as hard as you can grasp your order of as hard as you can
Yes, and pull pull for the fucking life of your stuff
Okay, it is literally where you you do like little pulls on your dick as an as an exercise to like tear it a little bit
So that it gets bigger. It doesn't actually to make your dick
That's what it is. It's what it is
I gotta say, I mean no it gets results
Oh boy, what was I saying? I'm saying
A good jelk my dude
That I fucking that that happened to me earlier today that has changed my life
I'm just gonna do this every day now. Okay, there's an app like you can get on your phone called brain.fm
And it's some like like weird. I think real science, but it might be pseudoscience
They have tracks of music that that they claim like changes, you know, they put your brain in a mood
So you can have your brain focused you can have your brain go to sleep you can have your brain relax
So put your brain in different moods
So I put on the focus track on brain.fm and I went for a walk
I swear to god, this has enhanced my by perception 10 fold
I was aware of everything that fucking moved. I was inside of the fucking earth and I was feeling every single
Vibration and nuance on the fucking earth's field. I was one with all of god's children
I was walking from just from like my house to my local 7-Eleven
And I had this fucking music on and I was aware of every like change of the light or any like homeless person out of the corner
Of my eye
I I was more alert than I ever been in my entire fucking life. It fucked me up and it was insane
I highly recommend everyone. I also got this awesome energy
And it was the best fucking drink I've ever had in my life pipeline punches. Good. I definitely would like to try doing that
Yeah, dude, we can do it together at rag-con
All of you have great. Those are all great remedies. Mine is simply a change up game
Like just change things change something about what you're doing
It could be any of the things that you guys just said
But like generally if I find myself like going down a dark path in my mind
The best way out is to just do something totally different from what I'm doing like listen to for me
If I don't have access to good pussy like Nate said
Um
Podcasts are like a great out. I would just like if I felt funky or like I was just pissed off at the internet
I would just listen to the dick show and play a video game and it's like I don't have to think
I don't have to be myself
I could just listen to the dick show and just listen to him talking
I don't have to think about my problems and I can just play a video game and be somebody else for a little while
You know and like forget about whatever was going on with me, you know, or I guess put on some better music
That's like more
You know like like much he said with that I don't have that program
But like when I feel bad sometimes I'll just like throw on onamonaguchi and try to get something done because like it'll just give you energy
Accomplishing something is definitely I think the the best like long-term solution
Like that's a that's a good feeling that you'll feel like into the future
But if I just want to know that you're having the worst days that you can't accomplish anything
That's probably probably true. I but the best like just my most pleasurable thing I do in my life
Is to sit back put on a movie I love
I I usually the godfather movies are like my go-to ones for this and I'm playing
Then I'm also playing a video game while I'm like watching slash listening to a movie
I love that I've seen a thousand times. Nate. Are you there to say you just want to play video games every night every day
I just want to play video games
Are you aware of the uh, kasey nice that godfather screen saver thing that he's got?
I am and I love it and I love it. I think it's super cool for the audience who doesn't know
Kasey nice that it's a monitor that just at all times is playing a constant loop of godfather 1 and 2
I've said it before. Oh, not godfather 3. I was actually gonna ask about that
If you felt the same about I actually love godfather 3 almost as much as the other ones and people who share godfather 3 are fucking idiots
um, but uh
Uh, whatever. I don't fuck what I was gonna say, but gibbs back gibb
What do you do when your day ain't going right and you want it to feel good if you want to fix a shitty day
Uh a shitty day
um, I usually just try to
Create something and distract myself with work
But if if work and what I've been trying to make is the the problem
Then I usually curl up into a ball and cry
Does that help?
No, it doesn't
I go through I go through yeah, I go through many crises
I like to rapidly cycle through mental crises. It really helps me, you know work out the case
I I always end up at the point where I was like wait nobody cares about my problems
Maybe I should shut up and then I do and then it's great. If you get bored of one crisis. You can just switch to another
Yeah, that's true when you're feeling down like this. Why don't you talk to your friends?
Why don't you talk to your friends about that? Why don't you just come on?
What is going on over?
Gay
I really want a procrastinator animated of like of when ben said you just switch from one crisis to another of someone like
In an arcade switching between two different time crisis machines because it's all
You know, uh, oh that'd be good when I'm feeling down
It it just feels like I don't like to bother friends with that
Especially since I have done it multiple times before and I will probably do it multiple times in the future
It is it's an important and it always ends in in in the same way that I realized that
Nobody needs to hear this. I just need to move on
It's a real thing that we got to recognize about like the people around us like we our friends will tell us
Oh, you can come to me with anything you can tell me blah blah blah like I'm always here for you
But nobody actually wants to hear about how sad you are over and over again. Nobody wants that
I recognize that and you know if someone comes to me and just is complaining and like if most of my experience of
A certain person is that they're just sad and complaining like I will not enjoy hanging out with them
It'll just be like well, it's like I mean if they're your friend if they're if they're your friend
They'll do it for you. They'll listen to you if you need an ear
But if like but if you're like doing it all the time and you're like really
You know taking up a lot of their time with like some sad shit. Yeah, like why would they continue?
What do they get out of it?
I think well here's the thing with it is like if you're a good friend you'll listen to your friend
And and help them through whatever they're going through
But if that friend the person who is going through things is a good friend
They will realize that they don't they shouldn't
They they need to fix themselves before they just lay it on someone. I mean, it's ultimately. Yes
Ultimately, it is your responsibility to fix your own shit
But like of course like I would if any of you guys came to me like as a one-time thing
Just just as an example and just said like dude. I'm just really sad about this. Of course. I'd be happy to listen
Everybody needs a sympathetic ear from time to time
I got a story to ask because like one of my old friends like he was that guy who would like come and you know
and cry about his life all the time and
Like everybody in my group of friends is like smart and good at giving advice
And this guy's probably the dumbest guy I know out of out of the people who hang out their friends
So like he's constantly whining and people are constantly trying to give him advice
And he just wouldn't fucking follow anybody's advice and he'd come to you crying the next day and you're like, dude
I already told you what to do. That's the thing. Like if you're not gonna do it. Fuck you
I will also say though
I will say that usually
It when it comes to advice like I get advice and it's usually advice that I agree with
Yes, it's not knowing what to do. That's the problem. It's never knowing what to do. It's just doing it
Also on the perspective of advice is kind of masturbatory or like a waste of time
That's definitely give or ask for advice and plus like at least if you know what you're doing
If you if you like I mean anyone who comes to me and like asks for my help about anything
I will like immediately pull out the fucking spreadsheet and attempt to immediately solve the issue
And I don't give a fuck what your excuses are. I will identify the blockages
I will figure out ways to circumvent them like anyone who comes to me with a problem
And I care enough about you. We will solve it then and there
We will identify the ways to do it
But a lot of people don't actually want that a lot of people just want a sympathetic ear
And I am the wrong guy for that. So that's what you're looking for. That's not me. That is not me. So
Yeah, you know just that
You should go to who you want like if you just want somebody
Honestly, like like like women do this more like my girlfriend is definitely like this
She just wants me to like listen to her sad day whenever she tells me about like problems
I'm just like a break it out the spreadsheet. Let's fix it right now identify the problems
It's been identified the solutions, but like sheet. What are you using a spreadsheet to help with in this scenario?
Well, uh spreadsheets are okay making lists is essentially laying out the facts. Okay. Yeah, that's what I mean, but I literally use spreadsheets
Okay, I didn't yeah, I'm literally talking about spreadsheets like spreadsheet guys
My job has awakened me to how spreadsheets are the only thing that matter in this world
They are the only thing that matters at all a human experience is subjective fucking excel spreadsheets are are absolute
Exactly what you're talking about because when I when I'm trying to give advice
There's usually either a list or like a graph of some kind involved. Like yeah
There's a lot of me making graphs with my hands when I'm trying to explain what somebody should do
There's there's not a single gray or rush of doping that that rushes for through my loins
Rather than when I open up a new google doc
That is the height of my fucking day
Also, just just to close this off. I I don't
Disagree with any of what she said I
I feel like like I I I'm down to you know talk whenever I I will just say I
Try and make it a real point to not make it I want to hear about everyone's you know
Sad days, but I want to make it known that I'm not letting them become complacent or just like I don't know
I don't know how to say this correctly, but I don't want to know that like it's a
I'm just kind of like you will listen to them all day, but you would rather they not think that you're not trying to help them
like you know
I just mean that I don't want them to be
Two's I want them to I want them to have a fire into their ass to fix their problem
I don't want them to just think that I like it's not that I you don't want to placate them. You don't want to placate them
It just left the language. Yeah, exactly perfect. It's like I'll listen to you at all times
But you're not allowed to know that like you know
It's I'll listen to everyone all the time, but I want to help them first and foremost
And I don't want to always just be like, oh, I'm sorry pat pat there there
I want to give them advice and I want them to fix what is happening
I don't want to just I don't want to just be the guy you know
I I am my life has come to a certain point where I've only got so much time
And like people who want to come to me with their problems like if I care about you I'll listen but listen buddy
I'm budgeting you 20 minutes of my time to fix your fucking problem or to like listen to you complain about it
That's what you got use it how you want
But then I'm out of here because I got shit to do and I'm not gonna just sit here all day and you know
Listen to your complaints and maybe that makes me a bad person
I call it like being a productive person who who optimizes his usage of his time because I have so little to spare
Uh, it's just you know, that's how my life is now and that's how I'm gonna be
I think I'm the same as you need. I'm just more lenient with the times
I think I think I mean we want we want to get it to be done
Not not to like shit on you or anything
It's just like I probably have like just less time to spare because I've got a full-time job and youtube stuff
So like that's forced me to be very stringent with how I use my time. So, you know, just saying just saying
I think we're over the two-hour mark here. That was good though. Man. I really enjoyed that. Oh, you know what?
Questions
Yeah
I don't want to give the questioners too much credit
Can I close this out everybody with an important message on on sex and relationships and everything from my hero matpat
All right, matpat's got the words of wisdoms. We need to go by so just forget everything
We just said only listen to these words. Okay, here we go real quote
From february 9th, uh, 2018 you can go find this at 3 55 p.m
Whenever I see people lined up outside a club on friday night
I just think look at these poor people who don't know video games exist
That really just that's how I feel about sex. That is how I that's some that's the
All right, thank you matpat that was our special guest for the day matpat
Thanks for listening to the pcp featuring matpat everybody. It was a great time. Follow him at matpat.com
Um
Yeah, that's it everybody. Hey, hey everybody
We were getting those questions from the bonus lounge, which you can check out if you go to patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators one dollar gets you into the bonus lounge with all that goofy shit going on and five dollars
Of course gets you access to the bonus episodes including the new one that is out
That should be out by now, right? Yeah, it's out like today or yesterday and that is fucking insomnia the insomnia cast
Awesome. Oh, we didn't sleep. That was like my favorite bonus episode. It was dope. It was tight as fuck
I think we've been doing good lately. I think I think we've been killing it frankly
I think we might just be able to bring it back. I think I might just be able to suck my own cock
Hey, and look we got we got a personal mate over here. We've got we got a brand new night in the fucking
I'm natin it up. All right, everybody. Good. Bye
I'm sucking
You