Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, and today we're joined by Lethal Aurora Mage.
Today's PCP is brought to you by My Burning Rage, aka Fighting.
That's what the topic is.
My deep frustration at the female gender for not condescending to have sex with me.
I will fight them for this.
Where is it?
Why is it?
What could it be?
You're the worst.
You're so bad at intro-ings, topics that you didn't think was good.
This is a real shit.
What do you mean where is fighting?
Let's just fight about this right now.
Where did it go?
Why is fighting not a thing we can just do in society?
It sounds like you want to fight about it.
Why are we all trying to be fucking civilized and advanced?
Why aren't we supposed to address the previous episode thingy segment, or do we do it?
Actually, that happens after our main section here.
We do the whole big topic and then we do that thing.
Now I have to remember for like an hour.
Is there something special you want to mention though?
We could do it.
Yes.
Is something important you want to bring up?
Yeah, because I was contacted by a concerned Lithuanian because of the last episode and
he was concerned that I painted a poor image of Lithuania.
What do you mean poor?
It sounds like a fallout for Radioactive, awesome.
I just want to clarify, you know, that was, I'm picturing Mad Max basically, like Mad
Max, Lithuania.
I haven't seen Mad Max, so I can't confirm.
People can use their imaginations.
Yeah, just keep in mind that was back when I was a little kid and I was born just a year
after Lithuania got its independence.
So it was kind of a little bit in chaos and I'm not sure maybe in the capital it was
better than it was where I lived, but those experiences, you know, those are, that's
how I lived.
I lived in a poor family in a poor neighborhood and that was my experience.
However, I want to make note that like today, Lithuania has done a lot of work to be a lot
more presentable and it's all pretty and nice and even where I live now, it's like
super nice.
I even see tourists.
That's so weird.
Tourists.
Imagine that.
My little town.
That's so weird.
This was before they came to see all the fighting.
That's what they came to see.
Yeah.
They want to see the roaming gangs.
This is before Mage, quote unquote, painted the town purple, if you will.
I was going to say, the Lithuania was independent and then its new savior was born to bring
it into a new age of purple and greatness.
The Lithuanian warrior who would bring the super predators to heal, the violent violence,
if you will.
Well, the rebels.
Oh my God.
The violent violence.
Dude.
That's fighting.
Fighting guys is real and here it is.
What is fighting?
I'm going to tell you.
In some countries such as South Korea, fighting is used as words of cheer.
The meaning of fighting is similar to the meaning of let's go or do your best or good
luck.
Oh my God.
Fight on.
This is like, you ever see an anime when like you'll see like sexy anime girls will
like be cheering on their friends and they'll go, fight all, fight all.
I think that's, and that just means like do, like do your best, do some, do some work.
Urban dictionary.
This is actually the worst definition you've ever forced me to read.
I'm going to beat the shit out of this master and work.
Yeah, I was going to say definitely.
And it's holding a gun to your head.
Here's a better one.
Definition two, fighting, physical contact, or in other cases arguing or disagreeing with
others, including teammates like dance groups, soccer clubs, what the fuck.
I don't know why it brought these up.
It's such a weird way to put it.
Like fighting is like a disagreement between human beings such as dance groups.
Yes.
Like, are you aware of these types of groups of, are they just like really a big, big fan
of like fucking like dance off movies or something and they're just like, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
It's like, bring it on.
Bring it on or something.
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
Okay.
All right.
We're fucking entries on Urban Dictionary.
That's a little terrible.
Yeah.
The right kind.
Man.
All right.
I want to start.
Okay.
Go for it.
I want to start by saying the, the fights that I've had in my youth and adult life, which
are like innumerable.
I kill everyone I see.
No, it's actually, it's actually, I've never really had a proper fight.
I've been in lots of like little boy scuffles in the playground where you sort of push
each other and sort of grab at things, but you don't really do anything and, and you
know, kick.
But like, um, I've never punched someone in, in the jaw, like a good old fisticuss, except
for that one time D'Vu asked us all to do that to him for a, for a, for a meme, a rad
car.
And I was like, one of the most uncomfortable moments of my entire life, I remember that.
The way I saw it was like, Oh, D'Vu, are you sure?
Because I want to do that.
Not because it's you, but because I just want to know what it feels like to really punch
someone in the jaw.
And he was like, yeah, go on, go on, do it.
And I'm like, all right, this is going to be cool.
And I did it.
And now I know what it means to be a fighter.
I'm a fucking UFC champion.
How hard did you hit him?
Um, I didn't go like as hard as I possibly could because you did not clean his clock.
No, I didn't actually want to hurt him, but like, I wanted to make him like, because he
was saying explicitly, I wanted to make him regret this decision.
And he explicitly said, no, as hard as you can, I'm like, all right, I'll hit you hard
then.
I will hit you hard.
Well, that's because he's a madman.
Yeah.
And so I, you know, I put pretty, you know, I've never punched someone.
So I don't know whether it was actually a strong punch or not.
Probably wasn't.
Yeah.
But like, yeah, that's, that's my, that's my, it feels satisfactory.
Was your curiosity sated by this blow?
Um, I mean, if you crave more bloodshed, you want to wake in the beast within, you know,
what it did.
And I pushed everyone in the chin every single day.
Hand shakes are just too beta now.
It's a punch in the jaw.
That's how you say hi.
I distinctly remember that.
Uh, and I, if who asked me to do, I mean, you know, everyone who was there did ride
con too.
Uh, I gave him like the lightest of taps because it was just so, just strange situation
to be in.
Uh, but anyway, but anyway, getting away from that, um, I also have never, ever been in
a proper fight.
But when I was young, I did do, I took like a handful of karate classes.
I, I'm pretty sure I did that.
I might even be wrong.
No, no, I'm pretty sure I did.
Um, I went there and we like grappled a little bit.
I mean, because I was like really young when I did it, like, like 10, maybe.
I can remember 10 years old.
10 years old was when I started my Pokemon journey and I've never stopped ever since.
I do remember playing Pokemon.
I remember a D this made me want to fight.
I remember the deep frustration I had at not being able to figure out how to leave the
first house in Pokemon red, because you have to walk down on the carpet on the bottom
of the house.
Why the hell would that mean you have to leave?
And to that day, I've hated Pokemon forever.
Well, I mean, that took me all of like 15 seconds to figure it out.
Well, fuck you.
It didn't make any sense.
I know the feeling because I think I made that mistake as well in Pokemon blue.
Bad conveyance.
That's what it was.
Get out of here.
You go after it.
Um, yeah, exactly.
I, I know I was, I went to karate classes.
I played Pokemon at the karate classes.
I went there all the time.
We did sparring.
It was cool.
And I fought and it was sick and it's, and it was like with pads and stuff.
I got into one fight in school and it was the, the, the, I didn't, I didn't get to hit
anybody, but I did have an awesome shown in the anime moment.
Um, so, so the whole, the reason there was like backstory to this fight is that there
was this kid who constantly picked on me and gave me shit.
And I was like a fat tubby beta bitch back in the day.
Okay.
So I would just like fucking roll over and let this guy steam roll over me and it pissed
me off more and more.
Like, and this went on for like two or three years.
He would like steal all my stuff and like all this crazy shit.
And then one day just like in gym class, I forget something, something happened, something
snapped and we got into like a legitimate like fight and, and, and, and I just like
got up in his face and I do just fucking leave me alone.
I'm sick of this shit.
And he just cold cocked me right in the face and I can fucking like my lips started bleeding
and everything.
And it was like, everything froze for a second and everybody stopped and I just stood there
like totally unfazed by his blow and just wiped the blood away.
And then he immediately ran like fucking bolted.
And so he was much faster than me.
So I could not catch up to him, but, um, he ran.
I thought you ran.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I was ready to fucking lay this guy out because like I'm a big fat
guy. So I'm twice his size, but he's twice as fast.
So I'm trying to chase after him and he's running away.
And then the gym teacher breaks us up right as I'm about to lay into him because he like
got to the door and was too scared to open the door.
And I was about to fucking unload.
And then we got sent to the principal's office and I got suspended too.
If we're getting punched in the face, that's so strange the way that works.
That seems to be like how it works.
Like when there's a fight, they suspend both people, even if one like is the obvious
aggressor, I guess it's because.
Well, they think you're a fucking pussy.
I mean, I don't actually know.
I don't know if it does happen to me when I hear something funny.
Yes. OK, so like in my childhood, there was
a kid that I would fight a lot with and he was a cubby boy as well.
And his name was Tom. Oh, oh, oh, my God.
You cold cocks me and J-Class mage, mage.
And then you ran away to Lithuania.
This is what was a purple blur. I never knew.
Deep floor.
I was a boy then, apparently, as well.
Jesus.
Damn, well, that's fascinating.
We've had trans representation of the PCP this entire time.
That's true. That's true.
For all of our horrible comments.
Well, I'm a trans anime girl.
But beyond that, like, Tom, did you?
So like, do you remember at all what sparked that?
Like, what finally made him hit you?
I think I think it was just some stupid, like, bullshit about whatever we were
doing in gym class.
But it was like, it was it was just like a thinly veiled excuse for everything
that had been building up over these last two or three years to finally.
The straw that broke the camel's back. Correct.
So that's that's how that's how it happened.
And you know what?
That that is that, you know, that it's very interesting.
There was a similar story that did not happen to me,
but happened to one of my close friends.
Let's call him a rocket.
I've decided I want to start not saying people's actual names.
OK, so. So rocket raccoon was your buddy.
Basically, yeah. OK.
So so so rocket here.
There was this guy.
We were, you know, this was a freshman year in college, as I recall.
And I got to know this guy like halfway through freshman year.
And we became great friends.
But like later on in freshman year, there was this guy.
I believe his name. I'm going to say his name.
I believe his name was Rishi. I believe his name was Rishi.
He was like an Indian name or something.
I don't remember.
But it was something like that Rishi.
And so this guy was just like an IRL shit poster
who would do things like you'd be getting food with the guy.
And he'd say something.
He'd be like, oh, man, I really want like vanilla ice cream.
And you'd be like, oh, yeah, I really like vanilla.
He'd be like, haha, I hate vanilla. It sucks. It's shit. Got you.
And then you're like, oh, OK.
No, it was things along that line.
Like he would simply like just say falsehoods
and then catch you in believing his lies.
Just a very mundane things like that.
Just and I guess it gave him some sort of jolly, some sort of thrill.
But so the point is just like he would he did this like for this
for the whole year.
He lived on the same floor as Rocket.
And Rocket is this short Jewish kid,
whatever, like good friend of mine.
But the thing is he had done Krav Maga, I believe was Krav Maga.
I might just be saying that because he's Jewish,
but I'm pretty sure it was Krav Maga.
What is that?
And so he knew he knew his shit.
He knew how to handle himself.
Oh, Krav Maga is like the Israeli martial arts.
They do the army gets trained.
So it's it's serious.
It's like this is how Gal Gadot took out those Palestinian children.
Krav Maga.
So we're talking about the serious shown in shit.
All right.
And so what one day Rishi, just for whatever reason,
to be the hilarious madman that he was simply stood in front of of Rocket's
door with his hands like across like blocking the door and just said,
ha, ha, you can't come into your room like Rocket's room.
Rishi, who did not live with him, was just standing there
saying you can't come into your room.
And Rocket is is is is a is a small, calm, peaceful creature.
But at this something snapped, something snapped at this moment.
He had simply had enough.
So so my boy Rocket just calmly lifts his fucking leg,
twist himself sideways and just fucking donkey kicks him right in the fucking
chest and sends him a hurdling across the fucking room, crashing into a pile
on the other side of the fucking room and has vacated the doorway now.
Let's go.
That's how you handle problems.
That's how you handle fucking people giving you shit.
And so Rishi just stands up, goes, what the fuck, dude?
And then just runs away and that's that's what it was.
That that's what that kind of leads me into something I wanted to bring up
and kind of you're a hero rocket.
But God, the main reasons I decided to be on this episode.
Do you think?
Because I do think I think that we have we have unjustly banished fighting
from our our culture.
I think absolutely.
I think I think it's I think there's just something primal in us
that like physical conflict can solve problems and strengthen bonds and make
and clear things up quickly and efficiently through physical combat.
And I think exercising that for more sophisticated means of conflict
resolution has made us worse as a species.
Yeah, I definitely agree.
I just think I definitely I feel like you know what's interesting,
mate, I was going to say, I bet this issue is a very male, female divide.
I was everybody.
I kind of I kind of agree with that, mate.
It's just the way the brains work and stuff.
I feel like there's definitely male bonding that I've never truly experienced
by eating a shit out of somebody and then coming to resolution.
I think I think we're all going to have to fight at RAGCon four.
So we're going to strengthen our bonds.
Mage versus the world.
I tell this for a while in the way that, yes,
it is more of like a female thing to not use violence.
But people are like generally scared of violence because you could get a medical
bill if you get hurt badly and it's like, oh, I don't want to be responsible
if I could go to jail.
But it's like it's turned like most men into like weak soy boy
pussies who don't do anything like they like not to make fun.
We are not immune from this.
We are just as guilty as we don't like not to like belittle women necessarily.
It is just like the other women are weak in the way that they don't fight.
But like fighting does like.
I don't know.
Is there's like a biological primal?
Yeah, there's a biological reason that like it's self preservation.
Like males used to fight for dominance, for attention,
whatever females have to preserve themselves because they bear children
and harm to them, harm to the whole, you know, species.
Yeah.
And it's like a lot of people.
Well, yeah, but like men, they they they they fight like that
and they communicate through physical violence and grandstanding
and being like, oh, look at me, I've got ripple dabs and giant penis.
And I'm really tall and I'm a snushew.
Yeah, yeah, we got to communicate so much back to the ancient Greeks.
We got to just strip naked and go into the arena.
But like, yeah, but what I'm getting at is like
men aren't as good at expressing emotions in other ways with with like speech.
It's like a lot of enemies, a lot of guys just, you know, fight it out
and then become best friends.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
That speaks to something inherent in our brains.
And it's not like every man has to be like that.
But every man at the moment is like forced to be like that
because if you do anything, you're going to jail and nobody wants that.
So nobody ever works anything.
And it's like, I mean, fuck, you know what it is.
There's been a trend these days.
And this is a real fact that it's a real fact that these days
women do much better than men in like the school system.
Oh, and I was having at least a little conversation with a friend about this.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And like the reason that people bring up a lot, you know, this has been said a lot,
but that we we have sort of catered our educational system
to cater to girls because girls are more peaceful.
They are like more calm.
They learn model student, you know, and they say boys are treated as defective girls.
Yeah, I feel like I feel like you watch the same videos I did.
Probably. Probably. I've seen quite a few about this.
Well, I mean, like even like, you know, back in like the 80s and shit,
if you got into a fight in school, like the gym teacher would ref it
and then you just fucking hash it out.
And then when you're done, like you just parted ways.
Like, you know, you know what it is?
That's how shit used to get settled, man.
It's also that's the thing.
It's also the helicopter parents as well.
Like, you know, they don't want their kids to get hurt.
Right. Right.
That's exactly what I was going to say.
It's just it seems to me it's it's this it's a risk aversion
that I think is the is the main like driving factor here.
It's that, like, if you're like the baby boomer generation was a
generation that had like they had like a million siblings.
And that was still that was like right after World War Two.
And those guys were like, like the times hadn't changed it.
But with the baby boomer generation, with like all the civil rights
stuff happening and like the way the world's changing and everything's
becoming like safer and more like organized and neat.
I feel like the baby boomer generations because this is definitely
my experience with my parents.
My parents are maybe it's just the world like the way the media has changed
things, the way we were aware of so much stuff that's happened.
For example, like child like like kidnapping, you know, like rape,
molestation, all that stuff has plummeted.
And yet concerned from parents is that an all time high and and like
parents don't want their kids like it feels like it's bigger than ever
because we get more coverage for the small events that do happen.
Exactly. And just like in the same way that this gives us a blind spot
with stuff like that, like you'd be very safe, much safer than you've ever
been in history to let your kids play outside, even at a young age.
But like it we don't we don't perceive it that way.
Exactly because we hear more about the same things that does happen.
Like I said, like last episode, I was just like it's the last episode,
you know, when I was like six, five, six years old, and I was allowed
to go play alone in the neighborhood, even though, as I said, toxic dump.
Yeah, you said like the neighborhood was terrible with like lots of terrible people.
But, you know, I wasn't looked after.
But like nowadays, my sister has a child that's my nephew.
And she probably wouldn't let him go play without supervision,
even even though the neighborhood is very small and very easily monitored.
And the weird thing is, though, like if you if you are the one parent
who like breaks this trend and decides to let their kid run around outside
like in America, you get fucking arrested or like neglect or something.
It's the whole culture is shifting a huge way.
The thing it's the same as like as like, you know,
letting your kids like fall over and graze their knees or like bruise themselves
or and do all this sort of stuff.
You're supposed to let them, you know, catch colds and and run around in mud
occasionally, not all the time.
You're not supposed to encourage it.
But like if you let them make mistakes like that, they then learn by themselves
instead of being told and you can't go outside in the woods.
It's it's full of bugs and bugs are scary.
You are scared of bugs.
And then it like it it ends up with like, you know, people my age
are like, they're so sheltered that they like a bug.
I can't I can't deal.
I mean, I know people can't deal with bugs, but like so many people can't deal
with any bugs and in any capacity.
And I'm like, yeah, you are an adult and you are a hand for my friends with them.
It's like like we have a bunch of adults who are like need babying.
They they are a handful and I can't imagine like getting along with them.
Yeah. And you know what?
This reminds me, I think the real problem here is utopian thinking.
And it reminds me of like my current like favorite phrase in the world.
It's a popular one, but it's still my favorite.
It's the perfect is the enemy of the good.
And this is what like society, I think we would all agree would be better off
if we are a little bit less helicopter parenty over our kids.
But the thing is, though, if you are less helicopter parenty
and you are the one in a million parent who gets your child kidnapped
and like killed or whatever, then like even if on a utilitarian perspective
that the greater good has gained more than has been lost by this one child
who was just, you know, by freak coincidence happened to be the one
who was kidnapped and like destroyed and fucking destroyed in a game of Pokemon Smash.
Then, you know, like then you'll feel like, oh, no, like this was a huge mistake.
What I have done and it's a risk aversion.
That's why I keep saying it.
And like our perfect society, everyone wants like the utopia
where no one's ever hurt.
Everyone's perfect all the time.
We all grow up into perfect people and there's never any suffering.
But that's not real life.
Suffering is an inevitable, unescapable part of being a human.
I think we should we need to be exposed to it to toughen us the fuck up.
The thing is, though, a lot of these laws and enforcements of this sort of behavior
is because people look at like the worst case scenarios.
And if we are even more lenient than the people who are actually terrible
to their children and stuff would get away with it.
And that's what we're trying to prevent, but in doing so,
we're also enforcing the sort of helicopter parenting.
It's kind of sad because like if you if it's a group
we're trying to prepare kids for a perfect world, you know,
you want to give them that perfect world, you want to give them that perfect life.
And because you're sculpting them for this like kind of utopian life,
they're too free to deal with what actually is.
But if you prepare them for what actually is a world where like you're going to get hurt
and you're going to get fucked up, you're going to be better equipped to deal with the world.
And you will have a better life.
So like it's counterintuitive.
But like you got to like let your kids know that shit's not going to work out all the time.
You really do.
Like there's a there's a fantastic episode of Star Trek The Next Generation.
I can't remember the name of fans, one of the most famous.
But the premise is just that I know this is fiction,
but it's that Cap'n Picard gets to relive a moment in his life.
One of his defining moments where he he got stabbed through the heart.
And I mean, he got he was saved because they live in the future
and they had technology to save him.
But he got his fucking heart stabbed and he almost died.
And like he gets he goes back and he changes that history so that that never happened.
And what it made what it did to him was it made him like much more of a pussy
and like much less like he had never been exposed to that kind of danger and like overcome it.
So he just was more of a pussy.
And so he was like instead of being like a fucking badass captain that everyone loves,
a philosopher god king, he is like just some pussy researcher
who like he has a fine life, but it's nowhere near as like amazing
or as like beneficial to the world or the universe as like the Captain Picard
that did exist who went through this like it was a it was a dumb thing he did.
He like fought a guy in a bar.
He got fucking stabbed through the heart.
And like if he had lived in the past, he would have died.
But it's those experiences that made him like such a fucking badass.
And you know, like that's really just what we're talking about here.
And it reminds me that.
Oh yeah, go on, go on.
I'm absolutely convinced that if I grew up in a more like
not necessarily a violent world, but like a world that allowed expression
through physical stuff rather than speech,
I would like be a much more confident, you know, person in general.
Because as a shy boy, talking is always like my least favorite thing to do.
But like action wise, I'm always the sort of person who would like,
you know, if there's something that everybody notices,
but nobody wants to do anything about it because they're like,
I would be the one who just does the action to get things rolling.
Like at the airport just recently, there was like a big old,
when you go through security, you got all the trays and stuff,
and they keep piling up.
And I just like, I get involved and I want this thing to move,
not just for me, but for everyone.
I grab the empty trays and I stack them in the thing
so that everybody can move along.
And I'm just, I work it like, I do more through my actions
than I could ever do through my words, because I'm not a talkative person.
Doing podcasts has turned me into somewhat of a talkative person.
But in real life, I would just rather,
I would rather be like, I would rather not be able to talk.
You know, it's the sort of like, I'm so much more physical.
It doesn't come across at all in my YouTube work, obviously.
But like, I'm so much more physical than I am vocal.
And in a world where-
Ibsby's talk is let's get physical, the little facts.
But like, in a world where like, I could, you know,
if a bully was fucking roughing me up and I couldn't like,
there was no system in place to tell him off.
Or like, if it wasn't scary for the bully to try and attack me
because he doesn't want to get detention.
I mean, obviously you would get in trouble if you try to fight someone.
But like, there was never any like, proper fighting
or like, resolving of conflict.
It was all sort of, you know, people yelling at me.
And I'm like, I don't want to yell back because I don't do that.
I would rather they punch me so that I can know for sure.
How they feel about me so that I can punch them.
And I'm like, I wouldn't love that.
But I never had any opportunity like that to like-
For you, for you, the ideal world would be to be like that manga called Gone.
Are you familiar with that one?
Yeah, the guy.
It has no words.
And you're just a badass little dinosaur guy,
just like going about world, kicking ass and just being cool.
I mean, yeah, it's, I'm sure like a lot of shy boys love Shonen
for this escapist fantasy of-
Doing violence to do, you know, to do anything.
For me, it's a little difficult to really say either way,
because like, for my story, as you could tell,
I was a very extroverted, very sort of fight person.
Mange did fight people.
She didn't fuck around.
I was very extroverted.
Like I said, I greeted strangers.
I fought with people when I needed to.
I wasn't afraid of anything.
But then I got a bully.
And the thing is, up until that point,
all my fights were more or less fair.
It's usually one-on-one.
Someone else maybe was watching, maybe not.
It's just, it's, you know, it felt fair, winner-lose.
But with this bully, she always, she was, I think, my age,
but she looked older due to makeup and clothes and stuff.
And she always hung around with guys much older than her.
Like, I was like 13 or so when I first met her,
but the guys hanging around with her were like 18 or so, probably.
Okay.
Much taller, much bigger.
Was she fucking, was she fucking them?
I'm just curious.
I don't know, but she probably was,
because why else would they hang around with her?
That's true.
No, but seriously.
My fellow big towels, hell yeah.
Again, it's a little hard to talk about this,
because it was very defining.
Hard in my life.
But yeah, she, it was never a fair fight.
She always had them around and she mentally harassed me,
I guess, verbally abused me before fighting.
But the thing is, I didn't have a chance to necessarily fight back.
I did try once, but that didn't end well.
And I was scared because those guys were around,
and even if I were to defeat her, you know, they're gonna beat me up.
And she was never alone.
And the thing is, she was-
Well, my guess is that, I'm guessing those guys never actually beat you up,
but it was that the threat was there.
Yeah, well, I was a little kid, I didn't know.
And I fought with guys before, I never really had the mentality,
oh, they're not gonna beat me up just because I'm a girl.
You know, I fought with everyone who would fight.
So yeah, and the thing is, she wasn't in my school,
she wasn't in my neighborhood.
She was kind of like the neighborhoods,
well, not even the neighborhoods, the town's boogeyman for me.
I didn't know where she would pop up, but if she did,
and if I was alone, I'm screwed.
And even if I was with a friend,
I couldn't really trust my friends to help me out because the first,
maybe I think the first and second time I met with her,
I was with a friend, the same one as well.
She wasn't really helpful, let's say.
And because of her, because of the unfairness and injustice,
I became very reclusive and shy.
And I think because of her, in a way,
because of the whole situation started just avoiding outside
and started being scared of people, strangers mostly,
I became very self-conscious, just fearing people.
And now I became the weenie I am today.
That's very interesting.
I mean, I can totally see why it would lead to that.
I mean, for me, my experience was definitely more like Gibbs.
I mean, I think it is an interesting phenomenon.
You know, they say that, what's the generation after millennials?
Gen Z, is that what they call them, right?
I have no idea.
Is that the right one?
The last one, the last generation before we all care.
The munchies, the Christ consciousness generation.
Yeah, whatever it is, whatever it is they call it.
The post jobs, the one after millennials.
They say that that generation is much more conservative.
That's what they say.
And I think I know why.
I think that, in America, the political landscape is divided
in such a way that the Democratic party just owns a set of ideas,
the liberal side of things, and then the more conservative,
including the Republicans, I guess the libertarians,
and that sort of group, that encompasses a different batch of ideals.
And going back to, so there was the greatest generation
who fought in World War II, then there was the baby boomers
who were their kids, our parents.
And the baby boomers were the free love movement
in response to their hard ass World War II fighting parents
who were the most badass people ever.
And so our parents, they rebelled against that.
And they felt like, no man, it's all about freedom
and treating people great and everyone being equal.
And everyone's a winner, everyone gets a gold sticker.
Exactly, because their parents were such hard asses
in the changing world of all this new technology,
and radio, well radio had been a while,
but all this new stuff that was happening.
And then our generation is the children,
the millennials, the children of those baby boomers.
And so most millennials were coddled, without a doubt.
We're the coddled ones who were raised by,
are caring and protective parents.
Yeah, and it's not just a normal generation switch
where you rebel against the previous generation
because it's just how it is.
But with the internet coming in and connecting the world,
it's sort of combined with people being soft.
It just sort of made it so that there was no way to become tough.
That's true.
Because you could hide it at home,
and laws will pass when people bruise their knees
or cut themselves on a piece of glass.
Like no more glass in the city, like what are you talking about?
Like all these weird things are coming up.
And it's like, if we had the capacity to rebel
against our soft parents, we would have.
But we just got sort of trapped.
Your kids, you can't do shit.
All you can do is become an adult.
All you can do is just sort of put on a balaclava
and say, Antifa, and be a big old crazy,
throwing rocks, molotov cocktails.
But like, there's so much police, they're so big.
They got truncheons and guns.
What are you going to do about it?
The problem is that we get involved.
They're going to slice us in half,
and we're going to die.
To me, the problem is seriously
that we've involved the government
in so much of what should just be private interactions.
Yeah, like small towns are now, you know, worldwide.
The whole state, it's fucking crazy.
Yeah, and it's kind of just a natural consequence
of globalization and just the increased reach
of through fucking telecommunications.
It's just a psychological reaction to the fact
that we're so hyper aware of all the minutiae of bad
that it feels like it's on our doorstep,
even if it's half a world away.
That's for sure.
But I think that the Generation Z,
or whatever it is, after the millennials,
those guys, and the reason they're conservative,
or getting more conservative, I think, is because-
The parents are all pussies and they hate it.
Yeah, they are the reactionary generation
who have recognized the damage that's been done by-
Mom, why are you so goddamn gay?
Yeah, why are you so gay, mom?
What the hell?
Mom and mom.
Like, it's just that, and it's that the right owns,
like the right just owns the ideas of freedom.
And the ideas of personal responsibility.
Those are just ideas that belong to the right in America.
And because of that, the whole generation
has been pulled in that direction.
And you see that with the whole, like, I don't know,
like the whole anti-feminists on YouTube and the-
How did this get political?
Or are we just gonna have to talk about fighting?
Well, it's all real.
I mean, fighting is quite-
I'm just talking about generational issues.
Politics is all about fighting,
but it's like the most boring kind with outlets.
But speaking of politics being fighting.
I've been in so many fights, dude.
I like Quarter Circle and Hadouken, so I'm the best fighter.
It's fucking sick.
I was gonna say, that's a good one too,
but speaking of political being a fight,
let's talk about like verbal online badass,
you know, urban warfare on Twitter fighting.
Before we do that, I wanna say a very quick story,
because I didn't get to talk much about my fighting days this episode.
A fun thing that happened that I had completely forgot,
but I remembered for this episode,
that used to happen is like,
my neighborhood would have fights with another neighborhood.
So it was kind of like-
Gang warfare!
The cop killers versus the rowdies!
The violent violence and her gang going against the fucking interlopers.
No, no, I was-
The indigo interlopers.
Violent violence versus the indigo interlopers.
The war of purple, which hue is best?
Fan art now, get on it.
Young mage with a fucking spiked baseball.
The fucking magenta mobsters.
Was there a leader of the opposition, mage?
Your indigo parallel?
I wasn't even the leader, guys.
I don't believe you.
No, revisionist history, you were definitely the leader.
Continue, please.
I'm sorry, mage, please.
I never really met the leader.
I saw, you know, I think our neighborhood won,
just because of the-
Who a shadowy figure.
The neighbors, because numbers, we had the numbers on our side.
The neighborhood was a lot smaller than ours,
so, you know, we had more people.
We still had fun with the fights.
I barely got to participate, because I didn't won.
I was still, I think, six or seven when they were going around.
The fights were mostly between teenagers, like 14 and up,
so I only got to participate in a few of them.
What kind of fights?
Are we talking weapons or just fist fights?
It was like, now I have to, like, dig back in my memories.
How was it?
Broken bottles.
They're just like, literally, shooting each other.
Just fucking gunfights.
Oh, wait, when the craze happened with the, like,
the, what do you call, those P-shooters or something,
those guns?
Like a BB gun or something?
Yeah, I didn't own those, so I didn't participate in those.
Those happened later.
But they used BB guns against each other?
Yeah, they used BBs.
Dude, this is sick.
That's pretty serious, all right.
The age was literally in a shonen anime.
This is insane.
But before that, but before that, I remember, like,
I was part in one where we were, like, devised a plan.
It was like, okay, guys, you take this route
and you guys take this route and we're going to surround them
and we're just going to beat the shit out of them.
And like, oh, they have, like, people watching over there,
so be careful, they'll see you coming.
Kind of striking for real life.
So this is, like, a lot of tactics for, like, little kids.
Yeah, and it's like, ah, we'll lead them
into our neighborhood's old Soviet minefield,
and we'll have them in there.
The closest my life ever came to stuff like that
was, like, snowball fights, which is lame.
I mean, it's kind of cool.
We're talking about how millennials
are all fucking pussies, but Mage over here,
six years old, was drafted into a conflict.
Child soldiers.
She's the real child soldier.
Fuck, Munchy, it's Mage.
It's fucking Mage.
We're not giving Mage enough credit.
The violent violence is fucking on the prowl.
You know, I just, when I was young,
like, the closest thing I had to anything like that
was when I was at summer camp,
I know I told the story last time,
but, like, my mom would roll up
and she'd find me, like, with, like, dual-wielding sticks
and, like, having pine cones in my belt as grenades
and, like, ready to fucking kill.
I, like, I don't know what we would do.
We would divide up into teams,
and this is at the YMCA summer camp in the woods.
It was fucking sick.
This is instantly less impressive than Mage's.
I know, I know.
Like, we didn't even really fight.
We just, like, got geared up and then just, like, felt cool.
Like, that's what we did.
Well, that sounds like the American equivalent
of fucking war-torn Lithuania.
Who wants to hear a story of how I got banished
from my own neighborhood?
Oh, I do.
How did that, how is this possible?
Okay, so...
Their own leader.
My neighborhood.
I wasn't the leader, oh my god.
That's what you say now.
My neighborhood got together to, like,
build a little base for, for itself,
like, a little house or whatever,
and they were building nearby my house,
because there was a really good spot,
and it was sort of like, it wasn't necessarily...
When you say neighborhood,
do you mean, like, all the kids and teenagers from around?
Yeah, it's like...
Just like...
I can't really describe it.
It's like, I live in this area that's like, it's sort of like...
There's a group of houses,
and they're kind of surrounded by streets,
or like, the city centers, or stuff like that,
and like, it has its own little area
that's kind of disconnected from other areas,
so I call that the neighborhood.
It wasn't like, you know, blocks or whatever.
Yeah.
It's a little hard to describe.
Oh, so like a cul-de-sac or something?
Is it like, like a road,
like one road that goes in and out?
Road street, home.
I guess kind of, it could maybe something like that.
It's, I mean, whatever I can describe...
A similarly kind of like...
Okay.
I don't think it's anything equivalent to American layout of houses or whatever.
Okay, that's fine, but how did you get banished?
I need to know.
Yeah, so yeah, so they came off the group project
for that little base and stuff,
and they were building near my house, near to my house,
and the thing is, I was really excited about it,
because, you know, I was sort of part of it,
and I was, you know, very excited.
Oh, hey, a base.
It's neat.
And the problem was, though, they were making a lot of noise,
so I think it was my parents or someone living above,
like, somewhere from my house,
because we didn't own a house,
we were living in an apartment,
and they were like, you know, sort of,
somewhere from that area,
complained and had all the progress sort of like,
told them to take it down,
but then like, for some reason,
the neighborhood kids, some of them,
got this idea that I was responsible for it,
like, I complained to my parents or something.
Oh, they thought you were a rat.
Yeah, they, yeah, and they blamed me.
An adult informant.
And they blamed me for it,
even though I was super excited about the whole project,
and they were like, you're not allowed to like,
go into the neighborhood for a month,
and if we see you, we're gonna beat you up.
And also, oh, Jesus, all right.
So I had to sneak around to go see my friends and stuff.
So you still went, you risked it all?
I wouldn't mind fighting the younger kids,
but like, the teenagers were a bit tougher,
especially since they never went around alone.
Fucking, now this is Metal Gear solo.
This is still famous, well.
This is like the main character gets fucking ostracized arc
of like a shonen manga,
where it's just him against the world for a while.
Mage is going through all the motions.
Mage, you should definitely make a manga about your life.
My life is a great idea.
It wasn't even all that exciting.
But you made it exciting for the narrative.
Yeah.
Mage, right now you're just like hiding,
you're in hiding just like being like the hermit weeaboo.
We're in the middle of a time skip.
So in like two or three years,
the time skip's gonna end,
and like you're gonna come out of hiding
more powerful than you ever were.
Mage knows, the Geneva boys, the fucking UN,
will convict her for crimes against humanity
if they find out that the leader of the violent violets
is in fact still alive and not dead.
Like, you know, as the Osama bin Laden ally
that she is in real life, you know, don't,
so she's gotta lay low, gotta lay low.
Yeah, I'm picturing you as solid snake violets
on top of Metal Gear Rex, shirtless, bare knuckle boxing,
like a snake, you know, who's the indigo,
what is it, ingrate, the indigo ingrate,
that's what his name is, that's what I'm calling him.
Beautiful.
Just like this,
Mage with this long flowing purple bandana,
the exact hesitalism of value we need.
Okay, so since we're really, like,
since you guys seem to like this narrative,
I'll tell you one more thing.
From the opposing, like, the neighborhood guys, people,
this was before I went to school,
and so when I started going to school,
I had this classmate and I had a crush on him
and it turns out he was from the opposing neighborhood.
Oh, my head hits all the beats!
Fuck!
Dude, how did it go?
What happened?
He didn't go well, he liked to-
You had to kill him in the end.
No, he had to murder her.
I actually confessed to him that he liked another girl
in the class that everyone liked, so-
Oh, but you knitted out-
Disgusting.
So he had to die.
No, I'm just joking.
Now he's dead.
Hell yes, that's fucking awesome.
Incredible, incredible.
Fucking, the rat is in cop killers embarrassing,
not even real.
No.
The violets and the indigos.
Clearly not even, like, we have a whole
untapped potential lore over here
that we've never even touched on.
It's true.
We need a dramatic retelling
of your entire childhood mage.
I want a graphic novel on my desk on Monday,
monochromatic purple, start to finish, go.
Yeah, you should re-tool the bot that's in your Discord
to make it turn it into, like, Endless War 2,
but, like, purple version.
Yes.
No.
The Violet Violets.
I don't like fighting anymore, though.
That's so sad.
You need to be reawakened.
Like, you're, like, basically,
literally Unohana from Bleach,
which I think is what you said last time.
I know, I know.
But that's pretty much exactly it.
You just need to reawaken your bloodlust.
No, I was gonna say, I was gonna say,
she's more like Simone right now,
because she's had a traumatic experience
that has made her sheltered.
She needs someone to come along
and reawaken her vigor for life.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Hey, I like drawing.
Yeah, just like Simone,
like staying in his room and sculpting communes.
But we all know Mage,
because the things you draw
are always, like, super creepy and bloody.
We know what's really down deep inside.
There's a killer that lives.
You just need some super sexy anime chick
to come into your life and, like,
worship you, and you'll feel so much better.
She needs a commune.
A new commune.
Commune 2, aka Nia.
All right, anyway, hey, hey.
Let's talk about fighting on the Internet
with people who give you shit.
No, it's lame.
No, that's good.
But that's how most fighting is done in the world.
Can we talk about how that is not real fighting
and it is gay and it's stupid?
Okay.
I want to say before we go on to that,
just one little thing.
Sure.
I went to, like, I forgot to say this.
I went to Taekwondo practice once,
and I thought it was really lame.
And I realized then that I don't care
about, like, being able to fight.
I just like being in danger.
It's so cool to be in a dangerous situation,
like, to do something you're not allowed to do,
to jump over a fence, to get a ball,
when there's the possibility of a CCT camera getting you.
And then you're getting put in jail,
and when you're a little kid,
that's what you think can happen.
Yeah, doesn't that mean you thrive in our current society?
Because literally everything has a risk of punishment now,
because everything's stated off.
Yeah, I mean, well, I mean, not really.
But, like, when I was young, and I thought,
I would go, like, there was this time a ball
went over the school fence, and I was like,
it was after school, and the school was closed.
And I jumped over it, even though I knew
that there was a camera there,
and that I could get in trouble next day.
And nothing happened.
But I was like, nobody's going to get this ball.
Everyone's scared.
But I'm the guy who would, like, silently do the cool thing.
And then everybody would be like, whoa.
That's why talking sucks.
I like jumping over fences and punching people.
I want to be a fucking gremlin.
I want to be a fucking real-life gremlin man.
And I'm not allowed to, and it sucks.
Speaking of Taekwondo, going to a practice and sucking,
it's definitely true that martial arts is so much
about the fundamentals that do not look cool.
And fighting really, even the coolest UFC matches,
look pretty basic and not anime, which is unfortunate.
But I've been watching a lot of Joe Rogan's podcast
for the last, I don't know, a couple years at this point.
And he's obviously a fighter, a trained fighter,
and he still has UFC people on all the time,
because that's one of his jobs to commentate or whatever.
And it's given me an appreciation.
I haven't watched any of the fights,
other than the really big ones,
of CM Punk getting his ass handed to him several times
at this point.
But it's just cool to hear an expert like him talk about it.
And just on a technical level,
to describe getting people into fancy holds and arm bars
and get their fucking neck in a chokehold or some shit,
it's cool.
And I'm sure for the people watching,
it doesn't look that cool to just watch two people like Bob
and weave and throw out a jab and then run away.
But that's just how a soccer game doesn't look cool
until they get a goal.
But once you understand it more,
you get that every little thing is part of a grand plan
to conserve energy.
Only you expend as much as you need.
I watch so much anime that when I watch UFC,
it eventually just turns to a ground game.
And it's two guys in swim trunks fucking each other.
And it's just too gay for you.
It's just like gay porn and not fighting.
I'm sure all the coolest things I've ever thought I've done
looked terrible and really cringy.
But the feeling of doing them was the main thing.
The feeling of other men's ballsack against my face.
The highest form of art is the male form.
So did you all try to take martial art classes?
I went for a while.
I went to a Taekwondo class
and I just didn't like it immediately.
That's not bad, Tom.
That's cool, Tom.
I only went to one class.
I don't even remember which martial art it was.
It was in the sort of gym.
So there were a lot of other activities
that other people were doing.
I didn't like my class.
So I just kind of pissed off to go lift weights.
Because I like lift weights.
So I've done that.
That's what I've done.
Yeah.
It's a lot easier.
If someone's going to kill me, then what am I going to do?
All you need is a gun and any amount
of martial arts training I've got.
I mean, yes, you could be smart
and maybe just harm them or something.
My dad's like a trained fighter.
He knows all this crazy shit.
And he's just like, martial arts is great.
But at the end of the day, you really
have to know how to like a street fight is totally different.
And all the forms and condoms and shit you learn
don't really mean things.
You have to know how to fight for real.
Sure.
The fact that policemen can fail to stop a guy
from getting them, even though they have a gun,
is just sort of like, even if they're trained in martial
arts or hand-to-hand, something or other.
Policemen have very low standards for physical combat,
which is why they go straight to the gun every time,
which is unfortunate.
Maybe in America.
I don't know how it is.
Yeah, OK.
I mean, in America, we have lots of guns,
so it's different from, you know.
Yeah, there's no guns in the UK except for special types
of policemen who are allowed to have them.
Really?
So even your normal policemen don't
have, normally, don't have guns?
I think they have like stun things and batons and whatever.
OK, we have a baton.
But like, pathetic.
And, but like, they're trained to use the hands
and to say, stop, or stop doing that really loud.
I mean, that's how it should be, you'd think.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think?
I don't, I don't want to say something.
Well, I mean, OK.
I shouldn't have said this.
OK, if you're like robbing a thing.
I retract my statement.
You're right.
Let's move on.
OK, fine, fine, fine.
Yo, Twitter is lame.
Twitter is dumb.
Everything that happens on there is a waste of time
and a problem.
Do you want, do you want to know why Twitter is a problem?
Why it's gay and why it's dumb?
It's because all of us have this urge
to settle our conflicts physically and we can't.
So this is how we get it out of our system,
inefficiently and pathetically.
You know, I definitely agree with that.
But and I was also going to say that I don't think Twitter,
like when you're man to man with someone,
you're a face to fucking face.
And you've got a grievance.
Like all I'm going to say is that like it's so different
than like tweeting with somebody back and forth.
There is a threat of physical violence.
Yeah, there's no threat of physical repercussions on Twitter.
You can say whatever you want.
And it's because of this.
If you go have your coffee and nobody gives a shit.
Because Twitter is so immediately,
Twitter is consequence free.
Things can really snowball
and like they can get way out of proportion
and especially because the fucking media and like I get why.
But people take tweets as like gospel
and they like if you use a word on Twitter,
that's offensive or whatever, like, I don't know, faggot,
then like, oh, well now you are officially a homophobe
because you use the word faggot on Twitter.
And like maybe you are a homophobe.
Maybe you're not.
But like the Twitter shouldn't be the arbiter
of whether you are or not.
You know, I agree.
And like I hate that we use Twitter as like a,
it's like the official, it's like we treat someone's Twitter.
The same as we treat like a published book they've written.
They're like equally valid a representation
of like the arguments of this person.
You know what it is?
It's like being a homophobe is only like,
I mean, I don't think being a homophobe is illegal at all.
So like the only thing that people have
to like leverage that like, oh, I don't like homophobes.
Like what are they, what can they do?
They can't punch you because everyone's a fucking pussy on Twitter.
Nobody's gonna actually beat you up.
The actions are illegal, but the stance,
the personal thoughts in your head so far
have yet to become illegal.
So far, so far.
There's a lot of thought policing been going on.
But yeah, but like since people can't like,
if somebody says yes, I think because I'm, you know, maybe,
I'm a Christian and I think gay people are wrong.
Like that guy, everybody know, like he's saying it outright
and people are like, oh, I hate that guy.
He's a homophobe.
What can I do to fuck with him?
I can't punch him.
I can't like physically do anything.
You fucking don't shop at his place.
That's what you do.
Well, you know, yes, that, of course,
but like people don't do that.
They sit on Twitter and try to ruin people's lives in other ways.
Yeah.
Well, like, for example, like that guy,
because they have, they have, they have like, you know,
an urge to fight, but they have no way to actually relieve the stress.
Right.
So your first, your first reaction in your body
is to physically lash out when you see something that embrages you.
Like how many times have you got a really retarded comment
and the first, your first reaction is like,
I just want to lay this person out.
That's just, it's biologically ingrained in us.
I mean, that's, that's true.
Just want to punch shit, dude.
We have to appear to our better angels and recognize
that like when you get a really mean comment,
it's more than likely this person was at their worst
when they wrote that comment.
And, you know, I mean, it's just to your benefit
to try not to flip out.
You know what I mean.
But what I am, what I was getting at is that people,
they, they, they're lobbying, no, not lobbying,
I don't know the word, but like they're trying to get
like more and more restrictions put on what people can say.
So that they're making things more and more illegal,
you know, for like less and less things.
Because people think the fucking government
should dictate personal interaction
instead of just like, if you don't like a guy,
don't shop at his place.
They want, they want to be able to ruin this person's life
for doing this thing that makes them upset
because they can't fight them.
So they have to make it illegal somehow.
But of course, the tool that put, yeah.
The, you know, the, the more it is just,
it just leads to like, where does the line get drawn
for like what a person can be.
And that's the problem.
Because these people go and jail at birth.
Yeah. And like, when you, when you make a speech,
like fucking criminalized or whatever, like, okay,
we've outlawed saying like, you know, racist stuff.
So like, you can't say that like, I hate all, you know, Hispanics.
Like that, that is like racist or something.
Okay. But apparently it is legally acceptable
to say like, I hate all white people.
And it's like, okay, let now logically speaking,
that doesn't make sense why you can do that.
But it seems to be sort of, it's just like, okay,
if the government institutes a policy where like,
you can't discriminate based on race
to stop people from being racist or Hispanics,
then like, let's assume a right wing government
takes over later.
Well, now you've given them the ability,
especially if you ignore that previous thing about like,
you didn't criminalize when people said that,
you know, like white people are all bad or whatever.
Like now you've put a system in place where like,
the attorney or whatever, the district attorney or whatever,
can like, choose to now we can criminalize people
who say they hate all white people.
And let's just let off people who say they hate all Hispanics.
Like the problem is that we put any of these rules into place.
You just need to let people sort out amongst themselves.
And that's exactly what the Supreme Court itself said
when they just fucking put that decision down.
And they said that that guy who didn't,
that serious Christian,
who didn't want to make that wedding cake
for the gay couple or whatever,
they could not compel the him to make that cake.
And damn right.
Cause fuck though, that would be such a fucked up precedent.
I want to say something about that case.
You have to force people to do shit like that.
Now, this could be just a rumor.
I don't remember where I heard this,
but these people who, you know, asked for the cake,
they deliberately went around every single cake shop,
cake shop, looking for someone who would refuse them.
So they were out looking for trouble rather than like.
That is interesting context as well.
No, I heard, I heard from DeVoo.
Like I saw a video he posted,
he was talking about this on Twitter a while ago,
where the lady who was like being charged said
that she knew the guy who asked for the cake and like very well.
And he was, he was okay with it,
but it was like the, you know, one of his friends
that made it a thing that became viral
and then everybody got outraged and neither party,
like the guy who tried to buy the cake
and the person who was selling the cake,
they were on good terms,
but it was like it blew up on the internet
and then she was like fucked over by the government,
which is the reason it's so fucking terrible.
Even assuming that's completely true,
which I would believe that's true.
I, you know, I haven't looked it up myself,
but like assuming that's all true,
I don't even care because I totally believe you should,
if you just are a sincere racist
and you don't want to make cake for whatever race you hate,
you 100% should be allowed to not do it
because you just don't want to.
There was no, I see no reason to force people to do that.
And just as everyone else is trying to think
you're a fucking douchebag
and you get all the social consequences that come with it.
Exactly, because what you do is,
you tell everybody that he did that
and then you stop shopping at his place.
And you know what, you know what,
I would prefer a world where somebody could like punch you
in the face for you being a bigot,
then go to jail over something that goes viral.
About the whole,
because you know what, going to jail does nothing to fix.
It does not fix the person's racism at all.
It doesn't do anything to fix it.
Whereas if you punch the guy in the face
and you have a man-to-man moment about like,
oh shit dude, I guess the Hispanics can punch good.
I respect you now.
Then you've maybe, maybe this person
is not ever as simple as that.
I mean, I mean, something like.
This is, yeah, yeah, but like I just wanted to quickly say
about the whole, you know, not,
if you don't want to sell to these people,
you're free to do.
I think that only for like maybe personal businesses,
like for like, I don't know, like what do you guys have?
Like we have ASDA, you guys have like, what sort of like.
I'm not following that.
Yeah, yeah, Walmart.
Like a Walmart or something.
Oh yeah, okay.
ASDA is owned by Walmart, I think.
Oh, is it?
Okay, well now I know.
Well, yeah, like shops like that should, you know,
accommodate all people of all walks of life.
I only like.
I kind of disagree.
I mean, I kind of disagree.
Well, yeah, I would say that there should be no restrictions
in place about that.
But like, obviously, if you are a supermarket
and you don't let a certain amount of people in,
that's a certain amount of customers you're not getting
and money runs everything.
So like, why would you not?
There's no reason as a big corporation to like deny
a certain group.
If there's no motive for a corporation to do it.
That's just less money for you.
That's just all that it does.
Like a big corporation, like you have this chain sort of
places and stuff like that, you're everywhere.
It's not just one person having their own private little shop
of their own private little things.
So I think.
I think it's the same thing though.
I feel like both the corporations and the personal people
should be able to choose whether or not they sell to anyone.
You can definitely have a situation where like,
let's say a Walmart comes into like a small ish town
and because Walmart can undercut the prices of all the mom
and pop shops, like they all go out of business.
Let's say like they were all ruled, you know,
by fucking Mexican people who, you know,
live in America, whatever, Mexican, you know,
historically, their ancestors.
And like, so all those shops closed down.
There's only Walmart.
Oh, and by the way, Walmart refuses to sell to Mexican people.
Like I get why that's a problem.
That makes sense to like be wary.
But what I would like is that the Mexican community or whatever
makes their own grocery store that does sell to Mexican.
And then they like, because they're such a large population,
they make all the money.
I mean, hopefully.
It sounds like a terrible like idea to have, you know,
just Walmart that only Mexicans can't eat.
And it's like, well, what the fuck are we gonna do?
And it's not necessarily possible for them to just suddenly
make a rival supermarket chain.
But like in like, hypothetically, they would make that
and then they would get so much like,
like a hundred percent of the Mexican profit from that area.
Right.
It's just, when you think about what it means,
like what we're saying is we are going to force people
in businesses to do what the government tells them to do.
We are, and like Walmart doesn't owe its customers anything.
Walmart existing is a pure boon to you.
Walmart could close down and leave today from anywhere it wants.
And like they were 100% in their rights to do so.
So like you're asking Walmart to basically like give you
something it doesn't have to give you if you're, you know,
like imposing.
The thing to understand about Walmart is that you can't,
you can't have a one Walmart decide,
I'm just not going to sell to Mexican people.
Like Walmart has a corporate policy that every Walmart has to abide by.
So if Walmart decided tomorrow they're not going to sell to Mexicans,
every Walmart would have to fucking abide by that.
Well, yeah.
Walmart corporation would not survive a move like that.
Like the backlash from social media would tank the entire company.
Capitalism is absolutely shown.
The whole point of capitalism is to get as much money
from as many people as possible.
So it's a great engine to fight against that stuff.
And also imagine that Walmart tried, like they said,
they had that policy.
No Mexicans allowed.
And then the entire country of Mexico is like,
they can't build there anymore.
That's like.
They just lost a country worth of revenue.
Yeah.
It's like, it's just, it makes no sense.
And it doesn't seem like it would ever happen.
But in the hypothetical that a company did decide to do that,
I would let them.
I wouldn't be like, I mean, I would hate them.
I think that was the stupidest and most horrible thing you could do.
What the fuck?
You know, it'll be all in the news.
But like, I don't think there should be a law that says
you have to cater to every person that comes in.
That's what I think.
And I'm totally for, I got no problem with any race
or any social group or whatever, sell to everybody.
But if like, if I really believe in a principled way in freedom,
and I believe in, you know, being consistent here,
I think it is morally wrong to compel someone's labor
at the point of a gun as the state does.
And by that same token, like as much as I think
it's stupid and retarded, I would say the exact same thing
to like, you know, those small businesses that charge white people
more for things to try and like redistribute wealth
for like black communities and stuff.
They're like small businesses that do that.
I wouldn't shop there.
That's fine.
I mean, of course.
It just makes sense to not shop there.
Yeah.
Like, I'm not going to do it because like,
why would I shoot myself in the foot like that?
But like, you're free to do that.
If you want to discriminate against me, that's fine.
But I'm never going to buy a coffee.
Or you know what, there was a,
like, I heard something on the news recently
about like a business that like, they just had like,
something like a reparations day.
But like, all it was was they just collected money
and then just like gave to like the local African American community.
But like, this was just their money.
So like, that's fine.
That's no problem at all.
They just wanted to give money to people.
That's totally cool for whatever fucking thing they wanted their money.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I just believe in freedom, man.
That's all.
I mean, we're kind of on a huge tangent here.
I forget how we got here.
But no, we're talking about Twitter fighting, dude.
Fighting, fighting.
That's the problem right there.
Uh-huh.
Disagree with the whole.
I mean, I believe in, you know, in the whole freedom.
Maze doesn't believe in freedom, guys.
I don't believe in freedom.
I just, I don't see a reason not to sell to a group of people things.
But Maze, you see what you're doing there.
As you're saying that you don't see a reason,
you're imposing your thought process on other people
by saying that because you don't see a reason,
everyone should do what you think they should do.
No, I never said that.
I'm just saying I'm so...
Well, you're implying it.
I'm explaining what that's implying.
Well, no, I'm not.
I want to say, I want to say, I like this, this, this, this,
this is a difficult topic.
And I, I've yet to set my opinion in any which way.
It's just, it doesn't sound right to me.
So I'm just like, I'm, I'm mildly disagreeing.
But I'm not, I'm not, I'm not agreeing.
It doesn't sound good to say.
I'm not agreeing with the opposite side either.
That's the thing.
I'm just sort of like on the fence, I guess.
I'm not sure.
I think, I think the problem is that like to hold the position
that we're talking about is letting the opportunity
for horrible things to happen.
Oh, yes.
And like that's, that is, that is the price you pay to let,
to, to, to be 100% free.
It's like, you have to give people the opportunity
to do fucking terrible things, like offensive things,
but they also get to reap all the rewards
of doing those terrible things,
which is to piss off everybody who's not a fucking retard.
I feel like there should be some sort of solution,
like a middle ground, like a golden mill between these,
but I can't find it.
The middle ground is that people have money,
and the more people you are nice to,
the more money you will get from your people buying stuff.
Yeah.
So like the more palatable you are,
the more, you know, open you are to anyone and everyone,
the more money you'll make.
So there's an incentive to be nice in a,
in a world where you can do that.
Yeah.
So that, we would, one would hope that that is the compulsion.
By the way, that is the compulsion that a lot of these
huge companies like Walmart are absolutely driven by.
Walmart wants to get money from everybody.
So that's, that's the policy they've adopted.
Seems that way to me anyway.
Anywho, that's my point.
Well, okay, issues noted, issues noted.
Um, all right.
Any, what else do we have to fucking say
about fighting and shit?
Why don't you just die if you fight me?
That's what I have to say.
I, I don't want to punch you.
I just want you to fall down.
Um, I, I've had like a number of like little boy fights.
Like when I was just, you know, I didn't know how to,
because people would, you know, how kids, they,
everyone's scared of actually doing anything
when they're the same age, same height, you know,
they're not bullies, they're just being brats to each other.
And they're like, you know, they say mean things
because they want you to do the first move
because then you're the one who gets in trouble.
And I'm like, I, I don't have a diss track.
I don't know how to say fuck you in any other way.
Or like if I was a rapper, I would just say fuck you
as the, my diss track.
And then bam, bam, you know, that's, that's all it would be.
It was just like, I just want to deck here
because that's all I need to say.
And that's, I didn't really like have like the,
the gumption to do it a lot at school.
But I would always like resort to shoves and like, you know,
being like a weirdo.
I guess it was just like, I was a shovy boy.
I was a weirdo.
I would be like excessively violent at sports.
Like in soccer, like I was, I loved playing defense
because I could kick people.
I think I've said this a bunch of times, like.
See, we're all looking for an outlet, dude.
We all have, you know, we need, we need to bring back duels,
but they just have to be non-lethal.
We have to have like, on the book, duels.
I'd love to slap a guy with a fucking glove
and say duel right now.
I'd challenge you to a duel.
And then it's, it's, you get, there's like regulation for it.
There's like a way that it's, it's, it's, it's designed to be done.
And we can just fucking throw down with people.
And then it's decided to be legal.
Oh, that's a good one.
Ring top hats.
Yes.
Radcon for dual.
Literal duels.
All right, all right.
We should literally kill each other in the ring.
Yeah.
Dude, Radcon four should be, we should hire out
like a wrestling ring and just do that.
Oh man.
Like easy to wrestling.
If we can have some sort of IRL wrestling thing.
Guys, you're missing the most of, we need to,
we need to have Radcon four be in Lithuania
in mage's hometown so we can join the violent violence and fucking throw down.
Like I said, it's a lot nicer now.
Yeah, we're going to bring it back.
As tourists.
We're going to bomb it the fuck out.
So you can bring back.
Mage, our arrival is going to be the end of your time skip.
And that's going to be the next chapter in your manga.
Yeah.
That's good.
When the B cash.
So it's all, it's all nice, it's all nice and presentable now.
But when we're there, well, things are going to go down.
You said you weren't much of a, like a verbal fight boy.
You just, you wanted to get physical.
I would, I would scowl and like want to kill them.
And that's all I would do.
That's understandable.
I was definitely more of a like, I was never good at it.
And I would get really sweaty and nervous and uncomfortable whenever someone like
dissed me via verbs as a young man.
And still to this day, like if somebody comes up to me and starts talking smack.
Oh, get a little hot under the collar when I realized the shit is going down.
And now girls are watching and I need to impress them with my, with my responses.
It's just like, I don't know, I've enjoyed those in history and it feels really good
when you're able to like bring a sick comeback like George Costanza and just like, you know,
defeat someone through a verbal confrontation like that.
I like those.
I enjoy those on the, on the occasions they happen.
But they were unfortunately rare.
A linguistic kill shot.
I was.
Oh, guys.
That's right.
Speaking of stuff like that, what do you think about like the phrase, be the bigger man?
Like in terms of like not resorting to violence and just letting people shit on you.
The thing about being the bigger man is I never really liked that.
It's useful up to a point, like because there is a time if you just continue to be the bigger
man forever, then you're just being a pussy and you're letting people like steamroll you.
So that's no good.
Like, but the thing, I would, I would argue that the idea of being the bigger man,
like we all recognize that at a certain point, like if some dude like punches your sister
and you are the bigger man and don't like confront and you're like, oh, he's not even worth.
Well, at that point it's like, well, now you're just like being a bitch.
Being, being the bigger man is also, it's like a subset of choosing your battles.
It's, it means don't swing wildly for no reason.
But sometimes you do swing.
Sometimes it is a problem.
Sometimes you gotta swing.
I was, I was sort of taught that eventually because like I said, I was, I was the tallest
kid around usually in my age group.
So, you know, for me, like for onlookers, it just looked like I was beating up little kids.
Yeah, that's true.
It's tough to be a big boy because you always look like the bully in a situation.
And it's, it's weird.
It seems like there's a pattern of like small, skinny kids, like bullying, larger,
generally fat kids.
It seems like a pattern.
And then I don't know, maybe it's cause like, I don't know.
I've seen this, like there's that one famous video of like the skinny kid,
like bullying this like bigger, fatter, taller guy who was just like quiet and timid.
And then he fucking like, he like, he picks him up and he like slams him on the ground
because he just had enough finally and it's awesome.
I mean, the reason that happens is I'm sure is because like the young, the small weak kid
is too scared to actually fight the people who are like the real problem.
So they go for, they go for the easier target.
So it's like, it's easy to say someone's fat when they are fat and that's what they do.
I have two more stories I can tell.
Okay, shoot.
Quickly in the neighborhood, like a lot of the fights I noticed I would have like consensual,
like it wasn't like no one was bullying anyone.
We were just fighting because it was cool and fun and we sort of picked fights with each other.
You just wanted to fight.
You kind of, yeah.
Literally a show.
We were not being, you know, watched by any parents or anything and fighting was a past
time I guess.
But anyway, like I think we used to do, the guys of the neighborhood would pester the girls,
but like this is sort of like, it's a, it was an agreement between us.
It was like a sudden agreement.
We all knew this.
We'd never really talked about this, but the guys would pester us.
They would call us names, a specific name actually.
They called us tigers.
I'll explain that later.
And whenever they would do that, the girls would chase after the guys and if they caught
up to the guys, they would beat the guys up and they would come back for more later.
So, you know, it's not like, you know, we were bullying them or anything.
They specifically sought us out to be beat up.
Damn, maybe it was like a fetish thing for them.
They were into it.
And the reason they...
That opens up a lot of doors, mage.
I'm very...
Yeah, it's true.
That's interesting.
And the reason we would call tigers, it wasn't like, it seemed a lot less weird than it does
now is because like, in a way it was for them to tease us.
And but at the same time, we sort of accepted the name and whenever we would like, hear that
and like, sort of like, to signal that we're about to chase them, we would let out a growl.
And so, you were literally a purple tiger.
Kind of, I guess, yeah.
Later on...
So, I'm just...
There's a character in one piece who's called the purple tiger, Fujitora.
I think you are that guy.
I don't know how they look like, but...
That's what I have to say.
Okay.
He's an old man who's blind.
Yes, that's me.
Uh, that's it.
Yeah, sounds right.
Sounds about right.
Yeah, one of my friends got a different name later on because there was a TV series about
like, Xena warrior princess.
And she could do like a similar kind of jump that she did and also the noise she did,
like the work writhing.
And because of that, she got started being called Xena.
The rest of us stayed just tigers.
That's pretty sick, dude.
And the last...
That's so funny.
Like, I just really like that.
How young were you when you were doing that sort of stuff?
No, it was definitely before Xena.
Before eight.
Because like around...
So yeah, it's just sort of a really cute, like child kids running around saying tiger,
because as like a, as like a known, um, initiation of like, let's play...
Yeah, like, let's play tag and then you get to beat me up if I lose.
How do you say tiger in Lithuania?
Tigris.
But that's like the male version.
So the, um, uh, and the general version for the tiger, but we were called Tigris.
That's the plural of tiger for females.
Cool.
And that's...
Yeah, like...
So next time we get to Radcon and Major doesn't show up, we just got to Skype her
and be like, and just call her out and she'll come running and like three hours,
four hours later, she'll be on the plane and then in the middle of the night,
she'll jump across the ocean.
You call me and then you call me tiger and I hang up and like 12 hours later,
you all get punched out of nowhere.
Yeah, exactly.
Out of nowhere.
The violent violence comes through town.
Yeah, exactly.
Just fucking wretches all our shit.
Oh, yeah.
Good to know.
Yeah, I stopped fighting around 12, 13 years old, by the way.
That's when I got bullied, uh, just for the reference.
So all these fighting stories was roughly 10 or younger.
I see, I see.
Yeah, one story, uh, it was around the time I sort of stopped liking to fight.
Around 12 years old, I think.
I think one of my last battles, I guess, so to speak, was in my friend's neighborhood.
The friend was like, she was the daughter of my mom's friend.
So we were friends just because our moms were friends,
but she was like six years younger than me.
And we were playing outside and she got bullied by these group of guys.
And so I stood up for her because, you know, she was a little kid and they were like,
sort of my age, a little bit younger, I think, you know, one or two years off.
So there were three of us girls and three of those guys,
but those two girls just watched, thanks.
And so it was supposed to be one-on-one with me and a guy.
And I remember, you know, throwing punches and punches,
and he sort of blocked by doing like an X in front of him with his arms
because he saw it in Dragon Ball Z.
And remember, specifically, he said, it's like,
hey, guys, this actually works.
And they punched him in the gut while he was distracted.
Why? What? Oh, because he was blocking like too high?
Yeah, he was, yeah.
And then like, because, yeah, because he kind of sort of moved his arms or something like that.
I remember I punched him in the gut because he got distracted.
So I was winning the fight, but then the other guys sort of started hitting me from behind.
But they were all being a little bit chicken about it.
They didn't like pile on top of me.
They just like hit me and then like went back again.
So I wouldn't hit them.
That's even worse.
I know.
And like, I wasn't getting any sort of backup from my friend or her friend's friend.
I hope they're dead.
Fuck.
No, it's okay.
But I...
Disgusting.
But yeah, like, I think I eventually did win the fight.
I don't remember how, but I remember I won the fight.
And then I told him to leave us alone.
And I told my friend I'm going home, well, her home because I was in her neighborhood.
And as I was walking up the stairs, I started crying.
Even though I won.
You did or...
I did.
I started crying.
Were you just...
Did it just hurt or something?
No, I was sort of frustrated mostly because I won all that fight all by myself.
And, you know, those girls didn't help me win any...
You know, at all they were just there watching.
They didn't even go...
Betrayed.
They didn't even go ask for help from like our parents or anything.
And, you know, it could have gotten a lot worse.
I was happy I won, but I was mostly frustrated that I wasn't helped.
But that was usually the case whenever I did fight and I had friends with me.
My friends never intervened, even though the guys would sometimes...
Bitches be trifling, man.
Bitches be trifling.
But yeah.
Well, what a world.
What a life.
And now it's over.
And we've got a new anime life lying before us.
Uh, well guys, I'm out of fucking stories.
How about we just get to the next fucking part?
How about we just fucking fight right now?
Let's just fight.
I'm punching my microphone.
Die.
I'm killing you all.
Fucking idiot.
I'm not his microphone.
All right, let's get the fuck out of here.
Okay, so we're done with the main thing.
That was good.
Let's...
So we're in our next little section here.
Anything to say about our last episode?
So everybody listen out there.
When you're here in this...
So we recorded this two days after the last episode came out.
And we did this.
The way we changed the whole schedule was so that we have time
to like look at the fucking comments of the last episode,
see what people are saying,
and just see if there's anything to be revisited
with that little extra window.
So what the fuck was last week's episode?
I can't even remember.
Childhood?
PCP.
It was the one with all the stuff.
Childhood.
That's the one.
Childhood, yes.
Which I think everybody loved and was great.
Not a lot of people because I think...
I saw a few people be complaining
because we had a lot of people on again, but...
That's true.
We might be slightly overdoing it.
But there were people who were saying that they liked the fact
that there's a rowdiness when there's a lot of people.
A lot of people, yeah, you can't please all of them.
So I'm sorry, you know, people sometimes
are gonna have a few episodes where there's a lot of us
and sometimes we'll have episodes like this.
Well, you know what I would say, though?
I would say that it is...
It's more accessible.
Like the people who are gonna listen
will listen anyway because they like the PCP.
But we should cater to the possible outsider
and do the thing that the outsider would like
because we've already entrapped the general reader.
But it's bringing new audience members is the priority.
You don't think so?
I mean, I agree that that is a priority.
I think that there's no reason to never do a big thing again
because clearly people do like that.
And if we stop doing that for the benefit of the normie crowd
coming in, then the people who did like that
are just gonna be pissed off and annoyed that we're not doing it.
Personally, I like the idea that a few episodes are like,
you know, just four of us and a few episodes are like,
you know, most of us.
I like the variety, I like the randomness.
PCP is like a box of chocolates.
You never know what you're getting.
You never know whether it's got...
You look at the labels and talk and you know exactly what you're getting.
Well, I mean, you know, if you're in the PCP fan discord, you know...
It's true.
Give us your money.
PCP is like a box of chocolates.
You never know whether it's too expensive or not,
and you don't want to buy it really.
Hey, here's the thing.
Here's a comment that somebody left.
EatSumoListless left this.
This is mildly amusing.
This guy says,
I got your Christian names here, fam.
So this is in response to the whole like middle name
that you guys named with your Christian.
Let's see, Nate, not a cog in the machine.
Best man.
Good.
Yes.
Digi played with sticks until 17, bro.
Uh, Mage...
Christianity is a fairy tale.
Purple.
It is.
Mage purple.
Or it was a fairy tale, whatever.
Ben, daddy watched me on cameras.
I like that one the most.
Munchy cartoons weren't cool until My Little Pony, Tiny Hats.
The dad raised us to be happy.
Davoo.
That's a strange one.
And hippo school was fun.
Correct.
Why is everyone, everyone you have like your username sort of divided up
that mine has purple?
I mean, I'm not complaining about the purple part,
but he could have had like...
I don't know, dude.
Lethal or at the end or something.
I guess because he would have had to start with lethal
and then put like something, something Aurora Mage,
and he wanted the Mage to be like the first part.
No, no, no, no.
He split up someone else oddly enough as well.
Well, he split up the Davoo weird the,
then like middle name Davoo.
I don't know.
In any case, like I'm not complaining about the purple.
It's a good enough word to use for me.
Just, I just found it as weird.
Indeed.
And instead of that was episode 111,
I see the memes, I see the ones spammed in chat.
They have been noted, observed, appreciate.
I kind of don't like that sometimes.
Because I feel like some people didn't give actual comments
because they wrote a one comment.
Well, maybe, but this is episode 111.
It's, if there was ever a time to spam that one in chat,
it had to be this time.
And what about the 1111?
Well, we'll get there one of these days.
That'll take eight years, I think, or is it 10 years?
10 years, actually.
It'll take to get there.
Hey, maybe the potty cuss will be over by then.
Maybe, it might be.
We'll see.
All right.
I mean, I got nothing to say about that episode.
Yeah, let's just move on.
Let's move the fuck along.
Let's go, let's do questions.
It's time for the questions, everybody.
It's time.
Let me, let me go to this whole, this whole Twitter over here.
All right.
What do we got?
Questions, please give us a good fucking question.
Um, here we go.
At Captain Thought One asks, uh,
what's the cure for cynicism, my boys?
That's a thought-provoking question.
Uh, cure for cynicism.
Season one and two of My Little Pony.
There you go, guys.
Oh, he's right.
I'm trying to think, cynicism, like, in what sense?
Well, okay, let me think.
Like, is that, um, like a nihilist sort of cynicism?
Yeah, like, I'm interpreting this the way that I understand it,
but it's like, okay, let's say you've been watching anime for a million years
and you get older and you're like, uh, anime isn't good anymore.
How do you, how do you enjoy, how do you love anime again?
Or, or insert media of your choice here?
I mean, according to Ratatouille, you gotta just go back to your past
and remember why you started, what you started.
Like, what, what, how did I get here?
Why do I do anything?
You know what?
You're right.
That was the message of, of yesterday's new My Hero Academia,
the fucking hypest moment ever.
Was it the manga or the, the anime episode?
It was the anime episode.
Okay.
Well, why would I have actually read most of that?
Was it when the, the big guy jumped around and he smashed the guy
and he said, fuck you, bitch.
And then everyone was like, whoa, he's so strong.
And that, I agree.
Help me out, Tom.
What happens?
I've actually read most of that.
Well, what, which episode was that?
This was the episode with the United States of Smash,
when All Might has to remember his past and where he came from
to fucking beat all for one.
It was fucking insane.
Is that, did he, so he'd just beat, uh, what was it?
It's all for one.
All for one, right?
Yeah.
He just beat those the last episode.
That is like the best moment in the fucking series.
It is.
Dude, they animated it so well.
Oh, it was delicious.
Oh, it was great.
I kind of want to watch My Hero Academia.
Like I've read the manga mostly, uh, but-
It's fucking great.
It's a lot of episodes.
It's, dude, it's like-
I hear it's animated so well, though,
that I kind of want to watch it just for that alone.
Have you, have you watched any of it?
I've seen like a couple, like, what do they call it?
Saka burros.
Like that one moment where like Ice Fireman,
like snaps his fingers, there's some sparks
and then like a big explosion of flame.
It's like the best anime thing I've ever seen
in my fucking life.
The whole show is like that, dude.
This is so fucking good.
Like, like-
Well, it sounds incredible.
The anime, the anime is better than the manga.
Like, it is unquestionably a better experience.
Have you read the manga, too?
Yes, I'm caught up.
Well, shit, dude.
Uh, I mean, that's a pretty good fucking sell.
Why don't we go to start My Podcast Academia?
My Podcast Academia?
Dude, um, no.
That could be the, that could be the Tom show on the PCP.
That's a terrible idea.
That's a humble bring on people and talk about that show.
I like, mechademia.
I can't wait to talk about how mediocre I find that show to be.
Well, I will hate you forever.
We'll have to fight about it if that's the case.
We will fight about it.
That's true.
I mean, I might be on that as well
because I generally, everything I see about my hero academia,
I'm like, ehh.
That's pretty much how I feel.
And I read like the whole thing.
Uh, but the anime, the anime is just better.
I mean, that's a plus.
The anime is better.
Okay, whatever, enough about bullshit anime.
It doesn't meander.
It's just like, every fight is like.
Okay, well that's good.
Until you guys get like murdered for saying that the anime is better.
I haven't read, so I-
I'm on record as talking about how mediocre I find the series overall.
Like, mostly to be.
I mean, Nate, you're full of terrible opinions.
So I'm not surprised there's another one on the table.
Yeah, fair enough, fair enough.
Um, what else we got?
I mean, here's a question for me, but let me put it at everybody.
At Diploid39 just asks,
Nate, oh, I forgot.
These are the pity questions on the Twitter.
So this will be our last one.
Hashtag asked PCP to at TP Crasnators.
That's the Twitter, but just use the hashtag, whatever.
Nate, how would you want the world to end?
How would you want-
Wait, didn't we answer that before?
I think we did.
Did we?
I don't know.
I- Meteor, smashing into the planet just blows the whole thing up.
That's definitely what I would want.
If I could just choose any of them.
That's the coolest-
Yeah, we definitely answered this before.
But whatever, maybe other people are here.
Any other good ones?
Frozen solid instantly in a block of ice.
That's also a pretty good one.
Heat death of the universe.
We should make it all the way to the end.
Oh, but that's like a slow, scary way to die.
I'd rather just explode all at once in my face, and then it's over.
Think of how-
Actually, a different kind of heat death.
I would rather it blink out of existence, and I feel no pain.
Then it doesn't matter.
That's what I want.
If it's a heat death of the universe, not going to be our problem.
That, I mean, yeah, yeah.
But like, the reality of the heat death of the universe happening-
Think of how far beyond Starfleet we could get to,
if we get all the way to the heat death of the universe.
Well, sure.
But the people who are alive then will be really scared,
and then they'll all die, and they'll be really sad,
because they won't-
That's welcome.
Yeah, fair point.
Mage, how would you want the world to end?
I said this before.
Meteor, quick, quick, quick, and destroy everything.
Okay, we definitely answered this.
All right, give just to reiterate.
I want a big space dog to come up and just take a bite out of the earth.
And then the core will be exposed,
and then it'll crumble into nothingness.
Okay.
That'll be pretty cool.
Well, fuck you.
Space dog.
Fuck you, Diploid, for asking an old question,
making me read it like an asshole.
Fuck you.
All right.
And he has a fucking micro-academia fucking icon.
What a fucking shock.
I have a good question from the patron-
Typical brainwrit.
Yeah, okay.
From Happy D.
He says, when you were a child slash young adult,
did you ever get in any really big fights with your parents or close relatives?
Not generally.
I, one time, I kicked Ben in the stomach for no reason,
and my dad got really mad,
but that wasn't really if, like, he just yelled at me for doing that.
I got screaming master with my mom a lot.
Yeah.
I was very...
About what topic?
Just, just, just everything.
We still butt heads to this day, so.
Yeah, okay.
I just realized that I forgot to...
Non-confrontational, so I never fought with anyone in my family.
All right.
You got it all out on the streets.
That's true.
I am, I didn't talk about this,
but, like, I did have fights with my brothers, like physical fights,
and since I was the oldest one,
I was kind of always the wrong guy,
even though, even though they would do, like,
the classic little brother thing of being an annoying piece of shit,
because they knew that if I fought back,
they would get me in trouble, for sure.
Yeah, they do all that stuff, but, like,
man, I, I was not a good brother sometimes.
Sometimes I was kind of a terrible and evil.
How so?
Um, I mean, it's not like they, it was out of nowhere.
Like, I wouldn't just come home from school
and then punch my brother in the face.
It wouldn't be like that,
but it would be like, we would be arguing about something,
and, you know, maybe one of my brothers had had a bad day,
and I had had a bad day,
and then we'd argue about something,
and then it would turn into, like, a scuffle,
and then a punch, and then a throw things across the room,
and then screaming, and it's like, oh, God.
Oh, not good.
That sounds hilarious.
I mean, it, we are, like, really close now, because, you know, we're just...
Brothers get closer, they get older, I think.
And I think a part of it is because we had fights.
If we never talked to each other and we just kept to ourselves,
we'd probably be like some of those weird, like,
estranged siblings sort of deals where, like, nobody talks to each other.
Like, I've seen that in media, and I'm like,
that doesn't make any sense.
My brothers are in a mere fucking tight...
Like, Ben and I fought, and, you know, I didn't think of this either.
Ben and I definitely fought sometimes.
We had, like, these trampoline battles
where we'd, like, do flips onto each other and stuff.
Those are pretty cool.
Oh, that's funny fighting.
Yeah, that's not, like, rage fighting.
Only once in a while.
Like, Ben historically was known...
Or my sister historically was known to, when aggressed,
curl into a ball on the floor and just, like, lie there
and attempt to just, like, you know...
Like, when she did that, like, you couldn't hit her
because, like, she's being too pathetic.
So you couldn't punch her no matter how bad you wanted to.
And I wanted to a lot all the time.
You know, it's where my addiction to beating women
really kicked into high gear.
You know, it's just, like...
And Ben and I, the thing was, it was mostly passive-aggressive
in my family.
Like, the biggest grievance I have with my family growing up
was that, like, I was sad we didn't, like,
do more stuff together.
And I was, like, lonely in my room.
That's, like, my biggest, like, I don't know,
thing I didn't like about growing up
that I remember the least fondly.
Like, I wish we'd gone out and, like, done more stuff together.
So, like, would that just create this, like,
weird passive-aggressiveness of, like,
everyone would be in their room,
and I'd just be, like, lonely, sitting in mine,
like, wishing we could, like, hang out and do stuff.
But, like, when you're, like, a kid,
and, like, your older brother is, like, doing his own stuff,
it's, you know, it's just, like, of course,
he's gonna be hanging out with his friends,
not his little brother.
That's gay.
You know, I'm sure I felt the same way
about my little sister, too.
So the cycle continues, and will continue forever.
So...
But occasionally, Ben and I would get mad,
and I remember running from Ben while he chased me
quite a few times.
And, you know, just doing whatever I could
to avoid this rain of blows.
Imagine that today.
Nate running from Ben.
I know.
Now Ben has learned to fear me and laugh.
Yeah, that's all I got.
I just remembered in terms of talking
about the fighting thing.
I think I've heard this, again, not confirmed to be true,
but little kids don't feel pain quite as much as adults do,
because I'm guessing it's because, you know,
they're in the stage of, like, learning and whatnot.
So, you know, they're supposed to, like,
get scuffs and scrapes and whatnot.
So pain isn't registered so much,
or at least it's not that big of a deal to little kids.
That's why I was so...
Maybe.
Maybe that's why I was so rowdy when I was a little kid,
because pain didn't scare me as much.
Mages confirmed for a row.
Listen to this question from AJ Shoup.
All right, get ready for this one.
Brace for impact.
You're fighting a dude slash gal
who is evenly matched with you,
and they straight up poop on their fucking hand,
smear it in, and get back into fighting form.
Do you continue with the shit show,
or choose to lose the fight?
What do you do?
It depends entirely on the stakes.
Yeah.
The smart man would run, or, like, just...
No, like, I don't...
Okay, like, sometimes it's okay to admit defeat.
I don't want poopy on my hand.
I don't want poopy on my face.
Right.
No way.
No, sir.
I feel...
Did this come from personal experience?
Is this, like...
This is an oddly specific question.
I'm just saying.
It is quite specific.
I feel like he might be the aggressor in this case as well.
I can say that I would...
I would basically do anything to avoid contact
in this situation.
I would not let that happen.
That is so disgusting.
Oh, my God.
All right, I now know how to beat all of you in a fight.
Noted.
That's true.
Like, I mean, could you live down the fact
that you pooped in your hand to win?
Depending on what I needed to get done,
and how badly I need to beat you,
I might have to...
Mistakes might have to be made.
Do you remember that...
This reminds me, like, it's like a game of chicken.
You remember that fight in, like, the last season of Game of Thrones,
where Theon, like, is exerting dominance?
And, like, this big boy, this big other, you know,
Iron Islands guy, like, he's trying to, like, take over.
Theon's trying to become a man at last.
And so this guy, like, punches him.
He falls down.
He gets back up.
The dude's, like, stay down, punches him.
He falls back down again.
Theon gets back up.
He won't stay down.
He keeps getting up.
Imagine if the man had dropped Trow, pooped on his hand,
and then said, like, what now, Theon?
What now?
Theon would have wilted, like, a fucking flower, you know?
Like, a flower in winter.
But no, he didn't take it to that level.
Theon probably would have done that, though,
because he would do whatever it takes.
He doesn't have much further to fall at this point, you know?
That's true.
That's very true.
Okay, done with that.
Next question.
You know what?
This is kind of just a public service announcement, actually.
Oblivion Fall here.
This is, okay, says,
Is there a deadline for the PCP intro contest?
I've had something written for a while,
but I'm having trouble getting musicians together,
and Fiverr is giving me trouble with PayPal.
I don't want to miss out.
This guy is getting serious about this shit.
I feel like if there is a deadline,
I want to give him an extension,
just because I want to see where this madness leads.
I feel the same way.
I don't know.
I don't really want to put a deadline into place,
but I feel like it would actually be helpful to do that.
I feel like we definitely should put a deadline.
We'll just get answers for everything.
But it shouldn't be soon.
It wouldn't be soon.
Maybe like a month?
Like a month?
From today?
From now?
Maybe a month when this episode goes live.
The end of the summer?
I mean, just have it be like a summer?
End of the summer.
You know, I really don't want to make it stretch out too long.
Like maybe we could say,
what if we said the end of July,
which is a month and a half basically?
I'm chill with that.
Okay, that's fair.
All right, guys, you heard it.
We are assigning a deadline right now.
July 31st is the final date.
That is the last day we are accepting applications.
If you send something,
August 1st, it will not be accepted.
We will not put it in the ranking.
It will not win.
July 31st, there's your fucking deadline.
It's in stone.
Don't forget to actually post it.
There you go.
Because, you know, some people...
Don't forget to post it.
If you send it,
if you've finished it July 1st,
and you forget to send that shit till August 1st,
you're banned.
And don't forget to use the hashtag.
Use that hashtag PCP theme, people.
You've got to use that so we can see it.
That's how we're looking for them.
So if you don't hashtag it, we don't see it.
Nate, Nate, I meant you.
Don't forget to post it on Twitter and stuff.
Because, you know, some people might want...
Yeah, if you posted to Twitter,
hashtag PCP theme, you got to do that.
You got to get it to do it in some way.
So, I mean, you could even...
Don't email me.
Give me a link on Twitter.
Do that.
That's what's helpful.
Some people actually did, like, email me links,
and I just asked them to post it on Twitter.
And then they did.
But speaking of which...
It's that way all of us can see it.
That's right.
And so we can easily use it here.
Plus, like, if you give me an MP3, again,
like, we can't listen to one on the show,
you got to give me a link to listen to it
so we can all listen on the show.
And speaking of which,
do we want to do any more questions
or shall we go to our...
I've got a pretty good one.
All right, let's wrap it up.
By Axelran, what is your favorite anime fight?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
That's almost as bad as what's your favorite anime.
Rock Lee vs. Kara is a classic.
You might say it's supposed to be that.
I mean, it's not...
It's not a traditional...
I mean, I don't know,
like, the final moment of Gurren Lagann
is sort of a battle.
Like, that's one of my favorite moments of all time.
Sort of a battle.
It's definitely a battle.
Okay, it's definitely a battle,
but it's not like a normal, like,
slug fest shown in Naruto-style battle.
It's like a mech, you know,
doing something at the size of the fucking universe,
like, continually being broken down
as, like, a guy, like, keeps plunging forward
through the other carriers.
Yeah, it's a hell of a time for shit.
I mean, it's, like, the coolest thing ever.
But I think I'm actually gonna say it if I want, though.
It is basically the coolest thing ever.
Like, Bellamy vs. Luffy in one piece
is definitely one of the greatest...
And again, that's also kind of a subversion of a fight,
but it is one of the most...
Like, I've read so many shounen,
and seen so many shounen fights,
that the subversion with the Bellamy moment
is, to this day, one of the most amazing moments
in all of one piece.
It's unfortunately...
Well, no, I'm just gonna say
that it's one of the best moments ever.
That's all.
It's great.
I don't like fights in media.
Like, it's not like, I don't...
It's not like I'm not against them, it's just...
Nate, you've said that yourself multiple times.
No, it's just like...
I don't like...
I don't like watching the fights.
Like, I don't find them entertaining.
I guess that's what I mean.
You want to be there.
Yeah, she's frustrated.
She can't actually be killing someone right now.
My brain just starts tuning out.
If it drags on for too long,
I stop paying attention to what's happening
because I'm just...
I don't...
I don't know why I just don't.
I can't pay attention too long.
As Tom was saying, I actually sort of agree
because the thing with fights that I always say
is that anime fights,
or any fights in any...
including like Game of Thrones, whatever,
I don't really care about the fight.
I care about who is won at the end.
That's like, narratively what matters.
It doesn't really matter how they got there.
But like, fights are just like fun in anime a lot of the time.
I'm like torn on it because like,
I definitely like the spectacle pieces
of like really crazy choreographed fights.
But at the same time, like there's...
I have like a hard limit, you know?
Because eventually, like Dragon Ball Z,
I don't know how I made it through Dragon Ball Z as a kid.
Like, it's so hard.
How did I...
I don't...
Wow, it's sorry.
Realization just hit with me.
That's what I like about my girl.
Did you watch Dragon Ball Z, bitch?
I watched Dragon Ball Z.
I cried when they stopped airing it on TV.
I put the date on my phone that I don't have anymore,
exactly the date that they stopped airing,
and I cried and I said,
every year I'll cry on this day.
Damn, dude.
That's incredible.
That's hardcore.
That's so anime.
That is so anime.
My favorite anime fight is from Dragon Ball.
Tension Hand, as it's written in the manga.
No, versus Goku.
Yeah, okay.
But when, you know, Tension Hand was still like a villain,
and Goku was a little boy,
that fight between them is like one of the most...
Like, it's...
I've never seen a reddit.
I gotta do that, man.
You gotta read it.
It is better than Dragon Ball Z in every way.
Dragon Ball, I believe, is infinitely better than DBZ.
Like, by a titanic margin.
Okay, quickly.
The thing is, like, with the fights...
Fuckin' general blue as well.
Holy shit.
I'm gonna Google him.
I don't know who he is.
Yeah, I don't...
Like I said, I don't like watching the fights,
but I do like certain fights,
like, aren't necessarily just pure action.
Like, you know, they pause,
and like, maybe, you know,
have a narration of what's going on,
or something that will what it means,
what this means, and stuff like that.
It's a little hard to explain what exactly.
Do you mean like an ongoing struggle?
I guess, kind of, like...
I guess a fight I like,
not necessarily my favorite,
but one I can actually remember,
was the last few episodes of this anime.
Now I don't remember how The Enemy was called.
It was this anime where, like,
creations came into the real world,
and sort of fought the Hatsune Miku of that world.
What?
Wait, are you talking about...
Is that the one with Saiyan the Cat girl?
You know, no one talking about?
Show by Rock?
No, no, no, no, no.
The anime was like these characters
from animes, mangas, and games, and stuff like that.
They were brought into the real world, quote, unquote.
Is that Gate? Is that Gate?
Is that the one?
Not this and something.
Okay, I don't know.
I'm just fucking guessing.
I don't have any fucking idea.
But yeah, the main antagonist was sort of like
the representation of Hatsune Miku.
Because of the backstories,
and a lot of the characters are resemblance
of other anime characters, or several anime characters.
It was like this little boy that had like a huge mech.
It was like a huge mech pilot,
and there was this girl with red hair,
and she also had a mech,
but she came to the world without the mech.
And it was such a fun anime.
It was an original anime as well.
It doesn't have a manga,
but I think the manga is going to be published.
But yeah, it was a really fun.
It was a really nice anime.
I quite liked it.
The pacing was a little bit off,
but I think it dragged on someplace.
I liked the final battle,
because in the end,
like the Hatsune Miku,
she was like all-powerful,
and they tried to defeat her,
but they couldn't,
and they tried different ways,
and they had all these plans built up,
and the way she got defeated,
in a way, it felt like a cop-out,
at the same time, it felt fitting.
I quite liked it.
I liked the whole segment of them fighting against her,
and losing, and it's just,
I don't know, it was neat.
Fucking Hatsune Miku,
god-level power.
That sounds pretty cool.
I want to watch this,
whatever it is now.
You've been treating me.
She's a god-level meme in real life.
It has my husband in it,
so it's like my husbando,
my guy food.
I liked episode three of Kill La Kill,
Satsuki versus Ryuko.
It was one of those fucking things.
There are so many good fights.
I'm such a sucker for anime fights.
They make me so happy.
I mean, they're so good.
They're really just the coolest thing ever.
I mean, I guess just some off the top of my head,
I really like the ending to Guren Lagin.
G Gundam, that shit was hype as fuck.
I love G Gundam.
I really like, I mean, I've watched this one,
I rewatched the most recently,
is the All Might versus No Move Fight from the first season
of My Hero Academia.
It's so fucking hype.
You just punched him so many times, dude.
It's only three minutes.
It's three minutes,
and it's exactly as long as it needs to be.
It's so nice.
If you want to rewatch the Frieza fight,
it's like seven hours.
You rewatch the All Might versus No Move,
it's three minutes,
and it's fucking tight, and it works, and it's dope.
Oh, and one last one for me, Bellamy versus Luffy.
Indeed.
In the Jaya arc.
So you agree with me.
So that was my, that's why I said it.
Recreators, there we go.
Oh, did you say that?
I did say that exact one, yes.
Sir, and guys, recreators, that's the anime.
Recreators, oh, okay.
I've heard people say that was good.
Also, people say that was shit, but fair enough.
No, it's just as good.
It has my husband in itself, of course it's good.
So it must be good.
Makes sense to me.
By the way, I just want to say that when you mentioned
that General Blue was like the best fight ever, Gib,
I googled General Blue,
and I think that you must definitely be right,
because look at this image.
Please edit this in, sir.
It's in the main chat.
Look at what's happening at this moment
between these two heroic characters.
This is clearly the best shonen fight of all time.
I like where this is going.
This is one of his,
I mean, this is when guns were still useful in Dragon Ball.
Yeah, yeah.
Would that have killed Goku?
Because he's like resistant bullets, isn't he?
That's a shotgun to the face.
He probably would have been hurt, I'm not sure.
Pull the fucking trigger, General Blue.
I want to see a boy die.
Don't quote me on this.
This is during the Red Ribbon Armour, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, this is the Red Ribbon in general.
Well, at this point, isn't Goku tanking like rocket launchers?
Yeah, yeah, don't quote me on this,
but I think Goku did take a shotgun to the head
and it hurt him like a peace shooter.
Bullets hurt him.
Oh, you know what?
He may have shot it,
and then his head was knocked back
and then he moved his head back like, ow, my nose.
Yeah, like bullets, he feels bullets,
but it's like when we get smacked.
Don't overanalyze it.
Just enjoy it for what it is.
No, no, no, no, this is a serious analysis
of this one frame of Dragon Ball episode 240, whatever.
What a fucking badass, I have to,
I need to go read Dragon Ball.
I've been meaning to for like a fucking decade.
All you gotta do is change his hair to brown.
It's basically you.
Okay, so moving on from there, we're done with questions.
It's time for the PCP theme contest portion of our program here.
So as we said before, hashtag PCP themes,
send us on Twitter using that shit.
I mean, that's really the only way that we'll get them.
If you're in the fucking Discord, the fan Discord,
or the patron Discord, you can submit them there
in like the fan art section, but the Twitter is even easier.
And you gotta give us a link to either a SoundCloud
or a YouTube link, and maybe something else,
but we can't play anything else on the show.
So SoundCloud or YouTube, please, sir.
We got a couple that weren't that, and they had to fix them.
So just letting you know.
All right, so let's see what we got here.
Our first one up here, let's see who's first.
Okay, first is from John J. Renz.
This is a theme called Let's Jack Off.
It's the name of it.
Wait, okay, hang on.
Okay, all right.
And here, we fucking, hang on, go.
Whoa.
You know, this is my genius.
Wait.
Oh, shit.
This is great.
This is an excellent shit.
Oh my god.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, this is, this is pretty great.
I mean, it is.
It's, I feel like his words are like indecipherable.
Oh my god.
Okay, that was incredible.
John J. Renzel.
But like, I really couldn't fucking tell what you were saying.
He did include the lyrics in his SoundCloud link.
So if you, if you go to that here, I'll just paste in the thing here.
You can see like what they were.
I, this was clearly like mostly based on,
wait, I pasted the wrong chat.
This is mostly based on the like, the Jesse's theme that he made.
Correct.
I could tell that much.
I mean, that sounded cool.
There was a lot going on there, but like the fucking,
like, are you a native English speaker, sir?
I love the piano like diddly doodly.
What was that good one?
I love the, the, the, you know, the sort of like, you know,
what's the word to describe the haphazard piano doodly.
Yeah.
That was great.
I'm kind of at a loss for words, uh, after listening to that.
That was so much like fighting.
You can't really respond to that with words.
It's true.
That would act.
I mean, could you hear that like being at the beginning of the show?
I think I could.
Good question.
I mean, I'm, I mean, that is pretty good.
I'm leaning towards no personally only because it's so strange.
I like the music.
Like it's really, dude, just like us.
Oh my God.
That's like perfect and stuff.
Uh, I mean, I prefer it to a generic rock beat.
It certainly has personality.
I mean, I agree.
I agree with that.
I'll give you this.
It's definitely better for the next one to be a generic rock beat.
That's way better than like, uh, just the, one of these like boring, like no words.
Like there was way more heart in that.
Um, but it was like kind of just strange and hard to understand what the hell was going on.
And also, I mean, this is totally subjective, but it didn't sound like to me the kind of tone
I would want to like kick off a show.
That's, uh, that, that, that is what I have to say about it, I guess.
But like, none of these are getting like ruled out immediately.
We'll like confer on these just as time goes.
And after we reach the deadline and we'll like listen back.
When we get closer to the deadline, we'll be like, uh, so what are the contenders?
Yeah, we'll probably make a fine.
We'll go over them.
Yeah.
We'll, we'll do something where we like talk about like the final ones and review all the
finalists and stuff and see what was, what's the best one.
Um, and then completely ignore all of them.
Definitely possible.
As just like Digi drops some fire and makes his own theme.
Yes.
Well, okay.
I mean, that's it for that one.
Okay.
Next one is what the fuck is it?
All right.
Themes.
Here we go.
Fucking.
All right.
Hang on.
Okay.
Here we go.
Next theme is from, uh, Das Exemptionist Biggles.
Oh, he's an exceptionist like, like made famous by the PCP in that episode of pyramid schemes.
Remember that one?
I remember that one.
I don't.
PC, hashtag, PCPermits scheme.
Still, still in effect.
It's still in effect.
Still give us all your money.
Uh, patreon.com.
Slice the burqrassinators.
Uh, okay.
Here we go.
Okay.
This is an art house, uh, film.
I like it.
Oh, it's called a Das article.
Is the name of the song.
It's German.
Yeah.
Definitely a German boy.
Hmm.
This.
It's interesting.
Oh, is it already going?
It's fading out now, I think.
Oh.
No, it's just getting quiet.
All right.
It's just getting quiet.
That's part of the theme.
It's fading to the words, I guess.
Whoa.
Um, okay.
That was a little, that was a little scribbly scrably for me.
Uh, I agree.
I agree.
It was definitely a little.
Yeah, go on.
Fucking out there, but it also kind of felt PCP-ish to me.
Like that, that.
No, not for an intro to the, to the episode.
It's just, it doesn't want to have this intro, but it definitely,
I felt like it kind of hit on our eclectic.
I do like all these people having.
I definitely like that.
Interpretating the PCP in music and having their own takes on
how the PCP sounds is music.
Me too.
It's really fun.
That's pretty dope.
Yeah.
This, this one definitely felt like like an, an RT like
noise experimental animation or something.
Yeah.
Like I could see like squares and lines like moving across
and going all bloop, bloop, bloop, bloop.
I, yeah, definitely.
Uh, but I, I, I've been generally with, I liked it,
but I'm not sure it works as a theme.
That's, that's what I'm saying.
Uh, okay.
Let's do, let's do one or two more here.
Uh, one's from at Captain Thought One.
Captain Thought One, or whatever, Captain Thought.
Uh, this is one called, uh, this is called Cursed Video.
Cursed, or Cursed Videos.
Okay, here we go.
Let's see what you got, Captain Thought.
Welcome to the PCP.
Grab your boys and grab some beans.
Hope nobody interrupts me.
Ben is always squeaky clean.
Is that it?
Okay.
Just said prep training.
I did like that, to grab some beans.
Now the old, okay.
Here's what I'll say about that.
If you, if you, if you mentioned specific things about like
individual members of the PCP, I immediately have a problem.
If you only mentioned like two people and nobody else,
you know what I mean?
It's like, I feel like there should either be like
group references, uh, or it should be like everyone gets a mention.
You think, you know what I mean?
You think of like the anime openings, like you always have
all the characters come across, uh, with their face at least once,
at least a little bit.
That's, yeah, that's how I feel about that.
Also, that was definitely, uh, not hype enough to be an intro theme song.
But, uh, I appreciate the work.
Thanks, buddy.
Let's see.
Tom, any thoughts?
Any thoughts?
Uh, plus one for bean reference.
But yeah, I agree with what you said about it.
But that, I did like beans.
Beans are good.
Okay.
You know what?
There's three more.
I'm having a great time.
Let's just listen to the next three.
Let's fucking go for it.
Yeah.
Let's go for it.
All right.
Let's, let me pull this up.
Okay.
This is from Augie Main.
And it's called, I just want to die.
Same.
Oh God.
This is a PCP theme, not my theme.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I know, right?
Okay.
Here we go.
Play now.
Okay.
It's like Ape Escape.
Is that what that is?
No, it's, it sounds like an Ape Escape song.
Maybe a bit chiller than Ape Escape.
This is quite chilly.
Ooh, I gotta put on a sweater.
Okay.
Hilarious.
And then he died.
I loved it.
Then he died at the end.
I liked it.
I liked it too.
I feel, I feel, I feel kinship to it.
Yeah.
I mean, I liked it, but you know.
It's like hype enough.
The hype, not what I'm looking for,
not what I'm looking for.
And that could be like the intro to like,
hello and welcome to the suicide cast.
That's true.
That's tall.
I'd use that as an outro theme for Wine Chamber.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
That'd be good.
Yeah, definitely.
I wonder if these guys would mind if we just like
use these for other stuff.
Probably not.
I don't know.
Ask me if that's okay.
I love the creativity here.
Yeah.
I mean, I think I said something about like,
we don't have to use any of these if we don't like them.
We should also add a clause to like,
but we can use them for whatever we want.
They, oh, we own them now.
I do.
If you tweet us with that hashtag, it's over.
You signed away all your rights by using the hashtag.
That's right.
They signed their rights away as soon as they opened Episode 1.
They just haven't realized it yet.
That's true.
That's definitely true.
I did love that one, but it was more of an outro than an intro.
Yeah.
Well, I definitely thought that was cool and chill.
I like it.
I do like it.
For a theme, for an opening theme.
It sounded like a Steven Universe song playing in the distance.
Whoa.
Yeah, it did.
That is on point.
Yes.
Totally true.
You know those meme videos that are like,
Redbone, but it's playing one room over.
And it's all like muffled sounding.
I remember that.
It's kind of like, I love that.
It's like, it's like Steven listening in on his dad saying,
oh, just from a guy like, dad, no.
Okay.
What do we got here?
Another one from Robert J. Lazarus.
And this is called PCP Theme RJL.
All right then.
Here we go.
What do you got for us, Rob?
Okay.
By the way, wait, what?
Do you say Ben's usually wrong about most things?
Because if you notice, the album cover for this is Ben's face with the words PCP just all around it.
Amazing.
Oh, amazing.
If you go to the Robote Nazi Techno state thing where I'm playing all the bots,
you can see the album covers for like each of these.
They're pretty.
Maybe we should edit these in.
I don't know.
I did last time.
I'll edit them in.
Oh, you did?
Oh, that'd be cool.
That'd be cool then.
This Ben, I really love this Ben's face.
This whole thing is excellent.
What an expression.
What a face of disdain.
I'm not going to bullshit it, Rob.
That was a little amateurish for a professional operation like the PCP here.
We're looking for a little bit higher standards.
I mean, I could tell that was the point.
Just like, Ben sucks.
Like that was the thing.
Yeah.
I mean, I did love that.
Message received, man.
Message received.
Hardly agreed with.
Okay.
And we got one more here.
And this guy submitted actually 36 minutes after we started recording.
Oh, this is some cool album cover.
It's like, oh fuck, stop, stop.
This is like, I mean, you'll see when I paste it there.
It's like this blue version of the PCP boys.
Oh, I think you actually redrew them.
Okay, whatever.
Let me paste this shit.
So this is from Artur.
Artur, I believe his name.
And this is PCP theme demo.
All right.
Here we go.
Begin.
Oh.
Ooh.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
I did not understand a single word.
But that was hype.
That was hype.
I want to go back and look at the words.
They're not posted on the SoundCloud, but that was pretty sick.
That's yeah.
And I like the mixing.
I like the voice, how it sounded compared to the guitar.
And I like the thumbnail.
This guy put some work into this.
Yeah.
Good.
If I knew the lyrics, I mean, I don't really care to know what the lyrics are,
as long as it sounds pretty cool.
I'm serious though.
But I would like them to be like, understand them.
Yeah, I'm a lyric.
That is true.
He says this is a demo, so he might be able to like, make it better.
That's true.
If I have any criteria at all for like the opening, what I always look for like,
it wouldn't be startling and it wouldn't hurt people's ears.
That's what I usually look for.
And this is both startling and with
probably be a little obnoxious to listen to.
I mean, I like the way it sounds, but like as soon as it starts playing,
I feel like if I was a listener, I would just probably want to click away.
We shouldn't forget that the PCB is a cold-blooded capitalist engine.
It's a cold machine for profit exclusively.
So we're looking to appeal to that mass demographic on a wide audience.
If that's our game plan, we've got a lot of adjustments we're going to make.
It's true.
We're going to have to fire everyone.
All of us will be fired immediately.
Only the logo will live on.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
I liked it, but I do think, I mean, this is a demo.
I don't know if there was an updated version.
I don't know if I'm alone in this,
but I would be interested in hearing an instrumental version as well.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, my favorite part about this is like the difference between like the guitar
and the voices.
You work well together, too.
I like it.
I'm curious.
It's well produced or whatever the word is.
I want some more development on this.
I want some dialogue.
I want some refinements.
I want the demo dropped, and I want the final dropped in,
and I want to check back and want to see how it goes.
I want some diagetic music that is like it's real.
And we are singing it every time.
Every time we record, it's like it's...
A catchy melody.
And this didn't put much emphasis on the melody,
you know, as a hip hopper type track.
It does feel a bit like a digi thing,
or like not as a digi.
I mean, I don't even mind this.
Like I could see myself using something along these lines,
but I don't know.
It's pretty good.
Pretty good.
That's what I say.
That is pretty good.
I'll definitely keep this one in mind as we progress.
All right.
You got one more?
That was the last one.
Oh, that was the last one.
All right, we're good.
We're fucking...
We did it.
So we're all done with the fucking PCP themes.
So we'll keep them coming, people.
July 31st, Harry Potter's birthday.
That's on purpose.
That's the finale.
Voldemort killed Harry on that day.
Who will be the PCP boy who lived?
And their theme?
Exactly.
Only one of you get to live.
It's the one we choose to put the theme.
The rest of you are murdered by Voldemort, a.k.a.
Much.
A.k.a. Davoo.
Mage.
Oh, right, Mage.
That's true.
All right.
Well, the last part of our fucking show here
is due to the little fan art corner.
So let's see what we got here.
Let's take a look over at our fucking fan art.
We got a couple good ones.
We got this first one by Link's.
Oh, yes.
Now, Davoo asks us to read a statement regarding this.
Davoo says that this depiction of him is in his top 20
of Davoo depictions, and he really likes it.
And this art style is cool.
And I agree with Davoo.
It is very fucking sick.
Yeah, it's got a good aesthetic.
I do like it.
I like how Munch is sort of like doing a weird stance
and wistfully looking off into the distance.
It feels very album-focused.
Oh, yeah, it does.
It does.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
I wonder if it's based on, oh, maybe not.
Also, I love the Kirby face.
It's just kind of floating there.
I like how the Kirby face is so happy,
as opposed to everyone else looking so mellow.
Right.
Everyone else is very melancholy.
That album cover, Disinterest, Don't Want to Be Here,
but Buy Your Shit kind of thing.
Gibbs Lyons being there is looking pretty good as well.
It's pretty dope.
Oh, yeah.
That's a zero out of 10, because I'm out there.
Oh, no.
All right.
What do we got?
Now, we got one that was just munchy,
but it was just munchy, so banned.
Remember, people, it's got to be either,
like, if it's one of us,
it's got to be PCP-related in some way
that's clearly communicable.
Like, maybe Munchy and his gesture outfit
that he wore at his lecture, that I could see.
If it's just munchy, though.
What if we just got all fanartididgy?
You know, like, nobody wants that.
Nobody wants that.
Or me, or Gib, or anybody.
PCP, PCP themes.
That's the thing.
But so, look at this one.
From I'm a Big Boy Yeah, Caleb Adams.
Okay, now, these are fascinating.
So, it's me and Munchy, drawn individually,
only it's drawn on those weird,
like, children magnetic-filling draw paths.
The, yeah.
I don't know how those work.
I don't know whether it's, like,
iron filings.
It probably isn't.
It's sort of, like, you push down,
and, like, the contact of the top layer
and the bottom layer creates a line.
Yeah.
But, like, you have to, like, shake the thing,
to, like, make them go away, or something like that.
Right, yeah.
It's pretty...
I mean...
No, no, I think what it is,
it's one of those, like, it's, like, a vacuum almost,
and then you, like, twist a knob and it lets air in.
No, it's not a vacuum. They have, like, a little handle
with the magnet thing, and it wipes it clean.
Like, you, like, you swoop, you squish it down,
and it wipes it away.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think he's right.
I think he's right.
Yeah.
Well, whatever, man.
I don't fucking know.
They're fucking sick.
It's all bad.
I know that I'm looking at angry as fuck,
probably for excellent reason.
Someone has wronged me this day.
Maybe Ben looked at me,
and I, he challenged my authority.
I mean, I have to destroy him.
The fact that he drew both you and Munchie,
it seems to be, like, you got mad at Munchie,
and then crucified it.
I crucified it.
No, he's dead.
I think Munchie crucified himself to save us all.
That's what I think happened.
And, like, how, like, square, and, like,
it's all sharp and pointy your images,
but, like, Munchie's, like, a soft, round boy.
Munchie's just all wiggly wobbly.
I think this is an angry, distraught,
Nate looking at his life companion,
Munchie J. Trump, on the cross,
and he's put his shades on
to hide his single tear of regret.
Oh, you know, you're probably right.
You're probably right.
And again, I just love the fucking gizomed
of Munchie crucified on the cross
with that happy-smiling Kirby shirt.
It's truly transcendent.
I absolutely love it.
It literally is.
Well, team, I think we've reached the end
of our show for today.
Hope you had a heck of a time.
And remember, everybody, Patreon.com
slash The Procrastinators.
$1.
Keep fighting the good fight.
Keep fighting the fight.
Like, giving us money.
Fight on.
Faito.
Japan.
Anime.
Do that.
Please give us money.
$1 in your fucking discord
with all the cool guys.
That's a good place to be.
You get the TPC feed,
which is an extremely convenient way
to keep track of everybody's posts in the PCP.
It's actually like the best way to do it,
in my opinion.
Except for me, because I'm still not on there.
But everybody else is good.
No.
Well, tell fucking who is it.
Vindi or, I don't know.
I have enough to change, but that's okay.
We'll get it someday.
One of these days.
And let me see.
What else the fuck is it?
Oh, a $5 pledge.
You get access to all bonus episodes.
There are like 15 of those motherfuckers out now.
And they're all gold.
The last one, they're all delicious.
Last one's sitcoms, it was incredible.
It was the best one.
The best episode of the PCP, basically.
In terms of editing, for sure.
Yeah.
Divu went crazy.
He edited like a sitcom.
It was so good.
Audience laughter and all that cool stuff.
Oh, God.
What a great job he did.
Beyond that, die.
Follow us at tbcrasnators on Twitter.
Send us those hashtag PCP themes people before July 1st.
And hashtag ask, or with hashtag PCP fan art for the art stuff,
so we can show off more of that shit.
And that's it.
Thanks for joining.
See you next time.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?