Good morning! Merry Christmas! Ben here, and before the episode starts, I wanted to make a quick announcement.
So recently, I have been shipping out and getting ready to ship the Road to Radcon books out to backers.
But I had extra copies, so I decided to offer them to backers that did not pledge enough to earn them in the first place.
And also then to patrons, and then also just to anyone.
Anyone on Twitter offered them, and they were very popular, very well received, and I was afraid I was going to run out.
I wasn't going to have enough to meet demand, and guess what? I did. I sold out.
But I hated the thought of telling someone, oh no, you can't have one. No, we got rid of them all.
So I'm printing more. I'm printing more copies. I'm going to have, I'm going to print a second run, a limited second run of Road to Radcon books.
Picture on screen if you haven't seen what they look like. Art by Michi Fostered, as you can see. A masterpiece.
The cover art, mwah. Delicious. This collector's item. I am going to make a few more copies, maybe 20 more, 50 more.
I don't know, however many I need to. So if you would like to get your hands on one, they are more available now.
They are up for anyone to grab, but if you are, if you back the Kickstarter, the Road to Radcon Kickstarter, or you are a patron, you get $5 off.
The price is $20 plus shipping, but if you are a patron, or Kickstarter backer, but if you patron the PCP, you can get it for $15.
So think about it for a minute. Do the math in your head. You pledge to the Kickstarter, you pledge the Patreon for $5, you get $5 off the book.
You get your base, that's patron is basically for free. You get access to the bonus episodes. You know, you get all the patron benefits and the pays for itself.
Because you are going to buy the book anyway. Because look at it, of course you are going to buy it anyway. You need it. You can't resist.
So anyway, info on the screen, DM the PCP Twitter, DM me on Twitter, DM me on Discord, and just ask, hey, you got any books left?
And I'll say yes, and then I'll say, here's how you buy one, and you go, OK, send you the money, and that's how it's going to go.
I will see you in the DMs, sliding into my DMs. OK, on with the show.
Gib, you said you need to be out by six?
Six, yes.
OK, so unfortunately, we're going to have to keep this one under two hours and 40 minutes. I know. I know.
So sad.
Just start the voicemails immediately, I guess.
The people will riot. The people will riot.
Oh, no, I'm looking at the voicemails.
Oh, no.
Well, not that many. We got a normal amount.
It's like 50, like 70.
But that's too many.
We could just talk, and then if we have to cut some voicemails, we could just cut some voicemails.
End of the episode, sorry.
True.
Have we started? Is this the beginning?
Hello, everybody, and welcome to this episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
You're going to open us complaining about the voicemails, and that's relatable, because I'm sure as you, the viewer, are opening up this episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
You are thinking, God, I'm not looking forward to 40 fucking voicemails.
Well, we're right there with you, friends.
We're going to stop together.
You can skip through the voicemails. We have to live through them every single time.
Yeah, we don't have to.
You could say we remember it so you don't have to.
No.
I wouldn't say that.
Hey, so I want to kick things off, because this is a big hot moment in video games.
What? Oh, he's talking about, oh, God, I know what you're going to talk about.
It's about Delta Rune. Chapter 2 came out. Have either of you played it?
I have not.
No.
Damn it.
I downloaded Chapter 2.
I knew you were going to bring, I knew you were going to, and I knew it was going to come out.
Now we're going to click bait another bunch of people, like, oh, PCP talking about Delta Rune?
No, it's just Gibbs saying, oh, I played Delta Rune. It was really good. You should play it.
We'll just have to revive the Buster Cast format for Delta Rune when we've all finished it.
You've all been tricked.
Oh, God, fuck, we never did the thumbnail.
Eleazar, make sure the thumbnail is nothing but Delta Rune.
No.
Nothing but Delta Rune.
We never did the Psycholomials cast.
Those poor Delta Ruiners, those Delta Variants.
Delta Ruin'd.
Those poor Delta Variants all waiting to hear about Susie.
The episode's Delta Rune'd, and it's just Susie in a surgical mask.
Oh, I'm Delta Rune-ing. I'm Delta Rune-ing right now.
That's what I said when I was playing it.
Oh, yes.
Did you make the face?
Oh, yeah.
On a scale of 1 to 10, it's a good one.
It's free, so that's nice.
Is it better than Chapter 1?
I would say...
Well, obviously, I've only played Chapter 1 when it came out.
I haven't played it again.
Kind of was waiting to...
I was thinking of replaying Chapter 1 as well.
I don't think it's that necessary.
As long as you remember the gist.
I don't, I don't really.
I played it with Ben.
That's how it was.
Yeah, we replayed it all together at Trixie's place.
Oh, yeah.
And that was the clip that you were streaming it,
and Munchie screamed sans when he saw him.
Yeah, we all screamed sans at the same time.
I totally forgot about that, but yeah, you're right.
I don't think I ever played it on my own.
Maybe I did.
It's a good time.
You're Chris, you're like a tall frisk,
and you live in a place,
and then one day you go into a fucking dark portal
with this girl Susie.
It's an Isekai.
Kinda, yeah, and well, yeah, that is what that is.
It's a video game.
Undertale is also an Isekai.
Wait, do you think about it?
All the best stories.
I mean, there's no...
Whatever.
I'm trying to think of how the world of Undertale
and the real world and the monster world
are they physically the same place?
Because then it wouldn't be an Isekai.
It wouldn't be like going into a different universe.
Just going into a hole.
By that logic, Alice in Wonderland isn't an Isekai
because she just falls down a hole.
No, she has a dream about it.
That's not a real hole.
That's not actually down there.
I never read it.
It's true.
You're in the same place.
You're not going to another world.
What is the difference between...
That'd be like saying if you went to Japan,
that was an Isekai.
Just because you're in a different culture doesn't mean you're in another world.
Why not?
Why couldn't the story of going to the Isekai?
Ben's Isekai adventure in Japan.
I can't wait for that vlog series to drop.
Hey guys, I'm going to go Isekai down to the supermarket
and buy some diet soda.
You want anything long gone?
Part of the role-playing as being in an Isekai
is getting to the store and being like,
where am I?
It's so amazing and so different.
If you go...
I think it's a bizarre to draw the line
that's like, okay, if you go through a portal
to another world, then it's an Isekai.
But if you just go down a hole and the world is underground,
that's not Isekai.
Because it's another world, a literal other planet,
another plane of existence.
Another geometric plane
and it is lower on the Z axis.
It's a new plane.
It's just lower underground.
I get it.
Metaphorically, story-wise, it feels like
it's a different world.
But you wouldn't say the same thing about climbing down
a hole in a medieval RPG
and those dwarves down there.
That's not an Isekai.
If you climbed a mountain...
The Mines of Moria is an Isekai.
Why not?
Give me one fucking good reason.
Because if you got a bunch of Minecraft TNT
and you blew it open,
the boundary would be...
It'll be open to the elements.
If you go somewhere
and you find a place
that is like a totally different place
that's different from the normal world that you live in,
and then you go back at the end.
I guess you don't even have to go back at the end.
That's the premise of an Isekai
is you go to a new world.
But the way you define world is like...
an island.
You could go to the island.
I guess I don't know...
Robbins and Caruso is an Isekai.
Go to Baskin Robbins, get lost
and be like, I don't know where I am.
This is a new world. I gotta live here now.
What's the one of the sailor that goes to the land
with the tiny little people?
No...
He's the land of little people
and the land of giants.
He's a giant in the land of tiny little people.
Oh, I know.
Gulliver's Island travels.
This is an Isekai.
Why not?
I don't know what the Isekai means in Japanese.
I would say...
I would say that on like a...
on like a...
on say like a 3x3 grid
of Isekai...
You ever seen like the sandwich,
like purism versus like...
It's like structure purist
versus like ingredient purist.
I would say on like an Isekai grid
like that, I'm like...
I'm like radically like an Isekai
is in any...
can be anywhere. It doesn't have to be a literal different
like world and also...
I would say I'm like the most like radical anarchists
on the Isekai grid.
World only has to be...
Respectable. Relative to the protagonist's perspective
of life. Yeah.
It doesn't have to be a literal...
The pure anarchist position is like
going to the bathroom as an Isekai.
Another world really is subjective
It is. It totally is. Living from moment to moment
like when a cell of yours dies
you're a different person. The world is different
every second, every
every time a quark moves.
Fucking...
The catcher in the rye
is an Isekai because he's gone to like
New York or whatever and he's never been there.
Becoming a billionaire is Isekai or living
in a totally different world. Isekai has to
just base it on his body and now I don't know
what to do with my buildings. You don't even have to...
You don't even have to literally travel.
Right. And now I'm thinking like that
Class is an Isekai. Normal
speech is like instead of going on a holiday
or a vacation, I'm going on an Isekai
to like Italy or something.
Yeah. 50 Shades of Grey
is an Isekai. Not because she goes anywhere
but because she enters a new world of
dating a weirdo. And that's
kind of like going
to a new video game world or something.
New fantastic point of view. Yes.
True.
Um...
Deltarune. Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Deltarune Chapter 1.
You go... You Isekai
into this place and there's a little goat
guy with a hat
and you have an adventure. And that's the
Deltarune Chapter 1. Then you leave and it's like
what? Was that real? Are we ever going
to come back? And then Chapter 2. There is
like a cliffhanger ending, isn't there? I just remember
that. Yeah. Yeah. Deltarune Chapter 1
is ambiguous about whether it was just a dream
or whatever. Yeah.
Chapter 2 answers a few
questions about how real it is,
but I don't think they're like concrete
answers. They're just sort of like
it's sort of like this. It's sort of like, I don't want to spoil
too much. Which is funny that
like... Yeah. You live in a world
of like goat people and monsters
and like skeletons are like you're just your
neighbors in the real world.
But then in the dream world
you go to a place with other different
monsters and skeletons. Different monsters that are made of
weird things that are slightly stranger.
Yes.
These monsters go to school. These monsters
are the darkners and the lightners.
Right. And I forgot about
that.
Do they still have the banger
fucking battle theme?
Because that was the best part. Oh, of course.
The root buster.
That's so good.
The combat scooter
there's...
What's different about
like the combat or is it
I mean it's the same thing as
Deltarune chapter one.
You've got the attacks and the
acts, the sparing of the monsters
by doing the right things. Is it better
than Undertale yet? Oh, of course.
Really?
Combat wise, it's better than Undertale.
There's more strategy
to winning a battle than just knowing which
thing to
to spare them with. I liked the combat
a lot more in Deltarune.
I was reflecting on
can we just reflect on the fact that
the PCP literally started
with the first episode
is just saying...
Undertale just came out
and it's the best game ever.
And this, the last episode
of the PCP is going to be talking about
Deltarune is just Undertale but better.
Deltarune is the new best game.
Yeah.
Childhood is loving
Undertale. Adulthood is realizing that
Deltarune is the true best game ever.
Combat wise,
there's more strategy to it
and it's tighter, movement wise.
The whole, if you remember
in Undertale, you just have to dodge
things as the little heart in the box
and that's neat.
But in this one, you have like
TP which is like
I forget what it stands for but it's like
action points where you can use that to heal
or and stuff like that.
You get a little bit
of TP by edging
close to a projectile
but not getting hit by it
and you get like a little
sound.
Like that fucking video game
with the anime girls.
Yeah, whatever.
Toho, right?
Toho games are like that. You move really close to the bullets
and that fills up your...
Can you get extra? Yeah.
I don't know Toho but
that is what you describe
and that makes
moving and dodging
a little reward thing rather than
just get out of the way
which is cool.
And then there's newer spells
and different things and more fun
little gimmicks that they use in battles
and there's a lot of really funny moments
and I laughed out loud
multiple times.
I guess I should play it or whatever.
How long is it?
How much of a time commitment do I have to make?
It is not that long. I completed it
the day after it came out
because it came out like midnight. I was too tired.
It was like three to four
hours and I was
pretty thorough. I want
to play through it again and do like different
things that I did the first time.
But I got to the end where
credits like Chapter 2
and then it showed like a list of
Deltarune chapters that you could pick.
You could choose to play Chapter 1 again
2 and then there's like 3, 4, 5, 6
and 7 which are not
clickable yet because they're not out.
So 7 chapters
apparently.
It's like a decade of work
at least that the radio is gone.
Yeah, I don't know.
I heard somewhere that he wanted
to release the entire rest of the game
in one go
but he didn't
and I guess
he's doing chapters. I guess I could make it more money this way.
I don't know how he's making money right now.
I think the next one is going to be like a bundle
of like chapters 3, 4, 5
and that's going to be the first
paid part of Deltarune.
And then like the last two chapters would be like paid DLC
or something maybe?
Well, the paid for the rest of the chapters. Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't mind.
How dare he charge for his game.
Toby Fox is a billionaire. He should charge.
In fact, I want to pay a lot because it's really good
and I should.
I would like to pay as much as possible.
I'm going to hide into Toby Fox's life
so I can know what it's like to be successful.
I'm going to Isakai myself
into the fucking poor house
by sending all my money to
Toby Fox for his video game.
I'm going to Isakai myself
into Detter's prison.
Isakai myself into Detter's prison
to play Undertale
but I don't have a computer anymore
to play it on.
It's the light novel that starts like, oh, I got sent to jail
and it was really bad and nothing ever good happened.
I sold my computer
to buy you a copy of Delta Rune Chapter 1.
I sold my copy of Undertale
to buy you a computer
to play on.
Oh, fuck.
I guess jailed by our own definition now
is also in Isakai.
That's a different world.
Absolutely.
And so is the grave.
Orange is the new black because a great Isakai series.
The best western Isakai.
The grave. Death is the ultimate Isakai.
It's like Dumbledore said.
It's like Dumbledore said and the Deathly Hallows.
To the well-organized mind,
death is just the next great Isakai.
I think I remember that one.
The greatest Isakai ever told.
That's the thumbnail.
Eleazar, that's the thumbnail.
Do it.
Yes, please.
Oh, I'm having a fucking
ball over here.
Ah,
blah, blah.
It was these really cute.
Rousey's really cute. Chris is really cute.
And there's a lot of characters
who are really cute. I don't want to spoil too much
about who appears.
But yeah.
Everyone who is excited about Deltarune
has already picked it up and played it.
But you guys,
I expected better.
I expected more gamer fuel
from you.
Sorry. I was too busy
making a video game channel.
I struggled.
I was too busy satisfying
our fucking satisfied customers
on road to Radcon
for
a Kickstarter
back rewards.
I got a huge stack.
I got stacks and stacks here of envelopes
that are addressed and ready to go out.
I've been doing that.
I've been handling all the orders.
They are soon
to be shipped. Soon to be shipped out into
the world.
You really don't realize how much of a logistical nightmare
mailing things is until you run a Kickstarter.
You're like, this fucking sucks.
It's taken me several days
just to...
It probably would have taken me two days
to address all the envelopes.
There's 126.
You think to yourself, oh,
addressing 126
envelopes, how long could that take?
An hour? No, there's always
a lot of this.
It's double checking.
I mess up the address.
I gotta start again.
Now I gotta arrange them
and organize them into
domestic versus international.
Everything ends up taking longer
than you think it's going to.
It's just one of those things.
But it's fine. It's not that bad.
It's not as bad as when I had to do the
vapors or something because it's just the book.
I don't have to organize them into categories.
This one gets this pin and this one gets that pin
and this one gets that extra bonus thing
and I gotta sign these ones and...
It's just book in envelopes.
It could be a lot worse.
Yeah.
I've got almost...
I think I've got
10 copies left and I want to mention that
I will be...
I offer them to the backers
the opportunity to buy
the extra copies and I think
most of those people have messaged me.
I think there's about 10 left.
Maybe by the time this episode comes out
I will have already tweeted about
anyone that wants the final copies
message me and let me know
and they can have them. They can buy them.
Maybe they'll be gone by now
but I guess we'll see.
We'll find out.
Yeah. I might run out.
Might actually run out.
We're close. I'm pretty close.
But we'll see.
Yeah.
There's that sweet Radcon payday
just around the bend.
Just around the bend? Well, after this...
Well...
I don't think I've mentioned it but the dojin
is being made. Have I mentioned this on the show?
I can't remember but
we must have talked about it sometime.
I'll summarize again.
The PCP dating sim people
or three of them. It was Never Paint,
Chip Wiseman and Ora Borista.
I think it was the three.
The three of them who were from the PCP dating sim
they wrote the script for the dojin.
We promised the manga dojin
and the artist Edward D. Al
who is at Wolfheart
H-A-R-T on Twitter.
We got him to do it
and he has started drawing
the page. It's going to be a 24 page.
It's going to be a 24 page
digital release.
The manga dojin
and that was going to be done
in maybe a month or so
and I'm hoping
and when that is done
and the dojin is done
and after that all that will be left
will be the
the Garling House
music video
and the OVA
and that will be it.
The nightmare
will finally be out of this
horrible radcon 4 isekai
that we find ourselves trapped in.
Radcon 4 really was an isekai.
It kind of was.
It was a hero's journey.
We all went to radcon 4
and then we returned
to the next two years.
We tried to return
to the regular world afterwards
but we couldn't. We found that we could never go home again.
The monkey's paw
of going to radcon
but having to throw the entire world into chaos
for the next 18 months.
We're the reason people are dying.
Fortunately, fortunately
that is literally the plot
of the OVA.
Fortunately, the plot of the OVA
turns on real world events
and we solve them.
We solve them in that
mad fucking video.
Yes, yes we do.
It's coming.
And in Road to Radcon
I don't know if anyone even remembers this.
I don't know if anyone is even keeping track of this
but there is actually a narrative
that goes from Road to Radcon
to the Brad Garling House
lecture
and the Brad Garling House diss track
and the OVA and the dogen.
It is all kind of a linear thing.
There were big plans in the beginning
from that narrative.
They were not followed through
with any sort of...
I don't know if we had big plans to begin with.
I think we had like vague plans
or at least big plans for the OVA.
Those plans were never solidified into anything
but the concepts were very big.
We managed to wrangle it into a continuous narrative.
I don't know if I agree.
I don't know if I agree that they weren't realized
but they kind of are being realized
or they will be when it's done.
I remember
the discussion about
what Radcon 4 should be about
is like we came up with the theme
anime girls on the beach
it's like a vacation
and also a school
because of PCD university lectures
and it's like
oh like anime
and that was kind of the extent of it.
We went to a beach
we had the idea of doing an OVA
and then all these other things
related to beach anime
theming
but I didn't think there was like
a plan for the narrative
of the entire thing to be contiguous.
Yeah, you might say
that the whole thing was a real dog's breakfast.
Yeah.
You're lying.
Yeah, and if you want to
and if you're curious about
does that mean anything to you?
No, maybe you should listen to the bonus episode
that isn't out yet, but it'll be coming out soon.
That's it.
That's just a taste.
That's just a taste of the FOMO
that you, the listener, are going to experience
if you are not pledged to the...
That is just a taste of the
all the inside jokes and japs
that you're going to be confused by
and feel like a total fool
if you are not pledged to the Patreon
and listening to the bonus episodes
and knowing what we're talking about.
Mmm, dog's breakfast.
Delicious.
Speaking of the Patreon, I guess I should mention
that the funny thing happened
and PCP Patreon now
is bigger than Trixie's Patreon.
Ow.
Oh, yes, I saw that.
By one dollar, at least in the image
it's...
It was literally the one dollar
that I paid that one guy two dollars
to un-pledge from her.
It made all the difference.
Got the moral victory, I suppose.
No, I got the moral L,
but I got the physical victory.
More money.
I sacrificed my soul.
I guess that's true, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
It has gone up a bit.
We're at 670, I think?
669.
669, yeah.
It has almost doubled since releasing those bonus episodes
and changing the model.
It has almost doubled.
So that's pretty great
and thanks everyone for pledging
and also fuck you
for listening to the playlist
without paying for it for all these years.
I guess people do need
consequences
and monetary incentives
to do things otherwise they just don't.
They just steal things and take things.
I'll be honest, I'll be honest.
I thought, I kind of knew
I knew that the playlist
was an insecure system
and it could very easily leak and anyone that had the link
could give the link, the playlist
and then they would never need to pledge.
And I was like, yeah, I know that's true,
but also I feel like
people are...
It's going to leak one way or the other.
If people want to hear the bonus episodes without paying for it,
there's always going to be ways to do it.
So whatever.
And really, people are going to pledge,
not really because to get the bonus episodes,
because leaks are inevitable.
They're going to be pledged because they just like us
and want to do us the solid
of supporting us.
Well, it turned out I was wrong.
They want the goods
and we weren't gatekeeping hard enough.
So now we've built...
I've built the wall.
You know what they say?
Big, strong walls make good neighbors.
They want to pay for it.
Yeah!
Based.
Very exciting.
Very exciting time to be a pro
procrastinator.
You might say.
I certainly lived up to our names
in securing that those bonus episodes
took a good four years.
Absolutely.
And we did the
fun fact contest.
It was the bonus episode that me and Gib recorded
the other day. It will be out at the beginning
of...
What's the fucking next month?
October?
Yes, September, October.
Beginning of October.
Oh boy, it's Inktober again.
You can't do that though.
No, because the guy who did Inktober
he did something.
He's bad for some reason that I can't remember.
He drowned someone
with ink because he loves ink so much.
Didn't he like steal something from somebody
to make Inktober?
He was revealed to be a squid person.
I don't...
I don't even remember
what it is that I'm bad about that guy.
He's got an Inktober NFT.
Something stupid.
Oh god, can you imagine?
He probably does.
Why not?
I did read about it.
He did seem like an asshole.
He did seem like a big asshole.
But I don't...
I mean, I don't...
I just forgot.
Oh.
My headphones are about to die.
Oh, so Tom, you mentioned
briefly there
Deltarune with your...
You couldn't play it because of your new channel.
Your collaborative, something or other
with SaberSpark.
Yes, everybody who liked
I Am Games and was like,
hey, it sure is sad that I Am Games
is no longer functioning.
And I felt that way too.
So like earlier this year in like January,
I was like, I'm going to revive
I Am Games and get back on the bandwagon.
I made a couple videos and I'm like, I'm going to talk
to Saber
because I talk to him all the time.
Just like run the content idea by him
and see what he thinks
about the direction I want to take the channel.
And he was like, you know what, let's just...
I was already going to make a gaming channel.
Let's just make a channel together
with the person working with you on I Am Games.
Let's make a new channel.
And I was like, oh, okay.
We lost them, but we can't find them anywhere.
Where are they?
Where's the co-hosts?
We just don't know.
Where's the content?
So...
We spent a bunch of time making stuff.
Trying to do a Where's the Podcast, but it's not a podcast.
Yeah.
No, not yet. I think we're talking about
possibly doing a podcast.
I Am Games had podcast episodes
that were just audio recordings, but...
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So we have the new channel called SaberSpark64.
And I made like low polygon models
of me and SaberSpark like narrating
the videos and stuff.
And they're just like gaming videos.
We have four out right now.
There's new ones coming out every week.
I have a bunch in the queue, so at least for the next couple weeks
there'll be episodes coming out.
You gotta play Deltarune.
I gotta get the Deltarune clicks.
That's what we did on I Am Games.
The funny thing is that
the channel's already
doubled the size of I Am Games,
and it doubled its size in less than
48 hours. It was pretty funny.
I saw that.
I didn't really earn any of this, but okay.
No. Well, whatever.
Who really earns anything
at the end of the day?
I'm curious what is the split
between you and Saber?
Like, I don't know.
Do you want to talk about who does what
for the channel?
Because I was like, you narrated...
You wrote all four, and you narrated one,
and he narrated the other three,
I think?
Also, I was curious and interested to see that
Eleazar edited one of them.
He edited the big long one.
Yeah.
It was Eleazar, Doonkun,
Kaijukun, and
someone else for the fourth one
where the editors listed?
Doonkun did a bunch of them. I've just been
bouncing videos off of them
and getting pretty good results.
I just thought, oh, I see that Eleazar
is cheating on us.
Yeah, yeah, I stole Eleazar.
It was a long process on that one,
because I had to go back and forth a few times.
We signed a contract. The pact
is broken.
I secretly wrote in a clause that said
he can work for me in other projects.
It doesn't break this contract.
You got to read that fine print
on both sides.
I mean, I do most
of the writing on the channel.
There's some subjects coming up
some longer essay style videos
because we have a big 40-minute
video right now called What Ruined Mobile Games,
and that's like a
sister video to the
thing that just went up on Saber's main channel,
which is looking at terrible
video game ads for mobile games.
They're cringy,
sexually charged, awful garbage ads.
So this is like looking at
the mobile phone industry and how it
turned really shitty.
And then the other ones are just short
little essays that will be
in between. We're going to try and do one big
video a month, and then I'll just do smaller ones
in between to keep the channel alive
in between the big 10-pole releases.
And those are the big collab runs where we both
do research and stuff together,
and then in the interim are mostly just
little essays, like, shit out on the weekend
to just, like, keep the channel
alive.
So...
Yeah, that's like the division of labor, I guess.
Hmm, okay.
Okay.
Pretty, pretty cool.
Um,
I'm a little, sorry, I'm a little nervous.
I'm distracted because my headphones
just beefed at me. They're about to run out of batteries
and I'm looking for my charger
for them and I am, like,
I can't find it.
Ben, you had, like, all morning to charge
your headphones. Got it. Got it.
No, I found it. I'm good. I'm good. Few.
Close one.
Ah, yeah, I didn't know they were low.
I didn't know they were low. I didn't know they were good.
Unlike Delta Rune, recording a podcast
and just missing your headphones dying
does not give you extra TP.
It just, uh...
Yeah.
Uh, I have a
I have a story.
I have an unfortunate story to relay.
I realized
well, I found something unfortunate in my closet.
I realized that when I moved out
not of my last apartment
into this fucking shithole that I live in now
but even before that, when I moved out of the first place
into that temporary place
so I'm over to almost
two months ago, uh, I realized
that I didn't
take the coffee grounds
out of my coffee maker
and I found my coffee maker in my
closet the other day
and in the, like, thing where you put the coffee grounds
it was just mold. It was just growing mold
for, like, two months
just in there and I realized, oh, maybe
that's why I have fruit flies in my room
because there's this fucking
this rotten fucking mass in my closet.
Oh, no.
Yeah, so, like, I scorched that
cleaned that out with, like, scalding hot water
trying to fix it.
Maybe I can salvage the machine.
I don't know how it works, I hope,
but it's gross.
So that was, that was a bummer.
That was a bummer.
That's a great story.
Yeah. You're welcome.
Well, what do you fucking have to say
if you're so fucking clever and interesting?
Well, I've been playing
a video game with my brothers
called Divinity Original Sin 2.
Called Delta Room. I thought you were gonna say Delta Room.
I have heard
of Divinity Original Sin.
I haven't. I haven't played it
because I suck. Divinity, it's
really fun. It's
a turn-based
well, the combat is turn-based, but it's sort of
like a top-down looking at
a really... It's like a spiritual
successor to, like, Baldur's Gate and stuff.
Yeah, it's like a Baldur's Gate game
Dungeons & Dragons-esque
role-playing adventure.
Yeah, sure.
There's, like, lore and whatever.
There's characters.
You can play, like,
across the internet.
And it's like a D&D campaign.
You can go around
the towns and talk to people
and have conversations and quests.
And other players
can double-click on your profile
image to listen in on your conversation
to see what options
you have and see what you're clicking on.
They can listen to the other
NPCs. They all have voice
dialogues, which is cool.
And then
they got all these fun, like,
classic fantasy tropes and stuff.
And then the combat is
like a...
I can't think of what is
similar to, but, like, you have action
points that you can use to cast spells,
do attacks,
or move, or use items,
and you get a certain
amount of action points per turn. Do you get more action points
if you get, like, close to the enemy
when they're attacking you and, like, you just kind of
barely miss them? No, it's not Delta Room, Ben.
It's a different game.
Well, then what's the fucking point? Okay.
Okay.
No, there's, like, spells you can cast, like, haste.
Gives you an extra action point on the next turn.
There's skills you can get.
You know, it's just a really fun,
quite engrossing RPG. We've been playing it, like,
every day for quite a few hours each.
Just for all, like,
I want to play more Divinity. I want to...
It's a really long game, it seems,
and, like, the leveling up
isn't really quick,
which is nice, and it's not easy, either.
So every battle is, like,
we got to really think. We can't just fuck around.
So when you
get into the perfect position,
like, you're on the high ground, you got a 20% bonus,
and I've been playing this
Fire Lizard,
and I got all this Fire Wizard magic,
and I'm specking really into Pyrokinetic.
Are you a Lizard
or a Wizard?
I'm a Lizard, and I chose the Wizard class.
I didn't call myself a Wizard, though.
Do that on purpose?
I don't actually think I realized.
I just like the look of the Lizard, because it's cool.
And then I wanted to...
I wanted to cast Fireballs, so Wizard was perfect.
Those are two perfectly reasonable
feelings to have.
Yeah.
But, like,
the status effects are really cool,
so, like, if you... certain attacks with Fire,
lights the ground on Fire,
which then will
set enemies on Fire if they stand on it,
or if you, you know, throw...
If you get, like, there's oil barrels,
if you break an oil barrel, oil spills
on the floor, and it slows them down, but you can set it
on Fire and burn everything in there.
It is, like, you can cast Rain
to put out Fires, but then that creates Smoke,
which obscures the vision
of people behind it
for a turn.
And then there's Ice and Poison.
And you can be a Skeleton.
Are you this guy?
Yeah, yeah, I'm that character, not literally.
Is that the guy, more or less?
Yeah, more or less.
You can be a Skeleton?
You can be a Skeleton of any of the races,
and the only thing that's different with a Skeleton
is that you have to hide your face,
otherwise people will think you're...
you're gross, because you can...
they can see your fucking no-face skull.
So you have to wear a hat or a helmet.
Yeah.
If you're told it's okay to be a Skeleton,
you just have to wear a hat.
And everyone's like, all right, okay.
It's like, oh, I can't...
It's just a normal person.
I'm not prejudiced against your lack of face.
I just don't want to see it in public.
Yeah.
What you do behind closed doors, what your face looks like
is your own business, but out in public we have standard.
You can't, like, kid so I can see that.
Yeah, so...
Skeletons can't get drunk,
because liquid just goes through their ribcage
and into their boots.
So they can't get the drunk...
But you can normally get the...
You have food and crafting,
and you can pick up scraps
of things, parchment,
apples, whatever.
You can make foods, you can make crafted items,
you can make spell scrolls.
It's really robust.
There's a lot of items
and a lot of managing inventories
and selling things and getting new weapons
and special, you know,
things on them,
attributes.
Oh, and the cool thing with skeletons
is that poison heals them.
So if you throw, like, you've got a poison magic.
You can throw it at a bunch of enemies
and it'll heal any skeletons in the area.
So if you're not fighting skeletons
and you have a skeleton ally,
big poison bomb is really good.
Interesting.
So it's very fun.
It's very strategic.
I like that.
Oh, that sounds pretty cool.
It's really fun.
You doing, like, couch co-op?
It's through Steam.
We all had to buy the game to play together.
There is couch co-op,
but you can only play with two people at once,
which, split screen,
it sort of works.
But there's three of us, so it wouldn't work for us.
I gotcha.
Are you playing that on Twitch?
Are you streaming that?
No, I'm streaming that.
That's my own personal video game time.
What's the point?
That's wasted content.
No, it's fun.
What's the point of playing a video game
if you're not making content?
The point of playing a video game
is to enjoy the process of doing such a thing.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Video games aren't fun.
That's just a way...
content. What are you talking about?
Why are you making one, then?
Because I need to make content.
Oh, my God.
Video games are content.
I can't believe people have forgotten that
there's such a thing as enjoying life.
They are content that breeds more content
when you film yourself playing it.
It's just the cycle never ends.
You're breaking the cycle,
and I won't fucking stand for it.
You must perpetuate
the content loop.
I don't know. Sounds pretty cool.
Sounds like a good time.
Sounds like a cool video game.
Yeah.
How long have you been playing that?
About a week.
And a bit.
Most days.
It's really enticing.
It's just like, I just want to wake up
and play Divinity
the whole day.
Really good.
That's how I was with Neo when I fell into Neo.
The entire month of June
just went away, and I just woke up,
played Neo, went to bed,
dreamed about Neo, woke up,
played more Neo.
It's one of those games for sure.
I have fallen off of Noida a bit.
I haven't really been playing Noida.
The last time I played Noida, I was trying to do
a pacifist run,
and it was proving very...
I managed to do a no-gold run,
but I have not managed to do the pacifist run yet.
Have you done a genocide run?
No, every run, every normal run
is a genocide run
of Noida.
I haven't really been
playing video games that much.
I've been making my fucking game,
which is really coming together.
I don't know exactly when it will be done,
but I would say it's mostly done now.
I'm really excited about it.
I think it looks really good.
How many bugs she got?
How many bugs?
God, I don't...
Uncountable amounts?
I would say uncountable amounts.
The entire game is just bugs all the way down.
It's just bugs stacked on top of other bugs.
Damn.
Certain bugs keep the
structural, like as load-bearing bugs,
some of them.
It's like, okay, I was making a game,
and there was bugs. Bugs occurred,
and I was like, hmm, okay, I could fix these bugs,
or I could add more
bigger bugs that will be the predators.
I could introduce bigger bugs
that will hunt and eat the smaller bugs
and get rid of them.
I was like, okay, nothing could possibly go wrong
with that plan, and I've just been repeating
that process over and over again,
and the result is...
Until opening the program
crashes your computer.
The biggest bug in the game right now
is that currently,
Phantom Horn has a weight command,
and I need to change it to a
DAB command that does
the exact same thing, but he dabs.
That's the biggest problem
in the game right now.
Yeah.
Oh,
fuck.
Oh.
I have some news. I have a funny story.
I got contacted.
C.C. asked me if I wanted to voice
a character in the Tails Get Strolled audio book,
and he put me
in contact with the guy who does that.
And I am going to be
the voice of the Dark Lord.
Satan, basically.
Oh, just like in real life.
Satan has one line
in Tails Get Strolled.
It's in the flashback when they all do the ritual
to become neutrals.
After the ritual is completed,
Satan says like, well done.
Now I will give you the power.
And that's going to be me.
Cool.
It's going to be pretty sick, I think.
Yeah.
I'm going to record that line later tonight, I think.
They just need to clip this.
They don't even need to pay you.
Just clip this episode.
You already did it. You did the work.
I'm doing it for charity.
No, I'm doing it for charity.
I'm so hungry.
You're doing it for charity, but not for content?
No, it is content.
Tails Get Strolled is content.
That's true.
That's content. That's voice clip.
That's my freaking 30 second voice clip.
That's content.
So it was Munchie's birthday this week.
We had a birthday party for him yesterday.
Is it like 14?
Yeah, something like that.
14 going on 13.
We got the...
I bought a cake.
Actually, I bought two cakes.
Actually, I bought so much of this fucking cake.
There was this weird looking Russian cake
in this Russian supermarket that I live near.
And the cake was called Smetonic.
And it's like a layer cake.
It's like a wheat based layer cake.
And I was like,
give me a fucking huge amount of it.
Because I thought everybody...
There was gonna be like 10 people.
And I thought everyone's gonna want a piece.
So it gave me like a huge fucking bunch.
I spent $40 on this fucking cake.
It was $10 a pound.
It turned out to be good.
It was good, but it wasn't that good.
And like less than half of it got eaten.
And I'm like...
But it looked really good.
It had chocolate shavings around the edge.
And it was the frosting on top.
It had a...
What's the word?
A confit.
A confit of reduced
the glaze of berries.
One was mixed berry and the other was blackcurrant.
It looked delightful.
And it was pretty good. It was pretty good cake.
But I shouldn't have spent $40 on it.
But you know what? I did.
And that's my story.
And I'm glad
you enjoyed it.
No need for flaws.
I applauded in my mind.
True.
Speaking of
turning things into content.
I've been on two drawcasts
recently.
One of them was a big movie movie.
Milka aligned drawcast.
Chip Wiseman
and Kelly.
I think their name is Kelly.
They're real...
Oh shit. I forgot my accent.
Chip is one of the writers
of the procrastinators
of the dating sim
and also now the Radcon 4 dojin
coming soon.
Yeah. And that was fun.
We drew like monster girls.
And then there was another drawcast
that was recorded a lot earlier.
I think I've mentioned it already
before on the podcast.
But it's the animation drawcast
with oblivion fall
that played
hours and
teleperte.
That guy who draws things like...
And Cetol, right?
Yes.
I saw teleperte
is in there.
Cetol made a post in there that was like
who anyone want to do a
drawing telephone game.
And I think I responded and I said,
yeah, I could do that.
Teleperte is so big.
Teleperte is huge.
He's huge. The tallest man I've ever seen.
He's giant.
Speaking of big
artists on Twitter,
did you see Cheesy's
comic that got everybody angry?
I did. I did see that.
Cheesy Man Freitas.
It was deliberately designed to be annoying.
And it worked.
It's funny how
a lot of the replies are just like,
oh, you're pivoting
a backlash and just scroll
through Cheesy's account and there's just
dozens of examples of
taking the piss like this.
You know,
call me a contrarian or whatever.
I just agree with the comic.
I just think it's
unironically correct.
There's definitely an argument to be made.
When people say
artists don't owe you a retweet, it's like,
yeah, no shit they don't.
Nobody said they do. The point of the comic
is just it's annoying when they don't retweet.
I wish they would.
What's fucking wrong with that?
I agree with the initial comic.
And then the people be like,
I don't even want anyone to retweet me.
I don't even care. And then for big accounts,
like fucking big accounts
to be like, this is just,
of course, this just means that you only care
about likes and engagement.
Yeah, no shit. That's why I'm posting on fucking Twitter.
You fucking moron.
You fucking losers.
I agree with the comic
in so far as
sometimes a bigger creator
than others. I enjoy
being able to say, no, I don't care.
I will not follow you.
I like your content, but not that much, idiot.
I won't even like it.
I will just say I like it.
I mean, it's
strange, because on the one hand, you have the
argument that like, oh, you don't want to
tell people, you don't want to make anyone
feel obligated to do something. And I think that's where
the kind of like
blowback comes from.
But like, there's been a discussion
in the art community forever
about like not re-blogging enough,
not retweeting enough. Like this is a point
that has been argued from like
sincerely for years.
So it seems very strange.
Like the reaction almost
felt like Elon Musk adjacent
where like, oh, these big
personalities, I have to simp in their defense.
Yeah, it's like
all these little little artists with nothing
to gain, no skin in it
at all. Just throwing it all out there
in the defense of people
bigger than them who don't give a fuck about them
who have everything while the other people have
nothing. But they're like, no, no, don't don't
attack them. They're my heroes or whatever.
I don't need, I don't like, I don't care that
like they fucking own my ass.
The follow up comic was a slam
dunk. I love the fault.
Yeah, it was it was
what does he say? Oh yeah, just who are you?
The guy like, you don't need to
you don't need to reflog me. It's okay just enough
that you appreciate my art. Who?
Who are you? Who? Yeah.
That was great.
It really is a weird thing because it's like
I saw a few people saying, yeah, well
we're people too, big artists.
And I was like, the original
was not saying you are not people.
Right.
Why would you take it that way? I think
big artists are people too.
What are you talking about?
It's because if you take the idea
you're viewing the
comic in the initial
you're viewing the comic is like
you're taking the concept
and pushing it to its extreme
of like you have to retweet
and if you're telling someone they have to do something
you're stealing their freedom in which case
you're not treating them like a person with free will.
I think if you can extrapolate it that
far, you can make that point
but like you're extrapolating
very far away. Great fucking
literally like
coming up with a guy and getting mad at them.
Yeah.
The thing everyone does on Twitter.
I guess white people would react like that
but I also think
it's weird to like then make a stand
like against it
saying actually
I am being attacked right now
and I, big artist
I'm not a, you know,
cringe look for
a big artist to be like actually
obligated to do anything for you people
and cringe for a little guy to be like
no they're not obligated to do anything
for me. I don't need anything.
It's so bad from either perspective.
I think they're sort of
assuming that
if they don't do
what Cheez's comic is implying
they should do that they are
you know
ready to get canceled like this is going to ruin
your career unless you start
retweeting smaller artists
it's not a threat.
You're stupid.
It's just like realizing you're in a very
I don't know
maybe powerful is not the right word
but like yeah you're in a powerful position
of like your one
retweet could make someone's career
if it resonates with your audience.
If you're big enough. I mean I read this comic
and I am bigger than
some people I'm not
the biggest but whatever to some people I'm big
I read this and I'm like yeah
sometimes I am that big guy sometimes
I'm just like nah I don't want to retweet
lol. True.
It's true.
And I feel bad every time that happens
cause it's always
I don't feel
too bad
cause I've always been like consistent
with like my twitter is
when I see something I really
like
I like it and then it feels
sensible to also retweet it so other people
see it as well. If I like
an artist I will often
like their tweet and I don't
retweet every piece of theirs but sometimes
if I really like an artist or I really
like a particular because I might retweet one
that I think is like particularly good
okay I particularly like this one
I'll give this one a retweet cause I think it's cool.
I don't go out of my way to do it
and maybe I should do it more
but I don't like to be
a retweet flood. It's a nice thing to do
it's not a bad thing
to do. It's not even really a bad thing to not do.
It's just sort of nice if you do do it.
And I mean this is Cheesy saying this
and Cheesy's feed is just
is a retweet flood.
I mean he really does put his money where his mouth is
he really is retweeting people all the time
so
there's no hypocrisy here.
What was it?
Hey, you guys there?
Yeah. Huh? Yeah.
Okay we got really quiet for a second
Oh did I say something?
No you said something cringe and
cancelled. I knew it.
I have to go to Twitter and say Ben Stinky.
Fuck. No!
Did you see I got a last
point about this.
Did you see the loss edit?
I did. I did.
I forgot who did that one.
Oh that one is genius.
That one is so good.
Can I find it in the quote tweets?
There's so many fucking quote tweets.
I can't even find the one I'm looking for.
The one where
whatever it's a loss edit.
It works really well.
Go on Twitter and look at the retweets
and find it yourself. I'm not finding it.
Yeah
my biggest criticism of this
is that Cheesy
cowardly to back down.
Cowardly to back down and say I did it
because I know.
You're just unironically right.
There's no bait.
It's just true.
I guess it can be both.
I guess it can both be true
and he just did it to make people mad.
They're not mutually exclusive.
I'm going to say something I believe in
that is going to piss people off.
Not because I want it to be out there
to show my opinion but to piss people off.
Says the N word.
Oh no.
Clipped.
True.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
What else?
What else we got on the plate today?
Did I already complain that nobody ate
my $40 worth of cake? Yes I did.
It was a Solaru.
I just forgot their Twitter name.
Solaru is the other person on the
Big Boobie Mommy Milkers draw cast I did
with Chip and Kaylee.
You know who did eat some of that cake?
An animator on Twitter
that I know called
Ekenzone.
His name is Ethan.
He drove out for Munchie's birthday.
He drove out from New York and he
gentlemen
took pity on me and took home
a big chunk of the leftover cake.
Immediately dumped it on the side of the road.
Halfway.
Honestly.
It was good.
It got an unfair shake.
I just bought too much of it. It's so sad.
What have I done?
What have I done? It was a learning experience.
I was standing at the counter and I was like
What did you get for buying so many carbs Ben?
And I was like do I get just one
big piece to share or do I get two?
And I was like just one or two.
Just one or two and I was like give me two.
And then she was wrapping it up. She was
weighing it and I was like oh my god this is gonna be
like $40 worth of cake. And I was like
no no actually just give me the one. And she's like
give me just one. Okay.
And I was like oh no.
I hurt her feelings.
Okay never mind give me two.
Oh no I got her hopes up and then I dashed them.
No I have to now. Okay give me two.
Give me two.
You just were guilted into retweeting
that lady's cake. What the fuck.
I was.
Doesn't she know that I'm human too?
Doesn't she know that I'm not obligated?
I'm not obligated to buy that
second piece of cake.
Hey I like your cake.
Thank you. But I'm so afraid.
Are you gonna buy more? Hello.
I'm gonna get cancelled if I don't ride the second piece.
What a life.
What a world.
I
met a guy
at mice. Me and Munchie
and Kazzy and Crack and a bunch of people
were hanging out. This was weeks ago
when we went to the MiniMice
comic expo and I was selling
Vapors and I was selling RFCK pins and such.
It was great.
Sold a lot of stuff.
But we met a guy there who had a podcast
and we just so happened to notice him
because his podcast's
logo is, it looks like
Endless War. It's the little Illuminati
triangle, you know.
It's the little pyramid head with the eye on it
and it's green.
It's a podcast called True Tales of the Illuminati
which I have not gotten around to checking out yet.
But I just thought it was funny.
We were like, hey, I'm selling green.
I'm selling a green triangle over here.
You got a green triangle over there.
Well, let's compare notes or whatever.
Let's make a green diamond.
We put him together.
We went out and we hung out and we got Chinese food
with that guy.
And talked about podcasts
and stuff.
And my chicken,
my braised chicken in brown sauce
was so
full of bones.
There were so many bones in my fucking braised chicken
in brown sauce.
I couldn't believe it.
I was like, wow, this is great for only $10.
But then I bite in and I'm like, oh my god.
It's like, it's all bone.
And it's not like, it's not-
It's a food equivalent of getting an iced coffee.
It's just 90% ice. Chicken's just 90% bone.
It's like it was chicken on the bone,
like a chicken wing that you eat off the bone.
No, it was like chopped chicken, like diced pieces of chicken.
Just many of them contained large bone segments.
This happened to me when I was in Ohio
and we went to this
North Market.
A bunch of small restaurants and stuff.
You can just order from local places there.
And I went to this place that was serving
African food and they had lamb.
It was like a bowl. You could get chopped lamb
with seasoned rice and some vegetables and stuff.
And so I got the bowl and I brought it home
and I took a bite.
And all the pieces of lamb had bone in them.
I'm like, this is a bowl.
How am I supposed to eat a bowl
if there's bone in there?
It was the same. It was mine. Mine was in a bowl
and it was diced chicken. I'm like, yeah.
I'm just gonna grab a fork and eat this.
Now I'm thinking maybe I'm the idiot
if this is something that's happened elsewhere.
Well, Joe, as can
speculated that maybe you're supposed to
maybe you're supposed to-
you put the piece in your mouth
and suck on it. Maybe you kind of just suck the meat off
the bone and spit the bone out.
And I'm like, I guess maybe.
I guess that's one way to do it.
But I don't like doing it.
I just want to eat the meat.
It seems like an extra unnecessary step
that also inadvertently
makes their products seem like
it's more substantial than it actually is.
I mean, I guess it would be
more work to
remove it from the bone.
That's why I paid you money for it,
the hard part, so I could enjoy the easy part.
Maybe I could have been like,
hey, this braised chicken in brown sauce
it's pretty good and it's pretty cheap.
It's only like $10.99. Can I pay you
like three extra dollars
to just give me no bones?
That was the DLC for the meal.
The DLC, yeah.
Alas.
The booster pack
or whatever. I don't know.
Can I buy a season pass
for no bones in my
braised chicken in brown sauce, please?
Sad. Good noodles, though.
Good noodles at that place.
Hell yeah.
Well, hey, I've run through my entire
list of things I wanted to mention
on this episode of the
pro-crastinators.
The only other thing I had on my list,
because I did make one once you said you were doing that,
because it was a great idea.
It's almost the end of September
and we still can't buy
a fucking graphics card. It's been a year.
It's been a year since new graphics cards
and new consoles came out and they're still
unavailable. And I know why
it's because of the chip shortage
and it's not going to get fixed for another year
at least, probably closer to two years.
But I'm just
double non-plus about it.
I just want to buy a new fucking graphics card
and I can't do it. And it's really annoying.
Capitalism is failing.
You just can't get one anywhere? Or are they
way too expensive on eBay or something?
It's like both.
The production is down
really low, so there's not as many
being made as there should be. The ones that are
are all being bought by scalpers
immediately with bots and sold for four times
the price. And it's like
I'm not going to buy a $400 graphics card for
two grand, like die.
No, absolutely not.
So it just is infuriating
and I cannot believe it's still happening.
It blows my mind that like the normal person
like dude, like
imagine being like 15
and being like, oh man, I can't wait to get the new X-Box
Santa bringing me the new X-Box
and it just says
they don't exist, they literally don't exist
for two years now.
For the second Christmas in a row, children's lives
are going to be ruined.
Wow, when you put it like that
they're going to play a fucking GameCube or whatever.
Oh, oh, we're going to have
we're going to get into retro gaming.
Oh, I don't want to play, we can't play video games
on this PlayStation 3.
That's fucking Grandpa's old console.
That's, we might as well fucking listen
to like put, turn on the fucking the
the, the, the short wave, the short
wave radio, put on the gramophone.
No thanks. Listen to the Undertale soundtrack.
Everyone just has to play Deltarune because it's the only thing
that'll run on their laptop because they can't afford
graphics cards or anything for their good computer.
True.
Fuck, that's just so fucking tragic.
Sucks.
I'm just thinking like in context of me, like
if I had to wait two years while all the cool
PlayStation 2 games were coming out that I couldn't
play just because it's like, oh, no,
like a bunch of jackasses
with more money than cents
are literally spending $700
to get access to a bot that lets them buy
150 consoles in 0.6
seconds and then they flip them
the rest of the year. Hell, hell yeah.
Hell, hell, hell I should get
in on the scalping game.
I need to see more of those
like triumph posts where like
some scalpers like
warehouse got busted into and all of this
shit stolen. Right?
I love seeing that.
You love to see it.
There has to be like a market for like, there's going to be
a board on 4chan somewhere where they just find
scalpers who post like screenshots of like
all the consoles they have
and they like fucking triangulate their position
based on like the fucking moon
and the window or something and then break into their house
and steal all this shit.
I'd support that in a video game.
I would as well.
The worst thing going on right now
in the video game game
sphere is that
you can't play the video games.
The gaming sphere would be a good name
for a podcast.
The gaming sphere.
Yeah, the game sphere. It's like the GameCube
but like it rolls off the table and breaks.
Yeah, the like the self park console
the okama game sphere
from that one episode
way back in the day. Everyone's like
they just keeps rolling and everyone's like
trying to catch them because they keep rolling downhill
and I think you know something else
somebody made a joke like that where the game sphere
just won't stop rolling downhill.
I haven't seen that since
like that episode came out
in 2001.
I see, I see.
Hang on, I gotta put, hold on
I gotta put some apple cider vinegar
in this fucking, in this seltzer water.
Directly into my face.
Yeah, nice and tart.
That's, that's the good shit.
Um, well
if there's anything, if there's nothing
else of interest we could move on to voicemails.
It's true.
We are on a time, a time budget
this episode. We have a, we have a
unfortunately yes we are
tragically limited to under
two and a half hours today.
What a nightmare, am I right?
It's barely, barely even a podcast
at that length. I would agree.
I would agree and I am ashamed
but nevertheless.
Alright, well you guys got Speakpipe open?
No.
In one second. Come on
we gotta fucking
Whoa, they changed their UI.
They did. They changed the way it looks.
It looks all different but it still doesn't work
because they still are letting us get
voicemails even though we're like
Oh my god. We're like ten times
over the data limit and they just haven't
stopped us.
That's, that's the puggatist thing.
I told them, oh
I told uh, uh
Tyler from the Anamorphon
Time podcast DM'd me to be like
how do you guys do the voicemail thing
and I told him about Speakpipe
and I told him like yeah they say there's
a data limit but don't worry.
There's not. It was like cool.
At least there's not
uh, when we made it
I don't know if they've patched that since then
and we just kind of are
grandfathered into their bullshit.
Maybe we'll find out.
I don't know, yeah I wonder.
They were making a request like
hey guys send in voicemails to be on the
to be read on the Anamorphon Time
which hopefully
they're probably gonna still be doing it so I guess this is a plug for
fucking go call into
the Anamorphon Time
and follow the Morphe Boys
on Twitter. Go watch my episode.
I feel like I'm contractually obligated to get
on the Anamorphon Time podcast.
I feel like you are too. I wasn't gonna say anything
but it's pretty cringe
that you haven't done it.
We talked about your lecture when I was on there a little bit.
Only bad things I'm sure.
Of course. Of course.
We talked about all the
you know all the factual and
accuracies
and you know how
your jokes were
we're all fascists.
We were all wearing masks.
We all went full mask off
in that lecture.
You know how it goes.
Okay
let's play this first voicemail
shall we?
The first one is Janice.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I
thought your refusal to watch R-Taxi
was just a funny joke.
Then I pondered
why you would do that
and it leaded me to a very
subjective interpretation
that you would rather just be spending
time working on your art
than watch something which would
just be okay.
That is the artist mindset I'm
wanting myself to adopt.
To eject the need to be busy
and become focused on being the ideal
artist I want to be.
That's
very
charitable.
I would say
I would maybe say
there's actually something
that I worry about a lot lately
is that I find it very
difficult
to get excited about
things
and I have
very little desire
to like
try new things
or
look into new art
like Deltarune. Deltarune came out.
What do I feel about the prospect of playing
Deltarune Chapter 2? Nothing.
I'm hollow on the inside.
So that's how I would describe.
But if you want to call that being
the ideal artist,
be sure.
The ideal content creation machine.
Yes.
You just gotta like stuff. You just gotta enjoy life.
You gotta play a video game.
Once you get too
terrible,
you just realize how broken everything is.
Socialism is next to nihilism.
All these things need to be fixed
but they never will be.
No, you're wrong.
You go hollow.
That's just the doomer mindset.
Socialism gives me hope.
Socialism gives me hope that things
can be better eventually.
Not that they will soon,
but that they could one day.
That's their idea out there.
That's being actively ignored.
You sure?
But it's...
The real doomer mindset is that
well, we live under capitalism
and there's nothing to even do to...
No point even talking about it.
Because we just gotta deal with it.
Because we live at the end of history
and nothing will ever change.
And that's good, I guess. Capitalism is bad.
Capitalism is bad, obviously.
It has its problems, but we're stuck with it.
And we gotta make the best of
in it. And also,
that's actually good, though, and I support that.
Right.
Is the attitude that I feel like I see
a lot.
The default attitude of
capitalism.
Yeah, it's got problems, but what are you gonna do?
But also, I like it and I like those problems.
I don't want them to go away.
At least it's not communism.
Whatever that is, I don't know.
The next...
You guys got anything else to say about that?
No.
I don't know.
No, no.
Yeah, next one is called
Doug Walker Screaming I Am Jesus for 90 seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
I am Jesus!
Annoying fly or Ben Saints ass cheeks you decide three, two, one, go.
Nobody knows.
It's a mystery.
Well, Ben, you would know.
Well, does that happen when you stand up?
Both of those things are in my room, so it could have been I would have to go back and
hear it in context.
There's just no way to tell.
I'm hoping I'm hoping that having found the rotting fucking coffee grounds in my closet,
I will have less of a fly problem going forward.
I'm hoping that that was the source of it.
Unfortunately, your ass cheeks will be with you forever.
Yes.
And of course, those attract flies as well, so there's really just no winning.
The next voicemail is called Sad 3, 2, 1, go.
Listening to corineatrixie content, like talking to a loved one who has lost her mind,
like it came from a single corineant form, like, I don't know, even if she had a form
that I would consider like a charming, quirky part of a personality, you know, fucking get
on my nerves, fucking self-involved fucking vapid ass.
I mean, I agree.
It's my opinion.
I mean, like, I don't think people came to her channel just for the anime reviews.
I think people actually liked her personally, even like they have music, like the game that
has 67,000 views and people really put up and people supported her fucking music shit
because they really liked her, but she fucking threw it all away.
It's sad.
It makes me sad.
Me too.
I mean, true.
We got it from our perspective.
This was like our friend who just like eroded her like, oh, okay, yeah, that's a bummer.
You see your, when I occasionally glance over at what she's putting out on one of the other
channels, I'm like, yeah, I'm agree, like I see it, I'm like, this person is not acting
like, I don't know, like, what are they doing, like, I don't know, the way they act in like
the, the, the, what are those, the one where she interviews rappers, the, what's, the, what
you do?
And it's like, it's, it's, I guess, like, she's the same person in some ways.
That's my question to Trixie when I watch those videos, she's just, it just feels like
there's nothing really going on in her, in her head, I don't know, I don't watch a lot
of the stuff she's doing, but she does seem like less of everything.
I think she's, she's just like not, just like, is she just like not into it?
Is she just like not feeling it and she's just going through the motions, but I have
no idea.
It doesn't even, it doesn't even know why she's doing what she's doing.
We'll never know, unfortunately.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know, dude.
I don't know.
Um, next voicemail is called based water god three, two, one, go.
If the definition of something being wet is, is having water molecules attached to it,
then unless you separate a single water molecule by itself, then by definition, all, all water
is wet because it is surrounded by water molecules, which is attached to it, check, check, mate,
that's a really good bit.
I like that bit.
That's really good.
That's was a great bit.
I mean, it got me laughing, I guess.
Um, um, yep, new molecule water.
Yep.
I got it.
Yeah, it's good.
The next, next voicemail is called a question from a lowly troglodyte three, two, one, go.
So wait, did anyone actually break in to Tritie's house or something to cover up the
break up thing?
No, that, that's, that really, that really happened.
There was like a pretrial and stuff for the guy that did that.
I don't know if it, I don't know if it was a break in, like may, may open the door and
the guy just like kind of came, like she opened the door and he came in.
So it wasn't a break in, but it was like, I guess you might call it an assault.
I mean, it was basically an assault.
I don't really know too much about it, but I never really got the full details.
A crime of some sort was committed.
I, yeah.
Yeah.
I honestly thought the story sounded so like bizarre that I thought it was made up.
I really thought like they have to be making stuff.
This can't have happened.
It was very strange.
But something happened because there was, there was a pretrial and stuff.
So I'm convinced that it's, I mean, a real thing occurred.
I don't know the details.
It certainly seems to have traumatized May.
Perhaps.
What makes you say that?
Well, maybe, I mean, this is, this is from an outsider looking in, but I feel like she
was a little more open to things like trans issues with, with Trixie and all that stuff.
And then around that time, this happened.
And then afterwards the breakup happened, but I don't know what caused what.
I, I certainly think whatever that, you know, the break in was fucked up something.
I mean, it could have helped, you know, a stroke on a camel's back sort of moment.
I don't know.
It couldn't have helped, but I don't think like that is what changed.
No, I wouldn't say that was like the main thing, but like, I don't know.
Sure, it couldn't, it couldn't have helped.
Next voicemail is called Addendum to the Previous Question, three, two, one, go.
And by break, I think I mean cheating thing.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Right.
Sure.
Fine.
Now, it may or been, you decide.
Three, two, one, go.
Wait.
Oh, was that a Trixie song?
That was a Golden Witch song, apparently.
Is that new?
Wait.
I assume.
Wait, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm gonna listen to it again.
Is that live?
I'm, I'm glad you're not here.
I'm glad you're not here because I don't want to forgive you.
I don't want to forgive you.
I thought she said, I don't want to fuck you.
I would say it's probably more likely about May, I mean, if it's about anyone, right?
It might not necessarily be about anyone in particular.
Sure.
Could just be lyrics.
It's just, I mean, I mean, it's, I mean, heck, it could be about anyone.
It could be about both of us.
It could be about whoever, whoever she wants it to be.
You know what?
It's, it's art, man.
It's subjective, right?
It's subjective.
It means whatever you want it to mean.
Death of the Author.
It could be both.
Man.
It is both.
And that's valid.
And it's neither.
And it's all these things at once together.
It's superposition.
And the universe is like connected or whatever.
Next voicemail is a, is this fucking fast upload link.
Okay.
It is called the biggest, most awful, most tragic events in human history.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm about to hashtag delete my own channel, if you know what I'm trying to say.
No.
I don't even remember when he said that.
No, Munchie.
Don't do it.
No.
Oh, it's too late.
Don't do it even though everything's gone.
Oh, he did it.
I don't remember when he said that, but LeMau, that's kind of what he did.
And what?
Oh, well.
Dude, foreshadowing is a genius.
When you say you're not going to do something, because you don't want to do it, but then
you change your mind and you decide, actually, I do want to do that.
And then you do it, that's foreshadowing.
Next voicemail is called women be three, two, one, go.
How did mage leave the podcast and the percentage of women increased?
Well, I really, I guess it's weird, right?
That's life.
I mean, Trixie's gone, so I guess it's the same.
The percentage is what?
It's, I mean, it's...
Oh, I guess the percentage, if there's only three of us.
We're a 33% saturation, womanly saturation.
We're almost equal.
We have...
We almost have gender equality on the progressions, almost, we're almost there.
So we need to kind of maybe pull back a bit from doing that.
Yeah, it's a little uncomfortably high for me, not going to lie.
We've gone a bit too far.
We've gone woke, we've gotten woke and gone broke.
And you're going to have to introduce a gender pay gap and pay me less.
You know what?
To compensate.
That's exactly what I was thinking, now we're talking.
You got to pay the woman tax.
Wait, that's a thing, right?
I'm going to say that about things that are sold as branded for women are just always
a little bit more expensive, right?
I have heard that, the pink version of the healthcare product.
I've always wondered if there's actually anything different, even something as simple as does
the color add to the cost, or if there's, it's just bullshit.
It might be just to like, oh, this is sold as a more specialized product, therefore we
can charge a little more for it, or it might be that we go out of our way to like...
We go out of our way to make it aesthetic, and it adds production cost to the process.
It's a mystery.
It might be a little of both, I honestly.
I'm sure there's some, I mean, I guess the good thing is for a lot of those products,
you can just buy the normal one if you really wanted to.
Most of the time, probably.
Yeah.
You can just get the regular razor.
I know they say that about razors a lot, it's a common example, but I'm pretty sure
regular razors will work just as fine, which is good.
Great.
Okay, next one is shoppin', so women be shoppin', you see, three, two, yes, it forms a, it forms
a dyad.
Three, two, one, go.
Manage left, and you guys all just stand and rush, we're like, fucking, they're gonna
kick us off YouTube, man, we're not gonna pass the Beckdale Pass, fuck, we got to all
transition.
We got to all transition right away, man, we can't fucking go out here with no women
on the show.
We were like, sit, guilt is charged.
I wonder when YouTube was like, oh, it has to have women in it, I forgot.
The woke Illuminati, they were, they were, they were like, the bringing the hammer down
everywhere, we're like, oh God.
It was like, you know, it's like how, it's like Passover, right?
When the angel of the Lord came over, I don't know, fucking, was it Jerusalem or whatever
the fuck, and like, killed your firstborn, and you had to paint, you had to paint blood
over your door, right, lamb's blood to like, get the fucking angel to not kill your kid
or something, right?
That's a story that happened.
Yeah.
Well, it's like that, you got to fucking, we got to fucking paint your fucking woman
menstrual blood on the fucking door, or YouTube is like, no, we can't kill your firstborn,
kill your podcast, kill your ad revenue, it's over.
I saw, I saw a, I saw a Babylon bee.
Article, you know, one of their satiric, I don't like the Babylon bee, but I saw this
article and I thought there was a negative humor in it, it was a, it was a, they said
that like the, the Taliban in Afghanistan were like, they were painting like the trans
flag colors over their doorways to like avoid Biden drone strikes, was like, no, we're trans,
we're painting the, we're flying the trans as like a, as like a, not as like a statement,
but as like a, no, we're woke, you can't kill us, we're a victimized something.
I don't know.
I mean, obviously it's bizarre.
It's a bizarre thing.
Like, yeah, Biden won't drone strike you with your trans, but like, yeah, yeah, but it's
just a funny visual.
The PR would just be too bad.
They're like, no, we're flying the flag.
No.
That's, that's why that's why they paint the fucking nukes.
They paint the nukes with the gay pride flags so that they could like, like find gays and
kill them.
That's why they're doing that.
Well, the gays are attracted to it.
They can't become flocking out of their homes and pouring out on the streets.
Oh, look at that lovely woke explosion.
Oh, we gotta go.
We gotta get some.
It's like, oh, it's a sonic rainbow.
Oh, the shockwave.
Whipple through the cities.
Can't wait to get my cutie mark.
Oh, yeah, we got them.
My fellow Americans, we got them.
We got them all in one go.
All the bronies, dead.
One fell swoop.
We painted rainbow dash on this, on this fucking nukes.
Doesn't that movie come out like next week?
Dropped it over Baltimore, which, oh, the, oh, the, the MLP movie, doesn't it, like,
a week or two or something?
It's soon.
I don't know.
I forget.
I'm looking it up right now.
Dude, I can't wait to go and.
Are we there?
Are we going to September 24th?
It's in five days.
Five days.
Well, are we going to be there?
Are we going to do a review on the show?
We have to.
I want to.
We said we would.
Are we going to do it next week?
Is that going to be our topic for next week?
I'll try to get around to finding, like, a camera for whatever.
It's on Netflix.
So it'll, I don't want to get Netflix.
But, like, someone will find it.
You don't need a camera because it'll be on Netflix.
It'll get, like, an actual.
Oh, yeah.
It'll be good.
I'll find it.
I wasn't suggesting paying money.
Are you kidding me?
I know.
I mean, it'll surely have Netflix.
In which case, you're fine.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sure I can find it.
Okay.
All right.
Well, get hype.
Get hype for that.
Unless, wait, would it be, would it be two callous, two mercenary, two capitalist of
me to say we should make it a bonus episode?
Is that going too far?
Is that over the line?
I don't know.
We have a lot of dead beats to punish for a year or two years of not paying properly.
Absolutely.
We were just saying before the podcast, like, it's going to be interesting to see if everybody
drops off next month.
But if we dangle an MLP video, that'll keep them on the hook for another month.
I'm threatening them with FOMO.
I'm already on the, like, these laps, these laps patrons better not fucking do it again.
They get one.
They do it twice in there.
They fool me once, shame on me.
Fool me twice, shame on you.
And also, I'll kill you.
I don't know.
I mean, we, no, we said, we said we would do it.
We'll probably just do that one of the regular episodes.
It'll probably just, unless we won't, unless we won't.
I don't know.
I mean, whatever.
Stay patron to find out.
Yeah.
It's the only way.
The next voice mail is called Donkey Kongo's Ginted.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys remember the teen CP?
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't, I didn't get that joke for like years.
I didn't know the child porn was the joke.
Yeah.
I don't know if it was.
They made it.
I don't think they made it to be like that.
Never really, never made it through that show.
Started again.
I'm going to kill my.
No, don't kill mice.
My circuit.
I don't, I don't know if, if it was, if that was meant to be the joke.
Although when it was pointed out to me, the phrase teen CP does sound a little, oh dear.
Oh dear.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if that was intentional or not from Rayman.
Oh yeah.
It's like they're very small.
They're teensy.
True.
The small podcast.
Next voicemail is pro crassinators podcast, more like three, two, one, go.
So yeah, I was just watching that old, you know, hippo and a munchie have tea video about
three years ago.
And one of the top comments posted about three years ago read something like, you know, this
video is nice.
I can't wait for, you know, more stuff like this to happen when PCPHQ becomes a thing.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, it was always up in the air whether I was ever going to be a PCPHQ.
Life comes at you fast.
Life does come any fast.
Yeah.
The closest it ever got was Boston.
But Trixie hated it there.
Trixie hated it.
Yeah.
Move to Virginia.
Man, she just got a shitty landlord.
I've got a shitty landlord.
What I have to do is just find a new landlord.
Everyone has a shitty landlord.
Yeah.
Hers was particularly bad.
She showed me, I saw some of the emails she was sending.
I was like, this person is fucking insane.
This person is not allowed to be doing this shit.
My friend was telling me his shitty landlord story and it was pretty fucking lame.
I guess like they were trying to raise everyone's rent a hundred dollars, even though like,
according to New York like law, if you have to give your tenants 90 days warning,
and they were just trying to do it immediately.
So you like got everybody in the building to be like, hey, this is illegal.
You can't do that.
So they waited and then when they finally announced they were raising the rent,
they raised it $150.
Okay, cool.
It's like, well, you can't prove that's retaliation, but that pretty much is retaliation.
Go fuck yourself.
Sucks.
If only, I don't know.
I saw a comment on Twitter that it was like, it's hard to complain about your landlord,
because if you come on Twitter and you say, my landlord is doing this,
someone in the replies will be like, they can't do that.
That's illegal.
They just can't do that.
And it's like, yup.
I know, but they're doing it.
It's like, yes.
They're just doing it.
And yet, here we are.
What are you supposed to do?
Call the police?
I guess you literally just have to take him to court over it.
You literally have to fucking lawyer up.
If you want to be like, hey landlord, you can't do that.
And they're like, yes, I can.
I mean, that's case scenario.
If you get into a tiff with your landlord, you just do, you know,
remember that fucking thing that I did where they were having the dispute with the landlord
and I just lived in their house when they weren't paying rent
because they were in the legal dispute over whether they had to pay it or not.
And they just didn't pay rent for six months and then they left.
Just do that.
Literally.
Here's the strat.
Move into a place.
Be like, hey landlord, you did something illegal.
It doesn't matter if they did.
Make something up.
Be like, yeah, this place doesn't have to code.
I've taken you to court.
And then you go, okay, guess we'll lawyer up.
And then you spend the next six months in court.
You don't pay, you don't pay lease.
And then it's like, okay, well, your case is dismissed.
And you're like, oh, well, bye.
Repeat.
So you pay, you pay off the legal fees.
And then you pay the early termination fee for your lease.
I mean, well, hell, I mean, since it's just a sham case anyway.
No, don't even pay a lawyer.
Don't even pay a lawyer yourself.
Just, just, just file, literally just file the paperwork yourself.
Never show up to any of your court dates.
Get them, just get them delayed as much as you can.
And when they finally are like, well, he's not showing up case dismissed.
You go, well, scams over.
Time to, let's go find the next one.
Well, I guess, Ben, try it out and let us know how it goes.
I will.
I fucking will.
Don't.
Surely if that happens at enough times, you will be known infamously as the guy who gets what he wants and the landlords don't get anything.
As the guy who's the guy who fucking wins, as the guy who's fucking king.
And then nobody will ever let you go into a building ever again.
They, they, what are they going to do?
What are they going to do?
Go on like r slash landlord reddit and just be like, watch out for this one guy.
Look out, it's Ben, the Boston border.
Going from place to place.
The Boston, the Boston squatter.
The, the, the slob, the slob squatter over here.
Uh, uh, there, what are they going to do?
Nothing.
They don't fucking know.
They don't know how to fucking, they will fucking hit them.
The next voicemail is called Harold three, two, one, go.
Hello, it is I, Harold Henry.
Our landlord came by and wanted me to remind you that rent is due on the third, payable in ectoplasms.
Slime coins can no longer be accepted.
No.
As the bank has run out of the necessary conversion catalysts.
That's not, that's Unpog.
No, no, what am I going to do with all these stacks of slime coin?
I gotta liquidate them.
Literally.
Yes.
Into ectoplasm.
Literally must melt them down into slime and then convert the slime through some arcane process into ectoplasm, I guess.
Is ectoplasm a thing in Endless War now?
No.
You bust ghosts and you get it?
I mean it, I mean in the sense that ghosts are a thing.
Yeah, sure.
There is ectoplasm.
If we assume that that's what they're made of.
What about human plasm?
What about ectocooler?
That's the real, the real winner there.
Why can't you buy ectocooler in Endless War?
You can.
Oh.
Wait, is slimer, is slimer, is slimer a juvie or is he a state ed?
He's a ghost and yet he's made of slime.
Like what a, what a, he's the two, he's such a dichotomy.
The universe is crumbling.
The dichotomy of man.
He's the ultimate paradox.
Stay slime, that's what he is.
We gotta, we gotta add slimer to Endless War.
We gotta add slimer.
There's just, he represents too much of like a, it's like, you know, it's like, it's like Knights of the Old Republic.
The story of Knights of the Old Republic is they, the story of that game and those games is they took the setting of, of Star Wars and they like asked questions.
They were like, why is the setting like this?
Does this even make sense?
Well, let's make the story about all these characters that, that are questioning, like why are the Jedi the good guys?
Are the Jedi the good guys?
What does it mean?
Why do they sit through what they do?
What is the ramifications of all these things?
This is what we gotta do with slimer.
Putting slimer into Endless War raises the questions.
What even is, what even is slime?
What even is it to be, to be dead?
What even is, is, is anything anymore?
Is there even a meaningful difference?
It's, it's, you gotta live the questions.
You gotta live the questions.
Okay, next one is called.
I am so hard.
Three, two, one, go.
Ah, ah, ah, hello, BCP.
I hope you're having a wonderful podcast.
I'm having a good one, thank you.
I'm just over here reveling in my power.
Is this Tommy J?
Knowing that at any moment I could ruin the voicemail segment by sending in hundreds and hundreds of voicemail with only fast noises.
He's drunk on power.
Of course.
I would never do that.
I love the voicemail scene.
Yes, me too.
Be ashamed.
If I choose to do so, and that gets me so hard.
Well, you're welcome.
The laugh at the beginning made me think of the count from Sesame Street saying all that.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Right?
Let's have a laugh.
Yes.
Um, well, I'm glad you're having a good time.
The next one is called hashtag general strike, and there's a link to http colon slash slash octoberstrike.com.
Let's give that a listen.
Three, two, one, go.
So some people are organizing a general strike in the United States starting on October 15th, and I'm tired and stupid, so I can't really appraise the efficacy of it.
But I feel like more people should know about it, you know?
Hmm.
Generals, what does it mean to be a general strike?
Like, everybody just stops working?
Yeah, I think that's the idea.
The entire labor market goes on strike.
The whole of America just stops?
Yeah, I mean, that's the idea.
I mean, it's pretty ambitious.
What would they do if that happens?
What would they say to the higher ups?
Fix things or your money stops.
But like, there should be a purpose for the strike, right?
Like, we want better this or that.
I'm sure the website probably clarifies what their goals are.
Well, I'm trying to go to the website and it's not loading for me.
Oh, no.
It's dead before it started.
It might be my computer that's...
What is a general strike?
A general strike is a strike action in which a substantial population of the total labor force in a city, region, or country participates.
General strikers are characterized by the participation of workers in a multitude of workplaces and tend to involve entire communities.
General strikes first occurred in the mid-19th century and have characterized many historically important strikes.
Our goals, 25% corporate tax rate, no loopholes, free healthcare for all, 12 weeks paid paternity and maternity leave, $20 minimum wage, 4-day work week, stricter environmental regulations on corporations.
If you support any of our goals, stand in solidarity with us on October 15th by taking off work.
Um, yeah.
I mean, all good, very, very harsh changes.
Um, good luck my dudes.
It's ambitious.
I mean, you gotta aim high.
Sure.
You gotta aim high.
You gotta ask for a lot.
It's all about setting your anchor.
And then when you negotiate.
Yeah, so you can cut some of those back.
Yeah, and be like, okay.
Well, all right.
Not 20.
Okay, well 15.
15 minimum wage.
I mean, the hard part is getting the numbers because everybody would be like, yeah, I guess I could do the strike, but I don't want to lose my job.
I don't want to get fired.
So I won't.
And then most people think that and most people don't.
I, I, it's, it's, I would really, I would really like it for something like this to successfully happen.
And I would really, really like it if it were to have the intended effect.
I, I guess I, it seems, it seems ambitious.
What am I trying to say?
It seems, seems like a lot to hope for.
But I mean, I don't know.
I don't want to be, I don't want to be a do-more about it.
The bare minimum, the bare minimum of just mentioning it wouldn't really be enough to make it happen.
You'd need to do a lot of convincing, I think.
Yeah.
I don't know what about it at all.
I'm not even in America.
I would, I mean, um, I don't know.
Maybe I should, maybe it's worth like spreading awareness.
Like, yeah, general straight.
It's pretty cool.
I just, I don't, I don't think most people, I don't think most people, even if they agree with these things are going to do it.
I just don't think people are going to do it.
Well, even if one out of 100 people who saw your tweet did it, you're still contributing slightly towards the effectiveness of the action.
You got to get critical mass.
Sounding pretty doomer logic over their band.
Do you think people are going to go to their boss and be like, hey boss, I am not coming into work on the 15th because it is a general strike.
I am on strike for one day along with the rest of the country.
So there.
What you should do is be like, hey boss, I'm striking tomorrow and you should strike too because your boss is putting the fucking screws to you as well.
That's true.
It's just, it's so general.
I think the thing is you need, you need people to be convinced that most of the rest of the people are doing it.
Yeah.
Somehow.
Because if you can't get everybody under the impression that everybody else is going to do it, everybody's going to think, well, I don't want to be the only person doing it.
Yeah.
And then nobody does anything.
The other thing about it is that it's not, you're not, you're not striking from your job and you're telling your job, but here's what I want you to do.
You're striking from your job and being like, it's not really about you.
This is something I want the government to do.
And it's like, I do understand, it's not that I don't understand how one affects the other, but it's like indirect.
It's like, I'm striking against my job, not because I want my job to do anything different, but because I want the government to do something different.
Well, I suppose the goals that they're stating don't technically have to be enforced by law.
Like you could have companies enforce these policies themselves.
They won't, obviously, because they're cesspools of evil.
I appreciate.
I've just sort of heard that smaller strikes with a single company are more efficient or more effective at actually happening because it's reasonably possible to get the majority of the people in the company on your side.
But depending on the side of the country, if you're trying to do a country-wide thing, so many things need to fall into place.
Definitely necessary and we're long past the point where we should be in the streets with pitchforks, hungry and thirsty for blood.
However, I don't think culturally we're there yet.
I think we need another decade of being absolutely dumped on before we get to that point.
America is so pacified and so docile that it would take literal destitution of everybody for things to actually get to that point where it's like, I guess I'll ride in the streets because I don't have a house to go to anymore.
That's when it'll start.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, things could be a lot better.
They need to get a lot worse first.
Until they get a lot worse, there's not hunger for it.
As long as you can get yours, your tiny little table scraps.
I appreciate the audacity. I appreciate the boldness of the four-day work week.
I appreciate them including that.
We need to start an October strike where we have to get in there and be like, look, we want all of our bosses.
Government mandated that our bosses with their big corporate accounts have to retweet us, not just like.
I feel like a perfectly organized society increases the amount of automation it has.
It decreases the amount of human labor that needs to be done and as that happens, the work week shrinks and shrinks.
The average person just needs to work less. Labor just goes down to nothing and eventually everything is automated and there is no work week.
We have luxury, fully automated, gay luxury space communism.
They'll find ways.
Because with the industrial revolution, there was already talk back then.
The four-day work week seems like an acknowledgement of that is the direction that we should move it, even if it's not going to happen.
But I like that they're acknowledging that is the goal.
We've been able to do that for decades and we haven't because there's a vested interest in keeping people enslaved at their desks.
There's a culture of work.
If you aren't working nine to five, five days a week, then you're weird and that's bad and that's deviant behavior and that's just what people should do.
To be out here being like, no, actually it would be better if people worked less.
Some people literally don't see it that way. Some people don't think that's true.
I'm glad they're calling it like it is.
Less work is better, actually.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll retweet this and be like, general strike is good. I like it.
I don't have a boss, so I can't strike.
It's strange how people will simultaneously be rise and grind and work smarter, not harder.
Those don't really work together.
Work less, not harder.
That's a movement I can get behind.
Yeah, yeah.
Next voicemail is called, it's one of these fucking fast upload. What is this?
Why is there another site? Why is this happening?
They're not over a minute and a half.
How to use the internet.
There's some reason you can do voice modulation or something.
People can do voice modulation, maybe it's easier.
I know it's possible through a speak pipe, but whatever.
This one is called snitch.
Three, two, one, go.
I love drawcast. I think it's the peak of your content.
I've saved every drawcast and quick draw onto my hard drive, just in case.
However, while doing that, I've noticed some people called procrastinators anonymous
using the title PCP drawcast for their videos.
They seem like soulless Twitter addicts, even more so than you.
You should sue them for copyright.
I think we'll get our lawyers on that immediately.
They've turned that into the good pro and on people have taken that
and turned it into its own channel, which is what I was on for the teleproto.
That channel is mine too much.
That channel is called the drawcast, and that's not really a copyrightable name.
It's not called the PCP drawcast, is it?
That would be weird.
I don't believe so. I think it's just the drawcast.
That's like what the logo says on everything.
Unless there's something else that this person is talking about.
They definitely aped the style because they do the thing in some of the earlier episodes
where it's like, oh, the only people who are worth it down, the ones that can draw.
That's the thing that Munchie came up with.
Oh, they say that.
Whatever.
That's funny.
Honestly, I appreciate it because we don't do them anymore.
Munchie deleted all of his content, so all of those catchphrases went into the public domain.
That's just the rules.
Yeah, true.
It's just like in corporate law, when the person that created a work abandons it,
when they die or they leave, it immediately goes to public domain
and is owned by culture from then on.
The thing about it is that...
That's the law, right?
Yeah, definitely.
It would be crazy.
Can you imagine?
If some company still owned characters that were made up by dead people hundreds of years ago
and they were still not public domain private property, that would be outlandish.
That sounds like you need a general strike or something to fix that.
True.
The thing with the show is that it's just people drawing.
They're drawn together and it's timed little attempts at certain themes
and it's like the title is the least important part of the thing.
I don't really mind people using the title or even the theme.
You can't copyright a show where you just draw with friends.
True.
Yeah.
So it doesn't matter.
We can just start doing them and continue to call them a draw cast if we want it to.
We could.
They can co-exist.
Did we ever release the draw cast that we did three years ago with just drawing with a mouse?
I remember we recorded that.
I don't think it ever got posted.
Wait, what, really?
I don't know if it did.
I don't remember it ever getting posted.
Do we have an unreleased draw cast?
I don't have the footage for it anymore.
I had to get rid of it a long time ago.
So if it's gone, it's gone like the ages.
But I remember we did a bunch of...
Would it have been a quick draw or a draw cast?
Oh, God.
Because I feel like we must have put all the draw casts out because we started doing quick draw afterwards.
It's so long ago.
I can't remember if it was a draw cast or a quick draw.
Oh, well.
It doesn't matter.
I don't think I was on that because I don't remember doing a drawing with a mouse challenge.
Did I?
Am I crazy?
I'm not sure.
It's so long ago.
I have no idea.
It's just like a vague recollection.
I just remember the files just been sitting on my Google Drive for years up until like 18
months ago.
I was like, you know what?
I don't think these are ever going to be used.
I don't need to hold onto them anymore.
Would it have been Eleazar, been the editor at that time?
I don't know.
Would he have maybe the file?
Maybe we could ask him.
Someone in the comments might be like, oh, that was posted years ago.
You idiot.
And then I'll look stupid, which is definitely possible.
If you know what we're talking about posting the comments, if you don't say no, you never
posted it, lol.
And then, okay.
Next voicemail is an image.
If you see this here, it is the Virgin American poo versus the Chad Soviet poo.
And I got to say, this American poo is looking kind of piglet-ish.
He's looking a bit piglet-y.
Those ears don't look right.
He's absolutely piglet-y.
They're not round.
The body is shaped like piglet.
It's very piglet.
Unnatural jaundice color.
Disney owns his soul.
Does stupid shit that's not even in the original books.
The Chad Soviet poo.
He's round.
He's brown.
He's down to clown.
I'll post the image here.
That is a bulletproof argument.
Have you guys seen Soviet poo?
No.
There's a Russian version of Winnie the Pooh and he looks like this.
Well, let me find it on YouTube.
Russian poo bear.
That's dangerous search by itself.
Here we go.
Copy link.
Post it right here.
There.
Winnie the Pooh Russian animation.
He's got crayon backgrounds.
It might not literally be poo, because it doesn't look like him.
Maybe he's called poo, but it's technically a distinct character.
Oh, no.
I see a pig.
Yeah, he's got a little pig friend.
Yeah, it's all the same characters.
They just all look completely different.
This is the exact same story of Winnie the Pooh.
Winnie is stuck on the balloon.
Yeah.
Do you think they just adapted the books?
Maybe.
It is kind of awesome.
Do you think they just adapted the books?
Do you think they just did it without the rights?
Or do you think they also bought the rights to animate the books?
I'm sure the Chad Soviets were like,
this shit should have been in the public domain years ago
and just took it and did it, because they were fucking cool like that.
This is really nicely animated.
The animation is unironically great.
I mean, the Soviet Union, they were communist,
so was that their thing?
Were they like, everything is public domain?
We don't respect copyright law.
Oh, dude, Rabbit looks sick.
It would make sense.
Wait, where's...
I just trumped 1856.
Rabbit, it's got glasses.
He looks fucking cool.
Oh, um...
Yeah, this is like the exact plot of it.
He gets stuck in there and everything.
It looks like the combination of Arthur and his boyfriend.
Look at this nerd.
Look at this fucking nerd.
Do it yet.
Yet.
Dude, this is awesome.
It kind of is.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
We probably shouldn't spend the whole...
Absolutely Chad.
Agreed.
Yeah, yeah.
I thought I was thinking it was a joke like, ha ha.
Goofy.
It's funny to say Chad Soviet poo is the Chad one when he's all...
But actually, he kind of is.
He's great.
I've been won over.
Next one is called...
The image is...
Here we go.
It's Kanga Mage.
Kanga Mage.
There she is.
As requested by Nate on episode 141.
That's a while.
I don't even remember.
I do not remember the context.
But I'm sure it's true.
I'll send it over to her, I guess.
I'm sure Nate will be excited to see that his dream has been fulfilled.
Definitely add him on Twitter and see if he remembers.
Was this because we were talking about her OC that is some fucking mammal that nobody knows what it is,
and maybe Nate thought it was a kangaroo?
That sounds very plausible.
Yeah, it's like a big ears long thin tail with a fluff at the end.
Yeah, I don't remember what...
The animal.
It's a real animal and I don't remember what it's called.
Chinchilla?
No, could it?
No, it's not a chinchilla.
Some weird shit.
A wibbly mouse.
Some sort of a mouse.
Yes.
Next voicemail.
Okay, we're back to actual voicemails.
The next one is called Not Petan.
Three, two, one, go.
Besides having your head crushed, what is the most disturbing thought or idea?
How do I even begin to answer that?
That's like a whole dissertation.
I mean, there's so much.
The whole finiteness in both time and space.
That's too abstract to get actually upset about.
Really?
Speak for yourself.
Yeah, that's the source of constant, unending, intracensual dread.
The universe is so big and I'm so small, but who cares?
I'm hungry.
Cool.
I mean, me too.
I mean, sure.
No, I don't agree, but I don't agree, but I respect it.
That's part of the dread, understanding the absolute massive implications of such a thing,
but your simple flesh brain is just like, oh, but I want food.
No, I have this huge problem.
I like that.
It's terrifying.
I'm a funny sack of flesh.
I'm a meatbag.
Gross, disgusting.
We need to transcend.
I'm like, damn, in time, there was a time before I existed.
There will be a time after I exist in the dimensions.
So deep.
Left of me, right of me, up and down and forward and back, there is space in which I don't exist.
I'm only inside of this little bubble of time and space and everything outside of that is not me.
And soon, that's all that will be left.
And I'm like, I don't want, if I were to go, if I were to go, if I were to travel, like, I don't know,
if I go next door or like in the house, in that room next over for me, it's like, I don't exist over there.
There is no me over there.
And I'm like, I'm only here.
And I'm only now.
I don't know.
Take my Minecraft shovel.
Digs two block hole, buries you as you think.
By the way, I'm not clapping because there's a fly that is my ass cheeks.
I'm jumping, I'm doing jumping jacks.
Next question?
There's a few left.
Okay, next one is Simpsons question.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, Gib, you know a lot about the Simpsons and I know nothing about the Simpsons.
When does it get bad?
And I don't mean goes downhill.
I mean, like, gets bad, unwatchable.
Please answer.
I have heard that it actually, it gets pretty bad for a while.
I mean, it starts to go downhill like around season, maybe like eight or nine.
And then by season 10, it's like, it's moved into like, okay, this is no longer really the original show.
And then it basically just gets progressively worse and worse until like season like late 20s.
And then I've heard that it actually sort of starts to get a little more watchable in like the very late seasons because I think it just sort of leans into being what it is now,
instead of like doing as much of like a hollow mimicry of like the old version.
But that's just what I've heard because I haven't, I've watched it up to around season, maybe 17, 18.
And I mean, I guess I thought it was still pretty all right at the time.
Yeah, I remember watching, being like, I wonder when it gets bad.
And I got to like season 20 and I was like, oh, maybe I don't know how to tell when Simpsons is bad.
You know, the consensus is that classic Simpsons is around up to season 10 or so.
And then I was enjoying myself.
So I don't know.
It's just good.
This is a good show.
People get too bent out of shape about it.
I don't remember thinking it was bad in seasons like, in seasons like like 17, 18.
I know, and I haven't really even watched that much of it past that.
So I genuinely have no idea.
It sort of goes from like, oh, Simpsons is like every episode is a banger.
Everyone is like killer 10 out of 10.
Yeah.
And then it goes into, occasionally there's an actually kind of annoying one.
And then that just sort of increases the amount of annoying episodes.
But like, yeah, it's just, I think it's generally pretty good.
It's a slow decline after the classic era.
It's not like, it's not like it completely goes over a cliff in any like one.
I mean, you know, people say like the Frank Grimes episode and the mod.
People say the Frank Grimes episode and the mod episode were like, oh, that's when it jumped the shark.
But like, it's not like the show, it was different, was immediately different after those.
Those are just like the first times that some people were like, that episode kind of annoyed me.
And then later there would be more episodes that people would find annoying.
I thought Frank Grimes was a good one.
It's, people fight it.
Is it contentious?
Yeah.
It's contentious because people think that it's like mean spirited and they think it's the start of like Homer is,
Homer is basically like irredeemable and he's not, he's not likable at all in that episode.
And it just, I think a lot of people don't like that.
And Homer has a likability problem later on.
He becomes jerk ass Homer where he's just, he's just an asshole and an idiot.
And like, that's supposed to be the joke.
But people like, oh, I kind of thought he was like a lovable oaf, not just like a fucking piece of shit.
But it's like, in that episode, he's like terrible.
So people say like, this is the start of jerk ass Homer.
But it's not, it's not a bad episode.
It's just has a tone to it.
I think some people weren't expecting.
It's also like, it's also very cult of work-y.
Like in that episode, you're supposed to be rooting for Grimes.
And Grimes' whole thing is like, work is good.
And like the guy who wrote it, there's a Renegade cut video about that episode.
And the guy who wrote it is like a pretty conservative guy.
And when you really think about the themes of that episode, it's like,
like poverty is good actually.
Like literally like raising yourself up by your bootstraps is good.
The American way of life is like degenerate.
It's like two Americans are soft because they don't have it hard enough.
Struggle builds character.
That's kind of the whole sort of attitude behind it.
It's very libertarian in a way.
I don't know.
Okay, I guess that's all I have to say about it.
Next episode is called, I never received the body.
Three, two, one, go.
It has been one week.
And I have not received Tommy J's body.
He must be getting hungry.
I tried contacting Amazon customer support.
But they thought that I was a child pulling a break phone call.
I don't even know what a break phone call is.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
There is a way that I think I can still survive.
I need a spark.
A spark from a saver.
That will inspire me to go on.
A spark from a saver held by a better Tom.
I saw me on that.
That's the one from power.
I don't know what to help you with.
I saw me on that.
Got it, got it, yep.
I'm still hungry.
This guy is so fucked.
He's pretty fucked.
Someone needs to tell him about Door Dash, like for real.
Tom, you got to help this guy out.
He's begging you.
I don't know the context.
He wants it.
He wants Tommy Oliver.
No, he wants a spark from a saver held by Tommy Oliver.
You got to give it to him.
Is it like a fire keeper soul?
I need to get a saver spark soul.
Yes, yes.
You must ignite.
You need to kill saver spark with his own saver.
Oh, is that like the drop?
You get the spark soul and then like saver spark saver.
And it's like an agility weapon.
Yes, why not?
Okay, okay.
Guy, don't worry, we're on it.
I'll look up the tutorial on YouTube and see what I can do.
We're not going to abandon you, buddy.
We're not going to abandon you like Biden abandoned the troops in Afghanistan.
Okay, next one is called Gibb Better Than Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Thank you, Gibb, for making sure.
So let's go up in a timely fashion.
Unlike other certain hosts.
What?
You got it wrong.
Gibb forgot to list to public the episode.
It was not my fault.
But I like that people think it's Ben's fault.
That's really funny too.
It seems like a Ben's fault.
I mean, you're the head honcho around here apparently.
I guess.
I'm in charge.
Sure.
Isn't it great that Digi's anime podcast has become Ben's anime podcast?
Ben's communism podcast.
Ben's cultural Marxism podcast based.
You know, it couldn't have ended any other way.
Yeah, thanks Gibb.
Next one is called Ben is a cave rapist.
Three, two, one, go.
So I was in DC this week and we went to the exhibit on early humans.
And in regards to like the wandering vagrant sexual predator caveman topic from last week.
Yes.
There was a cave called the Cindy Har Cave, I believe, in Iran.
That sounds familiar.
With evidence of family units in cave and Neanderthal days.
Yeah.
And it definitely backs up Ben, sadly.
Wait, what?
I don't know if that really proves my point.
Families doesn't like imply pornography.
Yeah, I'm not really sure what the proof.
I'm not really sure why this is proof of what I was saying.
I mean, I mentioned family units and that probably family units would have like defended their women from like rape, for instance.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, my thing was not like, oh, if it wasn't porn, then it must have been everyone was raping, which is what you took it as initially.
No, that's not exactly what I took it at.
I mean, I mean, I can't remember exactly whatever.
Yeah, I kind of remember, don't exactly remember the details.
It's fine.
Tom, what do you think about caveman rape?
You pro or anti?
You pro or anti.
You know, I'm really not literally going to discuss.
I'm kind of just going to sit on that fence and get nice and comfortable.
I'm just trying to grill over here.
The centrist take, I did.
I'm just trying to grill in my cave.
Yeah, seriously.
Next one is called Riley Gazers.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, this is Riley from the broadcast of yig, yig, yig, yig, yig, yig, yig, yig, yig, yig.
Void, void, void.
Good, good call.
Good, yeah.
Good voicemail.
Thumbs up.
Next one is called Riley Cyrus.
Three, two, one, go.
Yes, yes, that is the best one.
I know.
He loves it.
I love it.
He's a big fan. He loves it
What what am I thinking of what am I thinking of a guy yelling he loves it like I feel like I've seen a scene and something like that
We're just like I I he loves it
No, but that's Riley that that's right. I'm thinking of the loves and similar he loves it
He loves it
Am I thinking of am I thinking of?
Not not Chris Brown. Am I thinking of fucking who's that comedian?
the one that
Dave Chappelle and I think I mean I think enough Dave Chappelle
In that bit about the fried chicken when he goes like look at him. He loves it
I have no idea maybe the only one can answer that question Ben is you I
Am I mean that he did say that he definitely says that he loves it
Okay, whatever next one is Lego City for the win three two one go
You understand
This is like a Chinese
Advertisement wait, did he's recorded really badly? Did he say something at the end? I don't think so
He says he says I love I love Lego City at the end
Me too
Good
Next one is called yellow grooves cicada crusade three two one go
Go ahead
Oh
Some sort of an edit of
Of like a video of a guy trying to catch a cicada or something. Yeah, all there is he's getting it
but like it's an edit of that and
Recorded with music in the background on a like a shitty mic
I appreciate the aesthetic of whatever that was that was good. Yeah, I kind of liked it
kind of liked it
And I
Was funny a guy says it's funny. He says all good to get the cicada
Oh, no it goes in my eye and then I laughed and then I laughed next one is called seventh deadly sin
procrastinating hoarder three two one go
Is Jones
It tastes like
Is this like part of an album or something I mean a bunch of these seem like they're recorded with the same microphone
Life hack you can play it at two X
Oh
Yeah
All right, all right good boys. No good boys. No good loving it. Next one is called reelection campaign three two one go
Hi, I'm a piece of shit
Stuck to the side of your toilet bowl
Hi, I'm a full-blooded American
This is what it means to live in the greatest country on earth I
Have a piece of shit scraped off the side of a road lightly baked in the sun
American dream is alive in me
Like a turd squeezed through the anus of a dog
Rolling in the sand the sand clings to the exterior. It appears white, but brown internally
The anti-Oreo
I am a representative of the people
Like a turd stuck to the ceiling fan in the White House
Spin it too fast your walls are plastered
Spin it just right and you have democracy I
Believe in the people I
Believe and Ben saint
Sealing on the shit saying on the ceiling fans spin it too fast the walls get plastered, but it's just right that's democracy
I
Voice voice grail voice grail remember that
Yeah, that was pretty good
Okay, almost voice grail, but no just missing it goes in the fucking trash bin next next to it
Next next one is called to Ellie is our three two one go
Hi, Ellie is our what's your opinion on this week's episode?
Ellie's are edit in a text on the screen. I
Thought thanks. I thought he was gonna maybe just put a little clip of him voice saying and then I was gonna say
Wow, Ellie is our that sure was a you can't fucking say that Ellie's a how could you say that Ellie's are you gonna get canceled?
How come he didn't retweet my art you just liked it
You fucking idiot
Let a very contentious opinion got to say I don't I don't agree, but I respect the hustle got to respect the hustle
And I think this is the last voicemail is the next one. We finally fucking made it
Next scary link
Wonder what it is
It is uh
It's it's uh, well, I guess I'll post it in the
Sorry, it's Nate
Hope it a ho-ho tap Nate we was Kings. I think they've darkened his skin
I don't know what that had Nigerian Prince 69 at gamerzone.com
He looks he looks
At least having a great time
What a note to end on we did it everyone we made it to another episode of the
procrastinators podcast patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators if you want to get all those bonus episodes including the ones that we designed to make you feel bad if you
Don't listen to
If you don't want to hate yourself go there speak pipe comm slash PCB voicemail if you want to leave us
Some of this fucking shit that we have to deal with every goddamn week
Uh
What else what what else what am I forgetting?
Nothing
voicemails
Patron
Follow our personal social media accounts donate to our personal patrons as well
Read the law of ghosts and remember to retweet it and don't don't not retweet
Don't even fucking read it if you're not gonna retweet it you fucking idiot retweet it before you read it
I would say so if you if you if you have to read it to make sure that you want to retweet it
Then you're just a coward. I'm sorry. I'm sorry hot hot take hot take, but there it is
It's the truth. You're not you're not but you're not ready for that conversation
Big artist I follow retweet. Are you gonna read it? Hell no
Yes, that's the good version good version timeline
Did you read what you just retweeted? Hell no
Did you see all the fucking terrible all the fucking slurs and all the fucking like all the all the all the
Hargore with no trigger warning and all the all the all the terrible things that you can't fucking put on Twitter. Nope
I'm just I'm retweeting
Because it's the right because the right thing to do because it's the right thing to do baby
That's the end of the episode done
Okay, bye. Bye. Good night
Good. Yeah, good. Bye