This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was bought to you by our bonus episode.
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge five dollars or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
Last month's episode was Gamergate vs. the 2016 presidential election.
Donald and Hillary, the original Goku and Vegeta will unite when the world needs them most.
It is the Gurren Lagann to the elections Kill La Kill.
All of these fucking psychopathic, Ben-Saintian, blue-pilled motherfuckers.
A depression quest. The greatest indie game in ever made.
Jeb was a fantastic character. I want his narrative to keep going.
God-tier Dorito, Dustin, Crustin, red-pilled motherfuckers who said,
No, not our video games.
You don't give a fuck about Gamergate, but Donald Trump, he's my dad.
You don't know shit until you hear about my boy, Ted Cruz.
That's patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, making bonus episodes great again, every single time.
Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators podcast.
It's me, your host, and your boy, Ben-Saint here.
And I'm here with Munchywares Tiny Hats.
Hey everyone, welcome to my Photoshop tutorial.
I'm going to be teaching you how to make a gradient transparent.
Let's start with the break-up of the Ottoman Empire.
It's going to be a really easy Photoshop tutorial.
I have to explain the entire history of the Middle East first, though.
What the fuck, and we're here with Tom Oliver.
I'm here talking about the topic.
I also, I had Zabram earlier, so I'm going to be silly today.
Let's do it.
Whoa, and there's also the best guy ever.
I did the mash.
I did the race war mash.
What? What is going on?
What were you doing earlier, and why didn't you invite me?
And in a rare twist of fate, we've got Lethal Aurora Mage.
Can this mean that I'm not on the podcast die already?
You have to fix it. You're the master of your own main destiny.
I was on the podcast like a month ago for the whole month.
Mage, you're the only female member of the PCP,
which means you have to be here five times as often to count for anything.
I haven't seen you been Lethal once.
You're a representative for your entire gender.
It's all writing on you.
My gender is purple. Excuse you.
You're the only purple gender on the podcast.
The PCP is the most gender-realist podcast on the net,
and we need the other side to be there as a strawman
that we can defeat week after week after week.
I personally find this very vivid aquamarine.
That's true. That's true.
Ben, why don't you tell us what the fuck we're doing, you baby boy?
We're talking about monsters,
which we thoroughly, thoroughly covered,
and pretty much said all there is to say about on the drawcast,
the ultimate PCP content.
They say a picture's worth a thousand words,
but if all those words are fucking bullshit,
you've got to come in with some real words that are targeted.
All we have to do is increase the number of word count in this episode
by number of pictures produced in that podcast,
multiplied by a thousand.
We just have to talk more than that,
which I think is an easily attainable goal.
One of these Superfans, Denix Jack,
count the number of words that are in this podcast
and tell us if we meet it.
What happened was me, Ben, and Major were all squibbling
in our scribed in, in the inner walls of Jericho,
and the villain thief, Nate, was peering over the palace walls,
trying to learn our trade secrets,
and so he banished forever from the garden of even
that is the PCP drawcast.
Like Adam before, cast Wrout into your drawcast.
He has to reverse this podcast, this drawcast topic,
so he can get his grubby fucking hands on it.
That's what's happened here today.
There was just too much, too much delicious, rich content
within the subject of monsters to just be left there
in the festering dirty floor of the drawcast.
There's never enough monsters if you ask me, so I'm here.
I don't know, I don't even think monsters are real guys.
Ben, I don't know what a monster is.
I've never had that explained to me before.
Can I, can I cut in here for a moment?
I would like to describe to everyone what exactly
a monster is that we're talking about.
Okay, so here we go.
Urban Dictionary, our old buddy, tells us
that a monster is nuclear horse piss
sold as a disgusting energy drink.
Oh shit!
What a monster is, yep.
Let's see what else we got here.
Describing anything that is large,
these are all part of one definition apparently.
The creature that lives in your closet and under your bed,
okay, and then one last one,
a sadistic pedophile who molests and rapes children he abducts.
Whoa, I didn't know Nick was a monster.
None of these descriptions describe monsters
that we're talking about.
Monsters are scary, mostly fuzzy things that go brar
and I go, ah!
I know about monsters.
I imagine monsters are like creatures that don't exist.
Monsters are like big men with rubber on their face.
All I know about monsters is that they're incorporated
and they're great people.
Monsters are usually fuzzy fucking government fat cats
who just want to subjugate the weak.
Alright, listen to this one more definition of monster.
This one is like the third most popular.
It's what you become when you break up with a girl.
What the hell is this?
Man, listen to this quote.
Man, we need to talk.
Woman, you're a monster.
Dude, that's some real shit, man.
That's fantastic.
Monsters are fake things that scare me.
I know.
Much like all fake things.
As I exist only and completely within the realm of reality.
Whenever I'm confronted with things that are not in fact real,
I can't contain my emotions
and all my anger and sadness flows out of my body
when I'm confronted with a fictional being.
Alright, let's go around real quick
and everybody talk about either your favorite
or a favorite monster of yours.
The Slender Man is a monster who has tentacles
and he's really tall and he is a black suit.
Dude.
And all the fucking other ones,
okay, Marble Hornets is the best fucking creepy ARG on the planet.
And all the bullshit, like Tribe 12 and fucking Everyman Hybrid,
all that shit is horrible.
I tried watching Everyman Hybrid and it fucking sucked shit.
It made no sense.
It was purposely just trying to be like a weird meta.
It was fucking like the reluctant YouTuber,
but if it was a Slender Man ARG,
that's what Everyman Hybrid is.
Marble Hornets was OG shit.
Marble Hornets is fucking,
what does Alicorn Twilight Princess Sparkle mean to you?
That's what fucking Marble Hornets is.
That's the real shit.
I love Marble Hornets.
Slender Man, he's not even called Slender Man that way.
He's called the operator.
You can operate your sickness if you look at him.
The screen shakes.
I have operate your sickness whenever I get on the PCP
because the PCP is just too powerful
and it reminds me too much of Slender Man.
Slender Man used to be my waifu before it was cool.
Really? Is that true?
Has anyone else seen Everyman Hybrid and Marble Hornets?
Because I actually have.
I have seen Marble Hornets.
No, I've never seen them been.
Well, I mean, besides you.
See, I saw them thinking that probably nobody else
on this podcast would have ever seen them.
I saw Marble Hornets.
Guys, guys, guys.
I knew about Slender Man before it became popular.
It was just around the time, just before it became mainstream.
I was fucking post about it on Reddit.
So I can upvote you then, god damn it.
I was fucking Marble Hornets before it was even done.
I was Marble Hornets before they even found out
that Tim was the mascot.
I'm fucking day one.
I'm fucking day fucking one.
Pulls off mask.
My face is revealed to be a hornet made of marble.
That's me.
I did it.
Am I the joke, guys?
That's good, right?
You would like Marble Hornets.
You would like it.
Because there's a bunch of fucking...
I'm googling it right now.
I'm looking at the weird spooky shit here.
There's a bunch of shit.
Oh, I think someone beats a woman in it one time.
Oh, hell yeah.
Me?
I watched the video.
It's me.
Yes.
How many episodes are there out there right now?
Marble Hornets just recording me.
It's like 107 or something, I think.
Oh, okay.
It's me in my daily life.
It's just what it is.
I caught up with Marble Hornets in one night.
Like procrastinating, going to sleep for like my first day of sixth grade.
Oh, this is a show.
Is this like a TV show?
No, it's a YouTube show.
It's like a webtoon.
Oh, okay.
It's like a YouTube series kind of semi-found footage photo documentary.
Exactly.
Trying to document this weird thing that happens.
It's an energy.
It's recorded in a way that looks realistic, but it's totally bullshit.
Okay.
How old is this thing?
It's very old.
It's a fictional story.
It's not like it's trying to trick you.
It's like it's a Blair Witch project.
Well, yeah.
It's a YouTube video series.
You know, that's the weird thing.
I feel like a lot of people, okay.
I mean, first of all, you've got like those girls who like literally tried to sacrifice
their friend in the woods to Slenderman, who is a literal made-up fake internet.
Who is me?
Which was Munchy.
Munchy was the girl being sacrificed and the people doing the sacrifice.
And Slenderman.
You know, it was a big thing.
He's basically the Trinity.
He's the father, son, and the Holy Ghost.
Sacrificing himself to himself to appease his own wrath upon the people he created.
That's who Munchy is.
Okay.
This is cool.
Well, what I was going to say is like, people really seem to like get whipped up into a storm
and like take this shit seriously.
And it's weird to me.
It's weird to me that people are so...
I mean, it's the...
What's the opposite of skeptical?
You know, like believers or something or have so much credulous.
I guess that...
Yeah, I think that's right.
People like look for things to believe in like this.
And I've never understood that.
I guess because it's fun.
I guess because it's just fun.
Eggs.
You know?
What other reason do you need?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Like, is it fun to sacrifice your friend in the woods to Slenderman?
Yeah, because Slenderman like you then.
I know.
People like spooky stories.
Dude.
Oh.
Isn't that a fascinating thing though?
Why do people like being scared?
You know, I also don't quite get it.
I'm not as into it as I feel like a lot of people are.
As I said in the Ghost episode, ghosts aren't real, but they should be.
Right.
And I love ghosts.
And if I pray every night at some day they'll magically become real and I'll be able to
see a ghost with my own eyes.
Just like in season three of Korra where all the airbenders just literally became real
again.
It was awesome.
So good.
What a great development.
I love Korra.
Me too, dude.
That's some fucking...
Korra!
I just want to put it out there.
Korra is my favorite monster.
She is the most evil being who ever existed.
She makes the world a worse place with her mere presence.
The monsters don't always have to be evil to go.
Yes.
But Korra is.
Korra is undeniably evil.
Yeah.
I'm just making a statement.
That's true.
And you were saying this on the draw cast too.
You're a staunch defender of monster rights.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
We must defend a monster free speech.
It's important.
People like monsters because they put you closer to death and what do we all want but
death?
We all seek oblivion.
Blindly.
Now I'm speaking my language.
And I quickly just mentioned a dream I had before this podcast.
It has a monster in it.
And I just wanted to...
Sure.
Okay.
So quickly I'll try.
So the dream.
Man-made island and on the island is just nothing but this big building and I live there
and there's a mansion and other people and slowly one by one people are getting murdered
in very horrible ways.
You just see the bodies laying on the floor and just blood everywhere and they kept getting
dragged away and like me and the manager trying to figure out what's happening.
And then like I finally found out that like there's this monster here like and it's trying
to kill us.
And I was one of the few people left alive and the only reason I was left alive because
I kind of like casually flirted with the monster.
The monster just noked away.
I guess he didn't like me.
I'm sad.
But I like the monster a lot.
He was really cool.
He had like this skull face thing but not like a human skull.
It was like a like a deer skull or something.
And like these huge claws that he would rip people up and stuff and he was just he looked
really cool.
Your description sounds like that anime.
You know that one it's like it's called like a necromancer bought me or something.
It's like about a literal slave was bought by like this necromancer with a big skull.
I forget.
I have not seen that anime.
You know what I'm talking about.
Okay.
Well whatever.
I think I've heard of something like I heard yeah Twitter talking about something Stockholm
syndrome yada yada but no I haven't seen that anime I should look into that.
Maybe it's a sign.
I did a nightmare as well last night where I was on my computer and some invisible force
some some invisible insidious force moved my hand for me and made me type into my my
Google search bar laying with a bunch of pop up ads and you know I try to download various
like 40 cute clickers click down this ad and now my my my search bar is just filled the
brim with malware and very sorts of spyware I my my hand was trembling moving towards
that I typed in atop the fourth wall and I watched the newest link our video his videos
for Shaz seeking into my fucking soul like like like you like Photoshop color burn his
face color burning my layer completely obliterate all all sense of like pores on my body and
seeking into my into my fucking vessel like that's what link are you know with with a new
age with a new media platform we get a whole new wave of monsters out with the old universal
monsters now we get like the link cars as our poster style yes he has a magic gun where
did he purchase that that is what's the deep lore there we have a real life fucking don't
know but I want to donate to our PayPal to get us to remake all the universal monster
movies but with various that guy with the glasses crew members oh plugging real quick
Kickstarter still happening everybody please give to the fucking Radcon three Kickstarter
we need that money so I forget we can dress up as monsters in real life I if we're close
enough to woods I'll pretend to be the Jersey Devil on film that's a promise that's gonna
be a yeah go ahead back to slender man Ben what what did you think of every man hybrid
compared to marble hornets I didn't watch that much every man hybrid because it wasn't
that good yeah it's so it was it was fucking it was horrible like like a meta bullshit it
was it was fucking like dude home suck is so meta I love accents that's that's that's
a horrible horn that that's what I mean marble I mean marble hornets had some intrigue like
the barn and stuff yeah is Kino I barely remember anything from from every man hybrid at first
I thought that it was like at first I thought that it was kind of funny that it was framed
as they were making a YouTube show yeah some other kind that became a slender man thing
because slender man was there but yeah that didn't carry it for very here here here let
me explain everything hybrid to you so the gimmick of the channel is that it's these
like like three like bros make you like a fitness channel and then like like episode two slender
man is is like just awkwardly put into like the background of videos and then they're like
we were making a slender man ARG but now slender man is real and he's really trying to kill
us yeah oh I forgot about that yeah not not great fucking a fucking pitiful display every
man hybrid fucking you know they probably got like a cp they probably got like yeah they
should they probably got like exposed or something like in some way they like couldn't deny that
they were like doing things related to slender man in some way so they had to like rationalize
it somehow like I would it just seems like such a dumb idea to like admit that you like
we're from the start doing a thing with a slender man yeah like it just seems counter
to your narrative like acknowledges the fakeness of the whole thing oh yeah so like there's
no way I'm gonna take it seriously now in any way and then the fucking rake comes in
because just like that shows like another like creepypasta TM character that we can just
like like steal from another story just put in our fucking thing because we're hacks
speaking of YouTube stuff have you guys heard or seen poppy poppy yes yes poppy is a good
monster on YouTube yes interesting I don't know what her endgame is I guess release albums
and just be a weird oh on the internet um yeah she's cool she's got some poppy I don't think
she's active anymore is poppy like a monster no I mean poppy is a weird creepy semi-robotic
possibly internet creature maybe I don't like I've seen some of her videos and I don't know
what she is but I kind of like the associations will illuminati the devil and the possibility
that she's actually like a clone of herself well well they are been on explainer they're
both the same to me poppy is this fake pop star on YouTube who makes music videos like
you know top 40 like Katy Perry shit but she has sinister undertones in between music videos
which have you know they're just like fucking what I get fucked in my ass you know stuff
like that like put your hooves up I don't know about well okay between those she has I guess
I would call them like vlogs they're not like like hey YouTube they're like her staring
at the camera and kind of yeah there's like a childishly mumbling about things about how
she like she like loves her like Lord and she makes like five or six minutes of her just
saying that she's poppy and like ASMR and stuff yeah yes that's right that's right she's
like weird creepo ASMR in a way but mostly she's just obviously a bizarre freak and in the
best way I like her a lot I I really wonder what the endgame is here I think about that
all the time like what is the point of all these I guess the medium is the message I
suppose just doing these weird videos are just fun for these people I assume I don't know
it's something about fucking Illuminati and fucking you know like celebrities and shit
but fucking I don't know if there's like a message per se I think it's just like art
just like displaying this idea of like you know celebrities being like aliens and shit
like yes it's definitely that yeah it's definitely an artistic piece the character of poppy which
I is really cool I'm watching one called Dracula glam right now it's sick as shit she's just
like gnashing her teeth with these fucking vampire fangs and for no reason well this
spooky ambient music plays and then she's opening a box called nightmares at the end
of the video and she's bashing with a fucking bat incredible incredible I saw that's that's
yeah the stakes are really getting raised on the poppy show um yeah she's a fantastic
monster of the internet I love her let's talk about the greatest villain and monster of
all time binge Dr. Wolf Dr. Wolf works too I feel like they're intertwined binge run
and Dr. Wolf I feel like they're collaborating who has been drowned I don't know this been
do not know been drowned it's a creepypasta Nate you don't know fucking anything about
anything it's the it's the Zelda it's the Zelda guy right yeah I feel like it's the Zelda
fucking Jesus Christ the podcast the not a monster podcast major a mask is so creepy
you guys are gay I'm too old for creepypastas Tom no one's old enough for creepypasta I swear
my dad works at GameStop and got me a fucking copy a cursed copy of Pokemon black like the
original one for Game Boy Color the real one old lavender town guys okay go ahead speaking
of monsters and Nate just mentioned Pokemon our monsters I love Pokemon the only monsters
that I acknowledge is real the Pokemon are real having you play Pokemon go then you discuss
me you know I played Pokemon go before it was cool meaning as soon as it came out and
everyone immediately started playing but the real question is do you continue to play it
now that it is no longer I the real test I'm ashamed to admit no never ever again exposed
get a mile I still play it I haven't been forever did your mother are pretty now there's
all these now there's all these weird new Pokemon of yo what the fuck is that back in my day
Pokemon used to make sense like fucking Charizard it was a dragon that makes sense to me they
was a crow what even is that no you know what is this a bird get out of here there are only
realistic monsters in Pokemon dragons raw raw turtles black people you know the classics
exactly drawing inspiration from the real world Digimon are also cool monsters I love Digimon
fucking suck did you know shit I'm gonna punch you I'm fucking skull graymon I've got like
a thousand skulls attached to my fucking face with a fucking gigantic cannon and I'm like we are
like dragon dinosaur what is that it's the most complicated design I've ever seen in my fucking
there was there was machined Ramon and yeah metal and mecha height mecha dragonmon and puppet
mon and Piedmon and Piedmon was a clown you can't argue with that what the fuck are you
strongest strongest enemy in season one he didn't fuck around what are we discussing are these
politics yes the politics of the digital world love one is best Digimon do we do we impeach
love but he's keeping shit let me make sure I want to Google this what is it apmon it's
it's like a brown bunny with the horn super cute I got it oh he's pretty cute yeah and he
and he has like a dual evolution like he can he like an evil side in the light side and well it's
just it's that it's just like me guys look at this guy though hey incredible do you oh my god
do you guys you guys know how how digimon was founded do you do you know the origin story
you need to you need to you need to look up lady devimon then you'll be converted to we all know
how to start you know the the creative poke bunch sirgi Miyamoto what was touching some bugs but
do you know how digimon was made digimon was was you know you know during the japanese air raids
you know you know you know well will be bombed to shit the creator of digimon uh james digimon
was was was fucking sliding out of his war torn country he was his home roof collapsed upon him
and he was crawling out like inch by inch and he stumbled and staggered a chest ripped completely
open out of his japanese city and wandered into the nearby mounds and inside inside a pit a thousand
trucks long he descended and saw not one but two computers and thought i can make a i can make a game
out of this or or whatever digimon is i don't know that's the origin story it was and then he
heard those hear that ancient american war song hey we're champions and he was like wait
i'm james digimon i can work with this i can make something happen here and the rest was history
um incredible i'm glad we solved this crisis when louis and clark were doing the expedition
of the pacific coast they came across a wandering tribe unlike any any engines they had seen before
they were all playing their tamagotchi tm around their circles screaming various back in those days
you'd have to get a literal chicken to lay an egg that you would carve into a digivice so that's
how you would connect with your fucking digimon uh things have evolved since then obviously but
yeah exactly well that's digimon for you we've solved it uh uh yeah digimon uh superior pokemon
this is the superior franchise well here's proof that's not true because look at the screenshot
nate just put in that's proof the digimon is shit how dare you get a fuck he's wearing a little
he's wearing a little color i'm gonna have to prove all of you wrong but that color is decidedly
unpopped you but it's probable you know he's about to pop it okay he's about to pop it or
i'm not gonna stop his head with one finger no no look he's fucking gray and brown i don't
believe ever he's boring uh but no as bad look look you can think whatever you want about lot
mod but let me let me ask you this like how can you disagree with that that's fucking retarded
that's the that's the worst thing i've ever seen in my life that is the antithesis of quality
lady devimon the best her upper arm reaches her hips yeah exactly well you know that's just how
they roll the digital world they were able to digitally enhance and enhance and enhance the
length of that arm just looks like oh wait a minute wait a minute ben that's actually like
correct look at this other perspective of this fucking character her arm is decidedly weirdly
huge she goes to her fucking ankles um all right well she's christ enough in enough digimon
no no no this character looks like i'm just getting started this character looks like a like a
discorded grim dark sabre spark that's what that like human looks like a human that's clearly the
best thing in the world so you're just you're just proving my point right now well listen guys okay
the digimon are really cool and all but but and and yes digimon were the original monsters but
frankly i'm a little more interested in talking about like the people who are inspired by characters
like lady devimon as the as the monsters of the modern age a lot uh adolf hitler for example i
thought you were going to say women which i was going to say was definitely the worst monsters
should have gone with women i would like to nominate a group of monsters like like like i would
like to nominate a monster as the like number one monster in all categories all fear in fields
here it goes here's my nomination every creature in the ocean every single one of them are fucking
monsters the deeper you go the work the more monstery they are every single creature in the
ocean is despicable nihilistic uh they're pragmatic they're capitalist they're fucking they're all of
the things that you don't want a thing to be and they're all of them and yet still even more they
they're their scale of monster to priest is full monster full monster they're so creepy look look
just google like ocean and you'll see shit you don't want to see there are murkabahs are 100
inverted it's a nightmare down there i don't believe i don't believe in anything below sea level
yeah i don't either they're i've never look at this this is one this is one of the well-known
ones this is one of the ones like people like tankling oh yeah i know what that is look at this
i linked lotus oh look at that oh what the fuck is this okay it's a demon sharks are good boys
shut up that's a demon he looks like a he looks like a medium boy at best to me he's a good boy
oh he will murder you though no he has the chance no but what if he did
sharks can we afford to take that chance not not only are there hideous monsters such as octopi
and starfish in the ocean there's also the lowest rung on the pcp iceberg
oh that pcp fan iceberg yes is that a dolphin or a beluga whale it's the lowest rung mate that's
a beluga but yeah right i was gonna say beluga oh oh i love lilymon i love lilymon too lilymon was
great um i also really like garudamon garudamon was my favorite ultimate and lilymon but that was
not like he's like a native american bird looking dude right yeah uh yeah kind of he actually looks
exactly like blaziken in every way only better god uh yeah he's sick also he's got he's been
designing so much more busy he's literally got like a fucking bandana and like all these weird
mart including some fucking kanji and a weird helmet with like lines on it what the fuck is
god that's too much it's too much i'm being scared by ocean things i'm on google image i'm
being scared by ocean guys no no no wait hold on hold on hold on guys the ocean itself best girl
though who's the quiaman hold on sequoia man dude the ocean itself not even the ocean you you
fucking go to the seafloor and you're crushed by pressures grave the geothermal chemistry of life
human to calm down and look at the kriamon is i'm with bunchy though boiling me it's boiling
the ocean itself is the worst monster of all i was just gonna say just like how uh the skin is
the largest organ on the human body even though that's a lie and i don't believe it for one second
similar the ocean is the largest monster in the world i am the ocean do you know what comes from
the ocean though the king of the monsters himself god zilla the greatest true of all time uh destroys
your cities fucks your bitches and doesn't give a shit the greatest monster okay here's a real
question the ocean or am i wrong he does he lives in like an alternate dimension but comes from the
ocean in the the short story the call of kathulu where they're running away from the island and
kathulu himself rises from the ocean and is undecried but strikes fear into the hearts of all
who witnessed it i have heard of being described as a a like a water elemental guy like a water
kind of i mean it's all made up bullshits with a fanfic monster so he brought us tentacle porn
so therefore not a monster but a god for all of us to worship it's true uh lovecraft and some good
stuff i really love kathulu's appearance in the my love pony fanfiction my love pony the nae of kathulu
i really like that one i don't even know if you're bullshitting because that sounds a hundred
you can read that if the full length of that on uh on on fanfiction on fanfiction.net you can read
that all there yeah i was gonna say that um listen guys this is all good and all but here's a serious
question i want to add this is a serious question can a human be a monster yes in whatever way you
divide it yeah okay are we all just gonna say yes because like what does a monster actually mean
all all it takes is you just gotta put you just gotta put chopsticks in your mouth and stick the
the top of your nostrils yeah if you're a monster there you go you've left your humanity behind
and okay well you've become something greater here's why i'm curious are you trying to get some
intellectual discourse out of this shit show of a podcast right now maybe i would never attempt that
we'll see what happens uh okay so like no person ever thinks that they're a villain right so like in
their own mind they think they're doing like what's best i mean some people are psychopaths so like
they're the exception but like a guy like hitler for example thought he was doing what's best for
like germany probably as is the pcp as is that we'll do whatever it takes he'll do whatever it takes
so like he probably would not call himself even evil you know let alone a monster and of course
most of the world would disagree obviously uh but like i don't know does that does that count this
comes down to your to whether you think there's a subjective or objective view of reality if you
say there's an objective morality and objective standards and of course hitler's a monster and he
was just uh completely off his rocker but if you're a post-modernist kind of guy who's like
everything's subjective like no from hitler's perspective he wasn't so he wasn't and there's
no way of judging it's there's no way of saying what a monster is or isn't because there's no
objective standards anyways well there's no objective standards there are consent there's
consistent standards there's there's consistent whatever that word is however you say that one
i mean there's a lot a lot of people think he's a monster so for all intents and purposes he's
basically objectively a monster yeah i mean i hear what you're saying that's a fair point well
that just means that ever that just means that individual people think that he is i think a lot
of them do though a lot of them most of them in fact well i mean it's all it's all the individual's
opinion right if there are multiple individuals there is no actual like thing that is the
collective will it's not actually a real thing it is just a force kind of in society and you know
that's playing guilty gear where there's the universal will which i'll talk about in my lecture
at rack on three excellent fun the kickstarter fun the kickstarter click the description what do you
mean there's no force like like there's no like like the i mean okay well it's not think something
because it's not like a real thing but a lot of if a lot of people individually think something
and those the people in society then it's not okay here's here's an easy way to think about
things some way here's an easy way to to kind of like refute that it's just like okay so let's
say like literally everyone on earth believes things are a certain way then let's just say that
that whole population of humans just gets like dropped rick and morty style into a like galactic
population and now there's like trillions and trillions of other people who just totally
believe that morality works a different way so now what was the majority opinion is no longer the
majority opinion within like the actual population of like sentient beings it's like in an instant you
can like change how morality works like on a on the you know on the large scale so like it doesn't
actually it doesn't like scale that kind of approach like static it evolves with the society
so i don't know how are you trying to prove that like well i'm trying to prove that there is no
actual thing that is like a collective will it's it's that that is just the sum of the individual
people's will and like those are the things that one should try to change and that's what actually
matters like it's like if one yeah an example like that back in very old medieval days or whatever
uh people from europe when they were fighting people from where do elephants come from africa
or whatever like and they were like oh shit monsters but then you know they gain knowledge
about the topic and it turns out elephants are good boys not monsters that's true the the whole
whether or not to monster thing applies to animals just as well as it does to human beings
hashtag elephants are not monsters everybody stop the stigma and this hate
hashtag giraffes are monsters though have you ever seen a giraffe fight something it's fucking brutal
it does not i've seen every day of my fucking life because i get savaged by action giraffe
despite his emaciated body he still retains 90 percent of his full fighting powers you can't you
can't get rid of that fighting instinct that's right that that's his body material but his spirit
indeed indeed that's why he continues to place well in the pcp royal rumble that's true god i can't
wait for another fucking rumble so we can have action giraffe be back in the ring i can't fucking
wait and watch all my fucking characters get destroyed instantly again as they always do why
what did i fucking do okay well we'll see fucking donate donate to the kickstarter everybody
uh god what else is the rake i felt like the rake what is this rake you mentioned that before
but you didn't describe it dropping i'm so glad you weren't hosting this one because you don't
know fucking anything apparently i don't i don't i'm not i'm actually i'm gonna save my rake discourse
for the creepypasta episode because because evidently that's all i that's all the things i have to
say about monsters is from creepypasta okay okay fair enough oh by the way quick point as to why
objective reality is true uh it is objective uh what was the word morality is true uh to what
someone was saying before it's because there are baseline fundamentals that we can understand
consciousness is real as far as we can tell consciousness is at least real for you and there
are things that are and i know this is gonna sound like some fuzzy language but we can generally
all agree on things that are largely true even if there are some exceptions fuzzy like
things like fuzzy life is generally preferable to death too fuzzy pleasure is generally preferable
to pain generally but we know these things are like that is that is all just a matter of opinion
no one comes down to the individual to decide what is preferable okay but but if things apply to
like 99.9 percent of the population is it really correct then it applies that's what i was just
saying throw it out the window that's what i was just saying there's nothing outside of the person's
preferences that is made real by those preferences okay but it's okay well for example newtonian
physics is not 100 percent it does not fully map out reality but we still use it practically
to determine all kinds of stuff about the real world so it's super useful so in the same way
more our moral systems are maps to optimize the way we want society well newtonian physics isn't
real i well yeah i mean that that is true it is it is just a way of understanding shit no
that is not completely accurate guys that's that's not fucking even real because physics is mapping
out a thing that exists in the world and like morality is mapping out what people think about
consciousness then it's all preference it's it's opinion all the way down question like
would you prefer to get punched in the face or get it or get a free milkshake um milkshake but
that's just that's all the boys i might if i was if i was feeling really bad about myself i might
want to get punched in the face okay what if a bunch of bullies were coming to beat you up good
what if a bunch of bullies were coming to literally beat you up real real bad and your friend said like
oh here's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna punch you in the face so that you look like you've already
been beat up and they won't beat you up even worse and in that case getting punched in the face might
be a better idea than getting a milk you're changing the you're changing the situation yeah well what
is the situation we didn't get punched in the face so you get an offer get punched in the face or get
a free milkshake okay but the whole this doesn't actually prove anything this is just showing what
we personally want the real monsters are people who wax philosophically for no reason on podcast
you're all about i hate you you're fucking general preference implies some kind of greater truth
stupid uh there there is too large your truth you guys you just we just it was gonna be a podcast
where we have fun talking about monsters and now you're just i'm having a great time
here's the real monster the philosophical insights of who's a monster and who's not but that's
essential uh you can't describe something unless you know what it is you know what you know what
What's a monster?
Monsters are like porn, you know what you see them, god damn it!
Let's talk about enemy. It's the truest monster.
Why?
Because...
Tell me why.
Cause...
Thanks for everything.
Campaign,
campaign,
through the camera but like the camera extends it so it's like this long like
tube thing. I think they're actually called rods. I think they're like called
rods. Yeah. They were in a JoJo chapter. I think rods might be my favorite. Crypto
cryptocurrency. Well I know that rods trade exclusively in Bitcoin.
Yes. Which is why I'm trying to collect them so that I can enter their economy.
Bitcoin taking a beating right now under under 8,000.
Munch, can you like post a rod? I have no idea what you guys are talking about.
Just read JoJo part six. There's a part where I don't actually know.
I'll post a picture of rods. In case any of you needed convincing, this is proof
that the Mothman is in fact real and he's not like a fantasy thing. He's real.
Here's proof. Okay. There he is. I'm convinced. The Mothman is real everybody.
Oh no. I see no reason to doubt this whatsoever. This is less floofy. This
doesn't look like a Moth. This looks like a bat.
The bat man is real. I'd like to nominate this as the best monster of all time.
This looks like the one. You got this shit. Oh no. You found that right now because you
were searching for rod monster didn't you? That's exactly because I found the
same one. Oh hell yeah. Okay. I really touched about enemy earlier and I just
wanted to say there's had a lot of like like monster grills and I want more
monster boys please. That would be nice. Yeah okay. Okay. I just wanted to make
that statement also. You will never know the pleasure that I feel whenever I go
to Egypt and I plunder tombs sanctioned off by the government for being too
culturally significant. I plunder them anyway outside the the prying eyes of
the government. I plunder those tombs. I raid those caverns and I party down
with the mummies the various mummies that line the underground layers of
Egypt. I do that every single day and that's why mummies are the number one
monster because they are party animals. They want to get down just like I
want to do. They want to get down. They want to put their hooves up and they
love they love drinking booze and love fucking sluts just like I do. That's
that's nice but fuck the mummies. The coolest monsters were these. The only one
ever to play with these back in the day. That was the coolest shit of all time.
They were like they were like monster trucks that turned into actual monsters.
It was the coolest shit ever. Okay that is awesome but something looks vaguely
familiar. I think I might have seen commercials for them. Dude they were so
vaguely terrifying. They were like cars that like transformed into like monsters.
They have like giant mouths and they eat eight shit. It was it was fucking. Does it
like exude slime or something? Because I'm seeing some slime. Some of them some of
them do. That one did I believe. Oh my god this is up my alley. This is up my alley.
Into the fucking podcast because this is going to be a nightmare because no one
can see what the fuck we're talking about. We're giving this one a give. He's gonna
end all of these for being late. I'll put all these in the show notes. Click on the
link in the description you can see all of these. Okay fantastic. Okay here's a
thing we're doing this real quick. We're gonna go through all the universal
monsters and give them a score out of ten. All right here we go. Starting number
one Frankenstein zero. What Frankenstein's monster four. Frankenstein's monster yes.
Oh we're talking about the monster than a ten out of ten. The monster's a good
boy. I like him. He's a flesh golem. He's sick. I don't know. He's fine. He's a
little bland. I never read the book. I only played the video game. The most
interesting thing about Frankenstein's monster is Frankenstein himself who would
just bring a guy alive for some reason. But okay. Actually Frankenstein was the
real monster. If I remember the lore correctly he was. No no it was the mob
that was the real monster. No Frankenstein was a dick. No our real monsters was the
real monster. Okay good. He's zero out of ten. Count Dracula. Count Dracula. Seven.
He's got a funny accent. I like the fact he's a foreigner so I can make fun of him
without any moral justification. Dracula is honestly more boring than Frankenstein.
No Dracula's great. He has fucking teeth that he makes you go bye bye with. Dracula has to
be the best monster because he's a real person. He's not some fucking joke. He's real.
Nosferatu's are sick. I would give a Nosferatu like an eight out of the gate but this is
Count fucking Dracula. He's a bitch. Whatever. He's gay. The Wolfman. Oh that one is like
the worst one of all. He's fucking zero. Zero. He's a furry. He's a furry. I give him
one point out of ten for being ten percent real. That sounds good. He's a little bit
real but not enough to make the cut. I have never liked the Wolfman. I'm giving him like
a two. What is cool about him? He is a wolf. He's a fur sona. He is a wolf. Okay but you
know that guy is like in there was that one kid who's like in every way other than physical.
I am a wolf. Barks. This guy is actually a little bit along that. He is slightly physically
a wolf as well. So in that way I give him bonus points. And he goes aloo. He does. I like
him. Okay. What else? For some reason also in this line is Van Helsing is here for some
reason. Oh I love the anime. That was a sick anime. I'm going to give him like a I don't
know he's pretty cool. I get to five just for because Helsing the anime exists because
of that. Yeah. Yeah. Wait what is the real Van Helsing? Is he a real person? He's just
a dude who went around killing monsters. That's what he did. So he's a monster hunter not
a monster. He's like blood born but less cool. But he kills the beasts. He's seven. He's
at least a seven. I like him. I'll give him some points because all the universal monsters
suck so he's getting rid of them. So. Okay. Listen to this. For some reason the next one
on this list is Henry Frankenstein. Oh that must be the guy. That's the guy who made Frankenstein.
Yeah I told you he's a monster. He's terrible. But what the fuck. I click on the link and
now it's Victor Frankenstein. That's the whole point of the book is that he's the real monster
and the monster is more human. But why does he say Henry here and Victor on the other
page. I don't understand. Okay this must be out of date. Okay Victor Frankenstein. Fuck
it. The guy who made it. Now that guy's cool. He gets an eight. Is he such a bad guy. He
just wanted to do science. No no he's terrible. He just wanted to be God. How bad can he be.
He didn't do nothing. I will not approve the slanderization of Victor Frankenstein. He's
a wonderful camera operator. He went to college for the shit. He knows what he's fucking doing.
He can make better quality videos than we ever fucking could. He's gonna have his slanderization
Victor Frankenstein. I hate it. That's a very rude thing and I hope Mage when he is our
cameraman at RideCon3 you'll be a little nicer about what he's doing for us. Not that Victor.
It's too late. We understand what you meant. Next vote up. The invisible man. The invisible
man. I like that one. I'm gonna give him an eight. I really like him. I like the fact
that he's like kind of a mummy but like he's also invisible. There's like two things there.
I saw the movie. I'm gonna give him like four. He fucking sucks dick. Oh but really you suck dick.
Have you ever thought that what you say about people actually reflects upon you as a person?
He's only gay so he can sneak into men's locker rooms and literally suck dick. That's his whole end
game and so I give him like an eight out of ten. He does deserve points for that. Exactly. I respect
his gumption. I was gonna argue with you Nick but I googled the invisible man and I can't deny
what he's wearing and his bi-language indicates that he is in fact the most homosexual person
I've ever seen in my life. There's nothing to argue against. He just clearly is the gayest fucking guy
ever. That's correct. That's correct. Hold on. Look at this fucking photo of the
the original faggot. Oh man. He's looking fab. He's looking fab. Oh that's spectacular. I kind of
like it actually. He looks cool. He looks fucking dope. I was that cool. He's fucking dope as hell.
He sucks so much dick I can't help but respect him. Same. Same. Okay next on the list for some
reason is Elizabeth which is Victor Frankenstein's fiance. Does anyone know anything about this
character? Ten because it's a woman. The scariest monster. Yeah. Tips. Oh there you go. She's a name.
There you go. She has a name. You know what skip. I don't give a shit about her. Okay last on the
list of actual people is Igor. Igor the freakish. Igor's good. Hunchbacked. Ten out of ten. He was
just a real boy trying to make a living. That's right. You see the thing that's great about Igor
is that he looks like a monster on the outside because he's so weird and goofy and silly and
hilarious but on the inside he's just the greatest person, nicest boy who ever lived. Fucking
thumbs up if you've seen the greatest movie of all time Igor 2008. If not but it looks fucking
incredible. It's fucking dope. Igor 2008 is my fucking jam. Igor is played by John Kuzak.
It's the universal constant. It's fun and clever. Exactly. Wow. Wow. I'm just not pronounced Igor
and was sponsored by Apple to promote their new line of iPods that were coming out at the time.
The new deep web service Igor. Yes. Oh no. This may fucking 30 million point seven dollars at the
box office. He's powers before Igor. What the fuck. Powers before him. Cryptocurrency tanked when
this movie came out because real monster currency soared after Igor dropped and everyone. Igor
feel this right now. We want you on the podcast of all time killed cryptocurrency the US dollar
the scariest monster to ever live. That's true. That's true. Look how fucking look how fucking
co co co kawaii Igor is in this fucking movie. Hold on. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Those kawaii fucking
adorable. I love it. He's like an aunt. He looks like something from a bug's life. I feel
probably dream works animate or something fucking Igor. If you listen to the podcast we want you
on dude. We want you on this shit. We need we need you. We need you're wrong. We got one last
prowess. We got one last person here and it is mummy the mummy. What do we think of the
10 out of 10. He's my favorite 10 but I honestly I think that the invisible man wears the bandage
is better and like so mummies mummies don't have organs and somehow still are able to function
which means yeah what the fuck. It doesn't look real. I was that was a fucking slut.
Also I was going to say the fucking mummy the movie with Brendan Frazier was fucking sick because
that guy like fuck bitches and he like summoned like if we if we just guys if we have money on
this list why don't we have zombies on this list because well it's not a universal monster.
Yeah that's true. There are new things but zombies are fair. Zombies are fucking cool.
Before I'll just be that guy. I don't get I don't get the appeal of the mummy. I feel like the
appeal of the mummy is just the appeal of like ancient Egyptian stuff but like when I think of
a mummy there's nothing particularly Egyptian about it except it's just a zombie. It's just a
fucking did it. Yeah it's it's aesthetic which is not which is not true in reality but but in
but in movie land is the only place that actually matters and then listen listen the real okay there
is a there is a secret monster that came out in in the wake of the mummy and it is the realest
most terrifying monster that's ever existed so everyone's familiar with the saga of Brendan Frazier
I'm sure who has fallen from grace in the most tragic way possible and at the height of his
popularity he got a divorce and now he has to pay these like $500,000 alimony payments to his wife
and he is not getting into rules because no one wants to hire him because he got too tight cast
and exploded he burned out too too hotly and too quickly at the height of his career and he's
starting to get a little bit of shit now but like he's totally fucking dead and the real monster
here is alimony. Yeah alimony is the ultimate monster it ruins great men who could have otherwise
made something of themselves it is a beast like Brendan Frazier everyone's favorite alimony is just a
weapon the ultimate monster women yeah you know you're not wrong you're not wrong kill them all
that's that's my stance remember kids if you're gonna get married get a pc prenup get a pc
our patreon and we will personally give you a verified a twitter verified um every hundred
dollar patron gets a free pc prenup you know if you have a twitter checkmark you're you cannot be
the victim listen listen gentlemen gentlemen you don't want to get caught with your pants down
any second one of these suck you by could come into your life and sweep you into an illicit marriage
that is why right now which is before you find yourself awesome monster okay but that's true
succubus are great as i think you buy but that's gay uh but uh before you get yourself in that
situation young men you want to be donating a hundred dollars monthly to the pcp so that you have
that pc prenup ready to go at any moment when you need to fucking drop that hoe just trying to drain
you of all that cash you need to do this gentlemen we're trying to protect you from yourself remember
give us all your money before a woman can steal it from you if you don't have any money left then
she can't take it can she just just consider the pcp your personal bank that you cannot get any money
out of just you don't have any money left after the alimony how are you gonna pay the pcp yeah
yeah we exactly you're wield your pc prenup against women like a cross against the undead
wear it around wear it around your neck get a screen cap like a rosary print out the confirmation
of your hundred dollar pledge the pcp and wear it as a badge of honor wear it like a sheriff's
badge cut it into a little star a jewish star in Auschwitz camp and wear it the way they did
to protect themselves from you know the bad things uh-oh a bride is walking down the aisle then
the husband changes the music to the procrastinators theme for the last moment yeah that's in that
he got a prenup behind her back oh destroyed destroyed um we did it we tackled the ultimate
monster thank god i think we're done just one more thing no one more thing one more thing
okay okay go ahead mage like and another cool monsters are like the og angel designs because
oh my favorite how could i have forgotten yeah they're so cool they're even realer than real
they're they're they're they're beyond the scale they're post real yeah they're more real than
things that actually exist i think this is like just in a plane beyond beyond comprehension
they have a million heads and a billion eyes oh yeah the ring within rings within rings with
billion eyes on them that's like yeah and they're all like flaming and shit you know i was i was
skeptical but but i googled original angels and you know what you're right these are the scariest
things i've ever seen in my life i'm trembling like right now listen listen guys disgusting the popular
versions of of angels that people are familiar today that are just like pretty people with wings
that were like made famous during like you know the the i don't even know like greek in times here
when people are making you know whatever the fucking popes were painting them and shit the
fucking vistas sistine chapel and all that that's not the real shit in the bible we were talking
about angels from evan galleon because we're that fucking weebs oh those are pretty sick too i like
those i like the design my favorite is the uh what it's an octahedron the octahedron i forget
which name it's ramblethal or something whatever one it is that's the best character from guilty
gear also i think that might be the same name i gotta google that uh but yeah she's a sick monster
too she's got she's got that brown skin like a monster and just she's she's a perfect tan goddess
with white hair with big old shark teeth that will literally bite your dick off it's awesome i can't
find any images of of original angels i don't know what we're looking at oh oh um here i'll show you
i'll show you wait what what i i tried i tried searching for ophanim and it automatically
completed to ophanim on the digimon form digimon better than pokemon oh by the way the octahedron
in evan galleon is called rambiel rambiel i was mistaken uh there's just too many there's just too
many fucking good ones just google it people just google it it's incredible i tried it wouldn't
work i'm not using this the tried the tried and true chank youger argument of just google it all
right well here's here's one pretty good one uh dupe dupe dupe this this is my favorite whoa yeah
i was gonna i was gonna look that up one yeah that's my favorite as well because and the thing is
these these things are in addition to being awesome they are like the wheels of god's chariot
like is this like straight up biblical yeah please describe this for our list call please
describe it i think um but the okay the thing about it the thing about it like the reason why
angels are always depicted as like people with wings is because like in the bible angels appear
in the form of people right right isn't jacob that like wrestles an angel or something i don't know
someone wrestles an angel and and that angel is a guy but like that's not what he really looks like
he's appearing as a human but like in in the bible they appear they generally appear as humans but
that's not what they really look like uh this is what they really look like and they're fucking here
i'll find another one i'll find a seraphim and just describe this like at least cherub's cherub's
i think used to have like you know how cherub's are depicted as like little babies or not but
that that's not how they used to be i think they had three heads one human one lion one
bull or something yeah yeah they were like um they were like why do we make the bible so uncool
manticore i don't know man they were like it's because they baby did up i don't know this fucking
been advertising christianity in the bible has really made me thirsty to hunker down with the
with the good book one of these days he's thinking it sounds so so fucking you know advertise it's
if you know the boring parts it is yeah i've been wanting to take that the quest i've really owed
it to myself to actually read the thing oh is this like the thousand wings or whatever that's the
seraphim i love seraphim oh my god wait let me find the metatron my favorite guys guys you gotta
describe these because the people listening did not know what the fuck you're they're in the show
notes click on the fucking description look nobody wants to have to do they want to hear that
look it's a bunch of wings arranged around a central eye like that's all you have to say
they don't know what we're talking about they can't match images to what we're fucking speaking of
god well you just described it now google seraphim and find an image that matches your description
that is the worst idea i've ever heard in my life this is like furry porn i know
i know this is this one does look like someone on dvn art made it probably did it looks too
modern to be like this one that's a little too fan-ficking yeah yeah okay yeah i'm sorry there's
there's not like a lot of the pictures of the metatron are kind of stupid and like new agey
looking and i hate them so i'm gonna just like go to god and be like can you send us some photos
yeah yeah can we can you link us to your uh can you link us to your instagram
yeah fucking when when when madpat gave a copy of undertale to the pope you should have said
dude can you please do me a favor just get some some snapchats from the angels up in heaven please
ask them i could really use those that would have been sick that would have been sick oh well
instead they played undertale that's seeing in my confessions no answer me
exactly okay we're that's it we're done thank you angels uh i worship you forever good wait we
didn't we didn't talk about the most dangerous monster of all our fathers no i was that's you
know you're not wrong they bear such power we're already such power yeah i can't believe it i feel
like we said nothing wait we said this was the worst topic what are you talking about viewers i
want to let you all know that i thought tooth and nail for this topic to not happen so you
don't have me to blame i'm absolved of all guilt in what you have just listened to today this is
the greatest podcast yeah they're gonna be this is the best this is the best episode we've ever
done yeah look like an idiot now you got you got it you gotta hold lines like that until after
the hot take from the audience comes in so you can play both sides to your right you know he's
right about that uh but on fathers they are the most powerful creatures in our lives for sure
and they have the most ability to destroy us at their work they represent our most primal fears
indeed indeed you know what they say and the vagina of the mother the foremost powerful
feels are our fires thunders tornadoes and fathers and or something like that they're a
walking natural disaster uh okay that's it enough enough it's time to transition everybody
oh sweet poor fags head on over and check the hashtag ask pcp on the twitter jesus christ
do you guys are really dropping the ball if you if you're asking us a question on twitter and not
in our premium procrastinators patreon discord
that's how literally give a fuck about sure we're not even gonna finish this statement we
indeed but we do love the people in our patreon discord uh who we ask questions to we've got a
you know separate thing just for questions there that we will refer to uh but let me get the pity
question here from the the twitter real quick this is from at a mundane critic and the question is
the more of a request it is define meme define meme is it just meme is a joke that isn't funny
right that's your definition it's a viral joke that isn't funny i i i've led i've led this crusade
on arm retrieval the the the bible the bible retold for the for the modern era where we need to
make a distinction when we think things are funny refer to them as jokes and we think things
aren't funny refer to them as memes that that that's my that's my official doctrine and i
train from that whenever i can if there's one thing to discuss to me about the word meme it's
when it's used to mean like a still image of some quote unquote funny thing happening with text on
the top and bottom yeah that is a meme now that i hate that but like that's kind of what it
me people mean when they say it now like i don't i don't think i don't i think that i think we've
lost that battle yeah you're right yeah it's a shame i do it's not we've lost that that's what a
question from the discord chat western dragons versus who's it from ends western dragons
versus eastern dragons which are better i say western dragons eastern dragons western dragons
are fucking awful and i hate them so so so much they're cool lizards with with giant wings and the
brief fire and eastern dragons are just long noodles if i see western dragons for the win
if i see a single other castle night brown earth or dragon i will fucking buy off the handle
western fantasy it are the dregs of all fictional settings western fantasy is the opposite of
creativity and the graveyard for all potentially good ideas listen i when i was young i definitely
felt burned i read a lot of fantasy novels as a kid i definitely got burned out on like western
fantasy it's specifically like western dragons but then i got more into d&d which now i don't
really like so much but the point is i read the monsters manual and i read like all the books
and the like i would say that on average eastern dragons are just like they're cooler by default
but when you've got a really like majestic and like dignified looking like sick ass ancient
worm elder like gold or red or white dragon or something and they're just like so fucking wise
and so woke to the world they are so aesthetic and sick and i love them i think that they're awesome
dragons look disgusting they're fucking all no no dragon can look good you need to read the
monsters fucking manual you didn't need to read the draco nama con dude exactly i'll
look at this if you think this looks fucking good then you then you have brain damage look this one
looks a little goofy but the ones in the monsters manual shit looks sick like look at how this guy
looks a little silly look at his silly like smile and his like goofy face and shit and his head a
little too big and his body looks too small this looks like a young adult dragon but an ancient
worm oh they're so cool what's a good looking dragon then munch what what kind of dumb noodley
yeah do you think is sick yeah i think that i have this after one fucking shout out to the museum of
fine arts in boss and hosting the the the red dragon painting that is fucking huge and it will
and it like takes like two cars to fucking have it open hold on here let me get this munchie loves
japan period i do i literally do i don't i don't trust weaboos all right i gotta you gotta show me
the receipts on this shit let me get this shit fucking here here here fucking look at this
you fucking pieces of shit look at this the fucking red dragon it's huge um okay i mean that looks sick
look how big that shit is our face looks nice but not the dragon the dragon that those noodle
dragons will never look cool to me they're fucking real long you can just whack them you can just
you can just chop them off that literally looks may just looks exactly the same as one munchie just
sling like the facial proportions are identical um this and what may just link looks dope as hell
it looks great that's not even an argument it looks good no that looks gay as fuck no it looks
fucking cool i would like this one just the only the only time in east dragon it's kind of cool
was shenron from dragon ball and that's because i was a little kid and shenron does look cool
other than that he's not cool look at this fucking dragon bleeding look at this dragon
bleeding can western dragon oh he looks concerned no western dragons don't leave because they're
fucking gods look at his big goofy anime eyes exactly what the fuck is the worst the worst okay
no it's fucking it's a snake okay uh enough can we please move on to the next question
hold on uh who wants to who's got one from the thing i'm gonna i'm gonna oh oh oh oh here here's
like a quick one that i want to uh mention uh from the patreon lounge bozhen weeaboo are you
going to smoke weed radcon if i if i even see a single marijuana flower at red i know that the
entire building will be decimated and disintegrated before my vast power if i see a single as as the
children call it blunt i will fly off the handle well did you all right take notes i guess we've
been warned listen okay listen to this incredible question from at leo j larkin from the twitter
another pity question if you could feed a length to anyone living or dead real or fictional who
would it be feed feed a what feed a length like a length of something unspecified so you get to
come up with the the length of whatever you want to feed to whoever you want to feed it to like a
length of wire like a length of rope like a length of fruit rollups perhaps a length of sausage you
know the fruit rollups to myself i was gonna do something similar yeah like like everybody else
um no i'd like to feed like a length of sausages to like you know like like shenron for example
like he looks like he'd really appreciate like a long noodley sausage link chain you know that's like
that's like cannibalism that'd be cool he is a long fucking sausage or or length of like offended
by that a single very long noodle to like an asian man and watch him just like slurp it up over
like generations as he goes like from um yeah it'd be sick it'd be fucking sick uh okay that's it i
would like to feed the length of of a video game cartridge of donkey kong country 2 to my nintendo
we for it to play that's good you know i'd like to feed the length of this podcast to the dustbin
of history to feed a length of a hundred dollar bills to my wallet that's that's good that's good
okay let's do like one or two more questions from the lab let me go see what we got marron pan marron
pan marron pan yeah one pocket monster type is each pcp man's member type huh that's a nuanced
question i know my you're all pure fairy and i am steel no that's no i'm i'm dark fairy me okay
that sounds right that sounds right ghost ice hmm uh i'm steel bug so i don't know this is my
favorite i'm just saying my favorite one i'm i'm i'm i'm normal i'm just normal yeah you look like
normal normal like a burger uh what about you can have a team tom's definitely dark
anarcho capitalist i graduated from communism thank god had long last long last well finally
the ancap master i'm gonna keep i'm gonna keep going i think like digi would be like psychic
something psychic dark maybe uh um psychic ground ground you think okay yeah he's playing
type he's smoking all the weed oh actually oh of course could be psychic grass he'd be grass fire
because of that dank he's always blazing i think maybe i'm just biased because of his color palette
but i want to give duvou pure flying pure flying i like that i like that it's intellectual height
there's nothing i hate more than like normal flying types when they could just be flying
and like just please just do that everyone uh there's only one there's a um not thunderous not
that tornado tornadoes is the only pure flying oh that's right the balloon is ghost flying and
i let me say i want to do a gib as well what is gib gib is gib is gib is silly gib's rod type because
he loves castles so much he could be i think gib is i think gib is normal high he's hybrid normal
type what is that like two normals is normally he's normal and something else but i don't know
what the something else he's normal and rock maybe electric electric because he plays sick riffs on
his guitar dude i can't see him i was i was thinking grass but that's only because of the
color palette that he likes using with the yeah i was sort of thinking grass for him as well i don't
know his hair is like a bush
yeah like that chest guy in one piece
yeah that's good i don't know and what about and i feel like and maybe jesse would be something
like i don't know the tango is normal jesse is a fighting type oh he's definitely fighting type
uh he's got to be like fighting oh shit i don't know fighting normal i don't know he's fire and
fighting fire and fighting yeah why the fuck not that one there's too many of those you're right
that is too many fuck that let's pick up a better one of those jesse doesn't have to be a star and
there's too many bug there's too many bug steel too for that matter is it oh well okay i don't know
i think jen wanted to yeah i don't actually know what i'd actually be more like no buddy jesse's
fighting and fairy type of those like this is what we are what we need to get to yeah you know you're
right you're right i kind of think fighting fairy works for jesse i because he's like i think it
works he's kind of a softy on the inside you know he's tough on the outside you know i look i like
fighting fairy type for jesse i like that i like that a lot cool and uh whatever i'm sick of bug
steel no that's everybody that's everybody i think um all right we did it well that's congratulations
now now you all know this is this is canon put this on the wiki yeah indeed i expect it updated
within five minutes of this being uploaded some yeah i think i think the final project we want to
answer probably uh happy d from the patreon lounge thoughts on monster any or energy drinks um oh
disgusting excellent monster like diesel i used to be a huge fan believe it or not back in the
college days but i graduated to red bull and rock star and haven't looked back the no sugar kind of
the monster ultra series is my favorite of all hey in case you guys haven't seen ben here is
quite the connoisseur of monster energy drinks having just made an art piece using the cans right
that was monster right um the big old yeah i made volpix for jackie out of like 50 fucking monster
cans meticulously cut monster cans into one yeah it is into one inch pieces of metal and then like
linked together with a hole punch and tiny metal key rings how did you keep that a secret
how did you keep that a secret that's what i'm wondering well see because like i started working
on it a long time ago like i started working on it like almost a year ago okay but it kind of like
it kind of like lost momentum but then our anniversary came up and i was like this i think
this is the time to finish it yeah okay so i did i pushed through because like i already i mean i'd
already put i'd already put all that work in like i had to do it was like now's the time if i'm ever
gonna baggy and like pop artness at the same time i love it i love it made of fucking monster
cans it's oh that's great it's it's it's really it's something that uh i don't know i mean i'd
i'd want it in my house you probably have to like map out like pixel by pixel like i absolutely did
i have like i have like files um yeah i had to like i had to like divide the original sprite
into its pixels find out how many of each color i needed how and then like estimate how many cans
that was going to be uh separate them all and then like i took the thing and i split it into
its vertical sections and then i would link together one vertical section at a time um and
then i would connect them by the top and then i i yeah um it was it was labor and and energy
intensive it sure looks like it well okay you know there's one last question we have to answer
from AJ Shoup here that's just thoughts on monster cheese with a little o w o face
hey i love cheese i am i'm i'm not a white person because i don't really like cheese that much
i love cheese but it is the forbidden snack i cannot do it i like it but i don't like it
that much and i'm totally willing and i'm totally willing to forego it like i often get food with
no cheese on it because it's like well cheese has a lot of extra calories in it and i don't like
cheese that much so i'm willing to lose the cheese because i don't care about the cheese
well sure i mean you get like bakery pizza or something you know that's no cheese the bakery
pizza is like a different thing or you get greek pizza whatever i love all right i love i
shout out to monoray jack the best cheese and the cheese they use chipotle oh we ate a lot of
monoray jack as youngsters i was yeah it was my favorite it was my favorite cheese the best cheese
i have learned as a connoisseur i do love cheese they have like cheese little things at whole foods
all the time you can just like grab and eat with like crackers and shit uh uh fucking extra extra
extra sharp cheddar the sharper the better i want my tongue to fucking bleed and slice and dice on
the sharpness of that fucking cheddar god i love it it is so succulent it's the best but i don't
but i've never had monster or if i have i don't remember what it was like i mean monster is kind
of weird and it's not very good first time i'm hearing about it honestly for shame it's it's it's
it's white that's a problem yeah already yeah not starting off on a different we need some diversity
in our cheese okay enough that's it all right thank you everybody i think we're good here uh thanks
for listening people god let me out remember remember um we've the kickstarter still going on
to fund radcon that's right we'll have this video see for a week straight let me have at least
there's like two weeks left i think at this point so everybody please get the guy there's about like
a week and a half at this point guys seriously remember fucking radcon three make it happen
first of all just for the content you will make fucking lectures from most of us we have lectures
already planned and ready to go uh tom guilty gear lure me i'm telling you right now i don't know if
i said it it'll be it's a final fantasy lecture everybody it's gotta be goofy it's gonna be crazy
i don't know if i've said this but i'm do i'm gonna do a lecture on the on the lore of tales gets
trolled incredible in incredible this is the best that's straight up the best content out of radcon
everybody knows it it's gonna be the potato's fucking shit uh i also be in a lecture i'll be
in a lecture on on on spirituality could you do please do a lecture on um uh on catcher in the
ride because i'm not smart enough to like understand like what's going on in that story it all starts
with the great gatsby that's what i meant the great gatsby correction where i get started yeah we gotta
start with 101 you can't start with like 301 with catcher in the ride you know basic shit first this
is okay this is how you get smart is you read the classics like you know to kill a mocking jay and stuff
like that uh okay so everyone please give to the kickstarter support radcon three we really want to
happen be be lovely and beyond that if you just don't give a shit and you just want to support us
in general uh and get access to the bonus episodes uh there is a new one out now that has came out
like a week ago or so uh fucking gamer gate versus the 2016 presidential united states election like
holy shit it was honestly there's just really only one word for it transcendent kino fucking kino
it's incredible it was the best episode of the bonus episodes so fucking far without question god it
was incredible uh everyone go listen it's as good as it sounds i was i was honored to have been a part
of it yes same that is for five dollar patrons indeed five dollar patrons get access to all that
shit uh and that's it please give us your money we also got some shirts you want to click the red
bubble link go buy them they're on red bubble they're cool pcb logos and whatnot buy some mugs
etc etc and uh go listen to the podcast if you care to on itunes and google play our friend tom
here takes care of that shit and uh that's it that's it everybody thanks for listening
and we'll see you again next week with some more shit uh give money to the kickstarter
i love you time to goodbye goodbye
right now
myself i'm
i am an asshole i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it