Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever and I don't know what channel this video is going up on. We've got Ben
Saint over there. Yeah, we're still in this pickle here and this hacker pickle if you
know what I'm saying. And this ripple pickle. This ripple pickle. Gibbontake, Tom Oliver,
Yeah, I'm here and I'm sad. The usual reasons or anything? I'm sad about the hack. I'm talking
about the hack. I mean, I'm sad about everything. There's a coronavirus in Massachusetts. We're
all going to die, doom and gloom, blah, blah, blah, whatever. It's going to happen eventually.
There's Munchy. I don't know if I have all the paperwork to be on this show. I mean,
I went to the DMV and I got a stamp. I don't know if it's the right stamp. I tried to talk
to the committee, but they wouldn't talk to me this ago. We wouldn't talk to mudbloods
like yourself. And I went down to the other DMV that one that doesn't have a hearsay officer
and they don't have the hearing officer. And I went over there and I said, Hey, can I have
the paperwork to be on the podcast? And they said, you're already recording the podcast
right now. And then they put me in handcuffs. And here I am. What do they have you guys
for? Like, how'd you get in here? Like, what's the problem with you?
They said, you're a part of the PCP die. And there I was. Hey, you're part of that cryptocurrency
like scam, like a live stream, right? Yeah, that's me. We have lost 1000 subscribers
from the PCP channel. Thanks. How many subscribers are you down? I dare. I dare not ask, but
I ask anyway. Great question, Tom. But on the best gaver channel now rebranding permanently
as Brad Garlinghouse, they have hidden the subscriber count. So I have no, I can guarantee
you. Well, I mean, yeah, I haven't actually checked social blade, but I know social blade.
I mean, don't they not have access to like, you know, I don't know who knows. It's a mystery
to us all. Yeah, I don't know. I could check still going on. It's still like currently
happening. Yeah, obviously, he's still streaming every day. Are you not aware of this?
I haven't checked anything. Why don't we just all just spam YouTube like over and over and
over again? That I mean, well, at this point, I think, you know, it's been long enough that
I feel like they're not doing anything. It's been since about the 22nd or the 23rd is when
I noticed it. And I might have contact them as late as like the 24th or 25th overall. But
it's been, you know, about a solid week over a week. I think it's time to enforce mob rule.
We need to just hashtag Twitter, destroy YouTube. You know, I'll tell you, everyone's
everyone says that YouTube only really responds to people like humiliating them on social
media. That's the only way I sexually respond to anyone. Someone humiliates me in public.
Yeah, humiliation. I've been talking to a couple people who have had these issues or
people who follow them. And I have been informed that like just for example, I was telling you
guys before, but I'll tell the audience here that like, for your interest, there was a
guy with like a small following, maybe like a couple thousand or something who took eight
weeks to get restored, clearly because he's just, you know, not high on their priority
list. And then someone like Pogo with like many hundreds of thousands of subs apparently
took like a few days to like a week or something along these lines. And like, I don't even
know if they specifically, there was like a campaign with Pogo, but I think they just
were like, okay, this guy we should do something with because he matters. So like, I go, what
do you do? Music man, it doesn't matter. Are you high? I wish I was. I wish I was real. I
don't believe that. So I at this point, I'm, I don't like to do these things, but I'm left
with no alternative, but to think that like it's just about the pressure that's being
put on these people. And like the tickets exist. Like Google is apparently doing the things
they're passing them on to the internal team, whatever that means, but apparently the internal
team is not like actively fixing the problem yet. They're like in queue probably.
I really feel like it would only be a matter of a few button presses for them.
I feel strongly that that is the case as well. But like, so I have no alternative, but to
think that like, yeah, I mean, what exactly is the harm of getting everybody who listens
to this to spam at team YouTube with full authority, be polite, be respectful, but let
them know what the issue is. Cause this is what they're for, right? What's the harm in
doing so I, you know, go for it. I say, in fact, I call upon you that like at them on
Twitter, team YouTube. Okay. So our current society is, is thus the following. Um, like
basically just like huge like tech bros from San Francisco and like San Jose can basically
just like, you know, completely ruin society with a click of a button with, with half an
a press they're released as a society. They create robots and algorithms to run their sites
for them so they can maximize suffering and minimize the amount of money they have to
pay people to oversee things. And then when it doesn't work, the only way to get it to
like, you know, the site to actually, you know, function in any way is to constantly
bombard them with bad PR. And that's the only way to do it. And they have just created
robots and do nothing for us. That really does seem to relatively accurately reflect
the current situation. I just think it's ridiculous that like YouTube has all these people on
their site, like making a living through their platform, but their pay is so bad that people
have to go to outside sources in order to make any money. And it is that part of the
equation that is actually lucrative for hackers to try and steal your shit, not through YouTube
itself, but through sponsorships, because that's the only way you can make money effectively
on YouTube now because of their draconian policies. It's just like multiple levels of
failure, which I find hilarious.
Bro, bro, why, why, why are you leaving? Do you didn't even smash your Acai bowl? I say
twirling in my mustache with my thick rimmed glasses to my tech, bro. He says, bro, I found
the best way to destroy society, dude. I just found a way to completely obliterate culture
forever. We can make this brand new hashtag, which minimizes the amount of people that
are able to hear about third world issues. And I can also brainwash people and make them
spend all their time addicted to social media. I found this brand new way to hack into a human's
physiology and make them completely addicted to retweeting things. Dude, that's so epic.
Dude, I'm dropping my Acai bowl too. Can we stop and get some more flannel shirts on the
way over there? Hell yeah, dude. Also, I sleep in my car on the Facebook campus. I don't have
a house.
That does sound great. Should we, should we unify this around a hashtag of some kind? What
about hashtag save the PCP? What do you think? Is that, is that good? Is that too dramatic?
How about hashtag do the PCP and then it's drug marketed? How about hashtag do your fucking
job? I'm concerned that they will restore best guy ever and maybe the PCP and like everything
else like Canton and T-Bap and stuff will just get ignored. I mean, certainly a possibility
or at least like take way longer. If they do worse, then why wouldn't they do all of them?
I don't know the answer to that. YouTube is high school. It's just a popularity contest. If
you're not big enough, they don't give a fuck. Yeah, I just feel like they will do one, they
will maybe restore like the biggest channel and then be like, Hey, we did it. And like you
should be great. You should be grateful that we did literally any part of our job. Thanks very
much. The way that I had to submit the tickets, it's like basically it seems by Google account.
So like for example, on the PCP, I think the two channels that disappeared are the PCP and
the podcast, which was on like the PCP Google account as well. So like, I feel like if we get
the PCP back, probably as part of that conversation, we can we can fix the podcast as well. And the
same way, like my beachy channels, like a bunch of them got taken bestie boy and the live streams
one, like I can probably get them all back as a package deal. But T-Bap and content are on their
own. Those are on separate little Google accounts. I mean, maybe the fact that Digi's involved with,
you know, fucking T-Bap can help. Maybe once I actually get contact with like an internal person,
I can kind of be like, Hey, bro, kind of got a larger issue here. I would love to solve all these
at once. Maybe that'll happen. I don't know. I don't know. Literally, it would take someone at
like Google headquarters, like half an hour to just fix everything. I definitely think that's
correct. And that's being generous. Speaking of algorithms, completely. What's what's even the
word? Like putting like a boot on the throat of human endeavor. I was informed by close friend and
confidant and fellow occupier of space in the physical world, Kazi Snepp earlier today, of a
delicious, delicious, I've not like, so this person got a background check for their job. And the
company that he applied to ran a background check on him. They went through his entire Twitter and
made a report of every single tweet that he had liked with the word fucking it.
Liked? Yeah, I saw this. This was on r slash boring dystopia, which is an amazing sub-branded.
Did he get the job or something? I mean, what's the... I highly doubt it.
They counted it up. And the more fucks there were, the more likely he was to be high. Well,
they just, they had like different things like trig, like it was like, it's like, this is bad
because language is bad because alcohol is bad because all those things. This is exactly what
my mom warned me about when I was making Facebook posts like a decade ago about me at a party in
college holding a solo cup and being a silly boy. I'm assuming these are boomers who are
enacting these policies. So it makes me not surprised at all that the things our parents
that are now coming to pass as they are in charge of all the companies now. Okay, but, but I have
to pour cold water on everyone who's getting all hot and bothered about this. Sure. A report was
done on his Twitter, finding all the words with fuck. I need to know before I know how mad to get
exactly how that impacted his chances of getting, or was it simply a report about that? That is
irrelevant. That's fucked up. That has no relevance to the situation whatsoever. Of course it's
irrelevant. It doesn't matter. The fact that they're doing it at all is ridiculous.
To go through Facebook monitoring to make sure they don't say fuck.
This guy applied to a job and the company he was applying to did a background check on him,
went through his entire Twitter account and found all the questionable tweets that just had like
a swear in it or referenced alcohol in any form. That he had just liked. And just made a whole
print out and like said, these are all like flags. All right. Yes, that's very dystopian that they
looked that up. Okay, I totally agree. I totally agree. That's fair. But I'm also curious what the
next step was. Yeah, I am wondering like, did they get this report and look at it and be like,
oh, the computer's done something stupid. Maybe the boomers also said, well, obviously we don't
care about this. Why are you talking about getting a job at Facebook? It's not Facebook.
It's not Facebook. It's just some random company. In a hypothetical situation where there are two
candidates and they have the exact same credentials. It's like, hmm, which one do we pick?
Then tweets that they've liked with the word fucking, it might be the thing that people use
eventually to tip the balance. So I guess delete all your accounts.
Yeah, I mean, if you have two exactly equal applicants and one just says fuck more, you're
going to be like, well, that's not as good for my business as someone not saying fuck potentially.
So I'll just, you know, take the safer option. Who are these fucking alien like bug creatures?
They're like, oh, the people, if they know an employee of mine, you know, some like
janitor in one of my franchisees stores, if they said fuck one time on Twitter, that's going to
really hurt my brand. That's a bad representative of the company, dude. Bad representative of the
company. Get them out of here. The micromanaging is just sad. I can't imagine that this would
be in any way sustainable because of the amount of people that are on social media right now
that will need jobs in the near future. If like 700,000 people can't get a job because
they've said fuck on Twitter before, then what are the offices going to be filled with?
In 15 years or so, the millennials will be in that position, the boomers will be dead,
and this policy will go away because no one from our age demographic is going to think that's in
any way logical. And it'll just now that you can only get a job if you've said fuck on Twitter
before. Yeah, yeah, exactly. If you don't have pronouns in your bio, that's how you that's the
only way you can get a job. You know, perhaps social media is such an omnipresent force in
people's lives. And because you basically need like a Twitter account or at least a flirt with
Twitter for a while to have a a social standing in the current modern world. This means that if
you at all act, I'm going to say genuinely on social media whatsoever, and you anyway have your
real life persona tied to your internet persona, then this means that basically you have to perform
what 100% of the time, you know, existing as a human being online or off, you have to because
they have these such large degrees of like, you know, everything you do on the internet is completely,
you know, archive lockdown forever. You basically have to be performing from the day you fucking
start, you have to be like your parents just sit down with you and say like, Hey, Jimmy, look,
when you post on Twitter, make sure that this will be remembered forever, like every tweet you
ever like can be found and archives and your boss, big daddy, boss, monopoly bags will look that up
and use against you in a job application. So you've been well, hang on, that's the question.
Maybe there's a silver lining, not really silver lining, but maybe okay, because right now hiring
decisions right now still probably come down to a human being at the end of the day. So maybe we
can rely on our boomer heroes to get these reports and be like, Oh, you know, when I was young, I
was posting all my white nationalist propaganda too. So you know what, if the fact that you post a
couple of those, we'll let them off the hook this time. Maybe maybe there's no, again, it's not about
the job process part. It doesn't matter if like getting the job is not the bad thing here. The
fact that they even have access to this, the fact that keep in mind, this person gave them their
Twitter handle, they had to find it out, the company seek out the information, they seek out
this person's online account. The fact that these companies are so willing and able to look up
personal statements from years ago of people just because they want to be a fucking McDonald's cashier.
Ridiculous. I'm curious what this job was, what field it was in, you know, that would be perhaps
relevant, but I guess we don't know, whatever, doesn't matter, doesn't matter. Yeah, it's concerning.
It's not great, but like if you're an employer and you just like there's two buttons in front of
you, one is be willingly ignorant as to the private life of your of your potential employees,
when the other button is note a dystopian too much about them, be a morally upstanding character
in any way. You have a fiduciary responsibility as a business to try to pick the safest choice you
can. So like that is definitely not good for society, but business wise. There was a great
video by Philosophy Tube quite recently about data and data collection and stuff and he basically
argues with himself different characters playing about all of the different aspects of data collection
and how it's ruining society and how... Oh, are you talking about the Philosophy Tube video?
Yeah. Dammit, he just said that, Ben, listen. I'm sorry, this is really boring to me.
Well, it was a good video and you should all watch it if you like that conversation.
It's just called data and it ends with like a... Well, let's talk about it, but if you thought it
was interesting, don't just say go watch someone else's video. What was interesting about it?
Because it's so many fucking... All right, the cool part is... It's a conversation and it basically
shows every way that the conversation could possibly branch as they talk.
I don't care about the video, the way it's formatted. I care about what was said in that.
I mean, he's talking about like fucking problematic things that private corporations can
do with all this data that they're constantly collecting from you. The thing that I really
liked about the video was that from the perspective of the bouncer, he's just trying to do his job
and he constantly goes to that like, sorry, I just have to scan your ID and it boils down to
the ultimate point of, I know that all this data is ruining the world. I know it's destroying society.
I just don't want to think about it. I don't want to think. I just want to do my job and go home.
And that's where the video ends because ultimately that is the problem. People don't want to think
and the computers will do the thinking for them because life sucks and they don't want to have
to deal with all of that shit all the time. All right. I mean, there's only so much you
can put on any individual. Like if you're just in a system that just has these things in place,
like you kind of can't avoid using them. There needs to be, I don't know, some like higher level
thing, like a movement that's like, this is bad. We're going to stop using this through some mechanism.
I don't know. This guy needs a job. His job involves scanning people's IDs.
Yeah. Yeah. How can you blame him? Yeah. He could be, what's the word? He could rise above and be
like, no, I'm going to go and be gay instead for pay. I'll be gay for pay instead. That's the moral
choice. That's how we beat big data. Everybody's gonna go gay for pay. The new sleep type album,
gay for a pay day. But all that's going to change when they release the new gay bots
that will, you know, all gay men will lose their jobs. You're right. They're going to place this
out of the market. Dammit. I've been Boston of the fuck out, guys. I've really been so fucking
Massachusetts pill. It's really retarded. And I know everyone's like, oh my god, wow, the fucking
seven letter word or six letter word or how many letter words it is. Oh my god. He said it again,
wouldn't only shut the fuck up. And listen, I'm sorry, but fuck you. I'll never ship about it
because I've had strange and bizarre experiences and a like exponential Boston intake lately
for you see at my school. I have two courses basically dedicated to Boston in the terms of a
architecture class of the city of Boston, and then a like local activism class for the city of
Boston. I've been reading a Boston history book, which by the way, Ben, I gave you the pass for
the audible. You can log back. I have signed in and I opened that up this morning. I haven't
started listening. Yeah, I haven't started listening. And and I've been I've been just, I mean,
living here, obviously, I'm literally so fucking Massachusetts pill it hurts and I can't go back.
Our culture is not your fucking costume. It literally is. I literally want to paint my face.
I want a white face now.
Munchie is pulling a jauntron right now walking around dressed up like a pilgrim.
I wish I fucking was honestly. Dude, that book is so fucking crazy, Ben. The city
state of Boston. I recommend everyone Google search, Mark Peterson, city state of Boston,
because it has like a like a weird like, okay, so it has the history of New England from the
perspective, not of like Boston, the cradle of liberty, you know, oh, the famous American
Revolutionary site. Oh, you know, remember America? That happens later. This is just the
prelude to America. This is just like the first chapter of American history. It goes about it
from the perspective of the people actually at the time. And, you know, the decision they made
as a almost like a quasi independent colony, and the trials and tribulations, not of people
gunning to create the United States. That was not on anyone's mind. Yeah, no shit. Yeah. It was
for them to, you know, prosper as an independent city state, as the person says. And I love shit
like that. I love the best history is not the sort of, you know, popcorn, extra credits, like,
this happened, then this happened, then this happened, then this happened, then this has
happened. And it's not even the like, oh, you get really into like the heroes and the villains.
No, it's a great narrative story. No, no, no. The best history is the kind of history that makes you
remember, oh, wait, nothing was like planned. Nothing was ever like, oh, I'm like, nothing ever
had to be the way it is. So much of history is just like, coincidentally, oh, you stumble into
something. Oh, just coincidentally, oh, because of these various, you know, very specific, hyper
specific circumstances. Oh, now Boston has just, you know, randomly happenstance happened to appeal
to other like, English colonies at that specific point in world history. And oh, blue America
happened, wasn't even planned, wasn't intentional, wasn't destined or anything. And that stuff is
just like on a moment to moment, human level, it's always something that sticks with me. And
there's like, dude, at any moment, like, like the things that are happening right now, at any moment
could blossom and change into something that I would have never imagined happening before and
could potentially have ramifications for a long time afterward, like think back to my own experiences,
like stuff that like changed my life forever, like let's say going to Bronicon and meeting
Digi Bro. At the time, I just like saw Digi Bro. And like, I talked to him for like five minutes,
but that like changed my, I'm recording this podcast because of that small change.
And it's cool. Hey, speaking of destiny,
this slide aside, I do have an aside here, which I think will entertain the peanut gallery,
which is that my my down so I live in a house in Cincinnati, obviously, and your downstairs
name more like your down soy neighbors fucking accurate. Yeah. So so I had a downstairs neighbor
directly below me. It was a single guy, he moved out recently, I think it was like the army or
something. And like new neighbors moved in. So I have not actually met the man possibly I've seen
a man and a woman moving around inside. So I don't know who lives there. That's the
generosity. I hope you're married. I got I hope so. Jesus, but cohabitation,
big problem in today's society. They're not going to have right now. Watch the YouTube video about
that. Last week, I mentioned a political juice. I watched a six hour video about the importance
of civil society. And he spends a lot of it being like, I don't know about all this premarital
cohabitation. I mean, one could potentially make a case that it might be like better or worse for
society to do. Okay, but either way, either way, my Okay, so so like when it was a single guy
living down there, at least because I knew that guy a little bit, like he had like the back door,
there's like a back door in the house, which I that's how I get in my house. And like his window
did not have a shade over it. So like, and I would see him like playing League of Legends or
something through that window, as I'm like out walking the dog or coming home from something
or whatever. And like he has a he has a there's a porch that goes up on the right, it branches
upstairs to my thing. And on the left, it branches sort of into that door into his apartment or
whatever. And so once in a while, I would just be a little curious, there's no shade, I would just
I take a step up or two right on his step, I would peer in and be like, Oh, he's playing League
of Legends. And then I dip out and then I would go up my stairs, being a little nosy, it's true.
But I just want to know what he's playing. It's these windows wide open. If he doesn't want me
looking in, get a shade. This isn't my problem. This is your problem. I see my neighbors TV
constantly playing Smash. There you go. Exactly the same shit kind of shit. Okay,
but that man has moved out and there are now new people person living there. So the other day,
and I looked at him and I was like, Oh, boy, can't wait to look in the window and see some more
League of Legends and you're looking and oh, my God, they're playing smite. What the fuck?
Well, so the other day, I'm just I'm walking session or something and I like I just I walk
up to him and I happen to notice just kind of through the window that where they used to be
like a desk with the old neighbor. Now there's like a couch and I'm like, Oh, that's that's
an interesting change. But okay, still no shades guys, you're going to make this like your living
room and no shades. Okay, that's fine. And I go upstairs. And then the other day, the other day,
I'm thinking to myself, you know what, I don't know who the neighbors are, I should go introduce
myself sometime. I'll do that one of these days. But I'm coming home from something. I think I
just like dropped off Michelle at work or something. And I'm just walking in and I do my little, Oh,
you know, I'm just going to take a peek, see what's going on in there. And I step up on like
their side of the rail. For a good like three, four seconds, I'm standing there gazing directly
into this window, like getting the scene what's going it's like it's the middle of the night.
I know it's probably like 10pm or something. And I'm just standing there looking in at their
like couch and stuff. And then all of a sudden, like the focus of my eyes changes. And I realize
like one foot to the right of what I'm currently looking at, there is a woman sitting there looking
directly at me into her home. And I don't know if you guys have seen that vine where the girl
gets spooked by the possum, but I go like that. And I kind of dodge back and dodge downward.
And I run upstairs and hide and just hole up there. And now you can never introduce yourself.
I can never introduce myself. I mean, that's that's the full story. But like, I just knew,
man, that was not good. And I need to now, I need to definitely go give them like a pie or a bottle
of wine and be like, Hey, sorry about that. Just want to say hello. So your problem was
you panicked. You could have played it off as like you weren't actually paying attention.
I should have. I really should have. I okay, to be fair, I'm exaggerating a little bit exactly
how dramatic I kind of just step back quickly and then moved upstairs. But you know, it was it was
not ideal and I was even those subtle things. You've got to just like, just it's very, very
important split decisions happen in those situations. You failed the test, Nate.
That's when I learned what kind of a man I am. And it's a foolish, cowardly, panicky kind of man.
But I'll endeavor to rise above it. If only you were wearing your vampire Hunter D hat,
you could have just tipped it downward, blocked your eyes from view. You would have been safe.
What'd you say, Munchie? I think about the hours you could have spent playing League of Legends
with people and how well those hours would have been spent. And you know what, that's like my
old neighbor who lived down there, we would see he had like a little glass kind of porch that stuck
out like kind of in the middle of the driveway in the backyard. It doesn't matter. But like it's
another kind of like, like unshaded glass thing. There's a table there. I would see him with like
a bunch of, I guess his friends or contemporaries or whatever, gather around, I don't know, maybe once
a month or something and like play some tabletop game. And I don't really like tabletop games that
much. But I was like, I should have said hello to this man and like become, like me and Michelle
could have just gone and been paled around and been friends and stuff. But we never did. And then
he moved away. And I blew it. Don't be like me, everybody. Say hello to your neighbors. Buy like
a $1 fucking piece of bread or pie. Say hello. Give them as a warming present. Be friends.
Hello, Mr. Neighbor. Here's some Wonder Bread I purchased for you. Now, Queen Pieces James
are a slice of Wonder Bread. I would love to use you for your tabletop games, please.
I have one pallet of butter that I will also give you that you make smear on the bread.
Yeah. Unironically do that. Just go be friends and be nice and give gifts to people so then
you they'll like you. Yeah, it's better than being literally just like Stardew Valley. You just go
run around town with like a inventory full of eggs. Just give everyone one, just throw eggs
at people. Exactly, Ben. Egg for you. Egg for you. Everyone like egg.
In my experience. Yes, do that. I live in an urban hellscape,
but like the people who live in my house are generally pretty cool, it seems. So like,
get to know your neighbors. I mean, you literally know nothing about them and you've only stared
at them through windows. You remember that I got, you remember the time that I did Molly and then
knocked on my neighbor's door like, why aren't we friends? I mean, see, that's the wrong approach.
What a fucking moron. I also gazing through the window was also the wrong approach,
but there are good approaches to this sort of thing. If I had done what I did on some other day
and brought like a pie, then that would be fine. You'd make a friend for life. Everybody in the
voicemails are trying to ask us for advice on how to interact with like women or people in general.
Remember, this is the caliber of people you're talking to. Learn from our mistakes. This is what
we struggle with. Learn from our mistakes. This is, this is all fine. This is all fine.
What is this interest in brotherly love? I feel like this is like, I don't even, like,
this is so, people are not going to be able to relate to this because I think it's very
strange scenario to have your neighbors be someone you want to interact with in the modern world.
That's because the modern world is full of pussy ass, dumb ass, motherfucking bitches who think that
they can replace every relationship in their real life with like retarded online friendships
like this one I have with you guys. But really, you should actually get to know the people in
your immediate vicinity at least a little bit because it'll make your life, like I was saying,
I live in an urban hellscape and I don't know anyone and they're all scary potential murderers
or rapists on me. I mean, when Bernie Sanders gets elected and they institute the gulags and
come to take our guns away, like these are the people you're going to have to be like forming
a blockade on the street with to fight back against the federal government. Exactly. Exactly.
You better get those alliances sorted out now. It's funny you mentioned Tabletop because I started
playing D&D with one of my friends that I, from high school, he hit me up just like,
hey, I'm starting a D&D group because we've tried playing a couple times and I've really
panned out, but this time we've been going a couple of weeks and that's good. It gets me out of the
house and I'm like meeting people. But the weird thing is that like, he's like, all the people
we're playing with, they all are his work friends. So they're all just like talking about like,
isn't it crappy working for Comcast? And I'm just like, I don't understand any of this. And I feel
very odd. I think that more than anything else is that when, you know, the only people you can
potentially talk to all know each other on some level, such that the conversation is like,
almost 100%. Hey, do you remember that time where we did that thing? Oh yeah, let's talk about that
for 20 minutes. I don't have anything to say about these things. You gotta press through it.
These things can all be overcome with a little bit of grit. Oh, absolutely. I'm not like saying
it's like a total loss or anything. So I'm still going. I'm still having good time. But the problem
is just like, the vibes, you don't know what the vibes are. It's like, can I say retarded?
Because I will the character. That's every fucking day for me, Tom. That's literally every
conversation I have is I have to gauge, can I say retarded? And I wanted to make him like an
autistic retard. But nobody, I don't know the social cues. I don't know. Because my friend
is like a fucking like shit poster kind of guy who just like whatever. But like these people,
it's like, it's like his friend from work and his friend's wife. And I'm just like,
I don't know who any of you are. And I'm very afraid of being. You just, you just gotta swing
up in the door and say the n word. Oh, you're right. You're right. You're right. I gotta lay
down the baseline. It's true. It's true. What was I thinking? For real, like you gotta just like
say the things that you want to say, because all right, here are the two options for you.
Either be a little pussy bitch and don't say the things you want and get nothing out of the
relationship or say what you want and put them potentially hate you. And it doesn't even matter
because the, it's just where you're right back where you started. It doesn't even matter. It's
true. It's true. Losing these people as potential friends would not affect me in any way because
I don't care. It was like, it was like that legendary moment when I referred to PewDiePie
in my group of work friends as my nigga. And then their faces all fell and the total atmosphere
turned to mud right in front of me. And I learned what their boundary was. That's when I learned.
People in real life, they're not even fucking cool. You can't curate them. They're literally
pointless. All this shit about neighbors, all this shit about mean people. It's all stupid.
I mean, I don't need to go into why that I was really using that in a positive way. There was no,
yeah, I mean, you know what sucks like in situations like that though is that one or two
of them may have been okay with it, but they don't want to laugh along with you. Exactly.
Exactly. It's all fake. That is true. Everyone's fake. That's why you got to wait for after,
after that exchange, you know, in the cover of night on my work, you know, chat,
bot or whatever, I just get the word, just like the N word, just N word response from like one
of the co-workers who's trying to operate below enemy lines, behind enemy lines and, you know.
You just got to keep an eye on the one co-worker who just flashes through the okay sign and you
know that he's a fellow white supremacist. We found each other. Yes. Based. Now that's,
that's the good shit right there. Listen, there are so many people around you as a human being
and basically none of them matter to you. That doesn't mean that they're bad people. It doesn't mean
that they are NPCs that you have to mow down and get the extra high score with. It doesn't mean that
you have to sacrifice them for fuel and turn them into charcoal, but it does mean that like on the
internet, you can Google search group for spreading aids, get some bug catchers going on. It's great.
They call it the bug, bug, spreading. Bug chaser, bug chaser or whatever. Bug chasing,
that's the one. And that's great because you can now curate who you want to talk to. And you know,
of course, internet relationship is never going to be as full bodies, as robust as a real life
friendship, but it's better than real life friendships because most of them are born out
of convenience and most of the people you meet in real life suck because they aren't like you.
You want a good balance. You want a good balance of the people who you go with online.
My goal right now is to get more real life interactions. Now that I am able to walk and
move around again, I'm going to go out there and find people.
Tom, just get a fucking job, you idiot. Get a job. No, no, no, come on here.
They're going to look through my Twitter history and I'm never going to get hired anywhere. Are
you kidding me? Once in a while, once in a while, I do wonder if like, what if I just walk down the
street to like Whole Foods and was like, yeah, just let me be a cashier. Bro, they will do it
instantly and you will get $15 an hour. It is a good job. Like more just for something to do.
I'm absolute. I have been looking for jobs unironically, but I just hate the idea. It feels
disgusting. It's not disgusting because then you can actually do what you want and you won't have
to turn your art into a commodity to sell. That's the only thing I was just talking about.
Literally the only reason that I'm even considering it is that I'm so sick of trying and
found to be marketable. I hate it with all my soul. Right now, the grass sure looks greener
on the side of having a job to earn money and then just doing your art separately.
The real question is, the question really boils down to who do I want to be a slave to,
the public or the boss? Because that's really the only options.
I mean, right now, nothing in my life is sacred. When I was, you know, part-time YouTuber,
the YouTubing was mostly sacred except for what I like owed to my patrons. But you can just,
you know, Darth Vader, I have changed the deal. Pray I do not alter it further, you know, whatever
the fuck it is. And with your, you can renegotiate at any time with your patrons and they can just
leave. So, but unless you're depending on that income to survive, which certainly changes your
priorities and whatnot. So I mean, well, one day, these days, I may or may not go back to having
a full-time job, but I heavily encourage anybody who's like having a tough time reaching their
financial goals to have a job and then do their art stuff on the side. I think the biggest problem
with getting a job would be almost all jobs require you working on weekends, which means I lose all
my PCP money, in which case I only probably end up making like an extra $200 or something.
Well, that's not nothing, though. Well, surely there's going to be some job that leaves, you know,
Sundays at this time free. I mean, one could negotiate that, I would think.
I'm going to get a job, a stack and shit. I'm going to get a job going out into the world and
finding a bunch of crap and I'm going to stack it real high, real tall. I'm going to say,
please pay me and then I'm going to stack some more shit and I'm going to get cars and stack those.
They say make the job that you want, right? So just go out there and stack stuff, guys.
I'm going to stack some shit. I'm going to stack some shit and then the mother is like,
why are you stacking my children? You're like, I love to stack, please give me a $50.
I'm acquiring skills, guys. No, you say to them in a completely serious voice, give me 15 quid.
Give me some quid. I still don't understand British currency. It's like pints and quid and
pints, there's quid, there's 5s, 10s, 10s. Bob's.
10 Bob is like a word and you use it to refer to. This is why we fucking threw your tea in the
ocean. Hey, can I have some 25 schmlorp, please? Can you just define for me a quid and a pence?
A quid is a quarter. No, a quid is a fucking pound. A pound is a $50 note.
No, no, no, no, a quid is a fan. A quid is a fan. A pence is a pound.
Shut up, god damn it. You're not helping. All right, here's the easy way.
I'm ready to learn. A pence is a scent. Yes. They sound similar. They're the same thing. 100 of
them makes a pound or a quid. Five quid, five Bob note is usually to refer to the note. I don't
know what Bob comes from. Bob's your uncle, probably. A five quid is a five Bob note.
Five pound note is for us a buck. And hippo, how many aspects of a shield can constitutes a quid?
How many shield parts do you get? Like does it take? Isn't there only one part to a shield?
No, there's very many parts to a shield. You have to assume the shield. It's five of something.
The coins, the British coins have at some point in history, they started doing a thing where
they have some section of a shield. And if you arrange the coins, they make a full shield image.
I don't know how many there are. I think it's just all of the coins have a bit of it.
Huh. That's not how we say it. That's not how we say it.
Munchies English accent, just perfect. Just flawless.
Hey, speaking of cultural sensitivity, we can't keep changing topics. We can't just keep, oh,
I say something. Okay, that's cool. All right, next topic. We can't just like pivot back and
forth. There's no conversation here. Wait, shut the fuck up. No, here, I have to say something.
All right, I'm going to make an argument for interacting with society, not because society
is good, but specifically because society is bad, but you're opposed if you think society is bad
because you haven't engaged with society yet. So, you know, oh, smash cut to me back in 1908.
And I was hanging out, you know, I was playing video games and I thought,
being a normie sure is like bad. I sure was told that by someone at some point in my life.
Hey, can you pass the fucking loop? Can you pass the fucking anal beads? Bro, I need my kick.
And so I've come here. I've ventured out into the land of the real world, many, you know, for a while
now. I'm still doing it. I'm on the golden road. I'm on the golden ratio right now. And now I have
such a clarity of mind. I'm in like a Buddhist, like monk state right now. And I can finally
understand like, wait a second, wait a second, wait a second. Normies are bad, but I have actual
reasons to believe it now. Like I have actual like experiences and I can actually, you know,
give arguments and I can actually understand why people say that in the first place.
I'm not building a pond because like, you know, I've only been the internet. I'm like,
the reason I hate normies is because I'm literally too anxious. I'm too anxious to go outside and
fucking talk to them because I'm a baby bitch. And I was told to hate them by people on YouTube
that I follow. And it's just, it just shows like a lack of moral character and lacks,
it shows a lack of convention because you're pairing what other people are saying. And you're
too anxious inside. By the way, if you have anxiety, I fucking hate you by the way. You
literally are like not trying hard enough. And you're only saying that you hate normies out of
fear. But once you actually, you know, interact with society, once you have a job or once you
go to school and once you're interacting with people in real life, then you will have the
legit ass opinion that normies are shit, but comma and space afterward.
That's fair. I mean, you shouldn't judge something to leave experience.
Speaking of real life, cool experiences. The, if you remember, I talked to a while ago about
the, the mission to walk in a straight line across the country of Wales, where that guy
with a GoPro on his head did that. Then he went back to making fucking
GeoGuessor videos, which sucked. And it was like, damn. But recently he has come back with an
incredible new and different adventure. He and his friend decided to try and get all the way
across Europe without using money to pay for transportation. And they would try to use as
many different modes of transportation as possible and talk to people to like, you know,
black their way through things and, and stuff like that. And he's got the whole series and it's
finished. And the doable, it sounds like a very doable thing to me. It's, it's a very doable
thing, but it's really doesn't, doesn't not spending money basically limit you to walking.
No, no, no. You can hitchhike people and like the things include sneaking onto trains and then
avoiding the ticket man hitchhiking. But I did that a bunch of times. They got some subscribers
to get them some kayaks and bikes for various portions of the trip. And a lot of wait, so
they can let other people buy them stuff. Well, I guess not buy them stuff. But like the point is,
I mean, it's worth it because kayaking is fun. Yeah, they went like through like this river
near the Alps and through Italy on these kayaks. And it was so cool. And, you know,
they would, they would slip on the land and eat off the land. And, you know, it was all very,
very interesting. And a lot of the cool interactions they had with random Europeans
was like some of the coolest and heartwarming stuff ever. It's, it, it made me realize that
as long as you are, you know, confident and nice, you can get people to do things for you.
We hear a lot of shit about how fucked up the world is, which is true.
Most people are good people and will just kind of be nice to you if you're nice to them. I
firmly believe this about the world. So I definitely recommend that whole series. It's very,
very good. But Gabe, I was just curious, what's the start and end point? Where did they start and
where did they end? Yeah, they started like Portugal and they go to like Russia, Ukraine or
Europe. It's like from, oh, what country is it? It's, I think, through either France or Italy.
I think it was near the Alps. They started somewhere there. But they got all the way over to
Bretislava in fucking, I can't remember the country's name, but Bretislava is a place.
Lithuanian or sometimes like, somewhere to the fucking east.
So it sounds like they were going south to north.
No, they were going sort of west to east-ish. I can't remember exactly.
Why would you start in Italy then? I don't fucking remember.
Because they're gay. They started in Portugal, those cows.
Yeah, it would be obvious.
Italy goes all the way up to the Alps. Maybe they started in Sicily or one of those,
you know, places down there, Florence or something. It would be very hard to start from Europe,
west to east, and start in Italy.
All right, whatever. I don't remember the actual country, but it doesn't matter.
It's a bad video, Gib. It's actually bad. That's the point.
The things that happen are really cool. And on the note of that, there's this other YouTuber,
I should find the, I can't remember his name at the moment, but he does train hopping videos.
Maybe I talked about this before. But basically, he is like the same sort of thing.
He's got a GoPro, but he's a complete criminal and he's got his face colored.
And basically, he goes on freight trains and hides inside them and knows how to illegally hop
on trains and avoid guards and he films it all. And there's such a freedom sort of
feeling you get from those. Because he has this hammock that he has to sleep in. He just finds,
like he climbs on top of a roof and hopes that nobody comes to see him. Because it's like,
nobody's going to go up there. So he just goes up on a roof and he makes a bed with a sleeping
bag. And then he goes back on the next train. He's trying to figure out which trains are going
what direction. And he's like, hops on the right train, avoids the guards. And then when the train
is in motion, he just climbs up the top because they have the little metal ladders. And he just
sort of surfs the train. He's got a GoPro on a stick and he's just sort of looking at the
beautiful scenery in the sunset. And he's just got the wind in his hair. And it's like the coolest
thing ever. What a life. Being free is really fucking epic, I think. You know what hippo,
that reminds me of a very liberating sort of feeling when you're in the physical world and
you are kinetically moving around the world. It's a very like, it's a revolution inside your
brain when you realize that you can jaywalk. And I don't mean jaywalking literally, although I do
mean jaywalking spiritually. When you realize that the rules and customs that you have been told
to abide by, you can just break them all the time and it doesn't matter. Bro, that's the main thing
that keeps when I was a shy young boy afraid to talk to girls, which it is still terrifying to do
to this day, no doubt about it. Like that right there, that social conditioning that like it's
not okay to just like say hello to someone was so beat into my brain, maybe entirely due to my own
retarded ass thinking and just watching anime all day. But then when I realized like, oh, it's
actually okay to do that and like say hello to people or whatever. Bit of a revolution, a bit
of a mind change. You can basically do like so much more than what people think is possible. Like
they have like very like hard ingrained like paths in front of them that they feel like they have
to abide by. But you can get away with like a bunch of like, I don't know, like illegal, literally
and socially things. Me and Ben held a slime protest. And I know there was a few people
that like not at the con, but I talked about it with some of my friends and they were like,
uh, are you sure? Don't you need like a permit? Oh, god, yeah, absolute the absolute cowardice of
some people that are like, oh, you're gonna get you're gonna get in trouble. You're gonna get in
trouble if you organize more than like 10 people in this like public park and like make some noise
during the day. People, as long as you don't cause problems, like things work out. Even if you do
post problems. I'm always, I'm always saying sorry I didn't realize. You should apply for a permit
before you do, before you publicly assemble anywhere public. What's that old saying they say?
It's always better to apologize than to like. It's ask for forgiveness, not for permission.
That's the one. That's the one. Yep. Better to beg forgiveness than to ask permission. It reminds
me of a time where I accidentally got myself into a situation that was illegal, but I was not in the
right mind frame to like deal with it. I thought I was going to die. I thought the police were going
to kill me. Um, it was just that I got onto a train and I didn't realize that I didn't swipe my,
my, my, uh, my ticket. Yeah. Yeah. Like I didn't, I didn't swipe the, the beep thing. And then I was
like, wait a minute. That's me every day. Wait a minute. When I get to the other end, when I get
to the other end of this train, I'm gonna have to swipe the thing to open the gate and they're
going to know that I didn't get on the train. They're going to fucking tackle me at the other end.
But like, uh, it doesn't matter because. Yeah, they just don't really care.
Like I did the, I pressed the thing and it's like, oh, it doesn't work.
And then this guy just opened it for me. It's like, there you go.
Law. There's an, there's an episode of, um, I think you say at Le Las Gare, the French cartoon
where the guy, a guy just hops the style or the till or whatever at the, at the subway station.
And the fucking like train bouncers like descend on him. And he decides that a way to get away
with it is to pretend that he's an American tourist who only speaks English. He's like, uh,
I saw the officer is first time I do it. And I think he gets his ass kicked. But my experience
is that nobody gives a shit. And even if you just openly run through the thing behind someone else
and don't swipe your card and are clearly just cheating the system, the worst that will happen
is like a guy in a T-jack. It will be like, sir, you get, you swipe your card, please.
Oh yeah, that happened that fucking last time we were in Boston. It might.
Oh yeah. It might genuinely white privilege that I might only get such mild responses
because I'm white and I look like a nerd. Perhaps. We tried to go through the thing like
in the ticket of the train where you do the thing and then a bunch of people run through
while it's open. And then the guy saw it and it's like, uh, could you, could you not do that?
But like nothing happens. Happens, you know? Yeah, no, nothing. Like, like he never drops.
People are scared of getting in trouble way too much. I think it might be brainwashing.
It's by design. It's by design, of course. I'm pretty like 99% sure it's like actual
like dumb brainwashing. Fear is what keeps the majority of society running.
Dude, I am always, I always watch like, you know, crime shows or whatever. And I'm like
amazed every time that I see like people do things like, like commit like armed robbery.
Look, I know these things are exaggerated to some degree and like, like do actual like,
I don't know, be drug traffickers. And then they're like out on bail and just like are allowed to
continue their lives. Look, not for the extreme stuff, I know, but like generally speaking,
you'll like be fine in a while. If you're a first time offender, you'll like be fine. If you do
most things. I mean, it takes money. Yeah, money, which can be a problem for you. But like, yeah,
it doesn't end your life. And that's, we were definitely taught to like what they say that
like the middle of the, like the poor exists to create fear in the middle class to like,
you know, to sustain the upper class, they say or whatever. And then like, it's the same with
like criminals, like the hardcore crime and jails, whatever, like exist to scare people straight.
So that they're like terrified, like a fucking Tom in the boondocks scared of getting annually
raped in jail. I mean, he's the perfect example of like, that's a legit fear. Okay, sure. Sure.
Says Tom, I mean, from the boondocks, what if it's, what if it feels good? What if you like it?
What if you turn gay in his soul? I identified very strongly with that scene. Okay.
That is another Tom. That is, you know, I do too. I do too. But you know, speaking of like,
absolute, like small brained, like peanut, like regressed in the mind, childlike thinking idiots,
my girlfriend, Michelle is absolutely terrified of jaywalking. Because in Hawaii, yeah, because in
Hawaii, jaywalking is like considered, I guess I can't blame her, like an actual serious crime,
sort of like they actually prosecute people who jaywalk. In Boston, you're just expected to.
Yeah, no, that's the thing. I mean, I've been to New York and Boston, Philly and all over the
fucking place. And like, I jaywalk 24 seven, 365 and nobody gives a shit. But I guess in Hawaii,
they're like anti-curtle touchings for some reason, I still don't understand why. You get
arrested in Boston for not jaywalking because you're holding up foot traffic. It's because the
traffic in Hawaii is so bad because island, et cetera, et cetera, that like they really
take traffic violation seriously, I guess. I guess like LA or something. Ridiculous. But I mean,
Jesus Christ, her poor brain has been absolutely destroyed by fear of jaywalking. And she could
definitely get away with it most of the time. And I try, what I'm trying to say is long story
short, all this commit crimes. I'm telling you to commit crimes. I'm at the point where I'm starting,
I'm at the point where I'm starting to wondering, is shoplifting really illegal? Like is it really?
Ben does it every single fucking day. Ben shoplifts every single fucking day.
You can literally. Well, here's the thing. This is what made me start thinking about this. I was
at Best Buy a few days ago and like they had like all the video games, right? And all the games are
like in like these fucking theft proof containers and everything. Then they had the bargain bin,
where it's just like a bunch of games just in plastic wrap. I'm like, are they just telling
me it's okay to take these ones? Do they just want them gone? And I just take a copy of Monster
Hunter World and just bail. Here's your homework for next week. Tom,
I'm literally going to tell you what you have to do. Ask this recording, go to Best Buy,
pick up a video game, walk out of the store. Like just start running, just fucking run out of the
store. They're not allowed to chase you. Wait, hold on. Video games have like the little metal
tag in them that sometimes the sensors detect. Well, that's the whole thing. And the bargain bin
ones, it's just plastic wrap. And that's why I'm just like, are these like the okay to steal ones?
That's how I'm interpreting it right now. You know me boys and girls. I am, in fact,
actually a straight edge. But like jaywalking is actually a victimless crime, 99% of the time.
The thing about shop, well, Nate, so is like not wearing your seat belt, but that's illegal.
Okay, true. True. Are we divided each individually? I don't know. I mean, if the law on the book,
if like draconian enforcement of traffic laws like leads to like significantly reduced like
death tolls or whatever, then like, I'd support it. Here's the thing about shoplifting,
like imagine that you are a minimum wage fucking work or you're any fucking drone working the
floor of a supermarket or something. And you see someone like pocket something and walk out the door
with it. What are you going to do? Are you going to run after that person like sir, sir,
you need to stop sir. And then when they don't fucking tackle them and risk your life and limb
to defend your employer's property. No, of course, no, no, no, no, give a shit. I mean, maybe it
depends. If you're in fucking Texas, maybe they have different state laws, like I don't know. But
I worked in Massachusetts at a Best Buy. I knew the security guys, I will tell you what they do.
First of all, they are not allowed to even attempt to stop you in any way. They maybe would speak
to you or maybe say like, please don't leave. You would have to be like a police officer to have
that like that thing that calling the cops is the most they can do. So if you're just letting
you know, you can definitely be out of there. But here's the thing, if you come back later,
they will like call the cops if you show up again. So you got to live your life on the road.
That's what you got to do if you want to live this way. I got my $20 copy of Monster Hunter
World for free. It was all worth it. Right, right. Today, I went on a school project.
Well, I wanted us out of the house and I was researching architecture.
Don't move on. I just wanted to say a quick jaywalking thing that was funny while it was
relevant that sometimes like when it's quiet, the roads are quiet. I realized that I don't have to
walk on one side of you know, on the pavement and then cross over to the other side if I need to. I
can walk straight down the middle of the road all the way down. And when I do that, I suddenly
like things like buildings, they start feeling like platforms. I start feeling like I can jump
over them and I can climb all over them and I become like, this is just a 3D model. This is
all just fake and I can jump and do all this cool shit. You're literally a god when you do that.
You activated the god mode. When it was snowy, I would walk in the middle of the road because
like tire tracks would have like cleared more of the snow out of the way. So I would like have less
snow to walk through. No, there's like genuinely like a state of mind that you enter. At least
I feel this way. I remember very distinctly when I came into being and I was in school and I was
walking in class and I thought to myself, wait a second, wait a second, wait a second. I'm supposed
to go to class right now. That's what my body is like telling me. My mind is telling me I need to do.
But like I could just not. Like I could just like leave. I could just leave the campus right now.
And it was like, people don't think their body is their own. People think the way things are right
now. How about when you get to college, the reality says when you get to college and it's like,
wait, wait, I don't have to ask for permission to go to the bathroom anymore. What? Maybe Munchie,
since you did whatever it was, the weird school for retards and idiots as I understand it.
Dude, wait. Wait, what? I did what now? No, I said Munchie. Didn't I say Munchie? I meant to say
yeah, whatever it was. Nate, this is a quick aside. We're going to get back to the topic,
but I just want to say that you reminded me, as I was saying before, I was reading a history of
Boston, so you say Boston. And in that, there was a great little excerpt. Apparently, one of the
first schools for the disabled in United States of America, its name was the Massachusetts School
for the Idiotic and Feeble-Minded Uds. I mean, in the olden days, that was-
Xavier's rebranding was very interesting. Munchie, I was walking-
I want to be enlisted. Let me in. I was walking back to the food court or whatever,
because I'd left my bag and there's a building that I crossed that's called the Normal School.
Yeah, Boston Normal School, yep. Yeah, so I guess that's the opposite. That's like for the really
big brain kids is the Normal School. Yeah, and then you have the Idiotic and Feeble-Minded
Youth School. Sponsored by the Procrastinator's podcast. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. But people
don't think their body and their mind is their own. People think that the way that the society is
right now is the only way that it can be. People have such an unimaginative, smooth brain approach
to critical thinking. But it's by design. I don't blame anyone for that. You've been conditioned
from birth to live in these lanes. Human life is conditioned to settle into a groove of life
that you come across. That just seems to be how the human brain works. And it's less energy to
do your routine as opposed to trying to mix things up. So it's understandable why you
fall into grooves, but you should always remember that you can change things up and do things
differently. I think one of the earliest times I realized crime is okay. This is not to get
political or anything, but this is how I feel every time I see someone saying that free college
and free healthcare is socialism. I understand, I understand. We only think that because we don't
already do them. If we already did those things, like with fire departments or public school,
you wouldn't have a problem with them. You would just think it's normal. It's just an
accident of history and circumstances that people feel like they'd need to rail against that kind
of thing. I want to brush up on that too, just because it's a very easy way to illustrate it.
But this goes to every single fucking aspect of human endeavor, where it's like some people think
that capitalism is one thing. It is one institution that, if implemented, is the same across all
countries. When things like that, capitalism doesn't exist in a concrete way. It represents
itself through policies and theories that are different in every single region and any place
that it is implemented in. People don't realize that things can be slightly different or you can
improve upon things in any way. All of how life is, it was made by other humans and it is all
the result of thousands of years of discussion. Capitalism can be taken away at any time if you
cross us. Literally exactly. Capitalism is not natural in the sense that this is just the way
that human beings have evolved naturally. It is the result of theories, the result of discussion,
it is the result of countless upon countless iterations of designs. People seem to think
that America, the countries that exist now, the systems that exist now, will simply exist in
perpetuity. And there's a natural state about it. Obviously, the United States exists. Obviously,
capitalism exists. Obviously, these are the ways that we do things because this is how they've
been since I was born. But even if you go double your lifetime back, things will start radically
getting different because the world is always changing. This is what I was saying at my first
point in this podcast. I don't know how to say it because I said it in a really obtuse way.
But it's like these sorts of things. Nothing is ever natural. Nothing is ever how it's supposed
to be. It's all just the result of circumstance and upon discussion and theory and evolution.
And this is the sort of thing where it's like people getting their little mind cage, their
neoliberal mind cage to quote Ben's lyric from under the city.
Dab, right. Neath the city is what the song is called, but close enough.
They don't understand that things can be different. And again, this is not just for
politics. This is just for, again, crossing the fucking road in the middle of the street,
in the middle of the road, instead of going to the pre-determined spots where you're supposed
to do it. Oh, I do that because that's what the lies. And there are these signs on the ground
that lead me to do that. That's what I'm told I'm supposed to do.
You're right. You're right. And the point is fuck cops do crime.
Yeah. Dare to dream, ladies and gentlemen, dare to dream of a McNook in every backyard and a slave
child harem to every man, to every property owning in my anarcho capitalist future that we
are heading towards one step at a time. Dare to dream. Dare to dream.
It's going to be great. People need to realize that like,
no, go ahead and hit me. I was going to say the first time I realized that crime was okay
was when I learned of the TV license that you're supposed to pay to make the BBC run.
And everyone I've ever talked to, old and young, has never, ever said they pay it.
Because there's no way to enforce it because the BBC is not the government exactly.
And they don't, they can't have a warrant to go into your house. And even if they know that
you're watching TV, they can't really do anything. There was this video I watched where this guy
explained the ways the BBC has tried to scare people into paying it because they can't actually
do anything to enforce this rule. And they said back in the 50s that they had this van
that would drive around with a television detecting like antenna. And it could tell
when, what channel you're watching and where, in what room. And then they would come to your
front door and say, Hey, you, you're watching TV without a license. And people like believed it
because they didn't realize the technology is impossible and cannot exist, especially in the
fucking 50s. And there has never been, like the BBC has kept up the life forever, even though
it's completely obvious to everyone that they don't have these things. Nobody's ever seen them.
Nobody's ever been convicted using one. It's just like a blatant scare tactic, but they have to,
they have to keep it up because nobody fucking pays the thing. Old, old people do, I think.
They probably do because they don't know any better. But like, have you guys seen
those videos on YouTube? There's a million of them of like, like, Professor confronts
entire classroom, who like one of them like stole the test answers. And like, he's chewing out the
whole room. And he's like, if you don't turn that in, that computer actually had like state
secrets on it, you could be serving 20 to life. If you don't confess to me, like these are real
things that were said. And what I like, this is a popular video. It's like a professor who's like
working with the government or something on some contracts, his laptop was stolen or something.
He had like the test answers, which is probably why they took it. But he's like, it also has,
you know, state secrets. And he's like laying on this case that like, if you don't turn it in,
like first of all, we're changing the test. So those answers you had, they're useless. Second of
all, you know, you'll go to jail if you don't turn in the computer. I'm the only one on the planet
who can help you, blah, blah, blah. I just feel like they're lying. And what I want to see is a
follow up video of how no one came forward and nothing bad happened to anyone. Not that I support
crime. I don't like crime of people stealing stuff. I'm against that. But what I also hate are these
overly self righteous displays about like, Oh, you're all, I'm going to scare the whole class.
You guys are so bad. The American everybody feel bad for like a couple of people doing some fucked
up shit. And I don't know, I like people who are acting tough to get slapped down. It amuses me
greatly. And I would love to see that some follow ups where nothing bad happened to anyone. And it
was totally fine. Last semester, I sometimes crime is good. I had an auditorium class and
apparently there had been issues taking attendance the previous year. And so instead of tapping
your badge on the door, like you were supposed to and the building was designed for people are
just tapping their badge and then like leaving like they weren't going to class. Sure. And so
the teacher lied to us. Yeah, I didn't lie that no one believed and was not effectual at all.
But it was so outrageous that I was funny. So what so he explained to us the first day, like,
you know, that doesn't work. You don't tap your badge. What happens is every single day that you
come in here, there is a photo taken of the class. And we have a team of volunteer students who go
through that photo and count each face individually to make sure that you were here every day.
Did he say where the camera was? No, he didn't. He didn't. He did not. Okay. And he said that in
order to get your face in the system, because I guess it was AI like helped, you had to send
him a photo of your face head on. And no one did that. And it didn't matter. And it just
resulted to like a piece of white paper being passed around every class with your yeah. Yeah.
I mean, when it comes to college, the system that should be done is you don't have to show up to
class. But if you fail the test, you fail the test and fuck you. That's your problem. Yeah,
that's that's the system that should be done. You know, my school specifically is very,
very handholdy. And in fact, you know, just just before you go in further that I think
not only should that be the system, I think attendance should be held against the professor,
because if a bunch of people aren't in your class and they still pass,
you are irrelevant and they're paying you for nothing. I guess that's true.
Okay, I, I almost have like a weird opinion of this where it's like, I think that you basically
should be able to like be free to do like whatever you want. In the sense that it's like, there are
like, you know, if you if you miss these couple classes, you fail the class if you did. Okay,
yeah, okay, it makes sense. I understand why they do it. But on some level, I think like, okay,
the point of college is that it's like a service that you are paying for and you get things out of
it. So like if you just skip class, like why would you penalize that person? Because they're
already being penalized by wasting a lot of money and not getting anything from it. I'll tell you
why the answer to that is because college has been watered down and they now are officially
recognizing it as a kindergarten where they're forcing you to actually give a shit when actually
nobody of those people don't actually give a shit. Yeah, the real university is in the YouTube
tutorials now. It's literally true because that's where all information lies and everything you
need to be successful as a human being pretty much. Yeah, you can't get a teacher on the internet
that can talk to you one on one, but maybe in the future, like you almost have that.
What is your hairstyle? Yeah. I mean, obviously, there's utility to having a class with an actual
professor with actual skills. I got it understood, but you know what I'm saying.
Break the condition you need to do in VR chat. Don't fucking think that anything is right in
VR chat. What if there were VR chats where like people actually, you know, like you're there as
your cat girl, a big, big, titty anime avatar and you're the teacher. You're teaching your students
about, you know, Physics 101 that you're trying on. I mean, that's too low-level. The thing is
really just like the same as a stream. Like the talking and like asking questions and getting
specific answers to those questions is what a physical human teacher is as an informational
dump. They don't have to, like if you're on the internet and you ask a question,
Google is terrible. Google is the worst search engine ever made, all of them are,
because if you have a specific question, it doesn't use AI to really tell you anything.
There are a few websites where you can put a question in and humans can come and
like answer it like in Quora or like other things like that. But like AI does not do good
like with the teaching. So like as long as there's like an actual person on the other end,
it doesn't matter where you are. If it's in real life, it's more real and like that's one thing.
But online, it can also happen. Like I don't know why
like teaching streams don't exist. They don't really, they don't really exist.
There's a couple of them. Maybe they do, but like I haven't seen enough of them to be like
ASMR guy. Organized as like a real thing. There happens to be this one ASMR guy named Chicho,
who I passively follow, not particularly closely or anything. And he does like ASMR math streams.
He like is a teacher and just in his ASMR, he's like, Oh, today we're going to discuss like
quadratic functions that we're going to, you know, break it down. So it's really clear.
You know, I mean, it's kind of cool. I've never really paid that. I've never learned anything
from watching ASMR. I mean ASMR, I think it's like distracting, surely. It's gonna put you to sleep
literally. Yeah. So I mean, there's also sort of like a different like skill set that a teacher has
rather than even sites like that, because learning does not consist of you just continuously asking
questions over and over and over again. That can allow you to create the sort of art that you want,
but it doesn't necessarily allow you to grow. And what I mean by that is that a lot of the time,
teachers can provide things for you that you would not know to seek out or that you would not know
to ask or just information that you didn't know was even relevant. Like there can be sometimes
where you are given not just an assignment, but you are given advice or you were talking to someone
and they inform you of something that you would have not known about otherwise. Like
for instance, a big thing I know in the illustration department here is that you are told that you
should know other illustrators in the field. And that's the sort of thing where it's like,
you probably know a lot of Instagram people, right? You follow a lot of people on social media.
How many actual working illustrators, how many people actually making money doing what you
want to do? How many of those do you know? Most of the time the classes are like a zero.
Like there's no one that I can name at all. And that's not the sort of thing that you would think
yourself well-drying. Like, hmm, I wonder who's an illustrator that I can take inspiration from.
You kind of just like learn things through osmosis. And that's the sort of thing where it's like,
you were given insight into the field, you were given insight into job opportunities,
you were given insight into how to improve your craft in ways that you could not just, you know,
think to or know by Google search and things. You mean like, you mean like a personal connection
no, as in like you've talked to them and know who you are? Well, either or, either or. Because
the way I was thinking about that is like, getting, that like the teacher, like talking to like a
faceless username, asking a question in a live stream or some VR chat thing, some future teacher
thing is like one thing. But like, if the teacher knows who you are and they can see you in real
life, that is something that like they can get a sense of what sort of person you are, what sort of
like issues you may have, depending on the teacher and how much they give a shit, of course. But
like, I've gotten some like real good life advice from art teachers in the past that see that like,
I am not like the most like talkative and like, you know, socially active member of the class,
I don't usually ask the questions when I was in school. So they would like, bring me aside after
a class and like talk about stuff. And those moments would be very valuable for someone like me.
Those kind of unquantifiable things that you don't expect are definitely the main point of
But is that really worth tens of thousands of currency?
Who knows? That's up to the individual to decide. I'd rather just find a teacher and like meet them
outside of teaching, just like be friends with them. We have to go back to the Greek model of one
you know, wise older man personally tutoring one sexy little boy. That's right. This is the purest
form of love. And it's the purest form of education as well. And it's what I ascribe to
instead of instead of paying instead of paying for you know, years of college at hundreds of
thousand dollars in debt, you just pay with your with your with your with your with that sexuality
you weren't using anyway. So you might as well put it to good use. Makes sense to me.
Hey, I've got an update a life update. I hit Twitch partner the other day.
Did you make it? Did it work? Well, I hit all the thresholds that are needed. The application is
currently being processed. I don't know if I'm going, I mean, I assume I will. They're gonna
pull up every time you said the F word on stream. Oh, they're gonna give me my social media score
breakdown. Damn it, China. What have you done? I really close to making I got pretty close to
making partner that one month that I had Chris Chan on my on my Twitch. And I also did the
didgy debate on like the same week or the same month. And like, yeah, I also I was close to
hitting that 75 average viewers, but I think I got to like 71 or something like 60, 60. Thank God,
it's I mean, hopefully it'll be over. And like, I don't think you'll lose partner,
even if your views dip down. Once you make it, I don't actually know what the benefits like,
I'm sure you get more emojis. That's the main one. I know your streams more successful. I don't
think you just get more emotes. Don't you get ad revenue? You get a bigger share of
ad revenue. Yeah, yeah. Well, that's pretty good. Yeah, that's like the big thing. That might be
like a 5% difference. I'll be curious to hear if like it leads to like any substantial like
change in your Twitch revenue. Yeah, I mean, for me, since like I'm kind of like right at the
border, like I could have been affiliate or a partner at roughly the place that I'm at,
I'll be interested to see because I always track my income for these things month to
month. Anyway, like if there's a change, you know, I don't know, we'll fucking see if that
if that amounts to anything, or if I get more viewers, or like maybe now that I'll be partner,
hopefully, like it'll put me out more recommendations and more people see. I don't know. I don't
know. Maybe. Hi guys, I've carved more space for myself underneath of a thumb of San Francisco
Tech Bros. I can't wait to sell my personality more online. That's it's good. I mean, that's the
job, man. That's the job. You just literally you just debunked every YouTuber on the planet and
every online content creator who exists. In fact, every book writer is just literally just selling
their fucking personality and like their hard one knowledge to the fucking ignorant masses,
like literally like a fucking whore, like a fucking whore. It's exactly what every book
writer in history is. Every, you know, the guys who write the Bible, you know what they say,
whores are better than others. Sad but true. You hate to see it.
Sad, but you hate to see it. You hate to see it. I mean, Christ taught us that whores are cool now,
so that's the good news. He did. I remember when he did that.
We should remake the Bible, but Jesus is like a vlogger and he like assembly, like he's like the
PCP. He like assembles a bunch of content creators. We should remake the Bible, but Jesus is a woman
of color. That's he's channel terminated. That was him getting crucified. Yeah, right, right.
That was the big, the big F in chat, as it's known in the book. And then, you know,
three days later, his account gets restored, but he kind of, he uploads some weird vlogs,
like you don't really understand it. The way in Bibles where they have like the extremely
flowery like first letter of the sentence, but just one page is a huge big F. Yeah.
Oh, it's like there's this really like finely detailed H and then TTP slash and then just a
really long link in that one episode of SpongeBob where SpongeBob is writing the essay to pass
voting school or whatever. Didn't he draw like it's him like, yes, yes. And he spends like an
hour and it's just a big W. I learned in voting school is was it a T. It's just just writes the
Oh, it was the. Okay. I was hoping it'd be a W. So that could be used for epic SpongeBob.
W memes like here, bro. You would see it everywhere by now if it was a W.
You're absolutely like every other SpongeBob's still, you know, ever produced. Let me see. Hey,
a totally other subject. I was just going to say I, in my personal life update, I have finished
finally Star Trek, the original series, and I'm on to Voyager now. And I'm so excited this piece
of media from the 1970s. 1960s as it would have it. But I'm sorry. That's actually based,
actually. Maybe it's in the 70s. I don't know. No, Voyager is from like the 90s. Well, the original
series. The original series is from the 60s. Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, it was great. Really good.
Very excited to continue consuming media in this way. And yeah, it feels good. We'll give updates.
Yeah. I'll tell you, okay, the one thing, guys, I gotta tell you, a big problematic moment.
I've watched, you know, three full Star Trek series now. It's been all male captains. Well,
I mean, the Cisco Star is a commander, but it becomes a captain in Voyager. Janeway is the
only one I've seen so far who at any moment doubted herself and her leadership capabilities.
Is it a coincidence she's the woman captain? I don't know.
She's a pretty seasoned captain. Why would they choose to write this into her narrative?
Little suss, little suss, sexism in the writer's room? I hope not. Impossible. You
can't be racist and work on television shows. People can't be racist and sexist at the same time.
It doesn't add up. Yeah, that's, anyway, didn't matter. She's a good captain. She's all right.
Media to consume. Please consume the Lord of Ghost comic. Give and take dot sign.
Yeah, please. Lord of Ghost chapter two. It's another fucking masterpiece.
God, I love Lord of Ghost comic. When chapter three, Gib, give me more to consume.
I really like your shit. Thank you. I bring it up mostly to plug, but also because it is
something that I have sort of like slowed down quite a lot on working on. And I don't know whether,
like, it's a good thing that I don't feel bad about it. Like, I don't feel worried that I'm
losing pace. I just sort of stopped for a bit because I felt like it. And I felt okay.
And usually I would expect myself to be like panicking, like, oh, no,
deadlines that I set for myself are not going to be met. Lol, damn, kill myself. But I feel
all right. I feel like this was a break I needed to take. And I'm going to get back to it. But like,
do you ever feel that like you're taking a break and it doesn't feel like a bad thing?
Yes, because I literally never. No, okay, hippo, I'm totally with you. That is the sort of thing
where if you don't have a functioning brain, then you can kind of work yourself. I feel like I've
said this a thousand times before, go to munchuscripts.tumblr.com. If you think that your time
is always work time and it's always potential work time, then all breaks will feel like you are
wasting time that you could be spending. But as long as you are intentional and you like
plan to like, you know what, I'm kind of not feeling it right now, I'm going to take a break
and then you actually take a break and don't just, you know, have the Lord of Ghost, you know,
up in your Photoshop file and then watch YouTube for a little while, then click back to it and
then you draw like a couple more lines and click back to YouTube and you just waste your time that
way. It's great. I played Civ 5 for like six hours, like a couple days ago. I just got home from
school and I thought, you know what, I haven't played video games in a really long time. I'm
going to play a video game, played a video game and it was great. It was great. And I just,
that's the sort of thing where it's like, if I were thinking to myself, okay, all right,
I have stuff I have to do, I have to get it done and I have to do my homework, but I really want to
play Civ 5. I'm going to play a little bit of Civ 5 and then I'll do a little bit of work and then
Munchy, it sounds so good to be mentally healthy. Yeah, I know. I can't even imagine.
Well, it's almost like everyone can be mentally helpful, healthy if they just, you know, try
at all and put any thought into the actions that they're doing and just like reflect upon their
life and you know, just like set out rules for themselves and like have like a moral or like
intellectual standard that they keep themselves to and it's all, and everyone's like about the
same intelligence is about just about, you know, trying really at all. None of us would know anything
about that. That's, you know, it's, it was, it was weird though because it was like the first time
that I've been okay with taking a break. It wasn't even really a plan break. I just was not feeling
it. So I stopped for a bit and I played some video games. I watched YouTube and then I made,
oh no, it wasn't that. I finished the Sangetsuno Lion anime and read the manga, which is really good
and is definitely on par with the show. If you get to the end of the show and you want more,
definitely continue reading. Great manga, great, you know, art and stuff, but it's ongoing. So
it sort of stops and that after that I was like, dude, I don't know what to do, but then I got like
a block of wood and I made a shogi piece. I talked about this a bit. I have a picture now. I've sanded
it down. It looks really nice. I'm thinking of, of like maybe etching into it and then doing a
little image and then like painting it gold or white or something. Make like a pump like face,
like a little pumpkin head. Possible. That'd be cool. Not like the pumpkin outline, but like just
like the face, like a jack-o'-lantern face. I took a break for the purpose of being productive
in that when I hit the point where I was like, okay, finale's coming up for Slime and Punishment,
I was like, I'm not going to do anymore. I'm going to go back. I'm going to finish the vapor
scripts, which I finally did this past week. I got the last one done. All the guest artists
have their scripts now. So my work is done. Amazing. I felt really terrible while I was
taking the break because I felt like it was way too long. Because Writing the Vapors is like an
emotionally horrifying experience for me. As I talk about on the patreon.com slash ben saint,
the new monthly podcast, I went, I like had revelations about the topic of like, why is
Writing Vapors hard? Like while I was recording that. That's great stuff. That's cool. That's cool
to have moments like that. You should link it for us so we can listen to it for free and other
people have to pay for it. I guess I can do that just for you guys. I can do it guilt-free because
fair. I forget where I was going. Wait, can I just like post the, if I post the patreon link here,
you won't be able to see it, right? Even if I want to share with you guys.
Correct. We would need like, like if it's like a YouTube uploader, if it's on patreon we would
have to. I guess maybe I can just upload the raw audio. I mean, you certainly could. You
don't have to, but I mean, I'm curious. I will, I will figure out a way to let you guys hear it.
Okay. And the first one too, I guess. I was going to say on the subject of taking a break, I am going
on vacation tomorrow for like 11 days or whatever, going to Hawaii. And so that is indeed the first
like big, I mean, I spent like literally two days of the parents. So that's a weekend. That is one
weekend that I don't think that really counts as much of a vacation. Wait, our parents? Wait,
where are you going on vacation? Hawaii to see Michelle's folks. Okay. Okay. So that, I mean,
that's, I mean, we're going to be there for like a good solid like nine days of chilling. So that's
going to be an actual vacation that I'm very much looking forward to. What's the vacation?
Fun? I mean, we like had wanted to see my like her parents for a while and like a while back, we
haven't been there for a while to see her folks. And like they just said like, hey, you know,
like we will pay for you guys to come out like to fly out sometimes like let us know when's good.
And we were just like, let's pick a time that like fits into our schedule reasonably well. So
like they they're paying for the flight, which is very generous. And we're just going to go hang out
for several days. And then come back and continue life in beautiful sunny Cincinnati, Ohio. And so
yeah, I mean, there's no real occasion, but it'll actually be like a nice break. And you'll get to
see your folks and all that stuff. But like this happens to coincide obviously with all my channels
being hacked. And one of the worst things about that on the subject of, you know, holding yourself
to a deadline and whatnot is I had previously promised my patrons that I would get a big video
out during the month of January. It is now past the month of January. And I must admit I was had
had my head to the grindstone, working real hard to get it done, like my next big Nate video on
BGE. But when like the 22nd, the 23rd rolled around, and I discovered that my channels were
literally stolen. And I could not post them. I must admit, it just deflated me. And I was like,
well, I guess I'm just gonna not work on this as much because you know, dealing with some
shit right now. So you'd be able to upload to your patrons and you'd be able to upload as soon
as you got back or like whenever this resolved. Well, that's true. Like the video is not done
editing. It's going to be at least several more days of editing because I just was fucked up about
not being able to release it like on time. Like I could have probably finished it if I had had my
head to the fucking grindstone. But like for I had to deal with all these channels, you know,
there's work involved with that and stuff. But like it is, I mean, consider it a failure. I consider
it a failure. But it was due to circumstances that like, I don't know. I feel like that's totally
fair. Like even if you would put your nose to the grindstone, you got the video finished,
you still might have had to wait two weeks at this point to get it up. So like you can take time.
It would have been done, but like I can, I think it's not something to like work yourself up about
like, oh, I failed. Like this was out of your control. I mean, you know, people, my patrons are
the only people to the opinions I really care about on this particular subject because they're
the only ones I owe anything to. Actually it's not out of your control. It's entirely your fault.
Lol, die. I mean, you know, in a way, yes, in a way, you know, in the same way that like if you
get gunned down the street in a bad neighborhood, why are you in that bad neighborhood? I was in
the bad neighborhood of, you know, the internet and of, you know, sponsorship deals that I should
never have gone into. So that's, that's, that's on me. I don't know. I guess I just hope that my
patrons are a little bit understanding and they don't, you know, all of it. I mean, I suspect
they will, but like, I mean, if it was me, I have this thing in my head where it's like, well, I
mean, you didn't do what you said you were going to do. I mean, you know, you could have done it anyway.
So I mean, I can't blame people if they feel that way. I feel like like patrons specifically
would, would understand. Like random viewers, I'm not here to beg or anything promised it to
random viewers. They might like on serve or whatever, but like patrons care more. And so like
something like this happening that probably like really supportive. I mean, I would hope. I hope
so. And I mean, I do have a we Agua that's ready. It's been ready. It's just that my channel got
stolen. So I have one thing to release as soon as it comes. You're back on. This is that last one
that is the final way. Wait, you're not doing any more we Aguas ever? No, well, okay. That's not
what I'm trying. I'm trying like for now. This is the last of I'm calling it season three. Like,
I might pick it up again later, but like for now, the plans just work on the big videos and maybe
a we Agua if I feel like it, that's that's awesome. Yeah, I mean, I hope so. It'll just
hopefully make time for big videos and do stuff like that. But like, I was hoping to start off.
Well, there's been a little bit of a, you know, derailing of the plan. But okay, whatever, enough
about that. I just thought I'd throw that out there because it's like, I'm okay. What I was
going to say, the last thing on that is just like, I'm feeling good that like what I'm going to
Hawaii, I will just be tuned out of all this shit. Although I actually am going to call in for the
PCP episode from Hawaii. I'm going to bring a mic with me to do it. So I don't know, that'll be fun.
Hopefully have things to discuss. But like, I'm going to go as much as saying I'm going to use
my body, I'm going to go learn to surf. I'm going to go do that, which I've been, I mean, look over
at my fucking point break poster, and I'm just filled my eyes fill with tears at the sheer joy
of being a man on the ocean connecting with real life and doing real life things.
Yes. And so I'm just like, and you know, I'm hoping while I'm out, maybe I'll just get that call
from the boys at YouTube and they'll say, Nate, happy vacation, buddy. Here's your channel back.
We took care of it while you were off doing other things. And oh, won't that be nice. And
hopefully all the channels will be restored, but I'm going to be paying attention and all that
stuff. So I've excused myself for this like 10 day block of time to just not worry about all this
stuff. I worry about everything else when I'm back. And if I like, I definitely am afflicted with,
I am unable to stop thinking about all the things I have to do all the time. But when I block out
specifically, like a big chunk of time like this, when I won't be doing anything, I think this will
be a very, very helpful, recuperative block of time. So I don't know. That's it. Sick.
What's next? I got one like, bit of news, but it's not much. I put a new video on the hypocrite
channel. Oh, yeah. It's just a little five minute rant. And I was happy to see that the people
who have subscribed are still there, like very, very happy to see. Everyone was excited to see
that. Yeah. I was just really nice to like, I was expecting people to be like, what the fuck,
lol, die. I'm mad at you for uploading content. It's only a five minute rant and there's no
video editing. What the fuck? I care about standards, says the YouTube commenter. Redman is
looking jacked. Oh yeah, he's so angry about video games. It makes his blood boil. And he goes,
gear a second. You know what you're going to have to do? Yeah, I want you to go check that out.
Because I have like, banished YouTube forever. I've blocked it on my desktop and on my phone
and on my laptop and it's like, gone and I can't access it. The only way I can access it is if I
go to the school library. So whenever you, when any of you upload a video that's good, DM me and
then I'll go to the school library to watch it. Okay, we'll do. I'll keep you posted. I thought
you said like, completely blocking out something. It just doesn't work. Or do you actually feel like
YouTube has no value anymore? And so that's easy to do. I actually feel like it has no value and
it's easy to do. Yeah, I feel like that sometimes as well. Like I still enjoy looking at a couple
things, but it is sort of like the same video I've seen a few weeks ago. Well, I've got to be
fully redpilled on the YouTube. I've taken the full red YouTube pill, which is like 99%, probably
more than that, is just all people restating opinion that's the same as everyone else about
current event. That's like the vast majority of what it is. And in terms of like actually
insightful commentary, it's very rare. And but you know what? I aspire to be one of those people
that people actually be like, Oh, good. Thank God in the sea of garbage, a best guy ever upload,
I can count on this being at least interesting, at least something I haven't consumed a thousand
times before. I mean, if you're not doing that on YouTube, what's even the fucking point? Be your own
boss in a job saying the same thing as everybody else? How is that any better than just being a
corporate cog of some company where you make way more money and have actual job security?
Explain to me why that's a better job. You can't do it. So, you know, fuck it, man,
make good content or don't do it at all, or have it be a hobby. I guess if you want to do that,
that's fine too. Then do whatever the fuck you want. So much of YouTube is just like repeating
things like you're just saying, like not even just like repeating what other YouTubers have said,
but like reading a book and then boiling down that book to its like pure essence,
so you get none of the nuance and you get none of the actual interesting tidbits. So it's just like,
here's, here, I read a book, I'm just going to like repeat what the book said, but like worse
and like way like less insightful, you know, that's just what I'm going to do.
I'll just make, here's a little pitch, here's a little pitch about some, a video that I consider
worthwhile and I think it's why people like it. Like my, my smash videos, I do actual research
when I'm making one of those to find out like every appearance of a character.
Most people will have not know at least some of that. If you watch those, they're short,
they're punchy, they're hopefully funny and like they, I like to think at least they're actually
both interesting and amusing for people because I put a lot of fucking work into getting everything
I can and cramming in like every meme about that character. It's like a, I try to make it a full
like 360, everything you think about this character is all in one place and it's telling the story
of like a progression of something that would exist nowhere else. Like no one else has boiled
down the complete history of Simon Belmont, the character better than my sign of the cross video
about Simon Belmont getting into smash. In my humble opinion, it's, it's, it's making the world
like a better place. There's a thing here that did not exist anywhere else, except for I guess
a fucking like two hour history of Castlevania video, but you know what? I'm delivering it better
and faster and smarter. So fuck you, watch Mojo or whoever. I don't know. To me, that should be like
the bare minimum of what makes like actually worthwhile content. Now I consume lots of trash
content on YouTube too, absolutely true, but there's a distinction to be made and I know what
side of that equation I want to be on long term. Here's the thing about like people using YouTube
as background or is quote unquote, stop doing that. That's fine. It's, it's, it is a stupid idea
because there is music that you could listen to instead music on Spotify or YouTube. If you're on
YouTube, you're likely to get distracted. But if you're on Spotify, it's just music or band camp
or whatever. I made a tweet a while ago saying, give me a band, I will go through their entire
discography and I will do that while I'm drawing and I've gotten through, I mean the band I'm on
at the moment is Uriah Heap and they have like 70 albums, so there's a lot of stuff. But the thing
that's great about music is that it doesn't have to be good music and it doesn't have to be music
you like, it just needs to be background noise, just like a YouTube video. You don't care about
what is happening in the YouTube video, you don't care if it's a good video or a bad video, but
you get so much more out of music than people talking when you're not listening to it that hard.
So it's like, if you have like hundreds, like there's so many replies to that tweet, everybody
wants you to listen to their favorite band and nobody ever listens to bands ever. I never listen
to music when people recommend it to me. But through this tweet and this desire to like replace
background noise from YouTube, I've listened to so much stuff and it's just, it's great. It's
really good. That's good. That's good. I was more productive when I was listening to music than
when I would put on like background noise YouTube videos like speedruns and stuff. Because you're
always going to switch back over to the YouTube video. You're always going to have that over.
ASMR Chads unite literally worthless trash content that's just regurgitated to create
new white noise that it's the most intellectual content for background noise there is.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Part of the reason why, again, viewers read Munchie scripts, because I talk about all this
extensively and I'm probably going to post there more than I'm going to be on the podcast.
Like I say that like, you know, you can't block out things completely. But the reasons I gave is
just because like for some things, like, you know, I'm sure a lot of people are like really
addicted to YouTube, like how I was. And a lot of people like don't think as radically as we made
that, you know, it's all shit. It's all bad. Like don't even watch it. I'm sure a lot of people
have like a lot of joy that comes from YouTube. I'm sure a lot of people have like, you know, like,
oh, I really want to tune in to see this or subscribe. So like, like line just like cutting
out something completely is just going to like cause more problems because you're lying to yourself.
If you're as honest with yourself as I have tried to be and I've said to myself and I've
analyzed, hmm, does YouTube give me any joy? No. Okay. All right. Great. Okay. I don't need it
anymore at all then. And so that's fair enough. I think that they're like Marie Kondo speaking
of sparking joy. Yes, it's true. Throw away everything that doesn't give true joy. There are
creators who I would drop everything to go watch. For example, Twin Perfect uploading this gigantic
four and a half hour video on, you know, Twin Peaks season three and the whole thing. I know
that that video which took over a year to make is worth watching. I know it and that's why I'm
setting aside time to watch Twin Peaks so that I can go consume this media. And yes, it's just
going to be a breakdown, but it will also be an exercise in further understanding a media piece
that I would think is worth spending some time to digest anyway. So I would absolutely not agree
that it's all trash, but you do have to sort through the trash to find the good. And I would
totally agree. There's very little actually good. Yeah, like specifically, like, watch the challenge
you want to watch and subscribe from everybody that doesn't bring you joy every single time,
but like specifically for like if you're going to YouTube bar, turn off autoplay. If you're going
to YouTube for background noise, there's better things. There's way better things. And if you're
making a calculation that like by having YouTube, maybe there are once in a blue moon an actually
good video, but you know that you're wasting hours every day. So it's just not worth it. That's fine.
That's a totally fair calculation to make to, you know, turn it off. Yeah, fair enough, fair
enough. Guys, voicemails, voicemails, what do you say? I got shit I wanted to talk about.
Y'all are so fucking boring, though. You just keep going. What are we even talking about? YouTube,
fuck it. Say your stuff then. Amuse me then, Ben. Amuse me. Okay, well, get ready for disappointment.
I'm ready. Okay, scramble for my notes. Tomorrow, Iowa caucuses. Today's the Super Bowl. I don't
give a fuck. Tomorrow, the Iowa caucuses and I'm fucking high. Well, boring, Ben. This sucks so bad.
Why are we going to the topic? It fucking sucks so bad. Wow, it's terrible. Is that relative to when
they hear this or like relative to what's important? No, it is tomorrow for us. It will have already
happened when the episode comes out. Wow, great. This is really great podcast content. I don't know
if you're being sarcastic or not, Munchy. Just explain the joke to me. I think now he is being
sarcastic at this point. Yes. Okay, sick. Whatever. Fuck you. Okay, I'm going to hide from a man,
Bernie. I mean, the difference now is that it's not just idle talk about like political boys
going to be better. Now it's like, okay, it actually matters. The voting starts fucking tomorrow.
Yeah. I'm certainly interested to see where it's going to go. This does in fact impact our lives,
at least a little bit. It does. Bernie's been, Bernie's been surging lately. He's like,
top Biden in a lot of polls. Yeah, I don't know. Pretty good. The real challenge is,
will Ben have the moral fortitude to be gracious and victory? No. I hate my enemies.
Yeah, that's fair. Okay, whatever. That's the thing. I went clubbing on Saturday.
I got thrown out of the club. How'd it go?
I was, I mean, I guess, Kazzy's friend is like a bar promoter, and she was like,
hey, everybody come out to this club with me. And I got the second hand invite and I was like,
okay. Word. I mean, the long story short is we hung out at the bar and then they were like a dance
floor like opened up downstairs and I was down there, you know, drinking white cloth seltzers,
being a cool guy. No doubt. I guess I decided it would be funny or I felt what I felt like doing
was like sitting down on the floor in front of the bar, right? In hindsight, I can understand why
they wouldn't want me doing that. But mercilessly, they descended upon me, like pick me up, like
carried me out of the fucking building and just like sat me down and outside and were like,
you're kicked out. And I'm like, what, can I rectify my behavior? Not one word of warning,
you're not getting back in. So I wait in line again, like I wait, I get back in line to try and
like just wait my way back to the front to like be like, hey, guys, sorry about the whole thing,
promise I won't do that again. But like my shit, so can I just get back in? And I'm waiting in line
in these two like Arab guys, they turn, I start talking to them about Naruto, they both love
Naruto. And I'm just like, yeah, whatever, I guess this will, I'm out here in my t-shirt in like
freezing cold weather. I guess this will pass the time while I wait for the line for to get back
in. But it's no use, they're like, you got kicked out, you were dipped up, no, I heard word, word
from the top down is that this guy is trouble. He's not getting anywhere near our establishment.
So I had to finally beg them like, put my debit card, please just give me my debit card. And they
did. And then we all, we all left, we left and it was, fuck those guys. But like, yeah, they have,
they had like the two guys, one on each side, like grabbing my shoulders, like physically moving,
and I'm just like, okay, I'm, I like went limp. I went like, I'm just, I'll just let destiny
take me wherever, wherever it needs to take me. I'm not going to fight it. So like, I mean, were
you like, you know, drunk or like making a scene? I was kind of drunk. I don't think I was making a
scene. I just, I sat down in front of the bar. And probably that is offensive to them because
they want, I was probably like, someone might have been considering going up to the bar and
getting a drink and be like, there's like a guy sitting in front of it. Like, I do understand
the problem. I do. Seems like a disproportionate reaction. It's, I was a little surprised.
Cassie was a little surprised. She like, she like came out and found me in line and was like,
what the fuck? Why did they kick you out? I'm like, I, I guess I was sitting down and we were just
like, well, fuck it. I guess we're leaving. And that's what happened. Clubbing is well munchy.
No, I did not. No, he got, he couldn't, it was, it's 21, 21 plus. Oh, 21. That's right. I forgot.
Yeah. All the, that's fun. All the, all the other, it was all friends of this, of this
Cassie's roommate person. Yeah. There was only one, there was one that I talked to and seemed
nice, but then she had a boyfriend, which I think should be illegal. But that's, that's
for another, that's for another day. I'm like that. That's fucked up. Yeah. It was pretty fucked up.
I don't, if she, if she has a boyfriend, why was she not wearing the veil?
That's exactly what I'm saying. Why was she not accompanied by at least one adult male
at least. For Pete's sake. For Pete's sake. It's shameful. Don't worry. Brannis gonna get
Sharia Laan soon. I'm looking forward to it. All my favorite things. Okay. I guess I'm done.
Okay. Well, I'm glad to hear it. Thank you very much. Look, I just want to keep everyone
updated on my, on my, my day to day, on my goings on. That's why I'm here. I'm on this podcast
to maintain a presence and like have been like talk about my life with a, with people that want
to hear it. That's what I'm here to maintain my profile. It's working. Yeah. You know what the
best podcast content is? It's not like a, it's not like a conversation between two people,
like, you know, contributing their like personalities to create like a new thing,
a conversation. It's just like rapid fire. Like, hello, it's me. I'm standing up now.
Oh, wow. This ride today. Huh? All right. You sit back down. Sorry. Hey, it's me,
the next guy. I also have like the exact same life. What do, what do personal
anecdotes from podcasters live? What place does such things have on a podcast?
Indeed. Yeah. This is the question. Can't, can't imagine. I like the discussions.
Okay. I think they were interesting. Fuck you. No. Pointless. I'm glad to hear it. I'm, I'm
invested in the Ben Saga of, I don't know, uh, this, this could be a segment. This could be a
segment of the, the, the Ben segment, the bit, like, like, what, like, what stupid, what stupid
thing did Ben do and get in trouble for it? Ben got, Ben got drunk and something happened.
It has been, has been a disproportionate amount of that lately.
Okay. What could it mean? Let's get to our voicemails now. We've got,
we've got them all lined up. They're ready to go. And I think, uh, wait,
here. Yes. Ready. Yeah. Okay. You guys got yours as well.
Yeah. By the way, so, okay. Of course, this is the voicemails speak pipe link down below in
the description. Leave us your voicemails. We will review them and play the good ones on the show.
And was there any disclaimer I was going to make? No, guess not. Okay. All right. Let's go right
into them. Let's start with number 00 Radcon Kickstarter date. Let's already have to say
one, two, three, go. Serious Inquiry lads. The Kickstarter ends on such a whack date.
Like, could you extend it a couple of days? Maybe maybe extend it to like that next Friday
or that next Saturday? I think it'd be. I agree that it ending on a Tuesday is kind of bad planning,
but I don't think there's anything we can do about it now. I, I, you know, in regard,
response to this, I did look into it to see if it could be changed. Anyway,
it cannot be changed based on Kickstarter or anything like that. It's locked in once you decide,
but the good news is just figure it out. Just fucking get together. And that's the good news.
Fortunately, you know, you can just go fuck yourself and deal with it. Yeah. That's, I feel
concerned slash watch and alert sites. It's radiation. Modern insight has an RBL value set by
in ETC.com software, which is the radiation background level. Radcon minus one equals RBL.
Radcon two equals rising. Radcon three equals elevated. Radcon four concern slash watch.
Hmm. Is this, uh, this must be like some spectrum for. When you search Radcon four,
that's what pops up. I want to know more. I want to know more. Um, all right,
next one. Let's just move right along here. We've got a monkey is calling in with another
voicemail. Here we have the same on the count of three combination of me and monkey. That's
right. I'm looking forward to hearing from him again. Uh, okay. Here we go. One, two, three, go.
So I'm really excited about the newest member of the PCP, Brad, um, Brad Garlinghouse.
Honestly, I've been following his content for years and I always thought he'd be a great fit
in the PCP. And I was just wondering how, uh, how this might affect Radcon because, um,
you know, I'd really like to see, even though, even though he's new, you know, maybe you guys
haven't met in person yet, but like, I'd like to see him at Radcon four. I'm wondering if we can get
a stretch call to make this happen. You know, maybe, maybe even, um, maybe make it Bradcon four.
I think, I think that would be a killer. All right. Um, and, uh, do you guys accept donations
and ripple? Cause that's the only currency I have now. Um, thanks. Can't, can't blame you.
It's going to the moon is what I hear. It's exploding. It's exploding in all directions.
Well, tell you what, monkey, uh, surprise announcement guys, we even have, in fact,
got Brad Garlinghouse confirmed to do a lecture at Radcon four in the flesh. He will be there.
Uh, at least, you know, we've been informed it's Brad. Uh, he may be replaced by a stunt double.
Finally. No, don't worry about that. It's going to be Brad. He's going to be there publicly to
an audience about the benefits of ripple. That's what we get. Here it is, boys. New stretch call.
This is real. Look on the website. It's there now for a new stretch call independent of all
the other stuff at $15,000. Brad Garlinghouse will do a paid appearance at Radcon four. He will be
there in the flesh. We guarantee it. You're going to be excited. Check the Kickstarter. We'll have
some more details there, but, uh, we are pushing about 13 K right now. So that's not, that's not
too K away. It's not, not, not too ridiculous. They are not too far by the time they hear this,
it's going to be like, uh, you're going to have like eight days left or eight, wait, nine, 10,
no, eight days, eight days or so. Should be plenty of time. So let's, let's get it, sis.
Let's get Brad at Radcon for, uh, Brad hashtag Brad at Rad.
Oh yeah. That's good. That's good. Uh, all right. That's real. Well, okay. Good news.
I think man is here to call in possibly calling in right now. Let's, let's give him the floor.
Here we go on the count of three. One, two, three, go.
Attention all Nate heads. Best guy ever needs your help to get his channels back and banish
the evil Brad Garling house back to the shadow realms of this, but he needs your credit card.
No, the three digits on the back and the expiration month and year.
Don't forget that you got to hurry. His subscriber count is falling down into the darkness.
Hmm. Hmm. I mean, there you go. Please give me your money. Would really appreciate that.
Brad, Brad G is the financial genius. You just need his, you need their credit card. I mean,
you're kind of, you're not going to spend it or anything. You just like need them.
Like I think that's like a math equation you can do if you like you add all of them and
like divide them by amount of like entries and you can get like a password to access your
category. Right. Right. No doubt. No doubt. All right. Let's go right on to our next one. We've
got Aldorn. Oh, no, sorry. What's a teen CP? What's a teen CP? All right. Let's find out.
The count of three. One, two, three, go. Hey, PCP. Long time listener. First time caller.
I'm black. I'm 15. I live in Massachusetts. I'm an eight head. All this information matters.
Because I lost my virginity and it's crazy because did you set 14 year olds could do it?
So I thought to myself, why can't I? And I did. Thoughts and opinions on the Grammys slash
Oscars and teen preferences. No joke. This is the worst voicemail we've ever gotten. No, no.
Ooh, an eight head, an African American. I mean, it started bad and it just got worse from there.
Yeah, that's too bad. What's your opinion about me losing my virginity?
I think that God doesn't smile upon it and neither do I. Let's move on to our next call.
All right, here we go. Next one. We got Aldorn is next on the count of three. Let's
blue Aldorn. One, two, three, go. Hey guys, I have a huge fucking problem. So huge, in fact,
that it could be considered the biggest problem in the universe. That being how much I love
Munchie and hate discord. I tried endless war. I swear to God, I gave it a fair shot,
but it just sucks shit so bad. With that in mind, I absolutely require more Munchie content.
Those episodes of stealing your dad, for example, would go a long way towards filling
the hole in my heart. But it seems like that's the sort of thing that will eventually happen.
And I just need to be patient for what I'm more concerned about is a little comic by the name of
Investigator. Did this thing ever materialize? I searched for it, but all I could find was a
Steam game by the same name. And that game looks fun, but it also doesn't seem like it was made
by Munchie. So where the fuck is Investigator? Please tell me it wasn't just fucking a thing.
This guy's out of the loop. Yeah, wow. Welcome to like 2017. I sort of resented because like, yeah,
you've said like many times like, yeah, that project is not, I'm not working on it anymore.
So like, where does this guy get off? Another public source announcement. Okay, but on the
positive side, everyone, Munchie, we have previously instigated and continue to encourage
a social media campaign to harass you on all mediums to release stealing your dad and whatever
other shit. Release those emails. Release it. Release the dads. We need them. You know what?
Actually, I've had a change of heart. You know, I'm going to do them right now. Wow,
this has accomplished a whole lot, guys. Well, I thought they were done and you were just waiting
to release them for no reason. Why would you think that? No, no. Ethan, Ethan's editing them for me
like a good boy and he still has it. Is he really being a good boy? I said on like the last BGP that
like Ethan is editing the stealing your dads. I am so clued in to the state of Munchie's content
right now. Okay, I guess I was out of the loop. Didn't you say the first two are edited? It's
the last one that's still waiting? No, he's doing like an intro for them. So I like technically
the videos themselves, I guess, are done, but he's waiting for an intro. And you know,
people may say to themselves, ah, but I don't care about the intro. I just want it to be released.
But I mean, I don't know. Ethan wants there to be an intro. I want there to be an intro.
I think it'd be cool. I owe you nothing. There's no reason for me to release them right now.
There's no reason for me to do that. I have no incentive to do so. Well, the social media campaign.
Hashtag finish the intro. Can we have them finished by Radcon 4 so we can have like
Radcon 4 viewing of Radcon 3 content? Yeah, sure, I guess so. I don't know, maybe.
Hey, somewhat unrelated, what's the status of the RFCK lecture?
Oh, that can literally just be released, can't it? I'm pretty sure. Is it done?
Well, no. Are you kidding me? No, Connor and Ethan like extensively talked about how they
wanted to edit it. They're probably working on it then. Okay. Oh, God, you guys don't know? Oh,
Jesus, I can tell nothing's been done. Well, how would I know? You can just tell.
Probably nothing has been done. I don't know. Who's in charge? What's it matter? It will come out
when it comes out. Oh, God, that's a nightmare of an attitude. Okay, anyway, let's just move on.
You know what? Everyone's just waiting tooth and nail to wait for this lecture to come out.
Everyone's just on the edge of their seats. I'm going to stop giving a shit eventually,
Munchy. That's why you get it done as fast as possible. No, it's fine. Why do you give a
shit right now? It's not out yet. The lecture would be better. The lecture would be better.
That question doesn't deserve a response. The lecture would be better with visual cues
and imagery added to show what we're talking about. It's worth it, obviously. This has to
be a meme. Okay, this guy. Oh, he tried Endless War, but where's the Munchy content? That's what
is the Munchy content. If he actually liked me, then he would be in Endless War.
Kind of. His grouping seems to be with Discord specifically. I don't know what that means.
I mean, if Endless War is not his bag, that's fine. I mean, we're all heartbroken about no
investigator, right? But you got to move on. Everyone's heartbroken that they have heard a
project name before and they knew that a piece of art was going to happen, that something was
going to happen, and then it didn't happen. Oh, I'm going to really mourn that.
It's really strange. Oh my God, Munchy. You didn't hype the project up for little years.
It's not about before the investigator, right? Munchy was just a guy who occasionally drew
some pony art and avatars, and he was funny. Now that Munchy is clearly doing things,
it doesn't matter. It was just exciting that Munchy was doing a project that was going to
be a creative thing. Endless War is way cooler than Investigator could ever be.
Unless you don't like Endless War. I mean, I think that Endless War is cool.
I can understand if comics are more someone's bag than a free MMORPG playable inside of Discord.
Just read the Lord of Ghosts. This is an Endless War comic.
Yeah. Just write Investigator within the confines of the Lord of Ghosts comic.
Dude, just release Investigator as a zine. Oh, there we go. Well, I can just outsource all the
imaging for it. That one person that just approached us at the cafeteria bit, and I can just
like, hey, dude, do you want to write for my zine? You want to draw for my zine, dude?
Oh, yeah, perfect. I remember that. Damn it, I said I got another voicemail here.
All right, next voicemail. This one. Yeah, fine. Okay. Okay, cool. You should be able
to solve this. All right, put on your thinking caps, people, and click on this on three. One,
two, three, go. If a crab and a half weigh a pound and a half, and the half crab weighs half as much
again as the whole crab, what do half of the whole crab and the whole of the half crab weigh?
Oh my god, just cut that out. Just wait, he said one crab, I don't know.
Well, he said that the half crab weighs half and again. So, does that mean that the half of a
crab weighs 1.5 times as much as the whole crab? Right, do I have that right?
I'm not going to lie. I could not follow all those words. I'm just lost. Okay, well,
unless he misspoke there. It equals voicemail. If the half crab weighs half and again as much
as the whole crab, then the half crab weighs 1.5 times. So, wait, so it's a pound and a half divided
by five, and then times two would be the half crab. No, times three would be the half crab.
Ben, tell me how about how you have a degree. Hold on. Hold on, I'm going to do it. I'm going
to do it. I'm almost there. Okay. 1.5 divided by five times three. Wait, what? No, hold on.
1.5 divided by five. Yeah, times, okay. The half, the half crab, wait, the half of the
whole crab weighs 0.9 pounds and the whole of the half crab, no. Wait, wait, what? The whole of the
half crab. I don't even know what that means. Oh, wait, there's like some rhetorical trickery
happening here. It's just the half crab. It's a whole and a half. No, no, okay, but the way he
said it, then like at the end he says the whole of the half crab and the half of the whole crab.
Okay, well, they both weigh 0.9 pounds because both of those phrases refer to the same thing.
Exactly. I.e. the half crab. There you go. That's our answer. Please let us know. Okay.
Clip that whole bit with the half crab. That was a mistake. I fucking did it.
Next voicemail. Okay, get ready for this. Wanna play Minecraft with us.jpeg on the count of three.
One, two, three, go. Hey, PCP heads, do you like Minecraft? Do you hate Minecraft,
but like Pokemon? Do you can be the very best like no one ever was? The PCP Minecraft server
wants you to come and rock our socks. Dig a shitty hole in the ground, level up in the
out and get rich, collect all the TMs, marvel at how Thosetamus doesn't sleep, mispronounce those
Timmy's name, catch an Entei or just fucking lousy with Entei's, come see Victory Road where
Seven Maniacs built their own continent to stage honorable combat. Wanna be the champion? Train
a team and start fighting people. Just say you're the champion and dare anyone to prove you wrong.
That's how Gary did it. You wanna be Gary, right? Hate Pokemon? Play the mods factorial
ripped off instead. Lay conveyors, grind minerals, smelt the whole world and build a monument to
your avarice. Wanna be a shitty wizard? We've got at least two brands of shitty wizardry.
Twist reality to your will. Become God and dare the world to oppose you. All on the PCP Minecraft server.
We're doing what do you call them? You wanna do another one this week or next week?
You guys can, I'm gonna be away. If I got time, yes.
I want in the comments of this video, here's what I want. I want everyone watching this video to fill
out a form. In the comments, okay, to differentiate your comments from the rest of the comments,
I want you to do the following. Do a hashtag, like a PCP head form. I wanna give me your age,
your gender, a short description of your bio, and then I want you to say something funny and I will
give results of this form and the data that I collected next time. Don't forget those three
wacky numbers in the back of mom's credit card. That's an important final addition.
Sounds good. Okay, great. Just the three on the back. If we don't have the ones on the front,
it doesn't even matter. The problem is American Express has four digits on the front of the
credit card. I mean, that's, wow, we gotta think about those guys too. All right, anyway, let's go
on to our next one. This is the number one hooligan, Fred and Shid warning. Okay, let's, I think I
may have misspelled this, but let's see what he has to say for us. All right, one, two, three, go.
This is a warning. Hool 3.0, the new formula. It has more probiotics, so when I consumed it a few
more times after the first, it made me really gassy, made me fart and shit, and it smelled horrible,
like even worse than the first time. Also for the keto boys, he'll black addition, 50% less
carbs for you. And it's also the 3.0. Black addition. Yeah, they have a black addition. Yeah,
that's the new kind. That sounds cool. Let me check that out. It still has, I think, 10 or 11 carbs
per shake. I mean, that's not zero. That's not a nightmare. That's not terrible. Can you maintain
ketosis? I bought some ice cream. I bought some halo top ice cream, which is low. It's low calorie
ice cream. Oh yeah, it's so good. But it also has a pretty low, it's like, it's like 20 grams of
sugar for like the whole pint. So you could eat like a bit in response. Yeah, that's right, that's
right. But I also got this other stuff called rebel, which is like four grams of carbs for a
whole pint. So like nothing. Damn, not bad. It's epic. All right, let's wrap it up here. We got
double Satan here, our final caller, double man. All right, let's get to it. Here we go. Three, two,
one, go. Hello, hello. I, I am, am double, double Satan, Satan. And, and I am, am here, here,
to, to tell, tell you, you, to, to suck, suck my, my double, double dick, dick all the way, way down,
down to, to double, double, hell, hell. Go, go, double, double, fuck, fuck yourself, yourself.
Especially, especially Ben, Ben, Saint, Saint. Die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die.
Yeah, well, I mean, we got what was promised. I don't know why the double voice is so funny to me.
That was great. I loved it. So, so, go back again, double Satan. I feel like we're from
double God. Can double God call it? Is this like the new arch enemy to double Batman? It's gotta be
related to double Batman. The, maybe double Batman died and this is he went to double hell.
Well, when the double Batman died, Satan probably just like sucked him up and ate him like Kirby.
And uh, he got the double. This is his copy ability. I get it. It's like, like, like, like by the law of
conservation of doubleness, we know that there can't be two doubles at once. So, first say double
Satan to exist, double Batman had to end. Initially, I was imagining like it had two heads,
but the idea of him having a speech impediment, just saying it again. That's much more endearing.
All right, fuck it. That's the last voicemail, people. Speak, pipe, link down below. Leave us
more voicemails. They're always fun to listen to and leave. No, it's false. I'll make them good,
or you'll go straight to hell and I'll ignore you. That's it. So, hey, support the show,
patreon.com slash the procrastiners. We're not on our channel right now, but hopefully we will be
soon. That'll be nice. That'll be nice. Bonus episodes are still available. You can get them
from the patreon and they're going to be around and also on the on the discord, which you also get
access to for just $1 and for $5, get the bonus episodes. You know what is there's 34, including
a new one that just came out. There was a little comic talk, which me and Tom bombed into later
on. We talked about all kinds of stuff. It was a good time. It was a good time. So that's it. We'll
see you there. Follow us on Twitter for all updates. We'll let you know there updates of the
channel stats and all that stuff at TPCrastinators on Twitter. I would highly recommend you follow
that for any kind of updates if you want to know what the channel is doing. And that pretty much
sums it up right there. So we will see you soon. I'll be back next week calling in from a distant
location. Other than that, it should be a normal episode and looking forward to it, everybody.
All right. See you then next week. Radcon Force coming up everybody. 15,000 donation
dollar reduced. Let's get Brad Garlinghouse given a lecture. It's going to be incredible.
Check out the Kickstarter for all the details on that. I'm so afraid, but so tantalized of
Brad Garlinghouse. If we can just make all the kind of, if we can invest all our earnings
from the Radcon Kickstarter in Ripple, we'll go to the moon. Imagine it ladies and gentlemen,
all right, see you next week on the moon. See you then. Bye.