I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch...
...on account of three say sink. One, two, three, sink!
Really? Wait. One, two, three sink!
Why are you so far behind?
I'm thinking man. All right. Internet slow, I guess. I guess. Uh, all right. Um, welcome
everybody to the procrastinators podcast. It's me and Gib and cheesy manfredo. And all
right, bye. That's the end of the episode. I guess nobody has anything to say. Bye. I
thought cheesy was going to say something. I thought cheesy was going to say hello. Hey,
cheesy. I said hello. Give them before the episode. Give them before the episode started.
See, cheesy doesn't even know. Cheesy, what the fuck? Gib, what do I do?
Yes, we can hear you. Can you guys hear me? Cheesy. No, I mean, yes. Cheesy can't hear us,
I guess. God, I'm going to punch my fucking window. Jesus. I can hear you. No, you fucking
can't hear you. Stop lying. I can hear you guys. No, you can't. What's, then why didn't you answer?
What's a damn job? Oh, God, I answered. We didn't hear the answer, I guess. I answered the call.
You answered. No. Yeah. You asked to be on the show when you said show. I gave an answer.
Yeah, I did. I think you're just like 20 seconds behind us. And now I'm here. Your audio may be
getting cut off and also you're applying like very late to what we're saying. Yeah, we can't,
we can't do it. We can't do it like this. We can't do it like this. I think it's it. Okay, you know
what? Give me one quick second. You got to go to the internet router and turn it on.
God, I hope it's, I hope that's the solution.
Perfect, perfect time to log my breakfast calories since I forgot to.
One tub of marinara cheese. Close. Two chub tubs of marinara cheese.
It was oats, actually, but close, close. Oats. From the Scottish Highlands.
What? The Scottish Highlands, you know, where the oats come from. You said Scottish,
but I heard it as Squish from the Squish Highlands. The Squish Highlands.
Where they toss the kebab. Where they toss the, where they toss it a pizza. Where they,
where they toss it, they hand toss it a mozzarella and the dough and the cheese and the tomatoes.
Hey, I'm walking here in Italy. New York style. New York style,
Italian, authentic rustic Italian style marinara pizza.
They don't say, hey, I'm walking here in Italy. They say, hey, I'm walking here and then. No,
they don't care about going quick. They're just, they're just sort of, they're walking here and
they're like, hey, nice to see you. Hey, mozzarella or whatever they say. Hey, mozzarella. I hardly
know her. I'm walking here. Good old racism. Good old, like, cultural, cultural racism.
When I don't have anything funny to say, I just pick a minority and I just, then I just start
beating on them. I just start mailing on them. Fuck them.
Fuck. You guys can start. Just give me a second. Okay. Cheesy will try again.
I guess let's just start talking. Cheesy, she's got to get his shit together, man.
All right. Here's what, I don't know. I don't know if he always has these connections issues,
but Cheesy's mic is dog shit. He needs a decent mic if he's going to keep podcasting.
He's got to upgrade. What does he even have? I don't know, but it does not sound good. It's
not podcast quality. Like even like a blue snowball, like a baby USB mic. It sounds better, I think.
Yeah. Yeah. There's probably like, that was like the good mic for beginners a long time ago.
There's probably like really good for the same price. I know it's out there for beginners.
Not not even that long ago, I saw a thread on Twitter of someone being like,
it was really annoying. Someone was like, guys, if you're if you're trying to get into a voice
acting or any kind or any kind of content creation, don't cheap out with the blue yeti.
You know, you need, you should invest in your future. You should, you should invest, you should
actually invest the money that you need to be doing to like to be sounding good. And I mean,
first thing, no, no, unless unless you're doing like professional quality voice acting and the bar
is really high or you're doing ASMR videos or something, nobody gives a shit. If you're just
making shit for YouTube, nobody gives a shit. You can, you can use a snowball. I did use a
snowball on the PCP for like two years and nobody's even going to 95 people are not even going to
notice the percent of people are going to notice the difference. And then of course, of course,
it turned out that this freak, this was like a tube or something, but this freak had like
Amazon links and was like an affiliate with a bunch of like microphone companies and stuff.
So of course, she's spreading this fucking hogwash that like you if you're if you're using a blue
yeti, you've already failed, right? False false. Yeah, voice acting, potentially, you're a good
idea to invest in your future because if you do get a job, if it's specifically in voice acting
or ASMR, then maybe you might benefit from like a really high stream. No, like you can
start out with like is going to give a budget stuff. That's no problem.
Like I guess we're recording. Yeah, I guess I guess we've started now.
Ellie is our cut out as much of the anger as would make for the as would keep the pace of this
podcast brisk, but also funny. So I released a video. What? Oh, yes. Oh, I was just going to say
I released my YouTube video advertising my Twitch stream, as I've been saying, I wanted to do
for a while. Why didn't I see that? When did you do that just today? Just like an hour ago.
Well, two hours, an hour and a half ago. Now, yeah. The the conversion rate, okay, it's not,
you know, it's only got a couple hundred views, but the conversion rate of like Twitch follows
to views on it is like really high. I've gained, hang on, it's got it's got about 300 views now.
I think it's it's like an hour and a half old 300 318 views and I've gained 23 followers.
I mean, that's I wonder. I wonder if that ratio will be maintained.
I mean, it makes sense. You got a lot of subscribers and viewers from
the metal man, the metal man, the metal metal man video, you know, I should make a separate
the lore of metal man.
Nine hours long. But like those people, they don't necessarily do more than subscribe. They might
not go to check your Twitter, they might not know anything else about you. So the best way to get
them to know about stuff is to make a YouTube video. That I mean, yeah, definitely, definitely.
That was the it's my biggest platform by far. And that was that was the the logic.
I don't know. It's just this just a pretty high pretty high click through rate.
I hope I get a big hope it makes my streams really huge hope everyone fucking watched me hope I do
big number on Twitch platform because a Twitch a Twitch follower, I think per capita a Twitch
follower is worth a lot more than a YouTube subscriber. Oh, yeah. Like just the fact that if
if it translates to a viewer on stream. Yeah. If you've got if you got like, yeah, yeah. It's
just a generally speaking, a stream has a lot less viewers total. Yeah. On average. If you've got
like 10k 20k followers on Twitch, like you're good, like that's your career. If you've got 20k
followers on YouTube, it's probably it's probably it's probably it's probably just a hobby. Yeah,
it's probably just a hobby and you're you're you're a and then that's where I'm at. And that's me.
So trying and trying to convert that one number into the other number
for the big for the big money. I'm trying to get that big money. Although my audience isn't big,
but I'm finally getting around to making avenues for people to purchase my comics. Yes, they do
like them. So I'm on Amazon. I don't know if you saw my tweet. I took a few pictures of
the Clarissa Gunsmoke proof. But you got it. You got it already. That's fast. Yeah, it's quite
quick. Wow. No, I didn't see that. Let me look at that. Yeah. It's, it's nice. Colors are good.
Print quality is, you know, good. And like, no, no problems with any of the printing.
It is a book. And it's real. And the only problem. The only problem is that I messed up something
with the bleed area, the trim. They trimmed off a bit too much off the top. All I need to do is
adjust the size and then re put the manuscript back in and then look at it and then publish that.
And then it'll be on the store and I'll have an Amazon store and you can be paying money for me.
I love paying money for you. Yeah. You'll have Clarissa Gunsmoke volume one,
the first four chapters. So that's the new chapter included. I might do like individual issues as
well. If you just want the fourth chapter. But like, I'm going to be doing it like the volumes
are cheaper than buying each chapter individually. If I do that. Whoa, screen tones. There are screen
tones. I have screen tones in the new chapter. Holy shit. I'm advancing my skill power, my tool set.
I had a somewhat similar, well, on the proof that I got of the Radcon dojin,
it was pretty good the bleeds, but like the page numbers were like too far off and like the page
numbers got cut off. So like I had to move, I'm going to move those in a little bit before I order
the like the reorder. Yeah. Looks pretty good. Looks pretty good. I mean, how do you feel about
like the paper quality and all that? The paper quality is like decent. It's not like super
high end stuff. It's print on demand, but it's not like, it doesn't feel like it's going to
fall apart. It's like good quality. It's a quality product. It's a quality product and
you can put it on your shelf and it won't fall apart. This is one of those books that I've heard
so much about. Did you have the option to like put any design on like the spine of it?
Yes. The cover, they say you give the manuscript, which is all the pages on the inside,
then they say give a separate PDF as the cover, which includes the front and the back and the
middle is the spine. I didn't put anything on the spine because the spine is kind of shallow.
Yeah. It's kind of thin for just volume one. Although I could do like a Dragon Ball thing
where I have the sides of the spine showing a little picture and if you line them up,
they'll become a little thing. I should do that. You mean like, okay, the yellow like bar on volume
one, I assume that extends over the spine? Yes, it does. Like if you had four. It extends over
the spine and it goes round to the barcode, which is printed in the bottom right corner.
Like if you had four, if you had four volumes of it, I don't know, I think it would look good
if it's just like the four different colors, but the yellow bar like continues from one
onto the next, like that would look good too. If you wanted to get real fancy and yeah,
put a little picture that forms if you put them all next to each other.
Or maybe I could put like a tiny number so you could see at a glance like, oh, this is volume one,
this is volume two, one, two, three, four. That'd be nice. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so that's,
and there's probably going to be four volumes. First volume is four chapters,
then it's going to be chapter five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Oh no, just three volumes. Yeah,
three volumes for this Closer Gunsmoke and the Bandit King adventure.
Oh, you have drawn five?
No, I've been, I've mostly been working on the Amazon stuff and my website for the past week
or two. Wait, I thought five was done. No, four was done. Oh, okay, okay. Oh, right, right, right,
right, right. Okay, four is the new one. So you can buy, by the time this episode out,
you can buy it. So there will be a link, an Amazon link, to buy the physical version
in the description. Also, I'm going to put it on, I guess I'll put it on Kindle for people who
use Kindle just to access that marketplace. But also, I want to make a digital version for,
or like on Gumroad or something so I can get more of the profit from that,
because Amazon takes, my cut for the Amazon is 60%. You get 60%? I get 60% of the sale.
That's more than I expected. Wait, how much is it? I'm going to be selling them for like
15 bucks, I think, volumes. That book for 15 bucks and you get 60% of that?
Yeah, I think so. Wow, that's, I mean, I don't know exactly how. That's cheaper than I expected
and that's a bigger cut than I expected. Yeah, I think that's quite reasonable. Yeah, that's not
bad. I thought you were going to say that due to printing and shipping fees, it was going to
cost like 20 plus, maybe like 20 and then you would get like maybe five bucks off a sale or
something. No, I mean, it's because Amazon has such a large cut of the market. They can afford to
make it very, very lucrative for all the independent. And I for one, celebrate them
for doing that because they pass that savings on to the consumer. It's so true. So true.
But yeah, it will be like a 60% cut for me for buying a physical version, which is much better
and much less labor intensive for me than if I was doing it by myself,
sending out books. So I'm happy with that. I think it might be the same on Kindle,
might not be, but I think if I put the PDF that I put on Kindle, also on Gumroad for
the same price, then I'll get a bigger cut. So if you just want the PDF, the digital version and
you don't use Kindle, like Kindle has no meaning for you, you can just get it on Gumroad and I'm
going to make a Gumroad and that's going to be where it's going to be.
Well, speaking of... I'm going to do that. I'm going to do it for Lord of Ghosts as well.
I'm going to do it for Redman. Redman comics are coming. Do it for him. Do it for him. Yes.
Maggie, Maggie Poster. Speaking of things that should be out by the time this episode goes up,
we got our Patreon, not Patreon money, we got our freaking Radcon money. Did you get yours?
Yes, I got mine. It's done. It's done. The Curse of Radcon. The Curse of Radcon is lifted.
The Curse of Radcon 4 is lifted, Gib. We finally did it. We finally did it. Nate actually sent.
Finish the OVA. We've got to release that. We dealt with a certain nefarious individuals,
like a non-bullshit and then all the problems were solved and then we got the money now.
I'm going to cry just thinking about it. It's not about the money. It's about a job well done.
I would say that Radcon 4 was a huge success.
Yes. Everyone's asking, when's Radcon 5? Everyone's asking.
Oh, no. We'll do a VR Radcon 5 in virtual reality. Everyone come along.
That would actually be pretty funny. Do like an Oculus Rift lecture with all the people jumping
around. Honestly, well, I mean, that could be good. That could be good. The only thing that
would be bad about that is that you'd be standing there for who knows how long with a
fucking VR headset on your head. Yes. Six-hour-long lecture about the history of
boats. The history of boats.
We scoff, but that's probably very interesting. Oh, for sure. It goes back to the beginning of
humanity. Yeah. I mean, you would have to, every freaking
culture would have their own freaking, I mean, you couldn't make a comp... You simply could
not make such a comprehensive history of such a thing. We came out the water. We were like,
what if we became mammals? But then we were sad because we couldn't be under the water
anymore. We invented boats to visit our old friend. The sea. Well, you see, the sea wants
to drag us down, but the devil fruits want us to rise up and achieve our potential. We made
boats so that we could go and hang out with our old buddy, but he's kind of a jerk and he wants
to drown us now. We made a boat so we didn't have to actually get in there. Wait, is the devil fruits
metaphor for evolution? Yes. We evolved to be on land and the sea was like, you're not even gonna
thank me. You're not even gonna say thank you. You're just gonna leave. Yep. That's why I hate
the devil fruits. Yep. But we should, hey, we should watch that freaking OVA this week. Oh,
no. I know it's gonna suck. I know it's gonna suck. I know it's gonna suck, but we should do
it this week and maybe we can release the, well, I'll release the bonus commentary of it.
Sure, sure. On Friday. Okay, okay, we'll do it. We'll do it like soon. So yeah, by the time this
episode goes out, this should be, the Radcon OVA should be live and we can, there'll be a bonus
commentary track of us watching it and cringing. Cringing hard. Yeah, yeah. But that's a scar,
that's a battle scar that I'll be proud to wear. The scar gained from cringing so hard.
Oh, because it means Radcon was done and we did it and we did everything we had to do. We did
everything, we did do everything we had to do. Another Twitch follower. Did I say, did I say
on the podcast already the thing about the video that I just, the Twitch thing? Did you talk about
that? Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Couldn't remember if that was before or after the, because cheesy's nonsense
derailed the start of the video. I hate that guy. That guy, but also that guy, he, I'm gonna play,
I'm going to play the voice of Grimace in the voiced comic version, the video comic
version of McPagliacci. Did you know that? Yeah, I think I saw a post on Discord about
McPagliacci if you want to be a voice. Yeah. I submitted voice auditions for every male character
and cheesy, I guess he liked my Grimace voice the best. So I'll be, I'm gonna be Grimace. It's fun.
Can you give us a sneak peek of that voice? What's, what's the thing he says?
Well, Grimace. Oh, you're singing, you're singing is good. I really like your voice,
Bertie. You should sing more. It's like a dark, goofy, kooky monster combo.
Like it evil fucked up. Oh God. How long have you been there?
For like five seconds. I mean, you're for five seconds.
Okay. Okay, boss. Sorry. I was leaking the content. No, it's fine. Actually, I'm,
I'm gonna actually like try to pump out the motion conic before Friday. Oh God. I can do that. Yeah.
Well, that's a, that's pretty, that's a pretty fast turnaround, but okay, I think I can, I think
I can do that for you. Appreciate it. Doesn't take, doesn't take that long.
Did you say you were going to send me notes? I did. Oh, you already liked it yesterday. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Yeah. Just read the things I actually send you, Ben. No. For once. No. Well then. No.
I'm gonna have to replace you. Fired, fired, fired. No.
Uh, you know what? Hey, stupid. My Hamburglar voice was better than Grimace.
My Hamburglar voice was better. You should have given me Hamburglar. I found another Hamburglar.
Well, well, see, that's my problem. That's my problem with you is that you did that.
It's fine. My Hamburglar, I'm just saying my Hamburglar voice was, was, was a masterpiece.
Look, you know what? We could, we could like special edition this,
where there's another version of the motion. This is all me. All me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. No. Well, I'll give them, I'll give them my best shot. I'll give them my best shot. Even the
audience, even the audience members will just be like you, different voice, different use.
Yeah. I love the circus. Over and over again. Yeah. Okay. Okay. We'll workshop it. Interesting.
Working on it. Complete. Looking into it. Ben edition. Ben edition. Yeah, the Ben edition.
That'd be very cute. In case anyone who was reading the book thought like, man,
this would be 10 times better if everyone voiced by Ben Singh. Man, you know, they'd be
re, you know what would make, you know what would make this voice comic better is if it sucked.
That would make me McPoggliacci. Oh my God. McPoggliacci. Like Mc, like McPAWGliacci.
Do you know about Pogs Give? Do you know what a Pog is? Oh, I know all about that.
All right. You know, I, of course you do. Of course you do.
Um, where were we? Help. Um, we were talking about grimace.
Talking about, we were grimacing right then. We were, we were going to,
we're going to cringe and we're going to grimace when we watched the OVA.
Do you want to watch the uncensored version or the censored version?
I'm thinking censored version because I think that's the version people know.
Because I think the funny, some of the comedy will be, I haven't seen,
I have not watched as a single frame of it. I don't know anything that's in there,
but I think some of the comedy of it will come from like the places where Nate puts
like beams of light and steam clouds and stuff covering up the dirty parts.
Did I mention that? Did you guys actually show dirty parts in it?
Well, they, well, you know, they're, well, yeah, because we were all females at the time.
So all of our nipples became female presenting. So our nipples are not safe for work in that video
at the time. They're fine now. And to this day.
Well, my nipples became recently female. My nipples recently became female
resenting, if you will.
Okay, that's not what I thought you were going with that.
Like a repelling force.
Yeah, yeah, like a female looks at it and they're like, never, never mind. No, thank you.
Nice.
I have a, I have a complaint. Wait, okay. I got one more thing.
Uh, the plebeian wee blue rays. I'm going to run out. They're going to be gone soon.
And I'm, and here's the thing. It's not, it's not worth making more of them.
It's not, it's not worth it. So I'm not going to, I'm not going to make more of them.
You know, a lot of people have gotten angry at me about that lately. I've gained some haters over
it. You want to know how many I've sold in this, in this recent bout with me writing the manifesto
and all that three, four, four. Oh, it's up to four now. So all of, all of this, uh, all this,
this nonsense, all this, all these shenanigans have been for the sake of selling four copies
of these. And I have, oh, I have four more. I have four left on my shelf. So, um, yeah,
pretty sure when those are gone, uh, that's going to be it. Cause it's, you know, it's not,
it's just not worth it. It's just not worth the trouble.
You know what this means? What's that?
Write a second manifesto and you'll sell four more.
No, no. I think one, I think one sold because I wrote the manifesto. Did I mention the manifesto?
I just, if I,
I don't think you mentioned it. I saw it though.
On the podcast. Yeah, I didn't mention it on the podcast. I think I sent it on the stream.
Yeah, I wrote, I wrote, I wrote a thing on my website called the Blu-ray manifesto,
stcomics.com slash brm.html. And it's just, and it's just
an explanation of my reasoning behind why I think writing the Blu-rays was good
and the right thing to do. And you don't have to agree with it, but I wrote it
because I didn't want to explain it to anyone else. It's like, that's, that's my reason. And if
you don't agree, then I guess we don't agree. But the statement is there. And I think, I just
thought, I think it's really funny. I asked, you know who, I got to say, I got to tell Cody
LaRue, the butt chugger himself. I got to ask, he was mad at me and I asked him, did you read my
manifesto? And he said, I will after work. And I said, nothing.
I should have named the manifesto the Blu-ray question.
The Blu-ray question. That would have been good. I just, I just, I like calling it a manifesto.
Anyway, I'm, yeah, they're gonna, they're, they're going. Listen guys, I just, if you want one,
get one now. I have four left and I'm not gonna restock because I can't justify the cost of it.
So, you know, buy the, buy them while they're still there. Twitchsaintcomics.com
slash store.html. Or, or else, or you'll live or live in regret. Okay.
And if you, if you're not interested in buying that, actually don't buy the Blu-ray. Save your
money for me, for me, actually. And pre-order, make Pagalacchi right now. We have two days left.
I bought it. I bought a copy.
Yeah, yeah. Ben here bought a copy. I even follow, follow your leader,
PCP listeners and buy a copy of McPagalacchi. I mean, if there's one, if there's one McPagalacchi
fan, it's me. And if there's no McPagalacchi fans, I'm dead. I'm, I'm, I'm McPagalacchi
for life. I'm right or die. Yeah. Yeah. Ben auditioned for the Birdie Boys.
No, he did not. I told them. That's like the only, that's like the only voice in the comic that I
did not audition for. You don't need to lie. Maybe, maybe take a couple more years of, of HRT
Ben and maybe we'll get back to the Birdie, the Birdie voice. Maybe we'll have a discussion
about it. You know, I watched, I watched a bunch of McDonaldland commercials to, to like get a sense
of what the voices were like. And I didn't hear, none of them had Birdie in them. I didn't hear
Birdie even a single time. I mean, I wasn't, I wasn't classic silencing women. I mean, I wasn't
looking for, I think she was introduced yet you weren't looking for, I was looking, I was looking
for Grimace and Hamburglar and, and Ronald. What, there you go. Did you type in? But I, but I mean,
I saw other, like I saw Mayor McCheese, I heard Mayor McCheese speak many more times than I
heard Birdie, which was zero. Probably, you probably saw a couple commercials from like
the 70s to like early 80s. Did they introduce Birdie later? Yeah, she was kind of later.
She's kind of like the, the last like mainstay character. Okay. Yeah, that, that is probably
why then I was looking at the really old ones. Is she the Smurfette? They were like, we need a woman.
We need representation. They needed a mascot to represent the breakfast menu. Oh, oh, oh, she's
the early Birdie. Oh, I, that's her full name. I never knew that. First name, early. Last name,
Birdie. That crazy. That changes everything. Yeah, yeah. So wait, what, what are the rest of them?
What's Grimace? Grimace is milkshakes, right? Wasn't he like a milkshake stealing monster?
Yeah, Grimace was the original, originally a milkshake monster.
Makes sense because of how thick he is. Yeah. Didn't they talk about this in like the newest
red letter media? One of them brings up Grimace and so and one and one of them is like, yeah,
there's a whole backstory behind Grimace, but I don't remember it. And they're all like, yeah,
none of us remember it, but there definitely is one. Oh, anyway, let's talk about how Mike hates
old people. The Grimace backstory has been like retcon like two times. I didn't, because they were
talking about it, I looked it up and I guess he was originally like a villain. He was like,
he's like a reformed villain. He's like discord. He's like Vegeta. He's exactly like Vegeta.
Grimace is the Vegeta of the Ronald McDonald universe. He popped up and showed to be,
showed to be too powerful for Ronald to handle, but over over a course of time.
Like he became friendly. Like he originally had four arms. He had four arms for stealing milkshakes
and they just got rid of, they just forgot it. Oh, he's a milkshake stealer. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. So the hamburger is like a hamburger. Yep. The burger. And the fry guys steal fries.
Yeah. Why is everyone trying to steal all this food? It's an entire universe of tricks rabbits.
Okay. So basically in McDonald land, food is very like just plentiful. Actually,
food is just straight up alive in McDonald land, right? Literally grows on trees.
I guess it's implied that like Grimace, Hamburger, all the characters are not
necessarily like natives to McDonald land, not even like Ronald potentially.
So this is an invasive force. Colonizers. They're colonizing the nugget plan. I actually have my
own like head cannon of how all this like works. Let's get into it. Okay. So basically, how does
this relate to the clown force? So, oh man, we'll be here all day. Is this a potential lecture?
Oh, you're right. You know, honestly, McDonald land lore, but there probably is an hour's worth
of lore there. Probably. It'll be kind of tough because I really have to like,
I've seen the majority of the commercials. I swear I've seen the majority of them.
But every couple of months, like a new one that I haven't seen pops up. It's almost like they
manifest into the ether, right? Even like yesterday, I was like, I was talking to a bud, another of the
voice actors and I asked him, hey, do you think you could do just a quick like Mayor McCheese line?
Because he literally just has one line in McPugly Archie. And he's like, yeah, sure. How does
Mayor McCheese sound? And I'm like, oh, he's literally just like the Mad Hatter impression from
the. Yeah, like, like, I'm not a cheeseburger, don't you know? He says shit like that. And
and so I looked up a clip of myself in a McDonald land commercial Mayor McCheese. And the first
one that I saw was like, wait, I've never seen this commercial. Because it's literally like,
it's a commercial from the 70s. And he's like, weird aliens, aliens that look kind of like
crewmates from a mugga's that may make cheese because they think he's an actual cheeseburger.
Well, they think he's like an edible cheeseburger. Does he just does he just have like a congenital
illness that makes him look like a cheeseburger, but he's not actually a cheeseburger? Well, my
theory is that the thing is that you never necessarily see one of the good cheeseburgers
eat. Yeah, you never see any of the characters like eat any of the food, to be honest. And I think
I think what it is in McDonald land is that the food is just kind of sent to it, like it's just
alive. And in the commercials, sometimes there's like, there's like just a hamburger with eyes
with no body, right? What I like to think is that the older they get, they grow a body like
may or make cheese. And the like the ones with like just with just like that hamburger and two
eyeballs is like the young form and they and it kind of grow on like bushes and trees, apparently,
because you see like, you never see anyone make the stuff, it just kind of grows like it manifests
the Garden of Eden. Yeah, and there was even like, there was this one tree character that was kind
of like one of the main cast, but that never necessarily like brought back. And he's like
mentioned, he's like brought up in one of the cartoons, but never like, again, I notice.
My theory is that like Ronald, and this is from this is my like on this is like what I think is
the main kind of like line of continuity from, since like the early commercials up until like
the few handfuls that were made in the early 2000s is that Ronald has this kind of like aura
that like man, that like kind of brings out the kids and people, you know, kind of like comforting
aura, right? But but if you say he's like a paladin, he's like a paladin, like a heroic aura of
courage that nullifies fear effects to all his party members. Yeah, he's a holy warrior.
He makes you feel he makes you feel young, you know, in an innocent sort of way. But what I
like to think happens is that if you stand around him for too long, or if you hang out with him for
too long, you start like not just feeling like a kid, but you start de-aging. You start becoming
younger. That would be terrible. And my main my main theory to kind of the main kind of point
that I like to think is evidence of this is the fact that when the hamburger first showed up,
he was kind of like he had white hair. Yeah, like he kind of had wrinkly skin.
In his first appearance on now, he's like young. He has like red hair. He's like ginger now. Yeah,
he got younger. Surely it could it could just be the the air of the hamburger line lineage.
Surely surely it could be his little offspring. True. True. That being said, I like to think
that that's kind of the reason why maybe that's why the food in like McDonald's land doesn't like
rot away because they're just around Ronald that keeps them like weirdly fresh. You know,
it keeps them like young, in a sense. Right. He's a freshness clown. And if you haven't noticed.
Freshness. He's the power of freshness. He ate the fresh. He ate the fresh. Yeah, that's a yep.
And another another piece to the puzzle is the fact that when Grimace first appeared,
he had forward arms and now he just has two, right? And what I like to think is that Grimace
a species grows an extra set of arms the older they get. And well, Ronald is like turning Grimace
younger. Actually Grimace seems to get dumber, right? But maybe he's not that he's getting
dumber. He's just getting like that child like naivety, you know, his brain is is yeah, de de
forming. Right. It was early birdie going to turn into an egg. No, early birdie. Well, there's
there's there's a commercial where it's like when she first shows when like they they give her an
origin story, right? Like she was like an egg they found and she hatched and she was already she
hatched with clothes on and everything. But like her you stay as a kid, you don't like become a baby
or fetish, you just stay as a kid, you know, like you stay the target audience for a character like
Ronald, right? That that being said, I think Ronald probably realizes that he has his effect on people
and it's kind of like a horrifying when it happens. And I think other adult characters in the early
commercials kind of realized this. That's why they disappeared because they realized we can't be around
Ronald because we're going to river back into being a kid. That's why the professor, then there are
no more. That's why Captain Crook is in there no more. Mayor McCheese as well. They were just like
we've got business to take care of. We can't be we can't be messing around with this shit. I see.
Right, exactly. 30 characters kind of stayed around. It's also the fry kids. They were originally
known as the fry goblins, right? They learned that. And the thing is, there used to be like way
more of them. There used to be a lot of them because they seem to be addicted to fries, right?
They wanted to constantly eat them. I think what probably happened is that the fry goblins probably
realized the this weird side effect of hanging out around Ronald caused to them, right? So like
slowly they stopped like trying to be around Ronald, trying to eat fries and only like a concentrated
few stick around. And it didn't make sense calling them by their species name and only made sense
calling them by specifically what they are. They became the fry kids. They became younger.
Oh my god. There is. That's amazing. And a little bit back to Grimace, I'd like to think that
Ronald realized that he can't like he kind of had to there's this commercial that kind of red
cons the origin of Grimace. And it implies like Ronald said, because Grimace doesn't remember,
but Ronald says, oh, we used to be like literally kids that hanged out and we're usually we were
actually babies together that grew up, right? And Grimace just kind of buys it. But how is how
is it just Ronald like convincing them that, hey, this is actually implanted false memories.
Yeah, exactly that. Hey, you weren't an adult. And you were never an adult. Actually,
you're still a kid this whole time, blah, blah, blah stuff, you know,
you got Mac gaslit. Yeah, Mac gaslit. You got make light to what if okay, alternate theory.
Okay, here's my here's my alternate theory is that the McDonald Land commercials actually,
they just take place in reverse in reverse chronological order.
You think so? I don't know. I mean, wouldn't that wouldn't that explain all this all the same things?
I mean, what if they're just they're just they're just showing them in reverse?
You'd have to track the existence of things. The thing is that like, they kind of like,
I mean, the commercials usually end with like a current toy of that era, mostly the ones like,
as we get into like that. But you see, it's an it's an alternate time stream,
whose whose time flows in the opposite direction of our own.
Well, you see, like, if we become more into the 70s, like black people start losing rights,
women start losing rights, holy shit, you're right. Actually, in their in their
as their time goes forward, our time goes backwards. So, so, you know, our future is
their past. They're they're they're the two the two timelines point in different directions,
but they're parallel to each other. I'm gonna leave a little more evidence for this one.
I just I just think that wouldn't that also explain that like, oh, as the commercials
went on, everyone looks younger and like grimace. What if what if what if Ronald that would explain
Ronald would be telling the truth, they did grow up as kids, but then in the in their future
of the timeline that aired in the 70s, grimace grows up to be an evil milkshake stealing.
Beast, I don't know, because it's like, there's this kind of like when the characters are first
introduced, I mean, I guess it's implied there's some sort of like, I mean, I just I mean, I just
think you're reverse age. I just think you're reverse aging aura theory is so ridiculous. I
just think it makes a lot more sense that like clearly the time stream has just been reversed
and is flowing in reverse parallel to our own. I mean, you'd need to show it's just so much more
plausible each other more in the past than they do in the present. I think there's more evidence
for my they get younger. They become younger around Ronald theory. I think there's more evidence
to that. What happened? What happened with because obviously they retired Ronald McDonald
from like this the main look of a lot of McDonald's stores. I don't know if that still exists. I don't
know if they like still have kiddie. They mostly just they mostly just use Ronald for the was it
the McDonald house and just like a charity. There's one in my city and that's where I like
take the pictures with the Ronald statue because it's right in front of their building.
They mostly see Ronald here and there. He's on Instagram. He has like a social media account.
That's really funny. His look kind of changed and mostly just keep them for like I notice he
mostly does like little parade or events. Yeah. Yeah. And charities they don't do like commercials
with him no more. And it's a combination of like they'll bring it back eventually.
I think it I think it ultimately I think it does have to do something with the documentary
supersize me because I like change the shit load of things for McDonald's like that documentary
was bullshit too. Oh yeah but that was like like years later we kind of well I don't even know if
it's like public like everything I feel like it's because I always hear like oh the documentary is
bullshit all the time yada yada. How do we not know this is just because of our little
circles that we carve ourselves and everyone is aware of that but like to ignore me how aware
are they that like that commercial is bullshit because like yeah you know on a surface level
it's like oh yeah you know you too much for McDonald's this is bad for you yeah obviously right but
maybe the problem is that like oh how bad it is was kind of like misdirected in that commercial
in that documentary. I mean that documentary made like a huge cultural impact so and so and
everybody knows about supersize me so yeah it's going to be it's going to be fewer people that
hear about oh did you hear was kind of debunked like oh did you hear that guy was kind of like
lying about it like oh did you hear that like there was all this weird shit going on behind the
scenes and like he misattributed lots of things and he was like also an alcoholic at the time and
it's etc etc. Yeah I remember when the first like the first couple of times make the news in the
same way. Yeah I remember the first couple of times I heard it get debunked um people's first
reaction were like oh are you paid out by McDonald's lol yeah right what are you in the pot you're in
the pocket of big cheese. Big M. Big M. Big clown. Yeah big clown. Right. Right. I mean I don't
want to I don't want to I don't want to keep for McDonald's or anything but you know yeah it's like
the what he what he did it what it was the purpose the purpose for the documentary was to make
people realized that first food was bad and very bad if you ate it all the time which is true
it's just that like so like is it really that much of a negative outcome it's true but it's just
that the it was it was made in a way that is like the food at McDonald's will do this to you but
like he did it in an extremely unscientific way and he did it in a way that was like specifically
designed to guarantee like a bad outcome and it he also like never he also never like said that he
was actually going through alcohol like he was an alcoholic which is like an important thing when
you're talking about like the the effect that like the food you're eating has on your body
it's like that that might have had the could that have had an impact you never who knows he
fucked up his liver his liver got fucked by the introduction I wonder if that does anything
metabolism or like alcohol or it might have just been the alcohol that did it for you because they
interviewed a guy in the documentary said like oh I eat it every day and what's funny is that guy
looks kind of like fucking John Lennon yeah um and I'm thinking like well if it makes you look like
John Lennon it can't be that bad right it's you know feed it every day that you therefore it makes
you grow those glasses wait what was that I think I watched it at at the digi house uh with Trixie
and maybe Victor there no no not supersize me but like the response to it you know what I mean
there was like oh there was yeah there was like it was it called baloney or something there was a
counter there was a counter I watched it I watched the counter documentary and it was like yeah the
guy eats mcdonald's every day but like he loses weight because he also starts like exercising
and stuff that had a it had a really cringy like animated segment in the middle with like
yeah really like uncomfortable like stupid libertarian like moralizing
yeah that part's bad but like the point he's making is good it's like you know it's not
yeah you actually well if you wanted to you actually could eat mcdonald's every day and
still like lose weight and stay healthy you could eat mcdonald's I think I think it's just a bad habit
for children yeah no yeah yeah that's that's kind of like one every day that's kind of what
it took like ronald I mean they kind of already knew that even back in the day too because they
you'd never like there probably is like one or two commercials where you see ronald's eating
like mcdonald's food but like the majority of them he's never eating it they kind of just he's
just kind of sitting in front of it and he's never put it in his fucking mouth but yeah you never
see him like eating any of it yeah he never eats it he's he's a total I mean it's probably just
because he hates it it's not it's not you know this is alive yeah but I was it's probably just
because like it's not a very flattering like look for a person and also he would get his clown
makeup all over the food and it would probably just be messy and like he's already got red like
ketchup or there's a way to eat there's a way to eat with clown makeup on I done it before yeah I
mean I'm sure they could wait to eat out pussy that's disgusting clowns they don't have that on the
menu no they don't they don't have mine at my McDonald's they will we're doing a massive rebrand
pcp is now going to be a fast food chain I'm thinking about um I'm thinking about uh trying to get
a job at McDonald's for like a month and I just put copies of McPuglachy and people's bags
oh that would be so funny they get dude that would be they get home they're like what the fuck is
this that would actually be like really funny how would you how would you stealth it you'd have to
you'd be behind the counter or something okay I have to like it has to be drive through yeah and
like the thing is I'd have to like grease all over the copies that's true but luckily it's like
just it because it's just I had the test copy that I got it's just like yellowish printer paper
but uh that that being said I have to like um hide a stacked somewhere near the counter and
and you could probably hide it well enough that people just think it's like oh this just looks
like paper like it's just paper that's on the left there and it might be important yeah it'll
touch it right and then I just casually just put it I mean I can even pretend what would you do
kind of like oh do you want some sauce and then like you know get one and put the sauce in it and
then put it in the bag what's the conversation like when you're you're working at mcdonald's
in like two weeks into your you're working at mcdonald's your boss is like cheesy I need to see
you in my office what are these and he really is on a stack of mcpogliacci it's like where did you
get I don't know I don't know I they were there when I when I started I thought those were napkins
I thought those were napkins the paper doesn't seem like it's kind of like flimsy it doesn't
seem like such a what a piece of shit I can't believe they're in $15
I say like look it's yellow like the burger wrapper I thought you guys made it
he could wrap the burgers in the mcpogliacci or you know what would be funny I'd be like oh
fucking um fucking the man the was it the vice manager whatever the fuck they're called the
assistant manager like he I saw him just grab that and put a sauce in it and put it in the bag so
I thought oh that's what you're supposed to do and I just kept doing it um yeah I don't know who's
restocking it I mean I guess I think you brought them here's the dead giveaway
you just gotta go buy a pseudonym when you apply for the job that's true or I gotta print out a
special batch that just has to name cheesy man I mean they could just look up cheesy and find my
name it's not that hard oh man well that's a plan um it has to be I'm I'm imagining you're wearing
the clown makeup the whole time that would be such a weird like stealth market that would require
like a really incredible commitment to the bit which I would respect immensely it would it would and
I don't know if I got that it's a lot it's quite it's a lot to do you gotta have you gotta be like
you you know you're at the drive through the hand over the thing and then you ninja star throw like
like the the book in behind them so they can't see it and it's in the back of their car
um yeah true it's um it's something um I mean you know I'm kind of hoping that this is this is
my kind of what I'm hoping in my brain because I'm hoping that I by by the time this podcast
get out the motion comic should be available for people to like watch and I'm hoping that I see enough
yeah yeah yeah but I could do it I mean I already got everything in place I guess I better hurry and
record those lines then yeah please I appreciate it but um what I was saying is that um I hope I mean
either if it's out like by now or even I wanted to be up before the deadline because I'm hoping
that enough attention could be brought to it that like it makes it worthwhile to extend the deadline
a little bit more you know because like oh now a new group of people are finding out about
McPuglatchy because of the motion comic you know right it's it's it's it's kind of it's it's a gamble
but I think I think overall like over time you are gonna like talk about hey do you know about
this comic yada yada yada you know I mean yeah I know what I'm saying that's I think so I think
that's plausible I mean it's a really it's just a really funny idea I've heard something that could
exist so I think I think yeah I think you've uh if I could go slight yeah that's it if I could go
like slightly back in time I probably would have done the motion comic before doing pre-orders but
um kind of like spurred on them I mean it's not like you have to stop taking orders after the
comic right you can still take orders right yeah yeah I could if people like um I mean
because they send me it in bulk when they um when they say you have to like order a certain amount
so I know I know like I'm probably not going to get to that number but like I am going to have
so and like you know I have physical conventions I'm planning to take the book too so you know
people can get it in person if they see me um I'm doing another convention next month
too and I'm actually doing a panel for the first time oh doing a dynamic panel what do you mean
what's the what's the panel it's uh it's oh the panel is um actually there's a there's a page for it
but I think I think I gave it the name uh how to design a villain is the name of the panel
hmm and it's uh it's basically um it starts off as kind of a very like I give you like the
abridge basic um tips for designing a character and then we then we jump into talking about
designing villains and then I talk about like here's my mentality when I came to designing these four
villain versus characters and then the second half of the panel is kind of like a audience member
like they give suggestions for what to design and I create a character right in front of their eyes
like a magician yeah exactly and I'm doing that at uh the convention is called uh Fangia
it's here in San Diego and it's pretty it's pretty cool I was uh boofing there last year it's not too
bad um what was kind of annoying last year was that the one of the halls where they have the
vendors also doubles as like a hall with a stage and sometimes they're bringing people to play like
the loud ass music like live performances but the thing is like you're trying to sell so imagine if
you hear a fucking like Japanese drums in the same room as you're trying to like tell people like oh
this is what my comic's about but they can't hear you that's like that was like one of my complaints
about the event um also there was a guy there like cosplaying as christian which I didn't like
kind of was really bothered by that um luckily there was other people there who were too who
were also bothered by them and they approached this guy and told him like hey wait a guy doing
what you're doing say that again a cosplay yeah yeah he like he came well yeah he came in with
the striped sweater and he had like a sonic chip okay yeah and I was I was like what are you doing
there bud what do you think you're doing well I mean what's the problem was he bothering people
it's just I in my opinion it's like a hot take I think it's very inappropriate that I did that
I'll say that because I don't I think I've said this is publicly before I really don't like
like anyone who's really into like yeah into the I mean I guess I get that because I
I I'd see it like at the end of the day I see it as like this was like a massive like
like kind of like a well not kind I think it was like a cyberbullying campaign on like
basically a disabled person online and I think um I think like when you cosplayed it when you do
like the fan art when people like sell the christian shirt merch and stuff like that it's this weird
kind of like glossing over the fact this was kind of actually very terrible that's just happened to
this person and I know I know people like to say like oh well he turned out to I mean she turned
out to do this terrible shit sure but that was like very much at the tail end of the whole thing
the majority of it was her getting goaded to do awful like things it it was like ultimately like
bullying and I'm hoping that I'm hoping with that when we eventually get the Netflix documentary
about this um they go with that handle because it's like you're kind of right but don't you think
but don't you think it's going a little bit far to be like this guy's wearing a costume I don't
wear I'm gonna I'm gonna like make an issue of it and complain about it I don't know there was like
someone wearing a costume I I somebody it's them just like this guy's wearing a costume with
disabled person that the whole joke is like hey remember this like disabled person like they
got bullied online well I'm gonna dress up as that person and I I think I would I think I would
understand if it was like something like years ago like it was Henry Darker had like a look
okay I don't I don't know if it was you I mean the person's still alive I guess
a lot of it was like a recent memory sure I guess uh whatever I I know the the internet
makes things seem like they happen a while long ago because things happen so fast but
like I think the main thing is you you get a bit of a sense of the type of person who would choose
that as a cosplay and then you're I mean that's probably yeah I I don't I don't mind their costume
I guess I wouldn't like report them like I don't like I don't like most bad first impression
that's that's that's true I I I think there's like I think there's something kind of wrong with
people who like obsess over it I mean there's there's there's a there's a I know and I I'm
talking to Ben I'm talking to I know I'm talking to Ben who made like two videos about it yeah it's
fine I I know because of that I've had I've had I've had so many I've had so many interactions
with so many interactions with people online who are like so bad about it like I know the type of
person you're talking about I just wouldn't assume it I mean honestly yeah if I got it would I just
wouldn't assume it based on the solely on the fact that someone's interested in Chris or thinks Chris
is funny or even wore a costume of it but like yeah there's a definite type of person who's like
too into it and is weird about it and is probably a Kiwi farmer and probably doesn't think trans
people are real most of the time if you if you if you ask them etc etc but also live free or die
but also but also I'll never take away his right to say it I'll die for your right for your right
to wear that striped shirt in public sir okay well I the only thing I'll die for I don't like it
I don't like it I'm not a fan I think it's um I think it's awful well I think you're awful that's
okay well all right okay okay that guy who who made that twitter comic you made
that aren't you twitter how dare you criticize someone else for something when you did something
that I don't like you hypocrite you made big twitter artists and that was bad
you know it's so funny like answer the question that was bad
cheesy was it bad or not for you doing that just say yes no in fact just say yes no I just say yes
admit it admit it admit you did admit you did you did something or die okay what are you saying
um deep fake deep fake me on like uh passion of the Christ uh scene where he's getting
crucified but it's me and I'm like um I regret big twitter artists oh no what I was gonna say
earlier is that I keep hearing like people tell me about like um they tell me about other
bigger artists like just DMing other art bigger artists and be like hey just retweet this for me
and they just kind of do it and it's like they're they're not friends or anything they're just mutuals
and it just kind of happens like all the time casually and I'm gonna hear everything and like
well they're doing it they've been doing it yeah the problem the problem is that like you're not
big enough for them to give a shit about yeah um it's it's uh it's it's annoying it's a yeah it's
it's annoying um I don't consider like mutuals friends I think I only consider someone a friend
if I like talk to them in a voice call at least like uh 200 I keep count
no but I can send this so I can guess it I consider a mutual a friend when I leave a reply
and then they like their play I consider my friend is one mutual a friend when we meet up and and
fuck I consider my friend once he starts sending me salacious photos that's that's the line that's
when that's the confirmation like okay this person's in it he's he's part of the cheesy the the
cheesy on you know what the cheesy family you know what's weird you know maybe you you know what
I'm like I'm like I'm like not a nudes guy I like don't like nudes yeah really you prefer
talking over personalities and talking I would hate it if nudes no uh I just don't no no no
what I I don't when I'm uh talking to someone I'm not I'm not angling for nudes I kind of don't
care to see the picture I you know if I if I if I think they're attractive and I want to have sex
with them I would want to meet them in person and maybe we fuck and that's cool I I don't know I
don't need I don't need them to send me pictures of their body like I'll see it you know what I mean
like you don't like you're kind of like I don't look up what cars they have at the dealership I
just show up to the dealership yeah see what they got yeah I guess so yeah sure I mean I'm not a car
guy so I wouldn't make that comparison but sure close yeah of course I don't like nudes and I don't
like cars and I don't like oh my god I'm a woman I was a woman all along nude cars if I I don't
like guy things if a smoke show if a real if a real if a real hot babe DM view and saying oh Ben
oh let me show you this picture of my pussy what would you say like no no one's no one's say no
thank you your personality no be fine no be fine I'm just I just I don't I don't I probably wouldn't
I probably wouldn't ask for nudes even if even if I thought I could get them I would just be like
let's find you earn them let's meet let's meet and fuck baby let's let's but babe just show
show me a picture of your personality that's the real that's what I'm really sure I mean I'd like
to see a picture of your diet I'd like to see what she looks like and I'm like and then and then
from that I can be like do I like this okay good and I don't need I don't need to see the nude
to know if I'm interested I don't need to see the nude to know if I'm interested or not
but that's but that's not it is that that's how what nudes is about it's not about like
determining am I interested or not right it's usually like if you're getting nudes you're
already interested yes it's it's so if the so if the interest is there social interaction I don't
really need the nude let's just get together I think um now and now there's this now now woman
who's in Ben Sainz yeah I'm talking about yeah I hope god god I hope she's listening god I hope
you know I think there's this kind of like thing you hear all the time where like
um people are like oh why does anyone pay for only fans when there's like just titties free
online you know and it's kind of like well you're missing the point of it because it's not even like
necessarily about seeing titties just for titties sake but like um there's this kind of like um
almost like a a bond that you're paying for you know because a lot of like people who do kind of
only fans and it's not even necessarily like an only fans thing there's something like kind of
social interaction that you get from someone sending their own picture of their own titty to you
instead of you finding like a random there's a little bit more of a connection there yeah it's
like it's like yeah obviously it's paid for but you know it's part of it you know an incredibly
cringe way to look at listen I'm not I'm not trying to be a snob about it because I am on only fans
and I have I'll say at least one subscription but it's not but it's not a wait type type it into
the general no you don't gotta tell us just no it doesn't matter I'm gonna throw out some names
that you're gonna just just like wink look uh twice if I right I think I might have mentioned some on
the on the on a bonus episode one time but it doesn't matter but the point is it's not is definitely
not about oh I feel a social connection I feel some sort of some sort of a social interaction
with this person it is not about that is it is about it is about I want to get that I I like this
person I like their look I want to see a person that looks like this doing that they've got this
paywall content and I'm prepared to pay for it right I guess right it's not it's I mean I guess
it is a parasocial thing in the sense that like every like online interaction is parasocial but
it's not like oh I feel close to them I yeah I because they specifically sent me their news
because I made the request and they gave it to me no I made the request because I wanted to see
it I don't give a shit and they gave it to you sending a thing for it right right it's not it's
not about it's not about that so I don't agree with me Ben tell me Ben you're never taken advantage
of when they say like hey guys uh doing uh dick raid offers send your dick for the DMs you never
took an advantage of those deals I don't take advantage of women cheesy I don't take advantage
of women or deals because I believe in consent and consent and deals violate the non-aggression
principle I believe deals go against free market I believe deals are against and I trust the market
I believe deals are against God's law if you read the Torah it says uh it says uh don't eat don't
eat anything that's verboten uh uh no usury and it should have had a third clause it should have
also outlawed deals but they forgot God just God just forgot I am scrolling through the people
that you follow and see if any name pops up you don't I really want a pinpoint what on what on
twitter yeah on twitter I don't think the person I or people that I that I that I I don't think
they're on twitter oh okay this is this is your this is your special just for you
girl I mean not every not everyone who's on only fans is on twitter but many of them I mean that's
just what yeah many yeah many yeah because it's like the one social media platform where you could
post like Vaj and Bube for uh without getting in trouble uh it's probably true that it's probably
true that most of them are that's probably true I stopped going on only fans when I realized that
they you don't get good you don't get good payout they take a big cut of your money
what they take like forward they take like 20 it's kind of a big cut yeah yeah it is a big
cut I know a lot of people go like on fansly I don't know how it's the same it's the same cut I
actually looked into it and it's the same cut on fansly that's a shame I guess like I guess
then the idea is like oh they just go do both platforms I'd rather I'd rather do safe content
and get a better cut is there is there like a meaningful difference between uh doing one
versus the other I'm not necessarily I assumed only fans was just better because it's probably
got a bigger user base because more people have heard of it I I think I think the fact that like
I mean that's probably the bigger reason why people still use only fan is because more people
have heard of only fan so like even if they take a bigger cut you still guaranteed more people than
yeah yeah fansly or the alternatives although I see a lot of people kind of branching out
and doing other things did I did I mention that thing about how in that vlog Trixie said that she
thought that if she had joined only fans uh when when someone told her to that she could single
handedly have changed its reputation to be not just for for porn people I heard of it oh it's
super funny she yeah there's there's a there's a there's a picnic adventure where she and Bert are
driving and she's going she's talking about something it doesn't matter but she she's
straight up says like yeah if I had joined only fans at such a such time she says I made
patreon's reputation what it was because I was one of the first people to be successful on patreon
I basically made patreon what it was so if I had joined only fans when it when someone told me to
if I joined it at that time I would have single handedly changed it so that its reputation was
not just for sluts that's her her her wording now mine uh it it would have been for everyone
but unfortunately but I didn't do that so we live in the in the alternate timeline that's so
stupid it's so stupid it's so stupid on many levels because like many levels because the
thing about patreon is not even true at all she was never she was never in like the top
tier like by the time before she even joined patreon Amanda Palmer was making like $30,000 a
month like it's not even close I love Trixie she should livestream more and stuff like her live
streams her live streams are gold such as I don't have the money to give you a refund on
plebeian wee blu-ray just buy bends instead the ultimate uh the ultimate endorsement
true but I got four more please guys please just get just get these last four off my hands I'll do
she did rescind that comment just say she she okay she did she yes under duress she made the
written statement it's like I do not I do not endorse I do not endorse bends blu-rays under
any circumstances thank you and sorry thank you and sorry end quote she got the she got the endless
jess uh call she did she did get she did get the call she did get the call after the whole debacle
right and she's like and he's and he's like uh uh uh uh uh Trixie don't do that jessie finally had to
do something on the internet for once in his life jessie had to oh he actually he actually had to
do something or talk to someone Ben what were you Ben you fucking monster you made jessie
trick now I'm get out of this fucking trick she did it Trixie did it I didn't I didn't make her
say that I didn't make her say that I asked the question there we go no but it's kind of no but
everything is kind of just your fault then ultimately like I know you're you're the problem
you are the prototypical twitter follower everything's Trixie Trixie does something fucked up oh it
must be Ben it must be Ben's fault for doing the only logical thing that one could possibly do
under these circumstances I I don't I don't attack who but who but who made those circumstances
who made the market the invisible hand of which guided me to do the thing the terrible things
that I do the golden which it all comes back all the golden thread the the shiny golden thread of
hope they all come back to the same to the same spider spinning its web
in the branches of the studio I'm sorry all right let's let's continue let's let's go
I found I found a couple of spicy names and Ben's follow right now no stop Anna Anna Callahan
Erica Utterhoven Nicole Morel Christine Barber ooh Ben
those are 34th those are all like 34th uh Midlands District yeah those are those are all like
local like district level Massachusetts like like like a state representative candidate
ooh oh Ben Ben's got a tight Ben Ben likes a thinking girl Ben likes a girl who knows what
she wants and that's uh Ben likes a girl who fires those neurons
yeah exactly I I don't I you've caught me I don't I've been caught unfortunately Ben likes uh Ben
likes powerful women Ben likes powerful mommies that want to be like who's the and be like who's
a bigger who's a bigger dom who's a bigger dom than your elected representative
exactly then a local member of the student of the city council
talk about power you talk about a power dynamic
exact oh mommy mommy mommy's coming remember rarity said that gave you remember when rarity said
that yes I remember when right okay I'm not the only one they remember someone rarity said that right
was that when it was she was like enamored with boulder opal opal was in a tree opal was stuck
in a tree and she she said mommy's coming she's mama's coming mama's to get you down from the tree
yeah don't worry it's fine don't worry daddy's home daddy's home oh there's no daddy's in there's
no daddy's in my little pony nobody has daddy's in my little pony I think that's from like an
opening about fancy pants that's from like a Drake song I think no you just said that at the start
it was daddy's home don't worry don't worry don't worry don't worry yeah it sounds like something
he'd say check out this uh even though he's a lesbian no check out this tweet that I got
no no what do you think of this Ben um happy saint patrick's day
from yoshi I'm green so you can't pinch me body oh oh it's a video hey whoa it's a video
hey I mean look at look at that nice shell uh isn't that a saddle that's not a shell yoshi
doesn't wear a shell yoshi has a saddle uh inaccurate never my my boner just went down from noticing
that the shell that's yoshi doesn't have a shell that's a koopa why is she wearing a koopa it's
fucking women fake gamer sluts don't play video games right they don't they didn't they they use
their too busy showing their giant butts she probably used spells and dark souls
she probably did a this mad arcane build
but get this this is fancy pants do you remember fancy pants I do I do remember fancy pants and
I remember and I remember flirtally flirtally is my favorite my favorite background pony far
away these two these two stole the show and they didn't do anything yeah they did I like these two
flirtally that's a funny name I don't think that's her I just got a flirtally on our cutie mark I
don't think that's an official name I think that's just what fans call her I think this that she's
called flair well maybe I don't in that episode no she doesn't have a name maybe they gave her one
later I think they call it because on her cutie mark is a flirtally I guess it just makes sense
oh yeah that's that's why that's why pinkie pie is named balloon yeah balloon balloon balloon
balloon but babe as like yeah the baby little baby and that they it pops and like is pops
it's got a but you yo babe yo bitch you got a booty like a balloon in that it's popping
babe I need to I need to pop that balloon booty you got going for you I yeah that's right that's
what I said it's it's mixed it makes too much sense it makes too much sense pinkie but we all agree
pinkie pie is a pog right yeah but but if you have a big balloon we have a big balloon but don't
send it to Ben don't send him a picture of it he wants to see a picture of your personality he
wants to see a picture let me see let me see it in person let me see it in person let me see it in
person you would be a pa a papga that ass pony girl yeah okay pink okay sure right
you know you know you know this this is cool I don't know people this is really amazing
call me call me crazy I just think people don't really look good in nudes I just think it they
most people look better in person wow body-shaming humanity I think I've never seen a you never
seen a new uh a good no it's not that I've never seen a good nude it's just it's just that uh I've
seen I've had I've had I've had sexual partners if you can believe it and in my opinion I don't
think I've ever had I don't think I've ever known you know I've they look better in person
than in a photograph I think I think most people I think photographs are generally not flattering
most photographs are not very flattering the same okay okay but like I think you can't have a good
nude I think a lot of people like nude sending is not very isn't a very high art no don't people
don't bring like photography degrees to that some of them do if they're if they've got like an
account but it so so so that being the case if it's not if it's not a flattering picture that's
like very gotta learn how to take better picture then why do I want to see it I don't you'll look
you'll look better in person the thing is that the thing yeah true I agree in person is way better
but like I think there's something kind of like there's something kind of hot about the amateurness
of it in my opinion you know the amateur point it's like its own category um well it's there's
something kind of like yeah attractive about the the confidence something human the confidence
I get that I get the decision to do it in the first place is nice uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh so I yeah I get
it yeah especially if they do like you know you know actually I mean yeah you know I kind of agree
with that actually you kind of turn me around on it if there's like if it's like you kind of turn
me on on that yeah nice um okay good that's yeah that's the okay that's that's gonna say guys that's
consent that's consent for uh the person or people I'll never tell that I'm subscribed to on only fans
they're not they're not very professional they're pretty but okay but it's like okay it's it's not
it's not what I appreciate about them is that in their unprofessionality is that I like to see them
in let's say in in situations I'd like to see them but I like the the amateurness of it makes it feel
authentic makes it feel like this is a real person doing these things it feels unstaged
uh uh so I mean in that sense I I completely agree I don't know if I feel quite the same
way about oh I took a picture of myself in a mirror I think that I I feel the same way in
in this one specific sense that like porn doesn't have to be like nudes but porn sometimes is more
like interesting and engaging when it's people characters just doing normal things and they
just happen to be sexy they're not like going oh look at how sexy I am and doing all this stuff
and yes like that sort of is like that feels fake that feels like staged when someone when a character
just happens to be like wrapped up in like a spiderweb or like tied up in like ropes or something
you know I just just natural you know they're just going they were just going about their day
just doing their just doing their job they're just making a living you know filing texas with
their titties out like bouncing around right you know I don't like a fake girl if you're wearing
makeup ill disgusting no makeup makeup is just a default thing you just you can you can do you
can wear your makeup you can wear nice things and then you can be like hanging out on a on a
playing a video game or like on a bench you don't need to be looking at the camera being like oh I
see the the yeah the real um in like a lot of like porn that you find on like sites where the girl is
like uh you know like the art the artifice of it is very like because because I know that because
they make such a big show of it it like really feels like this is acting and I can and it it's
like calling attention to the the fakeness of it and that's a really big like ugh I don't like
people cannot act right at least they don't need to if they're pretty enough right so they don't
need to learn how right I am yeah yeah yeah yeah one of these days I'm gonna direct a very like
weird porno where I'm it's gonna be one of those things where like when people pass around a clip
of something that seems funny and weird and then everyone in the comments like uh they people
don't know there's no porno remember remember that lemon thing remember that thing with like it was
a lemon party no not lemon the lemon stealing whore yes yes lemon stealing whore that's the one oh
yeah uh with the James Dean love that I don't even really even remember what happens in it I just
remember that James Dean and a lemon tree and a lemon stealing whore there's two porn stars and
they're like sitting on their bench and they're like oh I love our backyard yeah me too I also love
my lemon tree yeah let's look at our lemon tree right now and and I'm not even exaggerating this
was exactly the dialogue so they look at their lemon tree and there's this woman who is the
self-titled lemon stealing whore she um she's stealing their lemons and she put in it in her
like I figure she's wearing like a onesie kind of thing like a onesie bikini kind of thing and
they're like hey that's the lemon stealing whore and like we only see the intro of this I imply
they potentially I think they punish the lemon stealing whore in like a sexual way yeah that's
what I would have done in that situation as well yeah if I were to catch a lemon stealing whore
my backyard to catch a lemon stealing whore I'm glad you remember you remember this better than I
do I'm really glad because I thought I might have like hallucinated this you know you know how you
know why that video like what the reason why that video got me the first place and this was like
early like YouTube why back when like people could see what what you like like every video you like
you know um and you know you know the person who originally like spread it through their likes
and everyone in the comment section was kind of like oh I did so and so like this was um it was
eagle raptor eagle raptor oh that's like yeah if you yeah and we can remember going when I watched
that video originally because I saw that for an eagle raptor like because I was like oh I love eagle
raptor and then I see is like what the fuck 11 ceiling horn is likes and I click and then everyone's
comments like oh why did Aaron like this because it's probably because the same reason a billion
other people liked it yeah at the time he was doing like that little he was doing those little
animation where it was called lemon and lemon and bill yeah yeah lemon and bill yeah and they um
and people were like oh he's looking for lemon and bill material lemon and lemon stealing bill
yeah let's ceiling bill yeah that was that was the time uh rest in peace eagle raptor
it'll be you'll never be forgotten those were the days never you never be forgotten that's right
did you know that game grumps still exists and and not only that it's like if you look at it's like
I can still hear the voice of Danny sex bang uh on the wind now they're doing thumbnails now where
they're doing like the the default youtuber gamer where they've got their photograph of
themself doing a whore face with the picture of the game next to them I was no longer the old
orange and the little faces that's that's amazing actually I can't it's so it's so different and
it's like well contents about about the same they're just sitting on a couch that's so weird
laughing and talking it's like you know I was yeah I was considering thumbnails for my uh for the
video the the twitch announcement video and I was I was picking out like which pictures of like
screen caps of myself from uh to use and I was just picking out and just thinking like you know
you kind of want to look deranged like you kind of want to look like you're a freak in the thumbnail
like like like mr beast like mr beast I don't know I think mr beast is extremely off-putting
looking especially the fakes he makes and all his thumbnail I mean and I'm not I know I'm not the
only person that thinks this but yeah it's not uh it's not like a it's not a an accident that he
chooses photos to look kind of freaky you I think that's just been a thing for a long time there's
something compelling about like a sort of deranged looking guy or something I don't know how to explain
it there but it has to be on purpose it has to be like an intentional thing I think I think a little
while ago a few years ago there was a trend of using like um like photoshop to like enlarge
the eyes and the teeth and to make it like look like absurdly horrifically different than a human
face like if you look if you look at it it looks really weird that trend has gone away a little
bit because it's a little too scary there's there's some that still works there's something yeah even
if it's not like good it's there's something that just grabs you about yeah like a human face
with some sort of like visual interest even if it's a negative interest but if like the eyes and
the teeth are really big your face goes right to it it's like a like a jump scare it's like ah
like um when you see it yeah it's really a sad and pathetic that that is how everything looks
if you want to maximize like clickability you have to be the same kind of a freak but I want
varieties of freaks you know there's a certain kind of thing that the human brain dreams
there's a certain kind of thing that the human brain just sees and has a visceral
reaction to and it's just all about getting that it's that reaction I think what I I like
book covers I like album covers those are cool this was on them I'll read them if they had if
like imagine if like albums and stuff were all physical now and then I mean they are physical
but like you know what I mean like albums like albums like you go you don't go to Spotify to
find albums you go to the store and they've got all these albums CDs and whatever but they've
all got the artist they've got the artist on the front cover doing well oh my god I can't believe
I made this sort of like face and like that's what gets people to buy it you travel to like
an alternate reality where everything is the same like there's no change except for one thing
and that's like the the album for Beatles rubber soul is them doing like the soy face pointing
and they're pointing at their own music yeah they're pointing at their album it's like a slip
so you could pull it out you could pull out the part where they're like pointing and it's like
the regular album cover but this is yeah I was gonna say earlier this kind of reminds me of
there's this like there's this kind of theory that like stupid insane people have where like
people were saying something about like have you noticed that you're just kind of just naturally
scared of like pale horrific faces and like you know maybe maybe maybe it's because like back then
our ancestors saw some sort of subspecies creature that maybe was a pale evil monster thing and it's
ingrained in our DNA and that's why we're scared of it and it's beyond fucking stupid it's because
it's like well like there's a lot of reasons now to kind of be scared of someone pale or scary looking
than like something stupid and like oh it's at one point there was actually pale scary looking
monsters who lived on earth and they and they were like one of the one of the lesser oh this is like
an eight this is like an alien yeah yeah um well not not necessarily an alien but that like there
could there's just a creature like that that is kind of like the way people talk about it they
seem to explain it some sort of like one of the several subspecies of sapien that exists like
what like early man was developing because there was like a shitload of different like subspecies
I mean there's lots of ways for a face to look uncanny and alarming and like yeah being being
extremely pale I guess is one of them but it's like right definitely not the only one it's like
a weird kind of thing or like someone out there heard about the whole thing what assassins create
where it's like oh do you know that like your entire family history is near a dna and shit like that
and that like kind of crops up back and it's like oh what if like what if like your great great great
great grandpa saw like a spooky monster and it traumatized him so bad that it like passed on
and now that's why you're traumatizing spooky monsters that's what we call lamarky that's what
we call lamarky and uh genetics you know about those malarky and more like more like malarky
lamarky said that like he thought that like the reason giraffes have long necks is because like
previous generations had to like they had to reach up with their necks to try and grab high fruit
and he thought that that physical activity like like physically stretched their neck out and that
and that then the giraffes would have babies and they would and they would pass that trade
on to their offspring and it was because they had developed it through like you know through their
the physical uh uh mechanical action through the through the grind set right yeah yeah it was not
that it was a natural selection by like gene mutation um so that's gene that's what that is it's
like oh your grandpa got really scared by a ghost so and he got so scared that he like it like he
learned that associate and then he and then his kid he's it was it was locked into his DNA from
that point on yeah so he gave birth to kids it's we're also scared of ghosts it's it's like it's
just like in the bible they said uh what it was like joseph or some fucking some fucking antediluvian
guy god was like hey god hey i'll tell you a trick to make to breed goats with stripes and they and
so he said cut stripes into a stick and put the stick in a water and then have the goats drink
the water and then their babies will have stripes and they did what fucking magic and hey and you
know that you know what else yes yes and you know the other part that's in the same chapter where they
describe uh the circular pool whose ratio of its diameter to its circumference is exactly three
lamal
whoa if you pi pi is i can't believe the number three is in pi is exactly three god according to
to the bible lamal
and talk about the bible okay all right all right that's my that's it i've said enough
that's that's our that's our weekly bible rant where we're talking about
we were talking about give and take dot say we weren't but let's do that
hey did you know that my website is is new now yeah it's been a lot of work getting it
getting it working and and stuff but it's not really much of like a big update until i have
new stuff to put on there but i'm i'm proud of it because it's you know so it's a lot of it's a lot
of uh it's my stuff it's my domain it's my little castle and i like that it's it's now no longer
associated with wordpress and i have a lot more control over the hgml and and all the stuff take
dot site uh and i'm gonna have like links to my to amazon so you can buy the chlorissa gun smoke
book right on the site oh yeah and it's easy it's gonna be easy to like uh well it is easy to like
use instead of how it was before i see yeah these link these where you had to click on the link at
the bottom of the page and now you can do arrow keys these links uh these links are uh yeah they
don't they just the buy print and buy digital links do they just they just like those don't
now lemau those don't work currently as we're recording they will when i've published it which
will be like tomorrow yeah cool um you know i should link your link the site oh yeah well i mean
you know what i guess as soon as they work i'll i'm gonna buy a copy of chlorissa gun smoke in the
bandit king i i guess i'll be i guess is it is it $15 plus shipping or is it just 15 uh yeah we'll
be plus shipping but you pay for it and it'll be shipped from america's they print it in the country
that it's probably going to be shipped to so there's really good shipping actually it's like two bucks
probably amazing can you you know how if you buy like $25 worth of stuff on amazon you get free
shipping can i like uh or maybe is that just an american thing i know i'm i'm pretty sure i mean
it'll i i don't know i wonder if i could include that in my type of item i wonder that i could
include that in my amazon order a copy of chlorissa gun smoke and a jar of a of a corn fiber please
to add up to $25 to get that that's what you should do everyone should should add a chlorissa
gun smoke volume to their shopping cart to save on delivery fee exactly you you can't afford you
can't afford not to and then and the corn fiber of course too and corn pop yeah what ben said
obviously but in in the course of of making the site i had to like go through all of my comics
again uh bail jake is great bail jake is really fun i should reread it it's been a while i love bail
jake i love ken and story i even love horse stuck even though it's like really really old and uh digi
is in there yeah right at the end uh boy i had to scroll way back to see that i think it's a great
feeling when you go back to your older work and you still think it like looks good you know yeah
a lot yeah i mean it's obviously like worse drawing than what i could do now like the the
things i tried my hardest at i remember certain panels that like oh i tried my hardest to make
this look good and it just sort of is okay but now i could do so much better uh a part of me
was thinking like oh when i do the volume one of villain verse where i have the the prologue to
chapter six maybe i should go back and redraw a couple those panels so they look a little bit
better but then i i look at those panels and i'm like ah this still looks good i still looks good
i don't need to change anything it you know it's still serviceable very i still think
about about which comic you're talking about uh villain verse are you still doing it are you
still gonna do more villain verse oh yeah i've been yeah okay i think i mentioned it before that um
i kind of put that on pause because uh it's not yeah making me it's not making me as much money as i
thought it would i've been trying to focus on more kind of like comics that will help me
stand out i understand i understand i i i get you because uh this should this should
as tough i um i hate i hate talking to other artists i think me too terrible people you know
you know i was joking but go on i might i might agree with you even more okay so what i what i mean
is that um so every time i like i'm not every time but there's a there's a there's a certain group
there's a certain type of artist that every time i tell him like yeah like what's kind of annoying
i mean i'm basically just complaining about like oh man i'm not making a living tough tough to make
money isn't yeah yeah exactly and then this person is always like dude who cares about the money
dude it's all about you know it's all about making art for yourself man all cool all cool shut the
fuck up shut up you fucking monster yeah i hate yeah i do people actually say that do people
actually say that in casual conversation people do say that to me like yeah i mean it's that's
yeah that's not reading the room at all if you're having trouble with money and you need the money
because you do need the money because everyone needs my job my job my job sure is hard my job
sure is all who cares how hard it is it's like because like i mean i get the ultimate in a perfect
society yeah of course you would be only making art for yourself because all that that's all that
matters ultimately but in this society where like i want to i want to make a living off something
that doesn't make me want to shoot my fucking like brains out yeah you know like and i basically
argue like man it sucks that like the job that i want is it making me enough i'm gonna be i'm gonna
be perfectly honest it's ultimately what i'm saying i'm gonna be perfectly honest i don't
really talk to that many other artists i talk to like gib oh i could tell how do you how could you
tell i could tell it's easy okay well i won't i won't ask i won't ask for any more details uh i i
don't uh i don't really talk to that many uh and i mean okay those when people say that something
like that is it people that like are they successful or are they people who are also no it's never
it's never successful okay it's so it's so it's cope so it's cope well it's not even like cope it's
kind of like i feel like because i noticed is that if if an artist has like a well-paying job and
then they do the art thing um obviously they don't care too much about making money off of art right
because they have the well-paying job and so they can do art for themselves yeah and that's fine
yeah um that's that's cool if you want if you want to go down that route there's no problem with
that but like there's something it's so it just feels kind of weirdly dismissive not like oh i want
to go down a route where like the stuff that i like to make is the stuff that's keeping me afloat
yeah and um to some people that doesn't like click like oh you should just if you like making that
so you should just make it and it's like yeah but you know i kind of want to kind of eat yeah i
gotta want to eat i kind of have rent to pay i kind of yeah it's it's it's just it's i would say i
guess there's two like if they're like a successful artist it's obviously hit like hypocritical of
him to say that if they're like yeah like wealthy or at least like their bills are paid by some other
thing and like they just they they're just like a hobbyist and they say that then it's like why are
why are you saying that like you don't you don't have the same concern as me so like fucking how
how dare you dismiss it like that right like who who are you to tell me oh don't worry about that
fuck yourself uh and then yeah if if they're if they're also struggling and they're then then like
i could see i could see someone who's like also doing that just being it is like cope this is
like oh it's it's not about the money it's just about it's about uh it's about the passion
and can i pay my bills no but you know i don't expect to uh i am a lowly worm uh this is what i
deserve yeah i i think um what i was gonna say another thing that i also kind of like
in the same vein as this is like uh can i tell people that like i i aim to make
stuff that like i try to make stuff that like is like popular like that can be popular you know
and a lot of like other i guess the same kind of artists who's like just drawing for themselves
like raises an eyebrow to that like comment because they're like oh you should try to make
stuff that appeals to you you should make art for yourself oh you should just make the art you
want to see uh have they ever had bakuman it's literally all about it's all about the reader
surveys nothing else matters except the reader surveys i with me i like to um i like to i i
talk about this i i've tried to talk about this on other podcasts and i keep getting interrupted
but hey i hey actually i mean you didn't talk about the pcb website for a second not going
sorry but but basically and i think i have mentioned it before on this podcast is like
there's the art that like um that feeds your soul but doesn't make you any money and then there's the
art that like can make money but like kind of hurts your soul and you want to hit the middle
ground of that like right because no because no one's like a complete contrarian where they like
you don't like something that's popular right like you there's gotta be everyone likes at least
one thing that's like popular and yeah and if you're an artist you should like think about
what are the popular things you like and that and try to do your version of that popular thing you
know yeah um because that's gonna like keep you afloat actually i would yeah go on someone said
i think it might have been like i just heard someone say i think it might have been majulaar
in a video not that long ago or someone i heard some youtuber just they it was not even relevant
who had said it but someone said like a lot someone just commented that like a lot of art
this reminded me the art is a lot of the time it's about like you just see someone else
do something and you just think that sucked i i could do that better like i could do that
better than that person get and then you and then you do it and then you try to do it and
just prove that you you could do it better than that other person did it and that's just where a
lot of art comes from yeah and that's fine that's like uh i i love that that's like when you do
something out of spite which is great not even out of spite it's it's just if you i mean it's
stupid example but that reminds me of like the pony the pony scene back the pony review scene i
saw other idiots making pony reviews and i was like well this any you could do a better pony review
than this and i did that's how it that's how it starts i remember i kind of had that same
mentality when i made my first like short film in high school because there was like a a senior
at the time and i was doing your who made a short made a short horror short film and everyone loved
that everyone thought like oh that was great and awesome and epic but i was like dude you literally
just ripped off a creepy pasta like i know this creepy pasta and he passed it off as like his
his own work and i'm like ah dude this will aim as fuck dude i could make something scarier and
original and i like the thing i did you know my short film was very weird it was very particular
like i i thought i thought it was funny i guess i think a lot of time did not get it i guess we'll
never know um it's still on it's still on youtube it's called it's on my cheesy's do even dare to
watch it's on my cheesy uh classic channel it's called the dog man okay i've ever even seen that
channel uh it used to be used to be called well link link link it if you dare but i guess we don't
have time to watch it right now i don't i don't want to link it okay okay okay just take my word
for it it was really good i totally blew that guy out of the water it destroyed that guy yeah his
is he was like he was shaking he became a little quiet after dog man came out he was a little a
little silent interesting interesting you know yeah speaking speaking of oh oh no are you going
yeah god i was just gonna say that yeah i just kind of i'm annoyed by those kinds of people um i
think it's pretty cringe to not understand that like an artist would want to do art as a living
and therefore the the struggle to make it a profitable venture is like really obviously
important and what kind of a f***ing flawed wouldn't wouldn't appreciate that
i mean i i want to play devil's advocate for just a second no no to these types of people
die die die um when they say just do things that make you happy or could they be referring to like
art that is successful being good because the artist who made it like doing it
no like that happens yeah that happens obviously it may be a very misguided because it's like they
only know that's that's that's that's that's such a uh that's such a but that's probably where their
mind is when they say that might be where their mind is i would think but that's such as like a
survivorship bias thing because when you when you look at like comics that are really successful
and maybe the artist behind them is like i just draw what i like and it's just what they draw is
like something that's wildly popular it's like then it's simply it's just a coincidence like
this they're just lucky that like the thing that they really like to draw just happens to be the
thing that the zeitgeist is like really into and and it was became successful like you can't you
can't just you can't generalize that advice to everyone because most people if they just draw
whatever appeals to them most it wouldn't people wouldn't care uh they have they have to think
about how can i how can i make this something make this into something that the people like
that's my cope though i still think that if i care about what i'm doing then people will be like
oh you know what to a certain extent it's true but i don't think it's good general advice for
like how to make it in the art scene no i mean i don't know how to make it in the scene because i
mostly have money from podcasts i think um true i think it i think yeah there's a lucky few out there
who like the art they want to make is already stuff that's like super popular so they're like oh
yeah oh wow hot wow the guy who uh the guy who drew fuck when did undertale come out like 2015
something something like that 2015 the guy who just was just drawing his own undertale
art in 2015 got super popular because oh obviously he was just drawing from the heart right well not
that coincidentally at the same time he was really into a game that was super popular at the time you
know yeah like that that can't be it yeah right there's like all these like like yeah there's like
all these like other things that people don't like speak taking count speaking for counterpoint
my work is great and people will look back and say wow i wish i was a fan of gibb earlier and then
i would be a cooler but nobody but nobody but nobody will find nobody will find you i'm sorry
but nobody's gonna find you through Clarissa they're gonna find you through other stuff
and if and if they stick around then they'll read Clarissa and it'll be good and it'll
i understand this i that's why i'm i'm trying to like during Clarissa or maybe afterwards
make a few videos make a few youtube videos see if i can get some of that back
so i can i can advertise again yeah send people that way having a good website that's like good
and not shit would also do some some good you know like having a having a good presenting
front-facing base of operations that people can go to like i'm setting things up and i think it's
it's gonna work guys it's just gonna work no i believe you i believe uh speaking of okay
two things one i do want to mention about websites the pcp website when the ova is out
you will be able to download the dojin and road to radcon digitally digital pdf it'll be free it'll
be on the procrastinatorspodcast.com or uh perfectcomicparty.com go to the pcp stuff link
and uh uh there will be download downloadable pdfs for the dojin once the ova is out hey gibb
did you did you did you did you make those letters did you make that lettering for me
i need that i want that lettering i really think we could use a little bit of custom a
little custom lettering graphics for the for the buttons yeah i was focused on on website and
amazon this yeah so i will do that um i would like to see some some letters please i just like
to see some some fonts yeah i'm also gonna make i'm also gonna make a template like pdf size that
i'm gonna send to you so that you know how big the pages of the perfect oh that would be very
there would be very helpful that'd be very helpful thank you gab did you get those pictures of
spider-man that i ask i told you i need that i need that i need that uh uh i need i need that
typeface i need that typeface on my desk by six a.m tomorrow or it's your uh have your gun in your
badge spider-man um i'll i'll i'll get you the typeface i'll i'll i just need to uh change
into my uh i'm just gonna go and do that uh yeah you're an unconventional you're an unconventional
reporter but you get results and i respect results i need i need pictures i need pictures of
trans spider-man okay uh i'm just gonna go to the bathroom right now and change
uh i'm gonna go put a powder on my spider spider-man uh the other thing i wanted to say
on the subject of things that are popular parker i need new spider-man no they're not flattering
i need to throw the pictures back in peter's face these nudes aren't flattering peter
he looks better in real life get out there and get me hotter get more flattering lighting
dim lighting low angles uh is his rival reporter like oh he's getting new to spider-man i can't
oh that makes me so angry ben gets the venom symbiote come venom in this in this continuity
fight spider-man so he can't spread his nudes speaking of oh i want a green symbiote because
it'd be like slime ha ha um uh ben slime ben ben smeels uh speaking of all that shit speaking
of piggybacking off of popular things uh to get popular uh my mega man video the the reason why
i rushed and got that uh that uh twitch announcement video out today or yesterday was because uh
mega man video is getting a big third wave it's getting like a big third uh like like uh wind
i think it's because uh i think it's because the battle network legacy collection is like
being announced it's gonna come out like next month uh it's it's uh we're doing we're doing
numbers we're doing numbers here i'll show you i'll show you the last 28 days of numbers on this graph
right here see you're lucky you've got you've got mega man that you care about you make a video about
that you care about mega man i don't care about mega man i would never force myself to care about
mega man listen here's the here's the thing i plan i planned for all this because i knew i knew that
mega man that the legacy collection was coming out and that mega man 11 had just surpassed mega
man 2 as like as like uh uh the best-selling mega man of all time so there's like renewed
interest there's renewed fan interest and there's renewed corporate interest in the franchise
and i knew that they have like bigger projects in the works that are still a secret but had
that have like huge budgets put to them i knew that there were going to be big mega man developments
coming in the future so i was like i need to do this now i need to make the definitive mega man
video that everybody's gonna want to watch when 10 years from now some big fucking thing comes out
and everyone is like what's mega man and they'll youtube and they'll go on youtube and they'll
say mega man lore and they'll see an eight hour video explaining and they'll be like guess how
watch that and it's happening it's paying off and then they'll get to the bit we talk about the pcp
and they're like what well maybe they'll click maybe they'll click past them maybe they'll click
past the intro it's too long huh look like click past the intro um anyway third wind baby
where is my mega man i bet if i were you um to make a to make a mega man comic no at this point
no um but here's the ticket just just retell the entire mega man story but don't
but change everyone's names everyone's like proxy characters it's really funny also make it edgy
and cyberpunk mega man axe is already the edgy cyberpunk version of uh of mega man it's really
funny i went to a local this was a couple years ago i went to i was invited to a local it was at
a college it was a meeting of like the the comics it was like a comics club at this college yeah
and it was a it was a bunch of hacks it was a bunch of you know it was college kids
it was it we thought they they were just they were just they had oc's they were just talking
about their oc's and they were like yeah i've been working on this i've been working on this
comic for like eight years now i've been working on it for eight years haven't started drawing it yet
but you know i'll uh yeah it's gonna be it's gonna be really good uh and one guy was talking about
his comic his comic idea and he's describing the plot of his comic idea and he talks for several
minutes and i'm sitting there and he's talking about yeah it's the future there's robots that are
that are alive there's uh you know they some of them go crazy uh there's a rebellion uh certain
good robots have to form a team to fight against the bad robots that are rebellious wow he's talking
listen there's more there's layers because he's saying all this and i'm looking at him and he's
wearing a mega man shirt and i'm like i'm just looking at him i'm like yeah yeah that sounds
pretty good yeah that's it's compelling yeah that's pretty good and then he talks for like five
or ten minutes about this idea for this this comic series that he wants to do and he gets to the end
and he goes like yeah so basically it's mega man like i basically just ripped off mega man
and i was like you know what okay i respect it at least at least he cops to it so at least he
under at least he appreciates that about his pitch so i couldn't be that mad i can't i can't
imagine working on a comic in your head for eight years and not it's literally just like
they have an oc they have an oc that they have stories about in their head and some maybe occasionally
they sketch them in a notebook and they think this would make a great comic one day and that's what
they mean by i've been working on this comic for eight years i cannot comprehend doing ideas that
are eight years old because like you're like a different person by then and it's like here's
the kind of trick if you have a genius idea right now that you think like oh i'm gonna say this for
later no do it now because like even in a year or so you're gonna like think that idea is not that
good some people have so i just do it now some people have uh like since they were kids even
they have like a cast of characters in their head that they've thought up and they've just continued
to like think of like scenarios for these characters to do you know who's like you know
who's like that is is emily ree you know emily ree that sounds she's a comic she does she does a
comic called anarchy dreamers and uh she's on twitter and that's that's her comic she's had
these these ocs for like uh you know since she was like a kid a teenager whatever and she's just been
i mean it's fine to like use concepts you've had lying around i just it's the it's the sense that
like anarchy you haven't like made anarchy dreamers okay look out right now um sure because i also
have like a bunch of like characters i guess a lot of them were invented in the process of like
making shit up while i was drawing bell jpe and stuff but like oh and like uh rfck lord of ghosts
i made up because it was like a fun character to play yeah yeah i don't really have anything from
childhood no i'm either no i'm either i think um yeah i think i mean her she's like the exception
i think also the creator of bone uh jeff smith he came up with the bone characters the bone
cousins when he was like a little kid because it's like he was a big fan of this comic strip called
pogo and it's like a possum character and he and he drew the main character um phone bone
is based on pogo and pogo and because bone phone bone looks kind of like pogo but like hairless
and that's kind of where he based the idea for all the bone characters and if you look up the art of
bone he he adds like his old like children like his old comics that he made when he was a kid
with with phone bone and phony bone and their design has that it literally never changed at all it's
like been the same since he was a kid um i've never i've never read i mean lucky for oh bone is
fucking a lot of big bone is bone is a real comics nerd's uh favorite comic like your favorite
comic artist's favorite comic is bone i saw it on a library once and i read a bunch of it and it was
like it was really really well drawn and funny and woody and and just it was great i really should
find more issues for more volumes yeah you gotta like you gotta like get that um you're probably
i feel like even the color version the the scholastic like really so the books are pretty good
i know there's like complete like versions of bone but um it's fucking it's fucking great uh
10 out of 10 every time like every time i see motherfuckers complaining about like oh like it's
so hard to get into like oh man uh western comics are dying i saw you've been you've been retreating
that you were retreating that one about like oh the manga section is bigger and i'm over here
thinking like oh please just read daniel claus please the reason it's so simple the reason the
manga section is bigger is because print manga is just a bigger business in japan because there's
just bigger demand there's bigger financial demand for serialized fucking print comics it's
literally just there's more money in it over there it's so and it's also kind of like every
time i see anyone complain every time someone makes this kind of tweet they're usually and they keep
it nice and vague i usually also see them talking about how like and the reason why is because of
comics keep pushing progressive politics right you'd have to be so fucking stupid not to see it's
because there's more fucking money in it you fucking idiot they pay them more it's a bigger
industry it's it's just so yeah it's it's really fucking annoying i really it's because they made
april o'neill well she was already black but they made her black and fat in the new change and that
was too far that ended calm ended western comics yeah exactly took the words right out of my mouth
and it's it's a shame there's a lot of really good like there's a lot of like really good comics
out there that aren't like big two superhero stuff i i try to mostly recommend non big two
like superhero stuff um yeah because it's just so much like like better damn i was thinking about
but but there's but there's not but there's not as much of it not as much of it comes out
that there no a lot of it does come out um it's just that like you don't like people don't talk
about it mostly that's kind of it i i think i think manga in japan is like
there's so many mangaka just churning it out for so many different publications
we just don't we just don't have the culture of that over here it's not it's not it's simply not
the same ecosystem i agree yeah i think i think that's the main difference well i mean but by
the same token a lot of the western comics a lot of the non-western like stuff like daniel
claus and stuff it's kind of like you know it's very it's very like kind of high it's a lot of
highbrow stuff uh you know 100 100 bullets or whatever uh uh uh you know whereas like yeah
the manga section is really big because there's a lot more schlock there's tons more schlock manga
coming out and it's just because they need to fill pages you know it's just cheaper to make and
yeah like people say like oh it's hard to get into but i'm like i feel like people get into
comics the same way they get into manga which is usually just recommendations right because like
yeah how many times was the last time you get into barnes and noble and thought like oh i've
literally never heard of this manga i'm gonna get it uh no you usually don't know if the last time
that happened was when i must have been like 14 13 12 and i went into walden books and i bought a
copy of ragnarok you know what that is yeah i know what that is the manga the manga yeah wait it's
it's not a manga because it's korean uh but it's a manhwa wife i thought manhwa was when it was on the
phone uh what was before it was before like webtoon because i'm old remember there's a western
comic called the ragnarok yeah a lot of things called ragnarok here here this one this one um
i just bought it because i thought i had a cool art style yeah and that was when i was like uh
yeah probably like 13 i was um i was lucky that i grew up like going to the public library like
religiously like i went like every week and what i did was that i would just read any comic if it
just looked interesting to me if i wait if i remember correctly i think that ragnarok
had like in the in the ending section along with like letters from the editor and stuff
i think it had the characters like statted out in like d&d stat blocks if i'm if i'm not
insane if i'm not completely imagining that which means that it was it was they it was marketed
specifically to me nerdy nerdy white nerdy white young high schooler
done for that nerdy white money so now that i think about it i feel it's shameful and now
and now i'm noticing oh my god it was published by tokyo pop no what have i done does it have an
over the oh is it ragnarok i guess may might technically be ragnarok ragnarok is it is it
kind of like a thing or like um what uh what japanese people do in english words where they just
pick words that sound cool i think koreans don't know what how's that little thing is supposed
to be pronounced so i i look at this i look at this and i and i think remember those d&d stat
blocks and i think this was probably made specifically for the west even though it's
by a korean artist uh this this says like made for the western market too much to me market
that's just that's just a hunch but uh um lamal there's god i need to get i just want to become
big enough that i can just recommend um there's this channel i think i mentioned that before
but they're called the cartoonist k fave have you heard of this channel no it's run by two um two
guys two comic creators who work in the industry um ed piscor and jim rug and they're both really
cool i really like their stuff um and and they they got a pretty popular like they're a pretty
popular channel with like people who like like comics and what i like about them is that they
they shine spotlights on like more obscure kind of stuff and they they interview all sorts of people
like they recently interviewed both creators of tmnt um and i think um but they talk about
something called the k fave effect and what it is is that like they there's this thing where like
they'll talk about an obscure comic and then the literally right after the video drops on ebay the
price for that comic goes like it's skyrockets because everyone just keeps like looking for it
like oh shit like where is it like i want to read it and that's happened a couple time with me when
they talk about something like obscure like oh you guys heard about this comic and i'm like oh that
comic looks so cool i want to get it and then like i look it up and i'm like wow that shit
cranked up in price because everyone had the idea and even now what they do is that on their
patreon they drop the videos early so those comics like go up in price even before they drop on youtube
right and i i think that's so cool because it's like oh now more people are getting into more
kind of the obscure things right yeah and um it's it's really badass and i want to like i want to
get to that point where i just could just recommend something obscure and it just kind of like blows
up i really i really wish would be pretty rad to be able to do that yeah right it acid that was
also kind of like i think also i think a big thing that would probably help um western comics is if
if we get like more like animated adaptations you know but not but not exactly like not exactly
like another spider-man cartoon put them on netflix we should i wonder if netflix is making any
cartoons i think they've got some budget for for for some new animated productions i think um i think
what i want is something kind of like just just just make good adaptations of things kind of like
when the walking dance started or like or like the boys or like invincible because when those shows
like first came out and they got super popular you know more like invisible because nobody watched
it that's not true you go on um you go on amazon and i look up oh what's like the best selling
comic on amazon that's not a manga and it'd be like invincible or the boys actually at
during the heights of the popularity of the dough shows the boys and invincible are like
outselling manga they're outselling like super popular things and i mean they just kind of just
happens when like oh when the chainsaw man anime dropped uh the chainsaw man was like
the best selling a manga on amazon you know and it like but i i mean i feel like we need more kind
of like we need more kind of like banger series that are based on like um i mean i guess the
the annoying part is that the boys and invincible is still related to like superheroes but i think
the nice thing about the boys and invincible is that it literally you start with volume one or
volume one volume one with the boys or volume ones have been invincible to start the story and
there's like an ending you know it's not like oh you got to read like it's not like oh it's implied
there's like five other books that you could also like are connected to this and yada yada right
mm-hmm i think i think we i think we just need like just more good adaptations of like
just like more non superhero comics and whatnot and you know people try there's like a lot of
like series that like didn't really catch on like there was a preacher show and i felt like the
preacher show should have been way bigger than it was and i don't know why it wasn't that successful
um because i heard people the people who did watch said like oh it's pretty good
but um it just never caught on like uh the boys did or um invincible did or uh they made a they
made a they made like an Amazon Prime show yeah it's hard to tell they might just been they came
out there in the wrong time or it might be that these fucking SJW cucks made the the girl character
into a black woman in the adaptation you know who's to say what really caused it but yeah who's
to say i mean i mean uh you got your theory i got my theory uh i think it's probably communism's fault
but uh it's the free the free market will decide uh the free market will decide if communism wins or
the wins or loses my brain is my brain is too small to think of such things i'm just gonna draw
i'm just gonna draw
i just want to draw okay
i just just draw just draw what you want to draw you know
don't focus on being popular that's so nice that's so nice to imagine that just draw don't even
think about it just draw whatever you want to draw and the money will just start just start rolling in
yeah don't even post it don't even post it just throw it or you just throw it in the trash after
you just draw it again i was talking to someone and like they were asking me because like
someone literally said like no one's ever like got in popular from trying to be like popular
with their art hey that's the dumbest that's the stupidest fucking thing i've ever heard yeah
actually uh actually that's literally all that's actually what happens way more often you freaking
imbecile you freaking you freaking you freaking loser you gotta get your fucking get in the
fucking real world okay you live in a fantasy nobody's ever gotten popular by trying to get
popular haven't you read bakuman you it it's so it's so like funny because it's like if you're an
artist that has like a family you're probably more inclined to like want to make popular things
because you want to feed your fucking family i brought up the example of like because i brought
up um brought up jack Kirby as an example of an artist who was trying to do popular things and
i got i got like shun when i brought that up like like what no no way no because jack Kirby is
considered one of the greats and i do consider him one of the greats that being said that guy was
trying to be popular like he um there was a period actually not even a period his whole life he was
trying to aim to do stuff that people that he thought like oh people might like this because at one
point he made a comic about a jazz singer because like oh people like jazz i'm gonna make someone
make someone about i mean i read i read a there's a there's a thing i think it was an
interview with like edgar allen poe that they asked him like boy how did you come up with a raven
like you must have been and you must have gone into like a freaking oh you must have like you
were you smoking edgar allen poe were you on depression pills you must have gone into like a
poetic fugue state and like emerged uh uh you know days later not having written it because it's
such a masterpiece and he was like well uh actually you know i just uh you know horror
short horror was like really popular was really trending and like doing well in magazines at the
time and i just uh you know i just thought i could really i could do that i could really
capitalize on that so i just wrote it and it worked yeah i was right exactly i thought it'd be
popular and it was idiot uh it happens it happens just so often that people don't even fucking
realize it's it's literally the it's it's probably the rule it's the rule it's the rule not the
exception yeah it is it is so nobody even talks about it because it's so unremarkable so you
hear the stories of oh this person was a surprise smash hit and they were like oh well i just do
whatever i wanted to and everyone loved it and it's like oh so that's so that's how you get
popular oh that's how you become a quote surprise splash hit smash hit like it's a surprise that
they did that yeah despite not having any work in the industry before then oda was just drawing
from the heart dude he wasn't you know he was just drawing for himself and just so happened to caught
on i'm so sad i saw i saw the i saw the quote from a couple years ago about like oda still he's still
really is like really he still loves the ronnie kenshin guy he's yeah it's uh it's it's a real
bummer i mean i understand feeling professional professional attitude towards him for getting
your start in the industry uh the ronnie kenshin guy is a what's the ronnie kenshin guy is a
child porn betta file uh there's a resident a freaking child porn sting operation but oda like
he had a shitload of odas like got his start in manga he was like an assistant to the ronnie
kenshin guy and like he still is like yeah i love that guy like he's a great guy we're like we're
like comrades you know i was like working for him was like the happiest time of my life
and it's like i i get i get being grateful for the opportunity i if you like to work it under
him like that's cool you should not you should not defend that guy far under him yeah yeah you
know every every time like something kind of the only shonen i really like i'm up to usually i'm
the most up to date with his like one piece that's the only one i read yeah yeah but like every but
usually like that's the only shonen i'm getting like a lot of like frustration from and every time
i have a problem with something in one piece or any shonen i always say to myself this shit never
happens in hunter hunter this shit never fucking nothing ever happens in hunter hunter because the
guy is he doesn't draw it um fuck you but also um what's up but wait hey you know what i hey you
know what i love about one piece is that it'll finish one day is that it will ever be completed
that's so cool hunter hunter hunter hunter is finished it's over oh really finished a while
wait really it finished for me it's over for me like i like the the ending i wanted to happen
and i'm like all right well i'm good when like when literally the two main characters go their
separate ways that's where it ends and everything else is supplementary material for me got um
that being said the reason why i brought that up is because um like someone pointed out that like
out of all the out of all those mangakas who were still in support of raruni kenshin guy
after the whole fucking pito shit came out uh two names that didn't pop up were uh kiritori
yama and uh to with tagashi which is the guy from hunter hunter well that's nice and it's like all
right that's pretty cool oh good thank god it's the ones who are for a good what about um good ones
what about miura was he was he like i don't know i don't know when did this happen it was a couple
years ago so it might have been before he died it was back it was like it was a little bit before um
yeah it was a little bit after the whole thing happened and people were like mangakas were like
oh i stand with this guy i stand with the pito and it's unfortunate oh boy you know
fucking also saw someone say something like oh another reason why no one fucks with western
comics is because there's so much like sexual allegations among like people
buddy acting like oda wasn't defend didn't defend a pedophile twice he defended two different
pedophiles with the other the the um the torah dora guy no not torah dora um yeah tori tori kogai
yeah um yeah i don't know the details but i know that oda is kind of a little bit
yeah i don't know um it'd be like that i mean i guess i'm glad there's no allegations against
oda like that would be very very oda if you if you're doing any funny business please get exposed
after one day really yeah i i was in a i kind of had that thought like i remember um literally i
think the the second week of january when um andrew callaham got exposed as like a sex past
and there was all these allegations yeah i heard about that like a couple i i fucking he came to
my city like the month before because he was doing like a tour where he was like there it was like a
little show i didn't really hear like what he actually did it sounded like damn i wish i went
before he got it sounded like it wasn't really anything that that bad it sounded like he um he
was doing the he was really like coercing a lot of women to like give fine okay but to find i mean
what doing the whole thing where like where like you're kind of begging for them to just say yes to
give me sex and he apparently was doing this a lot a lot like cross country because he was that
yeah a lot of girls came out and said yeah because he would he would do the thing where he was literally
begging for them to consent and a lot of like girls have like evidence that they got dms of him
doing this and a lot of people around them and even open so you're saying he so you're saying he
asked for consent no not that he was okay there's like a difference between like oh do you want to
have sex and she says no and that's over right that's the end of but what he was doing was they
would say no but he would be like but please i really want he was basically doing the but i
really want to have sex with you i really do please say he was doing like his version of that
um sounds fine sounds fine actually sounds fine sounds i mean it's it's it's lame it sounds lame
sounds like most girls would say no but it doesn't sound like a bad thing to do
but then that's when they say no that's just sounds pathetic the end of it as then what
is is not okay for guys to do that it's not it's not okay to to ask for sex i don't i don't
understand no it's it's fine to ask but when they say like he they would say no and he would keep asking
so like after they say no okay so they just say no again or they can just stop answering no but
the problem is that they would even he would even ask again that's dumb that's like after the first
no no that's not that's not really that's i mean that it's annoying it might be annoying
oh man that's not that's not a good is it is this like in dms like and stuff it was in person it was
in dms he would do this in person it's bad it's in person it might be in person it might be bad if
you i mean it would yeah it could be i think you could you could you could do it in a way you could
do it in a way that is that is potentially uh coercive or or something yeah sure it i mean it
is coercion i mean it's like pathetic jeez what you're doing what you're doing okay look i don't
know i don't know the details what you're what you're just the the bare facts of what you're
describing to me are simply not coercion like asking repeatedly is not coercion there may there
might there might be detail there might be details that make it coercion on top of that
i i think that it was all in the effort to no not that i think i know it's like it was all
in the effort to ultimately get sex even though they said like no of course it was to get sex
yes i understand that he was asking for sex repeatedly how am i i i can't believe them
it's a totally i'm not saying it's cool or good i'm just saying like
i'm saying it's atrocious it's atrocious it's it's atrocious to ask
repeatedly for sex yeah after they said no it's the same person yeah it's don't do that that's
that's not good that's awful it's atrocious they already said no it's can't it's cancel worthy
yeah you don't do especially if you're doing this from state to state with like different women
who cares who oh oh he did it with different women oh he would what are you talking about
oh you definitely can't do it with different women what are you talking about
now i'm not saying he can't have sex i'm saying it's how you he's how he got the sex that's awful
that's like no that's not a good thing to do that i listen what stopped the women if they said no
and then he said but i really want to what stop them from simply saying no again or simply not
responding i mean okay listen we can't we can't we can't talk we i can't speak to like how he acted
in person there he could have acted in a way that was threatening or or or something like that's
possible but in dms if he says i want to have sex with him and she says no and then he sends a sense
of but he says but please can i though why did she why is it coercion then is she what stops her
from simply saying i said no or not answering it it's it's it doesn't look good on andrew if he
doesn't it doesn't look good but why what's what's what's i i mean i get that it's not cool
it's they say no that's that's it like in the like in person when they said no like that's
that's it but if you keep like asking for it says says who then it says who he says the women the
one accusing the women accusing him of asking multiple times why didn't if if you at what what
stop you don't seem to understand what i'm asking what stopped them from simply saying
no again or just not answering him you don't have to answer a text
there's there's i obviously i feel like there's because it's happened a couple months ago
there's probably details and i'm forgetting that like really like pain a better it will like a
worse well maybe there are well maybe there are ultimately i i remember at the time i the details
of it i remember being kind of maybe maybe if i read maybe if i read the text the details of it
would be would like yeah it would be bothersome coercion is like a specific thing right i mean
it's i mean there's different forms it can take it's not it's not just a yeah but like it's it's
like similar enough to blackmail like there's a reason they couldn't just say no or block him or
like if he was stalking them if he was harassing them like is it is it harassment there's like
there's a couple of i remember there was a couple other like details about this thing
all i all i know is that he got a lot of he got a pretty awful reputation and a lot of like like
seeing i mean if you i mean if you're if you're if you're whiny would label the guy as like someone
to like if you someone to like watch out if you're if you're whiny and annoying and you beg for sex
what's yeah what you're gonna get a reputation that like you're you're pathetic and like avoid
this guy uh uh and i mean i yeah i mean i'm just telling you that at the time when it came out
and people were like didn't like like like what he did sure he was dropped by the the freaking like
production company that he was a part of like he has like he has like no career now is that true
is that is that true yeah he has well well like i mean obviously he's probably just gonna take a
break and he's willing to come back i mean i would if maybe if i maybe i would read
maybe if i read all the details and i read all the dms i would be like
that's an unacceptable way to behave but i don't know the the sim the simple fact of asking repeatedly
for sex and she says no and then you ask again like just just does not strike me as like a
particularly offensive crime in and of itself really no not at all not at all well it's cringe
but like it doesn't it doesn't go into the in the realms of like criminality there's obviously
there's worse i know there's obviously worse crimes but i mean it's all it's it's it's it's
just annoying i don't even it's pretty awful actually it's it's it's it's merely it's merely
annoying i i don't even know if it's it was just i would say it's more than just annoying that he
like was doing this that he was like repeating i don't know i think your values for the same people
was what you know what it what if they say no they can they can't change their minds
you but like do you think like in the like say yeah you could change your mind but like i
i would assume change your mind like takes a minute you know if it's like in the same moment
he just it's like i don't know it's like it's like you think it's like you think that by asking
again he is somehow violating their consent well like it's like you're it's like you're not accepting
their no well i mean maybe but if they if if it's still okay but if it's still a no the if they
ask again and you said no the first time and it's still a no one no should be enough one one no
should be well maybe it well maybe it should be but i think it's all there's no there's nothing
there's nothing about there's nothing about asking again that has any any power to make your
no into a yes unless you want it to unless you want it to be you can you can ask again yeah
this fine but i think like later when like you know there's like like maybe later in a different
time but i don't think if you already said no to not having sex with someone i don't think you're
gonna change your mind like in the next two seconds well i don't like to lay down well i don't
like to lay down hard rules for social interaction like if if they say no then it's like it's it's
never it's it's never there's never any reason why you might ask again like shortly i mean maybe
there might be like you could ask again but i'm as a habit as a habitual thing i i think it sounds
it sounds annoying it sounds needy it sounds clingy it sounds desperate and and pathetic
but it doesn't it doesn't rise to the level of coercion unless there are other elements to it
all right i guess that's all i guess that's we've been we've been over this same loop of
couple of times now uh oh boy fuck you fuck you who boy fuck you who boy who boy ben that's a
cause spicy take don't ask don't don't say please if she says no don't say please afterwards
though if you ask someone for their nudes and then they say no and then like you're always say like
okay oh but please but i really but i really want them though but i really want them i mean
listen that's not what i would do i my strategy well i didn't want your dirty disgusting nudes
anyway they probably wouldn't even be flattering you probably can't even take a decent picture if
your life depended on it ugly and then she said fuck you i'll show i'll show you i'll oh okay the
the ben the ben saint strategy works every time works every time
and if it doesn't work the first time i just do it again immediately and it would always
works the second time there's no response that you say hey by the way um i won't like it if you
send nudes i would i say just letting you know that i would hate and then i look and there's no
response five minutes later i'm back to texting okay well you're really ugly and you're really
stupid and you have daddy issues and you have blue hair and communist and you're probably woke
and you probably read manga even though western comics are dying and it's all your fault you're
killing the industry uh and and i'll let you know how it goes i'm still i'm still going i'm still
going i'll let you know what the results are you you're tweeting out i've never seen a i've never
received a good never received a good man you tweet that out now that's a bit that's a banger
that's a banger tweet that yeah exactly uh i've never i've never seen i've never received a good
nude i've never received everyone who's ever sent me a nude reads that and is like i can't
fucking believe this i can't believe he would say that i can't believe this this atrocious man
would say i poured my heart and soul into those nudes only to be spurned publicly on twitter
what are we even all right what are we even talking about
we're talking about uh how popular my mega man video is and how it's doing big numbers it's
seven a third it's having a third a third wind it's great um yeah we're talking about the difficulty
of making it in the human race right sucks oh you know what's really tough my house got broken
into this week hell yeah i mean that sucks hell yeah or sorry i hear that or sorry that happened
to you i'm not gonna read all that yeah okay so we found a couple of times we found our door
like our back kitchen door just like hanging open and i guess we just assumed that like somebody
wasn't latching it properly and it was just getting blown open by the wind and then one time we found
it hanging open and there was a can of whippets on our couch do you know what whippets are nope yeah
it's a can of like some gas it's like pressurized gas that i think it's sold as a thing to like
clean your keyboard with but if you blow it up your nose and you inhale it it gets you high
and it's really bad for you it's a really harmful thing to do they used to be uh they used to be
legal yeah yeah i mean they're still sold as like aren't they they're sold as like some other
thing yeah but people have used them for like whippets yeah yeah but but there was a can of
that on our couch and no one else got there and our rice cooker the rice cooker that i cook my
lentils with bacon in is gone some fucking junkie wandered into our house did whippets on our couch
and stole my rice cooker and now i can't make my green lentils that's terrible do you think it was
maybe a giant rat yeah well it probably wasn't the regular rats it wasn't the regular rat if you will
the regular rats aren't that big no they didn't even take they didn't even take the whole thing
they didn't take the lid or the interior pot they just took the exterior like mechanism of the rice
cooker which is useless it's useless on its own but they just i i guess they just took it
and walked out and um yeah yeah some some our house got invaded check a local pawn shop they
probably pawned it off i wonder if there even are any local pawn shops there's probably a
bunch around here is it worth like calling the police and reporting stone i know i mean the
all police is gonna do is check local pawn shops if i even if they if they gave a shit that's
important i mean the right the rice cooker is literally worth 20 on amazon so it's not even
worth reporting a theft it's just unsettling that that happens you should set up a shotgun to go off
when the door opens we set up a um we set up a plan we set up c4 in the in the doorway we set up a
camera we set up someone someone set up a camera in the kitchen that i guess you can look at through
an app or something i'm not gonna look at it i don't care um but maybe someone if it happens again
maybe i'll check the footage uh fucking i don't know wish wish that didn't happen but i guess what
can you do well i wish i did not get robbed hot take i mean i wish i still had my rice cooker
i guess i gotta buy another one well then first they might have it then think about this think
about how if i go to the person is they've stolen your rice they were probably happy to steal most
of a rice cooker than i was to have that piece of the rice cooker imagine how happy they were from
the money they got from pining off your rice the eight dollars they probably got for it imagine
how much meth they got off with eight dollars dude like come on they're probably happier they
they know a bless you can never never feel imagine just like walking into somebody i mean we said
we all said okay we got to keep the door locked for now on uh i i like never locked the door
but i guess i guess i gotta start locking my door uh i wonder if there are any pawn shops near me
hang on let me let me find out maps google maps pawn shops
yeah there's um there's one there's one oh there you go boom start
uh yeah i mean i guess start of your um detective journey there's i mean there's one kind there's
one pretty close to me that i honestly could probably walk to in like half an hour and there's
a couple more like it more like in the city um i don't know it's not even worth it it's not even
it's not even worth it just fucking go just buy another one on amazon
so you get rows then there's like crackhead sees it as like oh in this house they keep respawning
there's a respawning rice cooker it's eight the eight dollars every single time
respawning rice cooker glitch found in ben's house
oh she put c4 in the next recipe cooker
you should coat it inside i there's there's there's there's just there's just nothing
wait a minute what remember how i did all that weird chemistry stuff to boil down all the the
quinine oh you can make you can make a crack and then attract the crackhead and then you kill them
what would actually be much more like easy way to do that would be if i if i use that rice cooker
the rice cooker is designed to cook off all the water and only leave and and stop cooking when
there's when the water is gone so that would actually be a really useful thing to like be
cooking down a solution hmm i didn't think about that oh just got another twitch follower
am i at am i at 16 am i at 1600 am i at 1600
are you no 1596 ah 1596 soon though soon that's uh that's that's that's 30 i've gained 36 followers
i've gained 36 followers and i wasn't even streaming i gained 36 pounds
i wasn't even feeding that was nice nice i've gained no i'm staying at constant weight
even though i'm eating a ton because i'm lifting and i'm huge and my gains are massive
i uh gained i gained no bitches even though i said i don't like nudes and
and i would hate to see them i gained no bitches well let me read the comments comments on my on
my twitch announcement stream one black liquor ish two battle network is trash uh three fucking
dark void with another no jacky no watch i hate you i you know you're gonna say it in the comments
again you say that you i know you're you're in the comments of this video right now dark void
i hate you uh sweet this is gonna be great uh who cares who cares about people just genuinely
genuinely enjoying the content true all right that's enough
someone said someone said you will never get half a million views on your mega man video lol
but i'm yeah i saw that but i'm actually really i'm actually i i think it's a joke
i think it's like a joke like the meme of like the guy eating breakfast and then the second
panel he spits it out because he's proven wrong i i think it's it has to be a joke because i'm
obviously am going to hit a half a million if they're doing that joke the guy doesn't laugh he's
like dead pan when he says huh that'll never happen yeah you know you don't put a lull at the end
you fucked up yeah but yeah botch delivery i didn't quite get it but like that it can't he can't
genuinely think that i won't hit it like i certainly will i'm like i'm like less than 20 k i'm like 20
k away so i mean he doesn't know about the third wave he doesn't know that the third wind is hitting
right now so he might think that maybe it has stalled out not not the case is we might we've
got life we've got life left in these in these old bones yesterday was like a big day yesterday was
the i think i've got like eight or nine k views on that video just yesterday which is more than
i've gotten since like that's more views than in one day than i've gotten since the video was like
new although today does not look like it's quite as explosive someone was uh someone was talking
about you somewhere maybe was a gino you're talking about gino samuel um do you think that's why
i the views jump because everyone's like oh who's this ben saint character i mean the video
it i don't think so because it's just the mega man video that got the views like the other other
videos did not see a spike although it is weird that like yeah yesterday was like a had like was
like a spike within a spike and gino samuel release spike spike spike and gino samuel yeah
gino samuel release the new thing which goes into like the slime stuff which is very funny i wish
damn i wish i had i mean i it's better to release phantom's revenge after that is out and people
have heard about that but it would have been even better to have had the campaign running
when he made that video and announced it but oh well you know what can you do
what can you do what can you do nothing uh so many things can be planned out so much better
true right and you know every hindsight is 2020 2023
2020 12 when we all really died after this has been fake i want my green lentils
i want my green screen i want i want my rice cook cook are you mad man give it back motherfucker
i do i just want i just want my my green lentils and bacon uh hey have i told you have i mentioned
on the podcast that you can just put the bacon in the yes yes yes yes you have yes
you have yes you have yes you have yes you have yes you have yes you have yes you have
are you sure that i'm talking about that because it's like it's a pretty good trick it's a pretty
good trick you ever um you ever done a bacon wrapped rice balls before no but i did have uh
someone cook uh it was they made spam they fried spam in sesame oil and they put that on like the
bottom of a rice ball almost like like a sashimi that was really good
that was held i've had i've made bacon wrapped Brussels sprouts that's really good that's a
way i did um i did my second attempt at orange chicken a couple nights ago it was uh probably my
best so far but i said i've not perfected it sounds that sounds tough yeah because i'm
well kind of fucked me up is making the homemade sauce i uh i i took the baby way out and i bought
a bottle of like the pan to express orange chicken sauce and um all i did what it is like
after i like fried the chicken a little bit i like eat it up some of the sauce on a pan and i
put the chicken on it and i coated in it and um it tastes it tastes good but it could always be
better is it crispy yeah it was crispy um let me um oh hey i won't have one last thing
that i want to mention this week this is really funny i was asking i was asking chat gpt some
stuff actually the reason i started uh the the first thing i asked chat gpt was i i asked it
whether making the blue rays was ethical that was the first quest set of question i asked yeah
it said what did they say it did it said no it's but here's the thing here's the thing
i i explained the situation to it and i asked it like can like it did it said no
uh it sort of said like yes i acknowledged that like yes these are problems like yes the
artist should have delivered on their work however you know it's you know it's not it's not uh
one must be careful of like ethical the legal the it said it wasn't ethical and it wasn't legal
i think it was just really hung up on the fact that like i think it was just really hung up on
the fact that like it's technically copyright infringement and therefore it's like it's illegal
i think i think it's just a fucking narc and it's just obsessed with rules and it'll end
it only and it only knows how to operate by like there's no there's no room for lateral thinking
and there's no room for like oh but like what about what about what about uh what's the word um uh uh
extenuating circumstances it just it just wasn't thinking like that so yeah it said no
but like fuck jet gpt it's a narc uh but anyway after that i asked it about the pcp
and i think gibby probably saw my post i i asked it about like who what is the procrastinators
podcast and then i asked it who are the members of the procrastinators podcast and um here i'll
i'll show the screenshot and it listed these are the members of the pro procrastinators
podcast right here they were um digibro the best guy ever endless jess devour
hippo hippo crit monkey jones ben saint munchie tom oliver mage nate talks to you
trixie glink and radcon collective consisting of various members who attended the radcon conventions
um which i guess would include um zen huckstable and uh zen huckstable and uh jeff
yeah jeff's name jeff foo no no um i forgot jeff yeah i forgot jeff foo jeff burges jeff
rest yes yes yes there's the musician yeah yeah yeah i remember yeah yo yeah yo yeah yo um
and uh uh there was more there was more and it was really good and shade shade shade and victor
shade and victor shades girlfriend right who i forget right whatever her name was um yeah okay
they've all appeared in a radcon so then i so then i asked it uh so gib you didn't see these
i saw that i like um nate talks to you i think i asked it i asked it about nate it thinks that
natan best guy ever nate talks to you and best guy ever two different guys and it thinks that best
guy ever is this like german soccer player named jonathan berghardt oh yeah so so i asked it who
ben saint is and it said that i won't read this whole thing but it said ben saint is an animator
and the creator of the animated series munchie minute and then i asked and then i asked it tell
me about some episodes of the munchie minute and uh it said oh yeah munchie minute is a series of
short comedic animated sketches episodes include crash bandicoot breaks the law ben shepiro destroys
the snowman egg boys and nuclear fusion dance i asked it for some more but the next set wasn't as good
um my favorite here is jupiro destroys the snowman in which ben shepiro attempts to use logic and
reason to destroy snowman and then um so i and it ends in ends in a in a in a comedic twist ending
so then i asked it explain the comedic twist ending of uh of ben shepiro destroys the snowman
and the plot of ben shepiro destroys the snowman is he attempts to use logic and reason to prove
that the snowman does not have rights and then the comedic twist ending is that it turns out
it was all happening inside a snow globe which is very very funny and good and cool i i wonder why
i am imagining the reason is like they came up with ben shepiro destroys the snowman is because
of like special snowflakes maybe you're just a you're just a big collection of snowflakes maybe
sort of possibly villain ben shepiro i don't know it's hard to say um i i asked it so i mean i i love
this i pardon pardon me want pardon me wants to yeah pardon me wants to make like munchy minute
episode one ben shepiro destroys the snowman just because of this prompt um but um i i asked it about
who is munchy and it said munchy is not a person he is only like the the munchy and munchy minute
simply refers to the food related themes that are often prevalent in the munchy minute
also munchy is the co-creator of the munchy minute and he is an important person involved in like the
in the in the creation of the series it's like okay but he's also the co-creator he's not a real
person but he's also the co-creator of the series and then i asked it that the fourth episode called
nuclear fusion dance it got i asked it about the plot of nuclear fusion dance and it got really
it basically said okay in nuclear fusion dance two characters like kyle and trevor try to do the
dragon ball z fusion dance and they fuse but it doesn't go right yeah it leads to unexpected
consequences so i asked it okay what are the unexpected consequences and it said that they
merged together into like a big like disgusting flesh monster and then they rampaged through the
town uh but then they worked together to defeat it and i'm like wait a second so i asked it like
with chat gpt what do you mean they work together to defeat it aren't they the monster because they
fuse together into it and it's like yes sorry for any any any confusion they fuse together into the
monster and then they have to work together kyle uses his his intelligence to strategize
while trevor uses his physical prowess to perform martial arts maneuvers against the monster
and thus they defeat they defeat the monster and i'm like no chat gpt hang aren't they fused
together into the monster and it's like sorry sorry for the confusion they have to work together to
perform strategic maneuvers to get the monster to defuse so that then they can defeat it and i said
what do you mean what strategic maneuvers do they do and they said sorry sorry for the confusion um
yeah you see they they they they they strategy they have to get they have to perform the fusion
dance again and that makes the monster defuse so that they can fight how do they perform the
fusion dance again if they're fused into the monster instead sorry sorry they had to desync
they had to desync their behavior so much that the fusion came apart and then once they were taken
apart then they could do the fusion dance and that caused the monster to defuse and so that they
could defeat it and like okay okay and that i gave up at that point i'm like it doesn't understand
the concept of the fusion dance um but that i thought that was pretty great uh i had a very
had a very uh uh very laughs aplenty laughs aplenty from chat gpt um there was a chat gpt episode
of south park actually was the last one really yeah and it was pretty funny because the the joke was
that um uh stan's girlfriend wendy did not um she didn't like that stan wouldn't really like
dm her back or talk talk to her like she would send him a message and all he would do would
like reply with a thumbs up emoji tell her messages right and because that wendy was like
was threatening stan that she was gonna break up with him and stan hears the rumors that um
he wants his name i forget the name of the other there's another kid who who probably he's
not kyle um token now i think it's heart right craig maybe okay uh maybe oh no it's not craig
because craig is like i forget the other name of the there's like another kid who's kind of like
who's considered popular ken among the boys okay that being said this kid like apparently he's
always gives the best messages ever to his girlfriend and stan asks him like what's your
secret man and he's all like chat gpt so basically what he does is that he like gets chat gpt to come
up with replies for the stuff his girlfriend sends him he just copy and paste what the replies are
back to his girlfriend and his girlfriend eats it up his girlfriend thinks it's really him so stan
started doing that to wendy so every time wendy sends him a dms he just like copies and replies
and like gets chat bt to like come over reply then he copy and paste it back into
oh god i bet i bet i bet guys are like i bet guys are making like chat gpt write me like a good
opener to like send to this girl that i matched with on twitter on tinder i mean i mean maybe twitter
too i bet people are doing that i wonder i wonder like what it i'm gonna ask it right now i'm gonna
ask you right now and say uh chat gpt what's the best opener for this girl to make sure she
sent me her nudes make sure make sure what's the best opener to make sure she does not send me
nudes that's what i want i wanted to be interested but i do not want the news how do i how do i make
this happen all jabby chat gpt would say like hey bitch fuck hey negam just just negam just negam
uh she definitely won't fucking send you nudes and she definitely will not if you listen if you if
no nudes is your goal i have the solution for you um i know the guy i know a guy i know i know a guy
who can get you absolutely zero news for free his name is ben sake
oh you don't want you don't want nudes i don't just the guy
anyway the episode the episode of south park ends with um like so apparently um like kids are also
using the chat gpt to come up with like essays for a class you know for you know so they don't have
to do homework and um one of the one of the like supervising teachers realizes that um oh that's
not good so there's a guy that they hire who could check to see if any of any of the essays are written
by ai and the guy that they that shows up is like a like looks like a weird shaman guy who lives in
the woods and he has like a pet hawk like he's like anti technology and he um and he basically
uses his little shaman stick because he could detect like who's using ai with his shaman stick
and apparently they pinpoint it to stan's girlfriend because she has a bunch of ai messages
in her dms and this is what this this guy is like finding and stan is like oh no if um she finds out
about the ai messages i'm fucked i'm gonna break out with me but then stan comes up with a brilliant
idea he goes back to chat gpt and he says um chat gpt tell me a story about a guy named stan who's
been using chat gpt messages to like light his girlfriend and the story has to end with him
still being with his girlfriend and not having to tell her the truth about it and um and and then
and then the the last like the last like three minutes of the episode is literally like a script
that chat gpt wrote for the ending of that episode where stan still ends up with his girlfriend even
though he he comes out with the truth about the ai and then when the episode ends it says episode
written by trey parker and chat gpt chat gpt that's funny yeah that's funny okay so i asked chat gpt
i asked chat gpt to write me a good opening line to send to a girl i matched with on tinder but
write it so she won't send me any nudes chat gpt says sure here's a friendly and respectful
opening line that should avoid any unwanted requests for nudes hey there i couldn't help but
notice we share a love for insert common interest from her bio or photos would you be interested
in grabbing a coffee or drink sometime and chatting more about it and i said no i want to make sure
she won't send me nudes and chat gpt said my apologies for misunderstanding your request
earlier here's a suggestion for an opening line that conveys your intention and sets a clear
boundary while still being respectful hey i'm really enjoying chatting with you so far but
just wanted to make it clear that i'm not interested in receiving any explicit photos hope that's okay
with you i'm just gonna drop that in a casual conversation the conversation's going well we're
hitting it off yeah we're thinking of maybe a first date hey i'm really enjoying chatting with you
but i just want to make it clear i'm not interested in receiving any explicit photos i hope that's
okay with you you know i wonder okay i wonder i wonder if that would actually pique interest
because it's like hey this guy is telling me not to send him nudes he must he must get too many
nudes he must be so drowning and pussy that he simply gets too many nudes all the time and he's
sick of them this must be a high value alpha male and he doesn't want to see my nudes because
he doesn't want to see my nudes exactly what they'll say knows that they're not good enough
because i'm not good enough for him but but i will prove him wrong this is the this is the
concept this is why i say all right cheesy you're gonna hate this you're gonna hate this
the the the pick up the pickup artist community is unfairly maligned because oh okay some of the
norm because okay there's really bad guys there's really bad guys that pedal really bad stuff in
there but if you read just like bad guys on both sides but if there's bad guys on both sides but
if you read the normal books about it if you read like the mainstream most popular books about it
the stuff they tell you to do is actually really normal and one of the and one of the things that
people don't like is the idea of a neg which is like which people think that negging a girl means
insulting her and if you read the books if you read like like the the big book or the art of the game
or whatever it's called it makes it very clear that no a neg is not just an insulting a girl
it's just something that you do or say that simply makes it clear to her that you are not overly
interested in her and something and an example that it gives is like blowing your nose just to
make it like you you you you're not you don't care if she sees you blowing your nose you're not like
hung up on she's like oh we gotta make a really good impression because i'm so invested in in this
interaction right so this is a perfect neg perfect neg hey i'm really enjoying chatting with jafar
just wanted to make it clear that i'm not interested in receiving any explicit photos
hope that's okay with you that tells her that i have that i'm a high value male that tells her
that she's not good enough for me that's gonna get the juices flowing she's gonna she's gonna soak
her panties soaked and dropped it's over it's over thank you gbt you've changed everything for me
that's like going there and dm saying like hey girl just letting you know i'm not gonna look at
your cleavage do not the lowest cut shirt ever i'm not gonna say one peak i like to you're gonna
wear you have boobs or not let's just let let let's explore this what if i what if i jump into the
dm's and i open with a hey girl put a freaking shirt on don't let me see that don't let me see that
now we're negging now we're negging now this is now this is now this is
i hate you i hate you i hate you i hate you i hate you i hate you
i ugly ugly ugly ugly ugly ugly i have this this awful joke but i can't say it because it's
dangerously close to a slayer it's it's probably the most dangerously close i get they go to the
to the end serve i'm like oh you're a real neg and then say they are yeah i'm neggin i'm a negger
i tell girls the truth which is that they're ugly and it's normal and it's normal it's
etymologically unrelated to any to any to any ethnic slayers that you might be thinking of
this let's let's let's let's be mature let's be mature here okay let's be adults let's be adults
all right all right grow up cheesy cheesy grow up cheesy grow up let's grow up and say it say
no i'm not gonna say say i'm a say i'm a negger cheesy call me a negger right now
i'm good i'm i'm oh my god but the episode bed bed goes cheesy to say the end i don't know
i don't know what you're talking about i don't know what you're talking about all right uh
that was my last thing on my list the munchie minute i just wanted to remind everyone about the
munchie minute created by animator ben saint and co-created by munchie who does not exist
featuring fan favorite episode ben Shapiro destroys the snowman then the moment you're not a pcp
member you might as well not exist really it's kind of like the logic of chat yeah i mean that's
true that's true for most of our listeners as well yeah exactly munchie stop listening you ain't
real no more yeah i'm just a voice in your computer saying saying the n-word but not really though
but not really though but i really didn't actually i didn't actually say it though i didn't actually
he didn't say it guys he did not say and she's he's not even white so if he says i didn't say
thank you for being like gave me the thank you for being my shield the poc pat thank you for
being my shield thank you for being my shield the poc pat on the back thank you
anything else what else what else we're doing what else what else is going on
dudes uh i'm playing kids i'm playing more out of wilds again that's fun
yeah you were you were damning me about that cheesy have you played out of wilds
i've heard about it you know you know what it's about you're in space and stuff it is about space
and stuff and gravity of the little orbital the planets do gravity on you in a realistic
enough fashion they sure do they really do be doing gravity though it's really fun it's really
fun just flying out somewhere and being like oh shit i'm in an i'm in like a collision course
with the sun and that's no good and then you die i actually got really one of the most frustrating
parts was like just just when you would be like you would die and then be like oh i got to get
back to wherever i was going and then just the way it worked out getting back there meant going
around the sun but you would like try cut it too close and you'd fall in that happened like so many
so many times but it's on me it's on me for not planning my route more carefully there's this
one thing i tried i tried not putting my spacesuit on because some planets have oxygen um and i can't
remember what i did i got on my ship and then i flew to somewhere where did i fly oh doesn't it
doesn't the deep doesn't the giants deep have oxygen it does but only on the islands if you're
in the water you instantly drown which is funny right not instantly um well it's funny how like
yeah you you're in the water presumably you still have an oxygen supply when you're under the water
not if you don't have your suit on that's what i mean oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but i can't
talk about what i was going to talk about because this contains too many spoilers
um now i got you nice but there was a cool thing i did and then i died and it was funny
also the echoes of the idlc i finally i'm finally looking into that because the version i played
before was on like xbox live like whatever and it didn't have the dlc and i finished that that xbox
live um like month that i got for free and then i bought the game on steam and it had the dlc
you know i'm trying that and it's very scary very scary and i'm scared it seems a little scary
i'm not i don't think i'm into it i'm a little too scared i am a little too i am a little too
scared and also it doesn't really involve much like space stuff which is kind of disappointing
which is the real scary part it's that's the i i appreciate that they tried to do a different
kind of stuff of stuff in their engine i just it's kind of not what appealed to me about the
core game so i've sort of like found it a little disappointing that that's what they did with it
i mean what i'm enjoying so far is just that it's a new a different set of mysteries to solve
like i don't know nothing about all this this extra i don't like how scary it is i don't like
how scary it is i haven't actually got to a jump scare yet i'm just exploring but when i got there
for the first time the thing is like they have in the menu by the way the echoes of the iadlc
may be maybe too much for some uh gamers go into the options and turn down the scary factor and
i'm like don't tell me about that don't you've already ruined it now yeah yeah yeah it did
yeah it terrified me i bet it's not even that bad but that made me so i was so nervous about it
because it felt the need to warn me that i'm like i don't even want to i don't even want to do it
i don't even want to see it i'm i'm going in though i'm gonna go in i'm gonna pee my pants
i'm gonna scream and then i'm gonna go to the menu i'm gonna turn down the stairs
but i'm not gonna do them down yet i want to see what it what it you're going in p mode you're
going in p mode first first thing right off the bat oh congratulations hey hey gamer are you a little
baby bitch too scared of a little video game yes the baby mode in this i know i am baby i mean
there's parts of the main game that are so scary that i hate them oh yeah yeah yeah even the main
game has some what you might consider jump scares yeah they are so bad and i am so scared and but
it's like best game ever but it's it is the best game ever it's so scary the bramble is really like
it's rough it's really rough going in the bramble um sometimes i literally have to like
just close my eyes when i know something is gonna kill me i in outer wiles is like this is not going
to work out fuck it i'll uh close my eyes then i eventually kind of just got sort of like used
to what happens in the bramble that it's sort of just i got numb to it uh although if i probably
booted up again it's been long enough that i probably would have to re re but i just but i just kept
hey re but i just kept happening over and over again so many times that finally it lost it lost
its sting a little bit but never completely it's still like really you hate you hate it every
single time and another thing i've been playing recently is subnautica i've gone back into that
and that is similarly the scariest game ever but it's yeah for similar probably for similar reasons
yeah i played subnautica before i played out played outer worlds and subnautica is like you're in the
ocean and you're trying to survive and there are lots of very good sound design scary scary
sounds of big huge leviathan beasts far off in the distance that you can't see because the ocean is
like blurry and you feel like you're gonna get eaten at any point moment all the time yeah i the idea
of like being floating in like water and like you look down and down below you is just like
void and like something might come up out of it is like the scariest thing yeah i like i i'm i'm
like in the shallow areas i don't know if i could handle subnautica at the beginning you're in you
usually land in an area near in the same sort of place every time you play and it's like a
shallowish area with coral reefs and stuff and you can explore caves there but then you go out
a little bit and then there's this big long trench this huge and you have to go like a hundred meters
down i think and it's like if i were oh i think if i were floating above some kind of underwater
chasm and i would be so scared to look down and then if i did look down and if something was like
coming at me i think i it would be over it would be over if i look down and there was something
there with its mouth open that would just be over for me oh yeah if i looked down to the void
and i saw if i saw like a nude slowly come down yeah i would lose it if i looked into the void
void void void void void void these fish aren't wearing any clothes this is not like
this leviathan is is indecent uh but yeah um subnautica ocean uh when i played out a world
to the first time and i got to giant steep giant steep is a little bit scary but it's not really
that bad i thought i was gonna i thought i was gonna be way more scared of like the ocean in the
giant steam i was like turned the game off like paralyzed by giant steep the first time i came
there because i i landed in the ocean because it's mostly an ocean planet yeah and i saw some
stuff below me and i was like i know what subnautica is like i am going to be eaten by a giant fish
immediately i'm so scared i had to pause i had to leave my room i i when i got to giant steep i was
i think the first couple times maybe the first time i just swam around the surface and i was just
like i'm not looking down i'm not looking down i'm not looking down uh i think the second time i
got there i was like god damn it i gotta do it and i just like didn't even think about it i just
like pushed my mouth i was like go just look down just dive just go go and i looked down and you
know what's actually there is not especially unsettling so i was like okay it's fine now it's
fine i it's it's the similar to two things it's like the exploration the unknown it's the fear of
the unknown and the amazing sound design on both those games that really if as long as you as long
as you have it as like max volume like normal like if you if you put it down really low sound
when it's like barely there it affects you so much less yeah but um i like i like the immersion
that it brings because it's like that's that's what i want i want to i want to i want to conquer
this fear of the unknown of the ocean of space you're not playing you're not playing it in vr
you're not playing in vr are you i do not have a vr set so i couldn't but i would never do that
that would be in sub nautica especially yeah that's the sort of thing because i oh my god
i don't play with headphones when i play with headphones it's so much scarier yeah i can only
i can only the surround sound and it's like you hear like a little you hear like the the big
booming like growls of certain fish and you know those growls are kind of like those of her before
is okay those ones are okay but then you hear a different one and it's very close and you're like
what i don't know this and you just you're you're you're put upon you're put upon by by fear
put upon put upon put upon put upon put upon put upon um yeah now that's what my heart's doing
i uh it makes ooo love the leviathans of the deep make my kokoro go doki doki
doki doki in a in a uh korae way or what do they say uh is that korae
i know sugoi koi is scary koi yeah it's not kawaii it's koi koi yeah kawaii yeah
japan japan yeah japan they done it again they make the best comics and more of them too
the western market will never survive well good we're all gonna die we're all gonna die
you know i um so i tuned into nate's talking pirate stream for a little bit uh the other day
i was i was i was shocked i was shocked by what i heard what did he say
i don't i don't are you talking about the the the sound board
i was shocked by what i was hearing and maybe it's like a bit that i don't get
the guy does not seem to like one piece like what may yeah ever it seems like the attitude
in there is like one piece is just is bad i mean that's how it's always it always was on like
uh the podcast nate would be super cynical and be hyper focused on anything he could find that was
slightly like potentially incorrect yeah yeah or like that's what it was how dare this you know
like he's he's ready and willing and able to shit all over one piece the second it like
deviates from pre-established canon or implies something that he doesn't like
yeah and it's like i don't know like i guess he likes it and that's just how he likes it
it doesn't i mean it doesn't my i mean i came away from that stream being like i think i think he
i don't even think he likes one piece i'm over here like one piece is literally the best it's
ever been and he's reading it and it's like i don't i don't know if it's a bit it seems almost
like a bit but he's just like oh the art all the art so the line are so sketchy oh bad uh oh does a
hack uh uh oh this this jinbei is like oh these these the the the freaking seraphim are too strong
broken op oh uh uh oh does a hack uh sanji's eyebrow was swirling the wrong way and like this implies
some weird shit about uh the the germa's thing the thing uh oh does a hack oh he broke his own rules
again uh huh oh but he said it but he said it was like this in the sbs but now it's like this in
this panel but only for one panel and it goes back why doesn't why doesn't odi give a fuck about
about his own work anymore this is why it's it's a very doomery like approach yeah i like he he
sees like the inevitable demise of his favorite thing and he can't help but bring it into the
like he's all the time it's like he sees it in every panel it's like he sees every page is like
here's the the decline continues and there it is uh i knew this would happen he says reading the
best fucking chapter one piece ever had i knew this was gonna happen i knew this would happen as
well i've been dreading i've been dreading this day i i didn't get it i didn't get it that was always
the thing is that i would be the optimist and they would be the cynic we would balance each other
out i guess people i think liked it you know what's better if you just have two people on one side
of the seesaw that's why we're such a good team give because we both just love one piece we both
just uncritically love one piece and we'll just shovel down whatever slop oda puts on our on our
bowl suck it down and say thank you yep you see oda he he he makes his see he makes his chapters
of one piece bad on purpose right he makes them bad on purpose and the reader says no but any the
reader says no i don't like this but then oda says please like my shitty one piece i made it bad on
purpose but but please would you read it and continue to buy my comics and they go oh i guess
i have to i guess i have to keep buying it even though it's bad now because he's because he asked
me again um that's why he loves his pedophile friends so much they just have no they just don't
believe in consent are you referencing something no i feel like you're referencing something here
wrong i'm referencing reality yeah referencing the real life cheesy if you have if you don't know
we love y'all living it yeah i'm referencing um torico our twisted world our twisted my dark
twisted mind i'm maybe like i don't know you ever consider that maybe like nate has good taste
and you have bad taste that could just be it you know that that could be could be the real answer
here having the best taste means being the most miserable person on the planet and i don't want
that i myself i don't know if that's true i i don't know i think i'm gonna want you to be miserable
that was the intention with this chapter and you're i know i'm enjoying instead yeah i'm
i'm definitely authoring it i i found i found fishman island and the wano arcs a little bit
tedious like i definitely did not have no complaints about those chapters but egghead i like
unless it's unless it goes on and on like i have like basically no problems with it at all and i
think it's great and it's so cool to see all these like threads that are so old they were established
so long ago and they're coming together right before our eyes and like it's really happening and it
feels great and i just and i just don't fucking understand i just don't fucking understand the
mindset on display over there where it's like what was he uh yeah sanji's eyebrow swirl being
inconsistent uh fuck yeah what else was there the like like the the line line art is sketchy uh i
don't even remember there were there were like one or two other things jinbei's some like something
about like the the specific verbiage that shanji used to insult the lunarian jinbei i don't even
remember but like there's just so i don't see i don't see any cause for negativity at all i don't
see any i don't see call right thank you thank you uh i don't see any cause for negativity at all and
i was like i was watching and i was just like what what what where's this coming from it genuinely
like took me back like how could you i just don't see how you can be negative about one piece in
march of 2023 but that i don't know and that's why i'm like am i just am i just not in on the joke
i i don't know if it's a joke i think it's just the there's a there's a sense that
like your favorite thing could get worse it seems like it's a fear of a lot of media
enjoyers that their favorite thing could get worse and they're so scared that it's gonna happen
what if it goes woke now it's whatever whatever does this or that it seems like it just doesn't
look like anything particularly bad is happening but they're just so ready to be it's not just
nate it's like a whole community of like like uh what's the word um negative nancies uh they're
nate uh they're not negative nate heads negative nate heads it just it just seems like he's already
accepted that it will get bad and in fact it already has so if it is a why continue why continue
this charade any longer there's there's like if you've decided that there's points where there's
like an argument that this is worse than it was sure but i just generally i listen to those
and i'm like sure i can see why you would think that but i don't mind it and it's fact it's fine
actually there's a few there's a few nate nate is nate is still bothered by nika i'm like i don't
care i don't care about nika yeah it's fine cool the fruit wasn't the gum gum fruit cool okay
i guess we got nika now gear five sure like it's it's it's it's one of those things it's like um
would it like hypothetically i guess it would have been better if that had been planned from
the very beginning and been and been sprinkled like little hints towards it so that people could
come up with theories and and and then the theory would be true sure and then it feels like some
things that you they they were sort of made up more recently sure biota um and i think that is
like you know hypothetically would have been nicer if it was all perfectly planned but like real life
it's hard to it's hard to plan out like 900 chapters of a manga series it's hard to like
perfectly plan out everything yeah and i think that a little leeway is fine yeah it doesn't
break anything it's just you couldn't have seen it coming yeah oh jeez you said i like responded
to you on twitter because you said like one piece botches it's like it's like power reveals oh yeah
and i said give me an example and you gave me a couple of good examples i was like oh yeah that's
true okay that i did i did nancy one piece is not perfect but like it's so good i like that
so much of the good outweighs like all of the bad and there's a reason it's like the most popular
thing ever and that it's still going and still quality it's just maybe there's a few things that
pet peeves and things that make you sad a little bit i just i i doesn't affect me so much i don't
know why i know that um online i'm known as the number one one piece hater on uh twitter.com if one
piece has one hater it's me if one piece has no haters your cheesy's dead yeah yeah yeah but even
but even i cheesy manfredo i have to admit that um i i feel like what i always kind of liked about
one piece and why i'm i'm still i'm still like you know right there in the hot seat would it
are you are you current are you up to date on it no but i promise that the next time i come back
on this on this podcast i'll be up to date that's fine i actually i didn't read this week's chapter
again lol uh but um i think the one thing i really like about one piece is the the fact that oda will
like give you 50 things at the same time and like one or five of those things might not be the best
ever but like a lot of it is good a lot of it is like still good right he's really good at just
throwing things at you that are like entertaining that are interesting that are cool that are funny
that are base that are redpilled you know you'll still throw you all this like really good stuff so
like the fact that it just you can only think of like negative things it's like i don't know you
you might be like really like like reaching you know um one problem that i had and it's kind of
why i like kind of stopped reading at the at towards like the middle of the kaito fight um and
i mean i'll catch up whatever but i think one thing that kind of really bothered me is that um it
is kind of this problem that one piece figured out at the start but then they kind of just
went back into having this problem and it's like um i always like that one piece solved the the
waiting for Goku problem you know and the whole thing about like waiting for Goku is that they
in Dragon Ball they usually how it ends up is they usually wait for Goku to show up so all the
other side characters are getting their ass kicked buying Goku time right and i think one piece did
such a good job of solving that issue and what they did is that like there isn't just one bad guy
it's a crew of bad guys and we have a crew of good guys so while Luffy is fighting the the big top
dog all the other crew members are fighting their own individual battles right and yeah and it's kind
of like like like if Oda wrote if Oda wrote like the Namek uh the the the Namek arc in Dragon Ball Z
he would have had it that uh Goku would have been fighting Frieza at the same time all the side
characters would have been fighting the Ginyu force so he would have had those fights be
happening simultaneously while the planet is blowing up like that would have that's how Oda
would have wrote in that written that arc right but then and they did this they did so well but
then for some reason and this is kind of like something that kind of cropped up a little bit
um i noticed it a little bit in a dress rosa it's it feels very obvious to me and Wano
is that they start introducing all these other side characters like a lot of side characters
yeah yeah and and the side characters will be the people will be the people waiting for the straw
hats to show up so it just becomes waiting for straw hats so it's not about just like an individual
they're waiting for a specific straw hat member to show up and to take out the specific bad guy
crew member right and i guess that wouldn't be too bad if if not for the fact that all these side
characters also have very compelling motives like incredibly compelling motives of why they
want to like fight the people they want to fight and i think it's bad to let the one they'll let
the straw hats do it for them i think it i think it yeah i think it kind of kills a little bit
emotional connection to it you know because the problem with i think one of my issues like okay
look if you if you want there's nothing wrong with the straw hats there's no like there's nothing
wrong with the straw hats fighting the fights they fight i just want there to be kind of
something more going on rather than like the straw hat is there to just fight this one guy
because like i think my big example is all the samurai's that were like this whole time this
fucking what is like a 20 year plan that they had just to the feet kaito it all leads up to this one
moment where they finally show up at the top to like fight kaito right and i and and ultimately
they don't they ultimately they don't stand a chance again i mean it was like a 20 year plan
they all have this emotional connection to kaito elder problem seems to stem from kaito it's all
these things they're connected to kaito right but then no they can't do it and then luffy is there
luckily to the feet kaito and it's like there's nothing wrong with luffy fighting kaito but
luffy like there's not besides like what they're his friends with them sure that's fine but like
what's the thing with luffy and and and kaito and i and i feel like you don't have to like
there's not like there's ways to write this to not make it like you have to rewrite the whole
arc like maybe um kaito whatever ideology kaito is has is opposed to luffy's ideology in a way
aside from but they didn't really seem like kaito kaito believes in anything which is kind of i
always thought was kind of weird because when they first introduced kaito he's like straight up trying
to commit suicide yeah and i thought like oh there he's like he's going to be the kind of guy who's
interested in like he's going to be like an accelerationist or something he's going to be
interested in trying to like wipe out the world as fast as possible and wiping out everyone in it
and luffy's going to be the guy who's like no living his base actually but but no that really
doesn't seem to be kaito he's just a strong guy who wants to be strong yeah right exactly and
and then at the same time there's all these other fights happening where like other side
characters are fighting other like members of the of the what they call the beast pirates
and and they're not really dealing any major damage they're kind of just chipping damage away
until a strong hat character a strong hat crew member comes in and they like you know defeat
that person right they're kind of like warming up the battle for them and it's so it's so kind of
frustrating you know to read i agree with that as the the fact that there's so many new characters
they're always introducing and they don't have anything to do it's like the story could not it
could be told without the straw hats being there at all like early on it's this it's the plight of
the straw hats fighting against another pirate crew or trying to survive against like crocodile and
his organization and they're just like by themselves and that's why they have to pair off to fight
everyone but when there's like a whole bunch of people already doing a fight like in Dressrosa
there was the one armed a one-legged guy what's his name chorazon or chorazon or something
i thought i forgot his name he was a toy soldier the former king well the former former the
no he wasn't the king he was like the he was the gladiator he was gonna be though like oh right
like it was set up that he was gonna become the king because he married like the princess and
their yeah daughter whatnot right yeah so like he has um like a big reason to come up and fight
uh the the don flamingo pirate crew um you know he's finally been freed from his toy prison
and like he has a battle and it really should be about him
and but then there's all there's all this other stuff going on with the pirates
and also with law and uh it's it's it gets it gets it gets confusing and muddled the more
factions that are involved in any one singular event and i like it when a straw hat character a
straw hat member gets their battle because that's you know we were with them pre like uh the
battle at marinford with their little adventures the the straw hat pirates and they're trying to
fight like it's very simple one pirate crew is the protagonists against the villains and that's
like every island and um the more like side characters need their own screen time the less
the straw hat pirates get of their own screen time but luffy always has the main screen time at the
top so it's like it's spread out and it's just it's not satisfying yeah it's not satisfying enough
there's not enough time or space for all these individual characters to get their their their
emotional thing and and this is kind of what i mean by like oh this never happens in hunter hunter
because in hunter hunter they're not like interested in the main character gone fighting the bad guy of
each arc right because like there's so like in a traditional shonen there's like so many like
villains in the hunter hunter arcs that would have been like and the final fight of this fight
is gone versus this villain right but that actually never really fucking happens it's only like one
season or like one arc and with villain with a gone fighting the villain but all the other ones
um it's either like another character is like either fighting the villain or realizing something
about like the bad guy and about themselves right and and like i think in i think a big example
of this is in the chimera and arc like the chimera and king like um in the traditional shonen gone
would be the guy to fight him at the end right like if this was one piece and gone it was like
luffy they would have just made gone fight him but no instead there's like another character
who's like beyond stronger than gone who ends up fighting the chimera and king
and even that fight like goes in like in a very different direction i think what's also kind of
great is that in hunter hunter the the power system like is like so well defined that like they never
have to like introduce something new they just like everything they show is it could always be
explained like they always kind of they already explained how like everything works so anytime
something kind of new or wacky pops up we already like get that like this is this ability like we
know this and the fact of the matter is that we're constantly reminded that like uh our main
character gone is not the strongest not in an effort to like say like oh he has a long way to go
but but more like to kind of show how big the world of hunter hunter is that like
you're this one kid and sure you are strong actually it's kind of scary how strong you are
but there are at least like 500 other people above you and it's not about beating these people it's
about kind of like your own kind of goal you know and you're just going to get stronger as you go
through like the adventure but with like one piece i think it just boils down to eventually
luffy has to become the strongest guy on the fucking planet right and um it's kind of like i mean
i mean it works for like chun and i think like when one piece ends and it doesn't matter if the
ending is good or bad i feel like if it's good that's great that's awesome if it's bad i still
feel like at the end of the day that people are going to still label one piece probably the greatest
shonen ever written and i and i 100% agree with that sentiment but like hunter hunter is just a
really good manga like i feel like it it it passes like it passes the threshold of like a shonen
and it's just a good manga it's just i should i should read it i should read it story um yeah i
mean you might like i don't i don't know but i like it it's really good um i think the anime
doesn't really i think the anime does a really good job i'm always finding myself wishing i knew
what people were talking about when they talk about it so that's probably a sign that i should
check it out at some point i think the ending that the anime chooses is like the perfect ending
and if the manga ended like that i thought like okay dude bum 10 out of 10 banger manga but the
manga keeps going and it's fine right but i'm but the thing is like i'm just not that interested
in reading like the rest of it and it's and it's not like the quality has gone down it's like still
consistently good but like like the two like to me the um once like in episode two of the anime
once gone meets kiloa that's when the show starts because that's like this is this is these are our
characters this is our duo and it's all about it's all about them and once they go they're
separate ways that's it that's the end of the series for me right yeah um but yeah i would
recommend it it's really good really good anime well while you were saying all that i read the
new chapter nice so there's so pretty bass uh when it uh new chapter 10 it was good it was a
masterpiece well a twist a twist has been revealed twist well we found out we found out who the
butler was we found out who the butler was yeah i did the butler is that what they said
yeah the butler's wife and something vega punk
um i gotta i gotta pee i'll be i'll be right back i'm sorry i apologize
um you know i should read i should reclear us uh i should recourse a gun smoke i saw you have
three chapters out yeah i got three chapters fourth one is gonna be on fourth one's gonna be
first available through purchasing then it's gonna be on my patreon well i haven't figured out the
best way to like release it but i want to have like a you can bet you can buy it then it'll be on the
perfect comic party and then it'll be on my site and then it'll be that'll be it
that's pretty cool how many um how many chapters do you have on mine for clover sir i finished the
sketching the like blocking out of all the pages so it's just a matter of doing line art and shading
and and everything cleaning uh it's gonna be 10 chapters each chapter is around 15 to 20 pages
the last chapter is quite long it's like 23 actually there's gonna be more because i still
haven't drawn there's like a couple pages of epilogue because you gotta you gotta end a western
with the right enough into the sunset haven't got there yet kind of reminds me of um not really
an epilogue but um was it uh and for the the movie fistful of dollars which was like the start of
like the yes the good and the bad and the ugly trilogy um uh yes so julian yeah and in the
in the first movie um it's gone back it uh i'm freaking back it starts with all over shut up
jesus talking what oh i'm talking my headphones got disconnected okay go on but in the um fistful
of dollars um in the movie in the original movie the clint eastwood character just shows up into
town and he starts a fight with like the gang there right and that's the whole movie um but in
the tv version when it came out what they did was that they added a prologue because the thing is that
like um the clint eastwood character in the movie is not a good person like he's kind of like a piece
but he's fighting against people who are way worse so like you know you're kind of like
compelled to be on his side but i guess that was like too much when the movie was brought to tv
so what they did was that they added a prologue where they add like a narration talking to clint
eastwood saying like um they're talking to him like he's like a federal agent and they're like oh
this town has been overrun by a gang go stop them and to make it seem like oh he works for the law
like that's that's what happened the new prologue and it's just so like funny because it's like
you can't just have a character who just so happens to be like morally gray and then he finds people
who are a whore it it has to it has to be that like he's on the side of good so everything he's
doing is ultimately for the greater good that i mean that's the whole fun of the spaghetti westerns
as opposed to like the older like fifties sixties westerns where the good guy is the good guy and
everyone likes him and the bad guy's the bad guy and he's got a mustache um is the in spaghetti
westerns and like other cool western movies uh it's morally gray it's just like more realistic in
the like if you're a guy with a gun you can just shoot a guy and it might not be a good thing to
do that but you know um you do what you got to do a lot of there's a handful of like early westerns
where um one of the characters are kind of like morally good i mean that's where the term like what
is it white hat comes from yeah is the good guy and then black hat like and i think a big example
of like the kind of like um the major like difference between like a western back then a western now
and if you look at if you watch the original true grit movie and then you watch the remake um and in
the original the the character i forget the character i think he's played by jeff bridge is in the
remake but that character i think he's played by john wane yeah he's played by john wane the john wane
everyone's john wane in the in the old days yeah john wane character is like this nice he's i think
he's a nicer person he's like a good guy he's like awesome and cool but in the remake he's like a drunk
he's like fucking like past his prime and he's like an asshole and whatnot and the big reason why
like westerns kind of became darker and grittier is because of the movie blazing saddles that really
like killed that really killed the trope of the whole like a really like good guy western
man doing good and whatnot all they needed was one good lampoon right and you know you know what's
another you know what's another movie that kind of did something another parry that kind of did
something similar for their own is it spaceballs no not spaceballs okay it's fucking austin powers
what for like spy thrillers for for the james the james spawn reboot that happened in like the
early 2000s with daniel craig uh the reason so in those early like i think the first three or four
movies there there was no jokes no character would say a fucking joke in those movies and that's because
of austin powers like that's because they were like we're not we're not like austin powers right
because that's because i think it was this period where like people weren't like
interested in james bond movies and the popular side guys was austin powers right like oh this is
kind of silly right so when uh they they brought back james bond they're all like okay we're gonna
make a serious james bond or he's gonna be he's gonna you know it was very post-9 11 like the
pierce brazil movies are kind of silly yeah they are they're over the top yeah yeah because i mean one
of the bad guys was like fucking christ for walkings and one of those movies but but yeah but
with um the daniel craig one they took it super serious this new james bond is like very there's
he never smiles never smiles he has ptsd because you know we were in the iraq war and that was hot
to give it ptsd right that was some hot shit yeah that was some hot shit and yeah so it's funny
funny funny funny but yeah i'll read i'll read clara so next time i come back i'll have read
everything hell yes i hope you do i hope everyone at home also does
yeah they should also one one little thing uh john wane i gotta read the i gotta read the new
chapter i haven't read chapter four yet it's not out yet well it'll be out for amazon but it's in
the book it's in the book so you should buy the book you should buy the book you should buy the
i'm not gonna do that no i am no i am i am gonna do it oh silly billy and i gotta by this time i
will have i will have bought the the pcp uh dusty dumps a pcp voicemail uh a bandcamp collection i
said i was gonna buy that and i didn't get around to it yet but by the friday i will
gonna buy that and i'm gonna buy clara said yes and i bought and i already bought my cobble
mcpagliacci oh hell yeah but i'm i'm accumulating order now i'm consuming i'm consuming
western comics i'm support i'm supporting i'm supporting creators whose work i appreciate
the average supporter i'm creating
i'm created over here mom oh i'm creating but like uh uh john wane right he's like
he was the big movie star yeah he played a lot of cowboys he was known for that i think
john wane made famous in diehard yeah uh uh john wane he uh he just looks like someone's dad
which was always funny to me because he's always like in these cowboy films and he's like the cool
guy the the serious guy the sensible guy and the guy who knows what's up and he's got he's got the
quick hand but he just looks like a strawberry like a guy's dad it feels like it's a you think
like a vanity project that he's always in yeah well cowboy movies are very dad core
they're very dad core it's just sort of like that they're on they're on again again i was
thinking of clint eastwood no you're right john wane does just look like some guy's dad
yeah clint eastwood looks like a hot boy yeah yeah he was like a good looking guy
john wane literally looks like you've ever seen um the church of the subgenius
yeah i heard of it uh nope it was like kind of like a ironic cult that people would join
yeah it's kind of a it's kind of a gen X thing i think yeah it was like oh it'd be so ironic if
we were part of like a funny little cult and um yeah that's what it was well like their logo
the the logo of the church of the subgenius is um man there's something so i think i'm a little i
think i'm a little bit i think i got a little bit of that nostalgia for a time that i never
experienced about like fucking like gen X irony culture i think i probably would have been like
all in on the church is the subgenius if i was like you know at the right age when it was like
at its peak uh but um yeah this is its logo is this guy called jr dobs jr bob dobs and like
they that yeah john wane looks like that looks like this guy lamal that's pretty funny
yeah i thought this guy's like a generic like dad picture right yeah like yeah i don't know if it's
based on an actual person or what but yeah it's it's it's meant to it's meant to look like uh like
you know mr walton or you know the idea of like a post post war old timey you know american father
figure yeah yeah it's funny that it's funny to imagine that like the that stereotype involves
smoking a pipe because smoking a pipe is fucking disgusting smoking a pipe is like foul it's like
a foul thing to do but it's let's put together image of oh yes a respectable dad it's it's classy
he's got his pipe and it looks cool in an image i think you wouldn't want to be around a guy who
smoked a pipe in real life i think it would be extremely unpleasant unless you're also a pipe
pipe weed smoker and then it's fine that's why they have the smoking room yeah true and various
business but then they smell but then they smell everywhere they go they're gonna smell like it
everywhere i know they just they're just they're just being i guess they're just guys i guess back
in the day everything must have just smelled like smoke like everywhere you went must have smelled
like smoke all the time yeah everything smelled like shit back in the medieval times because there
was shit in everywhere well that's understandable day like like the shit that the the shit that guys
could get away with was like 10 times more than like the shit they could get away with now now i
can't even ask a girl to have sex with me twice or else cheesy jumps down my throat and calls me
atrocious now now now i can't now like they send you news when they know i don't want them i just
don't want them stop sending them to me all i know about jr bob dobs is he never takes no
parent answer he he will never stop asking he's got it's called the sigma grind set it's called
the grind set i was gonna say about how like oh there's this there's this like kind of illusion
of like people like ted bundy we're like oh the reason he murdered so many people was because he
was so swab and whatnot i was like no no because the standards of like hitting on women was so low
back then um there's this kind of like there was this tiktok trend i remember a couple months ago
where like people were like um like doing they were like hearing to their like stories of how
their grandma got their grandpa and it would always be like the grandpa would commit like a
sex crime or sexual assault to them and then they would get married and then the clip is like played
over with the fucking um the fucking what's the name of the show the doot doot doot doot doot doot
doot doot doot doot doot doot doot doot was a law and order a law and order yeah s sv u
right yeah special victims unit and it's like yeah that's that's fucking true yeah like back in the
day like if you wanted to get with a girl you'd sneak into her window and assault her at night
and then you'd marry her that same week because that's because the parent their parents would insist
on it's like oh you rape my daughter well you better marry her then you better marry you better
marry her then responsibility young man oh i suppose boys will be boys as long as you take
responsibility right yeah it's um atrocious terrible time we have to go back we gotta go back
i mean i have to go back though i mean i think of all those statues we're missing out it's the
what it's the wildling way it's the wildling way you got it that's how you keep the gene pool
broad and and deep you gotta you gotta you gotta kidnap a wife from a neighboring twine god you
know who's twine i'm maybe i'm enabling twine never doing twine you know who's really ruining
the gene pool i committed sexual i committed i committed kidnapping and sexual assault against
members of the enemy twine oh i impregnated them against their will that keeps the gene strong
our twine will prosper oh that was that was really like ruining the gene pool like you know who
was like the worst people brown people i'm sorry what we're fixing the gene pool and in my opinion
but all right tell me well um comedians ugly comedians that have hot wives are like ruining
the gene pool they're fucking they're putting their ugly just because they're funny just because
they're funny really you're gonna let them ruin the our fucking our humanity with right ugly children
just because they're funny because by eating by eating a lot of food uh they they grow become
very large and then according to lamarckian genetics that means that they'll pass on the
largeness gene to their offspring so they're they're gonna have fat children you see that they're
ruining the ruining the gene pool it's i agree i agree exactly uh i've never been swimming in the
gene pool i i've heard it's great somebody i've heard it's nice i think it was i think it was
galactic to be posted at something about how in the in the lion king like they don't they they
understand what genes are like scar is talking about like the gene pool but there's some other
thing where like they're completely baffled by some like really very simple like mechanical concept
i don't i don't remember what the example was but it's like yeah why is scarred
why are these lions in the pride land of africa why is he talking about
the gene pool what does he know about men gregor mendel it's messed up he's right he's he's
read a book he's the only lion that read a book he's the only lion that read a book and it was
mine conf and it turned him fascist i wish um i wish that uh galactic be like would be on a podcast
or something because i really do like his tweets i really like his tweets too i think he's he's a
he makes funny he's just always got some funny little like like just weird isn't it weird how
this how this 90s this early 90s cartoon had some i don't even whatever he's always pointing out some
dumb shit i am i dm them a couple times being like i really want you on my podcast and he said like
i really hate my voice so i'm not going to do that it's too bad my dude like please get some of
that get some of that fucking white boy self-esteem not to not to out him or anything but i i asked
arthur viader the guy who had made a zeta gal if he wanted to be on the podcast and he said yeah
basically the same he like doesn't like the sound of his voice or something like that he just didn't
yeah i got him to join the the server but like yeah i really wanted to talk to that guy but he
seems just seems not comfortable with presenting himself in the audio medium which is unfortunate
but what can you do that's lame i mean i hate my voice and i'm still here but everyone else hates it
too that's fine that's not true but give your voices like a sweet angel speaking to me hug you
say these things i'm afraid i'm afraid your baby's with the angels now
oh boy yeah um yeah i like to be is my white whale of what is it oh to get on to get on your
podcast to get my podcast yeah you know it's funny i made that joke somewhere else and i also got
the same reaction they're like whoa whoa what well first first i thought oh what you want to kill
him and then and then you've been oh it's like oh what you mean he's like a fat white woman that
you're attracted to and then oh no no he's like your white whale is someone i mean i guess you
could use it someone very something that you why was like it it could be used as like someone
you're really certain something you're something you're chasing something you're chasing after
yeah that's fine right i'm grinding i i i figured out my goals i figured out my white whales for the
year i um i i've got i've got i've got two things i got i got two lists i got my list of i got my
list of bug bears and i got my list of white whales my bug bears are things i do not want and my
list of white whales are things that i do want that's where'd you put your pet peeves that's
bug bears that's just the subcategory of bug bears bug bears yeah bug bears yeah like water bears
yeah okay yeah all right i guess also bugaboos i think bugaboos and bug bears are the same thing
bugaboos chuggaboos not like the boogaloo boy that's it i'm out of rhymes
if
it but but joker and bug peeves
what if we just set a bunch of random nonsense words for a while juggalo juggalo juggalo jili
juggalo i hear styrofoam javajiga that's a twitter account i hate javajiga
why do you hate javajiga because they're the the person who did the
the fucking whole like, oh, graphic novel section, manga section, it's so fucking over.
No, they're not. Wait, is that them?
Yeah, that's them.
No, I didn't realize it was them.
Every time, every time, like, I've never seen a good take from them.
I swear I've only ever seen, like, annoying ass takes from them.
Oh, I kind of thought, I kind of like, okay.
Maybe, maybe they did something.
Well, I mean, well, I mean, okay, you know what, you know what, you know what, I mean,
I'm actually not that mad because, I mean, I don't even disagree.
Like, it is over in the sense that, like, yeah, they're making more.
Yeah, they're making more manga because the money is there.
It's been over, like, the thing is, like, it's been over since, like, the 90s,
everyone has been saying, oh, it's dying, it's dying, it's dying.
It's like, yeah.
Right, right.
Just read, please.
Don't get drawn, you idiot.
Read Daniel Klaus.
He's gonna have a new book in October.
You can pre-order it now.
Really?
Yes.
Actually, have you read Patience, which was the last book?
That one came out in 2016.
What was the one you got me to read?
Dan, it was David Boring.
That was also Dan Klaus, right?
Yeah, that was Daniel Klaus.
Yeah, that's the only one I've read.
Hey, I just hit 1600.
Just hit 1600 Twitch followers.
Hey, oh, that's 40 followers.
Whoa.
I think you should read Defray next, Ben.
I think you'll like Defray.
It's kind of like David Boring, but it's kind of...
Maybe I'll order it on Amazon when I'm ordering Clarissa.
It's Daniel Klaus doing his version of like, oh, superheroes in real life, but it's like...
No one ever talks about how he really shows how pathetic it is.
There's been other things where they're like, oh, superheroes in real life, but I think
Daniel Klaus probably hits it the most realistic in what would happen.
How do you feel about...
Who was that guy who was the superhero in real life in real life?
Phoenix Jones.
Phoenix Jones, yeah.
Yeah.
Do you ever see that?
There's an atrocity guide video about Phoenix Jones.
Yeah, he's like, end up selling drugs.
Yeah, he was selling drugs on the side.
I think...
He was busting people for selling drugs while he was...
Like, that's the terrible thing.
I wouldn't begrudge him.
I wouldn't begrudge him a side hustle.
I wouldn't begrudge him a side hustle, but the fact that he was busting other people
for it while he was doing it is like, ugh, that's so disgusting.
That was part of the plan to come off as a superhero, that drug bust, everyone butt your own.
That sounds like a plot to something, like Spider-Man Story or something.
That's a really good video.
I wonder if atrocity guides made any more...
I think they have.
I really like that channel.
It is good.
It's like down the rabbit hole, but better, and they still make videos.
I think they pump out stuff faster, which I really like.
I really hate that down the rabbit hole would spend so long on just one video.
I think they've been working on one for a long ass time, and it's like...
It won't be worth a wait.
Yeah, that's the kind of annoying thing.
The Wings of Emotion video, bad.
Most of their other videos are very good, but I don't...
Do you know what the new one is going to be on?
I think that...
I hear people back and forth talking about it.
I thought I heard someone say that, oh, they're doing the Keemstar retrospective, or they're doing...
That sucks.
I mean, hopefully not that.
That sucks really bad.
That blows.
Or like some sort of expansion on Furries, or they're doing...
Garbage.
Did they do Gaia Online already?
I don't know if they did Gaia Online.
I don't think so.
Okay, Atrocity Guide has won...
Oh no, Atrocity Guide has only made one in the last six months.
Yeah, the last two down the rabbit hole videos I thought were kind of not interesting.
Wings of Redemption, I would say Wings of Redemption is a bad video.
Really?
I thought that one was interesting.
I liked how it was secretly in Origins of Keemstar video.
Yeah, I didn't feel like that was intentional.
It was slowly rising in the background.
Yeah, probably not.
That was like an accident.
8.6...
Oh God, okay, great.
Cool, his worst video has the most views, so this is going to be what his fucking stupid
channel turns into now.
Awesome.
Cool.
Oh fuck, I haven't seen the last Atrocities Guide video, even though I did a podcast episode
on the movie that they're talking about in that video.
Oh, the kidnapped and forced to make action films?
Yeah, they're talking about the only North Korean Kaiju film, Pogusari.
Well, I've heard you talk about that.
Yeah, Pogusari, it's great.
We do have an official Toku cast on it.
I haven't seen the two newest ones.
The one about Bob's Game is really good.
I mean, I've watched all of these and they're all really good.
It's a great channel.
Bob's Game is one of the few examples of earlier where we were talking about, oh, just make
games for yourself.
Bob's Game is the ultimate that because the guy is insane.
Have you seen the Mandalore Gaming video about, fuck, Mandalore Gaming?
I think I might have mentioned this one before, but I can't remember the name again.
Atrocity.
Oh, fuck.
It's the one where you play as the edgy teen who kills pedophiles.
No.
The Simpsons Game?
I know about the Kanye Game.
Anonymous Agony.
That's another one that is just like somebody made it in RPG Maker.
Bob's Game looks so dumb.
It's like, hey, what if I made a game about me in real life walking around my house?
You should make that game, then.
What's the name of that one guy?
Oh, Austin Cowell?
Austin McConnell.
Yeah.
That guy, he's the guy who made a video where he was talking about that film that he made
that was bad all those years ago.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's called, I made a movie.
It's Stunk.
Oh, Austin McConnell.
Yeah, Austin McConnell.
Oh yeah, and didn't that guy plagiarize his video about the Special Olympics team?
Oh, did he?
It might have just been a case that he made another, he just made another video with a very similar
content to one that John Boyce made.
And I don't know if it's like ever technically been called out as plagiarism, but
the John Boyce video is better, and John Boyce is better than Austin McConnell.
Fuck Austin McConnell.
Austin McConnell is very, he has such like a, the quality of his videos jump so much like back and forth.
I feel.
I haven't seen a good one in a while.
The majority of them are kind of like mid, and also I think you ever like,
I liked his one about the Harry Potter play.
I thought that one was pretty good.
I ever like, and this is kind of like a kind of like specific, this is kind of a certain
content creator where they're like, they have pretty good insight on like writing and like
criticism and whatnot.
But when it comes to them making art, it's always kind of like, wow, this is bad.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Many such cases.
Yeah.
Austin McConnell is kind of like that because I feel like he has really good insight on certain
things.
But then when he was talking about his, because he's all like, oh, we're making like a, we're
making kind of like an animated movie based on public domain superheroes.
And I'm going to make my own like little animated superheroes cinematic universe with public
domain characters, which isn't that bad of an idea.
But when I heard his kind of retelling of one of the characters stories, like his version
of it, it's like, wow, it just sounds just as dull as like the original.
Like, why don't you like do something completely different?
Yeah.
I see.
Because there's already like so many, there's been so many comics about public domain superheroes
and other public domain characters.
And like, I think people, I think people have done really like beyond amazing job as being
incredibly clever with those characters or going, going in such interesting directions
that like whatever like Austin McConnell is trying to do, it sounds kind of like whatever.
And I'm pretty sure when the movie, when this movie is finished, it's going to be like very
mid.
It's not going to be like, and he's not going to be like incredibly good or incredibly bad.
He's going to be like, okay, I'm going to forget about it.
Yeah.
Did you?
Okay.
You know, Vito Gizwaldi.
Yeah.
Is he making like a comic?
I don't know.
He's making some kind of superhero thing.
And I don't know what the deal is with it, but I don't like that guy.
So it's probably bad, but I haven't, I don't know what the, I think it's called super killer.
And I don't know what the deal is, but I kind of want to know just so I can be like, I was
right.
It's stupid.
Yeah.
That's the guy who just do the constantly like, oh, it's gone woke and now it sucks or he
does.
I think he does that like semi ironically, but not completely ironically, but like semi
ironically.
Yeah.
His thumbnail, learnaboutsuperkiller.org.
What is that?
You know, it's funny.
Like yesterday, a couple of days ago, I think I made like a tweet Friday saying like, hey
guys, post your comic recommendations that aren't like Marvel or DC.
And someone recommended the comic common America, which is not a good comic.
Common America.
Oh, I know about common America.
Yeah.
Common America sucks.
Oh, the one that Mary whether collabed with.
Yeah.
It's fucking even though they're like a bunch of fucking far right motherfuckers.
A bunch of fucking MAGA heads.
It's like, it's like the most mid person teams up with like the worst person I know.
It's I was thinking about making a video.
Cool.
Yeah.
I think because it fucking I have I talked about common America before on this podcast.
I think maybe a bit.
Yeah.
I know about it from you.
It's it's so it's so funny.
It's just so funny like the whole and I've probably have said this before where her origin
story is literally like, Oh, what's Peter Parker?
Oh, his uncle got shot due to him being like selfish and he's like, I must take responsibility
for these amazing powers I've gained while common America's origin is like one time my
science teacher told me to play baseball with boys, but I'm a girl.
I want to do girl things.
And then she gets the powers that's incredible.
It's fucking it's just it's just amazing.
And this this was this was the Marvel killer.
This was like, yeah, we're going to out so Marvel and DC fucking.
That's amazing.
All right.
Here it comes.
Super killer.
Give me give me the five give me the five second pitch on super killer.
Here comes super killer the multiverse is home to a variety of super powered individuals
nobles heroes who risk their lives to protect the world from destruction.
Fortunately, for a multiversal assassin, Sam King, these heroes won't be going down without
a fight.
So he okay, this comic's going to kick some ass.
Okay.
God fucking like like these these guys who are always like, like, oh, I'm going to make
my better superhero than Marvel and DC.
They always look awful.
Like none of them could design sounds like in superhero sounds so fucking generic.
He looks like a background character from my hero academia is a learn learn learn more.
This comp is going to is a hilarious blood soaked superhero romp where absolutely no
one is safe.
Okay.
So it's edgy superheroes.
I really super it's superheroes with blood.
It's terrible.
Here's a fucking sucks.
It's worse than I thought.
Isn't that Deadpool already?
This is like imagine if Deadpool had a bad design and sucked.
All right.
I come away from this pitch having what would what would I tell someone if I wanted to recommend
them super killer?
I'd be like, it's a superhero.
And he kills people.
What?
Oh, wow.
Never heard that one before fucking 10 and 10 idea.
I don't know.
Wow.
I thought there would be a hook, but there's but there's no hook.
I'd be lost at superhero.
I haven't been interested in a superhero design.
They lose you at superhero.
100 years.
Superhero.
But then you say, but and then you go, huh, then you get your back again and they and
then they put their mouth to you and they say, but he kills people.
And then you go, oh, no, you lost me again.
A superhero literally doing anything is like unappealing to me because I just don't like
what they are.
There's probably some twist on the formula that might be if they wear like a costume.
Get out of here.
They wear a mask.
If they have a double identity as a million is the same thing over and over again.
Superheroes are always the same.
Stop it.
You know, I'm so tired of superheroes.
The thing is, people talk about stuff like superhero fatigue.
Ultimately, you just need like one good superhero movie and then people usually shut up about
it.
But if someone's not interested in superheroes, that's fine, like there's no problem with
that.
I don't really care.
Okay.
I get it.
So the idea of super killer.
Okay.
He kills other superheroes.
It's basically like he kills characters that resemble other heroes that you might be more
familiar with.
Like he kills Superman types and he kills magical girls and he kills what's this guy?
What's this guy?
What?
Who?
Super killer?
A guy who looks like Batman.
He kills characters that remind you of comic.
This fucking sucks.
What if a superhero went around killing characters that you're familiar with?
God, you know this character.
You know, my expectations were low and I'm still disappointed.
Give, do you know this character?
Martial law?
No.
It's drawn by Kevin O'Neill, which is a British artist.
You should know this, Gib.
But he put an American flag on the gun?
No.
Oh, because the story takes place in America.
An American flag on a gun is like, it's like, that's good.
Anyway, super killer just sounds like this.
I can see he's got like a Batman cowl on his little thing there, his little belt there.
Yeah.
It's funny because martial law is kind of like, imagine if someone like, what's the
name of that one political cartoonist who labels everything like a for a writer?
Oh, he's a libertarian.
Ben Garrison.
Yeah.
So like imagine if Ben Garrison like wrote like a superhero comic.
But the thing is that what's great about like martial law is that he's like a fucking,
he's like my favorite fascist.
He's a really awesome fascist character.
Hell yeah.
And and and basically like, so the gist is that he's basically a cop for superheroes,
right?
And but the thing is that in their universe, superheroes are like several things that aside
from like being like propped up as like protectors of like good in society.
The majority are superheroes are like former like war veterans who are who have superpowers
and are fucking insane and they just kill random people on the street.
Yeah.
And the and martial law comes in and fucking shoots the shit under and and rips them up
part and yeah, this actually martial law is like a big influence on villain verse.
Oh, wait, you might you might have mentioned this guy before, maybe, maybe.
Yeah.
And the the the book was like co-created by a thing, one of the guys behind Judge Dredd.
But but I think this also Linkara hates his book.
He really fucking does not like this character.
But I love this guy because Linkara is
like for every because he's woke.
Actually, I would say he's just stupid.
But I'm damn.
But for every kind of like interesting thing Linkara has to say, I feel like he always has
two stupid things to say with it, too.
Because he talks about like, oh, I'm tired of stories where superheroes are bad.
We already know what superheroes being bad is like.
They're they're called super villain.
And it's like fucking the fucking card.
Wow, you know, do you not get the idea of a deconstruction?
Or or the fact that like or the fact that like, do you think cops are like all good?
Do you think like, wow, yeah, that really blows.
Do you think there's not like some sort of fucking moral?
Like maybe there's something else going on.
Maybe the fact that like you can't individually stop all crime one at a time
as a person, even with fucking superpowers.
And it's like, yeah, the idea, the idea is that the the superheroes are bad is not.
What if we made the superhero bad instead of good?
It's like the superhero does the things a superhero does.
But we see that, in fact, they are bad, actually.
I think what's great about martial law is that it has a really good design.
It's also very funny.
Everything is so exaggerated in martial law.
It's like it's also a cartoony, you know, like nothing is supposed to be taken like.
Like really seriously.
Like there's I think in the first story, I kind of have a problem
where they like take themselves too seriously at certain parts.
But everything else is like very it's very like goofy with it.
And I mean, the biggest example is that all the characters have their
like beliefs just like written out on them.
And like, oh, he has fear and loafing on on his like stomach.
His right arm has barbed wire because one of his power, his powers
that he doesn't feel any pain.
So like he like, you know, he fights other superheroes and they can't really hurt him.
And I think my favorite story is is the second story.
The second martial art story, martial law story where he fights the Avengers
and they're like all members of like an insane asylum.
And he's mostly and it's it's the story works so good when like
they're just doing like goofy shit.
Like there's like a one scene in in the second story
where he's like chasing a punisher proxy who has like a swatze gun in his forehead.
And and they're fighting in an elevator and this
this punisher guy is about to like electrocute him with some wires.
And he and he says the word superhero to martial law.
And then martial art like fucking like gets so pissed off from here.
The word superhero is all like like, oh, you said the you said the secret
world superheroes, my Shazam.
Many fucking like rips apart whenever it's holding them.
And it's it's just so it's just the more goofy it is.
I think it's the more funny it is.
And it's it's it's great.
I really like it.
The super killer looks really fucking dull.
Like this this concept has been done fucking.
I see I see nothing appealing about it.
Well, I'm glad I'm glad we put that to bed.
The thing of me is that superheroes
aesthetically are dead to me.
I hate colorful costumes with wacky powers
that a child could come up with.
And even if it's good, even if it's like a great thing,
I just don't like the look of a superhero.
I feel upset when I see such things.
Yeah, feel enraged.
Yeah, there's something there's something there's something a little off
putting about the whole just the whole aesthetic of the spandex clad hero.
I agree. It's a bit.
I feel a little bit like about it.
The way you see if it hadn't been like pushed when I was a film
when I was a little kid like 30 years when I was a little kid.
I didn't I'm completely desensitized when I was a little kid.
I didn't like movies that had animals like cartoons about animals.
I thought animals were for babies.
I wanted humans only please.
So now as an adult, I feel the same way about superheroes.
It's for babies.
And I just feel sick when I see it.
Yeah, a little bit even shows like the boys that people tell me are good.
I'm like, yeah, but like it's a fucking superhero thing.
They're going to have powers.
They're going to be like powers.
I get it.
They're going to show that the good guys are the bad guys, actually,
because they serve the status quo already seen.
Watchmen, I don't need to see it again in a TV show.
We've been going for four.
That's my trigger hours.
I feel like maybe it's time to be wrapping up
and maybe getting to to one piece discussion pretty soon.
Yes.
Cheesy. Let's let's do you have I mean.
Do you have if there's any if there's any last words
before you make you walk the plank, you know, speak them now.
I guess.
You know, I'm not interested in stories of colorful characters
with powers that children would come up with.
OK, just say you won't reveal it or skip it.
Just say you don't like.
I will not.
I already read it in my face until you make more of it.
Whoa.
Yeah, more, more, more, more, more is coming.
Villain versus different.
It feels different.
They're villains.
They're not in New York or like some alternative,
like the same New York where petty crime is the reason
somebody puts on a superhero mask.
Why would you do that?
Why would you feel like it's not like, I mean,
they're not even like in a society.
They're just like a completely chaotic.
They're just all in a bunch of like spaceships,
just like trying to all try to kill each other.
I don't know, it doesn't it doesn't feel at all
like a superhero story.
It's just a bunch of like monsters in space.
That like you want to sometimes they fight each other, I guess.
Yeah, it's just everyone.
Just like literally everyone that exists in the world
is trying to kill everyone else, right, right?
Because it's all villains.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much.
Well, there is a society, but like it doesn't whatever.
It doesn't matter.
It's not it's not crucial to the story I'm telling.
So it's not it's not like we don't really see it.
But yeah, anyway, pre-order make Paglacci.
You got like two days left on Sunday.
Should be the last day.
Actually, this Sunday, this coming Sunday,
I'm going to be on a live stream with a stereo.
Oh, cool.
And we're going to talk about we're going to talk about
make Paglacci ask him about his cancel Ben St.
shirt. Yeah, I'll I'll I'll ask him about that.
We're also going to be talking about the toddler show, Bluey.
I'm going to bluey I'm going to bluey pill
stereo on it.
I have some insight about the show.
I was on the ground floor for the show.
So, you know, congratulations.
But a bit of a deal.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, it's crazy.
Imagine imagine being into a kid's show for.
I can't imagine.
I would kill I would destroy myself.
I almost said I almost said kill myself.
But I would never say that.
Anyway, yeah, cool.
All right.
Prior to make Paglacci.
Thanks for joining us, Cheesy.
Now, get out of here.
You guys can you guys aren't going to do a voicemail.
We're going to do it after we do one piece of discussion.
That would be voicemail.
All right, then. Well, it's been it's been good.
I'll I'll talk.
Should we sink one more time?
Yeah, we can say one more time.
Yeah, that's good.
All right. Three, two, one, sink.
Sink three, two, one, sink.
Sink.
Elisa should probably use that one and not the early one.
Maybe sounds good.
All right. All right.
I'm going to stop recording.
Thanks for having me on.
I'll talk to you.
Our pleasure.
Thanks for jumping in.
All right.
Yeah, so I read I read one piece.
I read the new one piece while cheesy was talking about one piece, I think.
So let's go and 1078 escape limit.
So we've got a German 66
and Caesar clown.
They have formed neo-mads.
Yeah, I mean.
Neo-mads are two mad scientists together at last.
I think we could have gathered from the last one that they were going to team up, but OK.
I wonder what they're going to do.
Probably some mad science, if I had to guess.
Cool.
Well, I wonder how judge is going to react
to hearing that his son, Sanji, is in league with.
I saw.
For a while, I felt like we had too much Caesar clown.
I was kind of sick of Caesar clown for a while, but we haven't seen him in a bit.
So OK, yeah, yeah, bring him back.
Yeah, I mean, what was he?
He has been one of those consistent.
He was in punk.
He's been in like a lot of arcs.
Luffy. Luffy punched him and then law took his heart out
and he was a bargaining chip interest Rosa.
And then he continued with them, with law, I think,
as law still wanted him as a bargaining chip for some reason.
Like the thing that the thing that they wanted to trade him for didn't go through.
So he didn't trade him away.
So you got to keep him from trading away.
They ended up on a whole cake.
And I don't even know what, how he got there.
But he was involved with Capone gang, Beji.
And they had the the whole like big mom
assassination and Caesar is just like, I just want to go home.
I don't like this anymore.
Well, and now he did.
All right. He did.
Uncle Kizar is coming.
OK, you know, I'm just I'm just going to complain about Nate's complaints
because I watched him critique this chapter.
Nate doesn't like the the the the the the the diagram showing where people are.
He says they're he says their point.
They are a little hard to follow.
I think when when it's something big like the what's it called?
The big Skull Island in Wano.
Onigashima, it was very important.
I think the diagrams were extremely important in Wano.
You had to understand that the flying thing was going to crash into the other thing.
And you had to understand that like the lava was like, you know,
descending through floors and was going to hit the weapons, cash and detonate.
I yeah, I think it's more just to give you a grasp of the scale of the place
because you can't draw.
You can't draw like scene setting.
You can't waste time setting the scene every chapter.
You already know from the previous chapter that they're in a place.
But if you've forgotten, this is where they are.
And yeah, just give it like very quickly here, just in case you're confused.
And it is sometimes useful.
I don't really pay.
I don't really internalize them that much.
I mean, most of the time is like this building.
I can't remember which building is B, C or A.
I have no idea who is going from which place to which place or where everyone is.
They're just saying, during this scene, we're in this place.
And I guess it might be helpful later, but I don't hate it.
It's not doing much for me, particularly.
Sure, because everybody's walking around and.
Like on the map is not is not shown
where the seraphim have been fighting people.
Yeah, I don't really remember where everyone was.
I mean, it's true. I don't think about it like all the time.
But it probably is largely for people that are maybe a chapter behind or.
Just to just to just put a chapter behind you just read chapter.
I mean, just to establish that like these people are in separate locations that are related.
And then it's it's not really it's it's not always for knowing
it's not always for like getting a grasp of the whole situation for this.
I think it's just to show where these characters are without having to draw.
And then and then this next panel, this one of Stussy, Nate, Nate called this.
Can you believe he called this scuffed piece?
He said the line work was rough.
It was looking scuffed and we are in scuffed piece.
And like, it's fine. I mean, I fucking fine.
It is fine.
I I know what he means, though, over time,
Oda has obviously he's gotten older and maybe he's not as he's a bit looser.
If you go back to early chapters, it's a very much completely different style.
I think it looks.
Oh, you like the new. Yeah, I like the new as well.
I don't they don't bother me at all.
They they show you the thing.
That's how that's how it's got to be sometimes.
Sometimes it's just you got to get through
a panel of somebody talking on a thingy.
And it doesn't really matter if it's the most beautiful thing thing ever.
You want to save those moments for when you're doing like the big
the big reveals, the big punches.
OK, so.
And like, it's largely really good, even if it's a bit sloppy,
line art wise, compared to previous fine.
But it's got so much character, I say impression is wrong.
Well, sloppy in that it's like compared to previous one piece.
You know, lines don't always yeah, I connect.
There's some some some's like maybe the the pen is a bit thicker.
But like it's it's just it still has the character.
So that's been like it's been like this for a long time.
Like I literally I literally don't care and I literally don't understand
how someone could look at this and be like it looks worse than it used to
when the lines were cleaner, like I don't understand
feeling that way about the difference.
I yeah, I don't get it really.
I know that you can you can observe things,
but I don't know why you would get not even not even getting mad.
Just it to me, it looks better this way.
The the the the cleaness of the lines did not
make me did not impress me before, if anything.
I I would say that there's they're different.
I like old one piece as well.
I like an oil.
I'm I like I like scuffed piece.
I like it better.
I'm I'm I'm I'm reading.
So they're taking the government is taking the situation even more seriously
than Ohara. Yes, that's bad.
That's a bad sign.
They're going to do a super bomb.
Also, I forgot that Stussy was with Jim Bay
and we hadn't seen Jim Bay, I think.
So my my theory that it was to see with the gun, they're wrong.
Oh, Stussy, I don't know how to say it.
And I'm just going to say it wrong every time.
I it's got to be Stussy.
It's got to be Stussy.
Stussy, but then they say Luffy instead of Luffy.
So they so what are you what can be known, huh?
What can it possibly be?
That's you're right.
I mean, you're right. You're right. You're right.
I'm going to say Stussy until until I'm proven proven wrong.
Stussy, Factory A, Fabrio Stratum.
OK, I'm sorry.
I don't know if this is annoying, but to to to rag on Nate even more,
he got like in a previous page, this building was written with it was
spelled like F-A-B-I-R-I-O.
It was spelled Fiberio, but it's actually supposed to be called Fabrio.
And he spent like he spent like five minutes being like,
oh, Oda, Oda made a mistake.
What a goof. He put an extra I in the name.
I mean, it could be hidden by the little bit there.
Yeah, like there's a space for it right where the panel.
Well, the text, well, the text says Fabrio.
Yes, but that's translated and it's a fan translation.
So they may not have realized.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I guess. Yeah, it could be.
Honestly, true.
It's one of those panel things where he does like a tiny sliver of a panel
to show that we're changing scene.
Yeah, changing scene or time is progressing.
Third or so.
Yeah, so Centimaru is here and from Stussy that.
Yeah, the CP zeros are a mission.
Was to eliminate the doctor.
And wait for the arrival of.
Wait for who's arrival, Kazaru, yes.
So the the the admiral.
And so Centimaru is like, OK, everybody,
all you little goofs and I don't even know who you are.
These little citizens, get out of here.
Save yourselves.
These random these random egghead citizens are awesome.
Yeah, I love I love in that they're all running away.
The the big robot in the back with the clockwork head.
Yeah, he's pretty good.
I think I like the little hooded guy down in the middle.
Also, yeah, the little hooded guy.
I mean, all of them, they're just so.
Yeah, yeah, they're great.
Nice little that that guy on the right.
I like I like the Phineas and Ferb guy over on the right.
Yeah, he is kind of like that.
Sexy lady in the front, she's very cute, you know.
If only it was so easy later sexy ladies
for me, then I could draw them all.
Oh, it doesn't even have to think about anything.
He's just brainless.
He's just drawing all this with no brain power.
Oh, oh, it just sneezes in a sexy big boob lady.
Just appears on this in a panel and he's like, that's not good enough.
That's a good power.
It's pretty good.
OK, so we flip over to third floor lab
building, see, no idea.
Sure, we got Frankie, who's not fully stoned.
He's only had a bit of that.
How did how did that happen?
He took a bite of stone stone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How did he only become a half petrified?
How does that work?
I believe it's been shown to happen with her powers before.
I don't think it's like.
I don't know, though.
I don't know if it's like a her vision thing, like a Medusa or whether.
Like her beam is where you turn into stone, or whether if you see it,
your body turns into stone fully.
I'm not entirely sure how it works.
Maybe Frank is just resisting the cuteness.
He either was like, yeah, not fully taken in by the cuteness,
or maybe the beam just didn't fully hit him.
He's so big, you see.
He is quite large.
All right, so.
So Usob and Lilith are fucked.
They're just they're just they're just dead unless unless she reverts them, right?
That's the yeah, that's the state here.
I think so.
Yeah, it could be a thing in the future was like, oh, chopper,
you found a way to unstone if I people.
If I mean, if anyone can like reverse the effects of a fruit, what if like?
OK, crazy idea.
What if like Seastone could just reverse it?
I feel like that would have been tried before.
And it would have been known that that works.
I mean, if I'm thinking like a fruit did something, Seastone is what I would think
to like undo the effects of a fruit.
But yeah, it wouldn't necessarily wouldn't necessarily work.
It wouldn't work for every particular fruit, because like what if the fire fruit
or what if a set fire to something you couldn't put the fire out with Seastone?
You would just need water.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it was just an idea.
But Vagapunk, I'm sure Vagapunk could probably come up with something.
Yeah, so.
Little guy, I forgot his name.
I think it's Pythagoras.
He says Pythagoras.
Little lemon gets fucking crushed to death.
This is the guy that he puts his head in like the big body, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Poor little guy.
You snake.
Getting fucking killed.
So crush.
So Lilith is dead.
Pythagoras is seems to have been killed here.
Lilith is stone, Pythagoras crushed.
Wait, I said she doesn't fully stone him.
She just leaves him like that.
Well, she stops because she said somebody says wait.
Oh, it's not Frankie yelling.
Yeah. Well, somebody's saying wait, it could be Frankie.
It looks like she's walking away from this explosion.
Like I thought she crushed Pythagoras and that like caused the explosion.
And then she's walking away from it and Frankie is yelling like wait, wait.
But no, she's looking to the side.
It might think it's someone else.
That's a big explosion.
Yeah. Is that just is that from crushing Pythagoras?
I can only assume it's like one panel.
One panel gets crushed and then the other one explodes.
Yeah, I don't quite understand what's exploding, but I guess it's
guess it would explode immediately when her foot crushed him.
So she would be caught in the explosion and not walking away from it.
But a little confusing, a little weird.
Yeah, I get it.
Then we got Robin and Chopper and Big Lady.
What's her name?
I don't remember the big one.
Atlas Atlas. Yeah, there it is.
Well, all those they're they're hearing all about all of this death
and destruction that's happening.
And Robin's saying we should probably go and find the real Vega punk
because, you know, that's the that's important.
And so they will go.
And so I think they're going to Robin and Chopper are going to be the ones
fighting in that in that environment.
There's a room that's been sealed off for a while.
And I wrote it off since the place isn't useful.
OK, OK, so they're following Sanji's.
But they're following Nami's scream.
Because they think Sanji will go there, too.
And then no, no, no, no, they're saying that Nami will be fine
because Sanji will go to her.
We should instead focus on finding Vega punk.
And Atlas is like, oh, I think he could maybe be in this place.
And it's probably the right place.
Yeah. OK, so Brooke and Nami and Edison.
I don't remember. I don't even remember what Edison's deal.
Did they found they found him like this, right?
Because Edison got like jumped by someone.
I think so.
I think they found him busted up.
But they also were fighting the Jinbei Seraphim just then.
Oh, Nami used the cloud that she got from Big Mom.
I forget his name. I forget everyone's name.
There's too many names.
She zapped him and then Sanji is there
taking the punches, fighting him while they are thinking about stuff.
Brooke is going to go scout for Vega punk with his funny ghost ability.
So this so this bit of Sanji getting punched.
This is another thing that Nate spent a lot of time on
because his eyebrow is reversed.
Normal like like his normally his eyebrow curls at the bottom.
But here it curls at the top and apparently.
And apparently this is like confirmed in an SPS.
Apparently this means that like he's activating his germa powers.
It's like a germa. It's like, yeah, the like the left eyebrow.
OK, like, you know how the eyebrow that used to be covered
curls at the top and the and the one that's now uncovered curls at the bottom.
But the fact that it in this panel curling at the top
means that the eyebrow swirl direction has reversed.
And his eyebrows swirl the other way from his siblings.
But now it's gone the other way.
So now it's swirling the same way as the siblings.
So he's in like germa science mode. Apparently.
Is that something to be complaining about?
I thought that that means it makes sense.
They was a mistake.
Nate was complaining that he was looking at another panel.
I think the idea was that there was another panel where he did seem to be
using like germa science, but his eyebrow was not in reverse mode.
Yeah, one of them is a mistake.
I mean, I was just I was interested because apparently this is like a real thing
that's not bullshit and like it's in SPS's.
So this eyebrow swirl thing actually is real.
So I guess when he says it's the undying power of love, it's actually like.
I mean, everything everything he does is the power of love, right?
Yeah, because he's.
My I think it's he's like he didn't like his germa family connection and his power.
You didn't like using the funny capsule with the suit and the cape or whatever.
Yeah, but he is a super soldier.
So I guess he's like harnessing some of that power to get punched in the face
and not even doesn't look like he's using hacky.
I guess he might be so well.
So I'm sorry, remind me.
They said that like Sanji was the only one that didn't have superpowers,
but like he does have superpowers, right?
He can't. Yeah.
Yes, they call him a failure because he had too many emotions, I think.
The other ones were more emotionless and violent.
But because Sanji loved his mother and his mother was nice,
that he was like he's the freak and maybe he's like the half super kid.
So he's got some latent powers, but he's more of a human than his siblings.
A pair of parents aren't shown to be like totally like inhumane either.
They have the girl.
The girl has emotions.
Yeah, so it's not even like it's a it's a true thing that they're like robots.
Yeah, so she just doesn't like being nasty.
Apparently, the eyebrow swirl direction is like a is some kind of tell with that.
So that's interesting, never picked up on that before.
All right, yes, Zoro and Luffy Zoro, Luffy fighting Kuma.
We're weird little baby Kuma.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Hawkeye and Hawkeye, but he's gone.
He's reprioritized the order of his targets.
He's going after the weaker straw hats to demoralize the stronger ones.
Divious, devious.
Yes, so Zoro and Kaku have to go stop Hawkeye,
which is, I mean, makes sense.
They're already like paired up against that guy.
So now it's the two strong and the other two strong with swords going off
to the guy with swords and the other guy is going to kind of I kind of feel
like this actually puts the odds more in their favor.
I don't know.
I feel like a one on I feel like a two on one fight is more unbalanced.
Two two on one fights is better for the two than than the one two and one one four
on two fight. Yeah. Yeah, because you can do pincer attacks.
You can do strategic maneuvers, you see.
It is funny also that Luffy calls Kaku Usopp because of his nose.
Oh, I didn't mean I didn't even catch that.
Quick, go get him, I didn't even notice.
Lol, that's good.
All right, so Luffy's punching Luchi said, you can't just punch him.
Doesn't matter how many times you try hitting it, that won't work.
And it looks like it's not true.
It's I guess I mean, it's he's definitely he's definitely recoiling
from the blows, maybe he's not doing any real damage.
Yeah, if nothing else, he's getting interrupted so we can't be doing anything.
Yeah. OK, and then we've got.
Only one only one day remains before the famous egghead incident.
However, this is funny.
This is like the first future tense.
Like, yeah, what you're reading right now is going to be so big
in a few days. Is is that what that is that like a narration?
Or is that like her memory?
Like in the is that memory she's experiencing in the Kuma bubble?
No, I think we're just looking at Bonnie to see where she is.
She's crying. Yeah. Yeah.
And and it's not about her this narration.
It's about the egghead incident.
It's very strange.
It's very strange for the narration to just come up with.
Yeah, a big important thing called the egghead incident is happening one day from now.
But let's go back.
But for now, let's journey back into the past.
I think, yeah, it's maybe odd phrasing, but it's really just how do we get here?
And that's yeah, yeah, that's what they get to.
So marriage war and they're getting
marriage war is getting the the the the call from a head about the void century.
Dr.
Vega Punk is reaching the void century.
OK, this is the informant.
This is the trader informing the CP five agents were dispatched.
They didn't learn anything.
And the ships were attacked.
And so.
They send more agents and then it is turned into a big thing.
I wonder about this, because like.
I suppose the idea for this traitor is to, excuse me, I need a I need a water right now.
Oh, I have to pee.
You know what?
I mean, let's let's take a quick break.
One second.
Seltzer, pure Aqua Seltzer, very flavorful.
Yeah.
So.
So as I was saying, I'll say what I was saying again.
So CP five agents were dispatched.
And then their ship vanished and we know they ended up in a pod and then more agents were sent
and they also ended up in the same pod, starving to death.
Now, the reason for doing that, I wasn't sure at first, but now I guess the point is to escalate
the the mystery for the government if the agents are disappearing.
Because if you just say, Dr.
Vega Punk is researching the void century.
So anonymous informant, the government sends agents, they find nothing.
They go back.
They say there was nothing there.
Seen fine.
Right.
Maybe they maybe they think, oh, it's just a prank call.
It's just that it's not a real thing.
So you think the trader specifically kidnapped them so that they would send more powerful
agents?
Yes, I think that makes that does make sense.
Yeah.
Yes.
And eventually they got to talk to the Gorosei, totally exposing the full extent of the genius
scientist's treachery.
So they decided upon the assassination Cypher Cypher Paul Zero was sent and then the five
elders anticipated that Vega Punk would resist.
They said one of their own escorted by Admiral Kizaru, this is this is weird as talking in
past tense about the present.
It is weird.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, they sent them this this was the this.
This is how the decision was made to do this.
So it did happen a little while ago, a little while.
They also reinforced the fleet.
They deployed with backup from several naval broncers.
I like some of these designs are like the long beard guy.
We saw that guy.
We definitely saw that guy before.
I commented on that guy in like a previous chapter.
He was like standing.
I think he was like with the Gorosei or with Kizaru and I was like, who the fuck's that
guy?
So he's cool.
Yeah.
He does look cool.
And the many chins man.
Is that a fish man?
I think that's a fish man.
That's gotta be that's gotta be a fish man.
The caution level was raised to total war imminent.
So this is so like weeks ago when I was saying, wow.
So everything's going well.
They're just going to get Vega Punk and leave.
So easy.
Nothing's going to go wrong.
Right.
Yeah, they're not.
How could it possibly continue?
And they seem, of course, they seem intent on pressing the issue.
Yeah.
Then the sudden unexpected appearance of Emperor Straw Hat Luffy's shit.
Look at these.
Look at these simple clouds.
Look at these cartoony clouds behind.
This is scuffed piece.
You know what Nate's right.
It's comic sucks.
Wait, which where?
Oh, and the one of the going Mary.
You mean the sunny go?
Is it not called the going Mary?
That's the first one.
The sunny.
Yeah, the sunny go.
No, you're right.
Thousand sunny.
The thousand sunny.
Yes.
Just look at there's no no tone, no tone in the sky, no shading on the clouds, scuffed
piece.
Yeah, but they it's only looks good.
It's fine.
It could have used a little it could have used a little screen tone.
It could have used a little depth, but it's OK.
It's fine.
I'm not mad.
I like that.
I don't really think of the Straw Hats as like an emperor like a Luffy's an emperor.
Yeah.
Did they declare him one when the that the last yes, Morgan declared him one after the
events of whole cake.
I think.
Does he get to decide that?
Is that his job?
Well, I think there's no like official status.
It's not like.
Oh, it's not like the Shichi Bukai, which was like an official government job.
It's an official government thing.
And it's not like anything in particular.
It's just like who is who is considered the biggest, baddest pirate in the entire world.
Yeah.
The emperors.
So I guess Big News Morgan does get to decide that because he fucking he controls the narrative
and he thought, wouldn't it be fucking funny if this happened?
Yeah.
Lamal.
So now after the events of one, oh, they know Luffy has the the whatever fruit and the Nica
fruit and they're like, they they're looking at him more like with a, oh, we thought you
were just a rubber boy, but actually you're you're a protagonist, but actually you're
a joy for you're a joy boy.
Oh, you ate the joy.
You ate the joy.
Joy fruit.
Yeah.
Should have called it.
Should have called it the joy.
Joy fruit.
Yes.
He does laugh a lot.
So maybe it is.
Sorry.
Is it the is it the is it the hito hito no me Nica model?
It's not the Nica Nica fruit, right?
It's the hito hito no me model Nica.
I forget.
I'm almost positive that that is hito hito no me.
It's the same.
It's man.
Human human.
It's the same as a Sengoku hito hito no me model Daibutsu.
Yes.
Yeah.
You got the you got the different models.
You got Nica.
You got Buddha.
And you got Chopper.
You got the normal normal guy, the most powerful of all.
What a funny fruit.
So many different forms.
Yeah.
It's like cool.
If you think about like the idea that it's it's a devil fruit so like evolution and and
all that.
It's like they've humans have gone on to land.
They left the sea behind.
Yeah.
And one of the devil fruits evolution is just man.
Maybe it's like the first devil fruit.
Well, didn't we didn't in an SPSO to say that if a human ate the hito hito no me, it would
turn them into like the ideal version of themself.
That's funny.
Yeah.
It's it's it is very funny though that like there's a bunch of different hito.
I assume other if there are more hito hito no means they are other forms of like legendary
person or God type.
Yeah.
God type people.
But then there's one that's just a good that's just guy.
It's just a guy.
Normal guy.
But an ideal guy like a really a really cool guy though.
If you eat it, you become a really cool type guy, not just not just any guy, but but still
a guy.
So the government is like what straw hat?
That's an important character.
This chain of events is going to culminate tomorrow and the outcome will shock the world.
Wow.
Spoilers.
Will be surprised and delighted.
Will be shocked by what we see amazing.
So I for one can't wait to turn the page and learn more.
So we finish with the shaka shot through the head.
Reveal.
Brutal.
Fucking brutal.
Yes.
This helmet's just cracked open his blood.
He's not alive anymore.
He seems to be dead.
Seems fully dead.
Vegapunk.
Why are you doing this?
Slide.
And here we go.
It's Stella.
I mean, it's not Stella.
It's York.
York.
It's the foodie.
You know what?
Yeah.
Okay.
So she's doing she's the trader because she wants to be a celestial dragon and you know,
it kind of make.
Okay.
I guess she I wonder if like they offered it to her like they'd make her a celestial
dragon if she did this, but it makes sense because she's gluttonous.
And like the thing about being a celestial dragon is you just get anything you want.
You're just a spoiled piece of shit.
She's like, I want that.
She fits the bill, I guess.
Yeah.
For the mindset.
She just wants to eat and play video games.
Just just like that guy, Luffy punched.
She wants to be that guy.
You know, this is this is this is yet another time where Sanji's cooking could save the
for her sense.
You could make her a big sandwich and then she would eat and be like, ah, you know what?
I don't need to be a celestial dragon.
You know what?
I want to join your crew and eat your food.
This is fine.
Actually.
Yeah.
True.
Hey.
Okay.
So why did he not know that she was doing this?
Doesn't he know it?
Doesn't he know everything she knows?
I get.
Well, as we were saying last time.
There must be some way.
I was.
I was talking about like how it could be shaka before he got shot like two weeks ago.
Yeah.
And they don't seem to have like a connected hive mind.
They seem to be able to transfer data through the big brain, the big egg.
So in what sense is this Vega punk at all?
Because this is the person who poops all of Vega Punks poop.
Yeah.
And eats all of the food, I guess.
I guess.
But here's one thing.
Here's one thing I don't get.
I'm pretty sure Stella, I mean York was the one who was turned into stone and blown to pieces earlier.
What?
Like in the last chapter?
No, no, no.
A few chapters ago when they first meet Hancock.
Let me find the chapter.
But like it was Lilith and it was Usok.
Yeah.
And half of Franky.
And York was there.
What?
York got turned to stone and smashed and then they fell down off the bridge.
And I'm just going to check that that is the person that that happened to.
All right.
Because I can't think of who else it was.
Yeah, show me that.
That seems weird.
And I'm like, okay, if that was the case, let me just find it first.
1075.
When do we find it?
They're walking around.
Yeah.
So York is in 1075.
She is with Franky, Lilith, Usok, and they find Pythagoras's head.
He's just walking around.
And then yes, here we go.
I guess for spoiler reasons, I'll DM it to you.
Go for it.
But yeah, this page, she gets turned.
This is York.
She gets turned into stone.
Huh.
Yeah, she did.
And then in that chapter, I just I'll link the chapter, I guess.
In that chapter, Boa Hancock uses her BMU to explode everything.
But I guess we don't see.
Let me look at this.
Do we see her turned into rubble?
Into rubble, rubble, rubble, rubble.
Okay.
See York.
She's saying she's yawning, walking around.
And then I didn't order, Edison, order you to hold your horses earlier.
You should really still be waiting out there, even though you're so cute.
Hmm.
Turns to stone.
And then she's kicked, kicked to the side.
See what I thought was that she blew her up and killed him.
Oh yeah, she kicks to the side.
Yeah, I don't see her being killed or exploded.
She blows up the bridge and they all fall down.
So I guess it's not like a problem.
It's just that we don't, we may have assumed that she blew up York during that.
But she didn't.
York is still up there, made a stone.
I got it.
Hancock turned her back out of stone and then jumped down to fight everyone as York left
to kill Shaka.
I did not think that being turned to stone was like a real, the last time we were going
to see York or anything like that.
So.
I mean, I read that situation as York being killed and I thought, oh shit, they're going
to start killing these mega punk characters.
That's interesting.
They're semi disposable as characters.
At no point have I ever been under the impression that like being turned to stone by Hancock
is like you're dead.
Well, no, no, neither do I, but like I thought that she exploded her afterwards.
Oh, true.
Oh yeah.
I guess I didn't.
I guess I just wasn't paying attention.
No, I don't know.
I didn't think they were going to.
I didn't think they'd be killing these guys off with like, nah.
But what happened to little Pythagoras?
Well, she stepped on his head.
What's that explosion?
Yeah, that I don't know.
I guess she just made an explosion.
She may have done an explosion in between panels.
Yeah, I think she just did an explosion.
She crushed Pythagoras, did an explosion.
I guess the idea being that she was exploding Usopp and Lilith and maybe Frankie killing
them behind her.
But I mean, I'm sure they're not actually dead.
Yeah, we didn't see them explode.
So I don't really think any, I mean, some of these guys might die.
Maybe Shaka's really dead.
I don't know.
I feel like Shaka could be dead.
Yeah, yeah, shot through the head.
And what do we need all these vagabunks for anyway?
Yeah, the idea they were all going to join the straw hats together.
There's a lot of characters.
Wait a minute.
Do you think one of these vagabunks is going to join the straw hats?
Well, I thought the idea was vagabunk was going to travel with the straw hats to get
that information that he has.
Yeah, but that's not the same as joining the straw hats.
Well, no, I don't think anyone's going to join the straw hats from this.
Although they're going to travel with them.
I mean, you say that and I agree, but at the same time that gets me thinking like,
what if this whole thing plays out and like most of these vagabunks end up dead,
but like one of them stays alive and they just become a new crew member
and they're the crew scientist.
Well, I guess the Frankie's already the crew scientist.
He's the engineer.
He can build stuff.
He is a good vagabunk.
Honestly, honestly, I could see that.
I could see that.
I could see that maybe happening.
Maybe like they all die except Lilith and then Lilith just joins or something
and just is a permanent member or something like that.
It doesn't sound that crazy.
Yeah, it could be.
Lilith is cute and it is the one of I mean, a lot of one piece ladies are very cute
in the same way that they could easily add to the Nami Rubin.
Cute girls on the straw hat crew thing gets all the fans going.
Fans love it.
The fans love it when there's a cute girl on screen.
I sure do.
What if we got Pythagoras?
What if we got little ball Pythagoras who joins the crew?
I actually would.
Yeah, that's pretty cute.
Little Pythagoras.
That's different.
I don't see it just because these vagabunks,
I think they're going to stay with vagabunk.
However, along he remains relevant to the straw hats, pirates.
I'm imagining now like this plays out that like maybe Stella dies
and most of the other vagabunks die and maybe there's just one left
and he joins the crew.
I think that sounds plausible.
And it's like, hey guys, technically vagabunk.
Certainly they will travel with the straw hats to escape.
Oh, I mean, yeah, certainly they'll travel with vagabunk.
Yeah, certainly they'll leave with a vagabunk.
Joining the crew, it doesn't mean so much as it used to
because like a carrot was with the crew for so long
and she ended up leaving.
Yamato could have joined the crew, but he was like,
I'm just going to stay in one of for a little while
and they've got all those allies.
They've got those frenemies.
They've got people out in the sea doing their own thing.
The crew itself, I think, is quite good at where it is.
Yeah.
I think we're getting nearer to the end than to the beginning now.
I foresee a scenario in which maybe at least one of these vagabunks
become like a permanent fixture on the ship for however,
as they make their final journey to Raftel or whatever.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, even Jinbei felt like a bit of a weird addition
because he already had a crew and he had to say goodbye to them
to join the Straw Hat.
Yeah.
And it was just sort of weird.
Yeah, he already had a good crew and they were cool.
He could have been one of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet.
He could have been a responsible ally.
That's what I would have assumed he would do, but I guess that's...
But he joined the crew because I think there was expectations.
I don't even think that was...
They've got to have a helmsman give.
I don't...
A ship without a helmsman.
That always felt like an excuse to give him a reason to join
because he didn't have a lot of other reasons to join.
Other than that, he's...
It's not like he was at rock bottom.
Other than that, he's their friend.
And they like him.
Yeah, and he's a strong guy and he wants to help them.
He has his own crew.
That's the thing that's meaning...
The fact that he has his own crew means they have to invent a role
that he has to do on the Straw Hat ship, which was always a bit funny.
Yeah, it's dumb.
And I think the expectation that the Straw Hat crew grows over time.
I'm just racist and I just don't think that we should mix crew.
I just don't think we should mix racist and crew, okay?
I wanted him to join us just a big fish.
Humans only.
I think that would have been fine.
And Chopper counts because he ate the human.
He's like strong.
What?
Did you not hear what I said?
I was rambling.
Oh, I just said I wanted him to join us as a big fish
and I think that would have been fine.
He just needed to be a strong guy on the crew.
And now he's like an addition to their intimidation factor.
And he can do all of the things that require swimming
because nobody can really do that except Zoro and Sandy.
Yeah, Jimi.
Yeah, true.
But like the idea that the Straw Hat crew grows in member
is it's sort of.
It's gotten to capacity, I think for the amount of screen time
you can give to each one of them.
I don't think there's enough.
I feel like if you weren't there by the time skip,
it's like that was the crew.
The crew that got separated at the time skip
and then reassembled and got back together two years later.
Like that's the crew.
Jimi is also here now and that's cool.
But but come on.
Yeah, come on.
It's one of those things because it's like the way they joined
the crew earlier was like more emotional and more serious
because they were so small in number.
They needed everyone they could get.
And it's not even about like needing them.
It's just sort of the characters they had
really needed the Straw Hat Pirates.
Yeah, Jimi didn't need the Straw Hats.
Like Brooke, his crew was dead and he finally has.
He's the most recent one.
He has such a sad story of like sailing on this boat for whoever,
who knows how long living as a skeleton because of a devil fruit he ate.
Yeah.
And all of his crew is dead and he's just he hasn't met anyone in a long time.
Yeah, they rescued him from a real good thing.
And his shadow was, yeah, they got his shadow back for him
and they were friends and Luffy was just asking,
you want to come with us?
He was like, oh my God, a crew?
Oh, I'd love to.
It was like, it's so cute.
And that, you know, it's the same with everyone.
Pretty much, yeah.
They're all like crying at the chance to join the Straw Hat Zoro.
Zoro's like, yeah, fucking whatever.
I mean, Zoro's the first one.
When it's him and Luffy, it's just like, yeah, let's team up.
Cool.
All right, let's go.
Let's team up.
I mean, he smirks and he makes the same.
He's like, well, if I'm going to be the strongest swordsman,
the only one I can serve under is the Pirate King.
So you better, you better become that, I guess.
All right, cool.
Let's go.
Yeah.
And that's very Zoro.
And then things like.
How fucked up would it be if Zoro like wept tears
and he's like, finally a family?
Yeah.
Yeah, it doesn't have to be a big emotional thing,
but the thing is they made it such a big deal
that Jim Bay was joining the crew as well.
Jim Bay did get emotional.
Sure.
Whatever.
I think it's, it just, it wouldn't have made sense
if Zoro didn't have any reason to leave whatever group he was in.
Zoro was by himself.
Yeah.
So it's like, sure, sure.
Sanji left his kitchen because he wanted to find all blue
and he's very emotional about that.
And Robin had our whole thing where she.
She was in Baroque Works.
She joined because she wasn't going to stay with Baroque Works.
Baroque Works, she was a double agent for them.
She's trying to learn about the pony glyphs and stuff.
And then later, you know, she, she sort of,
her past catches up to her and it's like a whole thing to get her back.
It's like, you're a friend of ours.
And it's like, oh my God.
Oh, thanks guys.
Thanks guys for saving me.
And then Usopp had the whole thing where he joined just to see the world.
And then he forged in fire.
They're strong bound in, in Watcher 7.
When he was, he was going to leave because they were going to get rid of the ship
because it was no longer.
I'm getting chills.
I'm getting chills just thinking about it.
Oh, what a battle.
What, what a battle.
And God, what a seven.
Annie's Lobby is the coolest.
I love it so much.
It's my favorite arc.
Annie's Lobby is the, no, I'm thinking of Impel Down.
Water 7 is Frankie and Puffing Tom and the big going Mary.
What happened to Annie's, what happened to Annie's Lobby?
They saved Niko Robin from Niko's computer.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right, of course.
And then the, the Zabusta call was activated by accident by Spandam
because he's an idiot.
Right, right.
Wait, which one is Spandam's the guy with like half a face, right?
Yeah, he didn't used to have half a face, but now he does.
He's been punched and kicked so much.
Oh, good for him.
And he was.
That's character development.
Real, real busted.
Is he like friends with Kobe now?
No, I'm thinking of, I'm thinking of acting.
You're thinking of Helmapo.
I'm thinking of Helmapo.
Yeah, I am.
Who's Axe Hand Morgan's son, right?
Am I?
Yes.
He's still out there.
I hope he comes back.
Yeah, we saw him.
He finds the one piece.
In some like, in some like intro panel.
I remember there's like one, remember, remember Axe Hand Morgan?
Boy, that guy should, that guy should seem like a big deal back in the day.
Huh, weird.
Yeah.
Anyway, let's get back to the grand line.
And like, yeah.
So they're all characters who had nowhere to go except the straw hats.
And, you know, straw hats is something they needed.
Jim Bae just sees Luffy as like, he's the future pirate king.
Yeah.
But also, I gotta be their Helmsman.
I just gotta.
Is he there as like an envoy from the fishmen to like serve under the pirate king as like
a show of unity between races?
Is that the idea?
I don't think that's got anything to do with it.
It's just, it's just personal like loyalty to Luffy.
He sees Luffy as the person who will liberate the world and save and be the coolest guy
ever.
It's probably true.
And so he wants to help him in his quest and he will join his crew.
Okay.
I mean, that's all reasonable enough.
It's not the worst thing ever.
It's all makes enough sense, I guess.
Yeah.
It would make more sense if he didn't have a crew of his own.
We've been, we've said this before.
It seems more reasonable that he would become part of the grand fleet, but you know, he would
be, you know, a very, a very honored, very honored and esteemed member of the grand fleet
of the straw hats and, you know, part of their personal envoy to the fishmen would have made
perfect sense.
But we could do this too, I guess.
Sure.
Leave your crew, Jinbe.
I guess in the sense that some pirates, Jinbe's old crew are going to be part of the grand
fleet for Luffy, ultimately.
I mean, I guess we see, I guess this is kind of how like, like whitebeard's crew is all
the same.
I'm probably supposed to imagine that all the people in Whitebeard's crew, they were either,
they probably used to belong to their own teams or maybe they were even captains of
their own fleets or ships before and like, still to a certain extent, like they command
loyalty among those other ships that like, are not maybe technically part of Whitebeard's
fleet, but because they have loyalty to the captain that is like Whitebeard's guy.
Yeah.
See.
They have a connection there.
See, that would be cool.
Like if it's Luffy is so influential now that captains of fleets can just join him if he
asks them to.
But that's the thing.
You don't think he, did he ask Jinbe to join?
He did, right?
Kind of don't remember the specifics.
I don't think it was, I don't think it was clear enough.
I think it was like, I'll join you, but I just got to be like five or six arcs later.
He said he had to do something and then if he succeeded in his mission, he would join
their crew and then he finally got back from that and he's like, well, time to complete
that arc.
It looks like I'm joining now.
It was Big Mom.
He has like ties to Big Mom and that was the whole cake, I think, after that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
And then he appeared in Wano and he's like, I'm going to join, did you miss me?
I'm sorry, Jinbe just doesn't feel like part of the family.
Not yet.
Never.
Never have a filthy fish man.
I'll never call one brother.
But like with all that said, with all that said, who like, I think the idea that a vagabunk,
the last remaining vagabunk will stay with a straw hat crew because there's nowhere else
to go.
That means that makes a lot of sense in the same way that someone like Brooke is like,
my old crew is gone.
Yeah.
I've lost everything else.
And now, yeah, you've brought me out of what was a terrible fate.
And yeah, if all the vagabunks got killed, except for Pythagoras and Pagoras, like now
what do I do?
Oh, no, I'm just a little robot with all the knowledge in the universe.
Like, well, why don't you come to Raftel with us?
Yay.
Hooray.
I will.
Thank you, father.
I'd love that.
I'd love the little guy to be part of it.
I will call you prime unit Luffy.
You are now my central processing system.
You command my servos.
He can talk with Frankie about robotics.
He could be like, Frankie could build him a new body.
Yes.
It's Pythagoras.
I said Lilith before, but no, I wanted to be Pythagoras.
Lilith would be like just another humanoid, like normal person on the ship.
And she'll be in like, oh, like a swimsuit edition of the straw hats, like a wallpaper.
I defaulted to Lilith because she was the first one they met and because she's got the,
she's got probably the most aesthetic design.
She's the coolest looking.
She's got the most riz.
Yes, she's got the riz, but Pythagoras is the cutest and the strongest.
And he's my boy.
It sucks that the Triter is York, because I liked York.
I wanted York to join the crew in a way.
I had no.
She's huge.
Huge women on the ship.
Well, we could get Atlas, I guess.
I mean, I guess.
Oh, I guess.
Yeah.
Atlas is cool.
I like Atlas.
Oh, York is fine.
I mean, she's weird in an off-putting way.
And I guess I appreciate that, but I don't know if I want her like around all the time.
You know what I mean?
That's what I tell.
That's, I'm going to, next time I'm on Tinder, I'm going to message and say, hey, don't send
me a nude.
I don't appreciate not seeing any nudes.
Thank you for understanding.
By the way, you know, I appreciate you.
You're weird in an off-putting way.
And I do appreciate that, and they're going to, they're going to get so hot.
They're going to be so hot for that.
I just don't want you around all the time.
I appreciate how weird and an off-putting way you are.
And I love that about you, but I don't really want you around all the time.
And I'll say, yeah, that's true.
That is, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're not, you're not the first, but you're not the first guy to tell me that,
honestly.
I don't know what the next word is.
Pretty good chapter, yeah.
Didn't, didn't guess it would be York, but it's cool.
It's the person you least suspect.
I appreciate, they don't even, they don't even have to explain it.
I understand immediately, oh, she's tempted because she's a glutton.
And the celestial dragons live a life of gluttony and decadence.
And that tempted her to betray them.
I get it.
And I like that.
Perfect.
Yeah.
So like, like in this, in this one panel here, like, uh, Vegapunk saying, what are you saying?
You know the Marishwa, uh, you know what Marishwa is like from that visit a long time ago?
How could you want to be one of them after witnessing how vile we are?
And she just laughs and it's just like, ha ha, I like that though.
You made me like that father.
Yeah.
You sound like Shaka.
He, he also had that opinion, but it's dumb.
I like it.
I'm confused a little bit.
Not confused.
I'm just curious.
What is she going to do next?
Is she going to kill Vegapunk with a bullet to the head right here?
I'm assuming she's not going to because he's tied up.
But what, what, what do they need him for?
What does she need him?
So she, I mean, would she die if that happened?
Wouldn't she die because she's like attached to his brain?
I guess we could go back and check how they describe who, who all these people are and
what their deal is.
They share information through the brain, right?
And if Vegapunk dies, I'm pretty sure the brain dies because it's his brain.
So I feel like, I mean, maybe if he died, the brain would die, but like she is an independent.
So she would just persist as her own person with no like link to the brain.
That might be true.
It really just, it really just feels like these are not Vegapunk in any meaningful sense
that he just made seven guys who have a link to his brain.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm going, I'm going back to the chapters.
I forgot about the mechanized sea beasts.
Yeah.
The sea beasts who are just all over the place and the little, the giant robot in the ocean.
I think the Marines are going to have a big battle with them.
I wonder how that's going to play out.
I feel like Kizaru is like not even going to have to fucking think, think about it.
I mean, there's a lot of them.
I mean, maybe, yeah, maybe he probably can't defend the entire fleet.
Hmm, I mean, that's, yeah, that is, that is, I mean, I suppose that is an issue.
Might delay them.
But I mean, you know, the merry go got through it.
I'm sure, I'm sure the grand fleet can get through it.
A thousand sunny.
Sorry.
Yeah.
A thousand sunny.
Okay.
I'm reading.
Look at this good old fashioned egghead early chapters.
Where are you?
You posting them?
I'm reading through it.
I'm trying to find the part where they first describe what's the deal with all these guards.
Oh, it's the panel with the law turning into a woman because he's fighting Blackbeard
at the same time.
Wait.
Why did he?
Why did that turn him into a woman?
Do you remember?
There was a panel where.
Was that in turn?
He did the girl disease or whatever.
Oh, no, I totally forgot about that.
So it wasn't Ivankov.
It wasn't Ivankov.
Yeah, Blackbeard and Law are fighting.
Was that was?
Currently.
They're fighting now?
God damn.
Well, not now.
I mean, as I'm reading, this is happening during the egghead.
Okay.
So not that long ago.
Not that long ago.
I forgot about that.
It sort of rings a bell here.
I don't think we see.
Oh, and Pudding is in Blackbeard's ship.
No way.
No, Pudding is with Mary.
No, Pudding is not with Big News Morgan.
No, that's that's an alabaster girl.
Vivi is with Big News Morgan.
Yeah, Pudding is.
Is Pudding with Blackbeard?
In Blackbeard's brig, I guess.
She's in prison.
As a prisoner.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So I guess I guess at the end of the whole cake, a Caesar was leaving Blackbeard was
there to scoop up Pudding for some reason.
Hmm.
It seemed a valuable hostage.
Now, law is around.
Man, this is all very important.
I kind of agree.
Yeah, it's really important.
These are important people.
Got that giant robot.
He's so fucking cool.
I want him to do something.
Oh, the one that was like inactive because they couldn't activate him because they don't
have the power to power him.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
The one that finds them.
You see, remember how big he is?
He's holding their ship right now in this image I'm posting.
Is that Pythagoras?
No, no.
It's a different guy.
It's the guy that Lilith was riding inside.
Who?
Lilith.
Oh.
When they got there to the water, there was like a giant metal shark.
Oh, yeah.
And then there was a giant robot.
She was in a big thing.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then there was a giant robot.
And she came out and she said, I'm Dr. Vegapunk.
And they were like, huh, I didn't know Vegapunk was a woman.
They didn't know yet.
Right.
There's a giant monster down there.
Giant monsters down there.
It's like some kind of futuristic city.
It's exactly like that.
It's kind of like what if the city was the future.
She said the world of tomorrow is here, but actually it's the world of yesterday.
Oh, I forgot.
I forgot that the fucking swamp, swamp fruit freak with the long tongue is still on the
ship, on the storm ship.
He is.
I also forgot that.
He's a stowaway.
So they don't know, they don't know, they don't know that he's there or did they agree
to let him come with them?
Well, I don't think they agreed.
I think he's just.
He's just there.
I completely forgot about that.
It's funny, like One Piece has so many like stories that are happening in the background
that you have to really pay attention to understand what is going on.
Oh, wow.
This is a wiki moment.
I'd go to the wikis, see what he's doing.
Yeah, I assume he's just in a barrel or something.
He's such a fucking loser.
I love him.
He's such a scoundrel and a bastard, but he has no.
He has no successes in life.
He's constantly losing to the straw hats and he's just sort of like hiding.
I mean, he should be so powerful.
He's like a he's like a grand line pirate.
He's like he's not one of the he's not one of the new generation, but he's like a really
strong pirate with a freaking logia fruit.
But he's just this.
Yeah.
This worthless like hides in a barrel.
What is his name?
I don't remember his name.
Yeah.
I can't remember.
When does he say I'm on chapter chapters this 1065 explaining it there in the lab.
They see those Jim base Seraphim and they fight him for a second.
They fight him for a whole chapter, basically, and then Edison is there.
Oh, yeah, Pythagoras had a big butt and Edison was the guy who always was small.
Well, Edison is like normal size, right?
And Pythagoras is the little guy who has the little head.
He's just the little head.
No, Pythagoras is the little guy.
No, the Pythagoras is the normal size guy who can detach his head and Edison is the
little guy.
But Pythagoras is head is smaller than Edison.
No, look at.
You're going to have to show you're going to have to show me what you're talking about.
I'm looking at the introductions.
That's yeah.
Oh, okay, but Pythagoras, I mean, yeah, when Pythagoras is head comes out of his body.
It's like about the same size as Edison's head, but he just has no body.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean, that's about what I thought.
I mean, what's the difference?
It seems to me that there's like the only difference between Pythagoras and Edison is
just that Pythagoras has a big body that he can jump in and out of.
Guess I'd have to read it again.
I guess they embody a different trait, but I couldn't tell you what that trait is.
It's really funny that it's really funny that the one that betrayed them isn't the one that
embodies evil.
Yes.
I love that.
That's a classic switcheroo.
I mean, yeah, it was like, of course, it wasn't going to be that.
Of course, it's too obvious.
God, there's so many chapters.
I can't remember where anything is.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for when they explain how they work.
I think Vegapunk is going to talk about his fruit and he's going to say,
like how the stuff works.
Okay.
You met a little girl who called herself Vegapunk, right?
That's one of my clones.
There are six on the island.
Each one is a facet of myself and an expert in their own field, key field of study.
You get my full personality if you combine them, but they can get six times the work done apart.
You get my full personality if you combine them, huh?
So they're not literally him.
They're like a separated, like if he was one clone and then he separated it into six people.
He took his personality and then split it into six aspects and then he just built a body for each of them.
Oh, this is interesting.
Each of them connects to punk records once a day to synchronize on memories and knowledge.
Once a day.
And they say tomorrow things are going to go down.
So the next time they synchronize, I guess.
Well, they would already know.
They would all already know the stuff that Vegapunk has found out about the void century.
Yes.
Which means that Vegapunk Stella could die and then one of these other ones could join the crew instead.
Well, I don't know about that because all the information is stored in the brain, so I feel like they would lose it.
But if they've got in their mind from the brain, they might retain it.
Yeah, the brain might stop working, but if they have the info, they just can't connect to the brain anymore because the user is dead.
I think, I want to say probably, yeah, they only connect once a day.
They don't need the brain to continue to live.
So Shaka's been shot in the head.
Atlas is fine.
Edison, I don't remember.
Pythagoras was stepped on.
Edison was, like, beat up, but it's not clear if he's, like, dead.
And Lilith is turned to stone.
Pythagoras seemingly crushed and exploded?
Yes.
York turned to stone, but fine and evil.
Yeah.
You all share the same brain?
Think of it, just think of it as sharing the same library.
If I could let everyone in the world connect to my brain, all of humanity would have access to my knowledge.
Based.
Based, Vegapon.
Yeah, it would be cool if you could get the void sentry information just broadcasted to the entire world.
But I think Egghead will be destroyed before that can happen.
I'm sad to say.
I kind of agree.
It seems, I think.
The Marines that they're sending, there's too many of them, I think, that they can fight them and win.
They have to run away.
And so Egghead will be commandeered.
Egghead seems like it's like, wow, this could solve all the world's problems.
So I think it's probably going to be destroyed.
And they're going to be like, oh, no, we only have one shred of hope left.
And it's, you know, what's stored in Pythagoras' little robot mind.
Little lemon.
Little lemon head, yeah.
Yeah, that's what I think.
We're going to have to regrow a new...
What's the brain fruit called?
I mean, this is a brain brain fruit, but I don't remember what it's called in Japanese.
Brain brain brain brain.
What does it call it?
I can't remember.
A nominoming.
Nominoming.
Right.
Right, right.
We're going to have to wait for a new nominoming to grow.
Oh, he says that's because I ate the nominominominomin...
No, we no me no me no me no me no me no me no me.
Nice.
Loll, Loll.
Great.
That's one piece.
Good chapter.
I love one piece.
It's better than ever.
You wanna go to voicemails?
Yes, I hope there's not that many.
There is a normal amount.
All right, well let's get into it.
Uh, I see the first one is called the Ben St. Cancellation Hour from Quickman at EXE 3, 2, 1, go.
Heh, what's up y'all? Quickman.exe here. I have taken a break from parrying off Ben's attacks to jack into the PCP voicemails and cancel him.
Without further ado, here are three problematic quotes by Ben St.
A person of color, haven't seen those before.
This little boy ought to relieve my boredom.
And finally, with a cameo from Rusting Robot, Ben, that's a child.
She's a high schooler, it's fine.
Truly deplorable, how does this man have a platform?
Bye bye Ben, see you in Mega Man Network Transmission.
First of all, who among us has not at one point in their life seen a person of color for the first time?
Second of all...
It's been late for you Ben.
We're all born knowing nothing.
How'd you go so far?
I got so far, I got so close.
And was the second one?
Child?
Little boy?
This boy should relieve my boredom?
Yeah, because they're full of joy and enthusiasm and lust for life.
Not lust for anything else though.
And then the third one...
High schoolers can be 18, and that means it's fine.
It's fine.
Next one is called Twizzlers at PrinceIsolation at Twitter.com.
3, 2, 1, go.
I was listening back to one of Ben's recent battle network streams,
and he was talking about trying to make licorice,
and then he mentioned trying to make something like Twizzlers.
And I just have to say that recently, you know,
Twizzlers aren't that common where I live in the Netherlands.
And I just found them a few weeks ago at like a local candy store,
I suppose, and I bought some.
And I tried them.
And my girlfriend at the time also tried them.
And we both agreed that they are disgusting.
What is...
What?
They taste like nothing.
They taste like eating rubber.
Like what the fuck is that?
I thought that American food was supposed to be like completely annihilated with sugar,
but it tastes like nothing.
I genuinely threw it away because it would literally be just as fun chewing on cardboard.
Anyways, yeah, thoughts.
Is it different here?
Like what the fuck happened?
I know licorice.
Like I'm not a big licorice guy either way,
but like Dutch people like licorice,
but it's like fucking black.
Like it's dark and it's strong.
It tastes strong at least.
Twizzlers taste like nothing.
What the fuck was up with that?
I mean, I think if you're going for...
I would prefer the cherry Twizzlers to the black licorice Twizzlers.
I like black licorice, but like Twizzlers are not real licorice,
so I would try the cherry ones, I guess.
I like how rubbery and chewy they are.
I like it.
And I like that their flavor is mild.
I like them.
I like turkey Twizzlers.
You ever heard of those?
Oh, the like twisty fried things?
The twisty fried meat product.
Yeah, I've never had one, but I would definitely eat one.
I would definitely eat one.
No question.
I want one.
I want them.
They look cool.
Next one is called...
Do you like black licorice kid?
I think I've had it when I was young
and I thought it was a bit weird.
And I haven't re-approached it,
but I didn't hate it.
I hate it.
I think I could eat one.
Some people find it disgusting,
and I think those people are disgusting.
I'm a big licorice friend myself.
It's sort of like a mint, not mint flavored,
but like the sensation of like a spicy sort of peppermint.
It's a little bit...
It's a little...
Yeah, it's a little bit minty, so sort of.
It's like an herbal...
When you drink birch beer,
birch beer tastes like partially like mint
and partially like licorice, and I love it.
Yeah, it's kind of like an herbal, somewhat minty.
Yeah, I think that's a fair comparison.
It's kind of root beer.
It's not a sugar.
It's a herbal sort of...
It's a spice.
Spicy.
It's a little bit of a spice flavor.
You ever go to an Indian restaurant
and they have the little bowl of like the little brightly colored
like little candy beads that are like really small?
No, I haven't heard of those.
Oh, those are candy coated fennel seeds,
and those have a similar flavor.
I really like licorice, and I'm a big fan of it,
and a lot of people think it's gross, and I think it's fucking stupid.
I've liked it ever since I was a little kid.
I need another licorice to remember what it was like.
I wouldn't recommend black Twizzlers.
I mean, they're okay.
They're not the best.
I would get it like...
Sometimes you can get it like thicker pieces, like cut into chunks.
Sometimes they have sort of like a six holes, like honeycomb sort of shape.
I like those ones.
They're kind of chewy.
I think those ones are pretty good.
Anyway.
I remember there being like a licorice selection.
Licorice all sorts.
There's a company called Getz that makes caramel candy,
especially cow tails.
They also make a licorice version of like the creams.
It's like chewable black licorice with like a creamy sugar interior,
and I really like those.
All right.
I remember these licorice all sorts.
I think I kind of like some of these.
Oh, I've never had these.
I've never had these.
No, maybe I have.
These look familiar.
You ever had Good and Plenty's?
Nope.
Well, I maybe.
I don't remember.
Let me find a picture.
Good and Plenty's are a little...
I just remember this little mascot with the pink face.
He's a licorice boy.
Good and Plenty's are a licorice, a candy coated licorice candy.
They're like M&M's, but instead of chocolate,
they have licorice in them,
and most people would be very upset about that.
Here's a picture.
Good and Plenty's.
That looks like diarrhea pills.
You know, I see it.
It looks like Pepto-Bismol, yeah.
Okay.
Next one is called Old Lady Appreciation Hour.
Three, two, one, go.
Honestly, that one lady in the Battle Network II game,
who went to America to sell her chopsticks
that she made with her deceased husband.
And she keeps talking about it.
I feel so much emotion for this old Japanese woman.
There's an NPC on the plane.
When the plane is going through, it's a tribulation,
and you can talk to her, and she tells you that she came...
I mean, she went from electopia to netopia,
because in electopia,
she and her husband had a business making chopsticks,
and electopia is basically Japan,
and netopia is basically America.
So she was basically like,
oh, me and my husband always had a dream of going global
with our chopsticks business,
so I'm going to netopia to try and sell my chopsticks in America
and start a branch location,
and my husband's spirit is watching over me or whatever.
And it's pretty sad, but it's even sadder when you realize
it's not going to take off,
because Americans don't eat with chopsticks.
This business venture was doomed from the start.
It's a cruel joke by putting her in that game.
Just be happy that you had a successful chopsticks
making business in your home country.
That's more than most people think.
She's doing it for him, Ben.
She should do it for herself.
He's gone. He doesn't need a successful business anymore.
I'm looking at these liquorice all sorts.
I see the one that's like a black tube with white in the middle.
Is that sugar stuff in the middle,
or is that just more gummy stuff?
I remember having these when I was like six.
I want to try these.
I want to try these. They look awesome.
They're so weird. They're really strange looking,
but I want them.
What if you had color in your liquorice?
Weird little colorful pieces of liquorice.
Did liquorice originate from the UK?
I feel like it's probably one of those things.
I think it's Victorian in origin.
I know. I think it's older than that.
I mean, I think it's probably like a traditional...
I mean, maybe not in its modern chewable gummy candy form,
but as a flavoring for stuff, I think people have probably used it.
Oh, yeah, it's a plant.
Yeah, it's a plant derivative.
Where's it from? Where's the history?
They're just telling me the different types.
Yeah, Wikipedia is just talking about...
Oh, okay, there's a different article for liquorice confectionary.
Yeah, I'm looking at that, but...
Yeah, health effects.
Hmm.
German Nordic liquorice characteristic contains ammonium chloride
instead of sodium chloride?
Prominently so in salty liquorice.
Hmm, what?
Sounds good.
I've been finding...
It's miraculous how, like, adding salt,
when food tastes bad,
a lot of the time it just needs salt and then tastes good.
Just eats salt.
I saw a TikTok recently where the lady was saying
when people complain that food is under-seasoned,
most seasonings are just dehydrated vegetables that are powdered.
If people say your food is under-seasoned,
it usually just means there's not enough salt,
or else that it's missing something like an acid,
like lemon juice or vinegar.
And I think she's right.
Most foods taste good when they have the appropriate amount of salt in them.
I'm thinking back on...
It's true.
I'm thinking back on my dad's meatloaf.
My dad, he would make meatloaf all the time,
and sometimes it wouldn't be that good,
and I would think that the problem was that it was over-seasoned,
like it was too herbal, like he had too much seasoning in it.
And I think, thinking back, that it just could have used more salt.
I think that would have fixed a lot of what I didn't like about it.
I like at the bottom of this licorice confectionary Wikipedia article,
it says,
see also licorice international and list of unusual deaths.
Okay.
It's very related.
When I looked on YouTube for how to make licorice,
a lot of the recipes, they called for condensed milk,
and I'm like, what the fuck?
That's not candy thing.
Maybe for some kind of homemade shit.
But yeah, I'm looking here on the licorice confectionary page,
and it says the ingredients are licorice extract,
sugar, and some kind of binder like starch flour,
gum arabic, gelatin, beeswax, molasses.
So I don't know why, but when you look on YouTube,
every recipe you find involves condensed milk.
And I don't think that does not give you a product like you would buy in a store.
Not even close.
It can't.
It can't possible.
Okay, let's move on.
Yeah, yeah, let's move on.
Okay, next one is an image, but it's legal, bro.
It's 100% legal.
It is right.
It is.
You can really listen to it right now.
Yo, legal.
We got to legalize the procrastinator's podcast.
I'm running for president.
If I'm elected president, I will legalize the procrastinator's podcast.
Free them.
I don't know what else to say about this other than true.
It is legal, bro.
Next one is an album.
Oh, it's just one image.
Yo, Mr. Ben, where's my money, bitch?
No homework for the win.
Jesse, shut the fuck up, libtard.
Don't fuck with an April bully.
What does April boy mean?
Is that...
Oh, is this Jesse?
Oh, it's Jesse.
Right, okay, okay.
Jesse, shut the fuck up, libtard.
This is exactly how it goes.
Don't fuck with an April boy.
My giant egg head.
It's just like one piece.
Maybe that's why I like the current arc so much.
This is just funny.
When wait.
I'm laughing.
I'm having a good time.
Next is...
It's another image.
It's a Vinnie's doodle.
Sorry, no comic gear, but working on it now.
It's fine.
Hey, don't stress about it.
What's going on here?
This is unfinished.
You can see Uwupiti's uncovered physique.
Why did you put green on green like this?
I guess because this is green.
Is that my skeleton?
If you scroll down, it's different versions of the same image.
Yeah, I mean the last one is the clearest.
Yeah, last color correction.
This one's the easiest to see.
These look cool.
I think that Uwupiti's got the brain floating inside of it.
I like the Caliborn skull.
Is that Caliborn? It does look like Caliborn.
It just reminds me of him because of the green skull and the red.
It looks very much like Caliborn.
I don't know if it's...
I don't know what it's...
Yeah, whose skeleton is that?
And also, who is that sultry looking...
Slime.
Slime away down at the bottom there.
It's just a little guy.
They look like they're having a...
A good old time.
Cool.
I like my big green eyes.
Thanks, Vinny.
Thumbs up.
Next one is called,
Give Giving a Sex Ed Class, question mark.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm not gay. I'm not gay.
What is this from? I remember it, but I...
Oh, jeez.
I know exactly what it's from.
Oh, is it from the lecture?
No.
I'm gonna win.
What did I say?
I'm not bad and I'm not gay.
Everyone laughs at you and then you cracking up,
I'm gonna win.
Everyone laughs even louder.
What's it from? I forgot.
You want me to tell you?
Yeah.
It's Ten Paces and Draw.
Oh.
The contestant interviews.
What makes you think
you're gonna win this contest?
I'm not...
I don't suck and I'm not bad
and I'm not gay.
Okay.
Ten Paces and Draw.
I worked really hard editing that thing.
I should, but I find myself so embarrassing.
Oh, I was talking to the audience more,
but I mean...
I worked really hard to edit that thing.
That thing needed...
If only there was like
any B-roll at all.
It really needed B-roll.
But I made do with what I had
and I think it came out pretty...
I think it came out pretty fun.
Someone was talking about it in my discord recently.
That was a pretty good video.
I worked really hard on that thing
making it watchable and it kind of
came out pretty good.
That line is like really,
really funny.
Okay, next one is called...
I'm glad everyone laughs.
It's funny because
when you're saying...
You can hear people laughing afterwards.
Because you're saying it
and you're laughing at yourself
as you say it.
And then because you're laughing at yourself,
everyone else starts laughing at what you're saying
and then it makes you laugh even more.
And then you continue,
but then the fact that you're laughing more
makes it even funnier
and then everyone else laughs even more.
It's really good.
Next one is called...
Hi, I'm Ben St.
I'm going to kill all my friends.
Also from
Send Paces and Drop.
Yes.
True.
Next one is called...
3, 2, 1, go.
Let's see the music.
It's pretty fucked up if you ask me.
I don't like this show.
The patient is bad.
And there's just not a...
The patient is just really bad
and I don't like it.
It's funny shit.
That was funny shit.
The patient is bad
and the patient is bad.
What more do you want?
Next one is called...
Doodle Ben at Work.
I didn't plot the space when I started.
LOL.
I'm a green little guy.
How about that?
I think that's supposed to be you.
How about that indeed LOL?
LOL.
It's a really long sword.
It's really long.
Really short legs.
Pretty short legs.
I thought those were knees cut off, but now those are your boots.
Yeah.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Sick.
Okay, next one is called...
Cal, 3, 2, 1, go.
Some general advice.
I'm looking to move out
into a shared
accommodation like you do.
I just want to know
is generally a good thing to do.
I've got this weird fear
of looking at stuff getting stolen by my
roommates.
Yeah, like is it...
Is it really horrible?
Or do you recommend it?
Thanks.
I haven't really had any major problems
with people that I've
moved in with, honestly.
It's been fine.
Yeah, I mean, if you think about
their perspective, why would you
as a person go and snoop around
someone else's stuff and risk getting caught?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I feel like most people
just want to be left alone.
You're not going to have
those sorts of interactions
like that.
That you don't shit where you eat.
And if you fuck around with your
roommate's stuff and you like steal
their shit or you go through their shit
or you violate their boundaries in some way,
you're fucking with someone
who you now have to live with
and it's really bad
and you're going to ruin your own life.
Most people understand that.
I have never had any trouble
with anyone that I've moved in with.
Some of my other roommates
had trouble with people
who moved
in to their spare room.
People would move into a spare room
and then they'd be doing weird shit in there
or they'd be an asshole
or they'd make a mess in the kitchen or something.
Worst you're going to have to deal with
is people don't clean up after themselves.
Don't do the dishes.
And that can be really annoying,
for sure.
But that's the worst I've experienced.
So the worst part,
there's not really likely
to have to fight someone
to get your video games back
or whatever.
Yeah, I've never had
anything like that happen
with someone who just happens
to be living in the same house as me.
So, I mean, yeah.
Buy a katana, though,
to protect yourself.
Oh, I mentioned that
the break-in.
Well, okay,
I don't know if I mentioned this before,
but a guy who lives here
found a giant
combat knife
in our couch cushions.
Somebody's giant
sword knife
was in our couch cushions.
I think it probably belongs to another guy
that lives here but has just been away
for a while.
I think he might have just left it in the couch.
And it's in like a case.
It has a case that it's clipped into.
So,
the junkie or whatever that broke in
and did whip its on my couch,
there was a huge sword knife
on the table in that room
and it was not moved.
So, you know what? That's reassuring.
He could have had a weapon.
He could have stolen
the giant sword, but instead
he stole half of a rice cooker.
And that tells me that his priorities
are
in order and I don't have to be
afraid of him.
So, that's nice.
Next one is
They'll have like a thing on the
on the
like submit your
PDF and there's a box checking
like checked, like
a used slave labor.
If you click yes, much cheaper.
You get much better returns.
I'll check it.
Less money.
Less money for you.
Hey, slaves need jobs too.
Click.
It would be wrong to take that slave's job away.
The blacks are black.
We're all trying to make it in our little world.
Well, I guess there's no
ethical consumption under capitalism anyway.
It crushes
the blacks, even though it costs
more, but that's the price.
I mean, you like what you like.
If you if you enjoy that process,
that's not a problem.
It's just that's just how it is.
I mean, I do to a degree.
I do to a degree.
I mean, you know, I don't know.
I feel like I don't know.
I feel like they don't want to think about that.
I would say you're just not on that
Sigma grain set.
You're not gristling in the grind.
I'm not on that Sigma grain set.
I'm off the grind set.
That went on too long.
Oh, a little too long.
I thought they were going to have another funny edit
at the end.
After the crush is the blacks part,
what more did it need?
You needed it.
If you were going to continue on,
you should have added an even more
out of context bad sounding thing.
For me to say, yes, that's correct.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
I get it.
It's funny. I was talking about slavery
and then I was talking about blacks.
Little did they know I was talking about blacks
in the context of printing.
Out of context, it sure does sound
like I'm talking about race.
Oh, great.
Because we've been going for six hours.
Oh, boy. Well, let's get him back.
I wish we weren't going for six hours.
We need to start cutting these shorter.
Yeah, this went on too long.
Cheesy was talking too much.
We let Cheesy run away with the conversation.
I hate that guy.
I don't know how to say, all right, shut up.
Yeah.
I don't know how to do that.
We need to reign Cheesy
and we need to wrangle him a little better.
Lesson learned.
Next time,
or no, next one is called
like 18 exclamation points.
Three, two, one, go.
It's too loud.
Is the two piece signature chicken
with the regular side and the biscuit
or the three piece tenders
regular side and the biscuit
better at Popeyes?
I don't need Popeyes.
I've got this.
There's sort of no Popeyes in the UK.
It's more of like a southern
restaurant, I think.
There might be one around here.
The only difference is one is two piece
signature chicken.
Two pieces tenders.
And I'm like proof eyes.
So I really really going to need
you to go to Popeyes right now.
I don't even know.
Both of those and tell me which one is
more food or better.
Listen, man, I can't help you.
Let me just run your own.
Let me just look real quick if there's any Popeyes.
Oh, there is. There actually is one.
There's actually two
in Boston.
Boston's big city.
Well, there's actually three.
Well, that one's kind of up north
north of the river in Everett.
So that's like not really.
Okay, there's actually three.
Okay, but I mean,
there's a lot of restaurants around here.
I've never been to one.
I went to one Popeyes one time
in like Virginia and I thought it was good.
But I couldn't tell you shit
about what's on the menu.
Give and take cancellation hour
I'm the evil shadow
dragon Medeus
here to cancel
give and take.
Fuck. Once give and take
said
the more
people that are dead
the better
and once
give and take said
I don't want to kill
I just want to kill
I know
I think that what this tells us is that
give and take is a lot less
cancelable things than Ben Saint
but
she went to bed late
last night because she played a lot
of fire emblem so
maybe that's something
cancel her
yes cancel her
Did I did I mention that on
Friday I streamed for 10 hours
my stream went on for 10 hours and it was
horrible.
Somebody mentioned that in my chat
that you streamed for 10 hours
I hated it and upon hearing that
I realized that I didn't want to suffer the same
fate so I only had like a 4 hour stream
No I don't recommend it at all and you know what's really
there was a part
where I accidentally fucked up making a save state
and I like destroyed
I heard that yes I lost my save state
I saved at the wrong time I saved at
a game over and I had to restart
the in game save and I had not made
the in game save in a long time I literally
lost like 2 hours of progress it was
I was so angry
and the game okay the other thing
about it is that the game
I mostly
have liked battle network 2 more than 1
but I'm at a point in the
game where it's near the end and it sucks
dog shit it's literally it's worse than
the first one actually because
I've gotten to a point where
there's no more new maps
they just you log in and it's near
the end and they just are like oh shit
there's ice all over the net now there's a bunch
of different colors of ice and
to break the ice you have to get these colored
things and it's
they literally just make you run
through one dungeon to the end to get the thing
and then you come out and you go through one other
dungeon to unlock the thing and then you got to
back through the first dungeon to get another thing
and then you go through the second dungeon
and then you just send
you back and forth like go find this guy he's over
there in this place you've already been oh
go tell the guy that sent you to find me
that I'm fine
and then you get there and there's like oh cool well now that I know
that he's fine here's an item go bring it to him
and
I streamed for 10 hours and I literally
like I barely unlocked
any new territory it was all just back
and forth to places I'd already been before
it's so bad and then
on top of that this fucking save state
which is my that part's my fault
but um the save state thing happened
and I lost sounds
like a terrible it was not I had a fun stream
but maybe someone enjoyed me getting
angry about it
silver lining
yeah my fire emblem stream
the map
was very difficult and I had to restart
like a bunch of times and
after the four hours was over I had only
completed one map
hmm so I wasn't
prepared to do another one but that was
that was still enjoyable in itself
because sometimes fire emblem is just
really tough and like the strategy
has to evolve with your
many losses and you're like okay
so I know that they're gonna do this and their
reinforcement is gonna appear here so I need
to do this and that and I need to be lucky
that was the only really
annoying thing was that sometimes the enemies
would crit me and kill me in one hit and I just had
to be lucky before I could get
into a good position where I could like
control the situation that control the pace
of the fight that's kind of what I don't
really like about I used to really
like tactical like grid based
RPGs like that and I think one of the reasons
that I don't play them anymore I mean first of
all I just kind of stop playing
a lot of games in general but I don't really feel
like getting back into them because they're just really slow
and they just take really long about
one battle in one of those games is like a really
long engagement but I guess
that's fine it's tactical
and you're making decisions the whole time
I think it's better than running
back and forth and redoing content
in a pointless wild goose
to change sort of situation like what you're going through
I mean what I'm going through is complete
horseshit so yeah maybe
yeah probably
I do not want to sound like I'm defending
what battle network 2
is making me do
the worst
the worst possible thing to pad out the
the length so if you
ever heard like oh this game takes this many
hours and this other game takes that many
hours now you know
how much padding the second game has
there's a part where
you break some
ice and then
you find
I don't even remember
you finally get the ice to break a thing open
and you reach this NPC you couldn't reach before
just on a map that you've been to before
you have to go back to this map and go all the way
through it and find this NPC and the NPC
is like
yeah to break that other color ice
you need a heat
program look for a heat
program and
the only
okay what you what it turns out you have to
do the heat
program
belongs to this
you have to go
you just have to think of this on your own there's no hints about it
it's a grill
like an electric grill
at a campground
contains the heat program you have to go there
talk to a program that you just have to
figure this out you have to go inside
back into the grill talk to the program inside
the grill he'll tell you where
his boss went
that has the heat program so you go and you
you gotta go through another map that you've been to before
find the boss there
and then come back to the grill
and talk to him and he's like oh thanks
you found my boss well here here's the program you're looking for
it you just
you just have to think oh there was a grill
at the campground
I wonder if that's where the heat program and
I mean I'm sorry a grill is just such an innocuous
thing I wouldn't think like
when I heard that hint I had absolutely no clue
at all I had no inkling
at all like oh
where would something hot be like yeah I guess
when I say it out loud it sounds obvious
but like almost no attention at all
was drawn to the presence of this grill it's just
a thing that would be at a campground
yeah it's
I mean I haven't played the games I don't know
how
familiar you would have become with the campground
was there anything
leading you in that
or did you just have to remember it on your own
I had been to the campground before
and there is a cut there is a little bit
when you get there like your friends
like you have to gather up some ingredients
to cook some food on the grill
but I mean
I don't know maybe somebody else might have figured out
for me it was like
it doesn't seem remarkable at all
that there's a grill at a campground
that screamed to me like
oh this is a thing
where I would obtain fire
if I needed some in the future
I don't know
I didn't put it together
maybe somebody would have
but it seems like really obtuse and like
I didn't like it
I didn't like it they could have hinted at me
a little bit better than just being like
a heat program
okay good luck
next one
is called the munchie minute
3, 2, 1, go
okay so at first I thought it was just a joke
but now with it being mentioned
on Ben's stream as well as
on Ben's tweets
chat GPT just keeps mentioning it
so
is the munchie minute real
is that something that existed
I mean I know it wasn't
about Ben Shapiro owning
a liberal snowman
but
was there a munchie minute
is that a thing that existed on the PCP
no
I know it's funny
okay I google munchie minute
and there's a youtube link
and the video is called Monday's munchie minute
my top 4 nursing
shirt tips
it's like a breastfeeding
munchie
this channel with 25 subscribers
a video
with 50 views posted 5 years ago
munchie middlevert mama
what the fuck
and it's like breastfeeding
tips
I guess it's good that you can
get tips if you need them
my top 4 nursing
shirt tips I don't know what specifically
you would need tips about that
on but maybe
everything's gonna be a top 5
sure I mean
I don't take issue with the top 5 format
but what do you need tips on
nursing
first of all I didn't know there were special shirts for it
and I don't know what tips you would need other than
get one
but you know what I'm not gonna watch the video
so I have no
room to criticize next one is called
but my heckin copywriter
you know so
sorry that got me
3 2 1 go
the best part
what was that last bit
I couldn't understand a single word
maybe it's cause my headphones
it's very close to my ears
his point was
the important part of making blue rays
is reminding people
that Trixie can't make blue rays
and digi heads don't get to have anything good in life
and I agree
thank you very much
this guy gets it
next one is called
it's an image
here we go
speaking of gas giants
and other planets
have y'all played outer wilds
listen I know I was wrong
I'm not sorry
yellow
receipts $500
are there blue rays on this chart there should be
yeah this is me
yeah this is the Ben St.
stream experience
I know I was wrong
but here's why I shouldn't upon
this is about the receipts
I know I was wrong
he actually
just went back to net square
back to net square
this is the NPC that told me
oh that guy who was just here
oh you gotta go to that other place to find him
that keymaker you've been looking for
for seven hours
he actually just went back to net square
you just missed him
fem saint stinks really good
please don't block me Ben
it is a nice drawing Prince is really good at drawing
it's just for funnies ha ha ha
I'll probably read
I retweeted Prince's stream drawings
the last one because I think they're really good
so I'm going to tweet this one also
it's free advertisement
watch my streams everybody
um
stcomics twitch.tv
slash stcomics
how many subs am I up to
6,000
oh yeah
yeah
line go up
guess who just got
another little Ben head in the jar
oh is it one going to splash out no no
they're staying in there
there's oh can you see the jar
I actually I have OBS open right now
just so I can see
a little notification whenever I get one
wait let me show you let me show you the jar
I know the jar
but let me show you the current status of my jar
oh
check this out
it's a lot of heads
it's got a bunch of heavy coins that were
been in there for a while
and then there's like 30 40 heads
someone's going to drop
a nice a nice heavy a nice heavy
10 nice heavy thousand bits
on top of there and they're all going to go
I think
that's what's going to happen
next one is called
oh it's a vocaru link
it's a vocaru
it's what you call
a vocaru
I don't know why I posted it there
it was unnecessary
okay
three two one
three two one go
so
hey what's up
how's it going
this is going to be some dumb shit
I'm two episodes late
so I don't have anything thought coach will say
but I need to up here
yeah yeah true
yeah true
you don't want to leave that
you don't want to leave that mental real estate unoccupied
I'm just chewing
hey thanks for the call
buster hey thanks buddy
yeah good to hear from you
okay well
well guess what it's over
okay that's the end
that's the podcast
it's really long over six hours
you I know who you are
are you happy now
big episode for you
idiot
die
I would like some of my sunday back
I don't think I want to do another six hour
plus this long episode
yeah it's too long
we need to wrangle cheesy
it's not just cheesy
I think we just sometimes go on for too long
you know it's easy
it's easy to blame cheesy
so I will
okay
that's the end of the episode
check out my twitch st comics
whatever
become a patron for the ova
for the bonus ova commentary
which we will have out soon
I guess we gotta do that
okay goodbye