Hello everyone, it's The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint, this is Gibbontake.
Hello, I'm still a little sick, so I might be coffin.
Nice. We've got a guest today. We've got Deadly Comics, whose animations many of you, I feel like, might have seen around for a pretty long time now. Hi, Deadly.
Whoa, hello. How did I get here?
I don't know.
How did you get into our review?
Everything that happened in the past several weeks is just a complete blank, and I don't know why you're here or who you are. Why don't you explain who you are?
I should have thought this far ahead, at least.
It's okay.
You have a YouTube channel where you do really cute and high production animations with little furries. Little furry people.
And they're great.
I think the earliest stuff of yours I ever saw was some MLP stuff back in the pony days. I think you did a Scootaloo, right? There was one of, like, Scootaloo in her bedroom. Am I?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I remember that one from back in the day.
I remember the fucking Gibbontake GIF you did of me jumping up and down.
Oh, yeah. I forgot about that.
Eleazar, put that on screen. Find it.
Find it. I forgot where it is. I'm sure I've saved it somewhere.
Must have it somewhere.
Some DVD or something. I don't know. I really liked your character design. I just had to animate that hair flopping around.
Yeah, yeah.
You know how it is.
I do.
Most recently, I remember, I saw the one that you did where the golf ball goes down the golf hole and the fish is down there and says things.
Right? That was you, right?
Yeah, yeah.
And I also saw, a little before that, I caught, it was the one with Twilight and Mordecai on the road singing that Muppet song.
Right? Yeah.
That one was awesome. By the way, that one got, I mean, I know you didn't write the song, but like, that song, from watching that animation, that song got stuck.
It actually still, I still think about it because I saw that animation and that song is really catchy.
And I'll just say, while I'm gushing about it, I'll say the bit where, the bit where they say Cabot and they hold up the cheese is really funny.
I watched that over and over again.
The little one frame, with the little like one frame moment where Twilight holds up the Cabot cheese.
And then there's like, they just really fast look at the camera like, and then just move on.
That, that, that's not in the original, that's not in the original, that's not a joke the Muppets make.
That was you, so good job.
I'm glad you liked the one original part of the video.
Thanks, yep, the only one.
Uh, there's like, there's a mixed media too, because it was like, it was like a, it was like a real like, like toy set, right?
It was like a physical like car set and they animated the characters in it, right?
Yeah, I got, um, I thought it would be, where did that start?
I thought it would be really funny if Twilight Sparkle had a car, so I looked it up and she did.
It does have a car, a toy car.
So I thought it, Hasbro made one?
Yeah, like a little RC controlled car.
Let's, let me find it, lol.
I don't know, I thought it would be funny if she like had one in the show to promote the toy or something.
They should, they should have made an episode, they should have made like a drag racing episode.
That would have been great.
Um, Gabe, did you see that one? The one I'm talking about?
I, I, I must have, because I'm subscribed, I guess I forgot exactly what it was.
The most recent one with the, with the, uh, the little fish and, uh, I can't remember.
Oh no, I'm so bad.
Oh, deadlycomics.com.
Now websites have dated, I'm sorry.
Uh, two days ago, Grand Tour, that's the one.
I just saw that, that came out.
Oh, there's a new one?
Yeah, it's so.
I haven't seen it.
There's a new one.
Oh, it told me.
It got the little, little furry people.
And they're on like a, a cool like tree house.
And I don't know who these characters are.
I don't know if there's like a continuity that I've been like missing.
What's, uh, what's, what's up?
What's up with all your animations, huh?
What's, what's going on?
Yeah, what's the deal with that?
What's the deal with that?
I'll tell ya, I'll tell ya.
Uh, those cartoons is called cool times.
That's why I'm focusing on to like have a, try to have like more of a
narrative ongoing thing.
Um, so it's like all these characters live together in this like
repurposed lighthouse on a mysterious island.
And they're like all part of some sort of, some sort of company.
But it's unclear exactly what the company does.
It's kind of like, uh, like as a kid pretending to play business,
like pretending to have a company, uh, it's kind of like that.
But what if that happened, but, you know, it was on a bigger scale.
It just like kept going somehow.
Yeah.
That was the kind of loose idea behind having all these characters
together and just doing weird, uh, stupid things.
Uh, yeah.
I'm seeing cool times in vivo those two years ago where she's on the
little piano.
Is this, is this, is this the car?
I'm posting the car.
Ask the car.
Nice.
Very nice.
It's like little voice clips when you press the button.
Holy shit.
Little car noises.
Yeah, I'm scrolling through now and I see the moon right along.
I'm like, yes, I did watch that.
This is a whole year ago.
Animation takes so long.
That's fucked up.
I was going to do the whole song, but like, by the time I got to a point,
like the meme was already long dead.
Was it, was it like a meme at the time?
Was it when I started it?
It was.
And then.
With Twilight and Mordecai singing two halves of a song.
Yeah.
With Emma's paint.
Like, like somebody drew them singing a song.
Oh, the airplanes and then the airplanes in the night sky are like shooting stars.
I think the thing that Elon and Grimes had as their Twitter pfp.
I did.
Yeah.
I think so.
Unless everyone's lying to me.
I look, I don't know.
Look, I don't know anymore.
I don't know.
I mean.
Okay.
But okay.
But not that song.
Not specifically that song was not a meme, but the Mordecai and Twilight was a meme.
It sprung from that post though.
Okay.
I'd never, I'd never heard that song before because I've never seen.
Is it the great, the great Muppet Capers?
Is that the one it's from?
That's from the Muppet movie.
Like the original is this cover is from like a tribute album kind of thing.
Yeah.
It's, I know it's, I know it's a cover, but it's by like, it's by like My Chemical Romance
or Green Day or something.
Alkaline Trio.
Which is a band I don't know anything about besides that one song.
Yeah.
Shit.
What was that?
I was going to say something.
Cover for me.
Duh.
Oh wait.
I get it.
I'm going to see.
I'll see the new one.
You went to uni or college for animation I assume based on, based on a few of your like
short films that are out here.
Right.
Those were like school films.
Yeah.
I went to school of visual arts in New York.
How was that?
And that was a time.
Oh, I never know what to say.
It was a time.
One of the colleges of all time.
Did it, do you think it like hypercharged your animation skills?
I think, I'd say so.
Just like having the structure to have time to make stuff is good.
And having people to show it to and get feedback from.
That's good.
That stuff's good.
Yeah.
I went to animation school and I, I really enjoyed the, the sort of atmosphere of everybody
doing the same specific niche thing.
So there's always like, ah, talking about it, like getting a project together.
Because I always have big projects, big ideas, but in a place like that is actually possible
to make stuff.
And the stuff you made is like really cool.
Like really like avant-garde out there, but also cutesy.
I love your films too.
Spider One is a fave, is absolutely a fave.
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah, I'm looking, I'm looking through.
Okay.
There's actually, I'm realizing, I'm realizing how many of your animations I have not seen
actually as I'm scrolling through this list.
It's not like there's a lot.
So it wouldn't take any time to catch up.
Well, it feels like there's a lot.
I mean, I'm still scrolling.
I remember Rabbit Runner.
I remember when that came out.
Oh yeah.
That was, I think I got like all my weeb shit out into one video.
So I never had to put anime stuff in the cartoon again.
Hey, I see you just released a plush.
I tried to.
It did not reach its funding goal.
Oh, really?
No.
I know the feeling.
Well, I shouldn't have said anything.
I had fun making the video though.
Which one was that?
The Confined Bee?
No, it's What Has Science Done.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that's so sad.
There's such a cute little guy.
Is the campaign over?
Yeah.
So there was like an earlier campaign, which was successful for like a deadly comics plush.
But then the company makeshift decided to like re-do a bunch of plushes, but with like
cyborg parts for Cyber Monday.
Oh.
Which is kind of.
That's why.
Yeah.
It's, I mean, an interesting choice for your character here.
I mean, it doesn't make much sense.
No.
Which is probably why not enough people bought the thing.
It's a bit.
And also like people who bought the plush, you know, they only need to buy another one
just because this has some gold bits on it.
Definitely.
So it's like, nah, I'm not.
Wait, so did the company just tell you like, hey, so we're, we were gonna, you wanted to
make this plush, but like we're here to tell you that like, no, we won't make the one you
wanted to make.
We're making one with gold robot parts on it.
And there's nothing you can do about it.
I'm a little confused.
Oh, well, no, they made the first plush.
There was another plush campaign, which was successful.
Okay.
And then they like did this other ones so they could like reuse the, the schematics of
the plush to like do another run of them, but with gold bits.
Good.
I see.
Can I still buy the plush?
Oh, no.
I don't know if I can.
Like the original.
Oh, no, that's long gone.
Dang it.
It's a cute little character.
I like him.
Hey, I'm glad you think so.
Oh my God, you did a review.
You did a movie review.
Not really.
Deadly comics reviews.
The cat returns.
It's 30 seconds long.
Wait, it gives in it.
What?
What the fuck?
I just hovered over the thumbnail and I saw you from years ago.
The cat returns.
Oh, I am in that.
What the fuck?
I think you commented on it.
That's a six year old video.
Yeah.
It's, I'm just, I'm just watching it.
I'm just watching this review.
We're 10, we're 10 seconds into the 32nd review and the review hasn't started yet.
What the fuck?
I think the video.
20 seconds and I still don't know what you thought of the movie.
I think it's clear from how it's edited when I thought of the movie.
Okay, I think you might have thought of this good shit.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, now I know.
Okay.
Oh, no, and then YouTube recommended me a Night Mind video afterwards.
I hate Night Mind.
What's wrong with Night Mind?
I don't like his voice.
No.
His voice is so fake.
It's the, and the competition is stiff.
The competition is stiff, but Night Mind has the fakest voice I've ever heard and it's disgusting.
It's sickening.
It's not.
It makes me want to grow up.
I met him in person and he talks like that in real life.
I don't care.
That doesn't change my opinion at all.
He's still faking it, even if it's not, even if it's real.
Following the classic PlayStation style, there's a company released a stupid video game in 2002.
I love stupid video games.
It made a million dollars, but was the game haunted?
No, but people on a forum said so.
What do you think about that, viewers?
I don't, he doesn't, no.
It's not natural.
Maybe he talks like that in person, but he's faking it.
Fuck you, Night Mind.
I hate you.
I'm there for the spooky video game, whatever.
Night Mind is just a poor man's Nightmare Masterclass, so there.
Wow.
Yeah.
Vicious.
All right.
You know who else I hate?
Unique Namosaurus.
I hate that guy.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
Well, we don't have to say anything else about that.
We don't need to do the hate.
You know what I hate?
People.
Specific people.
Let me just read you off a list.
Let me just read you off a list of people I'm mad at.
Okay, I won't.
Read your nice people list.
Read a list of good things you recommend in love.
I don't have one of those.
I really should have one of those.
I would recommend Daily Comics.
Whoa.
I'll check him out.
That's a furry shit, though.
Yeah.
It's weird.
It's perverse.
Unnatural.
Definitely.
It's almost as unnatural as Night Mind.
Who is a furry?
Is that true?
Wait, am I thinking of someone else?
No, I'm not.
Well, I wouldn't know.
How's everyone's week been?
Well, good.
What have you been up to?
I wrote down some notes, but I genuinely couldn't think of anything.
Okay.
I have a lot of question marks.
No, I tried to write notes.
Like, what happened since last week?
I'm like, oh, shit.
Well, I finished a commission.
That's it.
Hooray.
Okay.
I guess it's getting sparklier around here.
I did talk about getting the decorations up.
There's still things to put up that sparkly lights around.
It snowed.
I don't know if I talked about that.
It snowed and I made a snow person.
It snowed here too.
Just a little bit.
Is that your first snow of the year?
Yeah.
Don't always get snow during Christmas time.
Sometimes it waits until February and then it snows.
But we got some.
Deadly, where do you live?
Are you American?
Yep, I'm in Brooklyn.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
It's snow here yet.
You're not even far from me.
You're like a two-hour drive from me.
Oh, yeah?
Two or three.
I'm in Boston.
Oh, cool.
Very nice.
Did you get snow recently?
No.
There's snow in Boston, though.
Yeah, a little bit.
Just one night and then it was mostly melted by the next day.
So that was cool, I guess.
Didn't have to shovel.
I had a family.
My family did their Christmas Eve get together early.
We did it yesterday.
That was all right.
That was kind of fun.
A bunch of my cousins have kids now.
So there were a bunch of little kids running around.
And honestly, I appreciated it because it was sort of something to distract everyone.
They didn't have to spend too long talking about what you've been up to, where you live
now, what's your job.
How much closer are you to the grave?
Are you ready to put a down payment on a house yet?
A bunch of my cousins have become landlords, which is like, I don't know what to say about
that.
Yeah.
Like big complex landlords or like a little two-family house landlord?
So whatever.
I'm not going to be like, well, I think you should get the gulag, even though it would
be really funny.
But I don't say that.
I'm just like, hmm, whatever.
It's just funny to hear them be like, yeah, I had a tenant who was a veteran who was running
like an illegal gunsmithing business out of my basement.
And then his girlfriend and him broke up and she rescinded all their like gun licenses.
And so the cops came and kicked my door down.
It's like, yeah, okay.
It's a pretty good story.
I know a guy who's a landlord and he talks about teaching his son to be a landlord because
that's the only way to make money.
What's there to teach?
But it was just interesting because I said, yeah, I'm not going to be a landlord.
But it was just interesting because it's like, yeah, I guess like there's so many people
who like going into the landlording.
Like if I think everybody should be a landlord, but you know, if they're our own building.
Hey, yeah, you know, we've got all these empty houses and all these homeless people.
We should make, they shouldn't be allowed to live in them, but we should make those homeless
people own those houses.
We should give them the houses not to live in, but to rent so they can have an income.
They can rent those houses to other people that can afford to live in them.
What do we think?
Make the homeless into landlords.
This is like one problem with another.
I'll workshop it.
This is like when they brought in the weasels to deal with all the snakes and then they
just had a weasel infestation.
And then they brought in the foxes to deal with the weasels and then they brought the
bears to deal with the foxes.
And then they brought the gorillas to deal with the bears.
And the gorillas reigned supreme.
No.
Then they brought the rhinoceroses.
Yes.
And they were bigger.
Then they brought in the blue whales.
Oh, we saw a video of, you know, those like giant, I don't know if it's a whale shark,
but they're that big fish that feed by like they go up to the surface of the water and
they open their mouths and they just like...
Yeah, they slurp up.
Yeah.
I saw a video of like a bunch of like people were just like swimming in like the beach and
like they have like a little like rowboat.
And this fucking like one of those came up and it just started like sucking water up.
Like it might have sucked someone into it.
It looks so fucking scary.
Yeah.
Like it's like...
It started screaming.
It's like, yeah, I would scream.
It looks so like powerful.
It's like the real version of like being scared that the swimming pool filter is going to
suck you up and destroy you.
Although it could actually happen.
Although it wasn't as big as I thought.
Like looking at it, I'm not sure if it actually, if that one actually could have like fully
swallowed a person.
It seemed like it could have.
It was hard to tell.
It's like the size of a couch its mouth.
If not, you get stuck and then drown anyways.
So it's still a little scary.
I wonder if, I wonder if it tried to suck you up because it's not meant to eat something
human size.
I wonder if like a medium sized one, it would just kind of like sort of like cough if it
tried to suck you up.
It would probably spit you out.
Yeah.
Like realistic.
Oh shit.
It's a rock.
I got it.
I can't swallow that.
I hope that's what would happen.
God.
I don't know where the rock is.
Rocks don't float.
Yeah.
Maybe a piece of driftwood.
Maybe, maybe very, very small rock.
Only very small rocks float.
That's a, that's a Monty Python joke.
Okay.
The spongy rock.
One of those, one of those volcanic rocks.
It'd be, it'd be one of those rocks with the funny jellyfish on it from Subnautica that
make the rocks float.
You know that?
I haven't played Subnautica.
Oh my God.
It's, if you are scared of the ocean, it's the perfect way to die.
Yeah.
The perfect way.
I think I would be very scared.
I've seen Subnautica and it's like, I know that like most of the creatures are not that
scary looking, but it's still, I think it would, I feel like it would be scary.
It's the fear of the unknown.
The sound design is like very impressive.
And if you've got like headphones in, you don't know what's going to kill you or what
can kill you, but you'll hear noises and you don't know what they do, what they mean.
And, you know, when the sun goes down, the sea is completely pitch black unless you have
a torch.
So you are, you are very scared all the time.
Something like that.
Until you aren't.
Something looming out of the, out of the depths of the ocean beneath me coming up to like
get me is like, is one of the scariest things that I can think of.
That's why it was very, it was really scary.
Oh, in Outer Wilds with the freaking, the anglerfish coming out of the mists and the
bramble.
That's just scary.
But anyway, why did it, why was I talking about that?
Why did it bring up that fish?
Oh, you brought up the fish.
Yeah, scary fish.
That video.
Scary fish.
That's it.
I was talking to one of my cousins.
One of my cousins did ask me a little bit about, a couple of people asked me how I've
been working on and I mentioned, because you know, I've been talking about finishing that
slime and punishment book for years now and I told them, yeah, I still haven't finished
it.
And some of them told me, some of them asked me what else I've been doing and I mentioned
the video.
Nobody asked me what the video was.
So I didn't have to explain it.
It was an eight hour long video explaining the history of Mega Man.
So that was a relief.
But one cousin did ask me like, how does YouTube work?
How do you make money off that?
And I explained like how ad revenue works.
And then he walked away and I was like, that was a nightmare.
That was the worst conversation I've ever had.
I'm glad nobody else asked me about it.
That's it.
Hell yeah.
Glad.
I missed out on a, I don't know if I talked about this last time, but I missed out on a
family get together because I was sick.
Oh.
I mean, I did want to see people, but apparently it was really awkward.
So I'm glad I didn't.
Why was it awkward?
I don't know.
It was just one of those, it was like a, it was grandpa's birthday dinner.
He's 90.
And so they were going to go to a restaurant to get nice food and talk.
But my dad has like an electric car and where they were going didn't really have that many
charging stations.
So it was kind of a nightmare trying to find a charging station so they could charge so
they could come back.
And it was freezing cold and it was snowing and apparently the restaurant food sucked.
And it was just sort of like one of those weird long tables where if you're sitting at
the wrong end, you currently talk to anybody.
So it was like, dang, dodged a bullet, I guess.
I did throw up though.
So, you know, I was not feeling great, but I think I would have felt worse.
If I had gone.
I missed, I missed my, last year I missed Christmas because of, because I got the coronavirus.
So, not this year.
Not this year, unless I got it then and now I'll miss Christmas because of it.
Because some one of my stupid relatives had it.
Lol.
I don't know.
That's all I got to say about that.
That's it.
How's your week been, Deadly?
Yeah, Deadly.
What's up?
This whole time I'm trying to think about what the heck happened and I can't remember.
What do you spend your days doing?
What's a typical week look like?
A typical week?
Let's see.
I work from home so I don't ever leave.
I work for a studio doing storyboard revisions.
Oh.
Which is fun.
Which is good and fun.
I didn't know you did that.
Yeah.
I draw little characters, fix little mistakes at acting and stuff.
I don't ever talk to people clearly.
Do you, do you mind if I ask like what studio or what your storyboards are for?
Yeah, sure.
It's a studio called Titmouse in New York.
Titmouse?
It's like, Titmouse.
Is it, is it family friendly?
Some of it.
It's a bird.
The Titmouse bird.
You don't know about the bird?
I've heard of it.
I've heard rumors.
It's a real thing.
Is it like Motor City?
They did, what else did they do?
Big mouth.
Yeah, they did big mouth.
Did you, did you work on big mouth?
I did not.
Good.
I don't like it.
Star Trek Lower Decks.
I've heard of Motor City.
Well, there's a lot of things on here.
Have you, have you worked on anything that we would have heard of?
Um, ever watched Ball Masters on Adult Swim?
No.
Just by the, um, the, um, Super Jail creator.
Oh.
And they also did some Super Jail, like early on.
But I interned on Ball Masters and then, uh, went through that, started storyboard revisionisting
on a show called Ducking Goose, which is like a preschool show on Apple TV.
And now I'm a revisionist on a show called Kiff that's coming to, uh, Disney Channel.
It's not out yet?
Not yet.
Hmm.
Okay.
This, this studio seems to be involved with a heck of a lot of shows.
It's very interesting.
I'm on their website right now.
I'm scrolling through this big thing.
I'm seeing, uh-
I got Neo-Yokio in here.
I'm seeing Ducking Goose books.
I assume this show is like based on the, oh no, it's the, I see it on YouTube.
Huh.
Well, that's very interesting.
Well, that's very impressive.
Look at you with your big studio job.
Yeah.
Well, well, well.
Look at you.
Big man coming on our podcast and flexing.
That is real job.
I'm a little, little cog in this big machine of animation.
That's right.
I've gotten like no say in the creative direction of shows.
So I'm not to blame if they're good or not.
Even though I think they are.
I absolve myself of all responsibility.
I'm lucky that I haven't had to work on something that I like don't care about at all.
And I know that's just a part of working in animation is that you're going to get jobs that you just don't like.
Yeah.
But you got to, you got to do your best, I guess.
You got to do it.
That's fair.
That's pretty neat.
That's pretty neat though.
Ball mat.
I've never heard of ball masters, but it kind of looks funny.
I don't know.
Kind of looks a little bit interesting.
I like the style.
It's very, it's very scratchy.
It's very like notebook doodly.
Yeah.
It's a little bit like mob psycho-ish.
Kind of.
A little bit.
I don't know if this was before or after that.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
We're good.
Let me tell you a story about my, let me tell you an embarrassing story that sucked for me.
It was just yesterday.
It was on my way home from my stupid family Christmas party.
There was a, there was this girl waiting at the bus stop.
And you know, I just asked her, I just asked like, hey, are you waiting for the 64?
And she just said, yeah.
And then she just, and then she just starts talking to me.
She just starts asking me like questions about like, you know, where are you going?
Do you live around here?
And I'm like, oh, okay.
And I just started answering.
I'm like, yeah, I live around here.
She's like, what do you do for work?
I'm like, oh, I'm a freelancer.
What do you do?
Do you go to school?
She was like a Turkish.
She was like a, she was from Turkey.
She was visiting America while she was learning English or something.
I was like, okay.
All right.
And she said, you know, she just likes to talk to people and like to like talk to
Americans practice English.
And I said, okay, cool.
Yeah.
It was nice.
And then so, you know, then what, what did you do to fumble this?
I killed her.
I buried her in the, she, she went under the bus.
I'm sorry.
She went under the wheels.
I couldn't save her.
No.
Well, she, where was it going?
Okay.
That's my bus comes.
And it's my bus.
And I'm like, okay.
So I go to get on and she is like, uh, uh, she seems like unsure.
And I'm like, is this your bus too?
And she, I don't remember what she said.
And I kind of just was like, well, okay.
And I, and I got on.
And then she also got on even though it wasn't her bus, I think.
And I was like, okay.
And I said, I hope this is going in the right direction.
And she said, yeah, it is.
Yeah, it is.
And I was like, okay.
Um, so I don't know, it was a short bus ride on the bus ride.
I was like, does this girl like me?
Is this, is she following me?
Is she interested?
And so I just asked her like, Hey, well, would you want to meet up sometime in the
future?
Would you want to meet for, I don't know, have a drink or have a coffee or something?
And she just kind of like laugh nervously.
Like she didn't give an answer to that.
And I said, okay.
Well, we don't have to do that.
Well, all right.
Nice, nice meeting you.
Uh, uh, you know, good luck with your studies.
And I got off the bus.
And I, I don't know.
Uh,
I think that's, that's not that embarrassing.
Yeah.
I guess, I guess I don't feel like I did anything particularly wrong, but I, I, I guess she
was just be, I guess she was just being friendly, which is like fine and cool.
But like, man, she should seem like she showed a lot of interest and she even got on a bus
with me that was not her bus.
And I was like, why would you just, why would you do that for a random stranger that you
were just practicing your English on?
I feel like I, I feel like I had reason.
I feel, you know what?
No, I was right.
I was right to ask, you know what was perfectly reasonable thing to do actually.
Maybe perfectly, perfectly sane, perfectly cogent response that I had to that situation
as a matter of fact.
Maybe in Turkey, that's just how they, they do things, you know, if you're talking to
someone, you can't stop talking, you got to talk forever.
Yeah.
You got to get on that wrong bus.
I, I guess we didn't even, we didn't even like say much on the bus.
I don't know why she did that.
She seemed to not, she seemed to not know what bus she was even waiting for.
What's your name?
Her name was like, it was like, it was, it was pronounced weird, it was like booze, booze
or something, booze, I had to, she like, you know, it has one of those like, are those
rhodic sounds that we don't say in English, you know what I mean?
You know what I fucking mean?
Um, I don't know, that was yesterday and, um, you know, what's, what's the point?
What's even the point of anything anymore?
You know?
You can't end every thought with what's the point of anything.
We'll see, we'll see about that.
You say that, but I'll prove you wrong.
But what is the point though, actually, no, stop, stop dodging the question.
I don't know.
Getting on the bus, going to your disc, deadly, deadly comics.
I'm glad you're here.
Why don't girls like me?
It sounds like, explain it to me.
She liked you enough to chat it up with you.
Maybe there was just something lost in translation.
I don't know.
It's not good enough.
I wasn't there.
I think it's good enough.
It's not good enough.
Thank you for your input, but it's not good enough.
You're wrong.
Okay.
Well, that was, all right.
You know what?
That was fine, actually.
Um, uh, well, just thought I'd share my one and only anecdote, um, up until yesterday.
Up until yesterday, I also have done nothing, uh, I pretty much, I pretty much wasted this
past week.
I know I said I had to work on that book and getting it done.
I, I like didn't.
I did that for like one day.
It's just, it's just, it's cold and I just, it's just too cold.
And the heating is off more often now because of like, uh, oil prices, Ukraine, specifically
the UK's like, stupid, uh, like not taxing of the billion dollar, like oil companies.
Just despite the fact that they're, they're making record profits right now and we have
our own oil we can get, uh, it, you know, the Russia's war in Ukraine should not be
affecting the price of stuff so much, but they're just letting it affect the price so
much, uh, so that people die in their millions.
That's, that's what they're doing.
They're making me too cold.
So I can't, I can't do my little drawings and it's, it's sad.
They're doing it specifically to prevent you from doing your little drawings and you
can't, you can't let them win.
I tried to draw a little drawing and I was just like, ooh, no, I can't, I can't have
my hand outside of my blanket holding a stylus.
Got to put it back in there.
Got to hide it in this blanket.
Speaking of, that's my week.
Speaking of blankets and being cold, I watched my dinner with Andre yesterday.
Well, yesterday, I split it between yesterday and the day before.
Because it just randomly came across my YouTube recommendations.
It was called your dinner with Andre.
It was the video.
It was on a channel with 600 subscribers.
It had like 150,000 views.
It's just called your dinner with Andre, but it's just an unedited upload of my
dinner with Andre.
Have you seen this film?
No, I have not.
You are you familiar, are you familiar with it?
Nope.
It's a, it's a Wallace, Sean and Andre Gregory.
And it's pretty much just them sitting down to dinner and, and they just talk for
like an hour and hour and a half.
And that's the movie.
And Andre or, uh-huh?
Is it just them talking as themselves?
Just them talking.
They're, they're, they're, no, they're, they're technically playing characters.
They're, they're, they're characters have their real names, but they are not playing
themselves.
Andre is playing a version of himself who had all these weird, like spiritual
awakening experiences in like the forests of Poland or whatever.
And he's describing to Wallace all these, uh, all these things.
Um, wall, wall is Sean, by the way, is the guy who, uh, played fizz, fizzig in, um,
the, uh, the princess bride.
Yeah.
I know him.
I don't know Andre.
Uh, yeah, I didn't know Andre from other stuff either.
I know him mostly from my dinner with Andre.
Um, you know, wall, wall is Sean's character in them.
I'm not sure if it's, if he's badly written or if he's written to be
infuriating, but he is like the worst conversationalists ever.
He just sits that he just listens to Andre explain to him like these most like
bizarre, like, uh, psychedelic experiences.
And that he's like, and then he's just like, and he'll just like smirk and
literally not say anything and then go back to eating his soup.
And then he'll be like, uh, so what happened next?
And like, that's, that's what he says.
Fuck you, wall.
So what happened?
There's a couple of times that he breaks in with his own, with his own like input,
but it literally takes like an hour into the movie before he replies with
anything other than, so what else did you do?
That's kind of like, I'm thinking about it, but it's, it feels like a
conversation couldn't hold an entire movie length.
But we talk for like hours on this podcast.
We talk, yeah.
Like conversations take a lot longer.
And then I'm thinking, wait a minute, how the fuck do they fit conversations
into movies normally with scenes?
Right.
How the hell do they do that?
You like, you can't, you can't put like a real
I think this is kind of like, I think there's, you know, last year I went on
this kick of watching movies that were just about people talking.
I asked people on Twitter for recommendations of movies where people
just talk and that's all that happens.
And I watched a bunch of them and most of them I liked.
And yeah, I think there's something that's very, that's very, uh, uh, very
artificial about like the way that like characters interact with each other in
just, in like normal movies, cause normal, normal movies, like nobody can just
have like a conversation with each other.
Because yeah, every scene has to be over in like a minute 30.
And that's just not real life.
Uh, I get the very cliffs notes.
It's very stilted.
Yeah.
It's very condensed and stilted and very like theatrical.
And that's why just like in real life, just like in real life, every
conversation that I has has to progress the plot or else what's the point, right?
You can't, you can't talk to a Turkish lady on the bus or the bus stop without
it leading to like, like a, you know, setting up for act two.
Why, why didn't it do nothing happen?
Yeah, this would be called a drop plot point.
This was in the film.
Yeah.
That was, you know, in reviewing, reviewing, uh, you know, Ben's life, uh,
release date, uh, 1988 to, uh, to, uh, nine to 2022.
Yeah.
That scene with Buzra on the bus, like total plot called a sack.
Nope.
Should have been, should have been cut from the final edit.
Wait, wait, I don't like the audience doesn't want their time wasted.
So, but think about what it says about Ben's character.
Yeah, no, it's character building.
It's like we're painting, you know, it's not about progressing the plot.
It's a character piece.
It's a character study of a pitiful waste of a man who's a waste of his life.
And he has nothing to offer society.
Right.
It's about, it's about establishing that.
It's about painting a picture for the audience.
You Philistine appreciate it.
Exactly.
What's your act three going to be, Ben?
Oh, God.
Well, I guess, I don't know.
We'll just, we'll just have to see.
Um, you know, anyway, I thought watching, watching my dinner with Andre, I was like,
they should do, I should, I should do what they did with the worst, the worst idea ever,
podcast or whatever it's called, where they watched, um, grownups to every week.
And then they commented on new things they noticed in grownups too.
What if we did that with my dinner with Andre?
We could call it my podcast with Andre.
Every week, you're just like, Hey, I noticed that like, it's weird how it's weird how Wally
just like casually brings up that story about the wait, like the woman, that woman who fell
out of her hospital bed and, and like became, became a, you know, paralyzed.
Like, wait, he, I didn't realize that was Andre's mom.
We, at the, at the first, I thought he was, he was talking about someone else's mom, but
then later he brings it up and he's talking about Andre's mom, plot hole, uh, uh, stuff
like that.
Um, sounds like a terrible idea.
It sounds too cyclical for me, like people talking about, people talking about people
having the same conversation, people having the same conversation, noticing things about
the same conversation over and over again.
I think, I kind of think the movie is ass.
I kind of think it's bad.
I kind of think that's not true.
It's not bad, but I do think that there's parts mostly Wally where he's speaking in
a way that does not sound to me like a real person talking.
It sounds scripted in a way that is like, okay, here's the part where we have him make
a point.
Here's the part where we have him push back on like, here, here, here's the part where
we have him expound a worldview that the audience has meant to shake their heads out and say,
ugh, disgusting, despicable.
You know, how dare, how dare he?
They should make a sequel called My Edibles with Andre.
They're both, they're both still alive.
They're both very old.
He should do some big weeds.
See if it's different.
That's the conversation I want to hear.
Let me call it like, like my, my, my blunt rotation with Andre.
My bong with Andre.
My puff, puff pass with Andre.
That's all I got.
Well, it was nice having you on deadly.
Is that it?
No, I didn't say anything.
It's all time.
Well, I haven't, I have no, I have no notes this week.
I'm just, I'm just spitball and I'm trying to think of everything.
Well, I got a question.
I got a question for deadly comics.
Maybe this is widely known already and I just haven't looked into it.
But did you have a comic that was deadly?
Is that why you're named deadly comics?
That's a great question.
The comic wasn't deadly.
I think that just came from like being a little kid in school and wanting to have a
comic company named a deadly comic because I thought that sounded cool.
That is cool.
Now it's just a username that doesn't mean anything.
Your, your cartoons are not.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry to.
They're just not that deadly.
They just don't, they just don't come off as particularly deadly to me.
When I see the little raccoons and cats and stuff, rabbits, little dinosaur, man.
Not yet.
I just think this can change.
Oh, no, there's going to be blood and hyper realistic blood in the new one.
We'll see.
OK, well, I'm unsettled.
The deadliest comic is the one you weren't expecting.
But did you, did you, I mean, you're an animator.
Did you used to draw comics?
Oh, yeah.
Before I knew I could animate instead.
I see.
That's funny because I did the opposite.
I tried animating because I thought that was what I was good at.
But in-betweens are annoying.
And I prefer just drawing the one frame.
So I just do that in a comic forum.
I don't know.
In-betweens for me are like therapeutic.
I think they can be.
Yeah.
Comics and animation are so close, though.
I heard a quote somewhere like that everyone in animation wants to do comics
and everyone in comics wants to do animation.
That's so funny.
It is kind of like a storyboard.
It's just sort of like not framed in a screen form.
You can change the shape of the.
True, yeah, yeah.
And it kind of, your head puts in the in-betweens.
That's how it works.
Your head fills in the space that's not there.
I've read, what is it called?
Is it drawing words and writing pictures?
The one by Scott McLeod?
Oh, that's Understanding Comics.
That's the one I read.
I think he has two.
I think he has another one.
He has a bunch, yeah.
Yeah.
I've seen bits of those.
I still haven't sat down and read each either one of them.
I know I've read one of them.
I might have read both.
I think there's one called Understanding Comics.
I've definitely read Understanding Comics and there's also,
I think he's another one called Drawing Words and Writing Pictures.
And yeah, you know, I think in that he sort of explains that like
the comic kind of happens in between the panels.
Like the action of it is when your mind is sort of filling in
the movement in between.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's sort of the, when at all, where the magic happens.
That's what I really like about like an action scene in a comic where I'm,
I try, well, I don't try, but I always subconsciously want to think of it
as like an animation.
And then I'm, I'm like showing just the important bits.
So like you can infer how the person moved their hand to get to the next
panel from the previous panel, even though the camera is like,
is a different position.
It's like, if this was a storyboard, you could turn it into like a full
like motion would be like, it would work.
And that's what they do with, you know, every, every manga ever.
That's how the animation adaptation, a lot of them are like super close
because the comics are already so, so clear in the posing and the staging
and everything.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, kind of, kind of similar, kind of, kind of sort of use similar
conventions in both, both mediums.
Isn't that interesting?
Isn't that, isn't that neat?
Um, I'm sure no one's drawn a comparison before.
Mm hmm.
Yes, we were, I think we're really smart.
I think that like, do you think that maybe like the same guy like invented
both things?
Well, like Disney or Tezuka, I was thinking of Tezuka.
I was thinking, I was thinking of Tezuka.
Does Tezuka do animation?
Well, I know he's the manga boy, but like, I
don't know whether he's specifically animated.
Well, wasn't it him that sort of, uh, invent, like made up the convention
of animating on threes to save budget?
That's what I've heard, yeah, with those old Astro boys and everything.
Yeah.
He definitely would have been involved.
Yeah, I guess.
Uh, I mean, I, yeah, I guess I don't know if he like, if he like drew like cells
himself or anything like that.
Maybe he didn't.
Um, I think he did.
He's got like, I know he's done some cool experimental short films and stuff.
Oh yeah.
But he had like a whole studio for the, like the anime series, things like that.
Just like, just like, uh, just like George Lucas.
And now, now he makes secret personal films just for himself that no one
will ever see.
Is that true?
Well, that's what he, that's what he says in interviews.
It's like, so what are you doing now that like you're a, you're washed up and
he's like, Oh, you know, I'm making, I'm making a small personal experimental
films that will never be seen by the public.
And it's like, okay.
Okay.
Got it.
Whatever.
Have fun.
I guess like doing stop motion with green plastic army, man.
It's a whole new medium.
It's a whole new artistic medium.
It's never been tried.
Um,
I'm still, I'm still looking at the image search for ball masters.
So,
this girl with the green hair is pretty.
I don't want to have sex with her.
Shut up.
Good luck.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Deadly.
How, cause I know you were like, at least you knew about me cause you drew that
gif, how did you find out about this, this group?
Um, I guess through you, I think I saw your things through, um, like a crown prince
animation that she did with like Dr.
Wolfe and stuff.
Oh, crown prince.
Yes.
Of course.
Talk about a blast from the past.
Talk about it.
Yeah.
Was, we're just giving a, was it a moment with Dr.
Wolfe?
Uh, you know, I'm trying to think, I think, I remember there was a crown prince, like
animation thing she did.
And then I edited part of it to link it to something.
I don't know what I have.
There's, there's, yeah, I remember it.
I remember I was in there and then I touched a painting and I got zipped into the
moment with Dr.
Wolfe, which was drawn by her, I think.
Yeah.
That sounds familiar.
Cause it wasn't me who drew it.
I drew the, the voice of reason one, the original.
Oh, that's right.
Oh my God, you drew the original.
How you, you started it.
I started it.
You started the madness.
I forgot about that, but that's true.
Oh my God.
But the first one, the first one was funny.
The first one was like a joke.
I know it was like a reason, like obviously, like knew it was like, oh,
it's so fucking silly, the idea of going to a wolf to talk about like your,
your, your manic, your, your, your, your, your cycle, the psychological
problems of your OC, like, like the cycle of the problems of your OC and
hating like friendship is witchcraft or something.
Yeah.
Like, like he knows, he knew it was silly.
And so he wrote it to me that way.
And I, it's a funny bit to bring your OC into a therapist and have your OC do
like discuss their like character quirks, as though they're like a
psychological like neurosis that they have to try and overcome.
Like that's a funny bit.
And then immediately they drop it and they just are coming in to be like,
I'm bullied at school for being a brony.
And I need this YouTuber to explain to me what I should do about that or whatever.
And it just became the worst thing ever.
I forget what the crown prince one, like the, my one, like I forgot what
I said in my one.
Yeah.
I don't think it was that good.
It was nicely animated, though.
That was, that was the fun part.
I mean, mine was about Phantom Horn, uh, base.
I mean, that was, that was in the era of Phantom Horn, where he was just
unironically a like, haha, aren't SJW stupid, like guy.
So his, his thing is literally like, people miss species me and that's a problem.
But also like, haha, isn't it funny that that would be a problem someone would have?
Well, so, you know, pretty, pretty cool, pretty awesome.
Pretty great.
I'm looking at his channel and he's still, he's still cooking.
He's still cooking.
Let him cook.
Good for him.
I don't see the therapist things much anymore.
It seems like it's more just, you know, talking about the show and stuff.
Yeah, I think I, I would assume he pivoted to talking about the CG stuff.
Yeah, as you see in that.
I saw the movie.
I don't think I don't know much about the show.
I assume it's just the characters from the movie having like little moments,
little fun things.
Oh my God, analysis anarchy.
They're still so prominent.
Eight days, eight days ago, they did another analysis anarchy.
The longest running series in YouTube history will be analysis anarchy.
OK, all right.
Mercifully, it doesn't seem like it's that popular anymore.
It only got, it only got nine K views in the, in the week it's been out.
So nine thousands, a lot of people.
I know, but it used to be, it used to be a lot more.
I scroll down a little bit.
There's more analysis anarchy and it's like 30 K, 31 K.
TF2 analysis, TF2 analysis, season seven, the movie part one.
Wait, what TF2 analysis, season seven, the movie part one three weeks ago,
an hour long, five thousand views.
OK, what?
It's when they say TF2 analysis, do they mean analysis anarchy?
Yes, that's why it's been so confusing.
It's why do they, why don't they call it analysis is the analysis
community of MLP and they play TF2 together.
So it's TF2 analysis for short, which confuses everybody
because that's not what it sounds like.
It's not, no, it's this doesn't make any fucking sense.
The show, am I crazy?
Is the show not called analysis anarchy?
It was initially TF2 analysis anarchy.
So why is this compilation called TF2 analysis?
Per colon quotation mark, season seven, the movie, parentheses, part one.
End quotation mark.
Why?
I mean, why not?
I guess it's not going to bring in more viewers, but the people
that know are going to know what they're clicking on.
Look, I just look, maybe I'm I'm sorry.
I might be the only one that cares about this.
I just why did they take a word out of the title of the show
when they they've always done that, though, they always do.
They talk, they say TF2 analysis, like, like interchangeably with analysis anarchy.
Maybe anarchy gets their video demonetized or something.
I guess I shouldn't complain because we are the PCP, but our logo
has always been TPC.
So I have no, I have, right, I have no room to complain.
Okay, it's fine.
Okay, so, so that's how you found me through the Crown Prince video.
Yeah, and then I just went to every possible way I could, you know,
listen to your voice some more.
That's true.
Oh, no, it's true.
It's true.
And then I found the PCP and then everything collapsed.
And then we have a pandemic.
And then surely, surely more time elapsed between those two things.
Does that mean you've seen my comics?
I have some of them, some of them.
For some reason, I have, I don't spend a lot of time reading web
comics anymore, but I got the load of ghost books and it's on my shelf.
Yes, I remember.
Oh, hell yeah, you bought one of those.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, that's good stuff.
How many of my comics did you buy?
Ben.
No, I know.
Ellie is our cut this.
Ellie is our cut this far.
Ben's taking the biggest L of his career.
Don't actually know you mostly for your Winnie the Pooh videos.
What?
Really?
That's true.
It's true.
I love those videos.
No one talks about them.
That's actually really funny.
Yeah, you created a niche and then you filled that niche.
Yeah, and then you disappeared.
I still do mean to go back and finish.
You know what?
Maybe I should, I have never entirely abandoned the thought that I will
finish at least season one of The New Adventures of Winnie the Pooh.
It's good.
I want you to get to my favorite episode.
Which one's that?
It's called Party Pooper.
Rapid throws a party, but is too controlling, too hard-headed about it.
So it's no fun for anyone.
I don't know.
I don't know if I remember that one.
I'm not sure if I've seen that one.
I don't even know what season it is.
Like as a kid, I had a VHS with three episodes on it.
And as a kid, I thought that's all that there was.
And then just stand up.
There was, you know, more episodes, a whole show.
Yeah.
So I just would just re-watch three episodes over and over.
But after watching your videos, they like founded on Disney Plus
and have been watching the rest of it.
Oh, my God.
It's a good show.
That's very interesting.
I think it was.
It was a pretty good show, you know, for what it was.
Yeah, thanks for reminding me.
I do I haven't been thinking about it that much lately, but like I would.
I've told people before that, like, I will eventually finish season one.
There's not even that much more of season one, honestly.
I could probably just do it.
You know, I've been I've been thinking, though, about.
You know what I want to do?
And I think I think I missed an opportunity by not streaming myself
playing the Mega Man games while I was getting ready for the Mega Man video.
I think I want to start streaming myself playing the battle network games
in preparation for whenever I eventually do
like the battle network continuity lecture.
Because I'm definitely going to do that at some point.
So I definitely need to play those games.
So I might as well stream them.
So I need to get like better internet so I can actually stream without it
like crashing all the time.
So yeah, that's my that's my next that's my next big move.
That's my next power play.
My memory of battle network is watching people who own that game play it.
And I then understand why why you were in a grid
and why you couldn't run around and shoot things.
Yeah, I've I've never played one.
I've seen it and I guess I I guess I understand that it's like a strategic.
It's like a strategy RPG, but like on a very small grid, basically.
That makes sense.
And I think there's card mechanics that I think it might be a little bit
like give or play chain of memories. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I think there might sort of be like you have cards in your deck
that you play like attacks and chain of memories, but it's on a grid, I think.
OK, I don't think my my child brain would not have been able to comprehend that.
I mean, I cards and a grid.
No, thank you.
I mean, I did manage to play chain of memories when it was new,
although I was not that young for that.
I think I think I probably
I think I probably could have gotten into battle network if if I had tried it
at the time, but I was more into the action jump and shoot man of zero,
which I think was coming out around the same time.
And, you know, I had a limited budget for video games.
I wasn't allowed to play battle network
because of all the violence in the world.
Battling was is too much too dangerous.
That's not true. That's not true.
And networking.
I was so scared of socializing and I couldn't.
I wasn't allowed to play Mega Man because my parents thought it was
unfeminist, like we already have men that are already, you know,
just a press environment.
Why we don't need Mega Man to do it even more.
And they were with a mega picture, yeah.
And to this day, we only have one female robot master.
Two, if you count role.
What the fuck are we talking about?
Oh, finding each other on YouTube and stuff.
Well, I don't know anything.
I remember feeling like really cool when my little give and take channel
got like subscribers from people who are like big like you.
Deadly Comics had a lot of views on like your Scootaloo animations
and you were like loads of subscribers.
And I was like, oh, my God, Deadly Comics follows me.
You were more subscribers than I was.
I was more, you know,
I was more ecstatic when I saw you upload the give and take jump.
Oh, yeah. Oh, what was that?
Oh, no, it was just for like.
I got the GIF and then I put like a Led Zeppelin song on it.
And I think Led Zeppelin took it down or something.
Hey, hey, did you know that like on YouTube are our channels at
is at the procrastinators 9667?
Is that something they gave to you?
I guess they like a guy in the email saying that YouTube has handles now
and that you could select your handle.
They've had them.
I don't remember ever selecting it.
I don't know why ours is 9667.
I feel like maybe it used to be just at the procrastinators
and maybe it got changed after the Brad Garlinghouse hack.
Oh, probably that sucks.
That's stupid.
I don't like that.
Maybe there's a way to change it back.
I I was just looking at the channel, though,
because I am I'm actually right on the cusp.
I have almost my channel has almost surpassed the PCP in subscribers.
I think the PCP is a twenty five point two K.
I am at like twenty five point one K.
Well, so any day now, the only thing that could beat you was yourself.
Exactly. I cheated on the game, but myself hypocrite.
I think Pita like twenty K.
I've been Ben St. Channel had been at twenty K for a long time,
and now it got a big couple, couple thousand more recently.
So cha-ching cha-ching.
Oh, yeah.
Did I mention that Chugga Conroy added me on Twitter?
I saw that.
Yeah, I know Chugga Conroy from like gaming stuff,
but I wasn't an avid watcher.
I just know I just know the name.
I just know he's a big name.
And so I tried to ask him if he he's
well, he said on Twitter that he would he would love
he said he would pay good money to be in the audience for a lecture.
And I was like, oh, shit.
So I tried to ask him if you wanted to come on the podcast
and I didn't get a response, which is too bad because like the same.
It's not the same as a big like, no, it's not the same.
Well, I mean, I mean, I wasn't going to do another lecture with an audience.
I wasn't planning on it.
So like maybe maybe you could check out Conroy could pay the big money
to just sit in front of you while you do your next lecture.
Could he just give me big money?
And that's it.
Could he just give me some good money?
You just invite him to your house.
He sits down.
What if we just did that?
I mean, honestly, if you wanted, if like him and maybe a couple other people,
maybe like Cybershell and maybe like a few others.
I mean, I guess we could just organize a lecture thing.
Anyway, I would still be down to come to America to sit at a lecture.
The only reason it didn't work last time because it's a covid happened.
I got covid.
Yeah. I mean, we could do that, I guess.
What's the next topic?
Just for fun.
Well, I don't know.
I would have to pick something else because I was going to do.
Well, I don't want to get I don't want to get into it.
Tf2 analysis anarchy.
Oh, my. You know what?
You know what?
I thought about it many times, but it's just like that.
You would have to watch it.
There's 16 hours of tf.
There's probably like wait, no, there's not.
Well, there's there's probably like seven hours.
There's probably like there's probably like five to seven hours.
There's seven five to seven too many.
It would be it actually would be really funny.
I'm going to put that on.
No, I'm going to put that on the list, actually.
I care about my mental health too much.
How many people would?
It would have to be people clicking on it who know what the tf2 analysis thing is.
How many people are there?
I mean, it could be an introductory thing.
Like that's true.
Like a weird niche of Brony subculture.
Like, hello, everyone.
I'm here to talk to you about this stupid thing that's insane that it exists.
Now, that's now that's what the Brony lecture should have been.
Is explaining like, who is Dr. Wolf?
Who is Josh Scorcher?
Who is I love Kim possible?
A lot. Who is Silverquill?
Where are they now? Yeah.
Oh, they're still there.
Yeah, they haven't gone anywhere.
Uh, and take.
Oh, where is Gibbon take?
That's like, I mean, you almost like like a compelling idea
in sort of the same vein of like, like what is like unicorn jelly
and pastel defender heliotrope?
Like, like what is this bizarre like, what is the rift?
What is the rift cafe?
The story, the history of the rift cafe.
That's a much better Brony lecture than the actual Brony lecture was,
which is just talking about was actually available.
Brony knowledge was actually just a history of the PCP.
Yeah, publicly available.
Brony knowledge mixed with how did the PCP form, which is like fine.
Um, I made a new fucking RuneScape video.
That's one thing I did.
Oh, why?
It's a it's a it's only a little thing.
Um, just as an update, because I finally I chopped enough of the trees
for my fletching challenge.
Oh, very good.
It was twenty eight thousand something you logs.
And they're in my bank.
And I just showed the people that I did that.
And I laughed in insanely.
I coughed and then I laughed and I was insane about like, what the fuck?
And then I then I then that's it.
It sounds very, very in character for you.
It's not much.
I just felt like like I didn't know what milestones to make.
It was a very small milestone.
But the next milestone will probably be like two years in the future
because of the amount of coal I need to get.
And the amount of time I'm willing to spend like focusing on that
as opposed to having it in the background.
I've been playing Noida again, and that's bad.
Noida is a bad game.
That's the one with all the sane and all the pixels.
Yes, yes, the pixel sands.
I wanted to play that.
It looks fun.
It is a good it's a good game and it's a fun game.
But I like I don't mean to toot my own horn or anything,
but I have kind of mastered it to the point that like
win, lose, like whatever, playing it is pretty formulaic at this point.
I know I know how to build a wand that wins the game.
And it's just a question of like how how quick how quick do I get that wand?
And then like, do I survive?
Do do I do something stupid that kills me or do I not?
So I'm not I'm not getting anything more out of it anymore.
So I really should just stop playing it.
And yet I and yet I continue
because it still feels good when I get a wand that goes burr
and just blasts out damage when it still gives me that visceral power feeling
and I crave it.
I just want to destroy my enemies.
It's it lets me it lets me live that.
Anyway, anyway,
300,000 views on the Mega Man video, by the way,
we passed 300,000 is a yay, yay.
Thank you. I'm very happy.
I'm very happy about it.
300,000 times eight.
Now, how many hours?
Oh, actually, well, actually, the watch time,
well, because the average view is not eight hours long, the total watch
hours, cowards, the total watch time on the video is two hundred and twenty eight
thousand hours.
Fuck, which is two hundred and twenty eight thousand hours.
In years.
That's 26 years, 26 years of useful human
endeavor and energy have been wasted.
That's how long I've been alive.
Yeah.
Well, so either you do whatever you were doing or you watch Ben St.
's lecture over and over again.
My lecture is is is pretty much equal in value to your entire life.
If I would say so, I would say so.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Hang on. I need to get a drink.
I'll be one second.
Just you and me now give and take.
Oh, no. My dreams have come true.
So did you you I guess you listen to the podcast?
Yeah, I think I stopped at some point and then I came back
and I didn't realize it had still been going all this time.
This is an old podcast.
Oh, we're still trekking.
It's been it's been it's been 80 years.
The we you know, I've been trying.
I've been trying to create a vegetarian or vegan
gummy alternative to the ones that I've been making
because the ones because the ones that I've been making
you know, they use gelatin, which is made with animal products.
And my mom asked like if they're because I guess my sister has become a vegetarian
and my mom asked if there was like a vegetarian way to make them.
And I said, I don't know, maybe.
So I've been trying to I tried to make them.
I substituted agar agar for gelatin.
And it works, but the consistency is completely different.
And it's not bad, but it's not a gummy.
So is it like not elastic?
Yes, it's not elastic.
It's it's just so soft.
It's a very well, I would say it's stiffened.
It's stiffened brittle.
It's a stiff if it's a stiff, brittle sort of gel.
And so I read about
Xanthan gum can can help make it more elastic.
So I tried adding some Xanthan gum and didn't didn't really like how it came out.
There's another thing called locust bean gum, which I know I have it somewhere,
but I can't fucking find my little tub of locust bean gum.
That sounds disgusting.
Well, yeah, but I mean like little beans that locusts
build in their little factory.
Well, I think it's a bean that maybe locusts eat them.
Oh, you know, it's just it's it's the gum.
It's it's the gum from some vegetable bean, much like much like Xanthan gum, I think.
So yeah, it's not.
It doesn't actually have anything to do with locusts.
But I just I know I lost it.
I lost it.
Maybe they ate it.
Oh, I mean, we had an inspector come into my house and inspect the place.
And apparently there are that I haven't seen the rat in a while.
Also, there's a strange smell coming from the downstairs bathroom.
And my suspicion is that the rat has died and is rotting and emitting a miasma.
But none of us can find a corpse.
So we're all sort of unsure where it's like fell down.
The drain.
Gross.
I mean, that's that's a thing that can happen if you don't have the cover on the shower drain.
Ew, maybe I'll check that.
Maybe I'll check to see if that did happen.
I think there's a cover on the shower drain, but I don't know.
I don't use the downstairs bathroom.
So maybe that's worth investigating.
Anyway, it's really gross.
An inspector came in, changed all the changed all the fire detectors.
And now and now the fire detector on the first floor works, which is nice.
But it goes off when I cook pizza in the oven.
So that's bad.
Hmm. Yeah, it's sad and makes me mad and upset.
And also, I guess they found rat droppings around, which I don't know where they found those.
I have not seen any rat droppings, and I do know what they look like.
So I don't know where he saw them, but his note said that, like, there were some around.
So that's too bad.
That's very unfortunate.
Should sweep the floor.
The floor. Nobody has, like, swept the downstairs in a while.
You should just do that.
Be so easy and everyone would love me.
Did I complain that I had to buy that I bought a huge, a huge box of toilet paper?
You did last time.
Nobody else buys a toilet paper.
It's all on me.
What would they do without me?
They would die.
They would have to get out without you smell bad.
It would smell even worse than they smell now and they would die.
Are you like in a townhouse kind of thing?
Or like a. Yeah, I'm like splitting.
I'm like splitting a condo with like five people.
Oh, OK.
So there's no, like, maintenance fellow who comes to clean.
It's up to the tenants.
No, there is no. There's no.
Damn. Damn, that would be fancy.
That would be fancy if we had a guy that came to clean the house.
That's what we got for like what for you or whatever.
Well, that's awesome. I'm jealous.
Somebody just has to sweep the kitchen.
Somebody just has to like sweep the kitchen in the front hallway.
It's not even that that much work.
I just wanted I've been meaning to just do it.
You should you should live stream yourself sweeping,
turning into content.
I need I need we need to change.
We need to change internet providers so that our
my stream will not cut out.
Fuck.
That would be a really funny reason,
like why nobody sweeps.
It's like, yeah, I mean, I would sweep, but I can't stream it.
Yeah. Oh, man.
Another. Did I tell you that I've sent?
Mention that like the boyfriend of the girl that lives here
said that like he wants.
Well, no, one of my roommates told me that he wants to start a podcast.
And another one told me that he wants to start streaming
himself playing like Magic the Gathering, because I guess he
he claims to be quite skilled at Magic the Gathering.
And I'm like, I can't I can't let these people know that I'm a podcaster.
Right. I've revealed I've revealed too much.
I've revealed too much by even mentioning to any of them that I like
do stuff on YouTube.
Like, I wish I I wish I didn't say that.
They'd be like, Ben, could you could you help me with my setup?
Because, you know, you you know about that stuff, right?
You're like, you're like a tech guy.
Never. Never. You're like a YouTube guy.
You could figure it out for me.
I do labor for free.
I wouldn't that would that would be bad.
That would be bad if they wanted me to like help with their setup.
It would be even worse if they wanted to like.
Collaborate or something.
Can you imagine?
Can you imagine if they want to like, hey,
let me shout out shout out my shout out my Magic the Gathering based
Twitch, Twitch channel, please.
Oh, dear.
You know, I'm just I'm just catastrophizing.
I'm just imagining the worst possible scenario.
Nobody nobody can know nobody can know that I'm a podcaster.
I didn't mention you should you should sweep.
I didn't mention it to that cousin who was asking about YouTube ad revenue.
You should sweep the floor so that they think you're a janitor instead.
Yeah, I'll tell them I quit.
I'll tell them I quit the posting life and decided to.
Return to the earth.
You know, you know, something that irritated me,
something that made me mad about my dinner with Andre was how shit it was.
But also is that the guy Wallace Shawn,
he's complaining about how poor he is.
He's complaining about like, business is not good.
I don't get any work.
I'm a failed playwright and then and his his.
The like the examples that they give for how how poor and and and unsuccessful
he is is that his girlfriend has to work three nights a week.
Like she doesn't even she doesn't even have a full time job.
She has a part time job.
Wow. Yeah.
It's like most nowadays, most people just it's most people,
just men and women, both partners just have a job.
You just everyone has a job, right?
Is this the 80s movie?
Hmm, 70s or 80s?
I'm so poor.
I had to sell one of my 70 yachts.
I'm so I'm so poor.
I'm so poor.
My girlfriend has to work.
My girlfriend works a part time job.
Oh, whoa, is me.
Oh, I'm so poor.
I usually don't go to this like extravagantly fancy restaurant,
but like, it's fine.
I will do that and I can afford it.
It's OK, 1981.
All right.
There's more.
There's more that I could say about that.
There's more like weird little things in there that just hint at like.
Just the the the the the economic differences in the economies of then versus now.
Yeah, ways that like.
Think things that he thinks that.
The way that you all is Sean is portrayed as like so poor in destitute.
He's so like so down in his luck, but like he, you know, he he splits like
he splits in New York.
He splits it like a Manhattan, New York apartment with his girlfriend,
who only works a part time job.
Like, my God, I live I live in a much cheaper area
and I split my house like seven ways.
Like, dude.
Dude, it's you know, it reminds me of like Homer Simpson,
how like home the Simpsons are sort of like poor.
They're down in their luck.
They're they've got a giant house.
They're a blue collar family, but they own a house.
They have two cars that yeah, the mom doesn't work, etc.
It's a hold over from an age when
it was normal to have like a big old thing like that.
It was it wasn't like that extravagant, actually.
I know cringe, cringe.
Those are the days.
Do you think they're going to I'm pretty sure they will.
But like the Simpsons doing like the
constantly breaking the timeline stuff with like
a new episode about Homer and Marge in the past of the 90s.
Yeah, and then an episode of them of the past in the 2000s.
Yeah, actually, they're going to have been zoomers this whole time.
I mean, I hope the show doesn't continue that long.
It will continue until 100 seasons.
I kind of hope that it ends soon.
I mean, I have heard people say that it is not as bad now as it was for a while,
that it has sort of like embrace its.
It's it's what it is as like new Simpsons and it's more trying to be its own
modern thing instead of sort of.
Aping its former self and that that's been good for it, I guess, I don't know.
It's still it's you know, it's cringe to see it continue on.
But it's already like they already had the Elon Musk is the greatest
inventor of modern times episode.
So like they've already got shamed themselves as much as they possibly can.
So there's no lower they can go.
They can only go up from here.
At this point, I don't even really think of it as like a show you can watch.
It's just sort of like.
How can something go on for this long?
Like, how is it continually getting greenlit for a new season?
Like, obviously, it's a giant thing, but like it's so insane.
Because people still watch it.
I mean, not as many people.
I just imagine the voice actors who have to.
Do this one role and get paid extremely well for it, but only have this one thing to do.
I mean, in the case of some of them like damaging their voice permanently in the process,
like, do they are they very tired of it?
I'm sure they rather do another thing.
I know.
I'm going to say no, like, because it's like you said, I'm sure it's like
it's what they're known for.
It's a very high profile role and I'm sure they get paid extremely well for it.
And I mean, not saying that like voice acting is like not, you know, hard work in its own right,
but like it's easier.
I'm sure it's I'm sure, you know, recording lines for a 30 minute
show is a lot easier than than the other jobs out there, even in entertainment.
So I'm sure it's a very, very pretty, pretty cushy, pretty cushy position.
That's probably why they've all been doing it for 35 years.
Mega Man just turned 35.
Yesterday was the anniversary.
Wow. Oh, I saw the 17th about that.
He's an old man.
What did Capcom do to celebrate?
I don't know what they did, but apparently there were no major like game
announcements, which is which is too bad.
That's that's that's unfortunate.
But I think no one was really expecting one.
So. Eh, nothing.
Mega Man, 35th, maybe like Kotaku has like an article summarizing.
Oh, here's one that says New Mega Man could be revealed for 35th anniversary.
Yeah, I guess a lot of things could happen.
That's not news.
It's not news.
Wouldn't it be so fucked up if there was something to talk about today on the news?
That'd be so fucked up.
Let's talk about that.
I don't really see any major announcements.
I feel like there would be like.
Higher search results, if there was anything noteworthy.
I didn't I wasn't really paying that close attention.
I figured I would hear about it if there was anything big.
And they should do they should do their own like Smash Brothers universe,
but just for Mega Man so that all the Mega Man characters can interact.
It's a little little like crossover game.
Like Power Rangers, every Red Ranger from every iteration of Power Rangers
gets together for a special episode, but it's Mega Man instead.
I mean, they had.
Well, they had Mega Man, the power battle and Mega Man to the power fighters,
which were like fighting games where your Mega Man against the robot masters.
I mean, yeah, there's enough.
There's enough robot masters that they probably could do that for sure.
Are there any games where you can play as those guys?
Um, well, I think in I think in like one of the remakes,
like in Mega Man, powered up, I think you could play as some of the robot masters.
Um, try to think.
There should be a school like a high school anime
visual novel with all the Mega Man.
I don't, you know, I wonder if they're I wonder if the mangas and stuff
like go more into like what does what does Rock do when he's not Mega Man?
Like, does he go to school?
Like, does he does he like blend in with society?
Like, does he go shopping?
Is he friends with Shinji?
Shinji from Everingale?
Is he friends with Shinji? Yeah.
Yeah, he probably he probably would be now that you mentioned it.
They're just doing like the the dejected like hanged heads.
Like pose, but together.
I don't know why that's so funny.
But but you know, they kind of hint in the games, they kind of hint at like,
oh, yeah, when when he's not when he's not Mega Man, he's like Rock.
And like as Rock, maybe he's just a normal kid.
Does he just does he live a normal kid life?
Like, does he have friends?
Like, what's what's the deal?
What game does he play?
Yeah. And do you want that?
Just read Astro Boy, because that's what that is.
I know. True.
I know. It's I've read a few.
Mega Man literally just is they made Astro Boy again, but they made it a video game this time.
Yeah, I need to read more Astro Boys.
I tried to read all of them and I got like to the beginning.
There's a few like little short stories.
They're like, they're so odd.
I would like to be fun to read some old Tezuka stuff.
I've like never read any of it.
It's really good. Blackjack, I highly recommend.
It's like a like a medical drama, I guess.
Yeah, I've seen your house.
Exactly. I've seen the Blackjack movie.
And it was OK.
Yeah.
Well, Blackjack is kind of like, isn't he kind of like an evil dude?
He's sort of, I guess it's like a.
I wouldn't say anti hero.
Yeah, anti hero.
Like he goes by his own rules.
He's a unlicensed, a renegade and unlicensed doctor who charges insane amounts.
But, you know, you know, it's what he's doing.
He does.
Like, oh, you got an uncurable disease.
I have this experimental new technique using shuriken.
I can throw them into your heart and they can fix everything.
Nice. You have to trust me.
No, no, thanks.
Well, it looks like you're going to die from heart death or whatever you got.
Damn it. Yeah.
Fuck.
I was getting off his back.
He's got other patients.
Got other fish to fry.
And they got money.
You got money to pay.
Yeah, you don't get the you can't pay the bills.
Then you then you then you keep then you retain your ills.
That's that's what I always say.
Did he do Usagi, Yajimbo, or is that someone else?
That's someone else.
That's like a I don't know if it's American, but it's.
Somewhere it's somewhere somehow related to TMNT around that same time.
Really? They cross over a lot.
What? Yeah, I think it's like Usagi,
Yajimbo is like from the early days of free comics.
That just happened to get a bit popular.
But is it? Wait, is it not Japanese?
Japanese born American.
Oh, OK.
Stan, Stan Sakai, yeah, that's a guy.
Oh, this looks cool.
I haven't seen this before.
OK, this is not I thought it was older.
I was older than that.
Maybe I'm you know, am I confusing it with is it like Wolf and Pup?
Yeah, that's another old one.
It's not Tezuka, but it's another like classical manga.
What's that one about the like set?
He's like a Ronin or he's like he's like a samurai,
but it's not like a battle manga.
It's just about like a samurai like hanging out at his house
and like cheating on his wife and ignoring his kids.
Is that Ring of Bell?
I don't know this one.
Oh, man, where did I hear about this one?
Someone was talking about it and some.
Oh, it's an old manga about a samurai
cheating on his wife.
Is it Hagure Gumo?
Yes, this is it.
Hagure Gumo is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by George Akiyama.
Hagure Gumo literally vagrant cloud is a Japanese manga, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Set at the end of the Edo period,
it depicts clouds, clouds family with his wife, Turtle,
their 11 year old son and eight year old daughter with his wife's name is Turtle.
The clouds are always ignoring work and playing.
Cloud is notorious for womanizing.
OK, and that's the plot.
Is this an old series or is this a new thing?
It is from it's.
Oh, my God, it ran from 1973 all the way
for to 2017. Are you joking?
Oh.
How did it how did it run for 46 years?
I guess he got around that samurai.
Here's what it looks like.
Someone in the comments, tell me where I heard about this.
His name is cloud, maybe from Final Fantasy Seven.
Yeah.
George Akiyama is the author.
Is that a normal, like George first name?
I think that maybe is a Beatles.
OK, his name is Joji, but I think that's like
it's Americanized as George.
Maybe he lived in America.
His father was Korean and an artificial flower craftsman.
Gay stupid.
You know, flowers already exist.
Hey, let me pick them.
You know what? Just pluck them.
If I, you know, you know what?
To continue, let me do some more toxic masculinity.
My I mentioned that the girl that lives here has this boyfriend.
She's this guy who's like always here and they always cook together.
And I got to say it's very effeminate.
It's a very effeminate thing that he has this girlfriend
and that he cooks dinner with her.
It's just not it's just it's just not it's just not manly.
Why depends on what they're cooking,
like if it's a big it's just a big beef stew as a man.
No, it's it's not it's not it's not manly.
So wrong. Is there anything wrong
with being an effeminate in the kitchen?
Absolutely everything.
No, I just I just seems seems like a big fucking waste of time.
It just seems like every time I see them,
they're always like cooking some shit in the kitchen.
And it's like how many fucking hours a day do you spend
preparing some nonsense, you idiots.
Just put ham on a wrap and roll it up and eat it and be done.
Be done with your with your garbage.
I don't know.
I think it's nice to be able to cook something.
I think, you know what, it's fine every now and then.
I don't know. I don't like I can't it just seems it just seems so tedious.
It just seems like they make it's like such a big production.
It's like that's what you spend your evening doing.
It's like preparing shopping for the ingredients to prepare this meal
and then preparing it and laying it all out meticulously
and doing all these intricate steps to do to in order for it to
and then you actually you just have to take the time to cook it.
And then, you know, you plate it out and you eat it afterwards.
And it's like that's your that's your evening.
That that sucks if you're by yourself.
But like if with two people, it takes not so long, I guess.
Oh, are you saying that it could be a fun
activity to spend with someone you love?
Yeah, that's what I'm effeminate.
That's what I mean. That's what I'm saying.
You would say that, wouldn't you?
Yeah.
Sounds great.
I like I'm going to keep shaming him for it.
I'll never stop.
You should be like me and make a pass at Turkish girls on the bus
and get laughed at and kicked off the much manly.
And now I don't have to waste my time cooking.
Now I can just eat ham wraps and it's no problem.
I'm I'm I'm I'm a man in the kitchen.
I'm manly in the kitchen.
I just mix my ingredients together.
I add some Xanthan gum, add some Xanthan gum
to my to my agar agar solution.
And then I taste it and I say, you gross.
It has a consistency of snot and boogers.
And then I throw it away.
And that's and that's and then it's done.
You know what? It's not a big deal.
It's not a big fucking federal issue.
Oh, I just pulled a leg muscle.
This is the new podcast talking point, everybody.
Oh, no, which muscle was it the hamstring?
Well, it's the one
that goes under the knee and on the inside of the leg.
Oh, I don't like that.
It like sticks out.
It's in a vulnerable position today.
It's like it's under the knee and then up on the inner thigh area.
It's sort of.
Are you talking about the vastus medialis?
Oh, that's the one.
I don't know the names of the muscles.
You know what? My, you know what?
This is a perfect time for me to mention my favorite leg muscle,
the sartorius.
Artorius of the abyss.
Yes, the sartorius of the abyss.
I'll show you.
It's I'll highlight it in red.
It's it's this one.
No, don't show me your muscles, Ben.
It's this one right here.
Is that the one that could be it?
You say that one's your favorite.
That's my favorite.
Just because of what it does for you.
No, I just think it looks cool.
I'll stretch over like that.
I have no idea.
Yeah, how it how it just kind of like crosses over
the over on top of the other ones.
Looks pretty fruity to me.
Fruity looks effeminate.
Yeah. No, no.
Need a perfectly cute muscle.
That's the man I am.
I don't know why. You know what?
I'm just going to write.
I'm just going to cope.
I'm like I'm like I'm like the ugly.
I'm like the ugliest, soyest, most beta male in my entire family.
It's very sad. It makes me sad.
It bums me out.
I'm the shortest.
I'm the shortest male of the.
I'm the shortest male son of the shortest male
uncle in the in the whole group.
Everybody else is taller than me.
And also just just just tougher looking.
Just tougher. They got better chins.
Even the women even the women are taller than me.
What do I do? Help.
That's always good when a woman is taller.
Yeah, that's not a problem.
Stupid, stupid.
This is not my this is not my dad's side.
All my all my all my cousins on my dad's side are like tall.
Sucks. I don't like him.
And then they also and also their landlords.
Well, that's.
You know, if you take estrogen,
you'll get even shorter.
I don't think that's true.
It is. I've lost.
I've lost half an inch since I started like two years ago.
How?
Because your bones, they they they get like weaker.
I think I talked about this already,
maybe not on the progress news podcast.
But the effects of estrogen on the bones
is that they become less strong and they shrink a tiny bit.
Sounds over the course of your whole skeleton.
You get a little shorter.
Sounds awesome.
So what you need to do is you need to chug testosterone.
You need to get as much of that as you possibly can
and just chug it to a dangerous amount.
I guess that makes a lot of sense when you put it like that.
That probably is what I should do.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
You know, I'm just it's just beta.
It's just very effeminate of me.
And I just think that it's lame.
It's nothing wrong with being beta.
Nothing wrong with being a little effeminate soy boy.
I'm so I'm a little effeminate soy boy.
And that's it.
That's it.
Nothing wrong with being a tiny, cutesy.
I'm just a loser.
I'm just a big loser and everyone hates me.
No. Yeah. Yeah.
No, fake, false.
I don't hate you. Yes, you do.
Stupid.
Prove it.
Prove how I hate you.
I.
Fuck.
I'm sure I'm sure there's a way.
Deadly. Come on.
Tell me you hate me.
I could tell me I'm tell me I'm a little soy boy.
But it's it's spent on me.
If that's what you are, then I'm even worse.
If that's I know you.
I know you are.
But what am I?
Better. OK.
Yeah.
Daily affirmations.
Um, I just, um,
you're short king, Ben.
Embrace it.
I'm not even that short.
I'm not even that shorter than you.
You are shorter than me.
I'm like, yeah, I'm like, I'm like pretty average.
I'm like, maybe just slightly shy of the average height
of the American male.
And yet.
I don't know, it's just it's just weird.
Like everybody, all my all my cousins are like,
all my cousins are like six foot two.
It's really weird.
I mean, my cousins are giants.
Is that true?
Yeah. Well, at least on the one side where my my uncle was
like a big guy.
He's a person now, but like, um, his sons are really,
really tall, really big people.
And I'm like, well, you know, I was small back then.
I'm smaller now.
And they were older.
So I always thought it was like, oh, older people.
Oh, they're just yeah, you know, they're older than me.
So they're bigger.
But no, it turns out that's just how people are just bigger.
Yeah.
Um, I mean, do you feel like they look down on you like
literally and and metaphorically?
Um, I don't know.
Some sometimes I get the feeling, but it's sometimes I get
that feeling, but I think it's a me thing.
I think I don't think I don't think actually anyone actually.
And it's not just it's not just that.
It's not like, uh, uh, that like they're big or like better
looking than me, although they are.
But it's also it's also like, you know, they have real jobs
and you know, own homes, are married, have kids, etc. etc.
Yeah, that's that's just normal.
Like I know it's normal.
Like, uh, societal pressures.
I know it's it's if you don't fit the mold that is set out for
you to be like, this is how you do normal stuff for normal
people. And you're like, ew, no, I don't want to do that.
And then you end up on a divergent path.
You're going to get pressured just by seeing other people
doing the normal thing.
I don't even I couldn't do that.
I like I don't even really think that anyone is like, oh,
Ben is such a is such a such a black sheep, such a such a
fail son.
I like I don't actually think anyone really even cares or
thinks thinks about it like that.
But I do get a little bit like everyone else like owns a
house.
God, I mean, that's fair to be upset about.
It sucks that owning a house is not easy.
Right.
Well, you know, I'm just griping.
There's only one thing to do.
Buy a house.
Build a house.
Yeah, build a build a bear.
That's the other thing you could do.
That's sure to help.
You could build a bear.
I could build that.
That would that would solve all my issue.
That damn it.
Genius.
Okay.
It's like, hmm, which way?
Miss Western man, build a bear or build a house?
Buy a house or build a bear.
Well, I've made I've made my choice.
I have so many bears, I can build a house with them.
Conquers the world, chief.
Just hit, hit, hit, cacking.
I don't know.
Somebody else say something.
Fuck you.
Well, I mean, I don't really have anything else.
That happened other than like kind of a bummer that I'm like,
I'm running low on some HRT medication.
And I'm like, okay, I got a restock.
Got to get like another like 17 months worth of pills or whatever.
But the site I used last time has been destroyed,
been found and like just like they got them.
They got them.
They just they shut them down.
Who did?
I don't know.
Just like the government's the police.
It's just sort of a thing.
It's not illegal to like buy medication from abroad,
at least in the UK for estrogen and stuff.
You can buy it.
It's you could have it.
You just can't buy it from British pharmacies
because you need a prescription.
And getting a prescription is like years long, decades long,
like evil system that is designed to make you die
and kill yourself before they give you any help.
I see.
So obviously I'm doing it by myself.
I'm buying the medication.
But the websites you buy it from,
they get shut down like quite frequently.
And I don't know where to get them right now.
And I found this new site and I tried to buy some stuff and it,
the money didn't go through.
Like my money wasn't left.
It wasn't taken from my account.
So it's not like I was scammed.
It's just something that's going wrong.
I have to call them up.
And it's just, it's just a little annoying.
It's anxiety inducing, I guess is the way to put it.
It's just sort of like, ah, fuck.
You know, the longer this takes,
the longer it'll take to get here.
And I don't want to run out.
I don't want to not have the things.
Then I'll be off the stuff.
Then what if my body masculinizes?
Ah, it sucks.
I don't, I don't know.
Would that, would that happen?
To an extent, yeah.
I mean, if the estrogen in my body goes down over time
and it's not replaced,
then the testosterone will take more of an effect.
And like parts of, you know, body hair will come back,
facial hair will come back just a bit.
Well, I mean, where are other,
I mean, where are other UK based,
special people like yourself getting there?
I, I, it's one of those like,
thinking about it is very stressful.
So it won't take too long to figure it out.
It's just like, oh God, no, I don't want to think about that.
Oh, fuck.
I understand.
That's been, that's been a bit of a...
Someone at my door, I gotta be right back, sorry.
Okay.
Did he say someone that has no...
It's the hormone police.
Good for them.
They're, they're, I'm glad they're working.
I mean, sure.
We can't just fire the hormone police
because then they would be out of a job.
Oh no.
I have to keep policing hormones for the economy.
You know what was really bugging me?
I mean, there's, it's, it's like nothing new.
It's just, there's lots of strikes happening right now.
And like lots of strikes in lots of different fields in the UK.
There's rails, worker strikes, there's ambulance strikes,
there's nurses strikes, there's postal worker strikes,
all of which are very important during the cold and Christmasy month.
Is there a reason they're all happening at the same time?
It's just because the, because of the Ukraine war, the price of living.
Because the, because the gas companies don't have like a cap on how much they can charge.
They're just charged as much as they fucking can.
People are getting to a point where they can't use their, their heating
and they can't like cook food really.
And they can't buy things.
They cut, they just have no money.
And the, the pay for all of these people all over the country has not risen to match it.
And so they're basically everybody all over the place.
It's just said, we can't afford to live anymore.
We literally can't afford to live.
We're all going on strike.
And I'm like, hell yes, please go on strike.
I see.
But then I see like politicians saying, don't they care about the,
the sanctity of Christmas?
Don't they care about like, yes, yes, Christmas pilled.
They're like, this is supposed to be a nice holiday and they're ruining it for everyone.
I'm like, the people who are negatively affected by, you know,
not having enough money are also not going to have a good Christmas.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck you.
The people, they're not letting down the country by going on strike.
They are the country.
Right.
And you, yeah.
I mean, of course.
It's just so frustrating.
That sucks.
I mean, I think they kind of, I think we talked about, they kind of,
they kind of crushed that like rail workers strike in America.
Yeah.
They didn't, they didn't get what they, they didn't get the sick leave that they wanted,
which is pretty cringe.
There was something else I wanted to say.
Okay.
It's not quite the same, but that really reminds me of the Elon thing from this week.
Do you see the thing about like the tracking his jet?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Deadly, are you, are you, are you following?
I'm back now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw your back.
Are you following Elon on Twitter?
Are you familiar with his?
I try not to.
Yeah.
It's just tiring.
It is, it's, it's tiring, but I mean, I don't follow his account.
Yeah.
But certain things that he's doing is like,
in like unbelievably like embarrassing for him, like it's so weird.
It's funny because it seems like it's so, like it's so embarrassing,
the hypocrisy is so naked.
And yet like the, the fact that like it continues and that like consequences are
not materializing for him is like so, it makes me really upset and it frustrates me
almost more than it amuses me.
Um, but, um, yeah, the, if he gets his comeuppance one day, then I'll look back on it very fondly,
but if he never does, then I will just have been infuriated for nothing.
But anyway, the thing this week where like, you know, he specifically said,
I won't ban the account that posts my jet, my jets, like, uh, location.
And then he did ban the account that posted the jets location.
And then he did.
And then he, and then he banned reporters who reported that he banned that account,
which again is only public posting public information.
And then the justification for this is first, he called them all doctors,
even the people that merely reported on the fact that he banned the account.
He called them all doctors because they were like referencing the fact that the account existed.
And, and then he, and then he, he said that he said that the account had to be banned
because like his kid was on, you know, it was assassination coordinates.
It was updating his location in real time and it's a safety issue and they're putting him
at risk and they're putting his family at risk.
And it's so amazingly, amazingly annoying.
I didn't really see that many people point out that like, if it's unsafe,
like it's not, it's not fair to be like, you know, you can't post my jets info
because that exposes my location.
And it's like, well, no, nobody else uses a private jet.
If you don't, it's public information where a jet is.
If you don't want your location publicly revealed, you could simply not fly on a public jet.
Like nobody's forced you to put your kid on the fucking jet and which supposedly endanger him.
Like you endangered him by putting him on a jet who's like,
if you think that's dangerous, that his location is known,
you're the one that made that information public by putting him on the fucking jet.
Man, it's multiple levels of like incompetence and misunderstanding of how anything works.
I think the reason, I don't know whether this is true,
but I get the feeling that the reason he suddenly started feeling scared for his life
because of the Elon jet and stuff is because he went on that Dave Chappelle show
and everyone booed him when he came on stage.
I'm honestly surprised that that happened.
I thought that I thought it was like Twitter that hates him.
I didn't realize that like the real people hate him.
I kind of thought the real people are just like neutral on him
or think that he's cool because he was on the Simpsons.
I mean, he's done so many like very publicly weird stupid things
during the whole getting of Twitter.
Yeah, but like I kind of thought that was like only Twitter people would care about that.
I didn't think that like the average person would give a shit,
but like, oh, he charged eight dollars for Twitter blue or something, right?
I just kind of thought that wouldn't matter to like the average Dave Chappelle audience member.
I suppose it is a bit weird.
I feel like it's just because Twitter is so like linked with normal people
as well as Twitter weirdos that anything that blows up on Twitter,
especially with somebody who's so high profile that he bought,
you know, he's in charge of the entire site.
Like a lot more normal people are being exposed to the funny things that he's doing
and the embarrassing things that he's doing to make more people just find it like through
journalism or otherwise.
I don't think the average person is like a regular Twitter user though.
No, but like that's it's big news, right?
BBC reports on Elon Musk's Twitter bullshit quite often.
I see. I wonder if like, I wonder if like sometimes I'll go to my parents' house and
they'll be watching like Colbert.
Is it the late show with Colbert?
I know he doesn't do the Colbert report anymore.
Whatever.
The Colbert report?
Are you not familiar with the Colbert report?
I thought it was the Colbert report.
You, well, you've clearly never seen it then because no, it's the Colbert report.
I mean, you know what it was, right?
I thought it was the reports though, like the Colbert report.
I mean, yes, it's spelled that way, but just like the T in Colbert is silent,
they pronounce the, they pronounce the report silently as well.
But there's a word called report, like, and it's spelled different.
Yes.
Look, look, I don't know what to tell you that they, they pronounced it the Colbert report.
And you know, you know that the shtick of it was that he basically like,
he was, he was basically like a satire of a right wing pundit, right?
Vaguely, yes.
Well, now, well, now he is no longer a satire.
Now he's just a, now he's just a, just a lib.
He's just a lib.
But sometimes I'll see, I'll see my parents watching Colbert report and he'll say like,
and he'll, you know, and he'll repeat back to me my, my DNC approved, you know, my liberal
opinions, my, my, my safe, my safe Democrat communist opinions that have been filtered
through, you know, global homo and fed back to me by George Soros.
He'll say NFTs bad.
He'll say, you know, Russia bad.
He'll say, you know, transphobia bad.
And I'll say, and I'll say, yes, I love, I love it when I'm told what to think by the establishment.
And then I'll, and then I'll take one microchip out of my NPC head and I'll put a new microchip
into my NPC head and the cycle continues.
And I'm glad my parents are getting their microchips from the right guys.
What is what is the point that I'm trying to make?
Okay.
Deadly comics, what is your extreme political opinions?
Yeah, what's your, I got so many.
What's your most cancelable?
What's your most cancel?
What's your most cancelable opinion about trans people?
It should be given.
All gun rights revoked except the trans people.
Okay.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right.
Okay.
You know what?
All right.
That's pretty good.
Guns are great.
Only in the right hands.
Gun girl.
Um, okay.
Good answer.
Go on.
Tell me more.
Oh no.
More, more takes, more takes.
Who should be assassinated next?
Let's see.
I mean, there's so many.
I know.
It's a smorgasbord.
Acornicopia.
Yeah.
Man.
I'll give you a hint.
It's um.
It's been saying.
I don't know.
I actually have no idea.
What does.
There's no, there's no wrong answers really.
When does murder become assassination?
It has to be a public figure, right?
Is that, is that the definition?
I don't know.
That's what it seems like.
Like if you can't assassinate your roommate,
if no one knows who your roommate is.
I, hmm, that's a, you know, this is a question.
This is a, I've always thought of assassination.
Yes, as a public figure thing, but also as like premeditated to an extent that
it's, it's for a specific like end rather than an emotional like I need this person dead.
Okay.
Well, according to.
Like if you're, if you're just mad at someone and you kill them, that's murder.
But if you have a political agenda and you need somebody dead, that's assassination.
Okay.
But assess like celebrities can be assassinated to even if it's not political.
Do you think I would, I would call like the Jung Lenin shooting a murder though.
Well, apparently according to dictionary.com assassination is murder,
murder of an important person in a surprise attack for political or religious reasons.
Okay.
Wikipedia says it is the murder of a prominent or important person.
Uh, well, that's it.
That's all Wikipedia says.
So Wikipedia doesn't even stipulate that it has to be like a surprise attack or for.
I always think of an assassination as a, as a ninja coming in.
Ninja coming in your room with a little, with a small katana.
I forget what they're called.
And then go.
A Waki Zashi.
Waki Zashi and they go on your neck.
That's an assassination.
That is, that should be the definition.
That's a textbook assassination for sure.
Premeditated act of assassination.
Premeditated act of killing someone suddenly or secretively, especially a prominent person.
Okay.
Some of these definitions emphasize the secretiveness of the killing.
Some of them emphasize the prominence of the victim.
Some of them emphasize the, the political or religious like significance of the act itself.
I think JFK was assassinated and John Lennon was murdered.
Seems right.
For some reason.
Because John Lennon's killer was like just a weirdo.
I mean, I, I could say, I could say.
I don't think he had a point.
He just sort of like, I want him, I just, I'm just going to kill him.
Didn't he do it for like some satanic panic, like he's corrupting the youth kind of reasons?
No, I'm not sure.
I mean, John Lennon is prominent.
So he is a, he is a prominent or important person.
So by that metric, it could be an assassination.
I guess, I guess the distinction I'm making is like, how, how like deranged are you as the killer?
So if you are not deranged, so what you're saying is that assassination is murdered is good.
No, assassination is murdered as cold blooded and emotionless for some, for some specific agenda.
And murder is like, you can just, you could just, it could just happen.
If you're, you know, a little crazy.
Well, I mean, the guy tracked down John Lennon specifically to kill him.
It wasn't like he just did it on a whim.
Well, no, not the premeditated part of it is the same for both.
But like the reason you decide to do it in the first place.
Are you deranged or are you, are you putting politics into my murder?
I hate it when there's politics in my murder.
Murders these days are too political.
Absolutely.
We need to go back.
Yeah, we used to have characters.
We used to have Jack the Ripper.
Used to have, you know, when they had like little, little things they did with the police,
little notes and things they would leave.
What happened to that?
They were nice.
They were nice and neutral.
They didn't, they didn't discriminate except when they only killed women or whatever.
But you know, that's just, that's just good fun.
Assassination classroom.
That I used, I have so many of those comics.
I never finished it.
I've read some of it.
I think, I think Mage got me to read it and I thought it was okay.
I thought it was kind of neat, but I didn't stick with it.
It's assassination classroom, the one with the main character who is a boy that looks
extremely feminine because the author wanted it to be a girl.
But the manga publisher says, no, we kind of have a female lead.
I don't think so.
I mean, that, I think that is, well, the character does look feminine.
And no, that was like the backstory to it, though.
I'm pretty sure that was the backstory to that.
Assassination classroom is the one with like the yellow smiley alien guy.
Yeah, yeah.
But like the protagonist, like main character.
Oh, I think he's a school person.
Oh, I don't know.
People ask, is assassination classroom inappropriate?
For what?
I don't know.
It's just,
I mean, you couldn't have that in a school, in a school library.
Kids with guns.
Yeah, it's not assassination.
It keeps doing murder politically again.
You can't have, you can't have depictions of guns in a school library.
I mean, not when the kids are holding them and shooting the teachers with it.
Yeah, the rob pretending to shoot you.
But she doesn't, but he doesn't actually get shot though.
He dodges really quickly out of the, so like, it's fine.
Yeah, assassination.
Well, like, they don't want to give the kids ideas
that they should try to assassinate their teachers.
Come on.
It's not me making the rules.
I'm just saying how it is weak.
Right.
This is the, this is the guy.
This is the male lead of the assassination classroom.
Eating a snack, holding the gun.
It's a knife snack.
Well, I forget why I read it.
So maybe it's incorrect, but it seems plausible.
Like, oh, you can't have, you can't have a shounen mango with a female protagonist.
We just don't do that over here because they don't.
Can we?
Do they?
Do they not?
The boy seems to be a boy.
Yeah, well, it is shounen jump.
Ain't it?
Boys can't read things with girls in it.
I'm trying to think if I can think of any shounen shows that have, I mean, um...
There's lots of female characters.
They're just always side characters or love interests or villains or whatever.
I mean, I can think of some animes with female protagonists,
but I'm not sure exactly which ones are shounen.
Yeah, like you specifically because it was in shounen jump, like
so shounen jump publisher.
Yeah.
That's what I heard, which is a funny story.
And it means that this guy is extremely effeminate and cute.
That's why I kind of wanted to read it, but I forgot.
I sort of lost interest somewhere.
I mean, Chrono Crusade has a female protagonist.
I don't know if that is shounen.
It probably is not from shounen jump.
I'm looking at a bunch of shounen jump covers and yes, it's all fellas.
As far as the eye can see.
It's all boys.
Well, now I'm wondering if there's ever been one with a girl.
Not in shounen jump.
I'm pretty sure.
So look at this, the fucking ninja turtle looking cover.
Yeah.
Every cover is just that with a different color, like a different expression.
This is the Japanese Watchman because of the smile.
I guess so.
I mean, Soul Eater has, I mean, it's got kind of like two protagonists and one of them is a girl.
Was that shounen jump?
I don't know if it's from jump.
Yeah, I would say it's shounen, at least.
It's definitely shounen.
Japanese manga.
Published by Square Enix.
Where is it?
Where does it come from?
Published by Square Enix in monthly shounen gang gang.
What?
Okay, so it's not shounen jump, but it is a shounen thing.
Shounen gang gang?
Monthly shounen gang gang is a manga in print owned by Square Enix Holdings.
That's funny.
Never heard of Square Enix doing non-video game stuff.
Oh, I mean, that doesn't surprise me.
They're like a pretty big company.
They have their fingers in a lot of Japanese culture pies.
I could go for some Japanese culture pie right about now.
I don't think the Japanese know what a pie even is.
I just don't think that that's a dish that they make.
They have dumplings, they have funny bread.
Exactly, exactly.
If the Japanese were going to make a pie, they would just make it as a dumpling.
They would just put blueberries and apples and cherries in a dumpling.
That sounds great, actually.
It probably could be pretty good, yeah.
Yeah, little steamed fruit, is that such a thing?
Sure, and I know this because in Pokemon, they eat fruit sandwiches, which are rice balls.
I know cakes are big.
Yeah, cakes are big.
My mind is blown just thinking that, yeah, I've never seen a chicken pie with the pastry
in a Japanese thing.
I don't think they do it.
I don't think they, I think it's a Western thing.
Wow, well, it's a European thing, which is a Western thing.
But also, surely they have pastry.
I mean, of course.
I mean, I'm sure they know what a pie is, and they could make one if they wanted to.
I just don't think they do very often.
And if they did, it would probably be like, oh yeah, this is like a European-style dish.
I looked up pie in Japan, and the first result says Japanese consumers love pie.
Boo, I don't care what they say.
That doesn't fit my narrative.
Okay, well.
Pastries in Japan.
I understand nice patisserie.
They probably have a lot of French things and Swiss stuff, Swiss rolls.
Wait, now I'm curious.
But Japanese-y-fying, some of them.
Wait, what does it say?
A pie with filling.
Do they have those?
What does it say about Japanese people that eat pie?
I want to know.
Oh, I closed the page.
Oh, come on.
I'm looking up choco pie now.
I'll never know.
My internet's broken again.
Once again, even though this call is continuing without issue, my computer says,
nope, you're not connected to the internet.
You can't view web pages right now.
A square choco pie.
It's fluffy with marshmallow filling.
I like the fact that they say it's fluffy.
I don't know why that's funny to me.
It's a good thing to have trademarked.
They trademarked it's fluffy.
I guess so.
I want to bake something.
I think I need that.
I think I need a baking session.
I need to make some muffins or cupcakes or something.
Gingerbread.
Maybe I could make a gingerbread thing for the Christmas.
It's very effeminate.
Yeah, thank you.
Gingerbread house is going to start big.
Or gingerbread man, gingerbread woman.
My dad has made gingerbread houses for Christmas party.
Oh, centerpiece.
But also you can grab it and tear it apart and eat it.
So I know that's possible.
I could do that together.
That'd be fun.
Nice, yeah.
What if I made a gingerbread...
How do you do a gingerbread trans woman?
They're just called two arms, two legs.
How would you differentiate them?
You start by making a man and then you turn it into a woman.
By like adding a dress or something.
I don't know, it's easy.
But how would you do a gingerbread man?
You do a penis in the middle.
Yeah, and then you use three legs.
And then you yank it off of there.
You yank it off.
To be a man, you must have honor and a penis.
That's what Shin Chan says.
Very regressive of him.
Shin Chan.
You remember Shin Chan.
Is that the little tiny little guy?
Yes.
Dang.
That's the one.
I didn't know he was cringe.
Such a transphobe, I know.
Wait, you know who that is?
It's the cartoon...
It's the little kid, the little red shirt.
The cartoon toddler, yeah.
Who shows his little butt.
I'm not sure if he's a toddler.
I think he might be...
I haven't read any of it.
I'm not sure.
I'm not exactly sure how old he's supposed to be.
It's very unique looking.
Yeah.
I like the style.
He's got a game out on the switch that looks really good.
You ever see the English dub of that show?
Yeah, that's how I started it.
That was where they redubbed it all with Americanized jokes.
They changed a lot of it.
But I think it's good and it works.
And it's maybe funnier for it.
They sort of like...
I don't know.
They kind of change it to be a little bit more goofy and fourth wall breaking.
Whereas I think in Japan, it's a more straightforward family sitcom.
Because I think some of the humor plays as a little more adult over here in America.
Shinchin shown as disgusting little baby dick.
It just doesn't play.
So it just hits different.
It just hits different over here.
Oh yeah, you can put them PBS kids over here.
I don't think so.
It's got to be an adult show now.
I think so.
LaMalle.
Merry Christmas.
Is this the Christmas special?
When is this coming out?
This is close to Christmas when this comes out.
Yeah, it's the week away now.
It'll be the 23rd.
It'll be the day before Christmas Eve.
Christmas Eve Eve.
My torrents are downloading at about half a megabyte per second and yet no internet lol.
It's getting slipped up by the torch.
I'm just so upset.
It's just not fair.
You know, it's like my internet.
It's like my internet.
You know, it likes me.
It's showing clear interest in me.
It's asking me questions about like, oh, do I live around here?
Oh, you know, it's getting on my bus with me.
But then when I ask if it wants to go out for coffee, it just laughs.
Then I ask, can you show me the images in my discord channel?
It just scoffs at me.
It just scoffs.
Well, what else?
What else have we got to speak about?
Well, now I'll never get to see this list of strongest female shown in characters.
I was pulling up a list.
I was going to go through the list and I was going to
find some good counter examples, but I guess, I guess it maybe it did appear,
but it was completely blank.
Yeah, it won't look because it doesn't exist.
I'm so stupid.
I'm sure there's more.
The only ones I can think of are Chrono Crusade and Soul Eater.
I mean, obviously there are more.
Chrono Crusade actually might be sign-in.
That might be a little too adult.
Not sure.
Who cares?
Are we moving on?
Okay.
What were you saying, Deadly?
I forget.
What was I saying?
Oh yeah, something I watched recently.
I want to know if anyone else has seen it.
It's the Adult Swim Yule Log video.
The Yule Log video.
Is that like one that you put on for Christmas and it just burns the log all day?
That's what you would expect from Yule Log video.
I haven't seen this.
I'm familiar with the genre, but no, I have not seen the Adult Swim one.
Okay, it's the kind of thing that is not a good thing to talk about because doing so would spoil it.
Have you ever seen the short Too Many Cooks?
Yes.
Oh, yes, yes.
It's the same creator had his hand in this.
So if you enjoyed that, I recommend watching the Adult Swim Yule Log.
That was all right.
Am I right in thinking that's the guy who did that series on YouTube about a character who was trapped
in an insane asylum and then there was a blue chair.
There was a repeating motif.
Blue chair?
Are you talking about Alan Tutorial?
Yeah, maybe.
Alan Tutorial, that's not the same guy.
Alan Rosnick though, he's got some crazy good stuff.
He did an edited footage of a bear.
I think that's one people know him for.
He did May Please Enter.
He did a lot of cool stuff.
But that's a different guy, I think.
Dang, I thought it was the same guy.
Yeah, Alan Tutorial.
This was fucked.
That was a great series.
I love crazy stuff like this, like great minds coming up with
such stuff and I'm watching it.
That's what I like.
I like crazy people.
Crazy people, please make more art.
This I recommend from him.
May you please enter.
It's a good story.
How long is the Yule Log?
It's like an hour and a half.
Oh, okay.
I found one that's like three minutes.
Dang, it's on HBO Max.
I see.
Well, okay.
Well, obviously I can't watch it right now then.
Lol.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Sell it down for it.
That's all.
Oh my gosh.
Next discussion topic.
I found the list.
Oh, I finally get those shonen girls.
I've never heard of that one.
Yep.
It's the sole leader girl.
Never heard of that one.
Search where they put the marketing budget.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ryuko Matoi from Kill a Kill.
Is that she?
That's it.
I mean, it's definitely not shonen jump.
It's not saying in.
I think you could argue it's shonen.
Definitely.
Yeah.
She's a good candidate.
I like her.
I think that one's fair.
Never heard of that one.
I've never heard of that one.
From like the Dragon Ball creators early work.
Oh, Dr. Slump.
Is that a thrill?
Yeah, yeah.
Is that a shonen?
I thought it was just a comedy.
That's a shonen jump comedy.
Oh, it was on cut.
Yeah.
Wait, what was it called?
It's called Dr. Slump.
Oh, yeah.
Dr. Slump.
Okay.
Yeah, I've heard of it.
I've never read it.
I should read it at some point.
It's clearly going to have like things like, oh, shit.
That's where that Dragon Ball thing came from.
Over and over again.
Yeah.
All right, these are not.
These are not fucking shonen.
These lists sucks.
Never mind.
Okay.
All right.
That's just proven my point.
There are none.
Need more women.
We need more Clarissa Gunsmokes and shonen jump.
I guess I am wondering now if there's ever been a single one specifically from shonen jump.
That would be interesting.
There's probably been at least one and then it probably was a flop and they were like,
well, I guess we'll never do that again.
Yeah.
There's something that just don't get like translated that don't last more than a few chapters.
We never find out about them.
Yeah, for sure.
Ooh, related 15 Naruto characters you definitely want as a roommate.
I'm clicking that one.
Uh, Gara, because if you get sand in your between your toes, you could just get it right off.
Well, Shikimaru, because he would be uninvasive.
Neji, because he's clean and organized.
Sakura, because she says what she feels and cares deeply for her friends.
Choji, because he's a nice guy with great snacks.
Kiba, because he has a lovable canine companion.
Hinata, because she's nice and cooks amazing food.
It's just every character.
Naruto, because he would never say no to a trip to Ichiraku.
I don't know what that means.
Is that the ramen place?
Probably.
He would never say no to ramen.
That's why you want him as a roommate.
Great quality and a roommate.
Kakashi, because he could teach you how to be cool.
What the fuck?
Tsunade's decades of life lessons lend themselves as interesting stories.
That's awful.
Konoha?
Wait, the Konoha Gate guys would always be happy to hang
just those two guys who don't even have names.
Oh, Izumo and Kotetsu.
Just because they're nice.
Ebisu is highly responsible if a bit overbearing.
Well, why is he a good roommate if he's a bit overbearing?
Oh, we're getting higher up on the list, by the way.
Konan, because he isn't such a bad person after all.
He's in reverse order.
A redeemed gara would be easy to get along with.
Asuma Sarutobi is a cool uncle.
And number one, Tenten always keeps her cool around others.
I am going to shoot myself.
That list started off almost tolerable.
Maybe I missed something, but Tenten is almost a joke
in that she basically has no lines in the entire manga.
She doesn't say it, she doesn't have any,
there's no exploration into her as a person at all.
It's everyone else.
She's just because they needed a third partner for Neji.
Like, I'm sure there's like a couple lines saying,
oh, she's nice or she does this and maybe she makes a face.
But they never focus on her ever.
Not that I can recall now, lol.
She's the number one roommate
because she always keeps her cool around others.
Garbage.
Maybe that's fair.
Maybe the others are a little too extreme.
They're all crazy.
Why would you want to live with them?
No, Shikimaru was right.
The good one is right,
because Shikimaru would just leave you alone
and just not want to be bothered.
Yeah, Shikimaru is good.
Shikimaru and Neji.
No, I think Neji would be.
I think Neji would be a picky.
He would like, he would like-
Neji would be kind of cunty.
He would be kind of cunty and he would be like, you know,
why'd you leave, why'd you leave dishes,
why'd you leave dishes in the sink?
We agree that we would keep the common space clean at all times.
You're violating the terms of our roommate agreement.
You're violating the pact.
Violating the pact, the main family wouldn't do this.
The main family wouldn't leave dishes unscrubbed.
Keep Kiba because he has a dog.
That's awful.
Okay, I've done, I'm done.
No more, no more.
He specifically has a move with his dog
where he pisses all over the place.
Is that true?
Yeah, I think that's one of his comedy moves early on,
where he's like, haha, I got a dog.
Watch this.
It's a trick I call the urination nation.
Why doesn't he just-
Spins around with dog pisses everywhere.
Piss his own piss.
If he just wants to piss on people,
why doesn't he just pee himself?
He may do that, I forget if he does.
He acts like a dog, he's a real like-
With his dog, he has twice the piss.
Yeah.
He's double the-
Twice, that's a small dog.
He gets bigger.
Oh, I have not got that point yet.
The time skip, he's a wolf dog.
It becomes big.
I'm thinking about early dog.
I'm still early in the series.
I'm behind on so many things.
Wait, when did you get into watching or reading Naruto?
Um, I guess a few weeks ago.
I'm only at teaching exams now.
Well, that's the best part.
That's what everyone says.
And I'm having a good time.
That part's really good.
And then, I don't know, it's okay up until the time skip.
And then I think at, well, I don't know,
the anime kind of falls apart after the time skip.
It got really filler, heavy,
and I stopped watching around there.
I mean, I was young when I was watching it,
so I watched everything without knowing what filler was.
That's just like, why was the last like 50 episodes
just about stuff?
When are they gonna get back to Sasuke?
When are they gonna get back to him?
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
I'll enjoy it while I can then.
Oh, yeah, I mean, I wouldn't say
it becomes shit.
It just sort of keeps going
and doesn't raise the stakes in a way that feels like,
like the stakes are raised, but I just sort of like, eh,
oh, oh, bigger and more powerful ninjas.
Yeah, sure.
It felt more scary in a battle with ninjas early on
with like Zabusa.
He's like, got a big sore and he'll fucking kill you.
Yeah, Zabusa was pretty scary.
It does feel like they're just scraping by a lot of the time.
Yeah.
And then later on, it's just sort of, I mean, that's the normal,
that's the normal shonen thing with like power level scaling
where the things they are capable of doing far outstrip
normal human capabilities,
so you can't quite connect to the danger they're in anymore.
Like if you see them take a thousand blows,
like blows, it's hard to know how many more blows they can take,
because I've never even taken one blow like that.
I'd be killed instantly.
Yes.
Like, I like things to be grounded in reality.
If a bullet is fired, it should be,
it should, you should be scared of the character getting shot
in the head and being,
It should kill you if it hits you.
Does this apply to one piece?
Because I feel like the opposite happens there.
I mean, I'm still early on,
but none of the guys Luffy has faced so far
seem to be much trouble for him.
Ah, well, with that, it starts off like, he's super strong.
In the same way that Dragon Ball starts off,
Goku is just stronger than everyone,
and it's kind of a comedy because of how strong he is,
and he's a tiny little kid.
But then it becomes more serious later on.
And I think one piece does that.
The first chapter, I think,
Luffy gets shot with a bunch of bullets,
like, ha, fuck you, or he gets shot with a bullet from a gun.
And you think, oh, shit.
But no, it goes, it stretches out inside him,
and then he like unstretches,
and he blasts the bullet back because he's made a rubber.
How did that happen?
And it's like, that's so crazy.
Bullets can't hurt this guy.
This guy's insane, but bullets very quickly
don't become important after that.
Yeah, it's the kind of joke you could only do once.
How, wait, you're not very far into it.
How far are you?
I got pretty far in high school up until Chopper shows up,
but then I forgot everything that happened
because I went to college and learning pushed it all out of my mind.
So I'm starting over now.
I see.
Yeah, that's, I mean, that's, it's kind of far,
but it's in the grand scheme of things.
It's actually not that far.
I know, it's not, it's not crazy far.
It's only like 10 volumes or something.
I think Chopper, Drum Island,
I'm trying to think of like the first time it feels like
it's actually like they could fucking all die.
And I think it's, it's maybe like the giant island
where Mr. Three gets them all in the wax.
And it's unsure.
It's like unclear how they're gonna get out of it.
I don't, damn it.
I mean, obviously there's danger.
I don't like super like remember that very well.
It's, it's the island with the two giants on it,
Dorian Broggy.
Oh, yes.
They're fight.
And then there being a, there's Miss, Miss.
Oh, what's the little girl with the paint?
It's called Miss Golden Week, I think.
Yeah.
Which is a Japanese holiday.
And then Mr. Three who has the wax devil fruit.
And they, and there also is like Miss Valentine
and Mr. Something.
Valentine is the spiky one, right?
No, oh, Miss Wednesday.
I can't remember.
But she's the one who like changes her white
and the guy who shoots boogers.
Oh, hers is cool.
Her fruit is cool, the weight, the weight changing one.
Yeah.
So those people are there and they're on this island
with the giants and they get all separated with stuff.
And then there's a part where Mr. Three makes this giant wax cake
and he gets them all waxed up and they can't leave.
And they're being turned into wax sculptures with this candle at the top.
That's like raining down wax particles.
And Zoro is like, well, I may as well strike a cool pose if I'm going to die.
So he holds his sword up.
I remember that very fondly.
Yeah.
That was a big like, oh, shit, is Zoro going to die?
He tries to cut his own legs off to get out of there.
I feel like I feel like I felt like they were in real danger like against
I think, I mean, against, I think it was against Kuma.
Or what's the one where like...
Spoilers.
Oh, yeah, never mind.
I'm sure by the time I get there, I will have forgotten.
Yeah.
I only mentioned the giant island because that's past, that's before they meet Chopper.
Right, right.
I vaguely remember that.
What can I say without spoiling too much?
I like One Piece.
Yeah, I like One Piece.
It is so fucking good.
Yeah, One Piece is not grounded in that way at all.
Even early on, I remember watching the anime and there's like a moment where
Nami changes her mind and decides to jump on the boat as they're leaving that little town.
This is before Arlong Park or anything.
Is there no new, there's no new chapter this week?
No, this wasn't a bummer.
It was on a break.
Damn.
But like she jumps and she jumps like 14 feet.
Like it's just like a super long jump, but it's not like mentioned as like a
superhuman feat of strength or special abilities.
It's just sort of like, yeah, people can jump really a lot.
That's just sort of a thing in anime or manga where like the superpowers are so insane that
like normal actions are also kind of like brought up to insanity.
That's kind of why.
They can jump off of the second story of a building and just land on the ground and not be
like broken-legged.
That's kind of why I feel like I wasn't that upset by the
I won't say what it is, but like the reveal about that fruit, that one particular fruit,
you know, the one didn't bother me that much because like we really already well past the
point where like these characters are powerful to the point that like you can't really relate to
them.
They can like take cannonballs to the face and like mostly be fine nine out of 10 times.
Yeah.
I think what I really appreciate about One Piece is more so the emotional
connections that they make and sort of the visceral like catharsis of seeing the bad guy
get punched really hard after being a real shithead.
It's I don't know how it's different from other shounen, but One Piece just does it really good.
They set up the villain so that you're so happy when they get punched.
Oh, man.
I feel like in Naruto, it's a little.
I really like there's a lot of emo stuff that's just sort of doesn't.
What was the feel the same?
Yeah.
What was the name of the villain in the Fishman Island arc?
Fishman Island.
Yeah.
That would be Hody Jones.
Hody Jones.
Hody Jones was so I hated him so much.
They did such a good job of making me hate that guy.
Oh, and Van der Decken.
That was the other guy.
Something Van der Decken.
Who the fuck is that?
Hody Jones was the Fishman and something Van der Decken was another Fishman who had the
devil fruit of throwing.
Oh, he could touch something and throw it at you and it would find you.
Yeah.
I sort of remember this guy.
Did he do anything?
Yeah.
He was the reason the boat, the Moby Dick or whatever it was called.
Like the giant ship, the Noah's Ark.
Yeah, that thing.
He touched that boat and threw it and he threw it at Fishman Island and they had to stop it.
Oh, I forgot.
I forgot.
He's the reason that was happening.
And I think Luffy punched it.
Yeah, but Hody Jones was like the leader.
He was the leader of the punk shark bastards or whatever they were called.
No, not the Sun Pirates.
Those are the good guys.
The Fun Pirates.
They're all Fun Pirates.
What was the name?
Wasn't it like, oh, didn't they have, they had like a tattoo and then they covered it up with
the Sun Pirate Tattoo, right?
Yeah, the Fishman were slaves and they had a brand marked on them front by the Tenryubito.
And so Fisher Tiger, like the freer of the Fishman slaves, the big boy, he turned that
branding into a new logo that would be the Sun Pirate logo.
Did Hody Jones, were they Sun Pirates too?
I don't remember.
I think they were like, they knew Arlong, who was a Sun Pirate guy.
Yeah, I forget if like, maybe they, the Hody Jones guys were not actually Sun Pirates.
I can't remember.
I thought maybe they did something else with the tattoo.
Looks like you're gonna have to read it again.
I guess I'll have to read it all again.
It's so great.
Oh, Hody Jones has, he's got like a different, he's got like a different tattoo.
Like, look at this.
Oh, he, oh, he's got like the big sun.
He's got like the racist version of the Sun Pirates tattoo.
Lol, so awesome.
What a little, little bastard.
Yeah, it's the sun, but on the inside is like the no humans.
No humans, that's his thing.
They love Hody Jones.
The most despicable villain.
They all got great names.
Yes, I love Otis naming conventions.
They're just so satisfying.
Like Thriller Bark as an island, as a ship.
I love that.
I just, I just love it.
Skypia.
Tell us how you really feel about it though.
Um, uh, I hate it.
Okay, that's cool.
Nice.
I'm sad.
There's no new episode.
I didn't realize they were on break, bummer.
I think it said break next week on the chapter.
Oh, well.
It's funny that Otis can just do that whenever he wants.
What are they going to tell him?
No.
I mean, he's a hard-working guy, but yeah.
I mean, many manga authors go on like hiatuses to like,
to like just still, you know, take a break after like years of
consistently producing high quality stuff.
To take a break after years of coming.
But Oda, Oda takes like a maximum like two weeks of a break sometimes.
Yeah.
Which is like, it's so, people still get mad about it, but it's like, it's unbelievable.
How much good shit he's made consistently for how many years?
Like 25 years?
How long has it been?
Uh, it's gotta be at least like 20 years.
Yeah.
1997.
Uh, that's why that's, um,
Check this out.
23 years and then 22.
Check it out.
It's the Virgin, Hodey Jones versus the Chad Arlong.
Racist for no reason.
It has a good reason to hate humans.
Uh, oh, that's right.
Hodey Jones wasn't a slave.
He was just, he was like of the generation after.
Yeah.
He was the generation after he literally just like carried on hating humans for no reason at all.
He just like, he just thought it was like what he should do as like part of like fishman culture.
Literally just like, we have to return to the good old days of hating humans.
Cause like, I just think things, I know I wasn't born back then.
I just think things were probably better back then.
He's literally like that.
Villain of the Ark where the series went from good to great.
That's true.
I think that's true.
I, yeah, I would say that as well.
I think at the time I remember thinking like, like the Arlong arc was where I was like, okay,
I think, I think this is actually, I really like the series now.
How long, when does that come about?
That's, that's when Nami joins.
That's when Nami joins.
That's pretty early.
It's in East Blue before the grand line.
So that's pretty early on.
But it's, it's such a cool moment cause it's.
Yeah.
It starts off goofy enough, but the, the, the villain is stronger than any other villain so far.
And it's just, they build him up to be such a, like a ruthless person that couldn't,
could not possibly be toppled.
The whole town is scared of him.
And then Luffy and the boys, they just roll up.
They barely know what's going on.
Luffy has no idea and he doesn't want to know.
He just knows that Nami's crying and he healed protector.
So he goes into the, he just barges in to the bad, big bad like guy that has been built up.
To be so dangerous.
And then they just fight and he destroys the building and he destroys.
Oh, and the moment, the moment where he kicks like Nami is like,
like indentured servitude, slavery, like a map charting desk, kicks it out of the window
and she sees it and he just destroys the room where they kept Nami like hostage
and forced her to draw maps for them.
And she starts crying and then, and they just, he just destroys everything
and it comes out of the rubble and he asked Nami to join the crew or something.
I like when he, I like when he just, just deflects how strong he is.
He just like flips houses upside down just because he can do that.
Yeah, they arrive and they're like, what's up with this street?
All the houses are upside down.
Oh, that's because of the fishmen.
They're so strong.
Or along just does that just to fuck with people.
What an arc.
Yeah.
What a, what a story.
I don't know.
I mean, the fishman, the fishman arc, I don't know if I'd call it a nothing arc,
but it is like way too long.
It's, it's, yeah, it's, it felt a little bloated, I think.
Yeah.
The fishman island.
Much like Hody Jones himself with his big old puffer fish gut.
No, no, it's a good, no, it's a good character though.
I gotta get back to drawing Clarissa Gunsmoke.
I gotta get back to make my stupid book.
I've only got, oh fuck, I've only got like a week and a half to finish it.
Ha, ha, ha, I gotta draw a cover.
Oh no.
Everyone needs to like Clarissa Gunsmoke.
She's such a female character.
She's a leading role female character.
You gotta get her put in Shonen Jump.
I gotta go to Shonen Jump.
I say, hey, I know I'm not Japanese and I have a very odd art style
for, for a manga, but put this in there.
Hey, I know that like you don't, yeah, first of all, not Japanese.
Second of all, not a manga.
Second of all, female characters and you never do those.
But I've got a genius plan.
What if we had the first female character in a Shonen Jump manga
and it was Western and it wasn't manga?
And they're like, oh my god, I can't believe it.
Oh my god, we've gotta do it.
I never, nobody, I didn't think of this before.
What if we broke convention?
Ah!
I'll be there.
I'll be reading it.
And then I'll go on, I'll go on all the Japanese forums
and they'll say, oh, this sucks.
Fucking woman.
Yeah, but yeah, they'll say.
But I won't be able to read it.
I won't be able to read it, so I won't even feel bad.
They'll say, they'll say, they'll say this lady's got bold ideas
of taking this company in a new direction.
We're going to make her our assistant vice president.
And then all, everyone on the forums is,
and then, and then everyone, everyone on the west
is like, oh, oh, this crying soy face.
It's like, oh, this new vice president.
Oh, they put her manga in the thing.
It's not even manga.
Oh, it's a girl main character.
Oh, this is not even Japanese.
Oh, real Japanese people don't even know
what trans people are.
They're ruining culture.
It's colonizing it.
Oh no, I'm doing colonization.
And that seems like it would be pretty fun.
So let's do it.
Yeah, that's my new goal is to take
over, show and jump.
Time to colonize with my British genes.
I'm made for this.
I'm made for destroying other cultures.
This is what I was built for.
It's good to see someone use colonization
for good to destroy anime.
I'm feeling like are we getting on towards voicemail time?
I think so.
I don't want to kick you off deadly,
but I mean, we are at almost three hours.
And you would probably be bored by voicemails
because they would not have anything to do with you.
You know what I mean?
It doesn't have to do with me for me to be not bored.
Try to bully deadly comics off the show.
If you want to hang out for voicemails,
I mean, yeah, okay, we can do that.
I guess I just, you know, I just, you know,
I just like to politely assume that our guests
have better things to be doing.
But I mean, if you don't, I guess.
Not really.
Okay, all right.
Hell yeah.
Let's grab a, let me do that then.
Let's see how many we got this week.
Hopefully none.
Oh my God.
So people just record things and send them to you?
Yeah, they just, we have a website called Speakpipe
where people can just deposit.
Yeah, it's basically like a voicemail service.
Do you listen to them before you put them on the air?
We used to, but no, under my leadership,
we have adopted an anarchist philosophy
where whatever's there is what gets listened to.
Yeah.
And if it sucks, that's too bad.
And spoiler alert, it usually sucks.
No, that's not true.
No, that's fine.
No, we love it.
We get some good ones.
We do get some good ones.
All right.
Oh, hang on.
Hang on.
We got a message from Cheezy.
Hey, can I jump in on this?
I'm totally awake right now.
Cheezy, you're too late.
This is the end.
I guess, I guess we can.
I don't mind.
Just for the questions segment.
I get to meet a new person.
What do you think, deadly?
Should we let Cheezy jump in?
I love to meet new people.
Do you know who Cheezy is?
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, he's a comic artist who is funny
and he gets people mad at him on Twitter sometimes.
He loves clowns.
He does love clowns.
Who doesn't, right?
Oh, yeah.
But nobody loves them as much as Cheezy does.
Hey, Cheezy, how you doing?
I'm doing pretty good.
You got any, what?
What was that?
I was going to say, do you got any updates this week?
Do you have anything interesting happening in your week?
Anything interesting?
Did anything interesting happen to you?
In the week?
Did anything interesting happen to me?
Yes.
I'm asking if anything interesting happened to you this past week.
Wait, wait, let me get this straight.
You're asking, wait, hold up, hold up, wait, you're talking too fast.
Wait.
So you're asking me, me, if anything interesting happened to me
in the past seven days?
I am.
Which you're asking for?
Indeed.
Okay, all right.
Okay, anything interesting?
Okay, no.
Anything interesting?
Anything.
No rules.
Any, how much longer, how much longer is this going to be?
I just, I just want you to be clear because I don't want to say something and then I don't
want you to be like, oh, you can count.
We are, you have 10 seconds to answer the fucking question.
This time limit wasn't imposed at the beginning.
I don't like this.
All right, so I guess, no?
Okay, well, maybe something interesting happened.
I don't know.
My business.
Let's listen to the first voicemail.
The first voicemail is called Aiden.
And it will be Aiden and a Benton.
I have a cousin named Aiden who I saw yesterday, but his name is not spelled.
Hey, I can't, I can't, it's not, it's not posting.
It's not posting.
Lol.
Is there a, is there a cousin white?
Is he like a white guy?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
That's kind of cringe.
I guess that's a pretty, I guess that's a pretty white name.
All right, let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello.
This is Aiden and I'm reporting from the Rowdy fuckers cop killers.
And I was told by Marilyn to say hello to Ben and to call you a cop kisser.
You are a cop kisser.
Fuck you.
You're a bitch.
And finally, killers once again, bullying Ben
as they should.
Yeah, uh, I'm bullying you.
You're a nerd.
I bet you get wedgies at school and you never asked Veronica for her number.
And you still get upset about it to this day.
All right.
Okay.
Bye.
Y'all have a good podcast.
But I asked, but I did, but I asked, but I asked Bousra, but I asked Bousra
out for coffee.
Okay.
Look, I took my shot.
Yeah, I didn't ask Veronica for her number, but you know, I learned from that mistake.
I learned that you miss 100% of the shots you don't take.
I'm more of a Betty kind of guy than a Veronica kind of guy.
Which one's the blonde one?
Betty.
Is there like, wait, aren't they both like exactly the same except one is rich and the other's not?
Okay.
Betty is the girl next door.
She's like your childhood friend ever.
Veronica is implied to be like new to the school.
But they're both just kind of like catty bitches.
No, no.
Veronica's more catty.
But one of them is your another, the Japanese word, another Japanese word that I learned from Tim Rogers.
The one that means your childhood friend from a time before you can even remember.
And also you are in love, I guess.
Yeah.
Archie invented that.
Archie and Betty are that?
Oh, that's so sweet.
Yep.
Yeah, they invented it.
Another thing those Japanese stole from us.
Tezuka stole the idea.
Well, wait, was it Tezuka?
Nah, wait, was it Tezuka who popularized that?
That can't be.
No, I don't think so.
I don't think it even comes from like Osan, Osananajimi.
I think that's what it means.
You should, I got a suggestion for a new segment on the podcast.
Each episode you learn a new Japanese word.
And then over a course of like 5,000 episodes, you will know Japanese.
Only 5,000 words.
Gib, you know what is actually better?
Probably better than any of the action button reviews.
If you haven't watched an action button review and you want to watch something by Tim Rogers,
genuinely, you should watch the slow translation of Final Fantasy 7 is probably better than any of
the action buttons.
And that's a really good series.
Okay.
And that's where I learned the word Osananajimi.
Looks like you need to rewatch.
Nanna, nanna, nanna, nanna phone.
Where did I put that, where did I put that link?
Alright, hey, I like that this killer is bullying me.
You know what, it's good.
I like, I like that spunk.
I like that spirit.
I like to see the grit and gumption.
You passed the test.
Yeah, good, good on you.
Good, good effort.
Let's see if I can actually listen to my fucking messages again.
No, Gib, help.
Oh, should I post the next one?
Please.
Okay, the next one is called,
By the Ways, Prince Isolation at Twitter.com.
Wait, why is it down?
Why did it, why did it post like this?
Okay, it's not playing.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna kill myself.
Oh, the second one?
No, Ben, don't kill yourself.
I'm gonna kill myself.
So you just have sexy.
Ha ha, don't do that.
I'll never, I'll never, I'll never, I'll never have coffee with Busuda and I'll never get to hear
what Prince Isolation had to say in his speak pub.
So what's the point?
What's even the point of anything?
Ben, the most beta move ever is to let Trixie outlive you.
Really, what if she like makes like a 360 and she becomes the best YouTuber,
the best anti-tuber again on YouTube, huh?
Yeah, I should, I should, I should keep living just to make sure that that never happens.
You're right.
It's a little life going.
I'll keep, yeah.
You're the guy for them.
It's a wonderful life, but instead you make like all the potential futures,
you make like trans women's lives worse by staying alive.
Well, that's, well, that's the, that's the plot of the Christmas.
It's a terrible death.
That's the, that's the plot of a Christmas, the Christmas special of married with children.
You know about this?
In married with children, there's a, there's an, it's a wonderful life parody episode
and Al sees that in the world, in the, in the version of the world where he was never born,
everything is better.
And so it inspires him to, to keep on living because he, he hates them all and he wants to
like punish them.
I mean, he's like, I won't let them have that.
I don't want good things for them.
I'm going to come back to life and ruin it.
And that's what he does.
That's also the premise of the robot chicken skit where, where Wimpy from Popeyes
killed, he's about to kill himself.
But then the angel shows him the, the universe where he wasn't born and everything's better.
All in all, it has like huge titties, Popeyes and Blutos aren't enemies no more.
Everything's going perfectly.
And the angel just kills and the angel just kills Wimpy instead.
Oh wow, fairly odd parents did that as well.
Well, that's the whole genre now is anti.
It's a wonderful life.
Well, now, well, now I, well, now I have to wonder if, if whether married with children
was even the first one to do it.
I mean, it feels like an obvious joke, right?
Like, yeah, it kind of does, but your presence makes things worse.
I guess if you were, yeah, maybe no, now, hmm, I wonder.
Ben, if you didn't exist, Nate would have never gone into ponies.
Thus, those who would never have met Michelle.
I wonder, I wonder, I mean, Charles Dickens was really popular even in his own time.
I wonder if people were writing like parodies of it's a wonderful,
wait, no, that's not by Charles Dickens.
No, it's a film.
What was it from like the fifties?
Uh, I, I think so.
I mean, it was a, it was a big film.
I wonder, I wonder if people were parrot.
I wonder if whatever the, like the, the, the contemporary equivalent of like Saturday Night
Live was at the time, did like a parody of it where they were like, ha, ha, what if,
when you die, if it was actually good, if you never survived, never lived.
Fascinating.
Ah, man.
For the longest time, I thought that it's a wonderful life was read in by, um,
Rod Serlin, the creator of the Twilight Zone.
But really, I was missing form.
I wasn't him.
I thought it was because like the whole premise feels like
the Twilight Zone Christmas special almost.
A little bit.
Yeah.
I see what you, I see what you're saying.
1947.
That's like two years after World War II ended.
Yeah.
And I saw they said it was communist propaganda.
Um, and they were right.
It's a beautiful wife.
It's a beautiful my wife.
You know what I had?
You know what I had yesterday at the my family Christmas party?
Eggnog.
Nice.
With whiskey.
Was that, did it, did it have egg?
I don't know if it had egg.
I've been told conflicting things that, yes, Eggnog always has egg from other people.
It's not true.
It's not necessarily true.
Commenters, please explain.
I mean, maybe like tradition, the tradition, maybe the most traditional homemade kind.
You guys heard that?
Was that you?
I did.
Was it you blowing your nose?
No, that was my partner's sleep right now.
Was it a snore?
Yeah, they were snoring.
Jesus Christ.
Yep.
I was a little tired.
I mean, it worked late.
I was going to say, oh, Ben, you think you could, if I put a gun to your head.
Yeah.
And I told you to rank your family members from everyone who showed up at the Christmas party.
From like your, your favorite to your least favorite.
You think you can do it being a ranked them?
Yeah, but like, you don't know any of these people.
It wouldn't mean anything.
Ben, I'm the man with the gun.
The point is to, is to get you to say something that, oh, they might hear and they might be like.
High tier.
Zero.
Cousin, cousin Maddie.
Base.
Uncle Peter.
Cousin Al.
Al's wife wrote, no, Al's wife Rose.
Cousin Luke.
Uh, and then, uh, should we tell oblivion fall to jump in?
You know, it's so funny.
It could be making up those names.
Yeah.
Um, uh, Uncle George, Uncle Paul, Uncle Ringo.
Okay.
I would say, okay.
Pete, Peter's family is just better in general.
Chris's family is okay, but Chris himself is kind of a weirdo.
Uh, your family member has family guy names.
Oh, uncle Peter and at Lois and little cousin Stewie.
Uh, of, uh, so, uh, yeah.
And then, uh, who, I mean, who else was even there?
Um, I think that was pretty much it.
Was it, was there, was there, I don't, am I forgetting?
It was all them.
And it was all their like wives and it was all there.
And then some of their kids, uh,
Are you anyone's cool uncle?
I, I do have some, no, wait, I'm not, I'm nobody's uncle.
I guess if my cousin has a kid, am I their great uncle or am I their like,
I think that's, that's uncle once removed.
I think I'm the second, I think I'm their second cousin.
I think, I think me and my cousin's kids are second cousins to each other.
Hey, that's, that's uncle Ben.
Oh, what's so great about him?
He's friends with Mary weather.
Oh, he is.
And then they go up to you and they punch you in your stomach.
Um, uh, I mean, I mean, uh, and then I, I, I, I feel like, um, I feel like, uh,
I kind of have to, I feel like I kind of have to put my uncles on a separate
list for my cousins on a separate list for my cousin's spouses.
Uncle ranking as opposed to aunt ranking.
So what's this voicemail say?
I don't know.
I'm just, I'm just wasting time because I can't listen to it.
Oh, you not, you cannot.
Yeah.
I mean, I can just doesn't, just doesn't play.
Dang, it just doesn't play and I can't download it from the website or anything,
even though my internet is like perfectly functional.
Download speed, uh, 300 kilobytes per second.
It's perfectly healthy.
Uh, well, what do we do?
Should we listen to it for you?
No, what if it's towards Ben?
Well, then we'll just lie.
We should just, I mean, I think oblivion is, is, uh, is jumping in.
So maybe he can save us.
I'm looking, I'm looking up who a deadly comics is.
You're popular.
You don't, you don't know deadly comics?
No.
Well, he didn't know you either.
Well, I'm not surprised.
I do now and we're all best friends.
That's right.
Stop lying to me.
No, you're lying.
You're lying when you say that isn't true.
You're lying to yourself.
Yeah.
Let us in.
Cheesy, let us in.
No.
Open up.
Oh, oh, I can hear it.
Let's, let's listen to it.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
By the way, if you're wondering,
hmm, where is that big bottle on Kemic Man's back attached?
It doesn't seem that he has any straps.
Is it perhaps bolted or glued to his back?
No, actually you Philistine.
Obviously it is supported at any and all times canonically by
Kemic Man's big, huge, fluptuous,
quirked up white boy ass.
And that is canon and real.
I said so.
I'm the creator and therefore.
He gets to make these decisions.
True.
Okay.
Well, thanks for clarifying.
Yeah.
I was wondering.
So you got that, that crunked up white boy shelf.
Did you see that video that was going around on Twitter of a girl
riding a horse and her ass is like so big and like jiggling out of her like,
like jeans and like her.
Link it.
Link it right now.
Yes.
I saw that exact.
Link it.
Yeah.
Like I'm talking about.
I saw it right now.
Like it.
Please.
Link it.
Hey, actually I'm going to link it.
I'll try to find it also.
Hey, oblivion.
Are you recording?
Yes.
I started recording before I hopped in.
Great.
Hello.
Cool.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Yeah.
Nice to meet you for the first time oblivion.
So oblivion, you know, we have Cheesy and oblivion.
Have you not?
Yeah, we've been on Cheesy's podcast.
He's crazy.
He's dangerous.
Stay away from him.
Yep.
I am a crazy dangerous individual.
Deadly.
Do you know oblivion fall?
Do you lie?
I don't know if you know me.
I thought you might have seen his animations around.
I may have.
Yeah, we have.
You ever seen that one video of the guy who puts a jar up his butt?
I haven't seen it.
I don't know if you've seen it.
Have you ever seen Lemon Party?
No.
That's not me.
Let's just say he hosted that party.
I'm trying to think because I used to, you know, I know you from like the My Little Pony days.
I was an animator in that community back then.
And they probably have seen your stuff.
Yeah, you must have the horse animations.
Yeah, I don't know.
It doesn't matter if you know me.
I know you and you're good.
You're good.
You're cool.
You're based and epic.
Whoa.
Thanks for the kind words.
You are all as well.
Wow.
Pleasant people.
I'm not sure if I can find this video.
I mean, I don't know how to find it.
But then you busted my balls now.
It was pretty hot.
You can't just talk about a jiggly butt.
Yeah.
And not show.
I wish I could.
You're hiding her from me.
You are.
I saw it.
You foul beast.
Oh, does someone's Twitter account and they had retweeted it?
Libyan can confirm that it's true.
I'm not lying.
Then you try to keep her to yourself, all to yourself then.
You're all just going to have to take my word.
Her butt was like a giant pair of titties that don't fit, that are like falling out of the...
Don't...
And her titties?
They were like a giant butt.
Sure.
Oh my god.
Listen, I would help if I could, but I can't.
It's out of my hands.
Dang.
That butt's in the wild somewhere.
It's out there.
It's out there if you can find it.
You're going to have my butt.
I left it for you all in just one piece.
Oh, I found it.
Yeah.
How'd you find it?
I just typed big butt horse, horse riding butt or something.
That scene, I'm amazed.
I didn't think you could find it.
We'll post it.
Well, these are reposts, but I mean, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Close enough.
I'll put it in chat.
In fact, I will press the button on my computer that lets me just download videos as mp4 is that way.
L.E.S.R. can easily put it in the edit.
Bzoom.
W.
Oblivion with the W.
What the hell?
It's not loading for me.
Oh, it is like titties.
Oh, you're right.
Yeah, you should have said the thong made it look like titties.
I mean, I guess.
More in terms of the way that it's spilling over.
Like it's made out of jelly, but there's zero muscle.
It's all jelly.
Nice.
I hate muscle.
I anti muscle.
Nice.
OK.
L.E.S.R. on regular show.
Muscle man.
Yeah, it's just a bunch of girls on horses with their butts out.
Like this is this is the ideal future.
But I need horses on on top of big butt girls is what I need.
All right.
Well, now I would thoroughly derailed the voicemail segment.
We got another voicemail.
Yeah.
We got yet more voicemails.
This one's called on the topic of Tim Rogers.
Can you listen to this one, Ben?
Yeah, it's not.
It's not working.
Oh, wait.
Yes, it is.
OK, let's do it.
Perfect.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Tim Rogers videos are about a man's connection to art or a video game.
They are as much about him as they are about what he is reviewing.
And that's all right.
I see art as a two-step process, the creation and audience connection.
This type of video is what Jacob Geller and H Bomber Guy do, too.
I find it fascinating to listen to an interesting person explain their experience
with a piece of art and it helps me to connect with art on a higher level, too.
As an aside, I think judging an artist based on their fan base
to be quite a strange way to approach it,
which is what you seem to be doing with your negative interaction with that white knight.
Um, no, I mean, no.
First of all, I agree with what you're saying about the point of the videos.
And yeah, I agree.
And I feel that way, too.
And it's fine.
I'm not judging the videos based on that one,
the fact that some people are weird.
I'm just saying that some people that are fans of him are weird about it.
That's all.
Yeah, I would agree with this statement.
But I do have a critique of Tim Rogers because I tried to watch one of his videos.
I can post it.
I wrote a little thing.
Oh, where did I write it?
This is the...
We're on the, like, Gibb's struggles to watch a Tim Rogers video, arc.
Yeah, this is the arc.
This is going on for like a month now.
Well, I mean, I've got to the point where I tried to watch a video and it was the last of us video.
And I think it's just the parts that people say are good were annoying me.
So this is what I said.
I'm trying to watch a Tim Rogers video on the last of us and I'm getting frustrated.
He's just showing me his video games.
I don't know what point he's making.
It gives me the impression this video is not long for a good reason.
And I want to start skipping around.
I think he does, like, eventually come to a point.
But I feel like he had, like...
Oh, that's the one, like, he's showing...
He's actually, like, showing his, like, collection of games.
Like, it's one that Naughty Dog sent to him, I think, right?
No, he's showing every single game he has in his collection.
And then before that, he explains why he has such a small collection.
And it's all building to a point, but it just...
It seems to take way too long because I feel like I get it.
But anyway, the next thing I said is I hate this guy, Lol.
I don't like how he enunciates every syllable of a word, every letter it feels like.
I thought it was a bit, but I think that's just how he talks or how he's choosing to talk.
And he's choosing to talk in a kind of weird way.
Like, the video is a joke, and he's above it and above me for listening to it.
And my patience has run pretty thin.
When is he going to be a real person?
That's what I want to know.
He's, like, 100% sarcastically saying everything, but some parts are framed as jokes.
So, obviously, some parts have to be genuine.
And I can't tell the difference.
I just wanted to talk normal.
I feel most of that.
That's my problems with Tim Rogers.
He talks annoying, and I can't tell.
He's very sticky.
And he's definitely putting on a voice at all times.
Even when he's not doing his, like, I'm reading a video essay voice,
he still has, like, kind of an affected voice bit that he's doing.
I'm convinced.
A bit.
I mean, he has his, like, I'm reading a script in a dramatic fashion voice,
and then he's sort of got his, like, he's kind of like, he's kind of casual,
like, I'm just fucking around, you know?
Like, that's his, but, like, that's also a living you don't know who we're talking about.
I looked him up, and then I'm like, oh, this is the action button thing.
People have been talking about this guy's videos and telling me to watch it.
I looked at this guy's face, and he has a dumb face.
Yeah, get his ass.
He looks like, to me, he looks like Monkey Jones.
He looks like, like, 70s Monkey Jones.
I don't know.
He's the Jones that will break your bones, man.
And the most recent thumbnail, anyway.
I'm not exactly sure what it, who I think he looks like.
I don't know what this guy looks like.
But yeah, that's, that's, my main gripe is just the way he talks is, is annoying.
But more or so, because I can listen to people with annoying voices,
it's that the video was three hours long,
and I don't think he made a single point for the first, like, 30 minutes.
And I was like, when are you going to say anything?
When is anything going to come out of your mouth?
Kind of like talking to my mom.
I'll be honest, I don't really remember
that one very well.
So I'm not sure like, maybe it's a bad example.
It's just sort of like,
I feel like I needed to be part of a fan club that is very well versed in Tim Rogers
to get anything out of the things he was saying.
Because I didn't get it.
I didn't care about anything like he's showing me all his games.
I'm like, cool.
Where are you going?
This is not really related to that review.
It doesn't really reflect on the quality of the video at all.
But I think in that video,
he mentions that he mentions that Vito Gueswoldy is his friend,
and then he tells Vito that like his house is dirty and he should clean it.
And I don't like Vito Gueswoldy.
So I think that's a cringe moment.
That's a Tim Rogers L right there.
I knew him look like Monkey Jones was a warning.
Anyway, I might give it another chance.
I might give a different video another chance.
I think you should watch the slow translation of Final Fantasy VII,
aka Let's Mosey, the whole playlist.
That's a great series.
That's a very interesting series.
You learn a lot of Japanese in it.
I hate Japan.
Oh, well, then I guess we're fucked.
I guess it's not going to work.
He only has seven whole videos.
How could there be a series?
Well, that's not it.
No, those are not here on his channel.
Those other videos were on Kotaku,
because he used to make videos for Kotaku.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I've heard of Let's Mosey.
Let's Mosey is not an action button.
Action button is like his personal channel
from after he split from Kotaku.
I listened to like two hours.
That's why people knew this guy before he had a channel
is because he was from Kotaku.
Yeah.
I listened to like two hours of the
Tokimeki Memorial video and like, I don't know.
It's I felt like it was talking too much about his own personal life.
And I mean, he definitely is doing that.
He definitely is doing that.
I just, I guess I'm not sure where's the end point.
Like, I feel like I already need to be a fan of this guy
to watch anything he's doing.
I watched the Tokimeki Memorial video first,
and I did find it strange and sometimes off-putting,
but I mostly enjoyed it.
And yeah, and I guess that was my end.
And now I was like, okay.
And then I went back and I watched the other ones,
and I was able to.
I didn't, I didn't mind the, like, yes, he definitely goes off.
He's definitely off on a tangent about himself most of the time.
Oh, are we doing, are we doing sight lines?
Look, he, look, I'm just saying
this channel is definitely disorganized.
It definitely makes no sense.
It's no cohesion.
Oblivio, what the fuck is this?
Did you do this last time?
He's looking in completely the wrong direction.
These are just incorrect.
None of his videos are connected.
None of them, like, he never looks at himself.
Only the characters look at him.
Why do you do this?
These arrows are completely random.
And you know what's even, when he posts another video,
the arrows are going to point in completely different places,
and it's going to get even worse.
That's video, they're going to be pointed directly at you.
He's clearly looking in any direction.
He's looking, like, vaguely towards the camera,
and I have to, like, interpret, like, yeah,
but, like, surely his eyes aren't exactly towards the camera.
They're, like, 1% up and down,
and I have to, like, interpret that.
It's really difficult.
I can't tell how genuine you're being right now.
Okay, but does Tim Rogers hide his dick
when he's posing for pictures,
or does he put his hands back like it's alpha?
Okay, there is a really, I honestly, I don't even mind it,
but it's weird to describe it.
There's a section in the Cyberpunk video
where there's, like, half an hour,
there's fully, like, half an hour of him, like,
in a white room, like, modeling various, like, jackets,
and boots, and jeans that he owns.
And he just is, like, doing that for a while,
and he sort of ties it in to the themes of commercialism
in Cyberpunk fiction or something, I guess.
I would like it if he would, like, tighten up his scripts.
Just say less.
I can't find a picture of Tim Rogers showing his crotch.
That picture does not exist.
The scripts are not, the scripts are not tight.
The scripts are anything but tight.
Well.
But tight.
Not like that girl on the horse.
Her butt was anything but tight.
Hey, I mean.
Now she was talking about video games.
Now listen.
Now if her butt was talking about video games,
I'd watch that for six hours.
The problem is Tim Rogers,
Tim Rogers isn't enough of a psycho for me to like,
you know, because I'm a big fan of white boys,
but especially if they're crazy, like Ben.
Absolutely.
Thank you very much.
Those are the best kind of white boys
that are crazy boys.
I would say Tim is a little bit quirked up.
Maybe a little, maybe a little too quirked up.
He's quirked up, but he's not,
but he's not busting it down sexual style.
No, I would not describe him as busting it down sexual style.
He's quirked up, but not busting it down sexual.
That's his problem.
You're right.
He's got one, but not the other.
You need both.
You have a point.
Now Donald Trump, now there's a white boy
who is busting it down sexual style.
Did you see his physique?
Did you see his physique in those NFTs?
Did you see he's like, he's like nine heads tall.
He's like nine heads tall in those NFTs.
He looks fantastic.
He gets nine heads every day from random women.
Yes.
On Truth Social, I go there and I tweet it.
You're no longer allowed to post about Truth Social on Twitter.
That's crazy.
They ban accounts that promote Instagram,
Truth Social, Mastodon.
They're like, announce this today.
Instagram.
Yeah, Instagram.
You see that?
Oh my God, my speech is so free.
Did you see that one?
Comedy is so legal.
You see that couple, half a day,
where they took off the Spaces feature on Twitter for half a day?
I'm not sure if we talked about that last week.
We didn't talk specifically about that.
Was that even the last week?
I thought it was just a few days ago.
Just a few days ago.
Yeah, okay.
He had a Spaces moment where he got a big L,
he got owned live on stream,
and then he destroyed the functionality of Spaces.
I don't know whether literally because he got owned,
but it was very funny that he got owned
and then deactivated that functionality.
It says, we no longer allow free promotion
of certain social media platforms.
Specifically, we will remove accounts created solely
for the purpose of promoting other social platforms
and content that contains links or usernames
for the following platforms.
Facebook, Instagram, Mastodon, TruthSocial,
Tribal, Noster, and Post.
It sounds like they'll fucking ban you
if you have your Instagram linked in your bio.
That's stupid.
Or even if you just post about it at all.
I feel like this is not even legal.
I don't know about that.
It's a level of like, oh, you can't talk about
a competitor's social media website.
Will ban you? Will ban mention of it?
Like, I feel like there's got to be some law
that prevents that sort of-
I don't know if it's illegal, but I think it's-
And it's a private company.
I think it's bad practice.
Like, you want-
I feel like it's got to be illegal somewhere.
You want to be interconnected.
Like in the EU maybe, for like anti-monopoly laws.
I'm going to start a social media where
it's like everything free.
It's the ultimate free speech social media.
You just cannot talk about my ex-wife's new husband.
That's the one rule is don't-
No!
Anyone who mentions Derek will be banned.
I might not agree with my ex-wife's new husband,
but I will defend to the death your right to talk about him.
No, ban, ban, ban.
Okay, shit.
Get him out of here!
Get him out of my social media!
Get him out!
Can we get that-
Yeah.
Next voicemail is an image.
And it's this.
This is the image.
Is it-
Is it you guys making up?
Was that not posting?
Why is it not posting?
I don't mind.
I see it.
Hey, does anyone know who these bitches are?
Wasn't it like-
I don't know.
These big titty bitches?
Yeah, have you seen these before?
I- I- These are from something,
and I don't know what it is, but it's somewhere-
Oh, did we not-
Did we not-
Her shirt says,
lesbians are awesome.
Yeah.
This is, um...
These are from, like, an old webcomic.
And I-
And I can't remember what it was called.
This is-
This is kind of awesome.
Wait a minute.
They didn't look kind of familiar.
What-
What is it?
Is it-
This must be-
This-
This must be the, like, Radcon 2.
This must be, like, Radcon 2 or Ben.
Um...
Well, I wish I could remember-
I- I wish I could remember-
Shanty Lover.
What- What is it about my posture here?
Is this-
I feel like this pose is, like, a reference to something.
Your legs are way too short.
I think you-
I mean, you're just walking.
Seems like it's clipped from-
From, like, a Radcon video.
I do look short.
I don't know.
Something about this pose just reminds me of something, but-
Is it-
Is it that Leonardo DiCaprio meme where he's str-
Striding?
He's walking?
No.
That's from, like, the front.
I mean, if I passed by these in real life,
yeah, I probably would turn around and look with a big smile on my face.
That's, like, the worst pants you could wear.
We're seeing big-titty lesbians, I feel.
Yeah, I- I don't look great.
I don't look great.
Yeah.
Right, exactly.
Don't look now, but here comes that anti-
that ant-
ant-gay-lover-nut.
So, one, the count of three lets me kiss you, like-
Like, it's our last-
This is, like, a panel.
This is, like, an actual quote from the comic.
I'm convinced.
Who is this?
Someone help me-
Show yourself now.
Yeah.
You want to find the source material.
You want to read it?
Yeah, I actually do want to read it.
That's the right-
We tried to find out on, like, shitty webcomic,
like, archive things, but we couldn't find it.
I couldn't.
Is it that obscure?
Who's sending in the voicemails?
It's not that obscure because I've seen it on, like,
something awful and stuff before.
Um, I like that.
I want to-
I want to redraw this.
This looks pretty-
Do they have a lot of legs or is that a dress?
I think that's full of a dress.
I like to think they got a lot of legs.
They're octopuses.
They're, like, Squidward.
They could also have that.
One of them is a cat as well.
One of them is a cat.
I'm not sure why, but-
Well, why not?
Yeah.
And that's, uh, and that's Ben in the corner.
That's Ben in the corner.
He's in the even more spot, like, losing his dummy worms.
Losing his virginity.
Okay, that was better.
I like that one.
That was better.
Good job, Giv.
It's the next one is a vocaru link.
Oh, thank you.
Can you click on that?
Yeah, I think it's loading.
Give it a second.
Let me-
Let me just say, can I just say that, uh,
I was being mean and bullying unique Namasaurus on Twitter earlier,
and he called-
He called me an idiologue.
So, uh, let's kill him.
Yeah, sure.
He's a log.
He is a log.
That reminds me of some other kinds of logs.
I'm gonna get his ass.
I think he's-
I think he's ignoring me.
I think he's giving me the brush up.
I am tempted to watch the short version of his video
to see if he kept the pan peaks upright in there.
I refuse to watch the shortened version.
I refuse to-
I saw a couple minutes of it,
and it just felt like the longer version,
but he sped up the audio and only got to the certain points.
He did add a couple of extra, like,
like in the long version, he goes through, like,
one at a time.
He goes for every small artist that NFTs helped.
And then this one, he just kind of just says, like,
oh, it's helped a lot of small artists,
and then he names a couple of new ones.
That's so smart.
I'm honestly, it's not even-
It's not even that he's, like, NFTs are okay.
That's not even why I hate him so much.
It's just-
It's just white.
He's such a fucking nerd and such a fucking dweeb,
and he thinks he's so smart.
He thinks he's so smart with his dog shit arguments,
and I just want to kill him.
I just want to kill him.
Ah, man.
I never did that one video.
The-
I watched the eight hour long NFT defense,
so you don't have to,
because I was too busy making comics.
That's right.
There's better-
There's better things to do.
Better things to do in my time.
The vocru is still not-
Well, we can-
I can just say it was sounds of jacking off.
Oh, okay.
The vocru is implying-
It's just 10 minutes of heavy breathing,
and then pfft at the end.
The vocru is implying that when gifts post selfies,
this individual views it as masturbation material.
Oh, I understand.
The vocru is implying that Gibbon take is sex-
I understand.
The vocru is implying that Gib looks pretty good.
Thank you for clarifying.
Finger, finger guns, bang, bang, bang.
Thank you, voice mailer.
Thank you, kind mailer.
Thanks.
Please send-
Please send more.
Next.
Next one is Aiden, again, Aiden II.
Don, it's been a minute long.
Okay, this one's working for some reason.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Hey, this is Aiden.
I'm reporting from Cop Kill Town right now.
I learned to mine sweeper just so I could kill rowdies.
Is that gonna be a nerd?
I have 20 million slime right now.
I'm aiming for 30 million.
Damn, this guy's actually playing the game.
I actually learned how to play mine sweeper properly.
This guy's mining.
Just so I could do this.
Does that make me like an idiot?
Yeah.
Does it make me like a nerd or something?
Yeah, definitely.
Or what?
But, you know, the base kind of idiot.
This is the petty that I learned to skill
just to focus on other people?
No.
Also, bullying Ben because I'm a killer and I have to.
He's struggling.
Ben, you got wet willies in class
and you didn't even tell the teacher
because you were so scared of stepping into the class.
It's true.
You just let it happen.
You got an ear infection and it really hurt
and you still don't do anything about it.
How'd you know about that?
Fuck you.
That's Ben now.
Okay.
You too have a good podcast.
Bye.
And if there's a guest, you also have fun.
Well, deadly.
Oh, wow.
I was expecting that.
He wished you have a good podcast.
His wish came true.
Yay.
This guy, you know, does it?
It's no, it's not dumb to learn new skill to fuck with people.
That's what you do in any.
That's what I do with Pokemon.
They go on showdown and I learned the skills.
I learned how to learn to type matchups and move sets
just so I could just so I could own noobs on showdown.
What are the reasons there to get good at something?
I can't.
I can't think of one.
Yeah, I get.
I guess just to.
I only draw Clarissa Gunsmoke so that I can take over Japan.
That's not true.
Colonize it.
We're colonizing, baby.
Yeah.
And what is colonizing if not pawning a bunch of noobs?
Did you see?
Did you see what Cameron the fucking, what's his name?
Um, Avatar man.
James Cameron.
Did you see what James Cameron,
did you see what James Cameron said about the Native Americans?
About the Lakota.
What did he say?
About the Lakota people.
He said like in an interview, he's it's so fucking amazing.
He said like, yeah, this story reminds me of like the Lakota
and how the Lakota were wiped out by like the white man.
And now like looking, looking at like how completely
their culture has been devastated and wiped out by that event.
You know, I think if they knew what would eventually become of them,
I think they would have fought a little harder than they did back then.
Like I think they would have tried harder if they'd known
they would get this fucked over by it.
What the fuck?
It's so, I know, like why the fuck, why the fuck would you say that?
I thought you were like here because you like liked Native peoples
and were like, hey, let's sort of adapt a story about them
into a cool movie.
Why would you say something so fucked up?
I thought it was going to, I was going to joke like,
oh, maybe they should have tried being blue
and then weird like gossip and say,
ooh, and like leave them alone.
That's probably what he thinks.
That's what he said.
I know I know that he's saying, I know that he's,
I know that like he's trying to express like a pro Native opinion there.
Like he wants, he wishes they had not been wiped out
and like, I guess that's cool, but come on.
They would have shown harder.
They should have fought harder.
Get out of here.
Jesus Christ.
What a clown.
Come on.
That being said.
Come on, come on, Jimmy.
Come on, Jimmy.
Do a little better.
That being said, don't forget to catch Avatar Way of the Water
only in cinema right now.
Right.
I genuinely don't understand why like I'm seeing people
seeming like they're unironically hype for this movie.
I don't get it.
Yeah, I don't get it at all.
Are we being Morbius again?
Is this another Morbius?
I actually did see it.
I saw an early screening of it.
I got free tickets.
Why?
Is it like amazing or is it just like one of the movies?
Because I wanted to.
Because, because James Cameron's never misses
when it comes to film, when it comes to cinema.
I didn't like Avatar.
I didn't, yeah, I didn't really care.
I didn't care about it when I saw it.
I thought like the cultural thing with Avatar is like,
oh, such special effects.
And then because it wasn't like a very interesting story,
it sort of faded out of relevance.
And then he said, I'm going to make 100,000 more sequels.
And that was like a joke.
Like that was funny that he said he was going to do that.
And then the second movie comes out and people are loving it,
which I guess is.
It actually is better than the first one.
I'll tell you that much.
It actually is better.
I don't know.
I just think people did really love the first one.
Like people were like crazy about it for like a short while.
For that summer.
Yeah, like, yeah.
For that summer, of course.
I'm not specifying a percentage of the population,
but they were definitely,
but I just remember hearing people raving about it for like
a couple months and then everyone was just quiet.
It was like a big, it was like a big movie of the summer
of that year or whatever.
And that's cool.
It made a bunch of money, fair enough.
But yeah, nobody talks about it anymore.
And I don't, I thought it was it was sort of a joke.
And then, but then I see that they announced the sequel.
And I see all this unironic like, oh, James,
oh, the movies are back.
Oh, we're back, baby.
Like big blockbusters are back and I can't wait to go to the movie theater.
They're gonna get baby.
Why?
I don't get it.
Why not watch my dinner with Andre and talk about what a piece of shit
Wallace Sean is.
Like that's way more interesting in my opinion.
Because there's no blue people in that.
I hate.
There is.
There's a blue minotaur.
There's a blue minotaur that Andre hallucinates when he's in church.
It's described in monologue.
Yeah, there's no special effects.
Yeah, but way the way of water is better than the first one.
I get this vibe watching because I saw it,
but I get this vibe that like I do want him to make all six of these.
Avatar movies.
Is that the plan six?
Yeah, six of them.
That's the plan.
And I get the vibe that by the sixth film,
they won't even like look the same as the first one.
Like what's ever going on in the first one will not matter in the sixth.
Haven't they like already filmed a bunch of them?
He's written the scripts all the way to part like five, I think.
And I think the rumor goes that the fifth one is like five hours long.
And the fucking executives like didn't have no notes
or didn't tell him to cut out anything out of the movie.
It's funny in like a like that you don't see that happening that much.
I guess he has the cloud.
I kind of would like to see it happen just because it's such so odd.
The movie kind of feels like like you ever written like a you ever like in your head.
And I feel like all like artists or storytellers have had this in their head
where they like written like a very long epic saga in their head.
And they're all like, yeah, I know I know at the beginning like part one is kind of
is going to be kind of boring compared to all the epic shit that happens in the middle.
But I have to go for part one to eventually get you to the to the kick ass shit in the middle.
That's like the vibe I'm getting from this series.
So was it going to be like the the first one they fly around so they're like
or maybe they're in the forest.
So it's like forest navi this one way of water.
Are they going to be like dirt like mole navi in one of them?
Well, well, maybe I feel like the slime and navi in the swamp.
They're going to be swamp level in the third one.
They're going to go like full magic.
There's like some fucking magic shit happening in the second one.
They're going to make it.
It's going to become World of Warcraft.
That'd be cool.
But it's the well of life.
I also like how like casually they drop like sci-fi concepts throughout the film.
Like, do you remember the bad guy in the first movie?
There was like that white military guy.
The guy who's like, we got to get that unobtainium.
Yeah, yeah, that guy.
So so he comes back, actually.
Because even though he died, he comes back because they put his memories into a navi
like clone body that they made for him.
So that's how he comes back, right?
And there's this kind of there's this like fucking very interesting scene where like
they go to the site where his old body died and he picks up like his own skull.
He's like looking at it.
And it's like it's crazy how good the fuck.
And that's another thing that's great about the film.
It's crazy how good the fucking CGI is and how much like they fucking like emote.
Just like you really like and a lot of other things like you don't get like a good
performance out of people who are completely CGI.
But with like with the Avatar movies, like you really like feel the fucking range
coming out of these actors for these.
I mean, it's a digital.
So yeah, they usually are the fucking goats of anything CGI.
Yeah, I think also to I get the vibe that like if it is kind of an element,
it is kind of a meme to be like, oh, this is a masterpiece.
It is kind of it's like half that.
But the other half is kind of like, when was the last time we got like a home grown
like franchise series that isn't based on like preexisting media, you know?
Yeah, like all the MCU is built on like crutches.
And each each movie feels like factory made.
It's like you're eating a bag of chips every time you watch an MCU movie.
But with Avatar, it feels like this is just one like millionaires crazy.
Like in an alternate universe, Avatar would have been some sort of like sci-fi series,
like a sci-fi book series like made in the 90s.
But in our universe, it's like, oh, this crazy like millionaire director who has like.
Yeah, the guy who made Titanic and made so much money off of that that you could do
whatever he wanted, had an idea that would have otherwise been a smaller scale project.
Yeah, I get it.
Like people say the story about like, like people say that bullshit story about like George Lucas
being like, oh, yeah, he wrote all the Star Wars out and he knew he knew he only had like
enough funds to start in the middle with with with a new hope.
Which is nobody does anyone actually believe.
Yeah, I met people.
I met people who say that I met people who want to ironically say that shit.
Believe me, I've met motherfuckers.
So so but this this avatar feels like that.
But like real like, no, this is the guy actually did that.
Yeah, which is why like he waited so fucking long because he was like out there charting.
And then he does like real life, like real crazy shit, you know,
he's kind of like James Cameron is kind of like over to compare him to a fictional character.
He's kind of like Kaiba from Yu-Gi-Oh.
Have you read that post about how like Kaiba is like the most real depiction of a billionaire?
It's a time where it becomes that's what I kind of mean.
Like he becomes obsessed with that.
I know that we'll post you're talking about the other.
Yeah, the one that's like the thing about Kaiba is realistic depiction of a billionaire
because he his literally his whole thing is that he has all this money and he could do anything with
it. He could help the poor.
He could like he could do, you know, make space travel.
He could, you know, reinvent, you know, healthcare or whatever.
But he just chooses to spend it all on ridiculous hologram technology designed for playing card
games because he just loves card games that much.
He's just he's shaping the whole culture of his world with his massive wealth around building
all this technological infrastructure devised to facilitate the playing of children's card games
because that's just what he likes.
And he's just going to fucking do it and no one can tell him he can't.
Yeah, that's James Cameron with this series.
Amazing.
And I think I was going to say all the like critiques people have about like the the the
movie like oh it's white saviorism blah blah blah all this stuff.
I agree with it.
I think yeah yeah like if you give me like a take that's like that I'll agree with it.
That being said, I think the one thing that makes me like not hate the series for that
is because it doesn't feel like malicious.
You know, like it doesn't feel like he's he's making a statement about oh yeah,
this you know why people do it better like no that just kind of like accidental.
Well, yeah, yeah, I'm I'm sure that Cameron has like all the it seems like he at least has
like his heart in the right place with like he wants to show these like you know indigenous
people as like you know good and like they should be there.
You know, they're the heroes of the movie that you're supposed to root for them in there.
I and I think I think another funny thing is that the movie has like five different degrees of like
race mixing in the movie because it's like okay.
So like Jake Sully, he's like he was human and at the end of avatar they fully put his like
mind inside his avatar body, right?
So he's like completely Navi, right?
Yeah.
And he but also his his like Navi his Navi body was also it has some of his like DNA in it
because that's like it's his brother's DNA, right?
Like yeah, yeah, out of his brother.
Yeah.
So so he has he has a little bit of human in him.
So when he has kids with Zoa Sildana's like Navi,
their kids like look like their face look like Navi, but they have an extra finger like a human.
Right.
And then later there and then also in their family, the Sigourney, I don't know if you remember
the Sigourney Weaver character from the first one.
She was like a scientist.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She she at the end of avatar one, like it shows that she's like dying.
So they put her mind in her Navi body like right at the end.
And then in the sequel, it turns out that it worked but it put her Navi body in a coma, right?
So she's been in a coma this whole time.
But in her coma, she was pregnant in her Navi body and they don't know they don't know how
the pregnancy happened.
They assume it's like fucking magic or something and her daughter and she has like a daughter.
She has like a Navi daughter out of her like Navi body, right?
But the thing that's kind of interesting, the thing that's kind of interesting is that her
Navi daughter, her face, like she doesn't have like that flat like cat nose that all the Navis
has.
She has like a human nose, but she's like still blue and everything, right?
So this is like, so this is like a different degree of mixed race than like a jake-like-
Did like a human impregnate her mostly Navi, like the human body?
That's like, that's like, they don't know.
It's never explained in the movie, but that's like, I guess one of the mysteries.
And later it's showing that her daughter has like a weird magical ability, right?
Like she like later it's revealed that she doesn't need to like connect her like little ponytail
to other animals to like control it.
She could just do it.
Like she has like a psychic ability to do it.
Right?
And it's like connected to like the world tree that connects like her whole planet, right?
And then another thing is that it turns out that after the war, after the war in the first movie,
there was like still like a baby human there left on that planet that they were raising.
And they couldn't, they couldn't send that baby human back to Earth because you should,
you're, you can't put babies in cryostasis.
That's not, that's not good for a fucking baby.
I think that makes, that makes sense.
Right.
So, so the baby is, wait, hold up.
The baby is raised on Pandora and the baby is raised with a bunch of Navi, right?
And he's like a human like, he's like a human white boy with dreadlocks and his name is spider.
That's like his fucking name.
Right?
That's it.
It's all these weird degrees of like fucking like race, race.
Yeah.
Cause they also have a friend who's like, he's like, he's like,
he shaped like a ball and he's bright green.
In the new one?
Yeah.
He's literally like, he's like a circle.
He's like got a circle.
He's got like a spherical body.
He's bright green.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get it.
It's just like.
Yeah.
Oh, I love Avatar actually.
Actually Avatar based.
All right.
Look at that CGI of it.
And that's like everything I explained is only like one fifth of the film.
Dude, I can't believe they make whole movies in the computer now.
Should we move, go to the next voicemail?
Next, next voice fail is an image.
Did you say voice fail?
Yeah.
Oh, I mean, voice fail.
It is image here.
And this is, I think, I think this is true as hell.
I wish that my computer worked.
I hope that it will load.
Well, I'll describe it for the, the people who aren't looking,
such as Ben St.
Ben St.
tears off the calendar for December 2022.
Underneath January 1984.
The woman is me.
I've got my name Gib on my shirt.
And I'm saying, whoa, they edited Munchie to look like a Nazi.
We can't show this on screen.
And it's true.
That's what I said.
That is what you said.
And I said, oh, no, political.
It's 1984.
This is 1984.
That's right.
Okay.
That seems true.
It seems true to life.
I can't see it.
You can't see it, but I can imagine it crystal clear.
Show me the next one.
Next one is, why do you, it's just a no, no voice.
Just a question.
Why do you act like a maniac on Twitter?
I assume they're talking to you, Ben.
What do I act like?
How do I act like a maniac?
I don't know.
I'm not, I'm just, I'm just mean to people that I don't like.
That's normal.
That's a normal thing to do.
You attack innocent YouTubers like you name a source.
I'm normal.
I'm the only normal one.
If you think I'm the maniac, that means there's something wrong with you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but you have to get a grip.
You have to get a grip, my dude.
Did a Stereo's Coconut compliment you on being a maniac on Twitter?
Like you said, that's what he liked about you.
He did.
I think he was just being nice.
I think he, I think, I think he was being, I think he was being diplomatic.
Nice.
Which I'll take it, you know.
How do you?
I hope people watch that stream I was on with the Stereo's because that was actually really fun.
I was really funny.
It was actually really fun explaining to him like what Channel Awesome was.
Oh, yeah, I haven't got around to watching that.
All the other kids in that stream, they like,
they didn't, they didn't like explain to him like actually what it was.
They would tell him like, oh, yeah, this person got canceled for being a rapist.
Oh, yeah, this person died.
And he was like confused.
And then I explained like, here's the deal.
Here was like the corporate structure hierarchy and how it became this like,
this, this enterprise built of like Doug, Doug Walker clones.
And he was like, oh, thank you.
Now I get why it's funny.
That's, but that's kind of like, like a Stereo's fault.
Not going to lie.
Because he's, he's, he's a magnet for people who, because, because here's the bit.
Let me, if you ever listen to like them, I've listened to a lot of like a Stereo's podcast
and usually the gimmick is the same across the board is that a Stereo's is a boomer
and he does it like, like edgy things and his co-host would be super edgy and we'll
tell him a bunch of edgy things.
And the Stereo's would be like, oh my God.
I see.
And that's every, that's every a Stereo's podcast.
So, so because of that, his fan base is a bunch of edgy people who just jumped
the calls and tell him like, Stereo's, you heard about this super edgy thing and he'll
be like, oh my God.
Ah, that's, that's his fucking gimmick.
Oh, I killed him.
Oh no, Ben's dead.
Ben's dead.
Is he finally got the best of him?
Ben's dead, baby.
I hope Ben is talking into his recording right now and that we're all talking over each other
in the edit.
Ben Stain has turned it to Ben Angel.
I'm going to post the next thing because it's the homo Juneus.
Yeah, I got the file in the chat so that Ben can listen to it when he gets back,
maybe if he's lucky.
Rest in peace, Ben.
We barely knew ye.
I'm, I'm back.
Sorry, I'm back.
My discord dropped the call.
I got the, I got the image to load.
I look, look at my hair.
I look like fucking, uh, I have like fucking Jerry Seinfeld like Kramer high hair.
You do.
It's a very funny, I looked so, I look so bad at red, the red con two videos.
What's the deal with Munchy?
He, they say he's a Nazi, but I did not see what they're saying.
I'm like, you know, it's Gib, you're saying we can't show this on screen and I'm tearing
the cover.
I'm tearing the calendar to 1984, but I'm smiling about it.
Like, I'm not concerned.
Like, like the original boomer.
Oh, you like Lantilator 4.
I'm like, yeah, time to go back, baby.
We have to go back, returned to 1984.
Cool.
Uh, let's, let's do the next one.
And next one is a vocary link.
Oh, okay.
Can you hear that?
Yes, I can.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, I swim in the ocean.
Swimming is all I know how to do.
Below me is water.
Next to me is water.
It's the way of water.
In front of me is water.
Behind me is water.
This isn't like a clip from the film.
If I dive down, it's more water.
Yeah, I've never seen.
If I swim up, it's more water.
I'm not having sex with you right now, water.
It's all very homogenous.
I don't know why the way you said it that time got me.
I don't know who this guy is, but I love him.
He, he's pretty homogenous.
He's very.
Yeah, his, his voicemails are getting a little homogenous.
They're all about the same thing.
Yeah, they are a little bit like they all have the same structure
and they all end the same way.
I wonder where this is going.
I don't understand.
Doesn't make any.
Sounds a little disturbed.
Australian.
Is that just me?
A little Australian.
Australian.
He's a little alien.
The next voicemail is another one of these.
These high things.
As you can see, Ben Stain's channel is very complex.
There's a lot of interweaving fiends.
I like on the Mega Man lecture, every single Mega Man on the board.
He's a little arrow.
That's pretty good.
I should say this is a low quality JPEG, so that it loads for you, Ben.
I totally forgot about the Ben St. debate.
Digibro on Bernie.
What happened to that guy?
Digibro?
Yeah.
He became, he died.
He died.
No, he became, he became May.
Nice.
He's gone.
Yeah.
He became May.
They became pregnant with the child of the, of the gunk.
And it, and the title was passed on through the bloodline.
My God, how old is that baby now?
Almost, must be less than a year.
Is it only been, okay.
I know how this works is like, oh, a family member has a baby,
and then before you know it, they're like seven.
Next time you see them, yeah.
Before you know it, I think that's a podcast.
That's how I am with all my stupid little second cousins now.
They're all turning like, one of them's like five.
God, one of them's like five.
Holy shit.
And then, oh, I can see it.
Oh my God, I can see it.
Thank you.
That's how it worked.
Oh, all the, all the little Mega Man's.
Wait, what is, these are, and yeah, yeah.
See, this is, this is coherent.
This is coherent.
They're all looking at each other.
They're all, it's all connected in the great circle of life.
The only, the only tricky one is you and Mega Man are looking at the camera.
I don't know what the fuck to do there.
We're all, you do nothing.
All together, all of us together looking at the camera.
Some of these are, some of these, oh, Endless War looking at about is good.
I like him.
I like him there.
I should release more Endless War animation tie-ins that'll get 8K views.
It is a follow-up to my, to my, to my big hit.
Okay.
Yeah.
Next.
Well, it's a good, it's a good thing, I think, because it is actually my time to go now.
Oh, thank you for stopping by.
I'm glad I could stop by.
It's been good chatting.
All 10 words.
It's been good, all 10 words.
You silently eat suffering.
Well, we all spurge about, yeah.
We're eating good in the neighborhood.
And I got to go eat something I'm feeling faint.
Oh, okay.
Oh, no.
Yeah, we have, we have been, we have been going, we are, we had four hours now.
Oh my god.
Yeah, we just, we just passed the four hours mark.
So, well, if at any point you're done, you can say so and leave.
Well, how many more voicemails, how many voicemails do we have?
Well, we've been going slow.
There's like, actually, one, two, three, four.
There's like seven to 10.
Some of them are images.
Okay.
I mean, I may have to skip that.
Oh, I apologize.
That's no, that's totally okay.
This is a long time.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, thank you, Oblivion, for stopping by.
And Deadly, it's been a great having you as a guest.
And thank you.
You're welcome to come back any time.
That's true.
Everyone, subscribe to Deadly Comics.
Watch all the animations.
Definitely.
Good.
Oh yeah, definitely everyone should.
I mean, if that wasn't clear by the fact that he's here,
you should definitely check out his animation.
But don't promote him on YouTube.
You might get banned.
That might be illegal next week.
On Twitter, if you mention that you have his YouTube channel,
you will get banned.
Yeah, just write my name on a paper and leave it in the public place.
That's how we get the word out.
They can't stop all of us from doing that.
They can only take some of us down.
Exactly.
They can.
I'm heading out.
All right.
Thanks.
We'll leave me on for a little bit.
Thank you.
See ya.
Cool.
See you guys as well.
All right.
See ya, Deadly.
Thanks again.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for having me on.
All right.
My pleasure.
Later.
See ya.
Bye-bye.
All right.
Well, let's wrap this up.
Okay.
Next ones are Ben's Weekly Reminder.
Played Delta in Chapter 2.
And to catch up on One Piece,
and then they sent another one said,
I meant to stay up to date with One Piece.
They're all non-voicemails.
Gotcha.
The one after that is this.
Just says Ben.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I'm driving Ben.
I'm driving beyond the speed limit, Ben.
Ben, I'm breaking the law.
No.
Why are you telling me?
That was me last night.
Was it actually?
No.
No, that wasn't me.
But I was, I speed all the fucking time.
I mean, I think a lot of people do.
I think it's, I mean, like,
I mean, they're speeding and then they're speeding.
I only go like 20 miles over the speed limit, you know?
I mean, on the highway, that's normal.
Yeah, exactly.
And you know, and if there's a cop, I'll stop on stop sign.
But if there's no cop, I'll stop.
By crashing into them.
And there's no cop, no stop.
You know what I'm saying?
You never know.
You never know when there's a cop,
because they hide.
I know.
Hide sneakily.
And they'll sneakily try and get you.
In my six years of driving, I've only been stopped twice.
Yeah, I mean.
Both unrelated to speed.
I'm not telling you.
I'm not telling you how to drive.
Yeah, I mean, I speed on the highway.
I think everyone speeds on the highway.
You come to California out and come in my car.
I'll definitely be speeding.
You'll feel the wind.
It'll be the last thing you ever feel.
The next one is called, you know that one.
Okay, hang on.
It is downloading.
Okay, I'm ready.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm so dumb.
Anyways, whenever you meet again,
can you take a picture of doing the soy jacks
pointing backwards in the face for?
That would be funny.
We should have done that when you visited.
Did you hear the voicemail?
Sorry, I got food delivered.
It's soy jacks pointing.
He just wanted us to do the meme
where we both point behind us.
Here we go.
Soy.
I don't know.
I would do it.
It is a funny idea.
We should have done it.
It's a missed opportunity.
I actually look like the guy now.
I look like the guy, not the real one in the picture,
but the drawn version that's bald and has a beard.
Like that's just what I look like now.
You should do that.
But you guys do the pose,
but you're guys are in front of Trixie's house.
In front of her like address.
Stalking.
Like, oh, we found her.
And then we do the faces like out on the street
looking at the house.
And then another one like in front of her front door.
And then another one like with the door open,
like pointing inside the house as like the people inside
are like, what?
They're like scared that we're like breaking in.
And then another one like on top of Trixie,
like duct tape and like tied up and hog tied.
We were like, oh, holding her behind us.
We just point to her, make the face.
And then the final one is us like over like an unmarked gray.
He was just like pointing back behind us.
Like, oh, so we did it.
This is my fantasy.
I think it'd be funny for the first one
when you guys are pointing to the front of her house.
She's coming outside just like that one picture of boogie
with the gun.
Or it could be Riley with the gun
because he's like fat enough.
Yeah, Riley.
That would be a fun photo shoot
if it weren't so actually dangerous.
Yeah, if it weren't, if it were,
if we could do it without like actually
He's about to introduce you to a big having connection right now.
If we could, if we could, if we just,
if we just happened to be there,
and like we knew that like no one would see us
and like we knew that like nothing was going to happen
and we could just do it just for funny.
It would be funny to pose in front of the house
just like, oh, we did it.
We made the pilgrimage.
But no, I wouldn't,
if I actually did it, it would be bizarre
and I would be rightfully shamed for it.
LaMau.
Smash cut to Ben doing it.
Smash cut to me being rightfully shamed for it.
Yeah, true.
Okay, how many more?
We must be getting down there.
There's like one, two, three, four, five, six more.
Seven more.
This one is a, what is this?
You said there were seven more.
Okay.
Seven to 10.
I wasn't, I did, I glanced at it.
What is this?
Fast upload something, something slash file.
I don't know what this is.
It's not loading for me.
I'll post the link in case somebody else can see it.
But I can't.
I mean, I think it's pretty unlikely
that it's going to work for me.
It's, it doesn't download anything for you.
No, there's no page.
It's not, oh, connection timed out.
Error code.
Okay.
That's not working.
Yeah.
Sorry, fast uploader.
That's too bad.
Let me try it one more time.
No, it's not letting.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
I wonder what it could have been.
Cheesy, you get anything?
Um, like fast upload.
Nah, this is.
No, no, well, ah, well.
The next one is a one piece chapters.com slash something,
something, and it's a link to one piece scans.
Okay.
Why?
Um, maybe it's the preferred scan.
It does look very good actually.
TCB scans.
There was a voicemail, but it's not loading for me.
Uh, yeah, I'll, I'll, I'll just post it.
It's not loading.
The voicemail itself is like eight seconds long.
So I don't know whether it's relevant.
Okay.
He says he recommends reading one piece through,
yeah, this, this website or a vis media,
the scan quality and the translations are better.
Understood.
This does look very good.
Uh, well, maybe I will use this going forward then.
Okay.
The next one, next voicemail is another image.
Oh, all right.
That's interesting.
Great.
Oh, this is how they're, this is how they're like seeing your
profile picture.
They think it's a beak with a beard.
Well, it's not a beak.
Huh.
It's your, that's, that's your ear thing.
Uh, I can see it though.
Oh, kind of.
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that one.
I thought you meant your profile picture on discord.
I was about to say that looks.
No, no, it's an older one, older profile.
Well, this, well, this is what I still use on Twitter.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, hmm.
Okay.
Yeah, I kind of see it if you, if you read the ear as a beak.
Sure.
Neat.
Funny.
Uh, lol.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll redesign.
So I should read, redesign,
reploid me to look like this.
I'll give him a name.
Why don't you use your profile for this one?
His name would be like, his name would be like
slime, slime corvid.
That's pretty good.
That's not bad.
You can, we can, we can workshop it.
Not slime, swan.
Well, does that look, does that look like a swan to you?
Does any of the fucking animals look like they're animals?
Looks like a furby with a beard.
They never do.
Sometimes chill penguin looks like a penguin.
Yeah.
That's, it's not an apartment.
It's not a fucking apartment really.
I mean, storm.
I mean, like, it's like most, most of the time.
Never played any of the Mega Man X games.
Most of the time they are recognizably.
Okay.
For confidence, I will say that they look,
they don't look like animals.
Sometimes they're a little iffy.
It's true.
Slime.
She's a cat.
Slime swallow.
Yeah, I have a cat.
I heard a cat.
Yeah, he's a, he's a little guy.
He's a little guy.
His name is spooky.
Oh yeah.
Poopy.
Spooky.
Poopy's on the strip.
No, shut up.
Stop.
Stop bullying me.
Stop bullying me right now.
Poopy's on the strip.
No, no, you're wrong.
We all hung out at Poopy's on the strip.
All right.
I'll, I'll post a picture of him.
Because he's a, he's, he's quite a little fella.
And he's, he's got like.
It's the next voicemail.
Guys, be honest with me.
Is this the worst podcast episode ever?
Or is it the best?
It's one or the other?
Uh, why would it be the worst?
Because it's long.
No, that's what they like.
That is what they like.
They like it long.
For some reason.
These piggies love to eat their sloth.
They like taking a long,
they take, like taking a long hard podcast.
He's got a little sweater on.
Yeah, we got him a little gay sweater one time.
He's got a, he's got a gay little sweater.
Look at that little twink.
Look at that little twink base.
That little, that little fruity boy.
That fruity little queer mo.
That fruity little, he's so effeminate.
We all, we train him to be homophobic.
This is how people, this is how your cousin see you, Ben.
Oh, look at the little gay boy.
He's a little gay boy.
This gay little sweater.
Oh, he's in a little, oh, he's in a little sweater.
Oh, he's got a little shoes on.
Sad.
He's got a little gay little podcast.
Oh, he's got a little, oh, he put a little YouTube video.
Oh, he made a little ad revenue.
That's nice for him.
Sorry, I got, sorry.
I got to go do renovations on my house that I own.
Sorry, I got to go, I got to go arrest my tenant
and give him over to the police.
All right, bye.
Damn, I'm just jealous.
You know what?
I'm just, I'm just hating because I'm jealous.
Anyway, next voicemail.
Good thing you said.
Next, next voicemail is do it.
Good thing I said it so that nobody else can say it about me.
Did you post it?
I posted it just above the, it was above the cat image.
Oh, right.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Please, please, please, Pokemon Park.
It's so fun.
Thank you, my big friends.
Pokemon Park.
What is that?
I believe it is that.
Is that a Switch game?
It's the one with like the Pokemon, like little wind up toys.
Wait, is it?
It's a theme park.
Pokemon Park?
No, wait.
What is Pokemon Park?
Can you hear my Google bit?
He also called it Pokemon Ranger.
No, I do not hear the cat purring.
Thank you very much.
And I would not like to.
Do not let me hear that cat purring.
Don't let that fucking cat purring.
There will be hell to pay.
What you gonna do?
You can't do nothing.
You're in Boston, bitch.
Okay, Pokemon Ranger is an action role-playing video game.
Oh, God.
It is radically different from the traditional Pokemon RPGs.
You control a Ranger in the Fiore region and catch Pokemon
by using a device called the Capture Styler,
which is controlled by the stylus.
The storyline of the game is set out in 10 main missions.
The only Pokemon that you have a Minon or a Plussel as your companion.
Wow, okay.
So it's completely different.
That's kind of interesting.
Is it good?
This guy seems to think it's good.
I guess we'll get back to you on that.
Might take a look at it, perhaps.
Okay, all right.
So you like circle man up the stylus.
There's a lot of dragons.
There's a lot of dragons on the cover.
The cover is Charizard.
There's Kingdra.
There's Flygon and Salamence.
Wow.
Okay, anyway, what's the next one?
Next one is called Nome Talk.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Oh, yeah, Nome Talk.
My favorite ancient gnome, Nome Chomsky.
Nome Chomsky's ancient?
No, my favorite Asian gnome.
Oh, ancient gnome.
I think it will be.
For a while, I was hearing people talk about Nome Chomsky a lot.
Haven't really heard much about him in the last year or so.
I feel like he kind of became a little less relevant.
Is Nome Chomsky the guy who is like pro-Russia in the war thing?
I'm not sure.
Was he like a cool guy who went cringe?
I feel like there's an old man, cool guy who went cringe on Russia.
I think you might be thinking of the guy, yeah.
I think he's still cool, just that his oldness has caused him to say cringe things.
I'm not really sure what his Russia take is.
I know that he's a leftoid and was kind of a lib.
And I remember he was very pro-Biden.
People were disappointed that he was very enthusiastically like,
you need to vote for Biden if it's even like, yeah,
it's bad that they didn't let Bernie run.
But you need to vote for Biden because climate change is such an important issue,
which is true.
And then, yeah, I don't know what is Russia.
I think I might have heard someone say that he's anti-NATO.
He's anti-NATO.
Yeah, that's it.
I think he's pro-Russia in the sense that he's not pro-Ukraine in the war
and not pro-NATO.
And saying like, NATO caused Russia to, forced Russia to fight back.
And I'm like, eh.
Honestly, I mean maybe.
I've heard things that contradict that, so I don't know.
I have not, yeah, I don't really have, I can't really have a take on it.
There's like too much to that situation for me to even really be like,
I definitely disagree with that or not.
Next one?
Okay.
Next one is called white lander, but I misspelled it.
Who's lander?
Three, two, one, go.
I just wanted to point out how funny it was when you thought that Argentina meant
white land because there is a meme.
The Argentina is white meme, which is based on how many white supremacists there are in Argentina.
Which is kind of funny because, well, you know, we, all of the countries in South America are
mixed race mostly and over half of the population in Argentina are, you know, First Nation.
So it's kind of weird.
There is so many white nationalists in Argentina who think that Argentina is both
like Aryan white.
I don't know what the fuck they think, honestly.
But it's, it made me laugh.
So that, okay.
Yeah, that's, yeah, that's the meme.
A lot of like Nazis escaped to Argentina after World War II.
That's what I was going to say.
Isn't that, isn't it the case that a lot of like, a lot of like Nazi people were fleeing
like the Nuremberg trials after World War II and a bunch of like Nazi Germans like
fled to Argentina?
I've heard that before.
Lol.
Yeah.
Did they go there because they thought it was the white place?
I, I don't think so.
No, I think I think I've heard about the government being super friendly to white supremacists
because like after the Civil War, apparently like a bunch of Confederates like went down
to South America.
Confederates?
Yeah.
Oh, that's the American Civil War, right?
Yeah, American Civil War.
They went down there.
I don't know if Argentina, but like somewhere in South America, I know there's like a whole
town that's like a Confederate town.
Crazy.
I know that different, I know, I know different countries in South America have different like
sort of like like racial makeups and in some countries it's more like the divide between
like Caucasian people and colored people is like broader and more distinct than it is in others.
And yeah, I think I was kind of, I did think I'd heard that specifically about like
Germans fled to Argentina.
Yeah, we're seeing them.
Yeah.
You ever seen that invincible meme where it's like, the caption is like, when you're
Argentinian grandson goes up to you and asks you why is his last name German?
And it's like, it's fucking of the man from invincible.
And he's like, it's like that one scene where he has to always telling a mark about like the
true plan of like invading the human race.
But of the man is like edited to look like like an old German man.
I don't think I've seen that one.
And I probably wouldn't get it because I because I haven't seen invincible.
But I have.
I've seen like similar memes like like never ask never ask a man his what he makes never ask
a woman her age, never ask a white Argentinian like what his grandparents were doing during
World War Two or something like that.
Law.
Every time I think about Argentinians that like Nazis, that's the Argentinian.
I think of that one scene in X-Men first class where Magneto is in Argentina.
Any fucking murders, both of those Nazis with his power.
That scene was so badass.
Which which one was that?
Which I think that was X-Men first class.
Okay, I didn't see that one.
Yeah, that was like part of the new reboots.
They did a couple years ago.
Those went to like shit real quick.
Yeah.
I don't I watched the old I watched the old ones.
I think I saw the first two.
I saw the one where they break Magneto out by giving him a little bit of they put the iron in
that guy's blood.
Yeah, he sucks the iron out of his blood.
That was pretty good.
That scene was base.
I love my favorite scene in the first X-Men movie is like when Wolverine first meets all
the other X-Men and he like thinks that them having code names is so goofy.
Yeah, he goes up to Professor X and he's like, what do they call you wheels?
What do they call you?
Wheels.
Abelist.
He was born in the 17th century.
He doesn't know any better.
Is he that old?
Yeah, he's old.
He didn't know that.
I knew he was really old.
I didn't know he was that old.
Oh, he was.
I had no idea.
I thought he was just a guy who's one day got like bones of steel.
I thought he might have been like a hundred because like I know he's like extremely long
lived because of his regenerative factor.
Oh, of course.
Yeah, like since the 17th century.
He's been around.
And he's short.
He's like he's like a short stocky king in the in the comics and they sort of they sort of
made him look like more normal.
They kind of race that in the movies.
Yeah, right.
But and in the cartoon too, in the cartoon, he just looks the same as everyone.
I got the same build as Cyclops and everything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's been he's been around a while.
I think his I think his first appearance was in I think he first showed up in a whole comic
was when Wolverine first showed up.
Enough about Wolverine facts.
You guys want to go for the rest of the voicemail?
Let's do the next voicemail.
How many more?
We must have not many more to go.
This is the last one.
Nice.
Is the Vinnie comic.
The Vinnie comic of the week.
Oh, it's Vinnie.
Okay.
Tell me when it's loaded for you.
What what is this what is this?
Vinnie, you can't you can't you can't put words in my mouth like this.
It's it's still loading for me.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to make a comic like this and make Ben and Gibb be like,
actually, cheesy royalty was a badass idea.
You should totally do that base.
I have a I have a funny feeling.
I have a feeling this one's going to be funny.
Okay, this guy recommended me on the anger too.
So you should look at this image.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, when I that's pretty good.
How much is that?
That is about that's got to be 200 and that's maybe like 250 or something.
That's got to be 30 pounds of dairy.
I think the blue and the yellow plates are 45.
And I think I'm not could be more, actually.
So it's pretty good.
That's way more than I could lift.
It's a respectable squat.
I am looking respectfully.
I'm looking for knowledge.
You see, I want to get to where this lady is.
And and good squat posture is important.
So I need to look at a lot of them.
And yeah, it's important.
Don't forget when when you get to here, you know, post plenty of pics online,
you know, we want to want to root for you.
We want to root for you, Gibb.
You know, we're yeah, yeah.
No, no, definitely, definitely.
Did I mention that I'm back to lifting?
Did I mention I'm lifting again?
I'm not.
That feels good.
I think you did mention I've been doing it for maybe like for maybe three weeks
for a month now.
And I'm it's fun.
I like it.
God fucking damn it.
OK, sorry.
I'm switching back to my hot mobile hotspot.
And maybe that will work this time.
You know, I'll be I'll be I'll be squatting this much.
In maybe in a few months.
And then just letting you know that if you're doing squats, you know,
post videos like these two, you know, because we're rooting for you out there.
Big man, because we're oh, yeah, OK, I want to be rooted for.
I want to be exactly, you know, we want to we want to admire the physique
that you're going for, right?
Uh, I want to be I want to be mired.
Yeah, I want to be mired.
OK, so it's just one image, right?
Yes.
OK, OK, so me go exhaling vape.
I love vapors in my lungs.
See, that seems true.
But then look, look at what I'm saying.
Tee hee, ha ha.
I love when Vinny sends me memes.
Heart react.
I've never done that.
I've never once heart reacted.
Shake your DMs.
Vinny, Vinny sends me memes.
And once that occasionally I will have a comment in response.
Most of the time I do not.
The memes have to be gold standard.
They have to be platinum memes for me to to even crack a smile.
I've got a I've got a very advanced palette.
Then I say, I wonder if Ben St would let me invite Vinny to an episode of the PCP.
Lol, maybe.
You know, this is exactly what I would say.
I can't believe you're always you're always wondering that you're all you're always
you're always wondering that as soon as the episode ends and we stop recording.
You're always asking me that and I'm always saying I know and I'm always
saying, you know, I was thinking the exact same thing.
We just never get around to it.
Vinny needs to redraw this and I'm going to give his place and I'm like, ha ha.
He's so funny.
I wonder if Pan will be down with letting him be a guest on the pizza party podcast.
He's really so funny.
Pan should let me be the co-host of the pizza party podcast because all his co-hosts
have abandoned him and I will be loyal.
I will be I will be unflinchingly loyal to pizza pan if I can be his podcast.
Pizza pan.
I think I think pan has like it's pretty much on this that peanut boat.
Like he's not he's not leaving this.
And I think I think that's like two things because like one like that peanut will do
everything for him, right?
Which is like, oh, thank God for him.
Right.
And also like like Daph is never going to like.
Daph is kind of like, oh, a weird like kind of yes man to pan and also like he's popular.
Right.
It's that's good for pan too.
Well, I see the appeal.
So I guess I can't compete with that.
Ben, do you think you could do you think you could bring up a topic to pan pizza?
And then he says, yeah, yeah.
And then you bring up another topic right after.
Do you think you have that skill?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, I think I got it.
Yeah, I think I damn.
Damn, are you telling me that I could do I should do what he does and he should clean my balls?
Yes.
That's so funny because he's cleaning pan pizzas balls.
And so you'll be doing that too.
If those balls will be spotless, you'll be able to see your face in them.
I want to I want to be able to eat off those balls because that's what I'm going to do
after this podcast is over.
He needs them balls nice and clean before neon coffee comes to visit.
He's a spotless man.
Well, if you're the man for the job, you gotta.
What would what would what would Vinny have?
What would Vinny even have to say on on on the PCP?
What does he want to be a guest for?
What does he want to talk about?
He says he says I wonder if Ben St would let me invite Vinny to an episode of the PCP.
But why?
Vinny is just inflating his own ego.
He wants to believe that I would say this.
Vinny, I love your comics, but I don't know.
Vinny, baby.
I mean, I guess you could give a good guess.
What's there to say?
It's just funny that you would make me say it in a comic.
I'm not actually to against it.
It's just I don't know why it's it's down down here.
It says I drew this real quick Saturday night on my tablet.
You've probably forgot, but I have sent in picture I've drawn on my tablet to the PCP before.
The one there was with CWC Sonichu with the shadow of a dick cast over her face.
Oh, that was you.
OK, I do remember that one.
Then there was the samurai baby, you know, in the ninja outfit with face covered by mask.
No, sexy law.
No, sexy.
OK. Oh, yeah, I do remember that.
I do remember that.
OK.
You know, I think there is another one.
I think we got a last minute voice.
Yes, is it Yo Sly Mernalia?
Yeah.
Should I post it?
I'll post it.
Yeah, I got it.
Sweet.
Let's see if it works.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo Sly Mernalia, everybody.
Hey, just calling in, checking in, letting you know,
join the PCP Minecraft server.
Just like the last few years, we're doing a little wish list, you know,
send type out your wish list, send it to Phoebus or I think it was mage.
I think that was the lore.
But yeah, you know, get some cool items for your Minecraft.
Oh, cheat, cheat, some Pokemon stuff, whatever.
I don't know.
Fuck it.
Have a good one or whatever the hell you celebrate as long as it's Sly Mernalia.
Right.
Remember, was it, was there a, was there a Sly Mernalia event last year?
I actually don't remember.
There must have been, but I don't know whether we knew about it.
I don't remember if it was last year, but I do remember doing some,
some holiday festivities in the, in the PCP Minecraft server.
Yeah.
That may have been Easter of last year or something.
There was like a rabbit catching thing.
How does, how does eggs, how does someone join the, the Minecraft server?
I mean, I guess if you're a patron, right?
If you're a patron, you get access to the Minecraft server.
I'm pretty sure Marin, I'm pretty sure Marin just lets people in again, against our will.
I'm pretty sure, I'm pretty sure Marin is just, is just, is just going behind our back
and over our heads on that one.
And I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not even.
I'm not even, I'm not actually that mad, although I should be, but I'm not.
So whatever.
Marin will get you into the PCP Minecraft, but please become a patron also.
Maybe we should just let people into the PCP Minecraft server.
Maybe we should just not make that exclusive anymore.
Because the, the, the, the, the, the upshot of that is just that there were very few people
in the server and that's, that's kind of not really beneficial to it.
Because most people who are patrons are not patrons specifically for the Minecraft server.
So maybe we should just open that up.
I think it'd be good.
Marin, let's just-
It'd be fun to see people around.
Yeah, Marin.
Maybe it'll get more people interested in the streams as well.
Let's just, I'll just say it.
Marin, just let anyone into the fucking Minecraft server.
It's not, it's not an exclusive patron thing anymore.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, it's, that's it.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Uh, I guess that's the end.
So I'll ask you one more time.
Did anything interesting happen to you this week?
To me?
Everyone.
I, um, I finished rough drafting Ms. Nick Paglacci.
That's coming out next month.
Oh, yeah.
The what thing?
Nick Paglacci is coming out.
Nick Paglacci?
First of all, I'm like 90% sure it's pronounced Paglacci.
Yeah, bitch, I bet it's pronounced that way, motherfucker.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
I bet you pronounce it that way.
But it's, uh, yeah, that's, um, it's the opera, the clown opera Paglacci,
but drawn with the McDonald's past.
Yeah, it's starting the Ronald McDonald gang.
I, uh, I think I told you that I thought that was a really funny premise a long time ago.
I'm glad you're finally doing it.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's all done in rough draft.
I just actually got to draw it.
And then I'm going to, if Twitter is not dead by the time this video's out,
I'm pretty sure, like, I don't know, the whole thing with like, oh, you can't link other sites
or blah, blah, blah, I'm pretty sure they're going to change that in a couple of hours.
Yeah, I think so too.
That's too fucking stupid.
It's the stupidest fucking move ever.
But if Twitter is not dead, I'm going to be posting that on Twitter.
And then how was that?
How long is it?
It's going to be, uh, it's going to be 60 pages.
Oh, wow.
God damn.
But, um, yeah, I think I could crank this up pretty good because it's not going to be
a black and white.
It's going to be a red and white.
Yeah.
Oh, like downwell.
It's going to be red and slightly yellowish white.
You know.
Really?
Like no black?
Uh, no, because I'm trying to like imitate like Ronald McDonald colors.
But like, I guess kind of like how the wrapper looks like when you order a burger.
Kind of.
Um, oh, I see.
I mean, you, you should use, you should use, you should use red on white, but with like
yellow dots for like screen tones.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm just, I'm just throwing out ideas here.
I, um, I did, um, I drew like a little test image for what the characters would look like.
I don't know if you saw it.
I think I read it.
I don't think, I don't think so.
Yeah.
But, um, it was kind of like, yeah, it was just to see like, okay, this is kind of like
the style I'm going to go for in the comic.
I mean, it's going to be as cartoon, cartoon-y as like everything else I've been doing, you know.
Yeah.
So, um,
Sure.
And, um, I'm pretty sure it kind of get out pretty quickly because there's not going to be no color in it.
And, um,
I think that's really funny.
I think that's going to be cool.
I think you'll like it.
You'll finally, you'll finally be proud of me.
It lasts.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
I think they're right there.
The way they look like.
Yeah.
All right.
Uh, I don't know.
I'll keep an eye on for that.
I think let's, let's wrap up.
All right.
Hey, hey listeners, become a patron.
Sorry.
I just, uh,
unexclusive your exclusive, uh, uh,
PCP Minecraft server access.
Sorry about that.
Become a patron anyway.
For bonus content.
And get access to the exclusive bonus podcasts.
Yes.
Episodes.
Um, when Nate, you know,
I asked Nate for a status update on the,
on the OVA and he has not responded.
Oh yeah.
I saw.
But, uh, I assume he will.
And, uh, whenever that's done,
we are definitely going to have some bonus stuff to do.
I have some, we should,
we should make some bonus stuff related to that.
Um, nothing new.
Commentary tricks.
Nothing new for a little bit,
but there's all the old stuff
and there will be new commentaries
and there will be new bonus content
in the not too distant future.
So become a patron if you like.
Uh,
Where's the status update of when is Nate coming back?
That's what I don't know.
I don't know.
He months ago,
he said he was going to start working on it
and then he didn't start working on it.
And then he finally said,
okay, I'm going to start working on it.
And then like a month later,
he said, okay, I've started working on it.
And so I don't know.
He says he's working on it,
but I don't know if he is or not.
That's the status update.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Anyway, let's end the episode.
All right.
Okay.
Bye.
It's the end.
Thanks.
Bye.
Follow Cheesy Manfredo.
Follow deadly comics as well.
Yeah.
Follow them once they follow me back on Twitter.