Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Here we are
in the desert drought land of the dark YouTube arc. And I'm here by my lonesome. Let me tell
you a story. Let me tell you a little story, okay? So I woke up today, wasn't feeling very good.
I like hurt my back again. I had like a second spot where I thought I might have hurt my back
yesterday. So I rolled out of bed. I use the term roll loosely because I can't really move that much
at all. But I rolled out of bed, came downstairs, started a 3D print. Have I mentioned on The Pro
Crastinators Podcast I got a 3D printer? I think so. I started a 3D print, been dialing in some
settings, making some cool shit, which you'll see in the few months I suppose maybe. And that was,
I went out, I got some some snacks, came back, checked on the print, it was doing okay. And I
rolled into discord and it's like, huh, wonder how many people showed up for the PCP today?
I'm like a half an hour late. Let's see. Zero. It hadn't started. Nobody even remembered to
fucking start it. So I messaged everybody and I was like, Hey, what's going on the PCP? And I had
to check the calendar. I'm like, it's Sunday, right? This is recording day. Hmm, strange.
I guess Ben is hungover, like ridiculously, according to Gib. So that's probably why he
didn't add everybody as he is one to do. And so here we are recording a little bit later than
usual. It's just me. I don't know what I'm going to say because I didn't plan on being on the episode
today, but the show must go on quite literally because this is a show. So Gib might be dropping
in at some point because I added everybody and he was the only one who responded. But we're just
going to do a chill episode today about something haven't figured it out yet. We'll get there though.
We'll get there, my friends. This is going to be a super chill laid back one man episode of the
procrastinators podcast. I guess we'll just start at the 3d printing stuff. 3d printing is pretty
fucking cool. It's been my new obsession. I talked about this on my Patreon bonus podcast,
but I've been taking a two week hiatus from the internet. I just got off of Twitter for the most
part, haven't really been going on YouTube, didn't go on any social media stuff and I haven't been
thinking about my work and my content in terms of like trying to make it good for social media
engagements. I have instead retreated and I'm trying to cleanse my brain of all that outside
influence of trying to like stress about fitting your creativity peg into the square hole of like
making things to satisfy the algorithms instead. I'm just like, I'm just going to do what I want.
And it opened up so many new possibilities. My brain's going in a million different directions.
You know, 3d printing is fucking based and cool and sick. I've been doing all these really cool
things. I've been making 3d models and blender and I'm scaling them down to little miniature
size and printing them out and dialing in the settings of the 3d printer trying to figure out
how to make it work to anybody who doesn't know how what a 3d printer is and how it works.
There are two kinds of 3d printers. There is an FDM style printer, which is the most common one.
And that's where you have like a nozzle that melts plastic to like a couple like a like 200 degrees
centigrade and then layer by layer. It goes up the entire model and recreates it in a physical
space. And that's the kind of printer I have right now. I have the anycubic i3 mega s. Maybe
I'll put a link to a picture of it in the show notes. If I'm smart, I will have done that.
So this is the printer I've been messing around with right now. And it's just really
interesting technology and how it works. It's printing at like one tenth of a millimeter
layer heights and it stacks up a bunch of them and makes figures. And I've been experimenting with
that seeing how that works. There's also another kind of printer called SLA or resin style printer.
And that's it uses like a vat of resin and then uses UV light to harden it like one layer at a
time. And those print even thinner and they make even better style of models. And those are good
for miniatures. But resin is like toxic and you breathe it and it'll fucking kill you. So you
have to wear like a respirator and wear gloves and shit. So that's on the list because that'll make
miniatures even cooler because that's pretty much exactly my use case. It's they make all their money
by selling to nerds who play D&D and want to print their own miniatures. But I'm gonna make my own
custom miniatures. So someday when I'm not gay, I'll have that. I think someone joined the call.
Who's here? Who joined? Hello. It's Gib. What's up, dude? Nothing much. I'm just on the procrastinators
podcast suddenly. Yeah, we procrastinated pretty hard starting this week's episode.
Yeah. I mean, a lot of the time it's been who's like, Hey guys, just just you know, I'm the only
one paying attention. I will announce that it's time to do PCP. But I think Ben is
indisposed in some fashion, you know, maybe a little bit of a alcohol related absence.
Hilarious. What what a what a what a good boy he is with his alcohol.
Yeah, I was just kind of killing time just talking about what I've been personally doing. I was
talking about how I took a two week break from social media and it's like reinvigorated my
brain and then you realize that making things just because like you want to is fucking cool.
Because like I was talking about this on my bonus podcast that like
my entire adult life has been spent trying to make a career on the internet like since I was 16
to right now. So like 16 years. And by just taking a break and just like purposely saying just do
whatever you want to do and like stop worrying about like how is it going to be marketable or
how's it going to work on social media like my brain just exploded. And I started thinking about
like learning how to do soldering and like buying like a raspberry pi and like soldering enough and
3d printing like cases around them so you can like make custom little micro consoles and stuff and
like soldering together like controllers so you can make little bar top arcade cabinets out of them
and like just all these crazy ideas that don't make any sense to like the kind of identity and
sort of things that I've been doing online because they're not really that marketable in terms of
being able to produce something like that at scale or things like that but they're fucking cool
and I'm just thinking about doing cool things and it's pretty liberating because like the first
time I've ever really done that in a million billion years. Yeah I really like all of that
the sort of inventiveness you have when you just like the idea of building a tiny little
console is like really cool I would never think to do anything like that. Right it's very interesting
just because like a lot of the times I'll try and I want to learn something new right because even
the stuff I'm doing right now like learning 3d and like trying to get better at it I always feel
the pressure of I don't have time to get better I need to make things I need to output things and
when you stop having to worry about social media it's like I have all the time in the world I can
do whatever the fuck I want I don't have to output shit I can just learn the thing I can learn things
that don't even matter I just do whatever the fuck I want it's cool it's fucking cool. Yeah I've
been feeling well the opposite of that that that urge to like constantly be producing
ever since ever since I announced I would do the Tezuka manga project I've been thinking
gotta stay on track gotta be focused gotta be working on that uh deadline deadline oh shit
the world is gonna end when I get one tweet who says uh you didn't finish that and that'll be me
like time to get the rope guys it's time to find a tree somewhere end it all no because
there's one tweet who said I didn't do it you gotta make a tire swing that's what you're doing right
that's what you're talking about making a tire swing just hanging out yes that's what I'm thinking of
and it's so I'm like you know I've realized in the past few weeks that I'm stupidly stressing
myself out over something that if I hadn't announced it I wouldn't even be worried in any way I would
just be working I mean I would still be worried by the fact that like you're surrounded by people who
are like collectively outputting content all the time even though individually they are taking
a while each to get their thing out but like there's always something new to watch as a viewer
something new to see something new to read and then you're there thinking I've got to keep up with
like the collective efforts of every creator on the internet and it's like it's stupid so I'm like
super stupid but I feel that all the time I feel like like when you when you and uh when you and
Ben I'll put comics I'm like oh I want to make a comic why haven't I done it why am I not doing it and
it's just like dumb dumb can't you comparing yourself even though that's like my modus operandi
like uh Ben's been working on the uh Sleiman punishment finale and he says it's very close
to being finished and I know when it's posted I'm gonna be like oh that's good like I get the
feeling it's gonna be incredible and everyone's gonna be like holy shit Ben whoa and I'm gonna be
like yeah yeah holy shit Ben you mother fuck yeah exactly it's like when new lord of ghost comes out
I'm like oh you're fucking god damn like you were doing those like once a week and I was like
yeah it's unbelievable turned into a magikar disgusting kill him kill him and seep his power
a vampiric ability soul drain that's what I need yeah it was I mean it was deceptively quick
what I was putting out I mean I was drawing the panels uh pretty fast uh but the first few weeks
I was like hurting my hand I had to slow down a bit but um the preparation for that had been going
on for months before like planning it out and and drawing all this the sketches and figuring out
panel lay on stuff so like actually doing the the the work of inking it was the only thing I was
actually doing and it made it seem like I was like a god suddenly and I felt like a god and so as
soon as I was like all right it's time to work on a new project because there's a special contest
that I want to enter um I had sort of forgotten maybe that the lord of ghost took months of prep
work and now I was expecting myself to do the entire thing in three months and it took two
months to get the story and I have one month left to draw the entire thing from scratch
and it's very daunting but I I have an announcement to make regarding that um
um for just you know just to make it a fun little thing um and so that I'm not like
suffering in silence in the darkness I'm going to be live streaming my attempt at drawing the
whole thing in a month over on my twitch uh in august I'm going to be doing like like a full
work day maybe a little less I can't remember the hours I was thinking of doing but I'm going to be
waking up eating breakfast and then streaming until like 7 30 pm me drawing the thing
and that that's going to be like every weekday of august I'm going to try and do that
and you're going to do like a regular stream or you're going to do like a silent stream where
you're just working and people can watch but you're not talking to chat or anything or you're
going to do full distraction stream where you're going to be trying to be entertaining on top of
being productive you know I I probably will try to be I'm going to have my mic on because
I do like interacting with the chat a little bit um if only if only to if only to like I don't know
express my frustration with whatever I'm doing like oh no and then people in chat can be like
don't worry and then I'll be like okay so yeah you actually react like that I can only hope that you
do ah gee you know I don't know I in my head I'm like there's no way I can actually do it uh that
quickly but at least I could make a bunch of content about it at least maybe you know people
will be interested in seeing the process maybe I could save the video and then you know when I'm a
super famous man and I have like a blu-ray of my new anime that I made this can be like footage
like commentary track I can commentate over my drawing of the original comic that started it all
or something stupid like that so it's it's that's that's august is going to be that for me
so it's like is this is this tesga comic is this like the start of a new comic that regardless of
how it performs in the tesga contest you're going to keep working with the characters and stuff or
is this kind of just a one-off thing um it it started off it was one of the characters I had
plans for a comic anyway so I was thinking you know if I want to make a comic about this character
now is a very good time to start because it's it's uh you know you gotta make a comic and submit it
so yes I'm gonna uh regardless of whether I finish it or not I'm going to continue to work on it
until it is finished and then make another chapter later and it's hopefully gonna be really cool
and I'm just I'm just I'm just it's like this is all happening from my perspective tomorrow I'm
starting tomorrow so right now I'm just doing nothing I'm just chilling out relaxing
doing stupid nothing stuff so that the color before the storm come before the storm so I know
that I enjoyed myself before I put myself through what could be hell I don't really know yet so by
the time this comes out you'll be on day five I will be yes on day five go to twitch.tv slash
give and take to to watch along uh so are you gonna start what time are you starting uh like
your time or you're gonna be streaming uh my time I'm hoping that I can get up and ready
to go by 11 a.m my time okay and then I will go all the way to 7 p.m my time and I think
I've worked it out in American in EST at least that's like from 6 a.m to 2 30 p.m so it's if
you're up at the the beginning of the day or like half first half of the day and you're like I'm
bored I will watch give and take that that that's that's the time so when this episode comes out
you'll be just about starting to wrap up on Friday yeah interesting go catch the last
25 or so minutes of of the struggle that Gibba takes undertaking undertaking
ooh now now I'm now I'm really invested now I'm ready to go if sans is going to be there
I'm I'm I'm I'm game I'm locked in uh yeah it's not sans it's my new original character times new
roman oh shit it's aerial the the new waifu version of sans she's got she's got like spine
bone hair you know like like hairs that look like little miniature spines coming down
it's pretty dope that's that's an original character do not steal right there yep put
put that in lord of ghosts you know I easily could lord of ghosts is just full of like cool
character designs in the background is lord of ghosts is done are you still gonna keep working
on them I cut it off at a point where it could be done if I wanted it to be but I do want to finish
like lord of ghosts coming back with his army of the dead and being like I'll take over the endless
war and kill it forever so there's some sort of plan but I don't I haven't actually written it yet
that would be cool be sick oh god I almost I have this giant can of golden bear light
lemonade and I almost knocked it off the table onto my computer that would have been bad I'm
gonna move that away from there oh dear um shit I'm so unprepared in terms of things I wanted to
talk about because I was not planning on being on today I was just gonna I was gonna let Ben
take the reins as he is one to do but holy shit we gotta we gotta come up with something we gotta
we gotta pull something ever it's only been 17 minutes 17 minutes is not long enough for a
procrastinator's podcast episode well I uh I can I can pad this out for a little bit
all right you have 45 minutes to go okay let me go very slow um recently uh geowizard
youtuber and cool bloke um the guy who did the mission across wiles I don't know if you if you
watch that uh was the um the the mission to walk across the country of wiles in a completely
straight line using a gps tracker and uh I talked about him on the podcast before and he has since
then done a couple another a couple missions similar to that but not exactly the same but
recently he did uh an attempt a second attempt at this this challenge and it was a it was really
good I really love his his videos it's it's just something like tv quality about the the production
not in not in a sense of like high fidelity um footage but sort of it's a really really
interesting concept with you know well structured storytelling beats and editing that just sort
of make it flow really nicely and he's very funny and it's really just very interesting
and that sort of stuff just really gets me going really gets me inspired I know how you
earlier you were saying like when you're not thinking about like being a content machine and
doing stuff for social media and you just let yourself do stuff even if it's not going to be
profitable necessarily it's just like what do you want to do I want to do that I have no like
real outdoorsy experience I've gone on a couple walks and a hike maybe I've camped a couple times
but that sort of thing is like it's just so cool like I I went on after watching uh the
latest episode and I was just like looking at google earth google maps and just scrolling around like
what part of england could I just walk across could I just walk all the way to the fucking sea
from my house how long would that take would I need to pack lunch probably it's like ah the world is
so big and there's so much cool shit even in even in the tiniest of of country is the tiniest of
islands there's just so much to see human beings are so infinitesimally small in the grand scale of
even the smallest part of the earth it's just so so big guys I love geology I love geography I love
all of that and I'm like yeah I want to do it but then I keep thinking oh yeah COVID
time to just crumple into a into a I don't know this is like the perfect time to do it
though because then you can just do it nobody will bother you you know you can just go like like
no one's gonna like chase you out of a place you're not supposed to be because they're all
locked inside you can just like this is the perfect time to like life hack and take like
weird areas and go to places you shouldn't go because there'll be less people around to keep
you out of that I suppose that's true yeah I'm thinking of like I don't know getting a backpack
together I mean it's August so it would be a very like if it was a hot day it would be a devastating
sort of time to do this because you'd need a lot more water with you and I don't really know how
to live off the land or start a campfire on my own I mean you need a lighter and wood
so that's not too difficult it's gotta gotta learn just gotta teach yourself all I gotta learn I gotta
do I gotta go I think first step is like learning from like going on a hiking club like a finding
a hiking group to go hiking with and seeing seeing how fun that is just you know doing doing it the
baby way before I like try to tackle the wilderness with nothing but my wits because I don't have any
I'm looking at the the wits tank and it's empty sure I mean I think that's a good
good mentality for learning any new skill is always start with like the least possible
resistance and then build yourself up because like so many times I'm going a little bit more
macro with this but I think it applies to really any new skill or any new hobby anybody gets into
you'll be a new person doesn't know anything about x subject and you'll go look online or
like go join a group or ask people or like research things out like how do I get started in this
and then they'll recommend something like two steps above like the very basic thing because
like it's the best thing to do it'll last you the longest it's the best value or whatever it's like
the best thing to do and then you'll do that but you risk like losing incentive because
it's a little bit above your pay grade because you're talking to enthusiasts you're talking to
people who have more knowledge so they can look at something that's a little bit more complicated
than a beginner level and be like this is a way better thing to get or way better place to start
or way better thing to like wet your teeth on but you'll like pull that back and be like I'm super
baby mode I probably shouldn't do that and then those same enthusiasts will kind of like give you
for it because I'm just thinking in terms of like when I started doing game dev like everyone said
you know like use Godot or use Unity or whatever and I use construct 3 instead and it's like not
real programming and they're like why are you using that it's like shitty and it's like not as good
as these things it's like yeah but I don't know what the fuck I'm doing I've told myself for 15
years I can't do this so like I need those little like small baby step wins to give me the the
confidence to keep going because if you just dive into the deep end or just like you know
like an enthusiast grade thing or you know put it bring it back to your example if like you just
went out in the wilderness like with a couple youtube videos under your belt telling you like
your best practices that's way different than like starting something really really simple just
kind of like ease yourself into it it was the same thing with 3d printing like there was like a
really like you know get a ender three kit and put it together and like then spend another
hundred dollars in upgrades and like pull it apart and put it back together and I got like
i3 mega which was already preassembled and had all those upgrades pretty much already installed
and it's like yeah I don't understand how the whole thing works like you would putting a kit
together but like I'm printing and making things and that's getting me much more invested in like
continuing the hobby as opposed to failing at putting this together or like getting frustrated
trying to figure out what all the upgrades meant and what they did and just getting pissed off so
like I don't know for anything you get into always like go at like the super beginner level if you
don't have any confidence with it even if that's not like the best way or the correct way to do
things that like people more into it would tell you to do yeah that such a thing that I've encountered
a lot is just the frustration of of people who are who are already know knowledgeable about a
certain subject or I mean specifically in art there are certain people who you know they drew
when they were very young and so they naturally gain some skills that they sort of take for granted
some sort of observational skills some understanding fundamental understanding that they don't even
know they have above like somebody who starts drawing at 23 or something um and when they
try to give advice they're taking advantage of not taking vultures that they're taking for granted
all of this stuff that they they sort of inherently understand and they assume other people inherently
understand it as well and they sort of just they don't know how to give the advice well
and then the person who is like not as not as like naturally into it or hadn't started at a young
enough age just doesn't understand these things that they're saying and doesn't know why it doesn't
working that's why that's why a really good teacher is important it's it's very difficult to get a
thorough proper understanding of anything from just youtube videos you need someone who knows
how to do the the entire teaching method stuff yeah I was about to say the exact same thing that
like this really like hammers home why a good teacher is so important because a great teacher
will be able to explain what they'll have the skills to do it at a high level
but the ability to describe it at a complete beginner level to like de-abstract a lot of the
kind of like essential building blocks that you don't think about as somebody new to it
but be able to then build upon those and give you that complex understanding over time
and there are some people on youtube and just teachers in general who are really good at that
and some that aren't and I think it's really easy to get into something and get a bad teacher
and assume you're too dumb for it where it's that the information wasn't given to you in a way
that works because not only do you need someone who can explain in a simple way
everybody also has like specific ways of learning things um because there's like programming and
stuff there are certain programming courses and books and videos that'll explain a subject that I
don't understand but then another person can explain that same thing and then it makes sense so
it's really weird like learning a new skill is very very finicky and you have to like be
patient with yourself to find the right teacher and find your learning style and find someone
where those two kind of paths collide and you can actually absorb the knowledge yeah you gotta
you gotta spread yourself out try try what is the word something the market you gotta you gotta
test the waters with all different like a variety of people because um in like if you if you went
to a class uh the teacher if you don't get what they're saying you can put your hand up and say
what ha like they can understand that you need help in this specific explanation but in a youtube
video you can't really do that you can like ask comments but like a lot of the time you find a
youtube tutorial and it's very old or like they just don't check the comments after a certain point
and it sort of feels like you can't really get into contact with the people because usually the
best most popular channels they obviously get thousands of comments all the time it's like
you're gonna get it's like having one teacher with a thousand students in the class you're
never gonna get his attention so if you don't understand what he's saying you're fucked
exactly so i don't know like i mean when you when you get to that point a lot of time you'll just
be like instead of raising your hand being like huh what you just have to like keep pressing back
like five seconds watch the same thing and just saying huh what getting more and more angry each
time until you feel like an idiot yeah i tried i tried a bit of programming but it was too i i
tried to like make this is the thing that frustrated me the most out of anything in my life
when i was trying to make my website which at the time was called aps adventures and uh
is now gib and take dot site where i just host my comics and i know what i wanted it to look like
i know what i wanted it to be functionally useful for and i didn't really care about it
being extremely technically marvelous i just wanted it to work but there's so much to learn
about the very basics of html and and coding a website that it was like so daunting all i wanted
to do is just say i just want a website how do i just get one how do i just have one right do i go
to uh what's that thing the thing that has been in every video um this video by square space um
like that i was looking at i was like hmm i get the feeling this is too expensive i don't really
you know i guess i'm being a cheapskate in that like i needed an easier way i needed an easier
way and i was like i'd rather learn it myself but it was so painful to learn i just sort of didn't
have the right mind for it like a lot of the things that they were saying would just not go into
my head right and it was very difficult to try and find a very baby explanation like a of these
concepts and i still to this day don't really know how my site works and if i ever need to edit
anything it's it's very scary and i i often i think on many occasions i've gone to discord and twitter
and just like cried like star web design sucks just like crying into the void like nobody understands
you know slip my wrists but with um with a you know hgtb slash colon slash slash my wrist that's
what i was going for yeah well i think it's one of the things that i do a lot which kind of falls
into the same sort of category is like you'll go right online uh and be like okay i want to make
a website and then everyone will be like oh just learn html just learn html and css bro like just
do it and then javascript just learn javascript too and it's just like you have to ask yourself
what do i actually need to know right because like if you're trying to become a web designer
yeah learn html learn css learn javascript learn all that shit like there's so many different
fucking like tech stacks for web design now it's insane i know because my sister is like a professional
like web and ux designer and she's like yeah i do like seven jobs now it's ridiculous so like
that's a whole nightmare in and of itself but like if you're just making give and take that site
do you need to learn html like that seems like almost like a waste of time right when there are
so many tools to just do it for you it's like why do i not just use something that does it for me
i don't you have no interest in web design outside of hosting the content you care about in a public
space and my personal thing is like so many times like when i want to get into something i want to
like learn it all so it's like i want to learn all of html just to make a website for a zoomie
someday it's like but why why would i do that you know i did that for sources loss i spent like
months building an entire website from scratch and it's like cool but what was the point like i
didn't need to do that i could have just gone and done what you did and just like use a website
builder or something and it would have been just as fine so it's just like i don't know there was
this interesting thing that um uh uh uh six tin uh uh showed me uh because we talk in uh a discord
group and stuff and it was like the valve t-pose skill set mentality thing i forget exactly what
it was called but um i guess it was like a graphic from valve and it was like you have like a character
standing in a t-pose and the idea was like the spine is like your central skill and the spine
supports that skill and that's like your specialty that's like your one skill you're really good with
and then the arms support skills that you're familiar with but don't have a lot of knowledge in
and i thought that was a really smart way of thinking about like laying out your skill set
right it's like you have one thing you focus on like this is my identity this is what i am if
i was going to have a job title this would be it the like supporting like structural center skill
then i have other things branching off of that that aren't nearly as strong that i should have other
people help or do for me or outsource in some fashion but i have a working knowledge of and can
support the main skill and i thought that was a really good way of kind of reeling in at least
my personal kind of like desire of wanting to be like a one-man band and just be the autodidact
who absorbs everything and learns all the things and becomes a master of everything which is literally
impossible in one human lifetime um it was fucking cool and i like that idea yeah god i i've always
been like skill hopping i never stick with any one thing for too long i've i've become
what's the term jack of all trades yeah so like it's always been a thing i do to like
get somewhat proficient in a skill but then find that i would rather also have other skills on top
of that and i never stick with anyone long enough to like become a master at it so i'm like pretty
good at a lot of things i'm knowledgeable about programming like i watch my brother do it and
he is like very very good at it so but i can i can i have enough knowledge to comprehend what he's
doing and maybe suggest things that don't like aren't stupid but a lot of the you know i would
never be able to do anything on the level of what he does uh programming wise and it just sort of
it frustrates me that i do this like i'm i'm pretty i'm pretty adept at the drawing stuff
i'm pretty good at animation i've dabbled in music when am i gonna be like really good at
anything though that's what i want to know yeah i feel the same way i skill hop all the time and
it's like it's not even it's subconscious because like i got the 3d printer to be like i'm just
gonna try 3d printing some of my models and then i got like really into that and just like like
researching how they work and everything and modifications and like all the different kinds
i'm like this is unnecessary and then from there i started printing out like little miniature
stuff because that was like the scale of models i wanted to make and then related videos on youtube
were like how to paint d&d minis and i started watching that i'm like oh it should be super cool
if i could like paint minis and learn how to like get the proper paints and mix the washes and all
the stuff and i'm just like this is completely irrelevant this is this is not anywhere on my
t-pose of skills why am i spending like hours and days on end researching like the proper like
kinds of of acrylic based miniatures paints and like i'm doing a comparison of like starter
kits that cost like 40 a pop i don't need to know any of this none of this is relevant go back and
learn more 3d you idiot yeah well what's wrong with us what are what are we gonna do how do you
ever like see an artist on youtube or on twitter or whatever that's just like does their one thing
and has been doing it for like 10 years how how'd they do that how how do people have the focus
to just be like i'm gonna do this and i'm gonna do this forever i i mean i really don't know
it feels it feels i don't want to say it gets boring doing you know a thing i like
because that sort of implies that i will abandon it but i never really abandon anything i always
come back around to it over after a few years or months when i you know whatever the time period
is that i'm like i've you know i stopped doing crochet for a while and then i got back into it
and you know i stopped again it's just sort of like a skill that i hobby like i'm a hobby
habit i i collect hobbies and and grinding away at a single skill i feel like most people who
get extremely good at one thing don't make the conscious decision to grind away at that as a
skill they just do it because they like doing it all the time and for me the thing that i like doing
all the time is not it's not usually like a skill that i can make money off of or like an artistic
thing it's it's thinking about i don't know video game analysis and watching video game analysis
videos and and thinking about stuff stuff that isn't i mean i don't know i guess there's a
number of things that i do unconsciously all the time that i don't really have a way to turn into
something profitable but other people they they do the thing that they can turn into something
profitable all the time they just love doing it and i i envy that to an extent yeah i definitely
envy the focus because like the things that i do i i have like a complicated starting point right
of like i want to like make an animation or i want to make a comic or something and that requires
multiple skills already because you can't you know you have an artist who just draws like
i'm just going to draw furries and that's just what i do i just draw furries that's what i've
been doing since you know 2005 i'm really good at it i take commissions and i just everybody
knows exactly what my my mo is and i just do that i'm like because i want to tell stories with my art
like just by default it's like well now you're gonna do writing layout you know like there's so
many more skills involved so like right from the get-go it's like a multi-discipline goal but then
like as you learn more about those things all of those skills like branch off into other areas
and i just find myself subconsciously like asking myself questions like what if i did this or what
if i could do that and it just the my brain just kind of naturally hops from one connected point
to the next and all of a sudden i'm like knee deep and like learning how like different brands of
washes affect the paints on a dungeon and dragons miniature or a warhammer mini i'm like why am i here
how did i get here why is this my thing why do i have like a hundred dollars worth of like
mini paints in my amazon watch list right now like what is going on i just i just want to sit here
and focus on my one thing but i feel like i have at the same time like adhd and like hyper focus
at the same time where like all my attention jumps all the time but like in between jumps it's like
hyper fixated on that one thing before it jumps to the next thing become hyper fixated and uh
it's like antithetical to being productive yeah it's it's it's like you know in in a world where
time is not an issue and you can go on forever you will eventually it's like you're you're working
on you're leveling up many different skills uh one of uh you know like alternating which
skills you're leveling up rather than going full on strength or full on you know intelligence or
whatever you know dark souls or whatever so like you're you're you're spreading them out and eventually
they will all be maxed out but most human lives end before and most dark souls play chess and
sessions end before you've gotten to the point where you have enough xp to max out everything
so you will be constantly halfway there on everything and never at 100 on any one thing
and other people i don't know whether it's like right to say that other people just think differently
because i um i i get the sense that it's it's more of a uh it's like
no i can't i'm trying to think of the way to explain it it's like i think about drawing
and i draw and then i you know i get into the comic thing and i'm like okay i need to figure out
how to write the story i look into writing things and now i'm i'm going on websites and blogs that
are talking about writing for novels for books for short stories and i'm thinking maybe i could
write a book as well or add you know instead or afterwards or something like the knowledge you get
sort of takes you off in a different direction right it like opens up a new possibility for you
like you're thinking about writing for comics and someone's writing for novels like oh yeah i could
do that like i could do that and then like that seed is planted and it's like well if i was going
to write a book what would it be and then like all of a sudden that's now another thing in your
brain and it's just like well i'm gonna have to deal with that rattling around in the old gray
matter for the rest of my goddamn life now yeah and i'm like i'm wondering for the people who
don't branch off like that is it that they don't consider it or is it that they are just merely
uninterested in doing something different or is it like discipline is there someone who's just like
they have all those things in their brains and they're just like no fuck you this is the right thing to
do i mean i i suppose it could it could be any one of those things i'm thinking of like someone
like uh steven king for example he writes so much all the time so many books feasibly could you
imagine steven king getting into a different creative thing i mean you know if he just did it
one day he's like oh now he's a painter yeah that you could see it happening because creative people
they they do creative things but i get the feeling that it's not like he would i just couldn't imagine
him like deviating so completely from the thing he has done for so many years do you think i'm thinking
like is is it like i can't imagine how much discipline you would need to see all of these
creative things you could be doing and just say no every single time i feel like do you think in the
case of like someone like steven king it's because he's older and like didn't have the internet like
i'm sure like back in the day he was not you know there was no youtube for him to go look for writing
advice on he probably just like maybe he just started writing or maybe he got a book you know
that was just about that one thing that didn't have thumbnails and and the fucking related tab
on every page attempting him to go to other things just like this is what i'm gonna do
and it's a simpler time there's less distractions i've made up my mind
and like the path i go down to learn this does not have all these branching avenues that the
internet gives us now yeah i definitely think that could be part of it can you think of someone who's
young who who acts very focused on one thing i just i just think like commission artists and stuff
or like the first like really simple example they just like settle in their style and they just
they're just happy drawing like you know characters just character portraits and character
illustrations i'm like never really going to do in comics never really go into anything else
like that it's just like i'm going to draw this character i'm gonna draw this character i'm gonna
draw this character and um i don't know and then you have people who just animate they're just
they're just i mean i guess animation is like multi multi-discipline so maybe that's like
once you get into animation you feel like you're switching gears all the time and it kind of
yeah is interesting in and of itself but even then like i've done animation and like even while
animating it's like well then what if you made it a video game you know which is how like the
video game stuff started was like it started with animation then it pivoted into that because like
that was just the next step was like layering another skill on top of what was already there
and um i don't know i guess at some point it's like i started drawing as a little kid
and then it went to comics and then comics went to animation then animation went to games
it was just like layering new skills on top of each other before like the the last was even like
kind of like out of the oven yet and like some people just stop they just stop at one level
of abstraction which is like i'm just gonna draw or i'm just gonna write and i don't really
i don't know i don't have the self-control every time i've done something i've completed a work
it's like very much like because there was like a conscious uh active self-control going on to not
like go off into the weeds i wonder like if part of that is like not that the people who focus on
one thing sort of only get to level one or like only find one skill and then stick with it forever
i'm sure many people try a bunch of skills and then they find the one that they like the most
and they stay with that but also what happens is they sort of leave the other skills behind
because like with you um all of these things the the drawing the the animating the 3d modeling
and the game development like they they build on each other but you feel like you since you
have been doing all of these things potentially could do all of these different things for the
video game you could be the animator and you know all you know all all of the aspects of video game
creation that you've learned you would you would keep using all of those skills even though it's
very difficult to be a one-man army and make an entire thing uh with all of the the skills
that are required of it which is why most games are made with a team even a small one right right
so it's like if i if i wanted to make i don't know fucking i i i always have this idea for
animated music videos when i really listen to a song i'm thinking you know very very classic
like everybody knows this feeling and i'm like okay well i can draw i can animate a bit wouldn't
be cool if i did the drawing and the animation and and the you know all of all the things and
maybe even the music i mean usually i'm listening to music so i'm not thinking about that but
in in like a real life like sensible setting i would instead like be like commissioning a
team of animators to make the thing that i have the vision for i would direct it i wouldn't do
all of the work right god imagine imagine being able to have a team that just did stuff for you
oh oh the joy the joy of like all the ideas finally escaping my brain and just being out in the world
yeah and then you look at it and you're like i don't know this key frame here is not how i
would have seen it in my mind's eye it's like a little bit of uh scrap it burn it all it's not
in my perfect vision i should delete the channel start over move over entire animation team i will
do all of the work and then i try and i fail it's the feelings that that feeling of it not
oh get out of here professional programming team i'm going to program my game with elif
is that threads for is that why i i feel i thought i don't know much about that guy but i feel like
isn't it like more of a scam that he's playing like he says he's working on it but he really isn't
well there was one point taking the money i mean i'm sure i'm sure that's what he's doing now but
there was one point where like a company tiny build like worked with him he like he hire i don't
know if he hired them but like they decided to like help him make the game and they had a programmer
come in to like rewrite all of his code because it was a nightmare and he got mad that he couldn't
like work on the code himself anymore because this guy was coding way better than he was so he
fired the entire publisher developer and went back making it by himself
lol like he was so close to being free like it would have been out it could have been done by now
but i don't know because of that hubris he was like nah nah i got this and now we're like what three
years later and it still barely has progressed at all like why would he do that is it really like
i'm like not i've barely looked into this so i don't know if i'm like being stupid but like
from what small things i've heard he would have like i feel like he did that maybe to get away
with it taking an extremely long time and taking the money that's the the vibe i get from maybe
how people talk about him i mean at this point like everyone just convinced it's a scam
but i this was a few years ago when like people thought it was a scam it's super strange right
like if he had a team who could have finished it then he would have had a video game that you
could profit off of anyway like right i just i don't know it's so strange but i like i'm always
afraid of becoming that you know just like being so blinded by my own hubris that even even in the
face of like a team willing to help me i'm like no good to do it all myself like uh uh never go
full yandere dev i i feel like i could uh what i want in in like the the near future is for me to
make some of these comics and for you know my drawing skill to improve over time be like pretty good
and you know it'd be like something i could sell on on the on the store shelves or whatever i could
be like a brand leo malley almost uh who's you know he's got a very distinct cartoony style
that's very appealing and he's good at making this stuff but he's not like he's not like the biggest
like draw god of all time like the scott pilgrim increased in drawing quality as he went
and so he was definitely like improving it you know still so like as i get to a decent enough
point i can start and then i can get better as i go and then the big ideas i have for like
dude what if there's a video game of like punk and and stuff i could i then i would have like
money to to pay people to do that yeah yeah you want to just like get the ball rolling
and like start a franchise so people will want to work on the franchise you have the
money to pay people to work on the franchise and make it bigger and then there's snowballs
and you're like all right the momentum's going without me slaving away every single day to make
it happen i go to edgar right and hi all me is zaki it's a guys i want to make a comedy ghibli
film uh with bell with punk in it and they'll be like hell yeah it's like we get to work with give
and take literally our dream yeah oh no it's too cool i'm getting upset
oh god the future you know as long as i don't like throw in the towel it looks bright i have
i have more skill at art now than i did a few years ago when it was merely a twinkle in my eye
and now like the idea of making comics uh that have cool characters in them that i did and made
and i could you know it's it's it's looking like it's gonna go well the tezuka manga thing might
be a big old failure but i will definitely come commit to the thing i have and then finish it
whenever it's finished and uh there's more on the way god it's so cool the idea of the future
being better than right now that's what i like yeah i got like i got like three or four things in
the oven right now that i'm not talking about publicly man i'm stoked i'm stoked to see them
finished it'll be fucking cool a zoomie and the vertical slice and then a to me the vertical slice
to the vertical slices the vertical slices the vertical and horizontal slices slices slightly
to the lower left major this is smash bowl oh my god zoomie confirm the perpendicular slice yeah yeah
there we go somebody animate that not me though i'm too busy with other things
oh my god dude we kill it we made it to an hour we did it well 52 minutes but like we almost did it
do you think we should open up the speak pipe and listen to any uh things i was gonna say we
should go to the speak pipe but unlike ben saying we should not play every voicemail we should play
the voicemails that seem funny because oh my god uh there's over 25 already uh uh yeah there's like
26 more voicemails i don't know if do you want to listen to 26 voicemails not really but i don't
know how to tell which ones are good and which ones aren't the short ones are the best
oh no okay so this we're gonna play a game we're gonna play a game okay uh this is how
the voicemail is gonna work i'm gonna pick a voicemail that i think is gonna be good if it's good
thank god if it's bad you can uh shit on me relentlessly then you have to pick a voicemail
that's higher up like a newer one than that one the next okay and then we'll just keep going back
and forth until we get all the way to the newest one all right all right that's that's the plan
i'm gonna start with oh man we have to go back to the previous page i don't know if any of those
seem good those seem juicy there's six on the previous page yeah um all right i'm gonna pick
the fun all the way at the bottom the joker thread it's seven seconds so even if this is a
total bust not too much of our lives or wasted it's the last one on the first page the joker
thread not the joker the joker thread okay all right three two one go if nate doesn't upload a video
within three days i blow up a hospital um weak wait what what this was five days ago when did
nate upload the uh gets ghost in the shell uh review i thought it was more than five days ago but
maybe i'm wrong is this guy this is the joker a fucking idiot let's find out either way this
this voicemail did not age well best guy ever three days ago oh so this was pre dates that
the video dropped so do you think do you think nate popped into the speak pipe and uh saw that
and desperately threw together the video to save the hospital yeah it seems it seems likely
even though the video even though this was marked as unplayed before right now that's still definitely
what happened all right thank god for the video it came out after all these millions of years
incredible incredible 2020 is saved okay so now i have to choose one yes uh oh wait uh
how about smearg all right let's do smearg um one uh three two one play
hello and howdy i'll get right to the point i have an idea to present i've been listening
to a lot of hello internet and core text recently and on those shows they have sometimes what they
like to call a quote unquote book club segment i'd like to propose that as a potential segment the
pcp could have a quote unquote quote quote book club of its own you could take turns having one
of the co-hosts present one particularly interesting maybe analytical youtube video each week the other
co-hosts and listeners could then watch this video over the course of the week and it could
generate some hopefully interesting conversation for the next episode that is all thank you
see nice you had me you had me until you mess said youtube video because books high tier youtube
videos bottom tier but nate can't read so i'm glad that you included him uh books you gotta
find them and read though just go to archive videos just go to youtube.com have a let's read
of of the book an audiobook if you will i've heard of those um yeah i don't know i thought i think
munchie or some of us have had something of this kind of idea before it's just sort of
no one would do it ever no one would ever like it would be like last week hey guys i said we
should watch this video and or read this book have you got any of you guys done it everyone
says no everyone says oh i was gonna get around to that the conversation ruined um we get attempted
i suppose but like in this in this episode only us two would do it because we're the only ones here
it's true the only youtube video i've watched recently is uh episode one of the spongebob anime
which was removed from youtube well it fits removed i guess criminal that's that that's that it was
amazing did you see it before it was taken down i i have no idea what that is have you did you ever
see the um the anime op's that this one guy did first that were just spongebob but like drawn
seriously as an anime i have not oh my god they're amazing but uh they came out like a couple years
ago i'll try and find one link for the show notes but they're like really fucking good and this guy
um did an entire 15 minute like anime episode of spongebob like and like got someone to hire
a bunch of japanese vas and then dubbed it it's incredible i i typed in spongebob anime op and
i got a guy called narmak is that the guy that is the guy oh wait it's a video back up i think the
actual episode is back up spongebob anime episode one bubble bass arc it's up it's real and it has
its eight million views uh yeah legendary incredible uh i'll link it in the the the chat right now
at least i'll link that shit it's an it's insane it's it's god dear it's amazing uh yeah it was
deleted it was deleted and youtube took it down because it said it was uh not suitable for children
even though it was marked as not for children yeah dumb uh thanks youtube doing great fix our channel
fuck you youtube get the fuck out of here as we send people to go to youtube.com hilarious
yeah but that's cool that was that was good it's worth watching it's funny uh it's great
all right i guess we're doing the the uh book club idea anyway i'm gonna watch this
and next week i might even say i watched it oh my god tune in next week everybody for gib's one
sentence reaction to spongebob anime episode one all right it's my turn to pick a voicemail again
isn't it shit uh you know what i'm gonna go with margar because margar did us good uh last episode
i was on so let's listen what margar has to say it's like a couple couple slots up from smirg
are you ready to go are you still here okay yes all right excellent three two one go margar here
pcp listeners and voicemail senders let my story be an example and testament to all of you
that you too can end up in voice jail for absolutely no reason if you just send good voicemails
just keep making good quality and you will indeed be punished for it just like society
is meant to function thank you ben yeah i mean you know when you mess with the bull society
you get the horns unfair treatment yeah that's what you this is a social commentary voicemail
service doesn't matter what you're doing you will get killed and fucked with yep there is no justice
there is no fairness there is no quality all will be crushed under the heel of our boot uh because
we can sorry well uh well i mean we didn't put you in there so that's true it's all ben's fault
ben's not here it's all ben's fault we go to take it up with ben saying dot com i'd say go kill ben
but it seems like he already killed himself yesterday and now he's busy dying yeah it takes a while
for him to to die he's very strong um i'd you know i'm sort of just drawn to the ones with the
people's names that i know there's crack here that's true coda for endless war and uh cool man
so let's do that all right three two one go hey ben did you see all the tweets about UFOs being
real it's really funny how everybody was saying space jam was real when they cancelled uh the
nba for the virus and now aliens are just real uh you're an astronomer retired space cam counselor
i know you're on top of it just thinking about you all right well that was that was for ben who is
who is currently bleeding out right now yeah yeah ben is exclamation point kill all over his bed
covered in puke i i did i do not know what he's referring to so i don't i guess i can't comment
on it yeah i don't either what the fuck aliens are real now i mean sure like it's 2020 so it
makes sense we're just pulling out all the stops for the uh the final arc of humanity
are they illegal though that's that's the question i mean technically yes right they're
definitely not citizens of any country so they would be illegal aliens shit i have to pick one
again i forgot uh uh uh uh uh uh uh let's let's listen to i don't like salad uh assuming this is
from simon because the the the next thing is simon at fuck you dot com all right three two one go
guys i don't really like salad what food don't you like lol ha ha oh oh terrible terrible i don't
like gay voicemails it's the worst food it doesn't digest well none none the worst you just roll up
to the drive-through you ask for a bad voicemail thinking it's gonna be a pleasant treat it's like
yeah i just need to pick me up right now and then as soon as like it touches your lips you're like a
fuck oh god why did i do this i forgot i forgot and then you feel like shit forever so thanks simon
love you buddy yeah um i i actually do have an answer to this what food don't i like marzipan
and i i've never had marzipan i don't even know what it is i've heard the word marzipan is a
thick icing like um thing you put on cakes to make them look really nice you can mold like little
figurines out of it and it's edible obviously um huh but maybe i have had this but just not
knowing what it was but it is it it does not taste like icing which is just sugary sugar um
it tastes it has a very distinct taste and i absolutely hate it it is so delicious looking
because it just reminds me of like really chunky like birthday cake ice cream and it's like ah it
should be the best thing ever but it's so odd and good and bad in fact and i hate it it sucks
something that nice looking should not taste like that that's what that's my food that i don't like
huh i'm tempted to try it now just to just have an opinion on this contentious issue i'm looking
up pictures of it not even looks familiar i don't have cake like ever so damn uh okay do i have a
real answer to this question um cucumbers i hate cucumbers the texture offends me the taste
isn't that bad but it's not good either so it's just like neutral taste with unpleasant texture
mm-hmm can't don't like it it brings down every salad it's ever been in don't recommend zero out of
ten celery celery is like bad because the texture is a little bit more pleasant yeah it has a taste
i don't really like i don't like the taste of celery i don't avoid it it's like a weird bitterness
yeah but like i don't know by itself it's it's not it's not terrible i'd rather have like that kind
of like downward kind of bitterness of celery than like the nothing like slop that is uh cucumber
so yeah but neither are very good especially like a slightly
un-fresh cucumber that's starting to mush
like sometimes that the crunch is enough like it you you crunch it it's like yeah it's crunchy
but when it's sort of like too wet it is kind of like what is this why yeah why does this exist
why are you're not a pickle yet so you haven't gone to something good you're just a worse version
of what you already are all right i guess i'm choosing one do it uh
none of these all right i guess i'll just do the next one application all right three two one go
so this is my application on the uh podge podge and uh reason reasons well there's clearly a shortage
of members and i'm a perfect guy for it i think i could leave sweet new angle to the pcb with my
food i can't tell if this quality is like part of the bit or completely accidental
intelligent conversation yeah and uh i guess uh i guess uh jones jones is slob another
oh my god well you know if you know if i wanna uh let me on uh uh sure sure okay i'll see you then
you're hired we have you have you you have the voice quality uh uh down pat to be on the pcp
you have our level of quality perfected yes we are we're starving for new members
seriously we need we need as many members as possible everybody should be joining the pcp
should be a new fad new craze should be should be able to if you go to patreon.com slash the
procrastinators and you become a patron you're automatically entered into the random drawing
to become a member of the pcp that will be decided uh 10 years after the last procrastinators podcast
member has died so if you want to be part of that drawing that will definitely happen be sure to
become a member yeah at patreon.com slash the procrastinators and you have to stay a patron
for that entire 10 year period even as we are slowly dying like flies every every month you're in
and uh your card clears is another entry into the contest so the longer you stay the more
chances you have i'm thinking of the implication of that is that we will all be dead in 10 years only
that's all the time we have doing the pcp we'll kill lucky
uh shit now i have to pick one don't i um hmm
fuck
um all right i'm just gonna how long we've been going for because i could i could just wrap this
up right now and pick the top voicemail i'm gonna do that we're gonna pick the last the
newest voicemail the last one we got a mere hour ago why munchie why
all right are you ready yep three two one go i am literally shaking and crying right now pcp
i want to know i want you to tell me why munchie left the patreon lounge i gave the pcp five dollars
to join the discord for perhaps the honor the privilege to have maybe one or two interactions
with the legendary munchie j trump and he's gone he's nowhere to be seen why why did munchie abandon
the patreon lounge i'm i'm shaking and crying how could you do this to me uh i didn't even know
that happened did you when when did that happen uh i feel like he's been gone for a long time or at
least i mean he never really looks at it does he most of us no i i i check you know occasionally
seeing what's going on same same um there's just so many uh uh channels in the the procrastinators
lounge i'm just like man that's a lot that's a lot to sift through but i only check the the main one
i guess the off topic usually the one i check as well yeah but uh if you really want to talk to
munchie there's an easy way to do it get on a plane go to boston uh find the crazy man just
listen listen for the extremely loud foot stomps and screaming you'll find him
oh man but but for real if you want to talk to munchie he's probably much more reachable
uh on endless war the ratty fuckers cop killers endless war discord server with slime is true
you just go in there uh you become a paragon of the community and then maybe munchie will
pay attention to you you'll you'll have to draw a lot of slime you'll have to become slime but
you know it's worth it yeah there's always you know uh price a price involved in meeting your
idols the people you respect you know and uh you know at first slime is like icky and gross
and you don't want slime but you'll learn to love it you'll learn to be addicted to it uh
and you'll make the a hair gal face every time oh oh sounds sounds great sounds like a grand
grand old time uh seriously i haven't talked to munchie in a long time i don't know why he's
he's uh sort of minimizing internet stuff i get the the sense i haven't heard from him
like exactly what he is trying to do but he's like he's been doing like what i did for the last
two weeks like ever since he started school and uh he's probably all the more powerful for it i
can't imagine the fucking titan of of divine energy he emanates now i mean the other day um
he just came into one of the discords i'm in um and he was just sort of like
ratatouille like at everyone ratatouille now rat spewley right now and then like i was watching
ratatouille with him and kazi and a bunch of other people uh like five a.m so he's he's alive
he's doing stuff but he's like with you know he's not looking at twitter he's not doing
really any sort of discord watching looking at he's he's just watching rat spewley
is he making stuff or is he just kind of just vibing and enjoying life he is currently
doing a lot of coding for endless war because there's a big update coming i don't know i'm
you probably have no idea but they they've been a lot of big updates recently the in the the endless
war map uh has been increased in size in the in the way of like now there used to be districts you
would type exclamation point go to district and within those districts there are a number of
like locations like there would be a pub in some area there's a cafe there's a uh the you know the
slime labs where you can make a slimeoid various places around the city and now in those places i
haven't even really done it myself but now there are individual streets that you can go down within
those areas and it's like orders of magnitude more exploration you can do and it's very complicated
i've seen a few images of like the behind the scenes of like what it looks like to program
something like that for discord and it is there've been lots of like hurdles trying to get discord
to cooperate with such a strange thing because it's a mod that like involves hundreds of players
asking the bot for like you know you know a server is like responding to all of these requests
and then all of these different like to be in a district or a location gives you an invisible role
and there's only so many roles that can exist and so they've had to work around that
oh Jesus it's like it's it's like a nightmare and i assume he's working very hard to get whatever's
happening are we going to get to the point where endless war is going to have to like move to its
own native application i feel like they're gonna hit the limits of discord at the rate they're
going i there's definitely been moments where that has been like on the table as a thing to
definitely think about um i'm not like in with the developer crowd discord like i i don't know
exactly what's going on but i've heard talk of like but that but also part of it being on discord
is the point so like yeah they would want to keep it there if they can i suppose like some of its
identity is very i mean like the whole pitch is like you know it's a mml you play in a discord
server so like if it's not a discord server part of its identity is lost but like i would hate to
have discord hamper the game's development and growth but interesting very interesting good to
hear munchies spend all that money went to art school is doing nothing but programming
lol i mean the whole thing with covid and him not being able to go to the lessons that he bought
is like so upsetting dumb dude it's like it piss like legitimately pisses me off because like we
had all those arguments and like his big reason for going to school in the first place was to
meet people and be in the like the be in the school around the people that was the entire point that
was his big defense was that like i'll be able to pay for it i have a way to do that but i just
want to be there and mingle and now like the whole reason for going to school is like invalidated
yeah and it's the teacher is teaching is a lot less useful through like zoom or whatever
and that there was like there was like i can't remember exactly what it was but it's like
a number of classes that you know they got basically ruined but he wasn't reimbursed
for the things that he like the pandemic ruined for him he still had to pay money
for oh no it was it was it was the student accommodation since he couldn't be in the the
campus uh he was staying with uh with kazi but the um student accommodation refunded for housing
they did not get refund they just still had to pay that lawsuits incoming as soon as this
fucking covid shit is over every school if the schools aren't refunding housing they're all
gonna get hit with fucking lawsuits and they deserve to get fucked in every single one of them holy
shit yeah that's ridiculous it sucks the whole thing so god the internet stinks real life stinks
what's even what's even it's even the point what's even what are we even gonna do god damn it
the final arc of humanity is a real downer that's okay i'll just i'll just draw a funny
comic about a lady with a gun she'll shoot she'll she'll say yeehaw and shoot some enemies that's
that's the the pitch for my comic by the way uh sick pre-ordered immediately
all right well unless you have anything you'd like to add i guess we can call this episode
a wrap uh i'll just like to reiterate that i will be streaming twitch.tv slash gib and take
for the month of august every weekday from 11 a.m roughly uh to 7 30 p.m bst which is
british summertime and you can adjust for your own time zone come and see me draw and be frustrated
at some difficult parts probably and that'll be that'll be going on for as long as i can
fucking stand sick i'll probably stop by now and then see how things are going sounds pretty cool
yeah uh don't forget patreon.com slash the procrastinators if you want to support this
podcast uh we got what like how many bonus episodes we got now for five dollars and up
we got more than 52 i can't remember the holy shit cannot remember the exact three or more bonus
episodes and we just guys just recorded a new one a couple days ago right no i'm thinking of weeks
of the year how many do we actually have we have we have one bonus lie where we have one bonus
episode per month it's been going for a while i was on the last one let me just check what the
file name for that was i figure since you were on it you would have had this right there right
there ready to go no i'm stupid uh unfortunate shit uh oh no i didn't remember what the number was
so i just called it bonus episode we got a lot of bonus episodes when there's a lot of them
they're really fucking good oh we just had a new one yeah the new one was me and ben talking about
how uh we uh tits it was just me and ben talking about tits and breasts and it was really fucking
epic and it's not as crude as it sounds we got along a lot of interesting uh tangential topics
about that and it was really good you know only five dollars gets you access to an entire
discussion about titties plus tons of other episodes with similarly interesting topics
it's it's it's it just bleeds value uh you'd be a fool not to pay five dollars a month over on
patreon.com slash the procrastinators and if for some reason five dollars a little too bougie for you
all you proliterates and get in at the one dollar tier gives you access to the the patreon discord
minus munchie maybe we'll drag him back in someday we're all there having a good time
minus munchie and uh it's great it's a great time it's fun go check that out if you want to
leave voicemails uh that's speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail uh we'll listen to some of them
maybe someday nate will come back and curate them uh but until then it's just whatever
game we come up for listening to them so put your best foot forward and maybe you'll get on the show
and not end up in voice jail and uh we have twitter uh at tpcrastinators to keep you updated on the
state of our youtube channel if it ever will be revived forever get the videos back um
are we are we still trying to find all the videos i know ben was starting to get that going uh to
like kind of like see if we had backups of everything and in case we uh have to unfortunately
face that reality which seems to be ever more uh like the case because yeah they just there's nothing
happening um yeah we're we're still emailing them so eventually doing our best but there's not much
you can do unfortunately it's fucking youtube if you go on twitter at team youtube and at the tpcrastinator
what was our twitter the procrastinators yeah at at tpcrastinators at tpcrastinators uh just let
them know that you want the channel back yeah doesn't hurt if you have backups if you have
backups of uh some of the videos uh let us know because we're trying i think ben is putting
together a spreadsheet just like where all the other videos are and what we need to get back what
we already have so uh in case we have to just re-upload everything from scratch it'll be good to
know what we do and do not have access to so that would be a huge help and uh other than that i think
we're ready to end the episode everybody thanks for listening uh goodbye goodbye