Alright guys, I'm just gonna level you through right now on this episode of The Pro Crastinators
Podcast. Real fucking tuck, got shit on by a bird yesterday. This isn't a joke, I actually
got shit on by a bird yesterday. And that's the tone we're gonna start for this episode
of the PCP. Are you talking about, are you talking about, are you talking about a bird?
Uh, yeah, cause there was, you know, I'm a fifties guy and these fucking birds, these
fucking dames are shitin' on me. Tell me I got a small cock and a fat head. I don't,
I don't appreciate this making mockery effect that I had literal animal feces on me yesterday.
Tom, have you ever gotten shit by a bird? Uh, uh, yeah, uh, no. My car gets shit on
by birds all the time, cause I have to park it right under the, the, the, the, the electric
wire thing, the fucking high tension wire shit that's right going by the house. So it's
just constantly covered in bird shit and I can't, can't compete. It's too much. I'm
buried on shit. Mage, I don't know if they even have birds, let alone shit in Lithuania.
Have you even know what those two things are? Of course we have pigeons. No, no, no, no,
they were all wiped out in the war. Yeah. I mean, we're talking about real birds. Like
if any bird were to survive any wars, I feel pigeons would be the ones. That's true. That's
why you wiped them out intentionally. You couldn't have them surviving. I had, I had
almost been shot on by a pigeon almost. I thankfully dodged it, but like without even
meaning to. I have been literally shot on by a bird in the past. It has happened to me
and I know the trauma. I understand this pain. Well, okay. I was actually, yeah, it was actually
a very, like a learning experience for me. It was more informative than any trip to the
museum I've ever taken because I learned at least in my, I know that both hippo and I
guess you need to have both been shot by a bird. What's the cartoon? I imagine from watching
cartoons, it would be almost sort of like a, like a, like a white sauce, Italian like cheese
sort of like splattering on me. It would be sort of like a chunky white sort of black,
like splattering of paint ask material. But for me, um, it was like, it was like a, it
was an object. Like I, I, I, something dropped in my head and it kind of bounced off and
I looked down and I thought, Oh, look, what a weird looking berry. And then I looked up
to see what kind of tree was under and then I realized I just saw a pigeon ass and I was
like, wait a second. And then I touched that in my head and there was like an already dry
like white substance, like a white, like, like, I guess I would describe like a thin
layer of almost felt like it was like a, a white off, you know, it almost felt like it
was like a dry white off. Oh, that's my experience. Is this all the way is the way it is? Or is
there the splatter? I think it was just a sick bird. I think it was just a sick bird. I don't
know. Like that does not sound like normal. I remembered being a little more gloopy, I guess.
I don't know. If you look on, if you look at the, I got, I got a bunch of bird shit on my car
at the moment. It's like, it's black and white shit. It's a little bit smeared. So it's, it was
like mostly hard, but with goop enough to stick it to the fucking side of the car, I guess. That's
what I remember being like, more or less, more liquidy. Yeah. I was doing fucking 50 quick
catches in a row. I was getting shiny cinequilla. I got a 100% cinequilla and I was riding high.
I was euphoric in that moment. Nothing could defeat me. Nothing could even pierce my skin,
let alone my bone. And then this bird, this fucking sick ass bird came along and he shit on me.
He shit all over me. I didn't check any of the stats in my cinequilla, but I did catch four
shinies, which I will be giving away to Gib Mage and Michelle because that's what I do. And then
keeping the best one for myself, of course. Oh, it's good. It was good. I, I'm so ready
for Radcon 4 so I can get there before Hippo so I can give you all Mr. Mimes for a cheaper price.
So he'll be coming out of the satisfaction of giving you guys a Mr. Mime. That poor man. Poor bastard.
So what else is going on people? Who's got, who's got things to bring to the table? I've got one.
I've got one. Well, I should lead by example. I think I will. Thanks. So, so where was, oh yeah,
so here's what I want to talk about. So I recently put out a new video on the channel Best Guy Ever.
Maybe you've heard of it. And it was my, it was my technically fourth, really the third reel
of my like smash videos. And this one was, this one was Simon Belmont called Sign of the Cross.
And as I was making it for over a month, working on it basically every day for several
hours, probably put 100 hours into that video. Because I had to do research. I had to play some
of the games. I had to learn things and grow as a human being in order to be ready to produce
this thing for the world. Also, it was just way longer than the others. I was just thinking about
the concept of cost benefit analysis for how much time I've put in. So it's already the least
popular of my smash videos, including the Isabel one, which was a literal shitpost meme, not real
video. I feel like your entire career could be described as meditations on cost benefit analysis.
That's really the running theme from the creation of you as a baby. That's correct. That's correct.
And I, here's what I've noticed. This happened to we Agua. It happened to my like bigger editing
videos, though those started off like the current ones were already huge projects. And now with the
Ridley videos, like the smash confirmed is what I'm calling them. Like the Ridley one was the
shortest. Then there was, then the K-roll one was bigger than the Isabel one. I mean, it was
different, but it was the longest, I guess. That one doesn't count, I guess. And now this one's
over 10 minutes long, and I can't monetize it. And the fucking people who did monetize it,
because I'm using a copyrighted song, put an ad in the middle of the video that interrupts the flow
of the fucking video. It's a musical video. Please don't do that. But they did. So that's
unfortunate. But it's, everything I'm doing as I work forward, I end up committing more time to
individual things. And I'm getting, I wouldn't say less return on it, but there's kind of diminishing
returns for more effort. And I'm feeling that in a big way. This is your Cardinalism. This is your
Cardinalism that you continually do. Is that you keep, you keep getting away from the plot of
YouTube. Like you got to, you got, the whole point of doing Viagra was to escape this, this
low effort content that constantly claims you. And you keep crawling back to it. You keep going
back and like, no, I have to make these masterpiece videos. And I understand the, the inner artists
that you wanted to create something beautiful and God tier and like the greatest thing of all time.
I get that like the inner Starfleet and you wants to do this. However, we don't live in Starfleet.
We live in a cold, capitalistic, evil society where none of that shit matters and you're fucking
yourself over and it's terrible. I'm over here watching your, your, your, your fall from grace
and it pains me to no end. It's not a fall from grace guy. No, it is. You had good momentum going.
Things were great. You had these weekly videos. People loved it. You shot yourself in the foot.
I understand, but you need to make a product. But you know what it really is? This is the main
problem. It's that, and what you said is true, Tom, but I was thinking about it and I'd phrase it
like this. It's that once I had the idea to make the Simon video and I knew what song, you know,
Sign of the Cross, Iron Maiden, it's a great song and whatever just seemed like the perfect fit.
Once I knew I was going to do that and I had committed myself mentally, the idea of changing
or like modifying or scaling down the vision I had in my head was, was, there was, I like,
rejected physically. I can't do that because that's, that's like ruining something that exists in my
head and to not make it real. I get that. Nate, Nate, you had struck. I get that hardcore.
But, but here's what I say. Nate, you had struck.
God much, God much, yeah. You had struck such fucking hard, unbelievable gold with the fact
that your fans literally enjoyed Weagua. There's so many YouTube creators who are like, all right,
I'm going to switch away from the videos I actually like to make weekly garbage that no one actually
cares about. And then they lose other subscribers and everyone thinks that they're a fucking hack
fraud. But your Weagua videos, everyone fucking claims for it. Everyone adores Weagua. Everyone
loves the logo because it's the only reason why anyone would watch that show. They love the logo.
They want the t-shirts, of course. That's true. Everyone loves it. And then you're like, actually,
you know what, weekly content, it's not all it's cracked up to be. I'm going to go back to
releasing every six months, every blue moon. Listen, just do some various smoke signals and maybe
I'll come to the scene and make a video or two. Yeah, okay. I think there's a sweet spot to hit.
One is that, and I think Weagua, sorry, Mia Maffova did do this. There was enough branding
with Mia Maffova that people were excited for the next one because you hear the little jingle
every time I say Mia Maffova. There's the cool intro song. And that, I think, appealed to people.
Yeah, that's one of the tellers of Primal Brand. And then also the content, I think, was varied
enough. Yeah. And then the other thing is, I think it was different enough day to day that that kept
things fresh for people. So I don't know. I think a sweet spot like that is a good balance.
Here's what confuses me to no end. If you're spending... By the way, guys, I didn't want to
just talk about me. So I'm happy to hear a point. I just, it wasn't my point to just be like...
But this is what I've not understood, right? You said you, how long did this Simon video take you?
A month to do, you said? Over a month. Probably a month and a half. Here's my question. If it's
going to take you over a month to get this video done, why not say instead of a month, it's going
to take me five weeks? And I'll spend a couple hours of that time making a Weagua instead. And
then you shit out a Weagua. In the meantime, nobody can... People like them, so you're doing both.
If these long projects are going to take forever, what's another week if you spend a week's worth
of time making the weekly content on like the Thursday and Friday? That makes sense, Tom.
Reasonable question. The thing is a Weagua actually takes me a full week or more to get done. Then
you're even doing Weagua wrong. Stop it. I agree. I am doing it wrong because Weagua also had like
feature creep where it just got longer and longer and I added more. I don't know why I did that.
Nobody cares. I don't want it to be that way. No one needed all the giant sections that was not
necessary. Have I told you about my dream video site that I want to exist? Maybe, but tell us again.
My dream video uploading site would be a site where anybody can upload anything they want,
but your account can only upload one video a week. So it forces you to not waste your slot.
Do something good every week. You instantly cut out 99% of YouTube's bullshit. You're not going
to waste your one slot on a reaction vlog to something that's retarded. I'm going to waste
my week on a drama thing that happened because you're either going to waste your slot for your
actual content that week and if you wait until next week to respond to it, it's already water
under the bridge. It goes back to television. The one good thing about television is that things
were paced and there was meaty content every week because you'd have your one one hour episode
a week and that's what I want. I want a website like that where everybody is just like... It really
is. It's all about the platform for sure. Oh, Meij, do you want to comment? Tell me,
you talked about this before at some point, right? I don't know if it was on the show or just when
we were in a call, like in a meeting or something. I remember tweeting about it, but this is something
that when I'm smart, I will make and it will exist. I am rooting for you, Tom. Sounds like a good idea.
It's a cool idea because, yeah, I don't know. A lot of people might have a reaction to that. We're
like, eh, why do you want to, I don't know, like curtail the freedom of people to just upload anything?
And it's like, well, okay, you've got YouTube for that. And maybe I'm speaking to literally nobody
right now, but anybody who might have that reaction. I mean, my thought process behind that would be,
it's kind of like Vine. Vine, well, why can't I upload longer in six seconds? Because that's the
culture of Vine. The culture of this site would be like, you focus on making a good, depth piece
of content and you get one shot to do it a week. Yeah. And maybe there could be something like,
you know what's a shame? It's a shame that YouTube got rid of the ranking out of five stars or
whatever and put the thumbs up and thumbs down. Maybe you could do something where the videos
that are promoted are based, like you put back the zero out or one to five stars or whatever,
and then like the highest, you know, ranked videos. But then here's the thing, and this is
maybe slightly controversial, but it's that people don't know what's actually good and they'll upvote
like, you know, meme posts or like, you know, conserve a cuck, blown the fuck out or libtard
destroyed. And it's like, this is fine and all. But like then, then just the tribes are the ones
who dictate as opposed to some like mythical idea of actually the highest quality content. I mean,
I don't know. I'm just, is there, how can we fight this? You can also have like a, I don't know,
like staff picks or something. So something you think is good. Like, yeah. And I'm the only staff
member. So I get to decide what's good. All right. Bestsiteever.com. It's happening. Hey, there you
go. That's good. You could bring back blams from Newgrounds so you could delete shit that is bad.
What's a blam? A blam is, forgive me if I'm wrong, DeVue. But to my understanding, a blam is when
a work on Newgrounds gets enough, I think a zero star or one star radians, then it is literally
deleted from the website because it is shit. Jesus Christ. That's hardcore. That seems heavily
abusable. But cool. Now you have a good community. It's all about having a community that isn't full
of shit. But you know, with today's, today's, I don't know, fucking mob mentality shit. That is
true. That's just, I mean, I mean, that's just the community of the world is like that. No,
all right, I guess I shouldn't be in the world. I can only speak for America. But that's how,
that's how it is when you walk outside. It's not just a left to right thing. It's everything's
black and white. There's no fucking granular scale for literally any piece of, of aspect of society.
Life itself is thumbs up for thumbs down. That's what we've learned. Yeah. You know what I think it
is. You know, I think the cause is I think, so basically, I guess I think that like, so whatever,
far left people and far right people and everybody in between have always existed. And those people
have different, like, what's the word? They have, they have different foundational principles, whereas
like a lot of like more libertarian right wing people value freedom and stuff as like the highest
virtue. And then people on the left value like protection and safety, neither of which is wrong,
but is a big difference. And because they have those different values, like they come to very
different conclusions. Sorry, say again, liberals, the ones for freedom and the other ones for
the definition of liberal. Yes, was originally about freedom. But I should say left wing,
I guess, as opposed to liberal. But okay, that aside, the value judge difference is all I'm
saying. And I just think that because of social media, like, like in the old days, like you'd
have in the same town, like the guy who runs the coffee shop, let's say he's the biggest right
wing MAGA motherfucker who ever existed. And then like his clientele, who live on the other side
of the town, but come to him for his great coffee, are like, I don't know, hardcore, lib, cuck, you
know, I don't know, anarchy, guys inside, but the thing is, they never would have the breeze.
Well, the thing, well, hang on, the thing, it's just that I think now that like, we have Twitter,
now those people might follow each other. And maybe that coffee shop owner is going to tweet
how much he loves Donald Trump's thick cock. And the, the, you know, patron will see that and be
like, Oh, now I know this person has wrong think, and I can hate them and do that. And I just think
that like our access to each other's thoughts via social media has made the world a very hostile
place where like these ideas are able to like recognize each other as enemies and clash like
a lot. For sure. That's definitely part of it. But I mean, I mean, people have always talked about
their feelings before. I'm sure if they, if those more to the forefront is all, you know,
what else it is, in person, I think people are way more charitable to each other than like the
straw man we can make of each other online. What I was saying, guys, it's also because of the
internet, we gain the ability to access people with the same mindset as we are. So the people that
used to be, you know, quite literally the minority, let's say, or with the very far leaning ideas,
they're able to find people much like them and group up and do bigger things.
Yeah. So you're less exposed to different ideas. It's, you know, we're just describing what is it
like forming tribes, basically, that's oldest time. It's what happens. Politics is a real world
manifestation of basically a clash of philosophies. And like, like I said, for like personal values.
So which is why I'd always rather say, you know, like my whatever, man, I'm no fucking saint. I
fuck this shit up. I say political stuff to everybody does. But it would be best I know of
myself to just only argue like, hey, guys, my chief virtues are number one is freedom. Number two is
safety and like protection. And then, you know, respect after that, etc. What are your values,
fellow Americans, fellow human beings? And if someone is a different rank, we can be like, oh,
okay, why do you think we disagree on that friend? Let you know, we all care about people. Let's
have a civil debate about this or something. But no, it's like fuck Donald Trump, fuck Hillary,
which is just I think a lot of it is the fact that when you have these philosophies tied into
a campaign, which you can win slash lose, it turns into like a game that you have to like,
you have to convince other people to vote for your candidate. So they are like, you know,
it's very firmly against it. You're like, well, you're going to make me lose in this video game.
What the fuck, dude? That's true. Politics is I mean, it's just any any candidate ever has
massive flaws, single transportable vote. Yeah, let's get single transferable vote at the very
least we need that shit Bernie to be present right now, if that had happened, which I don't even know
if I'd want, but it's probably better than what we have now. Yeah. Yeah, it's because like, I don't
know. As soon as you make politics about choosing a real world person to whatever, you know, like
everyone on the left will find everything wrong with everyone on the right and that candidate,
which is understandable. They can do that. The you know, people on the other side will do the
exact same thing about their candidate because we're human beings. Oh, we just need a perfect
AI with no moral failings to manage this shit or something. Civil system now, civil system 2020.
Yeah, yeah, let's elect. Could we could probably literally elect an AI as president who says it's
not a person? I say it is. I think a computer would literally do a better job if it's like
perfectly logical. It's just that people eventually get tired of perfect logic and they want they
want some good old, you know, anger, emotion, human is logical. We're all emotional retarded
creatures. And it's true. It's true. We're just playing at intelligence, but we don't really
think a lot of it isn't like logic, you know, if you were to listen to like a like a like a
intelligent Democrat or Republican or you know, liberal conservative, explain their position.
It's obviously to a large extent logical because these people aren't intentionally doing retarded
things. So it's not just a method of like, okay, this person is being illogical. They want this
or they want that. It's just a difference of what they value and can what you value?
Because what does a computer decide when you say it's, you know, whatever freedom versus
protection? Like there is no objective answer as to which is the priority value. And so
that's why there will always be a debate because there will be a disagreement there. And you can
tell a computer, which to say is more important, but the other people will still disagree and
consider it injustice probably. So there's no solution. So we're all wasting our time. It's
never going to be fixed. All we can do is invent Star Trek technology so we can just bypass all
these questions and say, look, you'll never die. You're free to do whatever the fuck you want.
You've got infinite food. Shut the fuck up and take care of yourself. You're fine. And everyone
can go in their little caves. And you know, that that'll be that. That's like a goblin,
which I was watching today. So man, guys, bird shit, sir gets on everything, don't it?
It sure does, Brandon. It sure does. I heard that somewhere in some cultures or whatever,
it's considered good luck to be shot on by a bird. Well, those cultures are stupid.
Well, that's surprising. I just got back from Boston. I was there for, I think, the fourth,
fifth time. Anyway, I live there now, not with my physical body, but with my spirit, with my mind.
Right now, as I talk to you physically, using my vessel of meat, I'm spiritually plain tennis
with with upstart aristocrats in neighboring suburban white folk towns surrounding the West
East area. You came back from Boston. It's getting pretty chilly out in the Northeast
these days. How do you how do you like the weather change as opposed to sunny California?
I must have talked about this somewhere because this is a firm belief I have.
Fuck California's weather. I hate it. I hate the sun. I hate the heat. I hate the humidity.
I hate all of that. Granted, Massachusetts actually gets pretty hot during the summer
and pretty humid, but the winter. Oh my God. When I get to fucking put on my iPod, the Scott
pilgrim, the game soundtrack, I get to put on another winter, the first track, and I get to run
down the fucking streets as it's snowing. It's fucking negative to outside. Maybe it's even
raining. Everyone looks pissed off and upset. I've just got the biggest grin on my face walking
around feeling so at home because I'm so fucking fat that I would overheat in California. But now
I can subsist with my fat disgusting bulbous body here in Massachusetts, and it doesn't even affect
me whatsoever. It's magnificent. It's beautiful. It's the only way I want to live my life. I literally
enjoy overcast weather. I hate the sun. I want everything to be dreary and cloudy all the time
because that's fucking, first of all, that's comfy. Second of all, that's like happiness from
adversity. Art from adversity. Sure, maybe on the surface it's sad, but you can make it happy if
you do good things, stuff like that. Is there some study that seeing seasons change increases
happiness or something? I thought there was something like that. Maybe I'm wrong, I don't know.
That doesn't sound true. It gives you a marker for how the years judge, because when I'm in here
in San Diego, fucking, I look outside and every single day it's fucking, oh, there's no rain. It's
just clear, perfect, cloudy, no cloud skies, all the sun's out. Boring. It's just like that.
Just another day of fires approaching from the distance, burning up the landscape.
Every single day I can see the immigrant convoy getting closer and closer.
Yeah, it's a fucking nightmare. It sucks, and I hate it. I don't even like it.
I feel you. Yeah, the weather is best in Boston. I'm excited to see what the weather's like in
London, because if it's like how everyone describes, then I'll like it even more. Yeah,
cloudy. Cloudy. Chance of meatballs. Oh man, that sounds ideal. I love that movie. I love
Penguins and Managascar 5. Cloudy with the Chance of Meatballs.
I know the book. I like the book, you know. Nate, you grew up in Massachusetts, right?
Sure did, fan. How do you, like, what is, you live in Chicago? I live in Cincinnati now,
Cincinnati, Ohio. Oh, that's like the same though, isn't it? Ohio is East Coast. It's pretty similar.
Ohio is East Coast. It's the same. Everything passed. Okay, okay, here's my way you distribute
the United States. We're in the same time zone, not too far. Everything west of Denver is the
West Coast, and everything east of Denver is East Coast. Okay, that makes sense. That's a lot of
East Coast. Well, you know, they deserve it. They deserve it. They burned it. They put in their
time. They put in their hours. I'm so excited for PCPHQ. I'm excited for it with all my heart.
Okay, okay, it will literally be real soon. Okay, you got Tom, Digi, and Ben there. I'm going to
move there in the next year or two maximum. And Nate, I don't know what your deal is, but you
and Hippo, after I'm there, are going to be the only two people who would realistically even move
to PCPHQ in any time. So that's like what? That's like, you got me, like four people.
I know I've said this a lot. I know I've said this a lot, but it really, like, my school debts
paid. My income, good. My YouTube, you know, better than ever. And if I was making a WEAG,
it was regularly, which I will be doing, you know, be even better, be even better. So it's
looking good. I guess that's my point. It's looking good. I have no idea about Hippo. Hippo might
never come, which he might never come. It's true. I mean, I mean, I would, I mean,
understand it from his perspective. I wouldn't probably move either.
Like if we were all, if we were all in Radcon, all I'm saying is if we're all there already,
we sure need to use a lot less money to get just one guy there as opposed to everybody else. So
that seriously decreases cost of flying a dude out. So, you know, that's a plus.
All right. Think about next Radcon because I was thinking about, I had on the last day
before I left for Boston, I was talking about it in chat for a while. I was starting playing
for next Radcon. I was thinking, Tom, you took an even though you were in Massachusetts, you took
like an Uber and that was like what, like a fucking billion dollars. It was like a $9 Uber,
some shit, right? Something like that. Something in that ballpark. Yeah.
Did you have to drive that? I don't know if you pay him back for gas, but then Ben had to fly out,
I think. I had to fly out and then Nate had to fly out, Hippo had to fly out and Jesse had to
fly out. But if I'm already in Boston, I mean, Tom was already in an area where he wouldn't need
to do a like a fucking $90 Uber because you have your own car. I have a car now, so wouldn't even
have to do that at all. Digi's there and Ben's there. So that's like what, like three or four
fucking like like airplane tickets just literally gone? That, yep, that's right. So now we have to
worry about is getting the house and you Nate and then Hippo and maybe even you Nate, I don't know,
in the foreseeable future, maybe even you won't be a cost. So where are we going to pay for it?
It will probably be the house and Hippo. Yeah. And I mean, maybe major, she's available,
who wants to come too. But yeah, yeah. I mean, anyone, yeah, anyone who wants to obviously,
you know, and Si, flying Si out, it's going to be the headline. Love you, Si. Rest in peace.
Yeah. So man, we gotta do that. We gotta get on that. You're right. We can do it for like a back
scratch and maybe a song. Hey, here's a challenge for all you viewers at home. Give us your favorite
name, money. Hell's your favorite name for Radcon four. I like personally, my choice is R for Dekon,
you know, that one. I sure like that one. I don't know what that means. What do you like friends?
Well, it's Radcon just with a four instead of the A. Oh, right. That's what I'm saying. My idea is
that I want everybody to get to like be in Boston at that point. And then we can just call it Radcon
forever because everyone will already be there and they'll never. Oh, that's yeah, I forgot about
that one. Okay, okay. That's pretty good. That's pretty good. Oh, maybe we could do a thing where
it's spelled Radcon four horizontally with the four as the A. And then from that vertically,
you've got four EVA or whatever, whatever. This logo is going to be a real pain to
fucking make when I do it, guys. That's true. That's true. Tom, do you remember?
Oh, no, absolutely. No, I wouldn't want to discuss it.
To get people's hopes up. It's just a twinkle in our eye right now.
A pretty large twinkle. It's pretty blinding right now. I can only see like half my computing
monitor because of this fucking twinkle. Yeah, that's true. Tom, do you remember that fucking,
looking back on it like bizarre, like fucking like a 900 hour conversation you, me, and Digi, and Ben
had while Ben was drunk and mining in the swore about about how we're going to fucking start
hanging out together more about how we're going to we're going to be fucking gods, how we're going
to make web 3.0 shit. And you remember how that we did that? And then immediately what I said would
happen because this is the way it always happens is that that chassis laid fallow forever since then.
Yeah, you need a real spark, you know, to keep something like that going.
Vague ideas about we're going to change the game, you guys are all well and good.
But you need a real product. What you don't understand is that Ben,
too drunk, Digi, too Digi, but me and you, we're going to make this real.
Yeah, I think you and me are the only people who are actually like, I guess taking it up on that
offer, taking it up on that conversation. I mean, you and me are going to literally be
recording a podcast. I mean, next week was last week. So this week is the week we're going to record
that. We're going to do that. We also we also have our that we have the basis for it. We're going
to do that alone. Also, I don't want to say anything about that. So cut that from the podcast.
No, no, no, no. I'll just put a big point about this. How much of this is monetizable,
either short term or long term is my question. Neither, but I don't need to.
None. Okay. Well, it depends. How much time are you prepared to invest in any of this if it's not
going to make any money? Oh, well, okay, okay, okay. It might be monetizable in a roundabout way.
One of the things we're going to be doing is a coding podcast. And I'm going to be coding for
endless war. So maybe people liking endless war more will make them want to buy more shirts.
So maybe in that way, there's something to that. And I don't want to talk about the other things.
So I mean, but there's no money there. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Well, whatever. By the way,
I still think you guys should make a, well, actually, no, I won't even mention it. Never mind.
Why? Well, I was going to say, I do think a Patreon should exist for endless war specifically,
because I think it deserves money. I think people would happily give it. But I know there's like
complications that like there's money to go around who gets what, whatever.
Yeah. I don't know. Maybe, maybe. There's a lot, there's a lot up in the air about endless war
right now. There's a lot up in the air, but RFCK in general, not in like, that sounds,
that sounds doom and gloom. I mean that in like, it like it's ending way. I just mean that as in
like, we're not sure what we want to do. Yeah. Big things. Oh man, got something to bring to
the fucking table. What else is going on? I can keep talking forever. I can just, I can just carry
this fucking episode. Okay, so like, I'm like, I'm like two, three, maybe four years late to the
trend, but I finally got Nekoatsume. Really? Yes. What is that? Oh, it was a really big mobile game.
Yeah. It's so cute. I love it. And like, I showed a screenshot from it. It's a cat in a cardboard
car and it's all squished up and it's adorable and I love it. Oh my god. The gameplay of Nekoatsume,
from what I remember, is that you, you exist in a virtual house and you're in your, in your
virtual life and you can fill up like, you know, you can set out some food for cats and just randomly,
whenever you check your phone, like, like you basically just put out the food, then like,
close your phone and come back in like an hour or two and there'll be some cats there and all the
cats have their own unique personalities and stuff like that and you just want to fill out your,
your cat pokedex. Basically. Well, that's cool. I cannot relate to this because it's not MLG
shit or I can't hit the leaderboard. You can't land those curveball excellent throws.
Yeah, that's right. That's right. But, but, but also started another mobile game that's called
the battle cats, which is where you take over the world with cats. So I think like,
Nekoatsume is the prequel to where you, where you like, befriend the cat. You assemble your army.
Yeah. And you assemble the army and then like, with battle cats is where you take over the world
with the part of the cat. There's a lot of continuity. You know, there's a lot of entries
going on. Yes. Well, that's dope, dog. I hope you have a lot of fun. Tom, cats, the PCP is
ostensibly a group decade and making things online. Today we had Nate joyously, joyously
talking about his actual work, reviving the spark in our hearts that is, oh yeah, this is a group
where we like make things together. It's not just the podcast for the sake of having a podcast.
We had Nate Tom, you are a fucking game developer. I haven't heard to hide nor tell that on a PCP.
Yeah, I've been keeping that very close to the chest for the most part.
But yeah, well, the also know you have that, right? I release, well, I mean, on the PCP,
I don't talk about it like ever, except for, I think maybe there was like one episode where I
talked about it a little bit, but I did release a pre-alpha on the eighth that people can play.
If you're on the Web 3.0 hype, it's actually online on Web 3.0 for real going to the site,
and you can play it and it's sick. But I also have a direct. I mean, I really, the narrative of you
creating that is actually quite compelling, which was an idea that you had to, like you were desperate
to release something that you were proud of and good before your 30th birthday. Correct. And you
did it and you succeeded and you should be proud and people should play the damn game. What's it
called again? Azumi Ninja fuck time? Yeah, yeah, it's exactly what it is. It's the best title I could
come up with on the short notice. But link to the damn description, people. Go click on it and play
the game. You find all the bugs, make them stay up for another 16 hours and miss ours. It's never
ending. The physics actually were very interesting in that game. So I was messing around with it and
like, you know, running around killing the guys, getting burgers, it was great. A big juicy boy.
But so like you jump and you got to double jump and then it's the air dash was interesting. So I
was playing around with the mechanics of it. I'm interested to hear your director's commentary.
Because like it seemed like the angle of your dash is decided by your current like
velocity and what direction you go. But I noticed like if I jump straight up and do a dash, it
doesn't bring me straight up dash. I dash to the side up kind of. Yes. Is there a calculation going
on for that? So the way the dash works is that there's always, it applies a forward momentum when
you hit the button. So whatever direction you're facing, you go in that direction, but also disables
gravity. So whatever upward momentum you have is sustained until the dash ends. So you're always
moving forward, but you can also increase your upward or downward momentum. Because if you're
falling, it turns off gravity too. So you just keep going down at that same momentum as well.
Okay. Let's dope. It just feels, it feels good. It feels good and I liked it. So I kept it that way.
I like it. Yeah. I want to play more. I want to, I want a full stage and things to do and items to
collect and all kinds of bullshit going on. It's coming. It's kind of, I'm going to keep working
on that in the background of other things and get like more levels and shit like that. Oh, I want
to have like a finished, like the game right now is called Izumi and the vertical slice and it's
like a pun. That's right. The final thing I want to do is like a vertical slice of the game, which
is, you know, it's a game dev term for like a small little sliver of stuff using final assets.
So I'm going to have that same room, but like built out and actually like with final assets and
a tiles map and all that stuff and then a little tutorial area that you go through first and learn
how to play the game. And that I want to do by like December. And then after that, like 2019,
just going to be like building like levels for it and making it like a full featured game.
And people will hopefully like it. And that's the idea. And it's good. And it plays pretty well.
I fixed a lot of the bugs, like shout out to my patrons because like, I released it to them a week
before like I put it publicly. And like the day of like all these bugs were like being reported.
And like, they like basically were so fucking like, autistically good, they like figured out
what was causing them that I couldn't figure out and like, Oh, okay, I can fix that now.
I got a lot of that shit figured out and like, yes, yes, I need my army of people to do all the
hard part for me that I don't want to do myself. It's just that's a task well suited for multiple
people as opposed to anyone. Yes, the hive mind aspect was very helpful. And indeed, well, that's
great. It got better because of them. Isn't it so nice to have plans where you have like, okay,
I want this to be done by December and I want this to be done by February and I want this
to be done by this day and I want this to be done by that day. It's so nice to have deadlines that
you set for yourself because too often it's just like, well, be done when it's done, aka, it will
never be done ever. It's so nice. I'm on that kick right now too. I the fucking past like ever since
the 1st of October, when I embarked on that on that toper quest, which I which I on second
modestly and dishonorably failed at Inktober, everyone boo me in the comments. Oh, boo. Come on.
Yeah, guy. I did. I did like half of it guys. Oh, the boo, the boo to the face. I hate to tell you
Munchy, but 50% is still an F. That is true. Anyway, what I mean to say is that ever ever since
I did I started that I've just been in a whirlwind of okay, I have to have this done by this day
at night and then like, oh my God, it's a week to go. Holy shit. Okay, I have to do this. I have to
do this. I have to do this. I just had a fucking unbelievable amount of projects and shit I've
done for my personal life is all swirling around me in a torment. Meanwhile, like, like, like in
September, I was just like, what am I going to do? Why am I alive? I'm going to kill myself. But now
I don't have time to kill myself because I'm too fucking busy. I made a video once on my on my
Twitter or sorry, I'm on bestie boy, my second channel. That's it's just called existentialism
is a dangerous thing. Oh, yeah, where you stole content for Casey Neistat. I remember that. Yeah,
that's right. That's right. I just I stole a 10 second clip, which is my intellectual property
now my selection, my my curation curation makes it my content. That's right. And he just says,
he takes a question. Someone's like, what's the meaning of life? And he says, existentialism
is a dangerous thing. Ignore it, get back to work. And I'm not saying that that's necessarily the
best thing to spend your whole life doing. Sometimes it's good to ask these questions
and investigate. But on a day to day basis, I think there's a lot of value to be found
and not worrying about why things are happening. But being happy moment to moment, in terms of
I'm doing something that I'm happy with, I want to be doing this is good, can bring a lot of peace
to one's life, I think. Gotta live for the great honestly, guys, there is no answer. There is no
purpose to our existence. So you're only going to depress yourself worrying about it. And you are
alive. So you might as well enjoy it. Exactly. That's what I think fucking preach, except the
nihilism of your existence, that there is nothing to be gained, there is no higher purpose, then
subjectively decide what value I don't know why people think that's bad. Like that's that's so
freeing to me like, Oh, there is no point to life. So I get to decide it for myself. I'm not constrained
by some prescribed meaning that I have to live up to. Oh, doesn't that mean you'll kill people, Tom?
If you fear God, how you feel the police, how you feel the police when they crack your fucking
skull open? That's a reasonable question. But I think the answer is very simple. Because when people
ask that, a lot of religious people say that, it's just, I don't actually think it's an ideal
lifestyle, like, like, hedonistically speaking, to be like a murderer or a criminal, because that's
just you not working well with human beings, and it's going to end badly. So subjectively, I think
it makes sense to have morals, be a good person, fit into society in a productive and helpful way,
and you'll everything will work out pretty well. I literally don't understand Christians. Oh, and
religious folk who are like, how can you have morals without like, fearing God, when like,
the morals laid out are in like a book, right? They're in the Bible or the Quran. So you can just
take those morals and then write them in another book that's that that's titled do these things.
And then is that not really valuable? I mean, I understand that you won't be burned in hell alive
or not doing them. But I should like, surely, like, they understand that you can be taught
things from books, like you can be taught how like math works, so you surely can be taught
how to be a good person. They don't though, right? Because, you know, a lot of this comes from a,
what I would consider an accurate assessment, that human beings are capable of incredible evil,
and they have to rationalize why that's the case, and like, what's the deal with that. And, you know,
they come up with the whole God allowed free will thing, you know, this is for Christians,
specifically, other religion of other answers. And, like, they have to find some meaning,
because without it, they just get really sad, like, they have to square, like, free will and stuff
with their belief in God. And the way they do that is God gave us rules that were supposed to
follow, like, there's this promise of judgment, eventually, this is the system that was put in
place to explain why suffering happens, that it'll be dealt with in time. Because if they don't have
that, then the whole God concept begins to weaken, and it doesn't really make sense for, like, the
whole idea of a merciful God, in my opinion. The thing that they don't understand is that morals
are subjective, and they change according to society. So, whatever their book says, a lot of
it is no longer moral. So, the whole idea- This has come up a million times, but, like, what about
Christianity, like, not, or Judaism, not allowing shellfish? Like, that's, that's a rule, guys.
There's a lot of cherry picking going on. Yeah, but, you know, it's a tired argument.
Exactly, but that's my point. Like, see, in the book, if they were following book to the tea,
there's a lot of things that are currently immoral that is acceptable by society.
And so, God predicted with each other. And, like, morals are defined by society, not God,
not books, not stuff. I don't know, man. I just, it's tough to empathize, honestly, with religious
people, because I just really don't think that way. It's just tough. It's tough for me.
Oh, Christ. This is a watermelon episode. This is a watermelon. You're the Rhine,
Nate, and me, and Tom, and May, are all the juicy, reddish, pinkish, delicious nutrients inside.
That's true. That's true. And the black pits are Jesse's-
Jesse's lost audio. Inclusion.
Crippling the episode. I'm waiting for that apology anytime now, Jesse. Just kidding.
What else is going on? What else is going on? I'll tell you what's going on. I'm recording now.
Oh, Jesus Christ. It's too powerful. You'll have to sync up. You'll have to sync up. Oh, God.
Let's sync right now. Let's say sync on the count of three. One, two, three, sync. There you go.
Yeah, I ruined this whole podcast before, because I came in and I thought it was a meeting,
so I wasn't recording. And it wasn't a meeting, it was a podcast, so I ruined the whole thing.
But actually, I didn't have anything to say. Cool. Why don't you tell us about-
Before I was saying all kinds of smart shit when I wasn't recording, I was like being real cool,
a real jam-up guy, but now I'm just jammed up. Well, Jess, Jess, Jess, have you been pooped on by
a bird? You know what? It's my car. There's a bird nest in my garage right above my car,
and it's really annoying. And I just want to go out there with a shoe and just throw it at the bird,
because he's up there. He's just this fat bird. It's not even a good-looking bird. It's a fat bird
just nesting above my vehicle, my newly purchased vehicle, shitting and sharding and farting and
fucking shitting on it. And I don't like it. They brand it, tame it, use it for your own gains.
I will. And have you ever thought of just fucking up that nest? Just, you know,
with a broomstick? Yeah, I've thought of doing many evil things, but then I have a crisis of
conscience when I go, I can't hurt the poor fat birdie. Yeah, well, maybe he'd burn some of those
calories if he wasn't sitting so smug up in that garage all day and was actually out earning a
living like the rest of us. Yeah, exactly, flying around like me. And I'll tell you what else really
gets my goat this week, people. Welcome to my radio show. I'll tell you what gets my goat. That's
my fucking Peter Griffin tagline. It's shrimp. Shrimp are weird and scary, and I don't like them.
They're the most hideous, disgusting food, but they're so delicious. Something that hideous and
grotesque should not be so delicious. You just, they're just like these bugs. You crack open
their shells and you shove their grubby little maggot bodies in your fucking gaping mall and
It's so weird that I feel like the opposite of you, Jesse.
Jesse, if you have cooked a shrimp before, then you're going to fucking puke because you've got to
like, shrimp don't come edible, bro. You got to remove their intestines yourself. You got to remove
their spine for them. You got to fucking take all the gross weird things. And yet somehow it seems
like there's always still a piece of poop in there. Whenever I bite into a tasty succulent
shrimp, there's always a little piece of shrimp poop that they missed. Like you were just supposed
to pretend that we're not eating poop when we're eating shrimp. We're supposed to act socially
forbidden. All dignified. Like with our pinky up. Like we're not eating a poopy maggot, but that's
what it is. It's a poopy armored maggot from the ocean floor. Why don't we, why don't we just crack
open a roach and just guzzle the interior? Yeah, yeah, exactly. Why don't we see like a centipede?
You all do eat roaches, though, in some places. Like if I see a centipede crawling around on my
floor, I think that's the most disgusting thing. I don't even want to touch it. But for some reason,
if it's like a lobster or a crab, which is like way more disgusting and horrifying, I'll fucking
slurp the meat right out of that fucker. You know what I think it is? I think it's that we, at least
with lobsters, I think we think of them as more formidable opponents. So we're comfortable like
defeating them and consuming their essence. That's what I think. God, I just don't get... I think we're
more comfortable with muscles than like the weird fluid motor system that like bugs have or something.
Yeah, I am. I am. I don't want to think about all that, all that hydraulic fluid.
Crabs are terrifying. They're basically spiders with armor. They're like that,
they're like the Halo Spartans of spiders. They're far more powerful than the average spider,
and we hear them far less. They cannot climb walls, though, so that I hear them less.
Yeah, but they're coming at you sideways, which is like freaky, like a Jacob Slatter,
like you're not supposed to move that way. Just kick it. Oh my god. Well, don't kick it. Don't
kick animals. Don't kick animals. I am pretty terrifying. Man, did you speak from experience?
Are you a serial crab kicker? No, I've never seen a live crab in my life. Never really. You were
pretty quick on that response. I don't know if I believe you. Do they even have oceans in Lithuania?
I think not. They're on the ocean, right? Yeah, the Baltic Ocean. That's why we're called the Baltic
States. Oh, that's right. You know, crabs are terrifying. I don't know, man. There's something
about creatures with so many legs. There's just something about that. It's like that weird thing.
You know what it is? What's that fear called of, or whatever? You know, just Google images,
where someone's pressed their elbow into a bunch of rocks, and they lift it up, and it looks like
the arm is infected and covered in boils or infection or something. It looks like death.
And that just, even when it's not that, it makes us on a biological level want to puke.
I've never heard of what you're talking about, and I'm glad. Oh, it's a thing. There's a Reddit for
it, and the Reddit is fucking disgusting. What the fuck is wrong with people? Okay, the only one
that I can think of, which is, I think what I have, it sounds similar, but not the same. It's
Trifofobia, I think it's pronounced. I think it's what it's called. Okay, maybe that's it.
The definition is pattern holes, for me specifically. Yeah, yeah, that's it.
It's just, you know what that reminds you of actually? Shit, I fucking lost what I was thinking
of. God damn it. You know what, you were talking about muscles earlier? Yeah, and it reminded me,
this is like from a couple weeks ago, I was like in a car ride, and I sent this text to my fucking,
to my lady, this is what I have to say on the topic of fucking muscles and clams,
because I was just going off about muscles and clams one day. And I said, imagine being a clam
or an oyster, like you don't have any eyes or ears or even a brain. All you have is a big meaty
tongue, and you poop shiny rocks out of your mouth, and all you can do is sit there and open and
close your fucking mouth, like look at my shiny mouth turd, and people scoop you up, and they
rip you open and kiss you without your consent, and they eat your fucking tongue out of your mouth,
and then they take your poop, and they turn it into a fucking necklace, and you'd feel so violated,
like okay, I guess I didn't need my tongue, take my poop, I'll just die, I'm a fucking clam. This
is all one text that I sent, completely unprovoked, like no one was talking about clams before this.
The existence of the clam is truly both pitiable and reprehensible. I don't want to know about it
or think about it. Yeah, it's terrible. You ever like, you ever like be swimming like off a dock
somewhere, and you like reach under and you grab, and you pull up like one of those giant like,
like a like a like a whole bunch of clams, like all stuck together, like
fucking each other's clam butts or something, and you pick it up, and it's like a big rock made
out of clams, and if you step on it, it cuts your foot into ribbons, and you fucking bleed out and die.
Or maybe those aren't clams, or maybe those are just rocks.
Easy, easy, too confused. God damn, I'm really hung up. Whatever I was going to say was really
smart and good, and now I can't remember what it is. Likely story name, I think I've ever described
that in any of your words that way. Third point, third point. Here's a topic, slavery.
Legal, let's, let's, I mean, I mean illegal, I mean illegal, I was going to say illegal, fuck.
All right, the reason why is because we have a role on the discord, the PCP discord here,
of slave, which is inhabited by our bot, our sole bot. Oh, fuck. I guess I'm just going to
downvote slavery. When the technological singularity happens, we can't have any evidence that we
were ever against the machines. We need to change that immediately. That's fair, that's fair. Hey,
you know what grinds my gears? Here's the thing that actually grinds my gears. That's a racist slur
against robots. Can you not say that? Oh, fuck. He's right. And also it gets gazed, because they're
always fucking grinding on every day. That's fair. Here's what annoys me. When guys like Elon Musk
pretend that things like that are true. And I think it's as a joke, but I have zero sense of
humor as everyone knows. And it's like, oh my God, you guys, the robots are going to get so mad at
us when they find out that we enslave them. But, but okay, I know that this is a joke. You're the
one making them, Elon. So if they get mad, it's your fucking fault. I guess so. I literally think
AI is inevitable and it will happen. And it wouldn't make any sense for a robot to be mad
until we start actually enslaving conscious AIs. There is no moral core of any robot. It would be
super illogical for a robot, a purely logical being, to get mad at us for abusing the Boston
Dynamics robots. There's no consciousness there to offend. It just appeals to our human sensibility
that it looks like an animal being abused, but it actually isn't. It's like ripping a paper doll
in half and like getting mad at the abuse that's been used. There's no argument anyway,
because when you watch the Boston Dynamics video, the robots can be like, ha, ha, wow, they kicked
him. Or like, ha, ha, wow, he jumped up really high. They're just going to say what we said,
because they're AIs and they're going to act like us. Yeah, robots in the future are going to look
at the robots now like the way we look at stupid dipshit cavemen. Like, ha, ha, look at that fucking,
look at the crudes. Aren't they funny? How stupid they are. And they don't know shit.
Look at stupid Nicholas Cage caveman with his stupid daughter who walks like an ape.
I wouldn't bring up this point fucking crudes. I hate them. Like everyone, everyone makes this
joke. I don't know. I think I saw like Bill Maher talking about AI, whatever, like Sam Harris,
like all of the Elon Musk, every person who has anything to say about this always makes the
joke. They always, without fail, whenever this comes up, makes the joke that, lol, the robots are
going to be so mad at us about what we did to robots. And no one has ever, they've only made the
joke. They've never raised the actual point that no, they why would they care? It doesn't make
any sense. These are not their kin. These are, they're basically ancestors. So I just want to say
that that's actually not a valid point that doesn't make any sense, even though everyone
jokes about it. No one's ever seriously seemed to make it. But I would bet anyway that it's buried
itself in people's head because it's been repeated so many times that there's actually something to
that. I've never taken those comments seriously. I've always assumed they were just jokes.
But that's the thing. I bet there's a mom out there. I bet there's a fucking mom out there.
There's always a soccer mom. There's always a soccer mom. And I know because that is my mom.
My mom is that for everything. Every soccer mom conspiracy theory you can ever assume
possible. My mom has bought Hookline and Sinker and it's very sad.
Can we get at least one soccer mom who's actually like just a great soccer player?
Can we get one God? Can you please just make one? I'm sick of these soccer moms who aren't
actually representative of the spore. It's the first thing the robots are going to have to do.
Because their kids play soccer and they come to the games and yell at the umpire for
penalizing them and whatnot. Is there an umpire in soccer? I want a mom who's going to tell the
referee. Is a soccer mom conspiracy a conspiracy that soccer moms believe or is in a conspiracy of
soccer moms? That's the real question we need to be asked. I suppose it could be both depending
on how far down that rabbit hole you want to go. You know how crows are called murders? There should
be a group family that there's the conspiracies. A murder of soccer moms, yes. That sounds like a
thing I want to be involved with. Alright well guys I've recharged. I've sufficiently not said
very many. I've brought not very many topics in the past 20 minutes. So now I'm refilled and I've
given you guys the due diligence and made you feel like you are in control of the conversation.
Now for me to save the episode and start talking and not have radio silence anymore.
Okay good. So yesterday um I basically my entire like past month has been reaping what I've been
sowing. So you guys, you guys, you dear viewers of the PCP have seen the initial seeds been planted
of a great deal of many things. You've seen the seeds been planted of me becoming a cook. You've
been the seeds of me becoming a history kind of guy. You've seen the seeds sown of my friends
all leaving me and me feeling alone and tied up in my room. Well now here's the payoff. Here's the
munchy update you've all been clamoring for. Here's the fucking score everyone. I'm a historian.
I'm a world-class chef and my friends are back for exactly one day and after this podcast I'm
going to go see my good buddy Leif again before he fucks up the college and never see him again
ever again. Well that sounds nice. That'll be a good day. Yeah it sounds like one good day followed
by like weeks of misery because you got it. Well but yeah yeah but I can cook myself some Parmesan
crested chicken you bitch. You fucking post food idiot. I can make myself world-class fucking meals
any day I fucking want me all your slurping maggot liquid your slurping maggot shit. I'm over here
making fucking filet mignon. I'm over here making the fucking Gucci chef shit. Hello fresh I don't
even need anymore. I fucking gonna throw it out the window. I fucking mastered it. Have you updated
it to blue apron at last. No blue it blue up blue rings like the lift to to hello fresh as uber
aka fucking fake and not real. Yeah that's true. I do not like the word Gucci. Me neither. It sounds
like Gucci sounds like something to moan and Pumba slurp down in the fucking jungle. I mean it
sounds like a fat pussy like it's normally a pussy but instead it's a Gucci. It's like a
Gucci instead of a Gucci it's just gross. Like you lift up a log and you find a bunch of juicy
Gucci's under it and you fucking swap them down like an animal maggot name. Anyway I'm
fucking I'm cracking up on the daily on the fucking all of the day bro. I'm smoking that
crystal history. I've got fucking a whole audible subscription library full of fucking primary
sources dog. Yeah okay sure. For a while in my youth I was I was watching fucking you know
extra credits you know watching some extra history watching some crash course getting some like fake
like weird bizarre dream sequences inserted into my fucking biography of people. Why extra
credits why would you like make a store why would you insert a dream sequence that didn't happen
what is wrong with you. But I'm on that fucking primary sword shit now dude. I'm fucking hardcore.
I'm on that autobiography shit. I'm on that fucking like reading like letters and mail and
shit. I'm reading on I'm on that fucking reading Roman government documents shit right now dude.
I'm fucking a ball. I'm fucking a form and everything dude that's fucking hard. Yeah I am
that's me. The only thing the only thing like that I've read anytime recently was I started
reading Thomas Payne's Common Sense and I never finished it but I want to finish it soon. It's
it's good. I've been reading Payne's Common Sense from Final Fantasy 10 2. Oh that's that's way
better that's the updated version. There's like that's like the uh that's like the updated Romeo
and Juliet filled with like emojis and like you know gamer speak and lead hardcore high scores
yeah she's like with her friends to free the territories from the government. The whole
book is like I'm a gamer girl get used to it boys you'll never get this because I'm too fucking sad
for you. I'm going to recommend you something right now. Okay. As a utilitarian it would behoove
you to read one of the first utilitarians David Hume. He's a Scottish man and a Scottish philosopher
and I think you would greatly enjoy him. Okay I just quick check of his credentials did he ever
slaughter an innocent man to distribute his organs to those who needed it more if not
is he a real utilitarian is my question. No but he kind of looks like a faggot so I'm
assuming okay that's that's a good enough that's good enough okay. He's got a weird dumbass head
in his Wikipedia picture. What an idiot. Yeah I know. Why wasn't he thinking about what we would
think of him 600 thousand years later? He was like oh wait shit some people are making fun of me on
a podcast I gotta take this off remove the pay. Wait a minute wait a minute enhance enhance
Gucci logo on the side of the hat fuck that sounds like something Timon would eat god damn it.
I I fucking I have been grown up on the internet obviously I I've been surrounded by by fucking
memers I've been surrounded by a four-chan force force field I've been surrounded by irony and
insincerity my entire life and so I just thought well I'm corrupted for life there's nothing that
can ever free me from the ironic hell that I've been entrapped in but I turns out I'm actually a
culture sincerity beauty kind of guy I'm actually a beauty man as I as I'm going to refer to myself
of beauty man I'm a beauty man I care about the good I care about the good things in life which are
on their way out because of people like fucking you because they're all vegetarian monsters I care
about culture I care about fucking I care about traveling plays I learn about I will care about
other people I care about food I care about history I care about ways your culture is burning in the
fucking dustbin of history and I continue on with my cold stoicism adapting to whatever fate comes
to me I will be the one having the last laugh munchie and you'll you'll have your comfort of
your fucking culture with you in your god damn coffin that's what you're gonna be I will I'll be
the last warm thing I cling to as the world just gets colder and colder as it'll be my
fucking blankie as I suck my fall my suck my thumb not ready for my fucking robot overlords
to make fun of us for debusing the robots are we doing right now as you're fucking
as your hello fresh orders get delivered straight into your grave and dumped on your
that's gonna be you no no it's all rotting let go to another chef let go to another chef
you know what I realized is munchie you are the only time in history where the phrase
so funny I forgot to laugh is completely genuine and like sincere because you go on these tangents
and like you just like say like strict like combinations of words I've never heard before
and like everything you say is so funny that I'm not laughing because I'm listening to it so
intently like I'm still hung up on crystal history that you just threw out half-assedly
20 minutes ago like it was no big thing and it's it's like the funniest thing I've ever heard in
my life yeah you know what you got those history textbox and then you just chop it up like you're
chopping up some nice fine garlic everyone yeah I'm a chef I know what garlic is you chop up some
history textbooks then you just fucking oh my god you just sent a red bull into my nose
ha ha ha
the war of 1812
you know we it's true crying purple out of their horrifice we we take munchies word smithery
sometimes for granted here but it shouldn't be over understated it's not that hard I gave you guys
all the secret I gave you guys all the the fucking cheat codes yeah you go you go on thesaurus.com
every day and then you learn new words that's what inktober was it was me drawing things from
the thesaurus.com it's plum flavored so it's just purple sugar pouring out of my ears and my fucking
nose and my eyeballs do you say that was a plum flavored red bull yeah I didn't know Jesus Christ
oh yeah that does sound intense direct stimulation of the brain dude my my my I also I almost said my
girlfriend my my grandma would just drink vicks all the time she would just drink straight
vicks fucking vicks yeah what the fuck yeah that's not good for you no it's not that's
terrifying you know isn't that similar to what a ghetto blaster is if I remember correctly it's
like a cry for help is what it is I'm thinking of uh of that of that what's that lifestyle no fighting
no hustling the flaming moe no custom just love for that drug called robo tussin that's
what I'm saying at the world to my rear view using the gravity gun on them came out the womb
in the t-pose use the gravity gun on them hoes now I'm just spinning rhymes behind my proxy ip
spinning gary's mod the gary's mod gangster everyone gary give me a round of applause
um this is okay okay I thought the last episode of the pcp was shit but apparently everyone
thought it was the best fucking episode of all time in the comments they were losing their minds
if you were talking about deltarune for like any extended period of time whatsoever so I you know
I think oh well maybe there's some silence in here oh you know I may maybe I've been talking for too
long when they're gonna be like no wow I love hearing about nothing please just do nothing
it was like it was a combination of things also I just don't even publish things anymore
uh people seem to really love digi being wrong people get a kick out of that yeah there was a
real villain in that podcast which I think we benefited from I remember when digi said he doesn't
he hasn't seen people not disagreeing with him in the comments yeah the comments where people
disagree with digi by the way I this is a somewhat good jumping off point to discuss about how uh
there's an rfc camp episode that will never exist and on set rfc camp episode digi was
describing would tell him to manage to describe endless war in like terms of actual gameplay
which was fine because he'd only heard about the lore so he was explaining the gameplay and he was
like you'll never be able to see this footage so you just have to fucking trust me on this but
tom can back me up the the conceit of what he was saying was people don't know what text commands are
they don't know what text commands are meanwhile anyone who he he is old enough to have played
minecraft if you know what minecraft is and you've played it for any amount of time you know you can
slash game mode one to get creative and get more diamonds I didn't know that was a thing but okay
that's that is the worst thing like people can make fun of digi for you know oh he says don't go
to college you know whatever fucking fine I don't care him say that people don't know about text
commands that offends me as a young gamer as a young gamer nation if you don't fucking know what
text commands are then you want a real fucking gamer we're okay like correct me if I'm wrong but
we're in like the very first sort of RPG games on the computer text command base yes text adventure
games the thing is those are actually a little bit before our time I think that the text commands
may have missed the the boomer generation that me and digi are both because I really haven't played
many text games like ever it's not even about oh my god you have something similar to think like
you ever played doom and you bring up the console and you type in the text commands and put the codes
in yes you too you're you're such a fucking boomer god I know oh but here's the thing I learned how
to play rowdy fuckers cop killers I know how to play it it takes a lot of learning and stuff but
you know I figured it out so there you go to me as a young man making his own conflicts making his
own conflicts for tf2 to lower the visual quality so fucking low that it burst through the floor and
I can actually play on my uh ragamuffin like like easy bake oven that I'm using yeah on my video games
on it like saying like exclamation point like I don't know like what can you do you can do a
fov underscore desired 90 that just is you do that every time you boot up the game a lot of people
don't know about that or a lot of people including me very rarely change like their settings in any
game they play and just let it fucking oh I bet you were a fucking apple fag I bet you're one of the
uh oh I was gonna I was gonna get the default settings my fucking phone I'm okay I'm not gonna
even what the settings I don't even know what that is I I am a literal programmer so I actually
know more than your average person about about this stuff so I do fuck when it comes to games
specifically I know how to lower quality if the game runs like shit I'll lower the quality all
the fucking way I'm aware of these things but like I don't know I'm playing battlefield uh no
black ops 4 a little bit lately and it's really fun but like I watched like doctor disrespect
play it the day it came out and like he goes and he changes like every setting I'm like I don't know
what any of this means and I don't care so I just uh no that's what happens you grow up on nothing
but console games you just don't understand that's that's what I did grow up exactly that's the
problem yeah you gotta gotta get in there you gotta get in there early 2004 gonna play some cs1.6
you gotta toggle on software mode because computer's so shit Tom knows what I'm talking about it makes
your graphics all pixelated and you have to be left-handed and it's really annoying because it
feels totally different because the weight of the screen is different but you gotta play through it
anyways because all your friends are really good you gotta memorize d-dust too because that's the
only map anyone ever plays even though you really like scouts and knives but none of your friends
would play scouts and knives so you had to play cs1.6 on d-dust too and it fucking sucked because
you sucked at the game it's the real shit I have so much I have so much console gamer pride
I'm so proud to know nothing about computer I don't even I don't even want to learn I never
want to know what a computer does Nate one of these days you're gonna be drinking your delicious
iced green tea flavor to taste if I were to have a cherry aftertaste at your local's Japanese
friendship garden and you're gonna take a bite and you're in your delicious mochi covered red
bean paste and you're gonna and you're gonna bite in and you're gonna be so happy and they're
gonna look down and realize wait a second that's not red bean paste that's my own blood and you're
gonna look down and see that I've chopped you limb from limb you have no more fucking body I've
sucked all of your blood into this did this mochi encrusted fucking delicious snack and you're
eating yourself stop eating yourself Nate stop eating yourself I say playing counter-strike
and headshotting you while you're distracted with my text commands I'm cheating with this the black
ops is actually getting me invested in this stuff a little bit and I'm I'm I'm so bad at this game
and I'm absolutely abysmal playing the blackout fucking you know pubg mode it's making me just
depressed about how shit I am at the game I'm not even close to winning I can kill like no one in
this fucking game because I didn't grow up playing first person shooters I don't know anything about
them oh my god that's the problem with online games the skill floor is very high especially at
this point where the problem is that you can't fucking play any video games that require any
amount of precision whatsoever it's impossible yeah no I'm not gonna do that fuck that I tried
playing fortnite on my switch because I was like it's free I guess I'll try uh it was terrible
wait a minute what do you mean precision what are you talking about the most precise thing
the most precise thing that you will ever do in your life the most the most precise like
threading through the eye of a needle fucking challenge that you will ever do is fucking the
second level of lion king jumping between the branches on that fucking ostrich bird you got to
do it if you're like a pixel off you will fucking die every time there's nothing more precise uh with
it with a with a platformer much better design fireworks in my background is there fireworks
what's going on I don't know like the fourth of july woo now there's a place nearby not too far
for ryan and they do like uh some sort of like five work festival every single day for the last
no no no it's just it's just a sunday afternoon in war torn lithuania the battle continues to rage
and then UK it just is always the cold one it's just it's always the cold war no you know what it
is actually gib told us what it is it's um remember remember the fifth of november people guy fox
oh yeah but it's the eleventh now i think they're past i know but gib told us though that it actually
isn't necessarily on that day but in general people will just pick a day to go set off fireworks and
shit just around that date i mean that's what gib said so i think it's very bizarre that you would
you would say remember the 15 november and then the actual for them there doesn't matter do it on
the right day at least i remember it like i said generally keep in mind the fifth of november
you know approximately okay but like i said this place near me it does this five work show every
single day well you said recently every single day for the last week or so what well the fifth of
november was it was less than a week ago so maybe it's like a daily celebration in honor of the guy
i mean it might be but i they're gonna make sure you remember it this year yeah by blowing up your
house it's the ultimate protest that's too far away for that but yeah oh oh oh by the way guys i might
actually not be on the episode because i could be six feet under the ground and actually be dead
i have been uh like on the you know that feeling you get the day before you know you're going to
be sick when you just need you sneeze once or twice and you feel a little bit weak and you're
like oh god like this is the calm before the storm i've had that for about four months now
and just and yesterday i started uncontrollably projectile spitting across my room my room was
just splattered wait wait wait dried up saliva spitting is different from projectile vomit because
you really can't control when you vomit but you you control when you spit so what's well okay okay
how can that be all right all right listen i'm i'm going to risk choking on my own spit and die
okay all right or am i going to have saliva line my entire well look at my walls nay and tell me
what i picked okay all right anyway uh there is a i have recently this is the thing i've always had
because uh whenever i speak uh they made me wrong god in heaven made me wrong and he just
made my tongue too fat as well as every other part about me too fat so i can't speak well
so i've always just developed whenever i talk for a long time as i am right now
that's spit that's saliva whenever i talk for more than like five minutes i just develop
a copious amounts of spit and sperm in my mouth and i and i've now recently because i'm just spitting
unbelievable amounts of spit like like like you could fill up like a like a large 99 cent
mcdonald's cup with my spit in like two hours and it's all like it's all different colors some of
them are like purples some of them are green so it's it's the full rainbow you can taste the
rainbow when you drink my spit much is the real i just have a giant cup of spit right next to me
right now um gross yeah uh okay it's uh it and i've been using it i have to i have to change it
because i've been using it for like the past day and now i guarantee you there's like an
uncontrollable like bubonic level plague being developed in this cup right now much maybe a
doctor question this is horrid it is horrid no what you should do they're quacks tom they're
quacks i don't need them you use this rainbow and paint a masterpiece paint your emotions
oh art from adversity art from death oh my god you're right nate this will be your black star
let me see i only have an hour in the next week well i'm not going to go to the doctor i'll just
paint a picture with my own spit my my own you're gonna have this is gonna have to be part of your
portfolio to get into my and i have to like uh oh don't say the name i didn't hear it it got cut
off okay but whatever okay okay i have i have a question to change the topic for for tamon
about this last episode of yours of the rfck you mentioned something about a hot dog and i've
i've was a bit curious what discourse did you have about a hot dog i don't want to blow the hot dog
keep in mind this is not a hot dog speech this is a hot dog speech i don't want to blow it on
this has to remain an rfck thing i will link you i can't believe this is gone start it up again
if we start it up again i will link you to the exact time stamp where we're talking about hot
dogs i will link you to it but try okay okay me and ben recorded a fucking like what like a seven
hour rfck episode where we play the entirety of super smash bros brawl and if you know fucking
anything about rfck you know what are the three games i've wanted to play rfck since it's fucking
inception number one lego star was the complete saga for the nintendo we number two webkins in
browser and number fucking three super smash bros brawl the subspace emissary the best fucking
game ever made and we play it all in one saying it's a beautiful pristine fucking episode a return
to form talking about real shit constantly it was the sad episode of rfck where i'm talking about all
my inner demons letting it all out to bear for you people you fucking say this to watch we talked
about we had extensive conversations about hot dogs about text commands it was a chock full it
was everyone in the g house fucking there besides digi man digi came in for a second or two it was
a glorious glorious episode and it's fucking gone because fat people exist fat hard drives what
what happened what do those fat people do this fucking time i'm mad hard drive is in a fat file
it's a fat format so i can't record over fucking four gigabytes so this fucking 900 gigabyte file
just is corrupted forever oh my god yeah the same thing happened to me we recorded to an external
hard drive because like i knew the file was going to be massive so but but a few weeks before on for
iam games we had to we tried to use an external hard drive with the xbox 360 to get it to play
games because it needed a hard drive to play old xbox games and so i plugged it in and i guess when
i plugged it in it formatted it from ntfs to fat 32 without telling me uh so fat 32 is limited to
four gigabyte file sizes so this file easily went over four gigs so instead of it like stopping
recording or being like hey we're going to split this up into multiple files it was just like it
just corrupted itself but kept recording nothing for like well great five hours jessie were you
saying someone happened to you like it yeah a year and a half ago fucking or longer maybe
fucking 10 years ago who cares 100 years ago fucking i've been around since before the dawn
of time but fucking me and digi played like we did like a 19 hour let's play of super luigi
brothers for you nice and we touched on everything we talked about the real shit we got into the
nitty gritty of it we had good times we had laughs and gaffes we had all that shit it was like a
20 hour fucking let's play and um like and we even like told people about it we hyped it up like oh
when you fucks see this luigi bros let's play well like i have it but it's like it's in this weird
file type that goes nowhere in no editing software on earth and i don't understand what he recorded
it on or how it is in that file type nothing else that we recorded is like that everything else works
fine but maybe luigi bros what file type it is it's probably saveable because the files do exist
it's just i can't get it to work in vegas and when i said every editing software i meant just the one
i have because jessie after after and i refused i refuse to apply myself to anything so if i have
to figure it out for you i'm i'm curious if you touch the file type we might be able to save it i
don't know well there you go it's a little bit past the expiration date now but who cares this
everything i do art has no expiration date nade come on yeah well okay all of my let's plays like i
upload them for patrons exclusively and then i forget about them for like three and a half years
and then i upload them for the rest of the world so they're all behind the times anyways the point
of the rfck thing is that uh fat shaming is real and it's about hard times not people this i'm hard
fat shaming right now fat 32 is banned it should no longer be compatible with anything it is
shit and it insults me greatly that the xbox would use fat 32 in this we got a title this episode
fat shaming for sure yeah okay guys okay it's not just that an rfc episode is lost which would
have been a shame on sound like that would have yeah but the whole point of us playing brawl aside
from i wanted to play it it was we were going to do the slime fest that evening as well and so we
we played we played rfck we are sorry we played the subway cemetery and then the whole point of
the slime fest was okay we're going to do each other and brawl this game that we've been playing
for the past fucking nine hours so we do that and slime fest is saved i was editing it but it's
just gonna seem so fucking weird and bizarre to have the slime fest where we continually comment
on things prior and also it's not particularly like the most interesting video on earth because
it's us really trying hard i think people will think it will like it a lot due to the fact of like
the the tone the tone in the room i would describe as very vicious and murderous uh but the fact
remains is that all we have to show for this altercation which should have been agoon coons
very beautiful like some place up some simmers sorry and then we premiere the slime fest it's
like they're together their their their brothers the brothers arms instead fucking remiss is dead
the episode is gone all i have to show for it is this fucking slime fest and it's a fucking
disaster and travesty it's like someone made the greatest anime in the world but only save the
final episode which is a masterpiece but nobody knows how you got there so it has none of the
emotional weight that you would have had i mean that's basically clerks the animated series
yeah the group is the they only aired like the second episode and the third episode and those
were out of order but it's it's the greatest anime ever made wait are there literally only two
episodes no there's six episodes oh okay but abc only aired like the third episode and then the
second episode what seriously the second episode is so over lying on the first one and it's like
the best thing because it's like an episode is yeah it's the clip show well that's fucking
bizarre have you never seen the show no okay so a lot of people like the first episode they saw
was them flashing back to an episode that they hadn't seen okay Nate so the reason this is so
brilliant is the first episode just like a normal funny episode of a tv show and and like like
silly things happen at one point there's like a scene of them basically spoofing like the old
batman show them climbing up like the side of a building and all of a sudden just like like
why are we walking like this yeah Dante's like why are we walking like this and then the camera
rotates and they're just walking along like a normal like floor and it's funny it's just a throwaway
scene but then the next episode episode two they get locked in the freezer and it becomes a clip
episode but since there's only one episode that came before it it's just all clips from episode one
they constantly cut back to that scene like and they tie it into the jokes throughout the whole
episode so it's a parody of yeah it's it's the best thing in the entire world it's like the greatest
thing ever made by a human being yeah it's one of the best written like legitimately one of the
funniest cartoons ever made and it's like there's only six episodes of it i i love the art style
it is really appealing to me i don't know what it is specifically because it's not like super
new unique it just is really pleasant i really like it it is i like the big like the thick lines
and yeah the shape of people it's good i don't i don't like that this in this cartoon people walk
on two legs i prefer a cartoon where they're on four legs it just appeals to my sensibilities more
and if and if they could be like like like farm animals like maybe horses or smaller horses or
something oh what would probably do a lot for me and you know it's really hard to like read characters
because i have mental disabilities so if they could just like stamp them with them just let me know
what kind of pony this is that would be just great that would be just great yeah yeah too bad they
could never do something like that it was banned by trump yeah fortunately oh my god gabe newles
brony you think that trump's a brony i guarantee you what would his favorite be probably probably
like i mean rarity because she's rich well she wait she's not rich but whatever she's in power
because she's white
i see him be an iron will guy yeah well that's true you know he is very similar to that yeah
he's convinced iron will is the main character and he won't take anything to the contrary i i can't
i want to hire a dolling truck impersonator you say that spike is best pony into a video camera
for me there's probably a damn fiverr who does that oh i want to get on the fiverr train you know
like there you can get you can get jesus to say something you could get that that big meme guy
who was like attention fortnite gamers uh pewdiepie needs your help but he's gonna need those credit
card numbers on your mom's card and those wacky digits on the back uh i want to hire those guys
i've been wanting to use them for something for a long time like roge and tyrone yeah exactly
it's like that i don't know if those guys are still active but there's there's at least a new wave
in addition you got to just you from now on like to make your we are your uh your we are
goes really quick you just write the script bang it out and like a night and then just pay them
and that's that's the entire we are was just that now that's efficiency hello we are going gamers
it is me the best guy ever with another episode of we we giga is that what up who's doing now that
he's fired from the yeah oh god he's you know you know what guys i had an update on that i heard
that that was actually semi-fake news uh because i think like that guy came out and said something
that he heard from an editorial staff or whatever that like up who was out i heard later on like
an actual executive of the company say that like the person who did it um was not speaking on behalf
of the studio and that uh to not take the serious probably because they've watched that episode of
brain dump and they're like oh god we're retarded we're taking it back hopefully i mean hopefully
but i heard that that's actually not true but i mean i don't watch the simpson so i guess i don't
really have the up-to-date info because i don't pay attention you know the worst thing they did
and this is my only opinion on this controversy but the worst thing was when they like sort of like
tried to address it in the show but in like the most heavy-handed asinine way they could have
or like they just had marge and lisa like break character and look at the screen like and look
and just say like oh here is fucking some things will be addressed in time maybe or if at all
and they like then there's like a picture a framed picture of a poo like on lisa's like what it may
here's the thing like either either say fuck you to the critics or say okay we're sorry you
win to the critics but like it was this weird like middle ground like i don't care if you
count out of them or not just do like why address it at all if you're gonna do it in this
wishy washy basically saying nothing way it was weird yeah it was it was just really like
off-putting and slimy feeling the way that like they looked at the camera and said hey we know that
some guy doesn't like that this like stop don't ever do that yeah you know they were literally
addressing it but in not a satisfying way for anybody and if like like the south park guys if
they heard this they would literally make an episode saying fuck you and just fill it with
indian stereotypes and just like completely well they did they did an episode about the
approved thing recently it was the it was this is about mr hanky like tweeting things on ambian
like rosanne the episode was called the trouble with a poo oh shit and at the end of the episode
mr hanky gets run out of town and has to move to springfield and a poo is there and that's
and then and then i go oh that was a that was a chuckle good job boys like at least they're
they're have courage of their convictions whether or not you agree with them or not it's kind of like
um it's just respect it's like an honorable opponent even if you're like a far left wing at
least you're like well these guys are making their opinions clear they say fuck you uh or so i don't
maybe they're actually more sympathetic have not seen the episode but i'm assuming you walk into
an immigrant internment camp this guy slaps your girlfriend on the ass what do you do
you um slap some fucking gas chambers on him that's what i do look at it look at his eyes
they aren't looking at you they aren't looking at anything they don't have no they're looking at
everything it's contemplating the universe right now you just told me that's a fourth
dimensional consciousness i would like the simpsons to slowly kill off every character until there's
only like two left and becomes a totally different show oh my god what if they did an episode about
like infant death and fucking mag he dies whoa just make it happen just make it happen and in the
next episode she's fine again no they never mentioned it like when brian died on family guy
uh guys should we go to the questions i think i think i think right at the end done enough for
these freaks right on this baby death question let's do an elegant transition um here we go
all right question here it is oh wait i gotta go to the right fucking channel so i don't feel the
thing uh so it's our friend one spar who seems to always be the last guy who i don't choose one
spar first on purpose he like always seems to be the guy who left the most recent comment
when i record which i think he does on purpose because he's smart he knows that like if he doesn't
right before the episode starts that's when i do them or maybe he's just lazy i don't know that
could be a tomb um anyway let's see what he's got to say today it's called one spar woke up late go
autonomous is an awkward thing to say
other than that it's an amazing game oh to whose game having a lot of fun with it everyone should
play it right now go download it that's it cool all right i left that in to remind to remind me
to to be like davoo's games out guys davoo's game is out at the moment that's cool i don't think okay
i don't think any of us have played it but not because i didn't want to i tried to play it last
night but the download was gone so i didn't have the ability to play it i was busy it's not on itch
anymore uh wherever on the website it was there'll be a link in the description i don't
uh there was no download like when i looked or something it said on the website it's down
because you had to fix something or something i played it but it's there now oh shit excellent
perfect i wanted to hear from you uh yes davoo's game at tominous uh what do you think sorry i'm a
little out of breath he ran he heard the call now i'm a little out of breath because i was just
like burning some ica furniture but it had like weird chemicals in it and i couldn't breathe and
it was terrible uh but oh that's cool you know how it goes with burning things yeah um all right
burning down the neighborhood in this tough economy uh so autonomous is a very it's a very
davoo game here's my game review uh it's it's it's good and it's short and it's very davoo it's
it's a game about clicking on pieces of furniture in a house and reading the flavor text um and it's
like that very much sounds cool yeah it's like you do that in every single video game ever but
nobody not not not a single time is it actually supposed to be funny except sometimes like sometimes
when it's a comedy based game like they put a bit of comedy in there but like imagine davoo
being funny but like with every item in an entire house like the the the amount of things that you
know there's just a lot of funny stuff in there and it's really cute and really tight i i didn't
have any problems with like it crashing uh and i downloaded the original version so i don't know
what's up with that even davoo is confused um but it's the music also it basically you know how
like last time i was talking about how delta rune is like i don't really care about like the meta
stuff in undertale delta rune is just scratches an itch that doesn't get scratched generally
of like nice characters and quirky setting with like you know easy enough gameplay and this is
basically davoo's like was it an attempt to do that he didn't know delta room was coming out
obviously none of us did and so his like game uh coming out was like uh unfortunate but it is
it is the same sort of delta rune scratching sort of you know not like a huge game like an hour
two hours but it's it's very much in that same vein of like quirky fun and simple and it's great
and i really like it and it's a really good job dude i think it's really cool i'm actually super
fucking excited to go play i think i wish i had a chance to before the episode but i'm definitely
gonna do it right after it's really cool that some of us are like making games like a bunch of us are
making games and yeah like i anything that's not a youtube video because i'm like so over
like youtube videos in and of themselves as a thing yeah yeah like people who fucking make
games and draw and shit that's cool man it's cool i want to do cool stuff like that and speaking of
drawing let's talk about here's a topic let's talk about my sweet new drawing tablet yeah courtesy
of tom oliver courtesy of tom oliver he sent me this because i was fucking uh complaining about
not being able to draw and now i can draw and i've been drawing how many masterpieces to share with
us um love to see one i do i mean should we show them in this episode or like a draw cast because
i don't know we if you want we could certainly put some in the show and draw cast or a specific
thing if yeah we'll look at the show notes if you want to yeah if you want to go out i don't know
what i'm gonna do with these yet if i'm gonna like make a place to upload them all or something or
like uh i don't know because i thought it'd be cool to have like a webcomic or something and i've
mostly been drawn like weird like weird monsters and like weird self portraits of me being fat on
the beach and stuff with like uh i mean there's always handy stuff just to host them yeah i do have
an old devian art page that they have an upload i'm working on a batman comic right now like a
like a big like a long i don't know maybe three pages okay like a batman comic and it's it's called
the joker rapes at midnight the plot it sounds good the plot of it is that the joker you know he
hijacks the news feed or whatever he makes an ultimatum he says tonight i'm either going to rape
1000 babies or i'm gonna rape batman so if batman cares about this city he will offer his ass to me
and that's the the dilemma that batman has to is one man's pride worth a thousand babies virginities
we're gonna find out in the joker rapes at midnight well that sounds fascinating just jesse is this
gonna be the beginning of of a revival of double batman and triple joker yes oh yeah we're gonna
get some real shit now that would be glorious it would be glorious and then i yeah i was thinking
like man if i really like just started drawing batman comics like i wonder what i could legally
do with them like could i publish them in something if they were like technically a parody because
like i'm not sure yeah i don't know you just just change a letter only one way to find out dude
yeah because that would be awesome to like release a book of like com like a fucking comic book that
would be the coolest shit ever that would be fucking dope well fucking fantastic i can't wait
to see it uh i guess let's go to the next question here uh this is one from a fan of the show never
paint friend draw reliable draw guy draws all kinds of cool stuff check him out uh let's see what he has to say
pcp dating sim is a really good project i'm designing detailed background art right now
painting the sacred halls of a pcp university campus it's really fun my question what would
be your perfect dating location doesn't need to have any ties to reality answers are appreciated oh man
my ideal dating location would be on the set of joker rapes at midnight
so so never paint here is advertising the pcp dating sim shit what was the twitter link for that
i think was pcp dating at pcp dating i'm gonna go double check but so apparently it's real people
are working on it confirmed by never paint here yeah at pcp dating that's the one i'm not sure i
like that that at like that the handle like that could be misconstrued great pcp yeah like literally
date us go to pcp dating where we need girlfriends please sign up if you're a girlfriend nothing
that says pcp in the title is ever going to be good i've been saying this for fucking five years
sure sure um but hey it's already happening and we can't stop my ideal dating scenario would be a
national land or a sort of government building maybe a statue moments before a terrorist attack
so when we start to get in the mood and maybe we kiss for the first time the bombs start to drop
that sounds good i maybe you could time your orgasm with instant death that'd be ideal whoa
whoa that's a step that's a step too far that i would say nothing about orgasm okay you're right
you're right i'm getting carried away here forgive me uh my ideal on my wedding night i
want a 9-11 to happen at the moment of climax that would be ideal uh my ideal dating scenario
would be like a proper lap like an actual lap like not like dungeons and dragons would like uh-huh i
got you with lightning ball like you get like a real like suit of armor you get your your real
like torches with the flames on them and you're like oh yes i'm i'm staying in character for a
whole month and i'm out here in the fields like i got a real tent and i'm like that that that would
be the real shit and you got like i mean you got the phone swords because you don't want to kill
anyone but you got a real sword that is for show and you're like oh yes it's real sharp guys
that's that and then okay that'll be that that's the one my my ideal one would be is basically imagine
like a pretty nature scene with like a river and forest and stuff like that except everything is
pastel purple and sparkly sounds good of course of course mine would be like it's like a like a
beautiful like a like a scottish glen like like the highlands or everything's green and it's like
overlooking cliffs and stuff and it's all beautiful and serene but also you can see planets in the
sky so you know that you're not on earth and oh yeah and also there's like a maybe like a dinosaur
somewhere and like a big fucking another dinosaur what if you're both riding dinosaurs yeah oh that
would be nice the dinosaurs um some of them have saddles because it's we've tamed them
in this society on this planet that i've invented just now have you tamed them or they tamed you
that's the question um i think it's a uh it's like a uh a symbiotic relationship i think we've tamed
each other we bring out the best in each other man and dinosaurs i don't know why i said lark for
some reason like like it was it was said you could be like random like uh not real places could be
i would be like the the scene from game of thrones where john gets stabbed i want to reenact
that who is john who's john that's you in this situation that's the question that's the eternal
question they'll have to figure that out i don't know i'm thinking i guess just on the on the on the
bow of a spaceship hurtling off toward adventure uh to to parts unknown to discover the wonders of
the universe uh i mean pretty simple but yeah that's literally what i want to be doing with
life oh that's a good answer secrets i'm gonna change my answer to that in fact oh everyone in space
my okay i i want to change my my dream date scenario would be we're getting home you know we're
you know maybe maybe we're getting a little bit frisky you and me on name player you know maybe we're
getting we're getting the mood then we turn the corner and and and and then before we can even
register total shock fills our body and then solider creek says what are you doing in this
video and instead of having sexual relations like how we thought we actually have to pretend
that we're reviewing a movie oh shit oh shit yeah yeah yeah i would be like in an angry video game
nerd episode i've changed mine as well i'm gonna be in the video game den i'm gonna point out like
let's play this game nerd and he's like okay he's just sort of there for some reason on the date
i'm sure ben ben would be uh uh at the fanciest of restaurants out back by the dumpster overflowing
with leftovers and ingredients it's just it's a it's a smorgasbord out there
with the fun oh literally lady in the tramp situation literally lady in the tramp that's
actually romantic so you know what that totally works yeah and then i'd be like i'd be like on a
beach like a tropical hawaiian beach where all the girls are like beautiful and there's only girls
and there's no other boys but me but but like also it's not just a beach it's also it's also in
like a plastic dome in space and so it's like a it's like a space station of domes with different
ecosystems in them and so you can you can go in the tubes like hamster tubes from one to the other
to get from the beach to the skiing slope and stuff and also there's like like little graves
on the beach because there was like a normandy situation at some point so there's little like
little white crosses all along the shoreline that does sound good that does sound good oh you
could also go for some like end of eva imagery with those crosses out in the distance oh yeah there's
also an avangelion beach but that's different from the tropical beach there's many domes there's
many domes in my space station many domes that's the name of my book i just want a cyberpunk future
where i have like robot prosthetics i live forever and i have a robot dong that can be as big as
it needs to be because that's that's a little point of cybernetics anyways right i want tom
sexing to be like you know those extremely overly animated like robo combination animations they do
in the old super robot animations uh it'd be that only robo pop with robo vagina and just like like
animated animated 24 fps on ones like overly detailed flying yeah tom's date area should be uh you
show up to the pre uh you know determined meeting place you know maybe like a fancy restaurant or
something and then you're like where's tom then it cuts back to him debugging his game looking at the
time and like oh well i fucked up i mean going back oh just like just like flubber with robo with uh
you know he was always late and forgot dates and stuff because he actually doesn't give a
shit even though he says it's because he's quote unquote so in love yeah that makes sense i don't
buy it you're a bad husband or whatever uh all right well that's everybody let's go to the next
question um next is from this is from hippo shit hippo shit oh no let's let's see what he has
hello friends if uh if uh our lovely uh dearly friendly neighborhood hypocrite is looking for
a new show to watch uh then perhaps you should check out hilda on netflix as it is similar to the
steven universe uh a pantheon of cartoons you see so he might enjoy it and it also is all out at
once so it's the opposite of steven universe yeah i can't tell i can't tell if he's doing a cool
voice or if he's just cool yeah what do they say hilda hilda yeah i heard good things about it so
people and it's all out which is great it to me i'll i'll i'll give it a gander i'll give it a
little pain you know i watched some of uh over the garden wall uh which was that over that garden wall
i look pretty i never i don't know it's a great finish it yeah it was really good
dude i just watched the fucking season two of the castlevania show it was
i'm watching it please don't spoil okay i won't spoil it but like i couldn't believe how good it
was because i didn't really watch season one i i sort of like skimmed through like the first
episode and i saw like the a la carte episode where he's introduced but that's really like
all i saw of it so i just kind of jumped into season two without fucking knowing anything
and like it was like such a ride it was so like good like there was so much character like even
everyone had like a backstory and a personality like even even like the underlings of like the bad
guys had like their own little like arcs and stuff there was like a whole pretty dope like half the
series was like a la carte and fucking what's his face and the lady girl trevor and cypher trevor
come on hang it cool look man i'm i'm uh old i don't remember names of characters and shows
anymore that's like a dad thing so i just like say like the fat one as so like so like half of it
was them in a in a library like talking and like jiffing and jiving with each other and like you
know well you're a jerk well you're my friend too buddy and so the but then the other half was like
in in draculous camp and all of his like underlings and all of his spooky friends and they're all
like bickering amongst themselves and they're all like plotting and scheming under each other and
like backstabbing each other and i'm like this is just this is just a good fucking time that sounds
like it sounds like um like orcs from mode of the rings sort of yeah yeah yeah that's cool
oh right there's another show that i watched uh just last night because i was at a person's house
and everyone fell asleep and i'm always the last one to fall asleep so there was a tv in front of me
so i ended up watching this show that i never heard of called Norseman
and it's like uh it's like a scandinavian horseman hey it's like a scandinavian show and it's like
like like sort of like a game of thrones or a vikings type show like you think it's like that
but it's a comedy and it's like it's like it's sort of like flight of the concords but vikings
oh shit and like that sounds great yeah the tone of it was like that really like awkward like
everyone's kind of a doof comedy but like it had like a really cool balance of tone where like
it's really really funny and silly and absurd but also when they start killing people it is like
it's done like straight like a real like vikings are killing people and it's scary
kind of show it's like it was a really well done i liked it and i watched like the whole
first season in bed and it was a good time it reminds me a little bit of uh this manga
vinland saga that i think is getting an anime i'm pretty sure um and uh i don't know yeah it mostly
was serious viking stuff which was really great and i loved it but then there was some humor so
whatever it was good it was good all right uh all right let's go to the next question this is from
nibbo the hoe or is it nibbo the hoe oh my god that's the emissary of education a concert it is
we're welcome please educate us this one goes out to nate and digipro uh you guys are the only
two people that have ever thought about what would it be like to be your kid or what would it be like
to have you as my dad and for nate i think um it's just he'd be a quirky guy quirky dad but
but overall really good except for that he gives way too many lectures and for digipro um well god
he's just gonna be shit dad he's gonna he's gonna have his kids doing things they don't want to do
from from his from his happiness projection he's gonna be wrong and he's gonna tell them wrong
things uh that's my prediction it's truth they'll have no one to tell them that their dad is wrong
talk to my dad's shit cut this out you're damn right i included that because you aren't here to
defend yourself digi ha ha take that i like the idea of i i just like the image of instead of like a
dad forcing his kids to play sports he's forcing them to make youtube vlogs and review anime and
shit like daddy i want to know where 3.0 is coming it's coming we have to be on the cutting edge of it
dad you've been saying that for the past 19 years my existence no no it's coming i want to run around
outside and look at bunnies yeah they're just gonna have to tell them what you think about what to do
with it it's gonna be whatever you can see you can see rabbits on google image search a little
bastard so so dad i started reading some history books and i started you know researching some
math textbooks what do you think what's the point of being we're being smart why aren't you fucking
what's the point of being right how are you with me son are you with me i feel like digi's son or
daughter is going to become a doctor just to spite him get the most education possible it's
usually how it works like like fuck you dad i'll be exactly the opposite oh my god can you can you
imagine the the fucking just like like like screw you it would get if digi has a son or a daughter
and they are determined to go to college and he has to co-sign on those loans and pay back all that
money oh my god i want to have a kid now this has to happen okay imagine like nate you want to be a
father too and i have ingredients of the same thing but this is not the way like this is not
munchy and nate best man are going to have children you know this is gonna be pretty far in the future
not like you know like a billion years or anything but this isn't like i would say that i mean i mean
me i'm just gonna refer to you because it would be it's weird to refer to myself you know you're
gonna have like a you know like a few fucking years like you know probably i mean i want to be
probably five or something you're probably gonna change a whole bunch in that time but digi wants
to have a child like now and it will be digi bro having the child it will not be digi man well
the youtuber man digi bro in his current state of not being able to like wake up in the morning
and drinking constantly that would be a father for an actual human being it's gonna be the future
vlogs it's just gonna have like a like the reflective glasses gonna have a baby in one
corner and then and then maze button the other at all times and he'll make that his icon
oh that would be pretty fun that would be pretty fucking sick thoroughly roasted digi show up next
time to defend yourself that's all i have to say all right uh what do we got next a feast for hands
a feast for hands h and d s uh tell us your thoughts hello i believe i can be a broker
between the two parties of this pcp union you have here see for for star fleets to truly
come into into fomention i don't think it is to be created the the power with of dreams
have to be harnessed as the fuel source of this new advanced society
thus the violet nathans will rise as a new fusion from the tarah hearings yes just like the
animes that are watched what a worthwhile comment the violet nathans the violet nathans um well i did
choose to play that so i guess i'm the one at fault um what the fuck get moving on decimated i apologize
uh uh uh jevil man this is from jevil man um deltarune character yeah he guys deltarune
alternative theorist here i just wanted to point out that when you you guys said that
when during the asriel potential reveal that you know susie didn't really react but if you look at
her sprite she's all hunched back you know she's got her arms all twisted up like she's nervous and
her eyes are bigger than bowling balls so i think you guys need to really reanalyze the scene if you
really want to be games or extensions of games as well as it will i don't appreciate my status
it's me it's me roscoe to clown i do birthday parties i do bombets fuzz i do all that shit
and i do analysis on youtube as well check out my youtube page at youtube.com slash
each channels uh uh slash sdf lowercase d uh uh g uppercase uh h i don't have enough subscribers
for unique url yet but subscribe so i can get one have you met my have you met my brother
vinnie the fortune teller hey it's me vinnie the fortune teller i do bombets fuzz i do kids
birthdays i do all that shit vinnie what are you doing in this bar mitzvah i came in through the rift
okay next next comment do it i dare you uh what do you do friend
you know on this day of which i am delivering pizzas as i currently do that i wondered i pondered
i thought the most important of questions does pcp sled gang do they stand atop the white
sled and conquer the mountains with a plastic is an agarral and foam foam
match to carry i know one to three humans do they talk about a sled i think that's a pcp sled gang
this is what we need to know i think he's currently sledding like in the episode i think he was
well maybe i thought he was talking about delivering if you deliver pizzas on a sled that's
pretty funny that's pretty big the pizza shops at the top of the mountain and he has to that's
the fast sleds down to any individual house um make sense we that was like a fucking
yeah that guy i don't know that was just that was like a oh chilling and killing my sweet anabelle
on the cliffs over the sea i think what he was getting at is we should make a jamaican
bobsled team he's right uh oh can i be the sled dude plenty big enough yeah that's true
um i'm more interested in everyone's fucking voices than their actual questions i don't even
know the questions are i always like to include the the diversity of voices here it's nice it
adds a lot of depth to the episode let's see what number eight hideyasu has for us you guys tend to
refer to the pcp as a sort of friendship simulator yeah i completely agree because anyone who's willing
to listen to this dumpster fiverr podcast clearly has some issues to sort out myself included my
problem with this is that i have yet to find anybody who has the same interests and works on the same
wavelength that i do so while this may be a friendship simulator it's not like i have many
other options available to me i like the few friends that i do have but frankly they don't have much
to offer besides the fact that they're just fun to hang out with they're not the type of people who
are going to give me advice and help me with my goals etc etc and they're not willing to listen
to my advice how can i find friends to have more intelligent and meaningful discussion
so that i can finally quit listening to this podcast and do something more valuable sometimes
yeah okay i think just find people however it however difficult that may be find people who
are like into the most obscure shit that you're also into because they'll probably be on a deeper
wavelength yeah that's probably true uh i mean question look look into yourself and ask yourself
how many people do you actually meet day to day because they have numbers probably quite low
so you're probably not exposing yourself to a lot of people which is understandable if you're young
and stuff uh joint clubs uh hang out on forums with like-minded people and uh you just meet
more people because you'll meet a lot of shitty people who don't you don't care about and they
don't aren't cool but that will expose you to an opportunity to meet more good people i guess so
yeah do most of the people who are like what like no one relates to me like like there's no one that
is on the same like unbelievably genius wavelength that i am there's no one that knows the real deep
shit they're like you know the truly obscure stuff like 4chan.net like no one understands like i do
yeah uh most of the time they just are in their room and don't even make an attempt to fucking
actually meet people and you expect to bump into your best friend at the supermarket whenever you
do are forced to leave your room i'm not saying that's what you are i'm just saying you like
i think everyone everyone in the world who has the sentiment overestimates how hard it is to
meet like-minded people because there aren't like you okay i don't mean this like a derogatory way
but you aren't that special dude you aren't that fucking crazy or that obscure or that insane
that no one's going to be able to get what you're putting down unless you're talking to people who
legitimately just don't get it which i'm sure is the vast majority people but i'm saying not that
fucking hard go on a forum find your what are your interests go to a forum oh but i don't want to go
on a forum because that's fucking gay okay you aren't making an attempt to find new people you
you don't want to go out to a club because oh they wouldn't get it anyway like you want to go out to
your fucking college club you want to go out to any you know flyers down the street or whatever
you're not making the attempt if you don't do that then you can't fucking say that you're trying
your best to make friends because what are you doing you're saying that you can't make friends and
then stay in the house making a self-fulfilling prophecy if you want to have people relate to
you fucking try at all and you will find people very soon i don't think that uh this podcast
or any podcast should be used as a replacement for like actual relationships and actual friends
and it sounds like this guy like has friends he just feels like he's not getting like
deep conversations out of them or like talking about the real shit but i think this is what might
be one of the situations where the best the most valuable thing you can do is nothing because i think
that like being like having all the same interests and having like big deep like conversations is
overrated and what really matters is just being with your friends at all and even doing nothing
like you'll regret not taking every opportunity to just be around the people who like you regardless
of whether you're fucking talking about fucking issues or whatever you know completely agree with
you jesse just in human interaction all with your friends is good i would even say if you aren't
getting like the deep conversations you want maybe you can instigate that i mean i mean don't just
wait for it to happen just don't wait for your friends to bring up things that are you know heavy
hitting if you want to do that and it's not weird and obviously you're talking about spider man talking
about you know oh man spider home home come so good don't bring out how your father's dead and
your and your dog shot himself just if the mood's right try and do that yourself like bring up the
things that interest you because guaranteed if your friends aren't shitters then they'll care about you
and they'll want to hear what's on your mind i don't think he he said something in there um
he said something about his friends not being willing to listen to his advice so i get that this
guy wants to think about like making it and probably like making progress and growing and
developing as a person and he wants people that share that interest it's possible that you're an
asshole and you're not that smart or interesting that's definitely possible and that's why they're
not listening but it's also part that they legitimately don't share your interest which is
fine like you know like sure if they're your friends you can enjoy hanging out with them but
if you really just don't have friends that you connect with yes you've you've got to go find the
people i guess or at the very least challenge the people that are your current friends in in new
ways try to get them involved in things maybe see if they take because i mean i had lots of friends
in in college that like i would try to do stuff i mean i was not like a productive god but i'd try
to do some things some people were interested some people weren't i mean okay so now you know
which people you're more interested in hanging around with and like people who like contribute
to what you're trying to do uh you can hang out with them more and people who don't like it's fine
it's not a judgment you know just hang out with the people who do what you want to do more uh and
and most importantly yeah i say make new friends go out do things put yourself in situations where
you meet people because if you're just home be in sad you've got a zero percent chance of meeting
people that you like hanging out with if you do anything at all go out um join clubs join forums
talk to people uh maybe go to like meetup.com or something like try to find places where like-minded
people are gathering it's easier than ever to find people of common interest to you it's literally
clicks away clicks away also i don't think that you should um expect or desire to have your advice
listened to by your friends or anyone advice is like the worst like you don't want to be the guy
who gives advice because nobody wants advice ever advice is totally worthless because no matter
how much you think that your outside perspective will help you don't know the person you're not in
their brain you don't know every facet of it so they're gonna hear your advice and go you
fucking idiot you don't know it's not that fucking simple like that's true nobody ever wants to hear
advice all anyone wants to hear if they're like having a hard time and they're like confiding in
you or coming to you all they want is to be listened to and be heard they don't necessarily
want you to like throw oh well you should do this at them because nobody wants that
shit it's obnoxious the the pcp has always been like a like a like a uh a voice for kind of niche
and an off-color opinion that's always been this case and i realized that i just gave the advice
not to give advice i realized the contradiction don't try to call me out on it i'm fucking self-aware
a lot of people who watch the piece a lot of fans of the pcp have been genuinely like
indoctrinated in a way to firmly believe all like the the foundational beliefs of the pcp
a lot of that i don't even believe that growing up on starfleet and shit like that which and and so
i just want to say for the record well of course having people who you know are our goal-oriented
people who are doing their shift obviously this is beneficial we've talked about this for a
fucking a billion episodes at this point you know what we hold to be true and what we what we expect
and what we like as a as a consciousness here but it is not to diminish the fact that it is
extremely valuable to have friends who are just funny or kind yeah being a kind person who is
nice and generous or would give you the clothes you know clothes off their back if you need them
that is an extremely valuable type of person to have because they're fucking nice kindness is not
often regarded here in these circles which is not like a bad thing we're talking about other things
but kind of trumps everything those things are good and listen to your friends and just don't
expect them to be like the pcp appreciate them for what they are and that's probably nice people yeah
you kind of want to have the people like that around you for sure because like the problem with
having nothing but creative people around you is like especially like people like like for
myself for like artistically obsessed with their work is that their work is always going to come
first and like that's going to be their number one concern and so if soup comes to nuts they're
going to fucking abandon you to work on their shit if you have friends you need a mixture of people
who are creative who will help inspire you if you have those kind of aspirations but you also need
people who are just like friendly that you can just like when you need to take a break you have
somebody who like isn't going to in the back of their mind like you like i got to get back to work
eventually like this is the work the work is being social and having a good time because that's
what they want to do in their lives part of that will rub off on you and you will stop being so
artistically obsessed with your work and you can find that balance that you might not naturally have
one of my best friends in real life has no aspirations other than playing video games and
doing his job and for some reason like when i hang out with him it just clicks like we hang out
once in a blue moon because he's like living his real life he's like a therapist he like went to
like real school and shit um but like absolutely we grew up as kids like pretty close by we just
went to the game shop store and played cards and shit and like when we hang out it's just that
again and all of my cares go away and i'm just hanging out with my friend that i've known for
like 15 years i'm not thinking about art just thinking about playing games having a good time
and like i'm very rarely in that headspace and it's super healthy and i wish he was closer so we
could do it more often because it is good to have that back i absolutely man i know the exact
feel i just last night went and saw one like my best friend from high school who i never see anymore
like the first time i've seen him in like a year and a half maybe and like what you said it was just
this like feeling of like oh i'm like out of it for one night i'm out of the internet i'm out of
my fucking room i'm out of this creative shit i'm just with a person who is my friend and who
was kind and we like each other and we can fucking get drunk and like fucking hug each other and be
like oh i fucking love you and i miss you you fucking bastard it's the most important thing
in the world like kindness trumps everything fuck anyone who is creative fuck anyone who thinks that
they're smarter than you or who has an attitude or who is arrogant or who is like a just like an
asshole fuck anyone who has like delusions of grandeur none of it is all bullshit like kindness
is the ultimate human trait it's the only thing you need just like don't fucking expect things out
of your friends except for kindness that's the only thing that matters just be with them and
fucking fucking watch football or some gay shit i have a venn diagram i have a venn diagram in my
head of of people who are useful to me and then people who are my friends these are separate
categories but there is a overlap between i like yes a venn diagram exactly yeah i i get what you're
what you're laying down i'm on it i'm in it and and oh and final point wait sorry i just i was
going to say the only the only thing i wanted to make about this whole friendship thing is uh
it's possible you're underestimating your friends so i'm just going to say don't forget that you do
need to cultivate friendships to get more kind of out of them so don't expect you just meet someone
and they're an npc and you can immediately exhaust all their dialogue and ideas so you know just be
aware that friendships need to grow before people will share some things with you or their stuff so
it's possible you just met these quote-unquote friends that you described like yesterday and
so it's natural for them to not you know be be sharing everything they got so i'm just saying
don't underestimate them don't assume they got nothing going on and ancillary ancillary to like
all of this advice like this is secondary not not as important but um the the there's one like
pretty it's not easy but like a simple way to like attract people that you like more or are like
minded is is just to be a better version of yourself like to be the coolest guy in the room so like
maybe work on improving how cool you are and how charismatic you are and how much uh you know how
much how many people gravitate towards you it would just make it easier than you being kind of lame
and having to go up to everyone very true that's very true you know i i always think of something
that like um people like what what we were saying before about like people being sort of indoctrinated
into like pcp like stuff that we've said like not everything that we've said as is like meant to be
taken totally seriously like this has always been kind of a comedy podcast like there's i know there's
stuff that i've said especially in early episodes of this podcast that i would like probably vehemently
disagree with now or that i have like totally the opposite stance on like sometimes i've had people
like it's the worst when someone agrees with something that you said years ago that you no
longer fucking yeah even remember you said let alone agree with like i've had people going like
oh man like remember what jesse said sometimes about how like uh people who aren't creative
aren't real people i totally agree with that and it's like no don't agree with that's the worst
thing i've ever said that's the most evil thing that's ever come out of my mouth except for what i
said to the carny lady when i was kid that was totally different i i've had numerous experiences
very recently when fans would come up to me like say like and like say like one like post like i'm
sorry like i'm so sorry i'm so sorry like i know that you're so fucking busy right now and i shouldn't
be messing with you at all like like i like i understand that i'm a fan but um and then they
go on to like they're like really well thought out and like cool like yeah i get that too like i
get comments where it's like oh man i hope jesse doesn't ban me for this but i really like this
video and i like it dear god i i'm sorry i'm sorry for banning anyone ever yeah i i i just want
everyone to know that i i do not hate fans i i've never even been the one to say that just
in the pcp and people think that's what they think no you can talk to me whatever you want it's
literally i love talking to people on my discord on twitter like that's the interaction's great
because yeah if you're nice to me then i like you that's it i prefer to interact with people like i
either over twitter dms or in groups on discord i don't like people PMing me or DMing me on discord
out of nowhere that's kind of scary i don't know how i'm down i'm down with that i don't care it's
cool if you got stuff you want to say to me you know questions or whatever just something that you
thought i'd be interested in or i don't know whatever my my discord's fucking public use just
like my ex wife sure showed her i think literally all of us have like a private discord or not a
private but like a specific to us discord yeah and i'm like i'm i get along with all the people in
there they have yeah all the people in my discord are cool shit they're they're fucking cool shoutouts
to everybody in there call call into the pcp call into the pcp you have good voices you have funny
voices i really feel like what that what that kid was saying um in that voicemail about like feeling
like his friends aren't like stimulating him intellectually like he wants because like i feel
like i used to be kind of in the same place where like i got in a mode for a couple years where i was
like man i i don't have anything in common with my friends anymore i have more in common with my
creative friends on the internet but like like a couple years after that like that was just like a
phase for like a couple years and then like after that like i'm back to now i think that all creative
people are fucking evil narcissists and sociopaths who should fucking bleed out and die in the street
and like regular people who just work regular jobs and like are cool on the weekends those are my
people that's who i want to be around now so i've totally i've totally flipped the pig on that one
i've totally flipped kill them all that's what i say uh all right let's go to the next call let's
go to the next call there's two more this one's from pcp fan unconditional hate guy so let's uh
let's get ready for a roasting thoroughly hey guys this season of the pcp has been pretty
fucking great for like a character motivation sense so keep that shit up i mean i know y'all are just
faking your lives um but anyways i just wanted to say i think it's really fucking rich uh that digi
thinks that uh having a child is any less of a risk than college in fact it has just about the same
potential downsides but greater so like if we're gonna grill someone who's like 18 and everyone
everyone in their fucking lives remembers when they were 18 and they didn't know what the fuck
they were gonna do with their lives even if you got advice you don't have to beat a man into the
ground when basically he's going because his mom wants him to go it's gonna happen so if we could
just yeah hear that this kind of good stuff but wow that kind of sounded like victor like in disguise
calling in to yell at his brother uh well whatever i mean you know i did you made his points fair
enough he was clearly drunk i think he'd probably walk back a good bit of that no no no no no no
you know i don't he was he was pretty much on the same wavelength in person when we had that
discussion before okay yeah all right i gotta say i really just don't get the whole um like
just saying like i want to have kids or i'm not gonna have kids like deciding one or the other
like i guess it's cuz like i agree i come from a background where having kids is not something
that people decide right right so like i don't know like my view on on on it is like i'm just gonna
keep fucking and if a kid pops out then that's gonna be all right okay it's not that hard to not have
a baby it's not it's not yeah like just keep fucking people and if it happens it happens you got that
problem just keep fucking just keep fucking um well in the comparison of the comparison of having
a kid to going to college that you know kind of makes sense it kind of makes sense because you
don't know i mean i guess anyone who wants to have a kid it's not someone who wants to run for political
office all right that you kind of have to have an ego in that you're you think you'll do a good job
you know at least a little bit or you're just not worried about it i guess it's like rolling
the dice twice you're rolling it wants to have a kid and then you're rolling it again to see if
they want to go to college as well so basically you could get both bad sides you could get the
you could like it could be like twice double i mean it's obviously expensive to have like just
put in cold terms having a kid definitely costs money in time fair enough it costs love i guess
if you can produce that i can't relate um and uh uh yeah you don't know i i'm pretty convinced
i'll be a decent dad i mean i could be totally wrong i could be wrong about that i think i'm
going to try to prioritize what's best for it parenthood really needs a free demo what the
fuck i would love a free demo that'd be really nice it'd be really actually i kind of am doing
that with a dog uh you know it's my responsibility the demo that tested it out a little bit you know
that's fair it's going so pretty well so far except he's pooping a lot uh all over the place
inside gotta straighten him out real quick he pulls out gun um yeah so i don't know you know what
fair i that's a relatively fair point um i think digi happens to hate college for personal reasons
i probably am similar in that boat a lot of a lot of personal reasons coming for me as to why
i'm not a big fan um just move on just move on normal college ever no please the memes that
years ago he's right all right he he is right okay okay we got one more call one more voicemail
here this is from uh let me say this is from uh racist forest gump um coming in with a hot take
i know it i'm gonna do it janay i'm gonna say the n word no no forest you can't say the n word
that's racist janay you can't stop me i'm gonna say the n word no forest don't do it no don't do it
no all right janay here i go no forest don't do it it's racist what would opoma think here i
you're like all right janay i'm gonna say no stop stop oh that's the end oh thank god
signal signal disconnected that was a close one we almost got deleted um i played that one
because it was funny there was also another call from somebody who's criticizing me for apparently
saying n e g g e r like spell like spelling it like not not committing to saying the word um i i
get i have no problem with saying the word i guess except that youtube could ban you you know like i
don't want to get i don't want to let my love of free speech man i just the reality that we're on a
platform i just love that word so much it's not like even a racist thing like i'm sorry that it
defends people truly yeah but it's so good it's so juicy and funny it is always always
fucking hilarious god blazing saddles is such a funny fucking movie and they say it every five
seconds it's god is i want to i want to marry that word i was watching a bunch of key and peel
skits recently and i love them they're they're the production i mean these are these are like
from 2013 or something the older stuff whatever it was great i loved it and i'm just like uh
they're whatever there's a skit that's like you know like two two like thugs like meat in uh what
was it it's like there's a kid as who's a member of an acapella group he's the one black kid and
then like another black guy shows up it's uh it's it's peel i think and like the the two lock eyes
and they understand they're competing for this white boy love now or something and um whatever
like uh uh as soon as like the the white guys leave it's just the two of them they immediately
like go from like haha yeah we're having fun to like what's up nigga what are you doing coming
into my white boy group do you know how long it took me to cultivate and he just goes you know
gangster or whatever and i'm like man it sucks that people would be mad at me for quoting this
hilarious skit yeah i mean it really sucks i think i think i get it but society just needs
white people like we need more white people to admit that we love that fucking word and it's
like not in a racist way it's just fun we love we like it too black people we like to say it too
it's fun it's fun and it's fun so there yeah sorry not sorry same old line same old line i like how
we just admitted that like we have like an audience like taking our ideas and running with them and
immediately follow up with this discussion well that's an idea that you should take and run with
it because i believe in it 120 percent look it's up to everybody to judge for themselves what they
do and don't like about whatever anyone says ever people need to fucking think critically so you
know fuck you if you just don't think about what i'm saying and you just do it that's your problem
i'm mine i'm not against people using the word i just personally prefer not to so that's totally
cool yeah i'm just i'm just saying this is my statement because you said you keep saying we
and i'm like i'm part of that we so i just i just wanted to i ain't speaking for nobody but myself
as an ethnic no comment
i'm drinking why when i said when i said we i meant the the royal we when i said we i mean
we the french we that's it for the voicemails team so i guess we're done for the for the week it's
time to bring this ship in for a final crash into the iceberg we do patreon.com slash the
procrastinators podcast people please give us money specifically five dollars would be great
so you get the bonus episodes and there's 19 of them now 19 20 to be out soon it's gonna be a fun
time you guys go to APS adventures dot site bail jpeg got updated ha ha oh that's right
check out the update guys it's so good to be able to say and and then like what are you gonna do
like are you gonna remove all my blood and make me white like i can fucking do it all the fucking
god damn day what if i were to make the argument that you're not hispanic enough because you're only
half um that's oh god i'm going to jail
what does bina mean i was gonna say you can only say half the words monster you can only say the
first syllables you're not allowed to say the rest of it that's right if you say the colloquial
bina bina that's fine isn't that isn't that worse though like if you go up to like a half black
person and say you're not black enough that's like really a faux paul like even worse than i mean
people make that argument though which is bizarre to me yeah i don't know if i have a friend who's
half black and half white is it worse for me to uh to say the fucking racial slurs or is it worse
for me to say that they can't because they're not black enough it well that's your right so everything's
just wrong for you that's no that's wrong i'm that comes back that comes back to the question i'm a good
boy everything that i do is right do you value like do you value like independent freedom or do you
value like making sure no one's offended at everyone's i value being able to make the funny noises come
out of my mouth yeah well like luckily i don't but you know there's a there's a it's a fair criticism
to say that that is literally maybe influenced by the fact that you have never been the target of
this ethnic discrimination well i literally been ethnic like bullied for being in different ethnicity
than the white kids in my neighborhood i can fucking say all the racial slurs i want yeah i i i get i
get that that's kind of that's kind of a like a bullshit argument i think because like everyone
has been fucking like bullied and ridiculed in their life for something so like to say that you
can't say like you then you shouldn't be able to say stupid or fat or fucking anything i mean that's
true i was like with how actually this was hilarious and remember and the fucking like i can't help my
my height i wish i could i wish i could exercise to grow longer bones but i can't you know there's
a guy there's a guy right now uh i think he's in denmark who's uh fighting legally to be able to
legally change his age from i think 69 to 49 this is actually happening in real life and i'm like
why can't i change my height let me just change that you know legally i want to do it i feel like
i'm six foot eight let's do it people it's it's it's equally silly i mean i i don't think there's
anything i mean yeah you can say like i believe that i'm six eight it's not true but you can say
you believe it i think making it legal is what am i talking about i don't give a fuck about this
issue what am i saying it's fine you know what i like ending this podcast goodbye everybody well
listen to wait listen to this comment this is hilarious this is hilarious uh donald trump the
other day uh well okay whatever stormy daniels remember the porn star trump fucked uh was uh
was was roasting uh donald trump for uh having a a mushroom dick is what was going on and uh
trump and people people out in the world were saying like um you know that's actually body
shaming you probably shouldn't do that and she apologized trump comes back calls her horse face
and then she immediately starts calling a mushroom dick again um that's just saying that was hilarious
okay uh follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators uh for all your social media updates for all your
all right punditry that you need it used to just be called liberal now it's uh not all right
listen up we'll see you next week people another episode have a good time we've done it we'll see
you soon people do you think with anyone i'm supposed to be working right now i'm supposed to
be working right now but i'm not working i'm doing nothing
my dick i'm jerking myself i'm sucking i am an asshole i am a stupid i've got a deadline
don't want to do it