I'm sorry darling, I'm listening to the PCP right now, it's so interesting.
Surprise motherfucker, it's me, Best guy ever back from The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
You thought you were rid of me, but no, I am eternal and I'm come back and I'm bronzed
and I'm beautiful like none of you will ever be or even understand.
With me is Ben Saint.
Everyone put away the good weed.
We only smoke shit weed when this guy is around.
I'm here, I'm ready to turn in, I'm ready to phone it in for another PC paycheck.
Oh yeah.
Digibro is there as well.
The motherfucking mission, get that quack.
Agreed.
And also Mage.
Yes, I am alive as I usually am.
Well fantastic.
Well here we are today, post Christmas.
How was your Christmas guys?
I had a good one.
You know what?
I guess I wish Christmas shit.
Damn.
Alright, I got a bunch of chocolate that I'm not going to eat.
I'm donating it to the poor, a.k.a. my fucking housemates.
Yeah, that sounds like the poor.
I'm curious, because you guys are brothers, did you have any kind of, did you guys meet
at all in this Christmas?
No, Nate betrayed us.
Betrayed his family lineage and went to Hawaii instead.
For the first time ever, it was not all of us together for Christmas.
Which made me a little sad.
It was the first time ever.
Yeah, it made all of us sad.
Made all of us real sad.
Aw man.
You might say it ruined Christmas.
Not my words, not my words.
It's good to know that my absence is felt deeply and woundingly by those who know of
me and respect me greatly.
Yeah, it was too bad, but you know, also fuck you guys, so I had a good time out there.
My gift, basically, to me on Christmas was to be in a very sunny, beautiful place.
It was like, I want a white Christmas, white sand, that is.
Yeah, also not so many blacks.
Not so many blacks, let's just, you know, tropical cocaine.
Although a lot more browns, you know, because there's a lot more Asians, a lot more Filipinos
and a lot of, of course, native Hawaiians as well.
Whoa, I'm clogging my ears.
I love none of this.
Hey, by the way, have you guys seen?
This tickles me pink, or perhaps other colors, because if you invert the word brown, it kind
of looks like N-word backwards.
That's all that.
This is, this is making the rounds, and I feel like there's something important going
on here.
Hold on, I'm trying to picture it in my head, but I can't.
Yeah, take your time.
Literally N-word, like that, like literally the phrase N-word, you gotta picture that.
Oh, if you switch the B to a D, because it's reversed.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Wait, hold on.
It just works.
Link in the description.
This is important to show notes, kind of.
Oh, RD.
Oh my God.
Well, this changes everything.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Anyway, it was great, it was nice, so it was with Michelle's family, and we had a wonderful
time.
Yeah, that's it.
Went swimming a lot, did beachy things.
I am, in fact, quite bronzed.
In fact, we have to link in the show notes to instagram.com slash bestestguyever.
We can see my bronze.
Hey, remember when you called us up on Christmas, and we all started chanting a vote for Trump,
build that wall?
I do.
Oh, what a magical time.
I can't even imagine being at the fucking beach, because I was up in the frozen north
of Rochester, where there was snow, and there actually isn't snow here in Boston this year,
so far.
Yeah, I had a good time, because I was also with May at her family, and they have like,
you know how they say like, divorced parents have two Christmases?
She's got that on top of that her mom's family has like three Christmases themselves, because
it's like every different grandparent gathers like a huge, it's a gigantic Italian Catholic
family, so there's like a thousand people, and like a million events.
So it was like a jam-packed like Christmas schedule, you know, it wasn't just like one
day event, it was like a week long Christmas Trist.
It was like a Hanukkah for the Christians.
That sounds exhausting, to be honest.
Well when you've got a dab pen and a lot of alcohol, and you know, you're getting lots
of free stuff from people you've literally never even seen before in your life, it's
pretty exciting.
I feel like I want one of those, you know, muscly arm like handshake picks, the meme
with the text over both arms, one that's like, I don't know, epic memers, and then vapors,
and then in the middle is loving the dab, you know, something along those lines.
There's potential there, there's potential.
Hey, so hey remember, you know what this podcast has been missing a lot of recently?
It's been missing that, it was the sauce in the good old days, was me vaping into the
microphone.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Did you get a new vape?
Did Santa bring you a shiny new vape for Christmas?
Actually our sister just gave me a jewel, so I'm jewelin'.
Oh boy.
Oh okay.
Oh yeah.
Wait, what's the jewel again?
That's just like a little baby one, right?
It's just a small little like vape thing that looks like a USB.
God, you're so degenerate out there.
Yeah, yeah.
She had a spare one, and she was like, I don't use this one anymore, you can have it.
Guys, currently right now in New York, they are in the process of simultaneously legalizing
marijuana and trying to ban like jewels and vapes.
I assume by ban, they mean like in the same way cigarettes are banned like from like public
areas, like as opposed to completely illegal.
No, they're just trying to take jewels off the market because they think that too many
like kids are the ones who like it's basically marketed to kids the way they see it, I guess.
Well, they are popular with the youth, which is bad.
I don't think kids should be should be vape and nicotine.
That's weird.
But I mean, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't see commercials.
I mean, they don't sell them to kids.
So it's like, what are they fucking?
Is it the same way that kids get alcohol?
Like kids are going to get their hands on the thing, you know, yeah, yeah.
Like if they it like, yeah, illegally, I mean, they're you can just get somebody to buy it
for you, assumably.
I mean, if anyone under 18 is smoking jewels, then obviously that's not a fault of it's
not.
I don't think it's cause for them to be banned unless you were going to ban everything else
that kids could also do that.
They didn't ban cigarettes because Joe Camel was a kid friendly advertisement.
They just said you can't run those ads anymore.
It's not cool.
Although, I guess a lot of the limitations on sales were probably put in for those reasons.
Well, I mean, aside from it being like, you know, what is it now 18 or older, I guess
for cigarettes, I like all the warnings that they were like forced to put on the cartons
and like, I don't know, does that shit even work?
Does that have an effect?
I don't know.
Uh, they got them, they got, they got warnings on, on jewel stuff, they got warnings on vape
stuff.
Yeah.
So like, you know, the system seems to be working properly.
Well, fair enough.
Uh, I don't know.
Is vaping even particularly bad for you other than that you get addicted to nicotine?
No.
It's kind of undiscovered thus far, right?
Isn't the science still kind of out on that?
I mean, sure.
I mean, yeah, in the sense that any scientific theory is always, you know, subject to future
evidence, you know, in order to, to shift consensus.
I guess so.
But, uh, you know, all, like none of the, none of the chemicals in it are like known
carcinogens.
It, it, okay.
People argue with me about this, but like I've done reading on it and I'm pretty convinced
that, that nothing in it is actually like dangerous, like to, to even like a, a, a,
to even like, like a, a, a percent of the degree that like the stuff in cigarette, like the
stuff in cigarettes we know causes you cancer, it just, it just does.
Oh, that's fair.
But like people would also make that same argument about sugar, which I would argue is poisoning
a large amount of the human population.
Well, you know what?
I think that I would probably be okay if we said that, if vaping is, is, is poison on
the same level as like sugar.
I, I guess that's fair.
I guess that's fair.
Yeah.
Uh, but hey, Mage, well, how was your Christmas?
What'd you get up to?
Uh, it was, it was fine.
As always, I went to visit my family and was gone for the week or so and been on my phone.
Uh, was, was Santa kind to you?
Did he, did he lean your, did he lovingly take your, your head in his arms and caress
you on that Christmas morning as is little Lithuanian custom.
Uh, sorry.
Yo, wait.
He's a very, he's a very my, he's a very intimate man in Lithuanian lore, as I understand
it.
No, uh, I said, um, you guys have Krampus over there?
No.
I tell you, we got Krampus over here and it fucking sucks, man.
You have, you have Chris, you have Chris Kindle.
No.
Oh, you know, some, some, some places have the Chris Kindle.
Yeah.
It's like Western Europe, I'm Eastern Europe, but uh, yeah, like Santa's not, not, not super
generous with poor, to poor people.
Oh no.
Uh, but I didn't, I didn't get a thing, uh, sort of two things, I guess.
Um, yeah.
Lay it on us.
Yeah.
I got, I got a new handbag that I didn't, I didn't request specifically, but it's kind
of a funny story.
Is it that Gucci?
Is it that Louis?
No.
No, it's not, it's not anything.
Expensive.
It looks nice though.
So, I mean, I don't care for brands, so it doesn't bother me, but uh, uh, it's red though.
And that's a little bit of a, for me, but it's kind of my fault.
How bold.
Red though.
Yeah.
I don't usually wear red, so it's a little weird, but, but like I said, it's kind of
my fault because during the summer, I'm, uh, me and my mom went for some shopping because
she insisted I got new shoes, but my old shoes are fine, but she insisted I got new shoes.
I hate shoes shopping.
I absolutely hate shoe shopping, but yeah, we went, yeah, we went shoe shopping and the
only pair that we could find that like fit me properly and I wasn't like batter anything.
There were a pair of red shoes and they were kind of nice, I guess.
And I sort of offhandedly said, you know, like they're nice, but I don't have anything
reds to go with it because it would kind of be weird to like be dressed in all black
and just suddenly red shoes, it just draws attention too much.
You look like Jade from Homestuck.
I was going to say the Wicked Witch of the West, but same person.
So your mom's interpretation was buy you something red so that you have something to go with
the shoes.
I kind of, I kind of treat the disease, treat the disease, not the symptoms.
I did my own grave though because I did, I did sort of offhandedly said like maybe my
handbag was red or something to match with it.
So because I was thinking like in terms of character design, how to like weigh out the
redness.
So you're something.
You dug your own grave.
Yeah.
I dug my own grave.
It's not that I dislike it or anything.
I prefer my purple one though.
It has more pockets.
More pockets is better.
I have a section for all the little things that I need.
Like there's a section for my keys, there's a section for like handkerchiefs, there's
a section for everything.
Well, this one doesn't have enough sections.
I mean, as a big fan of the Mage cast, I wonder if maybe these will be worn by red mage.
Remember?
Remember there was red mage.
Red and blue mage.
Remember them?
Yeah.
Well, she wasn't red.
Well, she red.
Did I make her red?
I made her red.
Yeah, there was a red one and a blue one.
Oh yeah, okay.
Don't nitpick on the goddamn like fucking, oh no, it's only slightly off on the hexadecimal
value.
Oh no, yeah.
This is actually the red one was magenta and the blue one was technically mauve.
So, you know, don't at me.
I made them past.
Why don't we mauve on from this boring ass topic, shall we?
How about your ass is grass and I'm going to mauve it?
What was that?
What else did you get?
What was your second gift though, Mage?
Then the amount went past post Christmas shopping and she got me a coat because she
insisted my old coat wasn't looking nice and I'm like, but it's fine.
And she was like, Mage, it's 10 years old and I'm like, but it's fine, but she got
me one and it's sort of purplish kind of.
So I'm happy.
Well, this is why you have to you have to ask for something specific for Christmas.
I didn't.
I didn't like, I couldn't add like all the things I want is out of my family's budget.
So I was like, I'd be fine with a new sweater, honestly, because I could use a new sweater.
But yeah, I mean, my mom usually asks me if she has nothing in mind, but if she has her
heart set on something, she'll do it.
So there was really no point if she didn't ask me.
Oh, I want for Christmas is freedom from this damn patriarchy.
That's where I'm at.
I don't want to sound like an ingrate.
I love my mom and she, she did this because she cares for me and I appreciate it.
Of course.
No, she wants me to be warm and she wants me to be comfortable.
A fair bit of bitching about our loved ones is always warranted and that's within Christmas
parameters.
Yeah.
Of course.
Those motherfuckers only spent $400 on me and I wanted something for 600.
You know what?
I think I talked about this the last time I was on, but like you make a deal where like
you talk to them about like, you know, I want that I like, I remember once I wanted a camera
and I'm like, this thing's like 500 bucks, guys, just pay as much as you want.
I'll pay the rest and then we'll just, we'll just work this out.
Uh, they got, they got me the, they, they got me the, they got me the jewel plated tooth
teeth grills that I asked for, but they got them for me in sterling silver when I asked
for gold.
What the fuck?
God damn.
Uh, that reminds me of like, now my teeth won't match my brass knuckles.
Uh, it reminds me like, oh, those posts I see every, every holiday season of when kids
like, like, oh, they got me the wrong colored iPhone or like the wrong colored car and I'm
just like cringing like my iPhone won't match my car.
It's such an expensive gift and they're still ungrateful and it's not like they're sort
of like sighing about it.
They're like mad about it.
Like, yeah.
You know what?
I'm siding with the rich kids on this one because you know what?
Those parents are rich enough to just buy whatever the fuck their kids want, but they're not
fucking listening when the kid tells them they want the black one, not the white one.
Maybe they should open up their fucking brain a little bit.
I would be, I would be kind of annoyed if like my parents were insisting on spending
that much money, but we're going to get it wrong in some way.
Yeah.
Right.
There was so much on the line here for you to get right.
Yeah.
How could you fuck this up?
You just spent $900 on the wrong thing.
Like what the fuck were you thinking?
Thanks for ruining Christmas, mom.
Sometimes the color difference is like a very large sum of money of a difference and sometimes
they just don't have just enough for that.
That can be true.
I guess so.
I mean, if there's extenuating circumstances, it's different, but if they just straight up
picked the wrong color, it's like you fumbled at the, at the last yard.
If it was just as easy for them to pick the pink one versus the purple one or whatever
and they picked the wrong one, then what that shows is a lack of giving a shit about the
details of this transaction when they may have meant a lot to the person.
It's like on the Kiki Ghibli cast.
You know, you can side with the old lady, yeah, the old lady, you know, oh, she works
so hard to make this herring and, herring and pumpkin pie or whatever.
But you know.
The girl didn't want it in the first place.
The girl told her she doesn't like that pie.
So why did she make it?
Why did she go to all that trouble if she just listened?
She should have known to just get her, to just get her a fucking gift card to Dunkin'
Donuts instead.
Yeah.
That's a far more thoughtful.
She always says she won.
Yeah, but there has to be a bitch about it.
It's a grandma.
But she is a bitch about it.
Yeah.
That's rude.
Oh.
Well, she wasn't.
Okay.
Well, she wasn't a bitch to the grandma.
She was a bitch to some random delivery girl.
That's also rude.
Don't be a bitch to delivery people.
And she wasn't.
She's just like, oh, I hate this pie.
Yes.
She was rude.
She wasn't that bad.
You know what?
She was rude.
You opened my eyes.
Did you open my eyes to that scene?
I saw.
It's because I'm spoiled as shit so I can relate better to the spoiled characters than
the, like, two days.
Band is not allowed.
Only wholesome things.
Being spoiled is wholesome.
It's wholesome.
Kind of.
Being spoiled is wholesome.
Speaking of being spoiled, I was so gratified to log in to teespring.com and see that it
immediately, upon posting the I'm Just Being Cool shirt, a flood, hundreds of thousands,
literally every single one of our viewers bought that shirt.
Yeah.
And yeah.
What shirt?
It's not true, by the way.
This is a fantasy.
This is a Christmas fantasy.
Oh, sorry.
I was confused.
But you can make it real by going to teespring.com, whatever slash whatever, link in the show
notes below or also the main description.
It was the I'm Just Being Cool shirt, which I mean, in last episode I said in the episode
I'm going to make the I'm Just Being Cool shirt and I did.
Now I understand.
And your fantasy.
Okay, I get it.
I love to speed.
I do like it.
A bunch of what I asked for from, yeah, that nice, that tasteful comic sans.
Yeah, that's the good stuff.
Just showing how serious you are about being cool in the, in the, a bunch of the stuff
I asked for for Christmas, because I couldn't think of a lot for my parents to get for me.
And you know, they'll dig, oh, what do we get you?
We got it.
We got to get you stuff.
Mom, just give me cash.
Just send me a check.
No, no.
So I had him get me a bunch of endless war merch from the, from the RFC cake store.
I see.
Yeah.
You had them buy your own merch.
Assumably you get kickback from that too, right?
Yeah.
You're getting them coming and going.
Who made it go?
Well, Munchie gets half.
Munchie gets half.
That's right.
You know, that was also my Christmas present to Munchie was getting my parents to buy a
bunch of RFC cakes.
Cleverly fucking played.
Yeah.
That's not bad.
I mean, you know, I got to, I got, this way I got to splurge.
I got to splurge on the big one.
Next year I'm going to tell everyone to just subscribe to my Patreon for Christmas and hope
most of them forget to unsubscribe before the next month.
You know, it's not a bad idea.
Oh my God.
That reminds me.
I don't know if I should say a name or anything, but I checked my email the other day and someone
whose name I have seen and like comments and I think he's in my discord and stuff, someone
just sent me like a hundred bucks as a Christmas present.
Sweet.
Why not say their name?
Thanks, David Toth.
Appreciate it.
There you go.
Security number 81723, you know, IP address.
I have geo hacked your location to send you a card and I'm going to say it out loud now.
That's sweet.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess on Christmas.
Christmas inclusion.
Did you guys?
Christmas is bad.
No.
Christmas is good because I love to go to the movies on Christmas.
And it's a great time.
What movie did you see on Christmas?
I saw Into the Spider-Verse.
I saw On Christmas Day.
Please don't spoil.
I really want to see it.
Okay.
I won't spoil it.
I'll just tell you it was very good.
I liked it a lot.
Everyone's telling me it's really great and that I should see it.
I haven't seen a single negative opinion about it.
We got to do a little X-Nate on that.
What is it?
Acke, Blay, Erector K.
You know, let's get some more white boys in there.
Other than that though.
Who was it in the PCP?
We were talking about how the movie flopped abroad.
Did it?
Because in China.
Oh, the only white people in China or something, right?
They didn't show miles in any of their advertisements.
Oh, that's fucked up.
Yeah.
The ads in Asia made it seem like Peter was the main character.
Thank you.
Because they didn't think a black person would sell and lo and behold, it didn't.
Well, I guess I aptly played.
Unfortunately, it wasn't enough, I guess.
That's too bad.
Because it's really good.
You should watch it in China and enjoy it.
I highly recommend it.
Go watch it in China.
Yeah, it's China.
I'm not saying it's not great or good.
But, you know, superhero movie.
Spider-Man.
Oh, man.
No, I hear you.
I won't go into detail.
Because I don't want to spoil it for an agency.
I'm not even burnt out on superhero movies because I don't watch them.
I haven't even seen Infinity War.
The last superhero movie I watched was Iron Man 2.
This movie?
Okay.
So, I'll just say it in general.
Or maybe the first Captain America.
Into the Spider-Verse was really good.
But Infinity War was way more interesting conceptually.
Although, this spider shit was the best looking movie I've ever fucking seen.
So, it's got that going for it.
But everything about Thanos was just way more interesting.
I'll remember more.
Whereas, I mean, this was about another hero becoming a hero.
Doing hero things.
I've seen it.
I get it.
So, when I call this one of the best things I've ever seen,
like some people were saying, absolutely not.
Infinity War kind of was.
So, that wins on that front.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Everyone should see it anyway though because it just looks so fucking good.
And Kingpin.
Oh, my God.
Kingpin's design is so sick.
He's just the biggest man I've ever seen with his little head.
It's so sick.
I know it's not original.
But man, should you like Spider-Gwen's design a whole lot?
It is sublime.
I was gonna ask if Spider-Gwen was in there because it seems like he was.
I saw her in a trailer.
She's so cute.
I like the colors.
Spider-Gwen's so cool.
Yeah.
Colors are great.
I mean, I love her costume and all.
I don't know if I like that her like buzzed undercut hair thing.
It's just not really the hairstyle.
I'm into that.
Me and Michelle saw it at the same time.
And a slight point on that was just that we both commented,
as we finished and were walking out,
they sure did that whole Gwen's better than all the boys thing.
So that was cool, I guess.
Was she the Lola Bunny of the film?
Well, only slightly.
She wasn't sexualized or anything to that degree.
But whatever.
That was only at the beginning.
Anyway, everyone should go see it.
I guess that's just the short version.
So you heard it here, everyone.
Into the Spider-Verse is a feminist propaganda nightmare
that you should all avoid.
It's intersectional, too.
Absolutely.
I don't even know what that means.
I mean, Miles was great.
Miles ruled.
I don't know.
I kind of liked the atmosphere and the music around Miles more than him as a character.
Because, like, I don't know.
He was just a kid who, like, he did it, and he did the battle, and he won.
He did it.
So, you know, cool and all.
But I've seen it a lot.
Yeah, good job.
Good on you.
All right.
All right, look at all these fucking Marvel movies.
Jesus Christ.
I haven't seen one of these things in like three years.
He's like, you know, Harry Potter was the boy who lived.
Miles is the boy who did it.
The boy who did it.
He really done did it.
Also, you know what?
Why the fuck does Miles get extra spider powers that Spider-Man doesn't have?
What the hell is that about?
Why can he fucking turn invisible and Spider-Man can't?
Why?
He got bit by the same fucking spider.
What the hell is the deal?
Turn invisible?
Yeah.
And he has weird electroshock powers.
Why?
It's not necessarily the same spider, right?
I was going to say, was it literally the same spider?
It looked the same.
I guess I just assumed.
Okay, if it's not, then fair enough.
You don't fucking know.
All right.
Okay, enough.
You didn't get your master's degree in spider-onomy like I did.
That's fair.
What's that made?
It's something probably no one has ever heard, or at least not many people.
It's not a movie.
It's a TV series that I sort of binge-watched the first season of.
It's called Gently's Holistic Detective Agency.
I've heard of it.
I've never seen it.
I read the books, actually.
Oh, okay.
I've been wanting to watch that show because it was directed by Max Landis.
Oh, shit.
What a good movie.
He's a YouTuber.
Isn't he getting me-tued now?
Did he get me-tued?
I mean, he's been getting me-tued his whole career, I think, or something.
Only a little bit, and it didn't stick, or something like that.
I don't know.
Maybe there's more to it.
No, he's just done a bunch of videos about how he just gets accused of really random shit.
There's lots of rumors and weird stuff about him because he talked shit about the girl from Star Wars,
and now everybody thinks he's an anti-feminist or something.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
Oh, Mage.
I don't know if you know this, but Dirk Gently's Holistic Detective Agency is a series of books
by the guy-
Who made the-
by Douglas Adams.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, the guy who did-which is why I read them.
I didn't know there was a show.
Well, there's two seasons.
I think they cancelled after the two seasons.
As my friend-because I heard this from my friend, and my friend said,
Oh, they cancelled it because they wanted to invest into a different series,
despite the fact that Dirk Gently was doing well, but not well enough,
and they thought the other series would do better, but it kind of really flopped, so.
Yeah.
Which is a shame.
I really liked it.
It was so weird, but like, I like that kind of weird, and it's-
I couldn't-I couldn't figure it out.
Up until the very end, I couldn't figure everything out,
but like, it all came together and it's very wacky, and I like it.
So I-so I loved Hitchhiker's Guide as a kid.
To be honest, I don't remember that much about Dirk Gently.
The one thing I think-I think I remember about Dirk Gently,
or it might have been from like, his final book of like, unfinished stories
that might have included some Dirk Gently, like, sample chapters, was like,
a guy, like, a character in one of the stories is a literal rain god,
but he doesn't know that he's a rain god.
Cool.
And so it's always raining wherever he goes, and he hates-and he hates the rain.
It's like, cause it-it follows him everywhere, and he doesn't know why,
and he's really depressed about it.
Um, yeah.
That's unfortunate.
I think-I think Jesse-I think Jesse designed a pony OC at one point,
that we were gonna-we were maybe talking about doing like, an ask blog,
and it was like-
I sort of remember, I think.
He was like a black pony with like, a rain cloud cutie mark,
and his whole thing was the rain.
And I remember, I was-I drew him for Jesse,
and I was thinking about this guy from the Dirk Gently story, this-this, uh,
this rain dude.
I don't remember-man, was that-was that OC's name?
Oh!
It really liked him.
Uh, Rainy Parade?
Was that-
Yeah, Rainy Parade. Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, I remember that now.
Yeah.
Um, do not steal.
We're gonna monetize that one yet.
Uh, we gotta put that on a PCP shirt.
Yeah, I really like the actor for Dirk Gently.
He just-he-he's really good at the whole being whimsical and innocent sort of guy,
and then when he cries, he just looks so-so convincingly sad,
like, innocently sad, and just so feel bad for him.
He's a really good actor already.
Was-was-is that a new series, or how old is it?
It's only from, like, a year and a half ago, two years ago.
What?
This is why Max Landis hasn't been doing YouTube videos,
is because he went to work on that show.
Oh.
No shit.
Yeah.
Which I'm wondering, what did the fuck-
Well, blow me down.
Now that the show's canceled.
Uh, getting me-tuned, you know.
Yeah.
It's just, uh, that's his full-time job.
Hey guys, just got back from a hard day of getting me-tuned.
It's time for a little Q&A.
I think we either ended, like, at the beginning of this year,
or at the ending of last year, so we'll turn this.
Uh, when are we all gonna get me-tuned?
When is my turn?
Um...
When do-when do me, too, get what is coming to me?
You know?
I want my turn.
Are you saying that, like, the dad joke way?
That, like, uh, uh, I want some of that me-too.
Like, how about me-too, get over here,
big, hip, waitress at my local pub?
Uh, no.
No, okay.
It's not what I meant, I just meant when is each of us
going to have our sexual misconduct come to light?
I mean, reveal just the sick people that we are.
Taken for granted that there is misconduct.
It's only a question of when.
Look, none of us-I can't believe none of us are deplatformed yet.
None of us have, like, a riot following us around at all times.
Like, where's our-
We're probably doing something wrong.
What about me?
Like...
Did she-
Yeah?
Never mind.
Not to give-not to give anyone ideas.
We're probably doing something wrong.
Yeah.
Uh, if-that we don't have that.
We're gonna have to go-
Well, yeah, I-I was just gonna say,
not to give anyone ideas, but I sincerely believe
you just need to create, like, a shitstorm,
whether-where-where there-like,
people just assume where there's smoke, there's fire.
So if a lot of people just mass-report,
like, you could absolutely organize a campaign
to just report the PCP.
For, like, the joke I made before,
uh, about, like, you know, not liking Black Spider-Man
is more than enough to get this whole fucking show shut down.
If people just choose to make an issue of it.
But can we not, though?
Can we just-
But-but-but all-mage, all they have to do
is be like, well, these guys have said
the N-word on this podcast before.
Oh, my God.
Can you believe?
There's a pattern emerging here.
There's a pattern of behavior.
I know.
And your guys are giving me anxiety
every time you make an off-color joke.
So if we get kicked off the platform,
then our fucking Patreon will spike.
Well, that's true, for a time.
We need this drama.
No publicity is bad publicity.
I've been saying it for years.
Yeah.
That we need to start beef.
We need to start beef.
Look, everybody-
I've had an ostrich and hide my head.
Everybody likes to-
I just don't actually do that, but-
Look, everybody likes having the comfort
of not having controversy surrounding you.
However, you've got to leave your comfort zone
if you want to accomplish anything in this world.
You know?
You get what you want just by sitting around waiting.
I still don't believe the drama is necessarily
the way to do that, but-
Drama is something to talk about.
And you've got to have people talking about you
for whatever one reason or another.
That's true.
I can steal my art.
Thank you very much.
I don't want more drama.
Fair enough.
Hey, here's an interesting concept.
You know what?
Okay, I'll say it because I already brought it up,
but it's just a small thing.
I put in my Goblin Slayer video that came out
a week ago or whatever.
I put what I thought was official art
because I recognized this picture of guts.
I was talking about guts.
And then, as it turned out,
it was actually not official art.
What it was was-
Like, a guy messages me,
and I've added this to the description, so it's fixed.
But what he said was,
hey, that's actually my art.
You please credit me.
And I was like, oh, sorry.
I thought it was official.
Turns out what it was was-
it looks like a tracing.
It's not a tracing.
It is a, according to this guy,
it's a hand-drawn recreation
from not traced,
but recreated elsewhere
in a slightly different art style.
You know what I'm talking about?
Another episode where we were talking about this,
we were looking at some fan art.
That's right.
It was not traced,
but it was basically perfect duplication.
No, we weren't sure if it was traced or not
because it looked identical,
except it was drawn on different medium,
but the guy could have easily printed it off
and traced it.
They said that it wasn't traced.
And I believe that,
yeah, well, maybe you didn't literally-
maybe you did just copy it by eye,
but still you just copied it.
I had my doubts, but yeah.
That's what this guy said.
I got no problem with this guy.
It's perfectly fine if he wants to do that and shit.
It just makes the crediting process interesting.
So he recreated an official piece.
It's volume one cover of Berserk.
It's like a picture of guts.
I have a little bit less of a problem with that.
I don't know where my morals lay.
Don't ask me, don't add me.
Well, did he reinterpret it?
Did he reinterpret it?
No, it was pretty much a one-for-one recreation.
It wasn't a different art style.
I don't understand defensiveness over your work
if it's like that.
And any of these people,
I mean, we've talked about this before,
I will link for credit for people
just so that they'll shut the fuck up,
but I don't think you deserve it
if you're just making fan content.
Like, it's not your fucking content.
No, I don't know.
Don't own the IP.
No, I think you deserve it first.
I think you deserve it first.
My fan art that I draw,
I'm a bit more lenient when people use it
because it is fan art for a different thing that exists
so long as they don't claim it that they drew it.
But look at this.
I'm posting this in the gross disgusting audio links.
Look at this picture of Zelda that somebody fucking did.
She never did this pose in the game.
This is a new thing that somebody made
based on a character.
Yeah.
How could you say this person doesn't deserve?
Fan work deserves its own credit.
If I throw this picture randomly into a video,
it would be no different from me throwing
gameplay footage of the game randomly into the video.
And I don't credit Nintendo in the description.
Like, you know, I don't see...
I don't understand how these people themselves
don't understand the paradox that's going on there.
They don't look at that and say like,
I don't own Zelda, you know.
Guys, my opinion might change this or shift
or it depends on the context or whatever.
But like, the way I see it, like,
if the image is a big part of your video,
you should probably credit it.
But if it's just like there for a few seconds,
and you know, you're using a lot of images
and it's not like a centerpiece or anything...
Like, it could have been any other picture of Zelda.
Yeah.
I do think if you're going to base your whole video around it,
then yeah, you're doing something very tasteless.
You definitely deserve to be called out on it, you know.
But like, yeah, if it's just like something that's just there
and like you said, could have been any picture,
then it's like, again, I will give credit if they ask
just because, you know, whatever.
I'll support the artists, you know.
Because I know that's what they really want.
I know that's what's...
What is upsetting to them is they're like,
you know, I drew this piece
not that many people have seen it,
but you've put it in this video that has tens of thousands of views.
This is probably the most that anyone's going to see it
and they don't even know that it's me who made it.
And I understand the frustration
because like I have a...
One of my fans made an AMV
with the anime Kase-san and Morning Glory
set to one of my songs.
And that AMV somehow, some way,
has like 150,000 views,
which is way more than any of my music,
probably combined,
and they didn't link to me at all in the description.
That's pretty fucked up, guys.
Yeah, that's bad.
I'm looking at it and I'm like,
well, I'm not mad.
I'm just like, this is such a huge missed opportunity for me.
They probably didn't even know better.
No, they didn't, because she was literally like 14.
Yeah, there you go.
But you know, I was just kind of like,
how could you not credit me when you know it?
It would be such a huge help to me.
I mean, in that case,
if it's an AMV,
the music is like core to this.
It's foundational, absolutely.
Yeah.
I was trying to say though,
if an artist does come up and be like,
hey, could you at least credit me?
I think it's just, you know,
common matters to just credit them if you,
you know, you did actually use their art.
You know what I've noticed though?
This has long confounded me.
I like PewDiePie, he's a good guy.
I've noticed he will credit things in videos.
Now we're getting deep platforms.
Yeah, it's over, we're fighting the king now.
It's just that I notice, I have a different stance.
I didn't credit tons of the stuff
that goes into his videos.
I have noticed this.
And like, yes, it's legal.
I feel like it's just like kind of rude.
Like, it's fair to be like,
just throw some fucking links in the description, dog.
I mean, he must have an editor, right?
Yeah, he's got a team of editors.
He's got a team of editors to put his videos together.
Yeah, I mean, he's got at least two editors,
and I think like they, on rotation,
they just like are given an edit,
like a video of like two edit and stuff.
They should be part of their job, I would think.
I just think, you know,
like, okay, to share PewDiePie
is like a really big, popular guy,
and like just getting your image in there
is good and all that.
But still though, like,
people have gotten mad at me,
and I think it's warranted when I use their stuff
and just don't credit them if I'm using it for something.
And so now I've adopted a policy where I do.
And when I just see like the big boys
not doing that, I just think the same,
you know, credit system should apply.
Maybe they just need a poke,
but it's kind of hard to poke someone that big
and out of reach, you know what I mean?
Like, I mean, because I'm getting notifications
from people saying like, hey, would you mind
crediting me, but I never see this stuff
like being added or updated,
I mean, I haven't done an exhaustive fucking search or anything.
Like to his discretion, is it just that,
I wonder if there's a layer of protection
that people accept that like this guy's so big
and probably gets so many pings
he can't possibly address any of them
and like worry about
crediting people.
I don't know.
I think probably people are asking him for credit
and just not getting a response.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
But like, is it an appropriate defense
that he just gets so many messages
that it's not his responsibility?
I mean, he's committing so many crimes
he can't possibly correct them all.
I mean, it's a small thing.
Yeah, I think in that case, it literally is just like,
I mean, it just goes to show you
how little it really matters to anybody
that like it matters to that artist.
It's not going to help them pay your fucking bills.
Yeah, I mean, it's just like not something
that most people are worried about
or something that's going to affect the creator
if they don't credit you.
It's not like they're going to get a fucking huge backlash
unless they've like really
egregiously stolen something
and like that is the basis of their content
that they're putting.
I guess a moral thing,
I just want people
who helped me make a video
producing something,
they just deserve something in return.
That's all I guess.
And I guess just being in a video,
sure, that's nice in itself.
And if you're PewDiePie getting your thing in there,
that's great, but I don't know.
I'd like to see more.
I'd like to see a little bit more here.
You fucking get PewDiePie
to throw your fucking
Gumball Rule 34
shit up on screen
for two seconds and you're made
for thousands, you're set for life.
I mean, I guess what I would do
The man just shits gold.
The man's like Tyrion Lannister.
I guess what I would do is what everybody else does
and tweets out the video
and say like, I'm in this video
because it's a PewDiePie video and gets millions of views.
So that's pretty cool.
You get a little boost.
You get a nice boost from that.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Alright, whatever. It's fine. Not a big deal.
God, I wish I could be in a PewDiePie video.
But you know what? My friends
Monkey's been in there, you know?
That's true.
My boy, well for bad reasons
but my boy AFY
had his dancing
lolly-titty
dancing crab meme video
showcased in a fucking PewDiePie video.
Dancing lolly-titty
Yeah, that's what it is.
Bizarre story.
I don't think this doesn't
know what to make of it. I guess it's just a weird coincidence
or something.
So there's this
fucking lefty
ass
blue pill
who is my hero
is
a YouTuber
called Jack St
or Lacking St.
Do you just like him because of the name?
That's why I clicked on him
originally.
So he
made a video
maybe a couple months ago
called The Story of Ascentar
a neo-liberal horror story
and in it he relates
a news story
or he goes into the story of how
an internet company
their equipment was faulty
and it started creating a
loud wine, a high-pitched wine
and people in the neighborhood
started tweeting about it and stuff
and people didn't
take it seriously
thought they were complaining
but it went on for weeks and weeks
and it created a high-stress environment
and ultimately there was
a violent incident
someone pulled out a gun
and tried to shoot out the transformer
that was producing the noise
and someone thought he was being shot at
and pulled out a gun and shot back
and someone got killed
so anyway
that's a crazy story
and meanwhile
the rich fat cats running the internet provider
just sit back and do nothing
they barely even apologize for the incident
shame on them
so a new video comes out by this guy
and he explains that in fact
this was a work of fiction
that he had written
but delivered sort of as fact
there were some hints in it that it was not true
but I had not picked up on them
I had thought this was a real thing that happened
kind of like real information might be
and he
compared it to like
Orson Welles war of the worlds
type of like
like a documentary style
like a work of fiction delivered
like a documentary as though it were true events
whatever the point is
that in that video
he goes to google
it should have been pretty clear
to anyone who wanted to know more
that this was not a real event because there's no
google search results about it
and he goes on youtube and google search
is like a sentar incident
and to demonstrate
that there are no results however
one of the top
results from that search
is a thumbnail of like one of
mumkey's videos
like one of the last videos that he posted
and I was like I pause the video and I was like wait is that
why would that come up
in that search?
a sento I mean it's possible
it's recommended for this guy who's making the video
that he's just a fan and that happens to be
maybe
but is it the search results though right?
yeah
you wouldn't think that does that
no
yeah I don't know
that was weird
oh thanks for the show notes
showing visually demonstrating how
brown is n-word backwards
yeah no problem well that's to remind me to get the image
to link it
to breaking
right
but that's a good video
the ascentar video by Jackson
is pretty good
kind of like it less now that I know it's not real
yeah it made me question everything
I mean is there something
slightly unethical about doing that
telling a story and presenting it as fact
I mean I feel a little
I feel a little bit embarrassed
trying to be like oh you know I was lied to
because like I feel a little bit like
I don't want to point out that the emperor has no clothes
because I'll be revealed
as the rube that I am that I was tricked
but I don't know
I'm a pretty canny viewer of media
I went into this video
feeling like I had no reason
not to assume
that the facts being related to me were true
mm-hmm
uh
kind of reminds me of the whole marble hornet thing
though you kind of knew it was not true
but they were very dedicated
well
I mean I wasn't I wasn't around
when marble hornets was new
but I assume that no one was really watching
marble hornets until
it became clear that it was
a slender man thing
and by that point it probably should have been clear that no
this is not real
that's right
that's my assumption I don't even know what fucking marble hornets is
they've explained to me like ten times I still don't understand
it's the slender man
video
I don't know
what's happening
what's a video on youtube
what is youtube
we need to start in round zero
where is web 2.0
um
I get all my youtube videos through
a youtube amalgamation website
where I never need to touch youtube
they're just fed directly into my brain
how about a web 4.0 now
how about a web 2.0
I need a fucking jewel
I need a fucking jewel after all this
I need to calm my nerves
I only watch the
current top video on all of reddit
it is the only content
I will consume
you know what would be a fascinating video
an analysis of the top content
on I guess all of reddit
like overtime if such a thing can be tracked
or I guess just like on youtube
or wherever just like whatever was
the most mass appeal
thing it was that history of dance video
fuck you know what I think I've seen some of this
actually and I think about it
I was thinking
I don't remember what
prompted me to think about this
but I was thinking about like
youtube subscriber inflation
and like
you know how in like
2005 or whatever
having tens of thousands
of subscribers was like you know
was a big deal and you could be like
the front page of youtube for that
I was wondering like
if you could take like who were
the top subscribe channels in those days
and like take that number
divide it into the subscribers of
the top subscribe channel today
would you arrive at like a rough
sort of you know
inflation rate or a rough sort of
conversion rate for like
subscribers in 2018
how many subscribers would that be
roughly equivalent to in you know
2005 or whatever
it's gotta be a huge difference I mean
I don't know what that'd be but
I remember I've seen I've seen some
infographics of like you know the top
the top youtube channel and like how
they've all you know
grown how the numbers have gone up
and up and up and they've all like you know
zigged and zagged and surpassed
each other and back again like h
no not h3h3 less
equals 3 equals 3 was was top
for a while
I've never even heard of that
never heard of equals 3
I remember him
oh god
nostalgia
I did not I did not I did not watch him
back in the day I didn't know who he was until
relatively
I remember when people were just
the
squirrel aids was funny apparently I never
found it funny but it was just
a joke
I did see some of his
you know music videos
I didn't know who they were
your mom
yeah I had I had seen
stalking your mom years and years ago
never knowing it had anything to do with
this ray william johnson I think the
general was titled doing your mom but then
they made it you know they remade it
they remade it I think
I mean in ray william
justin I think the end
or something like they had
a bit of a theme song that it was called
doing your mom but I'm not sure if it was by
them or anything so is that guy just not
around anymore what happened
what happened to ray william johnson
because I remember people complaining about him all the time
he was the guy who actually think I
that same guy that that jack saint guy
did a video about
ray william johnson I heard
wasn't he the dude who just like
just talk about what was popular on youtube
yeah he talked about memes
he would he would just like
show videos that were
popular on youtube and say
yeah that's true that was it
that was really funny
he was like he was like America's funniest
home videos but for youtube
I see that there is a channel
called simply ray that has
9.8 million subscribers that he
uploaded to one day ago
and oh there was a 5 month
gap here but I guess he uploads
things here I don't know
I think he sort of passed on his
equals 3 channel to someone
and that didn't do so
yeah he quit it he quit it
yeah it was
it was jack saint that's why
I was thinking about ray william johnson
he did a video about that and he still
uploads but like you know
or no wait maybe it was
maybe it was a quintin reviews maybe it was a fallen
titan quintin you know what that's what it was
it was a quintin reviews oh is that that one
that's the bearded dude right
yes that guy's pretty good
I only watched like one or two of his videos
but they were pretty good you know he's alright
I've watched a bunch of his stuff
it's pretty it's pretty deice
I've been seeing a lot of like negative
sentiments I was gonna say
I've been seeing a lot of people saying that he
he's an asshole for various reasons lately
I'm not sure why well it seems like
I don't trust what anybody says
people say I'm an asshole constantly and
they're probably right but I don't believe it anyway
I don't know I don't know what
it is but something I feel like he's made
people mad I I don't know how can't
I haven't watched any of his stuff but I
feel that he's a trump
hate man that people think is a little bit
over the top is anyone not a trump
hate man
orange man bad
that was a
yeah that was a god that was another there was
jack saint did a video on the NPC
meme and
talking about orange man bad
that's how I know about
orange man bad
I've never heard that before
I'm surprised
it's kind of a meme by now
it's pretty funny
I saw a good counter post I saw a tweet or something
there's a picture of someone posted the NPC
orange man bad and then someone
posted a pet posted back a
pepe with the NPC face
saying orange man good so you see
the knife cuts both ways
oh no
now that we've unleashed the monster
he'll slaughter us all both sides
well
all man bad
oh no
hey guys to sort of
change the subject and maybe
wrap it back to the holiday season
it's not new years yet
it is going to be when people are
you know after new years when people are
going to listen to it but what are your
new year
plans any resolutions
whatever
I don't really do resolutions
you know
I mean
I'm getting
I have lately been getting back to
drawing the vapors finally
so I guess my resolution is to
continue that
I'm sure you'll appreciate this
Nate but my new years resolution
for next year is to
just kick ass all year
excellent
normally
I have a more concrete goal
last year it was to make $100,000
I don't think I did accomplish that
but
ordinarily I would just make it the
same goal again shoot for the moon
Digi even if you miss you still
land among the stars
I think that what I really
want next year is not so much about
how much money I make but how much
progress I make
if you're just fixated
on like multiplying how much
money you make in a linear way
there's no sense of build up
an investment for like being able
to make more in the future
it's not so much about
that I want in the next year to get
to a point where I'm making $100,000
as it is to have set
everything up that I can
you know move
even faster going forward
this is too vague to be good radio
talk but you know what I'm talking about
I get the general idea
my general commitment
goal whatever
it's really just to buckle down
I was really hoping
to get this ghost in the shell video
I've been working on out
before the end of the year that did not happen
so just I want to get all my commitments
out of the way this year
which essentially is
there's a little bit of rad con stuff left
I mean this honestly that's too small
of a goal for the whole year because it's going to be done fairly quickly
but I have really cleared
the field and I'm not going to be taking
on any more burdens and like
I've got my first we Agua out now that I'm back on them
I'm really trying to stick to a schedule
of at least every other week or so
and using that opposite week
to like get other stuff done and I know
I say it a lot but frankly the finances are looking
good and I creep ever closer
towards this being
released from the day job thing so
we'll see
when are you coming to fucking Boston
we were talking about
I got to check the dates I think we were planning
people there's a little inside baseball we were planning
to get together sometime
in the next couple of weeks I think around the 13th
if I remember correctly
and do some planning for
PCP stuff and communal projects
and do some workshop
I need there's a lot that needs to be
discussed about the possibilities
and requirements
that we will have to meet
in order to be able to fucking
make PCPHQ real
yep and those are substantial
and we need a solid plan so yeah
yeah I'm down
I've been listening to what you've been saying in our
private things and yeah
that's right audience we're out here
making plans we're out here moving
moving money around
moving and shaking
shaking and bacon and taking
lots of big
hits on the bong
for inspiration
if only
Ben I might need you to
didn't you say that you knew a guy who could get me weed
don't
don't say it
don't say it on the podcast
don't let them know
the Christians will know
well now they know
let it go let it go
it's cold outside
nobody else smokes but weed
is literally legal now here in Boston
or in Massachusetts
you can literally just go buy it and it's too fucking expensive
I thought
it's literally
420 an ounce
straight up
they did it
$420 an ounce
oh I thought you meant $4.20
I was like that's not so bad
that reminds me I think recently in Canada
or at least Vancouver
legalized weed and stuff
and when I visited Canada
it smelled
everywhere
that's fucking great
I was told that they don't have
any sort of official
places they sell
so they're still buying it from illegal places
despite it being legalized
so it's kind of a weird situation
to be in I guess
did I ever tell you
when I was in Amsterdam
you smoke weed
I don't really smoke weed
in Amsterdam you smoke weed that is what you do
so I was like
I guess I should smoke some weed
so I got some weed
they have bars
you can just go into a bar
and buy a joint at the bar
nice
so I got one and I went outside
and I was walking around smoking it
and people were like you can't smoke that outside
and I was like what the fuck man
when I went to Japan
I turned 21 but the drink age there
is 20 so I could drink before
in Japan, in Tokyo at least
you can just drink on the street
you can just walk wherever you want
in America you can't fucking do that
in Europe you can
buy a beer and walk home
drinking your beer
you can't do it anywhere in America
nowhere in America can you do that as far as I know
the best they got
is some restaurants
they might have
an outdoor
that's pretty common
what the fuck man
but yeah
Digi
I live with a bunch of guys that smoke weed
one guy
the guy
I won't say his name
it doesn't matter
I asked him where he got his
and he was like oh my friends sell it
but they're not looking to deal
with buyers or anything so that was a bust
but then a new guy moved in
and I asked him if he had a hookup
and he said yeah so I was like
yeah new guy
I'm not sure what the prices are out on the streets
currently but it's gotta be cheaper than
the fucking official shit
I am shocked by that price
he didn't quote me
he wouldn't quote me like a specific price
but I'm sure it's less than what you're paying
is it bureaucracy and government overhead
that made the price so high
it's just straight taxes
it's just like a 20% fucking tax
because that's what tax included
it's 4.29
so like when we did Radcom 3
Kickstarter we went to 9001
for the meme
and that was a
complete joke
but we were doing it
we reached it
so that's all cool
what degree they went up to
versus what it would have been
if not just for the meme
apparently in all the places that they've
legalized weed
the prices always start off really high
and then they quickly go down
over the course of the first year or two
because of the fact that
it just shouldn't cost that much
and more people can afford it
so the places that are selling it right now
are all very high end
fancy places
they're all former medical dispensaries
we need a place for gutter sluts
such as ourselves
the proletariat needs weed
more than the rich do
yeah they got their zany anyway
exactly
give them their fucking
I smell benes
wait
what is the connection with
I'm very familiar with that meme
and I love it and quote it all the time
but what's the connection here
aren't benes benedral
which is a fucking meme
that I've
I thought the meme was I smell benes
the guy says
I finally got all these benes
maybe it was like
it's gotta be benzos
whatever that's short for
that's an actual drug
does anyone take benedral to get high
they might
isn't that what benzos are as well
you know it could be
and I wouldn't know
we need to know people
hey what do you say we do the voicemails
now how about
I mean we've only been going for an hour
yeah I mean I don't know
that's true
I'm happy to take you guys
have anything else you want to talk about that's fine with me
I mean like the voicemails
depending on what we're asked
or presented
you could also ask up to an hour who knows
yeah that's true
yeah okay let's do a voicemail
here's our first one
apparently it's a slang term for the drug
benzadrine
benzos
I guess it's all the same shit
I'm looking at something right now
do you guys know that endless war
has territory control now
I've heard about this haven't looked into it but I'm aware
have you seen the new map
no I haven't
I'm just gonna post a link to the map
which is dynamic and which now like updates itself
to show like what
it's so I'm looking at it right now
and I just can't I'm just it's
it's crack fucking did it
we the team the team did it
pulled together looks exactly like it always
looked in my head
this is
cause this is where Nate posted
this is where we put the links
so that the people who are editing
can easily just use them
once they're it's time to edit
it makes it real easy for everybody
okay fine
the fucking the juvie's control
cratersville what the hell is that about
no no that's green is neutral
okay okay well this looks dope
I see the killers are dominating that's excellent
it
it moves pretty fast
the killers are I think the killers
have a stronger strategic position
cop kill town but
to help that we're gonna
we're gonna put in a ferry we're gonna add a ferry
from cratersville to
assault flat speech resort
and as well
just break it down for me real quick
what is the general way the territory
is passed because I've been wondering
how does one control an area
you know once you could explain it better
because I was working on slimoids while he
and right and
and and be and we were
not do we don't think
mostly Munchie and lateralist
were most I think mostly lateralist
honestly we're working on territory control
so I don't know the ins and outs of it but I believe
mm-hmm the gist of it
is that you just have to go to
a place and just basically be
there you just have to spend time in a zone
okay and while you're there
you will be uncapturing it from the other
team making it neutral and then you will
start capturing I see for your only other
question what are the benefits of having
captured a zone I
believe right now the only benefit
is that they pass passively
generate slime for your kingpin
okay cool cool yeah
so they're forgetting your team ahead
I want to play slime rancher now
slime rancher is sick
I wish so bad that
slime rancher had multiple same
same so much I got I got my boyfriend
slime rancher for Christmas among other games
and I just I really wish we could play together
yeah
I would man
and what if we had like a team what if the three
of us what if I'm just beginning I'm just
going to third wheel really hard
and do like a team deathmatch
a slime rancher that would just be
great all right
let's do it here we go to voicemails
here it is people
you've been waiting for it and here it is the first
voicemail of the call
of the recording from Doopity
Schmoople of the year that's
the first one of the year doopity
you've done it here you go
begin
by the time you hear this
it will have been a week since the
conquering of the I am game server
the men have been killed
the women
also killed
the children have played
to the juvie's rose mine
and tom oliver admitting we have
passion, dedication
and excitement they can only dream of
with this overwhelming victory
we
the people of new los angeles city
aka neil no walkie
ask this question
to anyone who dares
pull a stunt like this again
are you ready
for the eternal violence
the forever conflict
the infinite bloodshed
the groundless struggle
I ask you
are you ready
for the endless war
I don't know if you guys are aware
but there has been official war
declared the only reason
the only reason that the
endless war people were able to
even have a foothold in the I am game
servers because tom foolishly
declared war while his co-leader
was completely away on vacation
and I had
no ability to help
in any way to
raise the armaments
and the defenses
and to retaliate
I'm just saying the next battle
might not go so smoothly
I think that the
endless war crowd
was pretty well
mentally primed for this
I think maybe we'd been
without even intending to
kind of indoctrinating them
for this eventuality
for the waging of war
in a discord server
they might have had some practice
that kind of thing
might be like the whole conceit
that's just a theory
a game theory
there's a
my boys
in the pod de escort
have also on record gone on
and declared war on all other
servers and
you know what
I gotta throw this in
there was something produced and while we're on the
subject of the war going on between all the
servers
I gotta throw this in
I'll play the next call and we'll get back to that
I just want doopity
I wish you had mentioned
if they had
rescued paradox crocs from the mud
knights in the mud puddle
there's still no
update on that
I forgot about the mud puddle
the mud versus slime war rages on
as I understand it
presumably
I can't see that ending
that's like an Israel Palestine
there's no understanding
you know what
everybody listen up
this is the pod de declaration
of war
let's play it for all to hear
made by AFY
and center point
go
there once were captains named Gibb and Nate
who were kings of the pirates
they had riches and autism
beyond your wildish
hey hey hey
I will let you finish
this discord is the best
PCP discord there is
we're so good in fact that we're ready to
start the war by dropping this
bomb of a diss track on all y'all
so go ahead Toya
use some dank rhymes all over
their butts
get em
where he goes we find out about a war on the
discord there's no doubt the patrons
whose eyes are on the mercy will be king
of the discord we're gonna be kings
yoyo yoyo yoyo
yoyo yoyo
oh boy they really
they really went for it
they're made of money that's everybody involved
they're gonna say don't lie
yoyo yoyo
the mud puddle, the toll, the poppin j
rfck meet and do thing
digwood swim that lolly thing
purple streamin
gay suck chicken way yoyo
yoyo yoyo
oh boy
it's the best
discord server on
grand war
yoyo yoyo
get up to pody
yeah guys
that's the whole crew there
I didn't even know there was a pody cast discord
but of course there is
I think I heard about it
and they just fucking
afy and centerpoint got everybody on the server
together and they all fucking recorded it
everyone knows now
about the pody
she just got real
my discord is not participating in the war
that's some bullshit mage
it's not participating in the war
Switzerland ass over there
I'm not telling anyone to do anything
sincerely
but I'm just saying
you ever heard of a little country called Poland
mmhmm
you ever heard of a little thing called world war 2
I also heard about switzerland
never heard of it
little thing called blitzkrieg
little thing called crystal knocked
just giving you some ideas ladies and gentlemen
no war is allowed
we win
it's over we already won this one
it's gonna be so tragic
what will definitely happen to you
alright I'm mourning you already
I made you just said
you're sitting it out god damn
you can't have it both ways you can't be like
oh if I was fighting guys I would
I said I like how you said you already won
even though I'm not even playing
that's sad
what the hell am I supposed to do
you took yourself out of it
the only winning move is not to play
unless you're poland in world war 2
like you are
poland
the fact of the matter is that it doesn't matter
whether or not mage wants
to be participating in the war
when a war comes to your doorstep
when the fuck are you gonna do
we're gonna delete your damn discord mage
we're taking it out
maybe we need to ratify
maybe we need to ratify like our own Geneva convention
or something
for the rules
the rules of ethical warfare
the Geneva convention was only established after world war 2
I think though
we'll just have to wait for mage to become a casualty
and then we can look back on it
with
better understanding
yeah but you got lots of natural resources
that I'm gonna need to mine
I'm gonna need to take those
we're seizing those
you're like um
she's rich with minerals
you're like rabbinaster in
fucking
final fantasy 12 that's right between the two gigantic
empires
that's not a good place to be
it's like that
oh god you're seeing
legend of the galactic empire
what's that neutral planet
right in between the two
mage how would one even get
to your discord anyways
is it patron only
it's currently you could get
in through patron it's sort of like
semi open
I can kick you I don't care
okay
listen alright
the
the hellfire hamlet all the
all the waystoids in the hellfire hamlet
all the image gravers and all the music boys
and all the code sorcerers
listen I'm not we need
we need to be prepared we need
we need to be prepared for war okay
we need a policy
we need a policy of mutually assured destruction
alright
that's true
any admins
on any of these servers please
contact us at
adios cord
we have such riches
to offer you such lucrative deals
can be made with just those
three little numbers on the back of
Ben's credit card
please send them at once
alright let's move on next fucking call
how do you even declare the winner anyway
when everyone else's discord
is deleted and they're all
when everyone else is dead
that's how
I guess it's just
when you say that you won
like that guy in that last call
who just said that
he's won
on no basis whatsoever
it's like
so can we stop
it's like saying you're cool
you just say it enough and it becomes true
I'm gonna say
I'm not gonna be in the war
that's why you gotta click below
click the link below to the pcpt spring
and by the I'm just being
cool as shit
that's the real winner here
behind all it's all to funnel people
to the tea spring
the entire war was orchestrated so people
want to be cool
all the runoff from the discord war
like as the bodies just
drop as the body count rises
all the casual teas
are just spat out the sewer drain
into the tea spring
I've got it we don't have white flags
in this war if you're waving a white flag
it doesn't matter you're a participant as much as everyone else
the only way to remove yourself from the discord
is to buy in I'm just being
cool t-shirt that's how you become
exempt and that's the only way
you can escape that's the way
all I know is the
the discord
the endless war discord
better be ready for when I march an army
of content machines onto their doorstep
I'm already firing machine gun shots
at my own subscribers right now with my
27 consecutive uploads
of rant videos today
so you know if you want
death at your doorstep of a nonstop
deluge of bullshit
rants then you better
get your fucking assholes right
we've had death on our doorstep
from day one didgy
okay next call
but seriously though I'm not participating
so please don't harass me
mage I don't even know where to find your discord
I have no idea how I could wage war against you
just don't make yourself such a juicy target
please don't pick on me bullies please
yeah why you gotta have all these rich veins
of oar
why you gotta have all this natural
petroleum
alright moving on
moving on our call
we've got a call from cloud strife
ladies and gentlemen he's got an important message for us
oh the man himself
as I understood that's what he said so I believe him
let's see what he's got
okay so I recently got final fantasy
seven and this is obviously
the best one but then I realized all
of the games have like a different
character in the story and shit
and I'm like what the fuck
I want cloud strife
tell me all of the games with cloud
strife in it and I will play all of them
because he is the coolest character
yeah cool
yeah go
man go do it get it boy
you gotta play air guys
oh there it is oh yeah that's the way
that's the right way to do it that's the one
that's the definitive cloud did he really
do you think that was him playing just there
was he just recording that that's awesome
we've been getting a lot of people just like thrown in music
I think I don't know I don't know if it's the same guy
I presume there's a guy who
will just fucking jam out a tune on the piano
in voicemail
there actually was a guy in the voicemail who just played
a little bit of the Ava
opening but it was just that
so it was kind of boring so I just didn't include it
but shout out to that guy
guys this is a problem the voicemails
are better than the actual show on this episode
they're way better
fuck
cancel the fucking show
we'll figure something out
we'll fix it in post
we'll make ourselves funnier in post
okay we've got a this is an important call
this is from munchie wears tiny
rats
let's get into it go
oh it's me munchie
wears tiny rats
and I'm going to go to art school
10 minutes later
oh I failed
arts
it's like looking into the future
it's like looking in the mirror
does anybody know if munchie's actually been accepted
into that school yet
oh he hasn't applied yet
because he asked me for a letter of recommendation
which I'm happily supplying
oh he asked me for one too and I completely forgot about that
that was like six months ago
oh I've got mine ready actually
what sort of authority do you have
to recommend I'm just curious
well I'm rich and famous
I mean you know not bad
munchie said
you get like previous employer usually you get
like previous employer
I mean I have literally paid
munchie a lot
well not a lot because he gives me a lot of
shit for free but like you know he is
responsible for like the iconography
of my channel
many times over over the years
I mean when he asked me
he just said like essentially
you know I'm quote unquote his boss
in the PCB not really we all know that but like
effectively it sort of works that way
so he just thought that like I'd be a guy who could
detail his strengths
you know as like a member of our little group here
so you know
plus I've commissioned him a bunch and he's always been good so
you know
speaking of commissions my commissions are always open
oh yeah always
yeah that's cool
until I stayed in other ways
munchie got uh munchie announced
he announced open commissions recently
and apparently he got flooded
yeah and actually uh
he told me what he was charging though
and I was like that's pretty low
balls I think that's kind of the reason that I
that I had been saying that like it was surprising
to me that he wanted to go
to school is that he can work so
fucking fast that like yeah he can do
commissions that are like 15 bucks and he'll
jam you out of picture in like half an hour that you're
completely satisfied with you know
so 15 bucks for half an hour of work is
extremely fucking good you know that's true
I mean
I don't think commissions is that
like he's got higher aspirates unless
you're like really famous and
personally I just hate doing commissions
I think munchie is less anti
I hate drawing commissions
munchie seems to like doing it
I used to not like doing commissions
but in recent times
I've been quite enjoying doing commissions
well that's cool hit me
I basically only do them when someone offers
to pay me what I would consider
to be more than what they're worth
by a significant like
the only price
that I think is worth me doing a commission
is something that I am totally not
comfortable asking for
yeah I'll tell you right now
that yesterday I filmed
all of these 27 rants
that I've been spamming everybody's sub box with today
those are
$15 a month tier on
Patreon I have like 50
people on that tier only like half of them actually
gave a rant
that they wanted to give
and of those you know I did it all
in a day so like whatever
that's not bad pay for one fucking day
right exactly so
you know in that sense
those were commissioned videos basically
and as long as the people are satisfied with them
which I have not gotten any response from anybody
who actually commissioned them
so far but
you know if that continues to work out
I would consider myself to be someone
with commissions open
in that case
you know I don't know
when else I'd have a chance to say it I guess I could say it anytime
but I might as well say it now
so yeah I have a lot of people
that have qualified for
like reward art from my Patreon
that have never contacted me about it
I have sent out some
I did send out emails at some point
to a lot of people being like hey
you qualified for reward art
and you know a lot of people didn't get back to me
they probably weren't pledging for reward
they just wanted to support me which is cool
but I don't know if you're listening to this
and maybe you are a patron
and you do want one
like if I haven't already emailed you
about it send me a message or something
because like you know I want
you know I want people to get
what they're paying for
yeah that's fair
at some point I feel like I kind of lost track of that
like I haven't had anyone be like
hey you didn't give me the thing
wait no there was one guy
but then I gave him the things it was alright
yeah
make band work
yes please
okay let's go to our next fucking one here
this is from
rance armstrong
go
hello guys and mage
well if she's on I just wanted to tell you
that I'm a huge fan of the pcp
the pokemon castration podcast
you
the main meta
I've got a really important message for all of you
well mainly the
mails are on you
please please
for the love of god don't start
vaping
it's not just bad for your health
it's not a big problem
vaping is gonna turn you gay
you don't believe me
just look at the prime example
band saint
so if you remember
patient zero
cause it's gonna turn you gay
but I'm already gay
yeah I was gonna say
oh yeah
it's too late for me but the rest of you
can all learn from this man's wisdom
I've learned
it's Vincent
is he gay
is your ya boi
ya g boi
ooh should I spoil
should I spoil the comic
no he's not gay
you know I haven't seen his rating system
canonically I don't remember seeing
his rating system
did it apply to men
did that do men as well
he does
yeah he does rate men
possibly on different criteria though of course
yeah it's not
spelled out or anything
at least yeah the things
it doesn't say
what it is that he's looking at
but in my head I knew what it was
that he was evaluating about them
he evaluates them on different criteria
um
bye then
sorry
looking at men
is one of the gayest things you can do
and he did it a lot in that one chapter
a bunch several men
remember how that guy hit on him
when he was sitting on the trash can
he didn't hit on him
that guy wasn't hitting on him
that guy was trolling him hard
I know I know I'm just fucking fun
although that man bun
is very metrosexual
I'll say
I saw a lot of man buns in Hawaii
incidentally
I've been thinking about going for the man bun
it's
my hair is long enough
it's almost long enough
I think man buns really
you gotta be ripped to wear a man bun
or like if you're fat that's one thing I guess
you gotta be a big boy to pull off a man bun
in my humble opinion
yeah it's not a look forever
it's definitely not a look for me
so that's not what I just said
total fabrication
just like jack saint tricking me
with the story of a centaur
the neoliberal horror story
indeed
kinsheen slayer
whatever go
yo pcp how likely do y'all think it is
that Sora is gonna be the next smash DLC
to be announced
since it'll be the absolute best time on january 25th
alongside the release of kingdom march 3
also this question is
the entire pcp
not just the guys on this episode
and I'm not gonna make any promises
but if you had a realistic warp sword
what would it be and how would someone mail it to you
axes and shit aren't allowed
I can't make those strong enough out of pvc
if you're in the rfck
discord you can just ping or dm me
my nickname is sword man
is he offering to make us
swords to fight with
in a pcp video
he's just putting it out there
but he makes them
I got a p.o. box dog check any we a go episode
there's a link to that p.o. box
I want a zvi hander
I don't have a p.o. box
that'd be cool
shit I got that video of you swinging that zvi hander
around at the fair I never uploaded it
didn't you tweet it
no I never did
I meant to
I'm just saying I know this is too much
but the only sword thing that's cool
is the absolutely retarded
keyblade that's made of
two swords crossed over
like a fucking keyblade
it looks embarrassing and terrible
no wait it's two keyblade
it's two keyblades
crossed over a sword to make
the keyblade yeah okay there you go
um
first of all is kingdom hearts coming
to the switch I think it is
let me double check right
fucking now if it is then I literally would not
even be surprised if uh if Sora came
to the game kingdom hearts 3
switch let's find out right now
I think it is
um not
not considering switch version until after
something something well that was in 2017
it it won't
if it's not on the switch then no
if it's coming to the switch then maybe
definitely okay I'm seeing things like in October
saying that it maybe
could maybe could square enix really
wants it to I'm not seeing any
confirmation but looks like
people are talking oh my god dude
square enix and Nintendo
together again you know what that could
mean Mario RPG 2
it's time it's time
Mario RPG 2 none of this paper Mario
shit hey you know okay I think
Sora is a super likely and frankly
a great choice for for Smash Bros
in my humble opinion but
but I wonder if Disney
is gonna be an obstacle in that
cause Disney owned Sora
and I wonder
if that's gonna complicate things
Square Enix doesn't own him? I don't think so
I'm pretty sure Disney owned Sora
damn
I don't know I'm just saying that could be an issue
I hope it happens though I think he's a
really think he's a fantastic choice
he would be really cool he'd be really cool
oh they could have like a Twilight Town stage or something
he'd be the one like human character
that I would consider
well I guess I'd play Rosalina
so never mind take back everything
yeah and I guess he would be
sort of an anime sword boy
but he's got tons of magic there's a lot of cool stuff
you could do with Sora he's got tons of fucking abilities
it's okay
it's okay that he's an anime sword boy
I would overlook that character flaw
thank god
okay my LARP sword
well I have
you know
what do I like in swords I like
flamborges but
I'm not I'm not married to flamborges
I like S stock actually I really like S stocks
I don't know if that would even work
as a LARP sword
I'm imagining like a sword with like a black blade
and like a black hilt and like white trim
and like maybe the pommel has my like
saint heart logo on it
those are both like a like a rapier adjacent
right
an S stock is basically a rapier
flamborges is like
it's a broad sword but it has like the wavy blade
only reason I know
is because of soul caliber
well yeah
I know from like dark souls and various like
final fancies and shit where you get these weapons
and fuck I'm imagining I'm imagining
a black blade black
everything white trim with the saint heart
like the saint heart pommel
yeah
other than that
I'm not picky I don't know wink
give me a make a keyblade that has sunglasses
as the keychain it'll be my key
blade haha got them
don't make a key
swordman don't lower yourself
to making key blades
what'd you say mage
chakrams are just round swords
yeah chakrams suck
they're just frizz
what even are they like the first time I ever saw them
was fucking axel and kingdom hearts and shit
like what the hell do those even do
how would those be functional in combat
if you use them with magic
and make them float
and you put them on fire
amaranth and final fantasy 9 uses them right
I don't know
I'm pretty sure
I imagine that the appeal is that
you could just kind of spin around with them
and cut shit
don't you just throw them like frizzbees
I really thought you just threw them like frizzbees
the first time I saw them was in kingdoms
of amalur
freckling or something
and like the way they battled with the chakrams
looked really cool and I was just like
and you make them float and you put them on fire
and they just whoosh and wham
and it's just so cool I love it
that's when you have like a drone
carrying your fucking chakram around
I guess it could do more damage
other than that
I mean in real life I really doubt that they are
very useful or whatever
I guess they're just projectile weapons you just fucking throw them
and they come back like a boomerang
like a very deadly boomerang
I don't think I want that to come back though
like how are you going to catch that thing
magic
alright let's keep going we got two more questions here
or calls or whatever
here's one from doodlebee
play
go
hello PCP
what I want to know is
why does everybody on this podcast
speak with the same
damn tone
even people in these
voicemails they all speak with the same tone
I'm doing it now
and
thank you
have you placed on everybody
thank you and
good day
it's just called having a good radio voice
it's like you naturally
it's sort of like
you try to project your voice
more than normal because
like you're
you want it to just come through as clearly and understandably
as possible I mean like normally
people like
if we were say acting
your top priority isn't necessarily
how clearly you speak
it's how emotively you speak
but if everyone is just emphasizing clarity
everyone's emphasizing
being understood as perfectly as possible
then we're all going to be speaking very clearly
in the same tone
that's true
I guess just the energy here
people kind of just sync up
when they're talking you kind of go to
somebody's fucking vibe or something
yeah I don't know some combination of that shit
you know that's the thing
like you start to talk like the people
you spend time around
your combination of like the six people
that you spend the most time with
I think our voicemails have undergone a really cool evolution
because early on it was very much like
in the exact style of like
biggest problem or dick show voicemails
where it's just kind of people calling in with like a rage
you know and everybody just has this intense
like I'm randin' about whatever
but now it's like way more like a
creative experiment
that's my favorite thing
it's great
I'm so glad we ditched the questions
me too
the voicemails are amazing
they're better than the show
and speaking of voicemails
we've got one final
strong contender
bringing up the rear it's a voicemail
from the legendary dumbass mcdumbfuck
let's see what he's got for us
alright bring us home boy let's go
alright so I'm a content man
I'm a content boy I want to make stuff
and I make stuff
the problem is I haven't made anything
so uh
can you tell me the first thing
I should make
should I draw a thing
should I music a thing
should I go to things
and literally any option is okay
other than it doesn't matter what option I pick
so fuck you
he really lived up to his name with this question
he really did
I'm thinking you make me a sword
I'm thinking like a black blade
like a black pommel like white trim
with a saint heart on the pommel
just express yourself to the exact parameters
Ben specifies
just take a shit and take a picture of it
and uh put it in a frame
everyone's gotta start somewhere
just fucking you know what you wanted
if you're listening just fucking do a let's play dude
just don't be a pussy
just do a let's play
just record yourself talking about something
and put it on me
Ben and I started just with
we saw other people doing it
so we literally just did what seemed popular
can't emphasize enough
how much you don't have to like each other
in fact it might even be better if you hate each other
could be
Ben and I just were like hey we talk about this thing
let's just record it
and then we did so just fucking do that
or I mean this guy is not even married
to like you two or anything
he literally just wants to know what to do
just tell him what you would want
over the last year or two
people in the hellfire hamlet
a bunch of like podcasts
a bunch of people make podcasts together now
it's cool
here's what I most want
so just create this
because it is what I want
is just make
like YouTube videos
that are just
entertaining enough
that I don't get completely bored having it
on in the background
but are not so entertaining that I have to actually watch them
because I don't have a TV
in my house so I just have to
use a constant stream of like Anthony
Fantano videos as my version
of television and I need more
yeah that makes sense
I do the same thing
I'm gonna go on a
slightly different tack
I'm gonna say make
the greatest YouTube videos
of all time and change the landscape
forever more
by everyone
comes to you because you're just so much better
than everyone else
and do that so that I have
you know hire goals to aspire to
yeah I want
I want and like and be so good
and then also choose to
not use Patreon anymore
and you know literally yourself
inspire a new medium
whatever you do do it on a peer to peer
network yeah make like
just make the greatest video ever
and get super popular on a peer to peer
network on a Patreon alternative
so we can all follow you yeah that's what I want
that's what I'd recommend
um
why don't you
why don't you draw your favorite character
just from your favorite video game
hahahaha
I mean it's not a bad thing to do
that's definitely something dumbass
McDumbfuck would do alright
with that thanks for calling in everybody
speak pipe there's a link
in the description go give us more voicemails we love
them get creative
happy new year everybody
I hereby solemnly swear to make the PCP better next year
yeah
that's my PCP resolution
that's a good one we're doing it
we're on the upswing and then we make our second
of the year podcast monsters
first podcast recorded
in the new year
wasn't there something we were discussing
doing as a topic
that like enough of us had
oh jesus christ superstar
once you wanted to do a podcast about that
are we like done recording by the way
no okay let's wrap it up
no we'll talk about that
maybe we can do that as a bonus
I'm just saying everybody there's a chance we will do a video
of some sort about jesus christ superstar so if you haven't seen it
go watch it before then
that's your warning good plan
so anyway
patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
we're on that godforsaken platform still
hopefully we'll find something better soon
and can stop giving those evil people our money
that'd be nice
you know we're
active procrastinators on twitter
go subscribe for updates
that'll be good
and I guess that's about it
thanks for being here
see you next time
and I hope to do it again
for another year
how nice
yes agreed
see y'all next year
see you in the next year people
woo
bye
actually it'll already be 2019 and this comes out
that's true
hello
right now
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick
I'm jerking
myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a
stupid
I've got a deadline
don't want to do it
you