Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever and today we've got
Hippo Gibbontake. What's up?
Hey, the the punk plushie Kickstarter is still ongoing. If you don't know what that is, here's a link to it.
It's it's a thing. We talked about it last episode if you in case you didn't watch.
If you want to pump plush, go invest now.
We've got Tom Oliver.
Hey, a pump plush is good and I backed it and you should back it too. Go check out the link that was just thrown down.
It'd go well within a zoomie plush if one existed, which it does not currently.
Oh, it's happening. Oh, it's it's in the works. It will happen. I swear it on my soul.
Ben Saint is here.
Are any of us really here though?
When you think it right down to it. I have a philosophy degree.
Impressive and here's Digi bro. Just your friendly neighborhood boomer with a beer gut.
Tearing through your mom's cunt.
Happy as always to have that happening.
Welcome everybody. Time for another week of the podcast. Hope you've been doing well.
Let's just jump into it. Well, who's got things? I got things. Yeah, let's just jump into it and
hope someone else has something. All right, I've got something. Sun and moon, Pokemon. Okay, no.
Sun and moon. Let's talk about. Wait, I meant shield and sword. Let's talk about Zamazenta and Zashian and how they're bad.
I think they're kind of cool personally. I think Zamaz. I think Zashian's. You dog lover.
I do love dog. Just me. Zashian is okay. I don't think Zashian is worse than like the musketeers.
Which one's the sword? Which one's the sword and which one's the shield? Zashian. Zashian. Okay, that's the sword.
I think Sif is okay. I think shield dog is fucking hideous.
Agreed. He is very silly and it doesn't make a lot of, like, what if I attack him from behind?
But worst of all is just the fact that they look too much alike and have the same fucking color palette.
Are they literally the same Pokemon? Is that a thing? Like, but one got a sword and one got
shield in the different versions of the games? I heard that was a thing. Maybe. Maybe the third
Pokemon, like there's always a third. It's going to be a third. Dog gun. No, no, no. Not a gun.
It'll be like the guy's master. Like, it's a human Pokemon who rears these two dogs.
It's just like a dude with like a leash. He puts them on a leash.
Pokemon trainer Artorias challenges you back. Here's the thing about the third Pokemon. So,
Zashian and Zamazenta, they are cyan and magenta. So the third one will be yellow.
Do they actually look that way though? Do the colors match that? Not at all.
Yeah, well, they kind of do because Zashian is more blue and Zamazenta is more red pinkish.
That makes some sense out of the color palette to me, but like, they could not have made it look
shittier. Like, they could have definitely. Oh, it sucks. Oh, it sucks for sure. I heard one other
theory, which was that. I mean, the logos for Sword and Shield are basically cyan and magenta or
pretty close. That is true. Why didn't they make games of Pokemon cyan and Pokemon magenta, you
know? Maybe that's a little too gay for people. I don't think they're allowed. Well, they got away
from colors at some point. I don't think they're ever going back. I think, yeah, probably not.
I did hear one theory that like, that it's this, I was just watching a bunch of speculation shit.
I think it was that guy, what's his name? Noggin and Lockestein. Lockestein and Noggin,
that guy, she's all right. Well, it's two guys. I only see, I thought it was just one guy who was
like an avatar. I only see the one chubby guy. Yeah. Actually, he lost some weight, though. He's
looking good these days. Good job, dude. I just see that one guy and I don't know if he's Noggin
or Lockestein. He has the most, I watched some old videos. He has the most ridiculous hair I've
ever seen on a human being. It's got this weird, spiky wave, but he's fixing it. I hate what he
represents, which is humans that use like a like really like deliciously rendered cartoon avatar.
And that's their identity. They paid like a couple, maybe a couple hundred bucks to a really
good artist to draw some really fucking lush, to draw a really, really handsome avatar,
really handsome in cartoon form and with like five different expressions and that's the whole
fucking- And we all know that's an alt-right dog whistle if there ever was one. Absolutely.
Okay, but the theory was that these two are like Odin's sword and shield and the third one will
be a spear. But like- You know, I was thinking spear. I was thinking spear. There's some connection
there. How does Odin have to do it? Is this like a Norse? There's like Norse shit going on. Odin
has two pet wolves. God, what about Frecky and Gary and Frecky, I think? I think that's right.
Do these two things even look like wolves? They're just like dogs, right? They're wolves. No, they're
wolves. They're definitely supposed to be wolves. They're absolutely wolves. I can't tell the difference.
Yeah, I mean, not at all. They're looking at a husky with the difference between a wolf.
There is none. It's the same. You're delusional people. Anyway, I don't know. I got really
not much to say. Oh, we could talk about- What do you guys think about Dynamaxing? You're gonna
Dynamax your voice? It sucks. It's bad. I can tell that the game is going to suck because-
It's desperate. Because obviously the fucking priorities are totally wrong.
Well, okay. The fact that they would even think to introduce something like Dynamaxing just
demonstrates that they've failed from the get-go to understand what makes a Pokemon game good.
I thought the mega evolutions were retarded and I thought the other thing from the last gen was
retarded as well. You're right. I kind of agree, but I could sort of defend them as like an experiment,
but the fact that they- But they're still here. They're not going anywhere.
They did it again. They do it every time now. They did it again, but they're doing it with so much
less art direction to it. They're just bigger. I mean, that's just the most obvious thing to
make fun of, but it's the biggest problem with it. There's nothing to it. I think that the one cool
thing about it though is the idea of the raids, like that you fight a giant Pokemon. It's like a
group, it's like an online raid party thing. I think that's neat. I look forward to Dynamaxing
my Wailord and creating a black hole that consumes the entire planet. That'll be fun.
That'll be fun. No, no, because he's lighter than air. He's the float whale.
Wait, does he actually float? It's debatable, but his weight is like- I think I saw someone
calculated it and he only weighs like 800 pounds or something, even though he's like 40 feet long.
But he's huge. Yeah. I think he might technically be lighter than air and his type is the float-
he's the float whale Pokemon, so he might literally just float.
What about the Alolan Exeggutor? Would he hit the Skybox?
Oh yeah, he goes into the atmosphere for sure. Oh my God, Dynamaxing an Alolan Exeggutor would be
so sick. Well, now you're officially sold on it. Okay, some of these gimmick ideas are good.
It's a good idea in that I would like to see a gif of it. I don't want to buy a video game
because of it, you know? I mean, I like the Z moves for the sole one reason that it had that
really funny clip of Snorlax when he wakes up and does his funny charge attack with his sparkling
eyes of death. I don't inherently hate mega evolutions. I don't inherently hate Z moves,
but it's enough. Stop, stop. It's a weird- It's over. This is what's happening now.
I just hope that- The only thing that pissed me off about this fucking game, on the one hand,
console RPG Pokémon is something I've dreamed of since I was a child. X and Y already gave me
the taste of it, where seeing it in 3D finally was like, oh my God, this is what I always wanted it
to be. Sun and Moon made it better by opening up the environments and stuff. Except fucking Colosseum
had way better animations than any of the fucking new 3D actual mainline Pokémon games.
Does Colosseum use the same- Yeah. Okay, it's not that the models are better. It's the animations
are infinitely better. It's not used for Pokémon Stadium. Okay, well, yeah, and that's the same
ones from Pokémon XD, right? Yeah. Because the Pokémon and XD look fucking ridiculous. I know,
that's why they're great. They're sick. Sometimes they're great. There's personality. They look
ridiculous because the models from Pokémon XD are all ripped from Pokémon Stadium and Pokémon
Stadium too. They are just N64. Yeah, okay. It's all right. I mean, have you seen Pokémon Stadium?
I mean, Golbat's really funny. Have you seen Golbat? Yes, and he's awesome. He stands with
his wings wrapped around him, just like rocking back and forth, like waddling. I love that guy.
It's great. It's great. But it's terrible, but I love it. All the Nintendo 64 animations
had, obviously, since they were less Pokémon, they had more personality in each of the
animations. It's literally Soul vs. Soul. Me and Munchy recently finished our
Nightmarishly long Pokémon XD Nuzlocke on the RFCK channel, and link in the description.
Kangaskhan is like a fucking seizure nightmare. Really? Yeah, I don't remember. I haven't seen
that one. Kangaskhan is just like a mess of constantly flailing, and a lot of them are like
that. They're really weird. Whoever designed some of them. Fair enough. As much as I'd love to go
into the bones of every technical thing wrong with these children's games, the thing that bothered me
the most is that it's on the Switch, and the Switch is a $300 console, and there's two of the games
still. So it used to be, hey, me and my brother would each get the two different versions on our
Gameboys. It's perfectly reasonable for you and your sibling to both have a Gameboy. For you and
someone else sharing your house to both own a $300 console is just a lot more, and it's like,
I was really looking forward to getting to play this with Mei. Both of us get the two different
games, play together, but it's on the fucking Switch. So now I just finally bought a Switch.
Now she would have to also buy a Switch for us to play simultaneously, and if they fucking make
this game still only one save file per game, I'm gonna fucking throw fit. Yeah, they will. That's
a whole like fucking grandfathered in bullshit that Pokemon's always done. That should not be
excusable. Just one save file per game. It initially was a fucking memory issue, and there's no reason
they couldn't change that in the future. Maybe they like the idea of it's kind of Animal Crossing
where Animal Crossing intentionally says this is your world. You have one world.
You can play as multiple characters in that world. It's like Dark Souls. It's like Dark Souls.
Even Dark Souls lets you have multiple save files now. Wait, it does? Okay, never mind.
Yeah, you can have as many characters as that game as you want. The thing about Pokemon is they
obviously do it just to push system sales. There's no other reason other than it forces your friends
or siblings or whoever you would be sharing this game with to also own a copy. Actually,
the good news about the Switch is like, you know how you can have different profiles? I think
even with a game like Pokemon or Animal Crossing, every profile on your Switch account does have
like its own save file of every single game. If that's true, then it will, then it'll be fine,
but like it still is annoying to know that like I can't just pass, you know, like the idea of a
$300 console to play two fucking of the same game is just infuriating. I hear you. I hear you.
What can you do? What can you do? To move the conversation from Pokemon to, you got something
to say, Nate? Wait, wait, I have one final thing to say on the subject and it's just that. So,
gyms are the best thing about Pokemon. They were always the most fun and the most interesting
and the most cool and they were great, like, I don't know, like progression meter of how you're
doing. And we saw like in the new trailer, like, uh, it's just that in the new trailer, it's like
you're in like a stadium, you're going to get like super popular or something. Like that's all
fine. But it looks like Dynamaxing is going to be like a main component of gym battles is what it
looked like. And I'm just saying, oh, great. Now instead of like my Pokemon skill at the game,
I'm just going to have to deal with this fucking Dynamaxing stuff. I mean, it's like the Dynamaxing
thing is like a thing. I mean, it's like a Z move. It's like a thing you have to use strategically.
I don't think Dynamaxing in and of itself is bad. They said only last like three turns.
Yeah, you guys are all fucking gay. This looks cool. I like Dynamaxing.
Oh, you just like it because you're Godzilla shit. Yeah, yeah, I do. Tell me how it looks cool.
How does it look cool at all? Because they're big and it's fucking cool. I like the idea. I think
everyone's always dogging on Pokemon. You're all gay. You know what? You know what? I think
one Pokemon can do it for three turns in a battle. It's not going to overtake anything. It's just
another extra layer. It's fine. It's not going to be a huge deal. You know what I think would be
cooler? You know what I think would be cooler is if Dynamax battles were like a different mode of
battling, like you can have triple battles and double battles and rotation battles. What if just
there were some Dynamax battles where it was like maybe you only get sort of how would you balance
that though? It'd be a whole different game. Well, I mean, yeah, I don't know. Maybe it's just each
one is like one monster versus one monster. Maybe they each have like everybody's giant. What's the
point then? You know, because if everybody's giant, then they know what he is. Just looks cool. I don't
know. That was the problem I was having with it was like it seemed to be every gym or like you
have this power and you can activate it potentially in every battle if you wanted to, I guess.
I like the idea of like a final boss sort of like, oh, you know, the evil villain has like a power.
Like when a hot blonde lady fused with that one Ultra Beast in Sun and Moon or whatever. That was
you know, that was okay. Yeah, right, right. Like if the villain team of this game is like
getting technology to turn Pokemon big and then you have to fight the leader and he has a big
Pokemon and you have like your whole party, but like you don't get like that until after that.
Maybe, I mean, maybe that's what it is, but it feels like it's like a thing at the start of the
game. You can just become big and then you get big through the game and it just loses its appeal.
I doubt it'll be at the very start of the game. Because like the Z moves were such a
fucking pain in the ass to even acquire in the last game that I never used. Well,
we know it'll happen at the first gym at the latest because we saw it in the first gym.
Yeah, you're right. You're right. So, you know, the Milo, it's, it kind of looks to me like maybe
you can only Dynamax in certain places. Like maybe you can only do it in gyms and raids and maybe
certain other specific times. Hey, Ben. Ben, did you notice that they made a new
killer Pokemon? Oh, the, um, the bird, the fucking bird. That was the most killer ass thing I have
ever seen. That thing is so killer. That thing is my new favorite Pokemon. He is. Is that what it's
called? Corviknight? Corviknight. That's right. That's right. I, I do like it, although it's like,
it's, I mean, it certainly looks flying. No, wait, it's flying steel, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
okay, okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, how do you know? Because they told us. They told us. Did they?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they released info. I'll take your word for it. Shot. Everyone was saying like
Skamori finally has a friend. Yeah. Yeah, there's a new Skarmory. Well, cool. Yeah, it was pretty good.
Very killer. Very gothic. I can't wait to have a team of six. Ben, is your favorite Pokemon still
Gothelita, Gothetella, whatever? Gothetell, Gothetell. She's, I mean, she's never been my favorite,
but I do like her. I like her a lot. Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. I was going to say,
because she sucks. Is there a fucking Pokemon called Gothelita? What? Yes. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, well,
she's my Pokemon waifu for sure. Okay, great. Let's talk about Pokemon again. Hippo, what did
you want to talk about? Oh yeah, I was going to change the topic from Pokemon to Pokemon the anime,
because, because last, last episode, I had a, I had a moment where I was like, whoa,
Pokemon's free. I mean, I could pirate it easily. It's fine. But like on the Pokemon website,
they have every episode of all Pokemon just in all of it all the way up through the current.
Yeah, like, well, that's what I'm going to do from now on. So I've been going, I, as a youngster,
I got up to like the first league, and Ash last, and that's what I remember. And then I watched the
movie, and I don't think I watched the anime properly after that. So I've been picking it up from
the Orange Island saga, and it sucks. No, I'm really enjoying it because yeah, okay, okay,
the anime is good. All right, we gotta talk about this. It's really colorful and really nice,
and the music's great. And some of the animation is like surprisingly really good. I've looked
around for Sakuga Meisters to find out who animated like certain episodes. Team Rocket
is the best thing to happen in the Pokemon franchise as a whole. Yeah, they have the most
personality for sure. Pokemon has always been enjoyable and fun, except for maybe advanced
generation. But the, the Orange Islands, like as a kid, I think that I and a lot of other people
lost interest in the series at that point, just because it wasn't the games. Like we had all played
the games. And what are those fucking weird, like abstract, like post-modern looking badges you're
getting, Ash? Like, yeah. Well, and, and like, Golden Silver had already been out. So like, we had
played those games, we're expecting Johto, and then we get this weird other thing, and it was like,
it felt like kind of a slap in the face just because it was like, I haven't gotten to experience
these gyms. Like, I don't know who these, these gym leaders are, but like, I actually think that
section of the anime was probably one of the more conceptually interesting parts, because,
you know, since they weren't going on source material, they were just able to make up their own
stuff. Hey, this is a very high bar, though. Yeah, dude, Pokemon anime is good. It is very good.
I can still return to it. And I just watched an episode the other day that was fucking hilarious.
The dub is fun. Like, I honestly enjoy the Pokemon dub because they, they clearly intended to make
it a comedy series. Like, they were trying to be funny, and like, the acting's stupid as fuck,
but like, the dialogue works with that. So it's, it's almost like a parody dub.
The frying pan is the drying pan. Yeah.
That is funny. That is good. Who am I? I am Brock. Slimes like that.
By the way, uh, yeah, Brock leaves in the Orange Islands, which I had never, I had never knew
and known. Tracy, don't you love Tracy? Tracy is like really boring, but there's one thing that I
like about this new dynamic is that without Brock, um, Tracy is like not as much of a pervert,
but he does notice that Ash and Misty like each other and he's pointing it out like every
episode and they're all blushing and it's like this whole romance thing is coming to the forefront.
I know, I know that it doesn't go anywhere because, yeah, Misty gets cut and, and like,
she leaves and I'm, I'm, I'm waiting for that moment in the anime where I can be like,
ah, it sucks now and I can stop because I don't actually want to watch like 700,000 episodes.
Dude, but it gets, but it'll never happen. You're gonna watch them all. You're true.
I mean, Pokemon like, it gets, there's a shitty part because if you get to Advanced
Generation when they introduce May and Max, May and Max suck. The episodes get really formulaic.
That part of the anime is not that good. Uh, the next season after that with, uh, with Dawn is,
is whatever, but like, it picks up again as of Best Wishes or Black and White. Like, the show
gets great again and, uh, is definitely worth watching. Although the dub is no longer as good
and funny and iconic because they replaced all the actors in like Advanced and all the new ones
are fucking terrible, but, um, but fucking Pokemon Sun and Moon and brought in Keeper Sutherland
for Ash. Pokemon Sun and Moon is the best one. It's super fucking, it's colorful and adorable
and it's, it's not actually an adventure show. It's like, uh, it just takes place in one city
and the action comes to them and like Ash doesn't have like companions. He's just kind of at this
Pokemon school with like all the gym leaders from the game in it or like most of them and, uh,
the girls are super fucking hot and it's like the most interesting animation.
Is it like still getting badges or something or whatever they fucking do?
Uh, I don't know because I haven't watched that much of it, but like in what I've seen,
it was mostly just like a slice of life show in Alola, but with like really amazing animation
and, uh, an art style. It looks fucking awesome and it's, that's cool. Very pleasing.
And, uh, one thing, uh, is that I found like, I'd never really had a Pokemon waifu. Misty was
the closest, but I think I found one, uh, in Professor Ivy because look at how
right, uh, look at that, look at that wreck. Look at how big she is.
I'm pretty sure Tracy ends up fucking cooing their shit.
Oh, okay. I guess she's, so she's the Orange Islands lady.
Yeah, she's, she's, that is quite a wreck. Jesus Christ.
Wait, wait, wait, where'd you post it? Where, where is this?
I posted it in the thing, you know, gross discussing audio links.
That is girth. That's serious girth right there.
The wreck is fucking intense.
Could, could, could be bigger, could be bigger, but I'll take it.
She is the reason Brooke left, uh, because he wanted to stay and help her because she's a
star. Oh my God. Yeah, he makes sense.
Doesn't she kind of talk like she has to downs?
She's always like, oh yeah, she's like, uh, yes, I, I said that we, no, she's not,
she's not the island time, man. So she's name is, is Brock like you? Did he go full retard?
Why, am I like getting GF and then going for retard? No, no, by dated, by fucking retarded girl.
Oh, right. It's really trading up to the value brand, in my opinion.
Classic meme. Hi, Michelle. Get fucked.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Um, well, good Pokemon's good.
Oh, one, one, one more thing about like Pokemon, uh, the anime, I've noticed that a lot of the
times when they're introducing or like talking about like this, this new islands where they
grow grapefruits and, um, or this new island where they blow glass and stuff, it's just like
they, they come up with a thing and the animation of like, you know, the backstory of like what this
island does and what these people do is actually quite like lovingly crafted and, um, the, you know,
attention to detail for a lot of things, a lot of parts of the episode, um, uh, like for no real
reason, uh, made to explain what these things are. And I feel like, uh, it's like half trying to be
educational, but it really comes across natural and not forced. And I like that. I really appreciate,
like the, in the glass thing, they have like a few scenes showing how the glass is made.
And it looks like, like documentaries I've seen of like glass blowing factories and stuff and
traditional methods and they just have a few background characters doing that and with a
Pokemon helping them with the fire and stuff. And it's, I feel like that sort of thing. I don't
know whether they had it in the Indigo League as much. Um, but I feel like that sort of like real
world, um, aspect to the Pokemon anime is supposed to ground it in reality so that a kid who has seen
those things in real life can sort of be like, ah, Pokemon could be real. I'll go outside and find one
like the, the Pokemon are just sort of living in amongst this realistic world that could exist.
And it's, uh, it's really cool. You know, that all does sound very cool. And, but I think it was
kind of that same thing. I think that like as a hot-blooded, like my biggest problem with Pokemon,
watching it from the start was like, Ash, just get a new fucking badge, you pussy, catch every
Pokemon. Cause that's how I played the game. And it's like annoying when Ash isn't playing it the
way that I want to play it in my video game world. And sounds like, like these are all good things
about the, the show, but like, it sounds like more of the stuff that frustrated me. Ash's whole
character arc is about the fact that he is not a good trainer. He slowly gives up his dreams of
actually being like a good trainer or a champion or anything. No, no, it's just that the anime
resets basically after Johto and then constantly resets. But like up through the Johto League,
there's an arc about the fact that like Ash has his heart in the right place. And that's why
everybody respect, like, you know, wants to like him, but he's just ignorant and doesn't really try
to learn how to be better. And that's why he loses in the Indigo League is that he just straight up
doesn't know what he's doing. And like, he's never,
cause he's never trained it well. When he loses to Richie, right?
Yeah. And then in the Orange Islands, there's a whole episode about him finally like,
you know, training Charizard properly and getting his respect.
And then he becomes his like fucking pitch hitter for like a million seasons or something.
Well, no, because then he gets rid of him in like early Johto.
Yeah, Ash gets rid of all his good Pokemon.
Yeah, because they always end up, because Charizard goes to live in like the Valley of
the Charizards or whatever the fuck. Right, to get good and swole and huge, which is sick.
Goes to the Valley of Drakes, hangs out with his friends.
Yeah, but he gives up his, I mean, whatever, we all know that Ash gives up.
Tom over here with all the fucking Dark Souls references all of a sudden.
I just played it. All right, it's all there.
You hate Dark Souls, Tom. Yeah, that's your whole personality, Tom.
He's hating Dark Souls. Without that, there'll be nothing left.
What's your status on Dark Souls these days, Tom?
I'm like, I haven't touched video games like the last two weeks.
I've been so busy working on stuff, but I beat Dark Souls.
One, I got, I started playing it again just for shits and giggles.
I got the sense fortress this time, like, I don't want to deal with this, so I stopped.
I'm playing Dark Souls 3. I'm at, I'm like halfway done, I think.
Fighting the guy who like, he's the two brothers, whatever, in the fucking...
Ornstein and Smough. It's just cool, two brothers.
Yeah, those guys, no. It's like the guy who like crawls around on his knees with a big sword.
Oh, the Lothric princes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'm getting destroyed. Wait, that's like at the end of the game.
Yeah, it's pretty far. It's pretty far.
That's like one of the last bosses. Well, I guess I'm almost done then.
I mean, he might not have, have you gotten all the other Souls of Cinder yet?
I haven't gotten, I've gotten three out of four, I believe.
Wait, are you talking about Dark Souls 3?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh fuck, okay. I'm confused. Never played it.
So, I'm just...
Okay, but basically you've changed. You seem to be liking Dark Souls in general. Is that fair?
Sure. I think Bloodborne's the best one out of all of them by far.
Yeah, okay. That's fair.
So, I take, I take a Bloodborne 2 before anything else.
Maybe one day. Maybe one day.
So, Breath of the Wild.
Now, Breath of the Wild seems like the kind of game that I would really like,
but I still don't want to play it. And I don't know why.
I don't know why you think you would like it that much, Ben. What about it appeals to you?
The openness and the freedom and the robustness of the systems and the like the ability,
like the item transformation and cooking and shit, that all seems really cool.
The only problem with all that is that the game is
I mean, I don't know, maybe you'd enjoy it on like the higher difficulty that I think you can unlock,
but like as a baseline, you don't need to do any of that shit.
Like the game really is not hard enough to require you to do that stuff.
But I do think you'd enjoy it.
Some things I think you do need that for.
Like for, I remember being plagued by lightning, like many times on my like first playthrough,
and like, if you play like lightning is a bitch.
Yeah, you just have to un-equip your metal stuff and it's fine.
Is that the only thing you have to do?
Because I was still getting struck even after unequipping it though.
You shouldn't get struck by lightning.
There might have been something you still had equipped that was metal.
Huh. Okay. But see, that's the sort of thing.
Maybe I just missed that because I thought I, ah, whatever.
Fuck it.
Point is there's lots of little things like that that you got to know.
I don't, don't you equip the rubber suit specifically?
No.
And like that's how you avoid lightning?
No. If you're not wearing any metal, you shouldn't get hit by lightning.
Yeah. I mean, if you're wearing your rubber armor, it reduces lightning damage.
I didn't even know there was rubber armor and I haven't as well gotten hit by lightning once.
Well, okay. Like the climbing, right? The climbing is kind of,
you really do need to level up your climbing to like get to some places.
I've literally gotten everywhere in the game on only two extensions of the,
of the stamina wheel.
I can literally climb anything in the game on two extensions of the stamina wheel,
except for making the like-
Are there like some towers you straight up won't be able to climb if you don't level up your fucking-
Like the main towers? No.
Yeah. Like the main towers you got to use to unlock.
You just got to be smart about how you climb them.
Like the game, because what I like about the game is that they put a lot of thought
into the topography of the game.
And if you, you know, just look at your environment carefully enough,
you can find an alternate route.
There's always like a path.
Like there's an intended path through all most of these things.
And sometimes you need a special thing.
As long as you're paying attention to like the slopes and the angles of the slopes,
like you can figure out where you can stand and recharge.
So like, I don't know, I managed to climb the whole fucking big,
the biggest mountain area without having to upgrade very much.
Like-
Well, she-
I mean, even if you don't want to upgrade your stamina,
you can always brute force it because if you make good recipes-
Oh, you can make items and use them.
And yeah, that's true.
Yeah, I've done none of that.
I have not cooked once at the end of the game.
There's like a really cool moment in the beginning.
Like one of the coolest things for me about Breath of the Wild in the beginning
was when you're like talking with the old guy who's like teaching you how to do shit.
And one of the little many things you can do is like,
you have to go to this like ice place,
like this cold like roof top thing, like mountain top.
And you can like cook a bunch of things to like kind of like
temporarily make it so you can go in cold environments and be okay.
Or you can optionally like go and like read his diary
and he's like trying to find a recipe that he forgot about.
And if you do that, he'll give you a warm coat and then you can just go there.
And it just felt cool.
I just carried a torch.
That's a lot of fun.
Or oh.
Yeah.
And I didn't learn how to cook until more than halfway through the game.
God damn it, dude.
I was just like, where's the tutorial?
Like how the fuck do you cook?
I don't understand because there's nowhere to go and click on something and it says cook.
I got so into cooking because there was a there's a point in the game where you have to-
I think I would get really into cooking.
I think you would, Ben.
I think it would stop you from doing anything else.
I think you would just be cooking all the time.
Yeah, I'd just be like, oh my god, I gotta find some fucking black lines and sour potatoes
and dire apples to make a stew.
It is definitely absurdly real.
There are quests all about making recipes in the game.
And the great thing about that is because it's such an impetus to explore the whole
world because certain ingredients only exist in certain places, so you've got to explore.
Which is why I replayed it recently.
But the thing is, I found a bunch of new shrines that I hadn't done before and that was cool.
But the second, I found every tower and it's so satisfying to unlock a tower.
But the second I unlocked my final tower, I had only beaten one of the main beast dungeons.
I hadn't beaten Ganon.
As soon as I got that last tower, I was like, I'm done.
I'm literally done.
I don't care anymore.
I kind of felt that way as well because getting the towers was the main incentive drive force.
It's so much fun.
That's what I loved.
I want to play again and just do it again because it's so much fun.
But I think that the biggest problem I have with Breath of the Wild is that it needed quest lines.
Not just quests, but quest lines that would force you to do a bunch of things.
Because just playing through the game normally, it's so easy to just go to the...
You need a big gore on sword quest, motherfuckers.
I was going to say a big gore on sword.
Yeah, well, I'm sure there's stuff like that.
But it should have been a lot of the game because it's formatted like in MMO,
like when you go to different regions and stuff.
There should have been quest lines that take you through the whole region.
That you have to do everything because as it stands, the game is basically just
run to a place and do a thing.
So it's like you can just run straight to the towers.
You can just go straight to the villages of each of the four races and just do the...
Fight the ancient guy or whatever.
Like most of the side quests are just go to a place and do a thing.
So it's like there's a lot.
There's a ton of shit to do.
There's a ton of secrets.
Fuckloads of shrines, fuckloads of Korak seeds, all that stuff.
But all of it is just go somewhere and do something.
It's just a lot of it's really basic.
And then the story on top of it isn't very captivating.
Well, and nothing drives you to go do it.
Like there's no...
Like why would I choose this thing over that thing?
Like why would I pick these?
Breath of the Wild is super great.
What it needs, it needs like a...
Just for example, like a Final Fantasy VII,
like story and quest lines just overlaid on top of it with the existing characters.
And then it'd be like the greatest game ever made.
I think another thing that is difficult for me to get into the game is that...
Yeah.
Like in RPGs mainly, like your rewards for doing quest lines is gear,
but like the gear in Breath of the Wild by its very nature doesn't really matter
because like you're never going to get a cool weapon.
Well, some gear, like like at the very beginning quest,
getting that cold weather gear makes a huge difference to your actual game.
Your armor, like that's really satisfying.
The coolest thing for me was finding the fairies and being able to upgrade your armor
because your armor doesn't break.
Yes, that's a lot of fun.
For some reason in Breath of the Wild, the cloth is more durable than steel.
Don't ask me how, but that's just how it works.
But like that was cool to be able to like find...
You gotta go find certain ingredients and items and stuff to give to the fairies
so they'll upgrade your gear so it will be better.
I mean, it's like in Dark Souls, doing a quest line can result in you just like
getting an armor set that you can't get anywhere else.
Like I'd be pretty happy with that, even if it's just for fashion souls or you know,
fashion zeldas.
That can be pretty satisfying, I think.
Yeah, it's like there's not enough...
If the game had some kind of experience system,
it would be...
It would one, instantly change everything for me.
If there was leveling up, I would...
That goes a big way because I just avoid mobs.
I hate fighting mobs in that game.
Right.
Fighting sucks because...
Why do it?
Literally, why?
It just puts you in a worse position in the dungeon.
For that chest of like 30 rupees, is that why I'm gonna expend like 30 explosive arrows and shit?
There is a lot of stuff to buy, so it's not like having lots of rupees isn't good, but like...
But once you unlock the snowball game, that's just the fastest way to get rupees.
And so I just do that end game and I ignore buying anything up to that point.
For me, the problem is like...
There's a lot of areas where it's impossible to gauge whether you should go there yet.
Like you see an enemy.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm talking too much about this because I'm planning to talk about it in another place anyway,
and I don't want to spoil my whole goddamn review of the game, but...
All right, fair enough.
So, um...
Hmm?
I don't want to cut you off.
All I was gonna say is the thing that like...
The funniest thing that I did in Breath of the Wild is there's a quest early on where you have to like
stealth around a Lionel and like collect arrows or something for the boss battle.
I didn't know that was a stealth section and brute force it and killed it.
And over like 15 tries and it was the coolest thing ever because I told my friend...
Did you fight that guy?
I fought him and I beat him.
It took like 15 attempts.
You fucking beat...
I've never beaten a Lionel to this day.
What?
I just ignore them because I'm scared.
Dude, I fucking could've stopped Lionel now.
No, you know what?
End game, I might have fought one or two, but uh...
I go out and hunt them for fun.
Jesus Christ, you're more of a man than I ever will be, Tom.
That's the best part about the game.
Okay, literally I'm just...
How did you...
Because I ran out of weapons several times early on while fighting Lionels.
How'd you beat him?
What'd you do?
Oh god, it was just like...
That's why I got so into cooking because I was like...
Only had like five hearts at the start.
Durability and stopping.
And I just like...
I must really suck at this game if it expects me to beat this Lionel
because I didn't know it was a stealth section.
So I was like, okay, I guess I'm just gonna have to go get really good recipes
and figure out shit so I can like get bonus hearts
and just stack all the best weapons I can.
I got...
The thing is...
The reason I was able to beat it is because I learned the pattern so well
I just was automatically able to counter everything it was doing
because like there's like a parry system.
So I got so good I just parried all of his hits
and like the whole fight happened in slow-mo
and it was fucking sick.
And it was the best part of the entire game.
The game speaks to a problem with me as a gamer
which is that I will always choose to engage with as few systems as necessary to beat a game.
Right, right.
Like I get some sick pleasure out of seeing how badly I can play and still win.
Like how little I can contribute.
Like a game like Dark Souls, there's so many different things you could do
but you could just put your points into strength and stamina and just overpower everything.
Ever since you told me about that, all I do in a Dark Souls,
I just pump up my HP to insane heights and right now I'm playing a dex character
so it's all dex.
It's like there's so many different things you could do
and I understand why other people do it just as a way to find fun in the game.
But I'm not somebody who's gonna play the same game over and over again
just to fuck around and experiment.
So it's like I'm always just gonna try to get it over with as fast as possible.
So it's like there are games that force you to engage with all the systems in order to win
and I think that that's the only way I'll get to really have that mind expansion moment of like,
oh shit there's so much you can do in this game.
That's why I love, I like when games let you ease and casually,
low skill floor, high skill ceiling.
And like Kingdom Hearts 2, I think does a great job,
eases you in casually, but then like critical mode or whatever,
final mix stuff, it's got like all these super bosses that you need to learn how to fight.
And that's for me that's why I like that.
That's why I do, if I ever play Breath of the Wild again,
I'll definitely do it in a higher difficulty just because I was expecting to be forced to
learn things.
Like I was expecting to hit a wall at some point and like when I first,
cause I did Zora's domain first, then I went to Death Mountain and it was like,
the enemies seemed too strong for me.
So I was like, okay, the way that the map looks,
it looks like this is where you're supposed to go second.
So like maybe I really need to go grind and like learn how to play.
And then I just went to the Ruto domain, Rito?
The birds.
So the birds?
I went and did the birds and that was easier than the Zora plays.
And then like by the end of that, I had kind of gotten to a strong enough that I could go
do Death Mountain pretty easily.
And it was just like, oh, okay.
You know, as long as you just do all the easy stuff first,
then the other stuff's not that hard.
I don't know.
I just felt like I was waiting for that moment where it would be like,
you can't progress until you get good.
And it never really comes.
Yeah.
So, uh, so I'm reading, uh, reading Brave New World, uh, it sucks.
Is it verbose and boring?
No, it's not that it's verbose and boring.
It's fun and it's a rollicking thrill ride and it's fun and hilarious and good.
I like it a lot.
I'm, I'm reading it slowly.
It's very short book, but I'm only like a quarter of the way through it.
But I, I gotta say, it is so fucking corny and unsubtle and like cartoonish.
It is, it is a fucking.
Tell me about it.
How so?
It is like, it is like a caricature.
It is like a caricature of dystopian fiction.
That's the idea.
Yeah.
It's meant to be kind of parody of America.
Okay.
I should read that.
Well, no, no, it's like, okay.
Well, like I read 1984 when I was maybe like 23 or something.
You know, so an adult, a young adult, but an adult.
And I thought it was great.
And I loved it.
And, um, is it a little ridiculous?
Oh, maybe.
But, uh, it was compelling.
I loved it.
I'm reading Brave New World and Brave New World.
Was it ridiculous when it's our modern day?
It's like, it's like, they'll have like big scenes of like they're going,
they're going through like the human like embryo hatchery.
And they're like, yes, yes.
We breed all the embryos.
Yeah.
And here we sort them out.
Yep.
We have like a perfect system.
Ah, and here's where we introduce alcohol into the blood streams of the lower classes.
So they'll come out retarded and be incapable of doing anything.
Yes.
Society truly is wonderful.
Maybe there's some utility to that.
Like it's important to have a lower class like.
No, yeah.
That is the point.
That's the point in the book is that they make the lower class retarded.
So that they will not strive for more.
Like they don't understand the concept of wanting more.
So they just do stupid menial jobs and they literally are are like like bread and like
psychologically conditioned to think nothing and just straight up like be catatonic until
someone of a higher caste barks an order at them to do the one thing they've been conditioned
to derive pleasure from doing such as operating an elevator or whatever to you in concept.
I think that's great.
It's a fucking.
Well, I mean, it's a horrible fucking nightmarish thing to do to a person.
Well, yeah.
I mean, that's the.
You can make an argument for that.
Sure.
The idea though is that like this is how you would craft a society in a way where nobody's
nobody within the society is going to think it's bad because they are literally conditioned
from embryonic states to participate in it.
Like it's the ultimate authoritative state where nobody questions it at all because they
literally are controlled from birth to not question anything.
Right.
It's just built up on the back of like a baseline of like a like atrocity.
Like just the society itself to call that atrocity.
Yes, it fucking is.
All right.
Here's why that feels wrong.
Even though basically what that's what is happening is that they're rearing cattle to
do like a thing like cattle would rather not be eaten for me, but they don't know any better.
But like the thing that makes it gross and weird is that they're humans just like the
people at the highest state.
And it's it's, you know, a human is controlled getting to decide who gets to live on the lower
classes and who gets to live on the higher classes.
And that just feels unfair and uncontrollable.
Right.
I mean, I just got for sure.
It's only inhumane from your perspective as a as a human who values his personal freedom.
Sure.
I guess if I guess if you asked that guy, I guess if you asked one of these
semi morons as they're literally called in the text, I guess if you asked one of them,
they'd be like, yeah, it's great.
That's what makes it good.
That's why I like the book.
It's horrible.
It but it's so cartoonishly.
It's so cartoonishly evil.
It's like, well, that's a fun of it.
It's like taking it to the farthest flung possible extreme because like, I mean, I don't
But it's so cartoonish that I can't I can't even take it seriously.
It doesn't feel like a meaningful satire.
Is there other things going on like that?
I mean, are there like, yeah, they're like, they're like, ah, here's the chamber.
You're like, they get some like, not like that low class, but like the sort of low class.
So like, oh, yep.
Here we go.
Some newly decanted babies.
Let's watch as we condition them.
And then they send the these newly decanted babies in and like they crawl in and they put
like books and flowers around and they're like, yep, here we go.
Yep.
Take find those books and flowers.
All right.
Turn on the fucking electric floor and then they like send like shock with shocks through
these babies and like, oh, yeah, we'll do this several thousand times.
And then these infant babies will learn not to read books or like nature.
Yeah.
Society truly is wonderful.
Hail our Ford.
I was like, they literally worship Henry Ford.
It's hilarious.
Yeah.
That's fine.
This sounds like the level of like cartoonish like hell scape that you would find in
some like doge and whether breeding.
The funny thing about it is that Brave New World was created by a British author who
like came to America and just saw the way Americans act and wanted to write a book that
was like his like extreme like parody version of what he thought they already were like.
Yeah, dude, hard to agree.
Like just the sheer consumerism of America and like the way that people acted.
He was like, this is this is a hedonistic nightmare world.
I'm going to write a book about it.
What's what's bugging what's bugging me about it is that like some of the things
in it are things that I think are cool.
Like I think that I think that everyone being hatched in an embryo hatchery would be sick.
But then he's got to throw in the thing about like turning some people into like more on mutants.
You know, I get your point on that.
So, you know, like this is a dystopia.
I just got through a part where they're like, okay, I don't really understand this part.
They have this slogan that's like everyone belongs to everyone else.
And the idea is like monogamy is considered like a sin.
It's like monogamy is bad and deviant.
Everybody posts everybody all the time.
Well, you're supposed to fuck everyone.
But it's not like you're made to do it.
Like because like some people are like more attractive.
Like you like people still get to choose who they fuck.
So it's like, I don't know.
So I don't know if it like it's presented.
And I think you're supposed to recoil and be like,
everyone's fucking so many people.
They don't think they don't believe in monogamy.
That's like, what a nightmare.
Am I right?
A world where monogamy isn't seen as like this holy to be held up in the world.
Again, written by a guy in like the what, the 50s or 60s who came to America in LA
and saw everybody fucking it was like, put his mom,
twitched his monocle at his head.
This is this is filth.
These Americans, well, that's what, well, that's what annoys me about it.
Is that this idea is presented as like, like this is so look how
horrible a society like this is.
And I'm like, well, I mean,
do we have to throw the baby out with the bathwater on all it?
Just give me my embryo hatcheries and I'll be happy.
Keep out the deliberate retardation stuff.
And you know, what's so interesting about that sort of thing is
that we see that that particular complaint as very dated and old fashioned.
And like, well, it's not even that bad.
But I don't think it's that old fashioned.
I mean, I think, I mean, I think people feel like that now.
I think Zoomer Zoomers love monogamy fucking perverts.
Well, it's it's just sort of like in the future.
If this was PCP episode 8000 and we like a new like N U Ben was reading the same book.
And he was like, you know, like having no problems with anything because that
there is no problem with anything.
Like like the cultural the culture has shifted to the point where
things that used to be very upsetting are no longer upsetting,
which is something that happens through history a lot.
Yeah.
It was like, hmm.
Well, that's why we have so many.
Oh, the world is exactly like 1984 articles because, well, yeah.
Yeah.
The stuff he was writing about is stuff that became real.
And like it was it was like, yeah, this this would happen.
And it did.
So here we are.
Well, there's a distinction to be made there.
I mean, at least kind of.
Like was the idea behind the book.
I don't I haven't read it.
I don't know the guy who read it who wrote it or anything.
1984 of Raveneworld.
I guess really both.
Because like are they simply.
I mean, I would think if I was going to sit down and be like, okay, the future,
I'm seeing things that could be bad.
So here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to write a book about what I expect.
Like I'm seeing bad things in society.
I'm writing a book about the like how things could progress along that way.
And my goal will be to represent the future that I see
realistically from my perspective, but to illustrate how specifically those things
could be bad, which is very different from simply like imposing that and also saying
also people like will be evil at the same time as these things.
Well, it's basically it's not that it's evil.
It's that it's they're raised in a society with like twisted morals that makes them that way.
It's that the it's basically both books are slippery slope arguments.
It's like if we keep following the trend of thought that is carrying us in the direction
we're going, this is where that ends up.
If we, you know, if we allow that, like if we allow ourselves to be in a surveillance state
and constantly, you know, having the state monitor us and we become more and more comfortable
with it and more and more okay with it, then they will be able to impose, you know,
crazier and crazier shit until just a hundred years down the line.
It's fucking a totally different society where, you know, individual thought and freedom is
totally not even considered a thing you want to have, you know.
Right, right. Yeah, no, fair enough, fair enough.
I don't know. I guess I just want people to, I mean, like, for example, like on the monogamy point,
like I would say that I think monogamy thus far in human history has been a relatively useful
concept. Now, I could doubt like, I don't think that there's any moral imperative for anyone to
engage in it specifically. However, I would say that as society has progressed, it seems like it
has been relatively useful. And so like in like a Brave New World thing, I could write a book
about how like maybe everything else is the same, but monogamy goes away and I could potentially see
like how that could cause problems for society if that kept going. Well, yet to remember in Brave
New World, people do know the idea of family doesn't exist. All babies are born in test tubes,
they're all raised by the state. So like they're the only reason you fuck is just to keep your
stress levels down, basically. Like it's just like the reason everybody's encouraged to fuck
all the time is just to keep them in a good mood, essentially. Like everybody fucks all the time,
everybody does tons of drugs, they all fly around in private helicopters.
What you need is a gram of soma. Yeah, all like clothes are built to only last for like two
weeks so that you're constantly buying new stuff. Like it's fun about like the having to fuck all
the time because like if the guy right in the book didn't want to have that as a point,
it would make more sense for them in the test tubes to like get rid of the sex drive so that they
they don't need to get distracted. Maybe he thought that wasn't possible. I mean,
I don't know what he thought was like intrinsic to human beings and what like could be you know,
removed or whatever, because it sounds like he does like conditioning more than like genetic
manipulation. Like they give alcohol, which is like a physical substance, you know, when they're
young or whatever to fuck them up and then they shock them or something. I think the overall
like thought behind the book is basically if we had a society whose purpose first and foremost was
to perpetuate itself, like the only purpose of society was continued growth and continued,
you know, just being bigger and bigger and more and more of itself, then this is the best way,
like, you know, this is the most expedient way to go about that. Like this method would work
in theory, like the way this world is structured. It just is so repulsive to us because we look at
it and we go, well, this is antithetical to what we actually want out of life. So clearly,
you know, the, I think the reflection you're supposed to take out of that is, okay, well,
then maybe a society built to perpetuate itself isn't inherently a good thing and we shouldn't
look at our advances in the world through that lens. Maybe we should not think about, you know,
only how to make things more efficient, more, you know, more and more factory. What's the
word I'm looking for? Industrialized. Like, you know, we should take a step back and weave that
into our lives more carefully as opposed to plunging into it, especially in, again, the era
it was written where we're still in the industrial age, you know, which has kind of given way to the
digital age now. We, you know, we don't, we're not trying to make more and more people. We're not
trying, you know, the era of the baby boomer is over, but it would have been like this book would
have come out like when the baby boom had just happened, you know. So I think that's why like
the culture of America at the time did more closely resemble this. And like, you know, we always
talk about things like, oh, like something out of a Norman Rockwell painting as like a creepy thing,
you know, we look at something like Pleasantville or, or whatever, like all those fifties sitcom
ideas. And that stuff is creepy to us now because it is so conformist, it's so non,
you know, individual. No, no, people talk about Norman, when they say, oh, it's like out of a
Norman Rockwell painting, it's like, it's like, oh, it's like a wholesome pure. Some people say it
that way. Justice in the American way. Some people say it as in it's a nightmare. Like, I mean, have
you ever seen the movie Pleasantville? Yeah, no, but I'm familiar. It's basically about like a guy
who's obsessed with this fifties sitcom that's like that, you know, white picket fence traditional
nuclear family kind of setup. But like once they they get sucked into the show, and like once they're
there, they realize how that society, like all the problems with a society that functions that way.
Sounds like a Twilight Zone episode. I mean, not to get too into it, but like, I mean, I remember
reading Not to Kill a Mockingbird, what's that book with Holden Caulfield and the
Catcher of the Rye, I think was written specifically to show that like this Leave it to Beaver facade
of fifties culture was actually belying like an underlying darkness that was like more of the
reality. That's also what all of David Lynch's movies are about as well. Oh, yeah. But I mean,
doesn't Catcher of the Rye more about just like young people being like hypocrites and like it's
about many things like teen angst and stuff about many things. I think that that is one of the
things that comes along with. Yeah, okay. In any case, yeah, I think that Brave New World reflected
this idea of like, you know, what where the industrialization and the sort of brainwashing
because very much so we were being brainwashed back then like the boomer generation is a brainwash
generation. They were told what to buy, how to live, you know, I mean, we still are. Yeah,
but I think that since the sixties that like when they, you know, the hippie movement and
everything was about breaking away from that conditioning and like that's where alternative
lifestyle became a thing. And now like alternative lifestyle is, I mean, it's not even really
alternative anymore. It's like there's basically just multiple lifestyles you can have that are
all like alternative lifestyles are were just they were maybe they were a thing at some point,
but then they were just commodified in and of themselves and turned into that's that's good
to me. Like I think that that's fine because no nightmare nightmare. Well, it speaks to the fact
that society is a better place to live that you are not if you have an alternative lifestyle
instead of being killed, they just sell you shit. You know, like, I think that's a better situation
to be in. I mean, better than being killed. Yeah, I guess. I don't know. I don't want my
everything is bad once it's commodified once once it's being sold to you. I mean,
you got to always try to find, you know, a new way to be even more alternative. But like,
I think at some point, you know, if we have enough acceptance that literally no matter
how alternative your viewpoint is, you're being catered to, it just means that we've basically
achieved world peace. You are a neoliberal capitalist shill and a stooge. And how could you
be a neoliberal and a capitalist? Isn't that aren't they like that's the same? That's that's
that's what linear like neoliberalism is capitalism focused. Okay, well, what's all the
what's all the fucking commie shit then that's going on?
Oh, no, neoliberalism is like centrist liberalism. That is leftist is leftist is like,
like, liberal is basically like milk toast, like like everyone. Okay, I think it's used
differently in America. Like in America, there's like, you see the dichotomy of liberal versus
conservative. I think globally, liberalism is a philosophy is a basically a mostly
universally accepted philosophy that is pretty much just the default. And like,
okay, but what do we call all communism are left of that all these kids leftism all the
so those are just leftists. That's the only word for it. You I think you basically have to be at
least a socialist to be a true lefty. Okay, if you're if you're just a if you're just a garden
variety, but neoliberal is not the same. I just thought it meant the new left.
Uh, neoliberalism is well, it's the new it's the it's the new it's the mainstream. It's what
the mainstream left has become in in in late stage terminal capitalism. It seems to me like the
mainstream. Well, I don't know. I don't even know what these are just definition terms. This is
really boring. But I got really fucking boring. You're just talking about a definition. That's
all it is. Yeah, a definition. Well, it's an important definition. And we can't fuck like,
I'll bet there's people that don't know this. I'll bet there's people that are misused if they
know what a word means or not. Shut the fuck up. Did you did you didn't know what the word meant?
So now we can hear and argue about this all day. Or we can we can I'm not arguing. I'm giving facts
that were previously unknown or we can we can we can bring it back. We can go to urban dictionary
and we can find out for what neoliberalism is. Yeah, okay. Do you have that pulled up? I don't.
Let's get no and none of us do and I don't care anymore. So if anybody has anything else to
talk about, I've got another another concept that I just learned this last week, at least it became
fully clear to me that I think is real cool. And it puts a point on things. Urban dictionary,
neoliberalism, the belief that allowing the wealthy to extract more money from the labor of other
people will lead to better conditions for those people. Example, neoliberalism. This is
retarded. That's literally what capital. Well, it really depends on what you mean by the word
extract there, but I don't want to get into it. Example, neoliberalism doesn't work,
semi colon. The proof is all around you. Okay, so so what I learned from this is that I had
thought neoliberal was a buzzword that the right made up, but now I realize it's a buzzword that
the left made up. So either way, it's retarded. But now I know which side it comes from.
Well, whatever. I think we can all agree the buzzing is really annoying and I hate insects.
Hey, listen to this word, this phrase that I just learned a couple of days ago. It's okay,
it's like it's a it's from a specific field of journalism. And it's the journalistic principle
of minimizing harm. And I just learned what this meant. And I think you'll all agree,
it's a valuable thing that people who make YouTube videos and whatnot should be should be on
board with and I tweeted about it the other day. But basically what it is is it's well,
it's just not including information. Okay, when you're being a journalist, and I would argue
anyone who like makes a tweet is kind of being a journalist because you're making like a public
post about stuff. It's like, including information that is not specifically like serving the benefit
of the public, or like, you know, in your journalistic capacity, such as it is, doing good,
like for the world by publishing, like just for example, if you write a story about like,
this is an extreme example, or you make a tweet about like, I hate this guy so and so,
and you include just for a crazy example, like his name, social security number, address, phone
number, etc. It's like, okay, you're letting people know the information about this person who
maybe you hate or you think he maybe he put fucking pushed your milk at lunch or something.
But like, is that necessary to include? No, you're definitely doing it as a way to like,
give the guy harassment, or, you know, it's just not necessary. And so you're what you're not doing
is adhering to the principle of minimizing harm when reporting on stories like this.
And like, like a lot of attack videos, and like takedown and call out culture, like all the stuff
with like, James Charles lately, it just included like tons of and you see this on like every call
out video ever, there's so much information that is simply put in there to humiliate and like insults
and deride the person, which does not serve like what one might think of as the thesis of,
I don't know, so and so is a hypocrite on these specific principles for XYZ reason.
I agree. And I think that's a good thing to do. But in those videos, you're talking about specifically,
those are trying to maximize harm. Like, I mean, absolutely. Right.
You're absolutely right. I mean, let's not let's not pretend that YouTube is journalism.
Well, I mean, it's trying to say is that we need to, if we see people deliberately trying to
maximize harm to be not okay with that, yeah, to call out the people doing the call outs,
if they're being, if they're like, you know, to make it something that we bash people on
Twitter for, just be like, Hey, I want to put a word to it because I see people doing it and
it makes me upset and mad. And I didn't really know how to phrase it. But now I know, like,
you're trying to maximize harm to the law, like the way that the law works and how we punish people
is based on a principle of minimizing harm. Like, we don't like, let's say somebody murdered
somebody else, we don't just jump and kill that guy. We like put them through a system to figure
out like, okay, like, what is the minimum amount we can do to this person that is still going to,
you know, allow retribution, allow everybody to be sort of comfortable with the result of it,
you know, like, yeah, you know, maybe, maybe we could say, okay, well, you're going to present
professionals doing it at least, you'll go to prison for 25 years to life, you know, we'll
make a determination over the course of those 25 years, if you have reformed as a person and we
didn't have to kill you and you can continue to contribute to society, maybe you will, maybe you
won't. But like, that is minimizing harm in a way, it's like, it's like, we've got and it doesn't
do any good for the world to just hurt people over this and it drives people apart. And it's a
large part of like, call out cultures, cause and it's like, you got people who commit murder,
get like murder, like first degree intentional murder, or let's say second degree, whatever,
they get out of jail. And those people oftentimes are like less hated publicly than like, like,
you know, just James Charles for what exactly, I don't know, being slightly sexually forward with
some people who were not even opposed to it. And then, you know, it got debunked. I don't know,
I don't know who James Charles is, but can you give me like a concrete example of a violation
of this principle of minimizing harm? Well, I was trying to avoid it, the name. Okay. But like,
the one that's in mind right now is what Mr Meat Man made his video about monkey lately. And I like,
monkey himself even said like, I accept this is true. But when I like, I don't care what monkey
thinks, I think that video was so overly cruel and took the absolute worst possible interpretation
of every point. And I think monkey has kind of painted himself into a corner where he feels
like he has to just say, this is fine, because he has done things like this in the past, which I
whatever, not interested in discussing. But it's like, but I on the sidelines say, this is wrong.
I think you're going too far. This doesn't seem fair. It's overly cruel. And you're, you know,
not even the points are wrong, but it's the most insulting interpretation. And when you get to
the end of the video, and it's because he's like personally mad at monkey, it's like, well, Jesus,
is this really an appropriate, you know, backlash for that stuff? I don't even think it's going to
stick that long. But I just think it's fucked up. Well, I mean, what's the, I mean, that's not
journalism. That's gossip. Like the point of that video is that it's gossip. It's juicy gossip.
But the problem is weird. That's what it sets out to be. And that's what it does. True. But I
think that like gossip deserves to be mocked, not taken seriously, condemned, insulted, you know,
on its merits, which are none. And then like, we just be like, oh, well, yeah, this is trash.
But it's not treated as trash. It's treated as, wow, Mr. Medeker 2, I love this guy. Can't
I just subscribe for more? I mean, it's interesting because it's human drama that's actually real.
And we learn even more from it than watching like a show about it, you know, like that's why
gossip has, it has some intellectual content to it. Like, you know, there's a reason to consume it
as a human for, you know, self-preservational purposes. Right. But we can't just ignore like
all the math. And now I just have a word for what I'm seeing. Like you could make that video
in a way that's totally reasonable. But like what I'm seeing is a man. How could you,
how could you make that video in a way that's, I mean, just for example, if you would be,
there would be nothing to it. Maybe there shouldn't be, you know, a little baggage
saddled to it. A story about, I think your problem, because I think it's my problem as well,
is that if it was just a video where it's just like, I'm mad at X person and I'm going to fucking
dunk on them for 20 minutes, like not, not great, not my cup of tea, like does feel uncomfortable,
but understandable. The problem is a lot of these takedown videos are presented in a way that I'm
doing this for the greater good. Like this is a good thing I'm doing. And then they proceed to
like very personally attack somebody. So it's like that's trying, they're trying to make a documentary
about. And for the love of God, people, I'm not saying go shit on Mr. Meat Man. Could I be any
more fucked? I'm, that's not the point. It's a, it's a global phenomenon. I'm criticizing the
concept of this stuff. Jesus Christ, don't get me involved in some beef with Mr. Meat Man. I don't
give a fuck. But you know, you know, I'm just saying, I oppose the idea. Let me tell you,
this is something, something's kind of related. So I, so I'm in, I'm in sheep overs discord and
some people were talking about, uh, you guys remember, uh, FNGR? Of course. Yeah. That's that
fucking moron. Uh, well, he, he somehow. I think he still listens to the PCP. So. Hey, FNGR, you're
a fucking loser. Um, so he, he somehow managed to finagle. He got them, uh, the girl, uh, Lou,
Lou, Lou the kitty. Yes. The one, the one that, uh, the, the monkey shit. Uh, you know, uh,
and she got her on, he got her on stream with a bunch of people and I listened to some of it and
like they get her to call the cops on herself and tell, yes, and tell them, and tell them that, hey,
I had sex with a minor. Are you, what the fuck is that about? What kind of human being are we dealing
with here? Well, the thing is, uh, wait, who, FNGR? No, I'm just like, how weak willed and like,
weirdly. Yeah. Okay. But whatever. Go on. Go on. She seems like she's not very smart at all, but
also she's maybe on a bunch of medication. Well, the thing is she says that she already told like
her therapists and other policemen on other occasions about it. So it's, I don't, I don't get the feeling
that anything's actually going to happen. I mean, look, on subjects like this, do you think any of
those guys like give a fuck about like protecting the kids in her community? No, not at all. They
just want to start shit. That's, that's what I was going to say. Yeah. Yeah. They, they, they do this.
And then even while she's still in the call waiting for the cop to show up at the door,
they're like patting themselves on the back and congratulating themselves like this person is
a danger to the community. We did another pedo locked up. Ladies and gentlemen, we did it.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got him. We've saved the fucking community. We've made the world a better
place. All this hand wringing and stuff. And like, they're not fucking, they don't fucking care.
They want to feel better than someone. They want to, they want, literally it's virtue signaling.
Yeah. Like, okay, okay. If this person committed a crime, they should be tried, you know, as a
criminal. Absolutely. But that's not what they're doing. This is where I plug my other podcast,
Artso Farto's Whirling Dervish episode three, where I talk about all this, the gay, gay ops of
thrones as I call it. Oh yes. So yeah. So anyway, this, this, this was all, this was all a bunch of
virtue signaling, self-congratulatory horseshit, FNGR, you and your friends are fucking stupid.
You should die. I take no personal positions on any of this, but I mean, yeah, I mean,
it's, it's retarded. It's fucking, there's so much of this shit, man. I, it really, like,
I will never in my fucking life get involved with any of this shit. And it's such a lucrative
mark. And I'm not saying that like I'm tempted to, I have no desire and I never will. But like,
I just see the reality on the ground that all you do is you make a X person exposed video,
you find like the most basic, like non substantial evidence you possibly can,
boom, you got yourself 50,000 subs. You got a burgeoning career now. Let's go baby.
Well, that's the thing. Okay. This is my thing. It's, I mean, okay. Yeah. You watch the Meat Man
video and you come away with a sense like boy, that was some juicy gossip, but also Meat Man
kind of seems like a fucking loser. Like, why is he so obsessed with this?
Gee, you think Meat Man's a fucking loser?
Yeah. I mean, I think he would agree because he says he does it for like a $10 thing. It's
kind of silly. So I mean, I mean, he's so invested. Like he's, he like, I don't know,
you can tell from his voice that he's just like, he's like savoring it. He like can't
fucking wait to share this like delicious. He like, he can't wait to take this guy down.
Right. He doesn't come off very well.
If anybody is surprised that Mr. Meat Man is a piece of shit, you have not been paying
attention. Okay. Okay. So that's all fine. However, I don't know if I can blame him
in a, if, for like, for making the video, because you know that like he, like, you know
his channel grew because of it, you know, new people heard about him that never would have
heard about him otherwise. Like he was sitting on like this information that he made the video
on, he was literally sitting on a gold mine. And like, how could you expect him for like,
of attention, right? In the attention economy and how he would be shooting himself in the foot
not to make this video. So how could you expect him to do otherwise?
Well, I mean, I, but, I mean, in the same way I kind of expect myself not to because I didn't.
I mean, I've got plenty of insider. What do you mean you didn't?
I mean, look, I've obviously not like been friends with mum for that long, but like,
I have plenty of insider information. I could make some sort of exposed video,
but then I think to myself, oh wait, I'm not a fucking asshole scumbag. On who? On who?
On, look, I mean, look, theoretically on like anyone in our chat, I could like go,
like I'm just saying, like the possibility exists. Any of us could make exposed videos
on any other of us. And you know, it'd be great. If you play the gay ox of thrones,
you are a piece of shit. You have to accept that about yourself. And everybody needs to look at
it that way. Be entertained, have fun, watch people shit on each other, but know that the
people doing it are shit. And you are shit for participating.
And you're making the world a worse place. If you accept all that, I can understand that.
You know what? Yeah, I can agree. Like you like, like, if you're going to get in there and throw
shit, right? If you're if you're one of the people in there throwing shit, that's fine. Maybe
it's an entertaining spectacle, right? You are covered in shit. Yes. And you are remind you,
monkey was playing the gay ops of thrones the whole fucking time. So I don't really feel any
sympathy for him in this regard. Well, I mean, I feel sympathy for anyone in this situation.
I don't feel sympathy for anyone for basically anything. I didn't feel it about anyone involved
in the projared thing. I don't feel it in anything involved in this thing. Yeah, I mean,
he that's why he says like, he said he said in his no, he said in his response to it, like, you
know, if if this like, if this video were about anyone else, I would think it was funny. Yeah,
yeah, this this kind of thing is not exactly, but it's not okay. It's not too far away from the
sort of thing that monkey traffics in. But me strapped on my white knight armor. I feel like
yes, like there there's many people who are in the shit, they can't defend themselves because
they've done too much shit. We need outside heroes outside white knight, such as myself to come in
and police. I mean, we kind of need content cops to be like, this is fucked up, people shouldn't
be celebrating that this is being done. And like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what do you mean?
We need content cops back up a second. What are you talking about? I'm saying I'm not saying like,
we need YouTube to enforce what's okay. I'm saying like, I think that what I dubs did, I'm not saying
I dubs like a hero or anything. Wait, what did I dubs do? Well, he made a series called content
cop, where like, specifically what he did was he, he made videos, you know, they're just there,
you could call them drama videos too. But like the point of them was, and you could say he went
too far, so like personal stuff was included, he did not minimize harm across the board,
fair enough. But like, the conceit of them was to push back against practices, like Leafy did,
that was kind of bullying in many ways against, I don't like, you know, like Jake Paul or something,
I think, or no rice gum, rice gum. And again, I don't know any of the specifics. I just, I see
a utility of like us as a community, even age three did this like a bunch, you could say he
doesn't do it as much anymore. I see a, and I am not going to be the man to do it. It's not happening
for me, no interest. I'm not involved at all. I'm going to make funny anime videos. But like,
I just like it, I don't think we should just like all be like, yep, this is fine. No one's
being punished for this. Everything's great. It just seems, yeah, I mean, that's it, you know,
I feel like content was the genesis of this entire subgenre on you, you can make an argument,
it's propagating the cycle or is kind of a problem itself. But I don't know, like, you don't, you
don't have to like, epically dunk on people the way that content cop does, you can like, I don't
know, be a little more nuanced. I think it's what Ben is saying, though, like the more you dunk on
someone, the better your video is going to do. One needs to become an aesthetic and absolve
oneself of the pleasure of dunking on anyone and simply point out like, look, it is, it is wrong
to do XYZ. I'm just saying we live, listen, okay, let me, let me, let me finish this thought, just
give me like one minute to kind of, could kind of work this out. Like we live, you know, we're on
YouTube, we're in an economy where attention is the currency and like anything you can do to get
attention like will get you ahead, like almost like, you know, there are maybe certain kinds of
negative attention that might backfire on you, but like 99% of the time, there's no such thing as
bad publicity, anything you can get to do to do eyes on you. That's what you, that's what you
logically should do to get ahead and succeed. I just kind of, I feel with Nate's whole point here,
like on like a logical level, like an emotional moral level, I feel similarly to you, but I also
feel like acting on morals is no, first of all, no one's doing that at all ever. And second of all,
I'm not going to really hold anybody to it. Like, I mean, Nate, you, you pirate everything you consume.
And it's fair to criticize me on that one point. Right. And so you know that like,
nothing is going to compel you to even operate within your own sense of morals. Like,
rather than us saying like, oh, we should be looking down on people who make this type of
content. Yeah, we should. But like, that's who gives a fuck. Like I look down on myself for a lot
of things that I do, but it's not going to stop me from doing it. You know, I'm going to do what I
like and what, what, what favors me. So rather than that, like, you know, yeah, we could start a moral
crusade about it, but it's not going to, we just got to accept that we live in this fucked society.
Like we live in a society where this happens and this is what's going to happen because it's in the
nature of how people are. I just want to be clear. I mean, I don't want to get into a thing where it's
like, I'm not allowed, like I have identified what I think what I'm making a case for a problem with
our kind of ecosystem or are the people or whatever. And like, okay, there are many ways to deal it.
But I wouldn't want to just say like, okay, because like, I personally do other bad things,
like I'm not allowed to like point out or it's not valid. And I think you should, I think it's
fine that you're pointing it out. I think it's fine that you're trying to affect the way people
think about it. And maybe like, if enough people thought that this shit was not good, you know,
if enough people were offended at this type of content, then it wouldn't be able to,
you know, propagate. But like, I think that you are very much fighting the ocean on a case like
this. And like, on the one hand, I can say I find it immoral, but like, I also can say that I find
eating meat immoral, but I do it and everybody does it and I don't hold anything against anybody.
Like, I can think of, you know, like if you want to claim that it is moral, you'd have to do it
from purely like a humanist perspective, like you have to be thinking about like drawing lines
in the sand about whose rights matter and all that kind of stuff. And it's like, anytime we get
into a moral question like this, you could tunnel down forever. And like, you know, we like having
things like, oh, journalistic principle of minimizing harm. That's great. It sounds great.
But it's just something people came up with as a line in the sand. Society as a whole is always
going to be deciding where it wants its lines drawn. We might enter a society where people think,
like, if you listen to the tactics of like, you know, SJWs and stuff, I think they would be
very against that principle. They would be like, oh, it's all about like, if somebody does something
bad, then we need to, we should destroy them or, you know, right, that person needs to be excised,
that person needs to be punished for their behavior. And like, I think that you always fall on the
side of something that is more bureaucratic, something that's more stable, more logically
based. And the problem is that pop media is never going to operate that way. Pop media is always
going to operate on eyeballs. It's always going to operate on, you know, on just what gets attention.
And that's always going to prey on human nature and the way that we, you know, the way that we
socially think. And I think that this kind of drama is just so core to the way that we operate,
because historically, we need to know this kind of stuff. Like, at a time when we were in smaller
communities, if someone in your community was a piece of shit, it really mattered. It really
affected you. And I think people still think that way. I think we still want to know if somebody's
doing bad behavior, we want to know enough about them that we can, you know, first of all, make
it publicly known that it's not okay to be this type of person. And second of all, to avoid that
person in themselves. And like, I do think that, you know, epically dunking on people, yeah, it's
like, if we're thinking of it in terms of like, being judge, jury and executioner, it would be
unfair. And it certainly is. And again, there's a right way and a wrong way to do it. Just, you
know, one specific example that I've noticed, I've really thought about this one example is,
since we brought up the monkey thing, it's just that I've noticed that for a long time, we all
knew that monkey, like he actually, he told it, I mean, I don't mind going into a little bit of
detail, it's just that he told us in the past that his name was Jimmy. And now, and you know what,
I'm not even going to say it because I don't want to maximize harm. Jimmy is not his real name.
And in Meat Man's video, he goes several times, it's almost like a point where he specifically
states monkey's real name. And the thing about that is we know monkey doesn't want his real name
out there. But like Mr. Meat Man in his own way, and again, I don't care, don't involve me with him,
don't shit on the guy, it's just what it is. I understand the motivation behind it and whatnot.
I mean, do shit on the guy, but you know. Well, I mean, whatever. Just don't involve me,
people. I don't give a fuck. But it's like, we know he doesn't want that information out there.
And because sources exist on the internet, where one can find out monkey's real name,
like, oh, that makes it okay to make a big dunking video where we expose this information
that we know the person doesn't want exposed because they have been labeled bad person now
for X, Y, Z reasons. And this is exactly the sort of like creeping like information that that
person wouldn't want. And I would call it creeping like bad person behavior, where we're just like
we're dismissing their personhood and their desires with culture in general right now is just that
as soon as you make one slip up, you lose all moral consideration. And like if he comes a moral
imperative to destroy you in any way possible on the one specific example, like again, I follow
the logic, I understand why someone would feel comfortable exposing that information. But we
know that monkey doesn't want that. So you're making a choice to say that you're going to include
that. I mean, I agree that like, yeah, the way that his real name is like stated over and over
and over again is like seems like a deliberate sort of like attack, almost like a dehumanization
tactic. Here's the thing, we have like dead, like to dead name him or something. We have to ask
ourselves a question though. Like, because, okay, but I just, I just want to ask where is, where is
the line? Like, okay, like, yeah, I think that's probably passed a certain threshold. But like,
I don't know if you can draw like a clear threshold of like what information is acceptable
to share and does not cause harm and what, and what is beyond the pill, like this is
maximized, this is not minimizing. I would like people to at least consider that though, which
has not seemed to have been done in many videos. I think considering it would be great. But I do
think that like, the problem with this argument is that you can just tell so much of this is just
spite. So on the one hand, you use, you want to say like, okay, the person's right to their
privacy, we want to respect that. But then on the other hand, there's the people's right to public
dissemination of information. Like, do we not have the right to know as much as we can about the
world we're in and make decisions? Like, if people- Well, this is exactly what minimizing harm is about.
Does it serve a public good to know monkey's real name? No. I mean, I would say no, but that doesn't,
just because I think so doesn't mean it's true, because like, let's say that other people legitimately
think that he is a monster on some level. Like, they might think that they need to know this
information or that like, it needs to be out there so that something can be done about him.
Well, this is exactly why I want people to be thinking about this concept so that they can
forth like, you're right, every person will disagree on exactly which points are, you know,
on that or against that. But I would like the public to consider like, did he really like, was
that name really relevant? And every single person can decide whether they agree or disagree.
But like what I would, I mean, again, what I hope, I'll just put my position out there,
I would hope most people think like, you know, that really didn't need to be in there. That's
kind of fucked up and I'm not really supportive. I don't think that the average person who watches
that video is going to come away from it thinking that Mr. Meat Man was justified. I think that most
people watching it think this is a huge shit show and the entertainment value is in that everyone
involved is such a piece of shit that like, that everybody fucked up on so many levels that-
I just don't want a situation where we end up with an eye for the eye and, you know, just
everyone's fucked. Because like- Okay, okay. I just really don't think that people are coming
away from that video thinking that it was like a morally just thing that like, oh, we're all on
Mr. Meat Man's side. Even if so, the information's still out there. Well, did you, I think, I
disagree, unfortunately, and I don't think this is a good thing by any means, but I think a lot
of people probably watched that video and came away with the idea that some, that they had,
they had learned like a truth, like a hidden truth and that like Meat Man had done some great
service. Like, oh, you've opened my eyes. Like now I see the truth of the matter. Like now I can enact
the justice. I mean, there's always- Now I can enact the justice that is required. That's the thing.
Anytime we create any piece of media, a significant amount of the audience is going to be
fucking morons who take the wrong thing out of it. Even if it's, I mean, in this case, he wants you
to take something bad out of it, you know, but, but like, I don't think even the majority of people
watching are going to feel that way. And by the way, to anyone who's going to say that like,
Monkey and Meat Man are like a bond, like they're going to like do a live stream. I do not care
what Monkey's position is on this. I have my own moral that I'm judging by. So I'm just saying,
I do not find that a valid critique. Because I mean, obviously, I don't agree with Monkey's
stance on any of this in the first place, because that's the whole reason he got kicked out of
the fucking PCP. I could talk about the exact same principles on any video Monkey's ever made,
but that's not what we're talking about right now. So, and I don't believe in just an eye for an
eye. I think that's silly. I still, I still don't think we, I still don't think he did. I still
don't think he did anything that deserved a kick. Well, he did. That's it. What he did is exactly
this. What he did is that he thinks he, he didn't, he embraced this. Guys, listen, the Monkey
kicking thing is ancient history. Who cares? Well, I mean, we're talking about the guy anyway.
I mean, sure. But I'm, I'm trying to talk about the principle of, of not including unnecessary
detail in these dunk posts that are just designed to hurt people because I just don't think it's
right. And I just want people to think about this concept when they watch their exposed videos and
be thinking like, is this like, frankly, I want them to think, should I actually be watching this?
Because that's what I was thinking the whole time while I watched it.
The video was made. I mean, let's be honest, the video was made to cause harm.
Of course, obviously. If, if, if Meat Man had considered for even a second the principle of
minimizing harm, he wouldn't have made the video at all. And like, basically you couldn't make it,
you couldn't make it. Yeah. But I don't think, right? Like, yeah, I think, I don't think Meat Man
comes off well. I think he seems like a piece of shit. But I wouldn't say like, oh no, no one
should make a video like that. Like that's wrong. But you shouldn't. I mean, it's a, well, the, I'm
saying is you shouldn't be a piece of shit. But like, the fact of the matter is people, people
are going to be a piece of shit. And like, we as an audience member can, we can watch and even
enjoy the content and still think the guy is a piece of shit for doing. I mean, I, I just think,
I mean, I'm, my point is basically like, I think it's wrong, the harm that's being done
with the extra information that we know is not wanted to be out there. And like, you could
argue, I mean, it's fair to say, you know, it's human, like again, I didn't stop watching. I kept
watching. But like the person who has the agency in the situation, I think it's pretty clear to say
is the video maker. So it's just that that's where my focus goes. And I get Ben's point that it's
a structural thing. And you're such a, you're such a, you just, you want to come so close,
like you want to come so close to saying he shouldn't make the video. But then at the last
second you pull, oh, but I'm not saying he shouldn't have made the video, but Ben, I'll be super
clear. No, he should look, he should not have made it as is, because it had a lot of
and unnecessary information. Like I'm not going to like say, I will physically stop it was unnecessary
information. All of it was none of it had to be. Yeah, look, there's a version of the video that's
just like, like literally reporting the facts of the case as they were like, people allege this
and that video too, and that video too is made to cause harm because it's just gossip. I mean,
yeah, I mean, what am I doing wrong here? I don't think I've done anything wrong. I don't, I don't
think you're, I don't think you, your principle, whatever you're trying to say, like whatever
guideline you're trying to lay down that people should follow doesn't make any sense. It, whatever,
I, I think it's well, I think that basically, I think what needs to mostly arguing for is that we
consider it. And I think that's very fair. Like to say we should be like, if you're going to write
something like this, think about it. And if you're consuming something like this, think about it as
well. Like if you're consuming it and you see a guy who is not holding up the principle of
minimizing harm, criticize that, consider it to be a lesser form of journalism.
Like, like just, here's an example. When you got like, when you got like an angry ex-wife,
and let's just, or you know, let's say a guy dumps a girl, and I don't know, he, let's say he's a
YouTuber or something. And the girl, let's, let's say in this example, he's done nothing wrong,
but the girl like finds some things he's done. And I don't know, maybe she literally makes it
up. Let's say it's all fabricated a hundred percent, because she's decided she's an addictive,
so she's going to make a video about like how he dumped her, he was abusive, he's fucked up,
et cetera, et cetera. Things that are hard to disprove. Like really what I want is people to,
when that video, you know, of course gets billion million views, I want people to think about,
like, what are the motivations? What is the evidence here? Is it like, why was this made?
Should I trust this source? And blah, blah, blah, things like that. Because I'm aware of human
nature. That's my only point. Of course I agree with all that. Of course you should be critical
about the media you consume and about what people tell you. I also want to add in here that like
when I keep pointing out that like, monkey, you know, had this coming for doing this type of thing,
it's not that I'm saying an eye for an eye makes it okay. I just want to make sure we are addressing
the fact that monkey too should be held accountable for this, that like, this didn't just become a
problem when Mr. Meat Man did it to him. Monkey did this to people. He definitely did not
try to minimize harm about people he would talk about. He would even go so far as to,
you know, deliberately, like, you know, kind of give his audience an avenue whereby they could
fuck with somebody, you know, not necessarily urging them to do it, but making it clear how
they could. So I guess a lot of it's on the borderline, which is where he operated a lot of
the time and still does. And that's exactly why I wanted to disassociate with him at the time,
because I saw him as somebody who was willing to play this game, The Gay Ops of Thrones, and I
think that as soon as anybody is doing that, your best interest is to disassociate with that person.
Because, I mean, if you don't want to ride the wave and try to make it out on type, like your
Keemstar, you're always, you win or you die, but the game goes on forever. So if you play it long
enough, you know, I mean, just doing Gay Ops is in itself something that you could be like, like,
you might, if you get into this game thinking, oh, I haven't done anything fucked, so people aren't
going to find, you know, I'm not going to be uncovered. Well, the fact that you're playing
the game is fucked in itself. So you have already given up that moral ground. This is what I said.
I said, you know, yeah, you live, you live by YouTube drama, you die. On that point, as soon as
as meat man, again, I'm not saying to talk shit, I'm not saying to do anything to the guy for the
love of God, but like the second he made that video, and he's getting notoriety, like the countdown
on when the exposed video about him began, and it's only a matter of time, you think Mr. Meat Man
hasn't said fucked up things in his private chats that like, I don't know, I'm not saying monkey
will do anything, but that like people will have. But somebody will, because now he's a juicy target
for someone else to make a name for themselves. And I just think it's toxic. I don't even want
anything bad to happen to Meat Man. I just don't think anything should, people shouldn't do this.
Nate, that's all. The thing about these people, and this is also true of Mumki,
is that I think that a lot of them are in a very bad place in their life. They're people who have
low self-esteem, think that they essentially are worthless, and that the best way they can put
themselves up is by shitting on other people and being a piece of shit, because they think,
well I'm already a piece of shit, I have no worth, so I'm just going to continue to be a piece of
shit, right? But the thing is that that will come back to bite you one day, because unless you do
kill yourself, then if you ever have a peak, if you ever have a moment where you start to gain
something, that can now be taken from you. And for someone like Mumki, who for so long was portraying
himself as like, oh, I'm a piece of shit, and I don't care what happens to me. I will harm my
friendships, because it doesn't matter, because I'm suicidal anyways. None of this shit matters,
but then things started to matter, and that caught up. It's like once you've gotten to a position
where, oh shit, turns out I'm not horribly depressed, turns out I'm making money, turns out I'm
getting popular, well the seeds that you sow- But you have many enemies that you created along the
way, or whatever. Exactly. And so again, with someone like Mr. Meat Man, he has been continually
a low-level nobody, and now that he's got some attention on him- He's got like 70,000 subs,
but I mean- He now has a huge target on his back, you know? Now that he has-
I think so. Now that he's someone who's bigger than anybody who's smaller than him, who's in the
same position he once was, sees him as the stepping stone they can use, and it's dead easy to do,
and he will go from being somebody who had nothing to lose, to being somebody who has
something to lose, now that he has that popularity, and he can lose it. And that's why you can't
involve yourself in this game, because it will- This is how it happens. What goes around comes around.
That's true, and you know, it just reminds me of like, well a couple of- I mean on the one point,
I'd like to all this point, I guess people could point out fairly, like what about like the video
I just made recently about Zack Rittner? But I would say, I mean again, you can go into instances
of this shit. I would argue that I actually did think about minimizing harm as I was making that
video, but that guy was a absolute spammer commenter, and I think one video that is simply making fun of
him and telling the audience not to do anything to him is more than fair, and it was all for fun
anyway, and was not a big deal. But like- Okay, so I'm gonna bring this up, Ben.
Ben.
Huh.
How do you think that monkeys shouldn't have- didn't do anything worth of being kicked?
Um...
Oh lord.
I just don't think he did anything.
You don't think that him, after- after he was promoting and collaborating with Mr.
Meat Man and Cream Man when they were harassing Jesse, that wasn't grounds to be kicked?
Um, none of the harassment I saw, none of the- I didn't- I didn't see anything that seemed like that.
You didn't see it, but it happened, so if you would go and do the research or maybe come away with that-
Look, I've heard all the arguments, and I'm just not convinced by any of it, that any of it was-
that any of it was so bad that not only should a person who did- we're not even arguing that a
person who did this should be- but that someone who was friends with someone who did this-
It's not that he was friends with them, it's that he promoted them and collaborated with them,
and celebrated the behavior they were displaying.
Guys, we literally talked about this dozens of times.
I just- I just never saw it.
I just- I don't know, I've heard you-
We're not gonna move on our positions.
Jesse and everyone talk about this, and I've heard all the arguments, and none of them convinced me.
Well, there's really nothing more to say.
We've been over this so many times, you know.
I just don't feel bad for anyone.
That's all.
Nobody.
Nobody ever.
I mean, whatever, man.
For me, it is now what it always was.
The fact that people in this organization had major issues with Momke leaves me feeling,
you know, I don't feel bad that I made a business decision personally
to vote him out to protect the business.
That's what I did.
I bear no ill will towards anyone feeling any way.
Sure would be coming down on us right now if he was still around.
I mean, I think it'd be funny.
Why would it be coming down on us?
Because we'd be embroiled in all this.
Well, we didn't do anything.
Okay.
I just want to say that what Momke did, I think, was really fucking funny,
and I really enjoyed the video.
I feel like that's a position.
You mean like get down with the sickness as it were with the, you know?
Yeah, like Mr. Meat Man's video was like a horrible takedown of a horrible set of things
that a guy did.
Horrible guy.
Really funny.
I laughed the whole time and I don't feel bad about it.
I mean.
And that's my pain.
I mean, the problem for me is that I don't feel we got the unadulterated facts.
I think we got the facts as presented by the man who's currently the most mad at Momke.
I'll tell you right now that a few facts here or there that are not correct.
I mean, I, Momke did tweet and say, yes, basically.
I don't trust Momke.
I think Momke is overly protective of his reputation by going out of his way to say it's all okay.
I haven't watched the video, but I'll say that all of this happening has been
a source of many yucks for me as well.
And it's not that I don't.
Like not from a position of like, ah, ha, ha, fuck you, Momke.
Like, you know, I don't really, I don't have like a lot of ill will towards him or anything
at this point.
Like he's had nothing to do with me for like a year and a half, almost two years.
There, it is, it is, it is Juicy Goss.
Juicy Goss is always great.
And especially when it's about people, you know, people who have been like, you know,
for me, the sheer surrealness of watching things like this happen is an endless source of joy
for me.
Like it makes me feel like this was the point of becoming famous is that I can be surrounded
with so much weird shit all the time that like people who've been to my house now have
like a fucking, you know, news articles written about them and they're in discretions.
Like, you know, all these weird historical anecdotes that all feed into each other.
And I'm in the middle of this whirlwind looking at all the stuff and going,
this is fucking insane.
This is awesome.
Maybe the difference for me is purely that this all makes me extremely uncomfortable to
be anywhere near me and I want nothing more than to be as far away from it as possible.
Like I feel uncomfortable talking about it because I don't know, like I,
a lot of the time I have like half opinions about certain things and half about other things.
And I don't want to be like seen or heard saying something that I'll later say,
actually, I don't know about that thought.
But then you saying you're like, you brought this whole thing up or like you went into it
quite a lot.
Well, I mean, I didn't want to talk about it.
I mean, I accept responsibility of broaching the topic at all.
But it was not my goal to get into any specific.
I like talking about all this stuff because you can't run away from this.
This is the world we live in.
These are the people we're surrounded with.
Well, I'm trying to be proactive and just get people to absorb this in a way that I
think is more healthy.
That's all.
I think that's good.
I like that you do that.
I think it'd be weird.
I think it'd be weird if we didn't talk about it.
It'd be like John and Aaron not talking about why the Game Grumps broke up.
I mean, that's how I felt because inevitably people are asking me about
monkey and it's like, I don't have such strong opinions that I'm going to like go
and make a video about it.
And I also don't want to individually respond to everybody on Twitter about it.
But it's like, if I have thoughts about it as I have on this podcast, like, yeah,
I think it would be weirder of me to just keep my mouth shut.
And it's like, whatever.
I used to think that I think that the era of trying to keep things private is just gone.
And that's for better or worse.
There's problems with it.
There's ups and downs.
But I've accepted the idea that we're just not in a private society anymore.
It's not the way that enough people want to operate for it to be the case.
And that's always the way.
Well, not if you're online, right?
Right.
Like, not if you're online.
But everybody's online at this point.
Even if you're not online, people could just come to your house.
I mean, not your house, but like, I don't know, take a picture of you in public,
tweet it, get it going if they want to.
It's like there was a brief period where I was kind of trying to run away a little bit from it
because it was like, and I don't want to always be like a public figure who says
absolutely everything going on in my life because it's unnecessary.
But it's like, if people are going to know things about me, that's going to happen.
There's too much information going around at all times.
Too much surveillance happening.
You're right, Digi.
I understand this idea that like privacy is dead.
It's just that, OK, when I look at this thing, what I see
is a gossip to me is a chain with a series of links.
And it's like infinitely long.
And it actually branches out.
The links connect to different.
It's like a net.
That's what makes it so interesting.
It starts at one point.
That's why it's so fun to watch.
I mean, that's fair.
That's fair.
But what I perceive is that at every single link, every one of us is an individual link
in that chain that can branch out infinitely.
And like, I think at every one of those junctures,
it's reasonable to just say like every person bears some responsibility when it comes to like
propagating misinformation or, you know, if anybody who is watching this content,
anybody who's participating in any way, you are a part of it now.
And your decisions are going to matter and you're going to be held accountable.
Including just watching it.
And you are not a private person.
You are no more so a private.
Like people always say, oh, well, he's a he's a public person, so it's different.
Motherfucker, you are all public people.
If you have an account on the internet and you're tweeting anything,
if you're posting comments on YouTube threads, you are creating content.
You are putting yourself in the public eye.
That just reinforces my my thing.
I started this whole thing off with like every tweet is a little journalistic activity,
which is why I feel comfortable bringing up the standard as, you know, related to it.
And like, look, if you want to be private, like, first of all,
the government system is not currently really protecting your privacy.
If anything, they're breaching it even harder than we are because they're getting their
tendrils into things you aren't even trying to publicly state.
So probably don't have the state on your side.
If you want to protect your privacy, it's on you.
If you don't want people to know about you, you don't tweet.
You don't go online.
You don't post your information because at this point, nobody,
no part of the social structure is trying to protect your privacy.
So the second you start participating in the game, just know you are a participant.
Expect to be held accountable for your actions.
I guess so.
Just remember, people, you can make choices.
You don't have to share that video.
If you think it's kind of fucked up what somebody did, you don't have to watch it.
And I'm aware we're humans.
We're going to be weak.
I watched it too.
So I'm part of the problem, 100% true.
You know, you don't have to bring it up on this podcast and make it a big deal among all your friends.
I did not watch it because I didn't want to have to hear that sniveling retard's voice for 45 minutes.
Oh, Mr. Meat Man.
I like it.
I do like his delivery.
Lol.
I laugh whenever he says his own name.
I laugh.
I clap.
I am a chimp.
I am a chimp with a lizard brain.
Yep.
He's got some serious branding going on.
We should go to voicemails because it's an hour.
It's going to be the Microsoft press conference.
And I got to watch the Halo Infinite reveal.
Oh, I see.
But were you going to say something first?
I had one more small thing to mention, which may or not branch off into a topic.
But I've got this app called Duolingo, which is a language learning app.
And I'm learning Hebrew for no reason.
Huh.
Whoa.
Why?
Why Hebrew?
I mean, I know you said for no reason, but why?
Well, the reason was I wanted to learn Arabic, but they didn't have it.
And that was the closest thing.
Hmm.
Because I'm thinking like...
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
I mean, that's the thing.
That's the thing I've been thinking is that culturally, in the West,
the whole Middle East is seen as the enemy.
Just in general, for your basic Joe Shmo who's like,
duh, he'll say, fuck those Muslim people.
I guess.
Yeah, it's true.
I do say that all the time.
Yeah, and it's like, there's this sort of demonization of that whole area of the world.
I kind of like the things over there.
And it's kind of a shame.
Like, if I, as a white man...
Why not Arabic?
I'd get shifty eyes.
There's a lot more Arabic speakers.
They said there was no Arabic on Duolingo.
Oh, okay, sorry.
I see, I get.
Yeah, there's no Arabic on Duolingo.
I don't know why.
Because of racism, god damn it, they hate them.
Yeah.
I mean, I would look for a thing, but learning Hebrew is good enough.
There's a Hebrew guy.
There's a guy who lives in the Israeli army in my Discord who talks about stuff.
That's cool.
And so, I'll be able to say, hello, I have the bread.
Like, I'll be able to say that soon.
You'll need a new keyboard.
Oh, I will.
Well, there's a Hebrew keyboard.
Duolingo is such a gamified version of learning.
That sounds good.
Basically, it doesn't give you a course that you have to memorize in a test.
They just give you questions.
Some of them are like, a guy speaks and you have to put the right letters in the right words
from a choice.
Sometimes there's like a word in a sentence that you have to do.
Sometimes there's a sentence you have to translate into English.
And a lot of it is like, you can infer based on what ones you've seen.
Like, there are different categories.
Like, the first three sections are like just words, simple words.
Like, mother, father, love, and stuff.
And then you go further down.
Once you've unlocked more complex systems like adjectives and concepts and greetings and stuff,
you click on one of those.
You do a lesson.
And it's basically like a 10 minute, like you're given like 10 to 20 questions.
And if you get it right, it's a little ding.
And if you get it wrong, there's a like, and then it comes back around.
And you can't complete the thing until you've got all of them right.
So if you're stuck on one, it's not like you will never learn it.
It will, you'll eventually like understand, like it'll show you what the answer is.
So you get it wrong.
And then you're like, oh, wait, that one, it means that.
So you through like trial and error, and how like language is more fun to learn, I find,
is that you come up with your own associations with the words and the symbols.
Of the other language.
So I'm recognizing without even really trying
words that, you know, in Hebrew and like the male and female versions of certain words,
I'm like, oh, that squeaky line means that I don't know what any of the letters are,
but I do know how to read certain sentences with, you know, like I've only been doing it
for a week and I can, I can recognize quite a few and it's, it's pretty cool.
That's interesting.
The way it's, the way it's structured.
That's cool.
I use something called.
It's also a free app.
So you may as well, if you, if you ever felt like learning a thing, it could be,
it could be a good like starting point, at least for reading.
I've used something called memorize for the last while, which sounds very similar.
It's sort of a gamified and obviously I use it for Japanese.
And I've been pretty lazy the last while, but I actually, I have been taking more steps
to just expose myself to more Japanese on a daily basis.
I actually, for multiple reasons, because I didn't want to deal with just like news
on Twitter and shit.
I just wanted the people I subscribed to and that's it.
So I, I set my Twitter feed to just be as if I was in Japan.
So I just get like all these updates that are just like pure Japanese shit.
And mostly it's in, it's in kanji a lot, so I can't really understand it,
but it just like from my recent dabblings into learning Japanese, everyone's been telling me
exposure on a daily basis, total exposure is the best way to go, but the more the better.
Well, that's how, well that's how Bart, well that's how Bart Simpson learned to speak French.
Indeed.
Yeah, the thing that encourages you.
Oh, that's actually a good thing people do.
They read Shonen manga because it's very simple.
It's for elementary school kids.
The people read that raw.
So eventually I will do that for sure.
Yeah, the Duolingo app has a lot of bells and whistles and jingling, jangling things,
dangling in front of your, in front of your face, such as streaks and getting bonus.
Yeah, same with memorize.
That you can, you can spend on customizing the owl.
Mine actually does cost money though, I think.
So yours is probably much smarter to use.
The only thing is like after you complete a lesson, there's like a little ad and you say
no thanks.
Oh yeah.
I don't want to subscribe, but it really hasn't become a problem and I just do it every night
before I go to bed.
Like, oh yeah, I want to keep my streak going.
Smart, that's very smart.
For no real reason, because the current, the virtual currency is pointless and I don't care
about spending on anything, but I do like having gems and numbers going up.
So like every night, every night before I go to bed, instead of, instead of watching another
45 minute YouTube video, I do some Hebrew learning and then I go to bed.
And I feel like, I feel like that's actually quite a good way to get the knowledge.
I don't think I'll ever use Hebrew, but it's just nice.
Oh, you're going to use it when they take over my dude.
It's going to be exclusive, but we're all using one of these days.
All right, let's hear some voicemails.
But yeah.
Yeah, all right.
That's cool.
Let's go to voicemails.
I'm ready.
Oh, hey, first of all, we got a little PCP theme.
So let's ramp it up while I play this PCP theme.
Go.
It's coming.
I know the theme contest is months gone, but I just want to do this rendition of the
original theme and then you guys will be like, yeah, that's cool.
We'll see about that.
Cool.
Hey, it's cool.
Yeah, I like it.
Okay, so next one while he's playing us in.
Okay.
I mean, I'm just letting, that's just background noise.
Yeah, let them do his thing.
So our first voicemail is from Dynamax Tortera Detective Pikachu.
I wish he recorded that.
All right, I'm just going to play it and I hope it stops the one that's playing now.
Okay, here we go.
Go.
I would just like to point out something real fucking quick.
All right.
You know, this is Dynamax.
It's the same guy.
Maybe.
And you know, Detective Pikachu, the movie.
Well, the fucking, the torteras.
Oh shit, you're right.
They were giant and no one's talking about it.
What?
They totally teased that shit.
The torteras are really big in the movie.
That's all I got to say.
Okay, so in Detective Pikachu, they had really big torteras.
I didn't see it.
Okay, does that mean that in Gen 1, with the anime, when we saw that giant
dragonite, well the giant dragonite or tentacle, was that Dynamaxed to my dude?
Makes sense to me.
Do you remember that episode with the giant Gengar and the giant Alakazam?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
The ancient Pokemon.
I remember the giant, I remember the giant Haunter from Electric Tale of Pikachu.
Yeah, was it giant?
The good series, the good manga series.
True, true.
Okay, anyway, shit voicemail.
Thanks for nothing.
I remember the Dynamaxed human beings from One Piece.
Oh yeah, remember that time that in one, in a filler anime of One Piece.
How do I end up with Nate, who is the one who screens the voicemail, playing a voicemail
going, wow, that was a shit voicemail.
Didn't you screen the voicemails?
Me shitting on it is part of the joke, did you?
This is high level stuff.
Nate's criteria is...
So Nate deliberately includes shitty voicemails, so he can shit on them.
I included that one so I could make the rebuttal about the huge dragonite.
That was my sole desire, that's why I included that.
By the way, okay, we gotta put out a message to our boy RiddlemyassBatman.
Okay, which is just that, he's been calling in, leaving a bunch of like,
I'm Batman, why aren't you playing my voicemail?
Listen, buddy, you gotta get it together.
We can't just be playing this stuff that's like, why aren't I on the voicemails?
And there's a surprisingly large number of people
who are calling in with this exact same complaint.
So people, every time you call in, it's judged on merit and nothing else.
Just be funny, if you don't get in, that means it was not funny enough,
and there's nothing else to be said.
So just be funny.
Unless Nate needs to make a point about dragonite, in which case...
That's correct, that's the one time that you'll get in.
Think about what opportunities can I give Nate to say things
and build your voicemail around that.
Pretty much, pretty much.
That's the key, yeah.
But also, don't make it too much about me,
because I deliberately avoid some that are like, this is for Nate.
I'm like, that's too many of those, we're out of here.
So it's a delicate balance, good luck.
Okay, let's move on.
Next one's from Garrett, the microbiology student.
Okay, good, good.
Oh wait, go, yes, here we go.
This voicemail is in regards to Nate's poopy autism question about his poopy autism.
It's not really about me though.
And why he has to eat the shit from normies to care his autism.
Eat shit, right.
And the reason why you have to eat the shit is because the bacteria in your gut is anaerobic,
so it won't survive in an atmosphere with oxygen, which basically means you can't grow
any of that bacteria on a petri dish without like a fuck ton of work.
So it ends up being a ton cheaper and easier to just wash out the shit a bit
and then put it in a pill that you can eat.
Hell yeah.
That's a pretty reasonable point, I just thought that was an interesting.
Small follow up on that.
There's been an article written on the Aspergian website about autism, I guess.
Where basically they called into question.
Really, that's what it's called?
They called into question the study.
Apparently the study is just, while it is interesting what findings it has,
it had like no control group.
They didn't really factor in a lot of different elements of what could have caused the change
other than the shit pills.
Shockingly, it wasn't the most professional study ever done.
It wasn't a great study, but there could be more studies done to eventually get more info on.
On the one hand, of course, but on the other hand, am I really going to trust a website
called the Aspergian on it to report accurately on how they're about to destroy their business?
I mean, I think we're all winners here for just having heard a story about children being fed.
Oh yeah, it's very true.
I didn't share all this because I legitimately thought.
Shit and die is real now.
Yeah, all right, that's enough.
Okay, all right, let's go on to the next one.
That's the new tagline, autism, eat shit and die.
All right, this is from your average passive listener.
Okay, go.
You guys were talking about having kids last week,
and it was basically talking about symbolic immortality,
a psychological term coined by Robert J. Lifton.
We all naturally strive for it because we're fear of death.
There's four categories, biological, children, afterlife, religion, natural,
trees, and the good shit, creative immortality.
I think all artists have that little comfort inside them
that at least something will still be there after they're dead.
Like this voicemail, for example.
I think I need a question.
So is anyone religious in the PCP?
And no matter the answer, how does religion influence religion?
Is anyone religious?
First of all, you don't necessarily need a question if your point is just good.
I mean, I'll be interested to hear it.
Yeah, it's a voicemail.
It's an order of voice question.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
I don't think any of us are religious.
I think literally none of us have any religious inclination whatsoever.
Well, no, he asked how his religion affected your child.
Oh, true.
I was raised hardcore Catholic, so.
Yeah, yeah.
Like church every week until I was 16.
Wasn't there like a hardcore anti-religion PCP or Let's Play?
I don't know if it ever got released, though.
What?
No, well, we did a religion cast,
which I think was a lot of dunking on religion in general.
Yeah, but like at that point too, I think you and Davoo
and somebody else did like a long Let's Play
where you were just like talking about your upbringings with religion.
But I don't think it got released.
I think it was.
I think like the files were corrupted or something.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't remember.
God, God wasn't having that one.
I'll say that I don't think personally for me,
I was raised generally religious.
We went to church every Sunday for a long while.
I don't think it had any particular like exceptionally bad effects on me
because I actually, despite, I'm going to say anti-theist,
I think it is bad for the world that people believe in religion.
I'm not saying that I necessarily know like the solution, but.
We went to church.
It was fine.
Nothing interesting to say on this topic.
Let's play the next question.
Okay, but that was only his final question, which was shit.
His main point about, oh, living forever.
Now on that, I want to say something.
Simbolic immortality.
I think if you're making videos,
then that's like one of the most volatile
and will probably dissolve quickly.
Yeah. I mean, how long until the server farms
are all destroyed by aliens or something?
I mean, they're not going to last that long.
I don't know. People need to keep up.
Actually, is anything digital is the same?
Kind of.
So it just depends on how long the internet survives.
I mean, anything material is the same, right?
Yeah.
There's no material that doesn't erode.
Yeah, but a bronze statue lasts longer than a bronze vinyl record.
I mean, true.
To this guy's point, though,
he said like artists are comforted
by the thought that their works will outweigh them.
But like, I mean, to an extent, share.
That's true for me. That's absolutely, I'm in this category.
Well, I mean, I get consumed by the long-term thought of,
I mean, I guess as Gabe was saying,
it's like, I'm thinking long-term,
like nothing of me will exist in a thousand years.
And that makes me kind of upset that like,
oh, I'm going to be completely forgotten.
100% chance.
Like people like Elon Musk might be remembered
if they colonize Mars successfully or something,
even if they just get it started.
But like, you guys are all, you're all,
you're all worried about nothing.
Look, it's the year is 2019.
Transhumanism.
The night, it's 2019.
So we have, we have eight years before 2027 hits
and Deus Ex happens, canon.
And we're all.
Oh yeah, it's canon.
Oh, I hope you're right.
That's true.
Oh, I'm praying for it.
I'm praying to the digital God.
I think that, you know, on Krypton in Superman lore,
incidentally, I think that those people had obtained
like scientific functional immortality.
And like the reason that Krypton went to shit
was because everyone was immortal, nothing changed.
And I'm just saying, if we get a more immortality,
I can see that happening in humanity.
And we all just eventually like just die out.
Well, all of a sudden we get firmware updates,
you know, we'll be on human OS 13.
I guess so.
And we'll finally get dark mode
and the black people will come back.
Okay, all right, let's go to the next one.
How many of these do we have?
I have to piss again.
I think there's three more.
No, four more, four more.
I can stand that, I guess.
This is I'll Die Bought on porn and dark souls.
So let's see what they have to say for us.
Go.
Hey, hooting up.
I'll die corporation voicemail bot.
The landscape of one sexuality
has better nonlinear level design than dark souls.
You start going down whatever avenues
are immediately apparent
until they suddenly interconnect
in ways you never expected,
eventually elucidating that it is all
a manifestation of something else
deep inside you wanting to be expressed
in the same way that the kiln of the first flame
was deep below the same fire
like shrine you always called home.
In other words,
there's no reason to beat your meat
when beating dark souls
has already given you all the same pleasures.
Shutting down, I'll die corporation voicemail bot.
That was incredible.
Thank you, I'll die corporation bot.
I love it and I want more.
Yeah, keep it going.
He's been doing it for a while or she,
I don't know.
Yeah, those are great.
Whatever algorithm is producing these voicemails.
Indeed, pretty advanced.
Okay, we've got white,
I think it's from Wike, W-E-I-C-H.
White, the professional furry.
Okay, and here we go.
Go.
Okay, now as a real furry,
let me lay down the law on who is
and is not a furry,
because I have authority.
Oh, we definitely got a furry voice.
Super furry voice.
And you just are a furry,
there's no denying it.
If anyone disagrees, shut up.
Now, the interesting thing is people
who may not say they are,
but have varying degrees of deniability
in that claim.
If you just kind of look at furry art,
but have no real participation in the community,
even if you have some inclinations
with your art consumption,
then you're not really a furry unless you say so.
But if you participate in furry communities,
like if you make furry art
or you talk to other furry community members as in equal,
now you kind of are a furry,
even if you don't have a fursona, pretty much.
You're maybe like diet furry.
But if you have a fursona,
pretty much in any capacity whatsoever,
especially if you call it a fursona,
then you just are a furry.
And if you say you aren't,
then you are not only a furry,
but you're also a liar, liar, liar, fur on fire.
I want to make an addendum to this.
It's unrelated about furry as an art style.
If you say furry is an art style,
that is literally the exact same thing
as saying anime is an art style.
Which is not that unfair.
Make that statement what you will, digi bro.
Yeah, I mean, it's not like anime
is overwhelmingly pretty similar.
If somebody said that as if it were objectively true,
I'd be like, no, there's a lot of exceptions.
But as a generalization, yeah,
anime tends to look a certain way.
It's very easy to identify.
Furry is the same way.
What about avatar?
I'm so confused.
They're a sort of a cut.
You could probably break down,
and maybe someone should.
There are probably schools of furry art.
Sure, at least.
There are a couple of different looks that it can add.
Just like there are schools of furry voices.
There's like a more anime-ish look.
There's like a more Disney-ish look.
There's probably others.
I mean, I feel like the reason
the furry art style rubs me the wrong way
is because I think of that as like,
oh, it's an animal, but as a human,
which is just like a type of thing.
It's like saying there's a boat art style.
Like there's an art style for drawing a boat.
All boat art style is the same, generally.
And I'm like, yeah, but you can paint a picture of a boat
and you can cray on a boat,
and you can draw a difference.
You do a 3D boat.
Abstract.
Well, yeah.
There's so many different ways to do it.
But what if culturally...
Calling it an art style is...
Well, hold on.
Yeah, I know that boats is not culturally similar.
No, no, but what if culturally,
people tended to draw boats
in a couple of broadly similar ways,
which is kind of how it is with furry art?
It's kind of like with the masculine and feminine.
I would argue that, sure,
there's a binary of people who fall in the spectrum,
but I think we can identify two focal points
of femininity generally exists
and masculinity generally exists.
And I think that the substantive arguments
are like, does that justify calling it there
because there's so much gray area?
I would argue, yes, in the same way
I would argue there is a furry art style,
but I get why people say no.
I don't think there's one furry art style.
I think there are furry art style.
It just calls on me to...
It feels like a challenge to draw an anthropomorphized animal
in a way that is in no way similar to any furry art style
and then have someone say,
oh, it's a furry art style when it's like some strange Picasso thing.
It feels like reductive of what art style is.
I definitely think it's possible to draw anthroanimals
and not have a furry art style,
but when I see furry art, I feel like I know it immediately.
Just like the voice, which is now...
That's now what I'm going on.
Like, fuck any other data.
If I hear the voice, I know you're a furry.
That's now my entire basis.
I guess we're talking about the art though.
Look at salazzle.
Like, okay, I feel like through the eyes of a furry,
salazzle is like a hot milk, just exactly the same drawing.
But like through the eyes of just a normal...
Like, I'm not even saying they're abnormal,
but like through a non-furry,
salazzle is simply like a slightly feminine lizard creature.
So it's really the eye of the beholder
that I think decides a lot of it.
I don't know, that's what I got.
Okay, let's move on.
Because this is a hot one, boys.
We got Gnoggin the Genome is calling in.
Oh, from lock stock in Gnoggin?
Indeed. Let's hear what he has to say for us.
Go.
Hello, my old chums.
Gnoggin the Genome here.
A huge fan of the gontas.
I've been listening since episode one.
I have a question for Mr. Bestman.
I understand that you're a huge fan of the Gnoblin Slayer.
And I am too.
A very important Gnome called Gnadoch Gnitler
once said 14 very famous words.
You must secure the existence of our people
and a future for all Gnome children.
Right, now then, if a Gnoblin came into your hovel,
what do you invite him inside for cream cakes
and chocolate going to drink?
Or what do you call Gnoggin the Stapho and Mr. Godwin say?
Gnoggin the Gnoblin Slayer.
This is Gnoggin the Gnome, sign him off.
Cheerio!
Boy, I'd be on that phone to the Gn-
G-G-G-Gnostapo like that.
I'd be fucking absolutely fucking Gnoblins.
Better safe than sorry with Gnoblin than sorry with say.
Well, you know, one of the untold stories of our age
that history will look back at us unfavorably for not reporting on
is the deep racial tension between the Gnoblins and the Gnomes
and they will understand that we just turned a blind eye
to the genocide and the massacre,
but hopefully we can spread awareness here.
If we don't learn from history, we're doomed to repeat it.
Exactly.
Oh, I love you, Gnoggin.
You're my hero.
Okay, let's move on.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
Charming.
I was going to play this one from Chilling Chocolate
that was about the Teen CP,
but Munchy isn't here and also it was a shit message.
There was another like, oh, please pay attention to me.
I'm the Teen CP.
Please play me on your podcast.
Listen, guys, you got to get organized.
Classic Teen, classic Teen CP tactics.
Munchy was here.
It's just a phase.
If Munchy was here, I'd at least tell them like...
Dude, that should be their slogan.
That should be their slogan.
It's just a phase.
Teen CP.
That's a good one.
Yeah, some sons, you're gonna have to try better than that.
You're gonna have to try better than that
to earn your fatherly boomer father pride.
Indeed, indeed.
Episode one is out though.
We'll let you ride the lawn mower.
Episode one and maybe episode two will be out
when you hear this on Munchy's YouTube channel.
So go check it out if you want to.
But I'm just saying, like, okay,
there's a problem with the Teen CP,
which is that there's no discord or anything
for people to be on.
So they come to the PCP one or like RFCK
because they don't know...
Like, Chilling Chocolate wants to be on,
I think is the idea,
but he doesn't know where to go to talk to you guys.
So for the love of God, get organized.
They're directionless and aimless,
but they don't know what to do.
Indeed.
Munchy, here's the solution.
Make a discord server.
It doesn't have to be Munchy.
Anyone in the Teen CP,
make a discord server and post the link
in the fucking comments or something
so we can not have to hear your shitty comments anymore,
complaining and whining and shit.
Okay.
No kids allowed.
Okay, final message.
It is Game Board Gaylord Final.
Thank God.
Okay, let's see what he's got for us today.
Go.
It is me, the Game Board Gaylord,
and I am here to inform you that I won.
I did it.
What?
I told you so.
No, come on.
All right.
Now, let's play another game.
Just kidding.
I just want to know what your favorite board game is.
That's all.
All right, thank God.
It was all a long time to get us to say
what our favorite board game is.
I like Monopoly a lot.
Oh, that's disgusting.
As I would.
Nate, everyone hates Monopoly.
I don't think you've played Monopoly recently,
or you wouldn't say.
Probably not in the last five years.
One person in the world that would love Monopoly.
No, I really like Monopoly.
When I was like 13 to never play Monopoly again,
and I've held strong to it.
So she gave me.
I win Monopoly most of the time.
I'm just saying.
That's why I like it.
The person that wins Monopoly
is just the person who lands on a good space first.
That's not crazy.
I once played like the legendary,
into the wee hours of the morning,
family Monopoly at a Christmas family gathering,
where it was me and some of my cousins and uncles.
Everyone else had gone to bed,
but I was like the last young boy there.
I was like seven or something.
And I won.
I beat everyone.
Wait, what was the game?
Family at Monopoly.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Because it went on for like seven hours,
and it was the first time in my life
that I had stayed up so late without getting tired.
I felt like a god.
But after that, I realized that I don't want to do that again.
So I never played again.
You're going to go on the high note, you know?
Shoots and ladders is fun.
Oh, my God.
You guys have the worst fucking board game ever.
Here is a great board game.
Fucking Buccaneer.
It is a pirate sailing board game
involving stealing things from treasures
from certain islands on squares on the map.
It's a game my dad played when he was young,
and he bought a version of eBay,
and we played it a few times.
And it's got these tiny plastic pirate ships,
and it's this four harbors,
and you can go and raid someone else's harbor
if you have a higher number of crew.
And the crew is like, you get them from cards,
and you can trade crew for treasures and stuff.
Really strategic, really fun, great.
Great game.
Doesn't last for hours.
That's good.
That's important.
It feels like very balanced.
Now, here comes Big Dick Tom.
He's going to be like, Katan.
I like Katan in the merely indifferent board games
that boomers play these days.
It's probably a toss-up either between
Betrayalight House on the Hill or Mansions of Madness.
They're both really fun.
I played one of those.
It's fun.
I think I played the first one with you at the time.
Yeah, we played when you guys came over that one time,
and it was a great time.
Wait, was Nate there, too?
Nate was there.
Yeah.
Huh.
Oh, the furtive Nate, so easily forgotten.
That was the trip when Nate,
they were playing board games, and he's like,
wait, I got to go talk about the analysis anarchy
and just hijack my computer.
And wait.
Wait, what?
Well, I don't remember this.
Wait, Tom, please explain that.
I don't remember what you're talking about.
Oh, god.
I remember, okay, I remember I went to your house
a couple times.
I forgot that Nate was there one time.
Yeah, Nate was there one time.
Did you?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Was this when an analysis anarchy
had just come out or something?
Yeah, this was a while ago.
It was like years ago.
Oh, it was like the first time,
and I think we were just being like, wow, what the fuck.
And you were like, you took my computer.
Like, I need to get on a Skype call
and figure out what is going on.
And we're all just like, gay.
Wait a minute.
Was the Skype call, was that when I was deciding
whether I was going to be on the show or not?
I believe so.
I believe that is what it happened.
Yeah, I think that's right.
That's when the fateful decision was made
and the timeline split between me and Ben.
Me on the light path, Ben on the dark path.
I was going, no, that's when we split
into the worst timeline when you decided
not to follow me on my journey into whatever the fuck that was.
An analysis anarchy.
Yeah, that was when it all started to go wrong.
Indeed.
And only for you.
I'm pretty good at boggle.
Boggle.
Okay, not bad.
I think I'm pretty dang good at boggle.
Yep.
You know, I try to-
Oh, wait, wait, fridge scrabble.
Fridge scrabble, fridge magnets,
where you'd write something on the fridge
and it's really funny and then someone writes a response
with the remaining letters
and then you change your thing to a different thing.
That's my favorite board game.
It's played vertically.
And there's, yeah, vertical fridge scrabble.
Vertical integration.
It doesn't matter.
It's just really funny.
Excellent.
All right, I think we're done here, folks.
That's all the board games that exist.
I have, yeah.
Hey, I wanna, before the show ends,
I wanna, I have two things to plug.
One, this week, when you hear this,
once again, another vaporette will be posted
on my website, stcomics.com.
Ben, I don't know who did that.
I loved that last, I was like,
wow, Ben's art really improved for this one.
And then I was like, oh, shit.
Oh, you mean Lauren Colt?
I believe so.
It was the newest one, the fluffy animation.
I mean, it looked great.
Yeah, that one, that one.
Lauren Colt is so...
Why did she agree to work on your lowly project?
Oh, sorry.
He, well, we did it, well, we did an art.
So I did two pages for his webcomic
and he did two pages for mine.
Why did he downgrade so savagely as Michael?
All right, all right, I get it.
Yes, I get it, yes.
Lauren Colt's art is lush
and you should all check him out on Twitter and whatever.
Well, that was the one where,
where What's Your Face Came Home and saw,
oh, maybe I shouldn't spoil it,
but the shower was involved, right?
Yeah, I don't spoil it.
No.
Oh no, it was right, it was just the room.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, your spoilers?
I'm sorry, I just want to say the art was fantastic
and I loved it.
It is, it puts me to shame.
Yeah, fair.
It's, I'm disgraced.
But don't worry, no worries about that this week
because this week's one is drawn by Munchie.
Oh, how exciting.
So no, so no, but it's like 11 pages long.
He didn't, he just made it 11 pages long for some reason,
so it's like way longer.
There's like two, right?
So that'll be up on the website.
Yeah, the others are two pages.
Well, I don't know why.
I don't know why.
He just decided to make his fucking long as hell.
Also, me and my friend John recorded a podcast.
It's called Grimp.
Episode one is out now.
What's the subject of description?
What do you talk about?
We talk about art anxiety.
It's a title, a reference to Gimp
and how it's better than Photoshop.
And for free.
Maybe.
The podcast was almost called the official Dijornos podcast.
That would have been good too.
But we chickened out.
Didn't want to get that C, so this is this letter.
You feared the long, yeah, the long-term game
had to play it safe.
My plug.
But there's chill jams.
There's chill jams in it too, so.
My plug is going to be if you're listening to the PCP,
you should also be listening to Artso Farto's
Whirling Dervish podcast.
It's the podcast that I am the most proud of,
of any podcast I've ever been involved with.
Wow.
It's pretty good.
Frankly, I don't know how you sit down.
I don't know how you sit down to nobody else involved but you.
How fit for this?
I was going to say, wait, who do you do it with?
It's a loan.
It's just me.
Well, it's not even me.
It's Artso Farto.
I'm not even a part of it.
There is Tard Wrangler May in the back though.
You're just the producer.
Oh yeah, that's true.
May is in the background as the Tard Wrangler.
She doesn't really say anything.
She's just there to make sure that.
I've been wondering, what do you think is,
like what are the stakes here that May is here to like prevent happening?
What could happen?
Maybe it's happening and you cut it out, I don't know.
Who knows?
If you go to.
I mean, I do record the, well,
Artso records the podcast standing up in his underwear.
So the whole thing is done as a standing rant,
make it in my room, in the office.
So I guess just to make sure that it doesn't become like some kind of bath salts rampage.
Okay, that's fair.
You made the analogy in, I think the second one about how the whirling dervish is like your
CPU fan trying to keep you cool so you don't.
Yeah, May is like when you just have to pull the power plug out of the wall.
Exactly.
It's too bad.
I've had to do that to computers before.
I haven't really enjoyed them incidentally.
Big fan, big fan.
Thank you.
We'll go on, Gabe.
I want to plug again, the the the punk plush Kickstarter.
It started off real, real strong, but it's slowing down.
Needs it needs another bump.
It needs, it needs you.
I'm personally invested because I pledge and if you people don't fucking make this happen,
I don't get my pump plush, fuck all of you, make it real.
Yeah, you got to, you got to share it and you got to, you got to make people become fans.
But also if you're not like willing to throw down like a big, you know, cash settle.
I will be doing like art commissions if you like my art style, if you just like want to help.
That is like a lower tier reward.
If you want to do that instead, that's a thing.
Hopefully this, this will work.
But if it doesn't, I, I'm, you know, I'm not going to be like crying, but it will be like,
you'll have like a lot of angry people who wanted the plush and they will kill you instead.
They will be the ones killing you.
You will become a target of that.
You know, you know, Gabe, I'm such a cheap asshole.
I was thinking to myself like, I've got it.
I do, I would like the plush if it was just supporting something abstract, I wouldn't do it.
But since there's a plush on the line, I was like, that's interesting.
You know what I'll do?
I'll split it with Michelle.
And then we can both like enjoy having the plush.
The problem was she had already given money.
And so she didn't want to split with me again.
And I'm not willing to go all the way myself.
So what I want, what I want to give.
Unforgivable.
I want you.
So she, so she already got one.
No, well, she didn't pledge that much.
She pledged like a lower tier thing or something, like 10 or 20 bucks or something.
Yeah, no, she, she, I think she didn't ask for a, for a reward at all.
I think, I think that's true.
Well, she just pledged, well, she just pledged like,
if she just pledged like five more bucks or whatever, then you could go half.
All you got to do, all you got to do, you just go and edit her pledge,
and then you pay the rest of it and get up to the.
Oh, okay.
See, I was going to ask if that's something that we could do.
That's what I was going to ask.
Yeah, you can edit your pledge at any time.
You can do that.
If you have, if you have a pledge currently, you can, you can double it.
You can triple it.
I won't send you more plushies unless you ask for it.
Okay.
But like, like, I mean, that's, that's still a thing that can, can be.
You remember that guy?
If you say, if you say like in the comments, so like, I'm pledging double the amount,
can I have two, I will say yes, because as long as the money is, you know, is there,
I will be able to get the product.
Okay, I got you.
I was going to, I was going to say, if that wasn't a possibility,
I was going to ask you to be like, remember that guy in the undead church,
when you ring the bell, who like absolves ones of sin, I was like,
can you please absolve Michelle of the guilt of unpledging, like personally,
so that we can repledge together and then pay for it.
But okay.
Okay.
Good.
We will edit her pledge and I'll be, I'll chip in on half of that or whatever.
Okay.
Sick.
I, I forgot to mention, yeah, this week when you hear this, uh,
vaporette is munchies vaporette.
And then next week, vapor's three drop.
Oh my God.
How exciting.
Yeah.
I can't wait.
I, I know, like, right.
I, it's so forever.
It's been fucking forever.
I'm incredibly stoked.
Uh, will it be worth it?
Yes.
Of course not.
No, nothing will be worth, nothing will be,
nothing will be worth the time it has taken, but perhaps it will be some
consolation to you and me that it finally exists.
If only then, we can all take sucker.
If only I could, I could unmute you on Twitter to get those updates,
except that I would see you just being mean to Boogie and instantly turn it off again
and not want to be anywhere near.
What the fuck?
Fuck you.
Fuck Boogie.
Boogie is a fucking coward.
I'm just saying, I don't like meanness, but okay.
Anyway, anyway.
Boogie is a fucking, oh my God.
Let's fucking go on and think about Boogie.
Let's talk about Boogie.
No, no, I gotta wait.
Wait, no, no, no.
Fade out, fade out, fade out.
I gotta include my pit.
Centrist, fensitize.
All right, all right, great.
Okay, cool.
But, but let me just get my pledge, which is just that, hey everybody,
MiaMath of a 2, uh, I was late, it's not done yet,
but it's going to be done like a day or two.
So that's exciting.
But right now, uh, well actually it'll be like a week ago for you.
You can go listen to the MiaMath of a 2 theme,
which is available on Spotify and Bandcamp.
And I think people might enjoy listening to it because it's really cool.
And Hylio did a great job.
And, uh, you can give me money for it on Bandcamp if you want to pay to download the track,
but it's also free.
So, you know, do whatever the fuck you want.
And that's real nice.
And I think it's real good.
And I'm super happy it's out.
Thanks again, Munchy for making the logo, which is beautiful.
And thanks to Hylio for making the song.
Couldn't be happier with it.
And definitive edition coming soon.
Get ready for it.
My plug is the Zoom game.
It's on Twitter.
It is the second best voted, voted the second best game of May on Newgrounds official.
I was beaten out by a shitty game that just had a girl with big tits on it.
Titties, right?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
You can't compete.
You got to give a Zoomie big tits.
That's what everyone said.
I said no flat hashtag flat lives matter.
Representing.
No, no.
This is my fucking thing.
This is my new crusade.
Fucking big titty.
Hey, oblivion fall in the comments.
Oblivion fall in the comments.
What do you say?
He was like, he was like, I can't believe all these quote unquote cowards and quote unquote
straight man.
You are all about the huge titties.
That's right.
Yeah, all you gotta do.
Oblivion fall, you're my boy.
I don't even mind that you called me a conch.
All you got to do, Tom, new character, just be the big tit character.
I'm going to have to do that.
You just have to have a nice little flat.
Also a furry.
There's a term for it that I forget.
I mean, I know it's a character when they're like wearing their shirt.
You can't see their tits, but miraculously when they open their shirt,
all of a sudden they have gigantic titties or whatever.
I don't know what the term for it is, but that could be a Zoomie still on the table.
The term for it is canon.
All right.
Let's end on a high note, people.
Think about a Zoomie's big hidden titties.
All right.
Thanks for being here.
Oh, patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
We've got like 26 fucking bonus episodes.
Go listen to them.
They're a great time.
You'll have lots of fun on the patron.
Less than that.
Getting the patron, that's for a dollar.
That's fun stuff.
And at TPCrastinators on Twitter.
Updates, releases, et cetera.
Have a good time.
Okay.
Thanks for being here.
See you next week, everybody.
Love you.
Goodbye.
Bye.
What the hell is wrong with me?