We can climb the bus right here.
Okay, we need to lighten the mood. Ready?
It doesn't matter how much you push the envelope, it'll still be stationary.
What is that?
It's a joke book. No pun intended. Vol. 2 by Will Livingston.
Let's keep going.
What did the Confederate soldiers used to eat off of?
Civilware.
What did they used to drink with?
Cups. Dixie cups.
I walked into my sister's room and tripped on a bra.
It was a booby trap.
A book just fell on my head. I only have myself to blame.
Hold on, let me read it again.
A book just fell on my head. I only have my shelf to blame.
Ruin it.
What is the leading cause of divorce in long-term marriages?
A stalemate.
That's awful.
You're awful.
Do you even understand what that means?
Nope. Doesn't matter.
Alright, I'm done. For now.
Jeff of the Mother's Basement.
Hi, hello. This is me again.
And the rebel pixel himself, Tom Oliver.
Yeah.
Alright, so guy, who do I have to fuck around here to get started on this podcast?
I've been waiting for all this time.
Let's get this thing going already.
That was some good witty dialogue right there.
What we had going right there.
Yeah, I suppose.
Well, I've seen better witty on Tuesday.
Now, let's begin this conversation.
Witty banter, what you say?
Witty, what now?
I'm comedically pretending not to understand the phrase.
Alright, I don't understand what anyone's saying right now,
but the point is, the topic of the podcast is witty, witty.
Alright, the topic of the podcast is witty banter,
and we've all got feelings about it,
but really, I think we need to take a good long time to describe exactly what each of us is thinking of.
Shall we open up Urban Dictionary and look up witty banter?
Witty banter is what the lowlifes do over and fly over country when they're not busy picking corn.
Well, okay, I looked it up on Urban Dictionary, and here's what we've got.
Even if they are ugly, the witty banter will redeem their unfortunate looks.
And here's the quote.
Alright, listen to my example here.
This is a real life usage from the Gilmore Girls.
Jake had the best witty banter yesterday.
I know it totally made me want to bone him.
This is a great jumping off point, because whoever wrote that is totally under the persuasion
that if someone can snap off a real quick witty one liner,
if someone can snap off some real cutting jpe or jab or jib or whatever it would have you,
then that's cool, and they're a cool guy and it's funny.
And if you can write someone whipping off one liners and zinging people off, snap, ice burn,
then that's good writing, and I don't think so.
I think that that is an overused thing in fiction and in writing in general,
and that it's a crutch that a lot of people use, and I don't like it.
I'm sure there's times when it's appropriate, but most of them are not.
The only kind of reminds me of, the scene that comes to my mind most of all when I think about this is,
and maybe it's a bad example, but the scene in Metal Gear Solid 4, where...
By the way, I'm Ben St. St. Cops.
Patreon.com slash Ben St.
If you enjoyed this kind of witty commentary, you can head over to Patreon.com.
If you enjoyed the couple sentences I just said, please consider supporting me.
Alright, but what I was saying was that, you know that scene in Metal Gear Solid 4
when Poop Man and Meryl are fighting for their lives at the end of the game
and they're talking about their wedding that's coming up,
while they're getting murdered by everyone around them all the time.
It was really uncomfortable, and this seems to happen a lot with this stuff,
where something really serious is going on,
and I don't know if they think that they can inject some levity into it,
when, meanwhile, Snake is crawling to his death over here,
he's being fucking cooked alive by microwaves,
well, these two are like, oh, we're gonna get such pretty dresses, boom, killed another guy,
oh, we're gonna have all the flowers, it's gonna be awesome, boom, killed five more people,
got shot in the arm.
It's, you know, it's not something you can just add slap on top of something
to just like enhance what's going on.
I mean, in Metal Gear Solid, that is kind of to an extent the point,
because Metal Gear Solid is, you know, I mean,
it's part Hideo Kojima's crazy fucking fever dream fantasy
about what's really going on in the world,
and all the secret conspiracies,
but the other thing that it is, is it's a send up of action movies, right?
Like, yeah, so that's something that they do in action movies all the time,
and it's not necessarily about like, you know, being respectful in the moment,
it's about being entertaining to the viewer.
The idea is to portray coolness that makes people really impressed,
like, these people are so excited about what they're talking about,
in an action movie.
Davoo, shut up, he's trying to say something.
In an action movie, you guys gotta turn my volume on, discord back up.
I was done talking for like five seconds
when everyone told me to shut up the stupid lab.
Yeah, yeah, okay, so what's, so the thing is, in an action movie,
violence isn't like a bad thing, violence is performance art.
So in that sense, you know, throwing wit on top of that
and trying to make it as funny and entertaining for the audience as possible,
is in service of the goal of the scene.
So like, when Arnold Schwarzenegger fucking freezes somebody to death
in Batman and Robin, and he's just like,
what killed the dinosaurs?
The eye sage, I mean, that's a terrible example,
but that's, that is, I mean, that's a great example.
I actually think that that's hilarious, but what I'm saying,
like, the things happening in that scene of Metal Gear Solid 4
are in the same sort of situation as like episode one of Star Wars,
where like, there's this big battle where all these different scenes are happening simultaneously,
and one of them is like this witty banter while they're fucking fighting.
Well meanwhile over here, Snake is fucking dying.
But that's done for the sake of juxtaposition, right?
Yeah, here's, I have not seen, I have not played Metal Gear Solid 4,
so disclaimer about that, but it sounds to me like what the scene is trying to do,
like one, it's trying to be goofy and funny in that they can have this conversation
while they're fighting for their lives ostensibly.
Also, I think the other thing maybe it's going for is that these two are like
such good and powerful super soldiers that they can have this kind of conversation
while like, Run of the Mill mooks are gunning them down, is that, is that maybe part of it?
Tell us a little about whether or not it makes sense.
You know, I'll give you the benefit of the doubt and say that's what they were going for.
Like it doesn't even take their full concentration to engage in this firefight?
Yeah, and this is like the ultimate battle of their lives,
okay, but you know what, whatever, I'll give that to you.
That's meant to be the comedic side of it, right?
Like, that's a common thing in film to juxtapose something that's goofy and light hearted
with the most serious moment of the film in order to elicit like,
in order to take people on like an emotional roller coaster and keep them engaged.
Like, I don't know if you've seen the movie Cloud Atlas,
but Cloud Atlas is effectively five different shorter movies,
each with vastly different tones and subject matters.
And one of them is basically like a British slapstick comedy
and it's got like this really goofy chase scene
where like a bunch of old people are running away from like a home
and that's juxtaposed with this super dramatic scene
where these two slaves are trying to escape from being captured
and trying to find freedom, these like clone slaves.
It's a weird movie.
I think I saw it.
And there's like a few other things and like that's,
the purpose of that is to compare and contrast
and make the funnier parts of that funnier and make the dramatic parts
of the other scenes more dramatic in comparison.
I'll give you all of that and I'll say that that is totally something
that you can do effectively, but you have to admit that there is a right way
and a wrong way to do those things.
And my only contention is that in my humble opinion,
I think Metal Gear Solid 4 did it the wrong way for that one scene.
That's all I'm saying.
I mean, Kojima is not a very good film director.
He's a terrible writer and he's not a great director.
Let me talk about a good writer
and someone who used Witty Banter in a way that I like a lot.
George R.R. Martin in Game of Thrones, right?
Yeah, okay.
I mean, in Game of Thrones, not every character engages in Witty Banter, right?
True.
Like Ned never, I think at some point Ned even thinks to himself like,
man, I can't do this sparring with words that everyone does here
and keeps landing.
It sucks and I can't do it and I hate it.
Let's just, yeah, let's just get on with what we're doing here.
Like Tyrion is this kind of snarky guy who doesn't have any respect for anyone
and just sort of will flippantly say what he thinks all the time.
And people like Varys and Littlefinger are these kind of like crafty dudes
who like engage in all these, you know, court politics and stuff
and they're always like trying to advance their station
with like a well-placed word and a whisper and whatever.
So like those kind of characters do have this sort of Witty Banter
but then other characters like Brienne is like dumb as a stump
and never could never in the books anyway.
Hey, that's misogynist.
No, in the book she's so dumb and she's also my favorite character.
She's not that dumb.
I don't remember that.
To me, she comes off as pretty dumb in the books.
Oh, doesn't George R. Martin say at some point
that she's supposed to be really dumb or something?
I don't know.
I know he called Victarian dumb as a stump.
Oh, right.
That's what it was.
But anyway, like she would never engage in that.
The Starks generally wouldn't, things like that.
So what do you get that?
Did you like the way Tyrion did it?
I'm just saying that it's appropriate in some context
but not all of them and in that series the characters are in.
Ben, maybe if I can springboard off that,
I think what you're trying to say is that like Witty Dialogue
and like Witty Banter is a character trait and not a writing crutch
because there are a lot of...
There's so many times where you can have a Witty character
but like something that I, as much as I like the MCU and shit,
everybody has Witty Banter.
It's not a character trait anymore
because like every character in those movies fucking snaps one line.
And if you want to have...
That's exactly the issue that I was trying to raise with this topic.
That is what I'm complaining about.
Whether personality traits are Witty and cool
and they do snarky things like that.
When a writer basically conflates a character
being clever with the actual script being clever.
A writer tries to show how smart they are
by giving the character smart dialogue even though it's appropriate.
One of the interesting things about the MCU
because I think overall that the MCU is well written.
By the way, I have not seen very much of the MCU.
What's the MCU?
I would say Marvel Cinematic Universe.
Marvel Cinematic Universe.
I would say that the MCU does run into that problem
with certain writers.
Joss Whedon.
He's the one.
He's the guy.
Yeah, so...
Jeff, you need the Lawsons.
I got some water here.
Saying something cough, saying something cough.
Very shade dialogue.
Hey, that's Witty dialogue.
That's pretty witty, yeah.
But yeah, Joss Whedon does that a lot.
Sometimes it works like in Buffy the Vampire Slayer
when you've got a bunch of high school kids trying to prove something.
Yeah, it makes sense for those kids to be engaging in that kind of banter.
In Firefly where the tone is cowboys.
It kind of makes sense in Cabin in the Woods.
It kind of makes sense.
But it gets exhausting when every superhero is trying to one-up each other
including Bruce Banner, who's by his very character a man of few words.
And Iron Man is the only character in that who should be really doing that all the time.
Black Widow, she's an assassin.
Yeah, and the problem with that is as soon as it blew up,
everyone started writing all the characters like that.
And it's unfortunate.
But I mean, in the main movies, or not the main movies,
I guess the side movies where each character gets their own thing,
the writing's a lot better because they're allowed to actually breathe and tell a story
as opposed to just, here's a bunch of people, we want them to bounce off the walls
and get people to give us an 8 out of 10 on IMDb or whatever.
That's all you need and you're in the clear at that point.
It gets really interesting with Captain America Civil War
because they do break away from that at some points.
And Spider-Man, who is a character who a lot of people define by his witty dialogue,
ends up being one of the most interesting characters in that movie
because of how he's written.
He's clearly trying to be witty, but he's using it as a defense mechanism
and he's pissing his pants scared and you can tell that from how he's written.
Which I've heard people say that they've interpreted that's how Spider-Man has always been.
That's why he has all that witty dialogue.
That is how Spider-Man has always been and that's why Andrew Garfield,
and that's why Andrew Garfield's fucking terrible and the Amazing Spider-Man series
can go fucking die in a fire, witty dialogue ruined that too,
in addition to fucking Mark Webb not knowing how to direct anything other than a music video.
Mark Webb.
Yeah, that's who they brought on to direct Spider-Man!
It makes sense, dude. It makes sense.
That seems like a corporate decision to me.
Ten out of ten on that one.
That seems like a corporate business meeting where they were trying to have witty dialogue,
like somebody's like, how...
Yeah, you know, like Jeff was alluding to, you know,
the corporate decisions are falling victim to witty dialogue themselves.
Holy shit, let the dude talk, man.
Yeah, I have to really get a head start with all this lag.
Man, so much lag around here.
It's worse than Sarah Palin.
So, you know...
Did he just say that?
And we hear him cut out as everybody laughs.
Like eight minutes later.
If you want to have a show where everyone is talking inappropriately,
with inappropriate levels of levity when they're all doing death-defying stunts,
you know, it's all about whether or not it makes sense for the characters.
Cowboy Bebop's a good example because the three...
All the main characters in that show are all really bad at talking about their problems
and how they feel and they don't like talking about themselves or anything seriously.
It's true.
And I think it's always been suggested that it's because they all have the same kind of personality in that regard.
That's kind of what makes them naturally team up in the first place
and the fact that they all smoke.
And there's these natural causes for the witty dialogue to happen.
Now, it's part of the story and that's what wit is all about.
We say witty.
Witty means smart, intelligent, creative.
But at some point, some witty, intelligent, creative person invented dialogue
where all the characters were taking a bunch of rhetorical jabs at one another back and forth
and everyone associated that with witty and then proceeded to copy it in a way that wasn't witty at all.
It's like if you ever listened to the...
There was... Ron Tomatoes had a show.
They had a web show where they would play a bunch of people trying to do the stereotypical film critic type of reviews
for a movie and a montage and it was all a bunch of witty dialogue.
Like, ugh, these two people didn't have very good performances.
It was about as good as a deflated balloon.
And it wasn't very witty at all.
That's cool.
So what we're saying is witty dialogue, as it stands today, is not very witty.
Sounds like you're saying that the definition has morphed a bit.
And what we perceive now is not...
I suppose I'd like to think that the origin for all these was because it was in keeping with the way that we wanted the characters to be portrayed.
But perhaps now, like with the Marvel Cinematic Universe, it's more about...
I was going to say this before, maybe audiences just like everyone to be doing that shit.
Or they've come to associate that with smart dialogue and good characters.
I think the definition now, I think, is the characters themselves thinking of themselves as witty.
I think that's the new definition.
I think it might come back to that definition that you read to us, the urban dictionary thing.
About men who need to get laid even though they're ugly using...
To an extent, that definitely works.
Look at Casey Neistat. He's married.
That came across as mean. He's a very intelligent person.
What I'm trying...
It's okay. People are ugly. It's alright.
What I'm trying to get across, though, is like...
I think maybe a lot of screenwriters and a lot of Hollywood people are just trying to create characters
that people online will say they want to fuck.
Look at the Avengers. Everyone's like, I want to fuck Chris Hemsworth.
I want to fuck Loki. I want to fuck Captain America.
I want to fuck Robert Downey. They want to fuck all those characters.
You have your Jeff Soundboard. Get working.
Oh, no!
Now everyone's going to know everyone I want to fuck!
They didn't before by watching my live streams at youtube.com.
But no, that's kind of a facetious thing.
I think it's true for certain writers.
The person Digi asked us to bring up Diablo Cody.
Diablo Cody can't write a scene where somebody doesn't have a quip about something.
When she's working with other people's characters and she's working within other script constraints,
like when she did the script revisions for the Evil Dead,
like the remake, which is one of the only good remakes,
I think we brought this up on our remakes podcast.
We did. We did.
And when she was like a guest writer for Children's Hospital,
which great show, if you guys haven't seen Children's Hospital, that's good.
But when she writes her own scripts, when she writes shit like fucking Jennifer's body,
or Juno, like it's insufferable.
It can be absolutely insufferable to hear all these, like, again, with teenagers, it kind of works.
I was going to say that the thing that I do like about it with Juno
is that you really, at least when I watched that movie,
I got the feeling that these people were really trying to act super cool,
and they totally aren't.
And like Ellen Page is totally that kind of person in that movie.
She is not cool at all, but she's really trying to act that way.
And I remember till the day I die, at the very beginning,
when she does the pregnancy test and walks up to the, what's his face from the offices up there,
and he's just like, your ego is prego.
That's the greatest line I've ever heard in any movie ever.
It is pretty good.
The problem for me with Juno is that I watched Jennifer's body after watching Juno,
and that throws in, like that movie is so bad that it throws in the question, her ability to write,
and will make you think like, was Juno really that good?
That's fair.
You know, did she just bamboozle us by getting lucky?
God.
Like the script would have been the same no matter who the characters were,
but it happens to work because they're teenagers or something.
Yeah.
Another person who has this problem is Aaron Sorkin,
who's the writer of The West Wing, The Newsroom, Social Network, a bunch of others.
I would consider him to be a great writer,
but a lot of people are put off by the fact that all of his characters
are basically always trying to save the wittiest thing in any given situation,
and a lot of them are just mouthpieces for his political views.
But if you've watched The West Wing, if you've watched The Newsroom,
the dude writes a stirring speech.
The dude can make a scene just like move you,
but to an extent, I think that his desire to impress you with,
oh, this pun that these characters came up with on the fly based on a situation that I wrote,
which doesn't make it impressive at all,
trying to impress you with that witt can take away from how good his characters actually are,
because they're well-defined and they've got a lot of depth to them,
but in the moment-to-moment thing, they come across as being a little,
ugh, this shit again, you know?
Yeah, you know, that's interesting,
and I kind of want to raise a distinction based on what DeVoo was saying before,
and what everybody's been saying.
That's like the new type of witty banter where the characters think they're really clever,
versus actually clever dialogue between characters.
So like, I'm thinking of Quentin Tarantino as the guy that comes to mind for me,
with like, in Reservoir Dogs and Pulp Fiction,
but like, the Reservoir Dogs tipping scene at the very beginning of the movie.
Oh, I actually just recently watched that first scene.
That whole first scene is brilliant.
That is like my favorite movie of all time.
To sound like natural dialogue,
but condensed and compressed just enough to make it perfect.
Right.
Yeah, it's witty.
I mean, the guy writing it's witty.
What makes that so witty?
And the characters themselves are also witty.
Everyone is witty.
The writer and the characters are all doing a great job.
That's what I'm saying, because the thing is, in the scene,
he's making an actually fairly persuasive argument as to why tipping is bullshit,
and you shouldn't do, I mean, obviously, you know,
people are not even going to agree.
This is this character's interpretation of what tipping is,
which obviously comes from, you know, some element down in Tarantino
that he's had this thought that tipping is kind of retarded,
and it's being expressed with these characters,
and they're all relating to it in a reasonable way.
And it's totally good.
And my favorite thing about that scene is that Mr. Orange is like,
you know what, I'm convinced.
It's giving me my dollar back.
I'm not tipping anymore.
Like, he convinces another character using this real life argument,
and that's real wit.
And I'm a little bit convinced by that too.
That's a real wit.
I already had that guy's position.
I mean, I do tip, but I totally agree with his philosophy going into it even.
Yeah, man.
The way that like characters are walking to the scene later on,
and like they have to, because there's a part where like the older guy
comes back into the scene later on,
and they have to like repeat some of the information.
What do you mean you don't, Tim?
Yeah, but it's doing just such a way to where it's even more funny
to hear it all over again.
It's great stuff.
I feel like Tarantino, he, his dialogue is, has wit to it,
but that's because he makes every scene like about something
as opposed to just being about two characters bouncing off of each other.
You know another great example of this is, is that scene in,
I forget the movie.
He wrote like one scene for this movie.
God, I can't remember the name.
But basically there's this speech where, fuck, what's his name?
Christopher Walken is, he's like a mob boss,
and he's, you know, you know the one I'm talking about
where he calls him an eggplant?
And he just, he explains to this guy who's like a Sicilian mobster
that like Sicilians, like Sicilian women were raped by like the Moors,
who were black, who took over Sicily for a time,
and that's why Sicilians now have dark hair.
And he's just like, what I'm saying is you're a nigger.
Like he's just like, he builds up to this like,
slandering like his bloodline and shit.
But it's so funny.
And like this whole speech goes in a huge tangent about like the history of Sicily,
and like all that's happening is that he's telling this guy to fuck off
and that he's not going to do what he wants.
But it's hilarious, the way that he does that through this big story
that's historically accurate.
That kind of reminds me of that scene in Hateful Eight
where Samuel L. Jackson tells that long story
about horribly torturing and murdering this kid
and cuts out of it with him being like,
yep, he had my big black dingus in his mouth.
That was a fantastic movie and a fantastic scene.
I don't know if I'd call it fantastic.
It had its perks, I guess.
I quite enjoy all of Tarantino's movies, except for Death Proof,
because I haven't seen that one.
That's his half of Grindhouse, and it's not great.
Planet Terror is a lot better.
I think Robert Rodriguez is just a lot better at doing schlock.
But anyway, you look at pretty much any dialogue exchange
in any of his films, and there's something going on
that's building up the characters,
and their wit always relates to who they are as a person.
He frequently plays witty characters off against dumber characters
who are also morally more in the right than them.
If you look at, say, In Glorious Bastards, fantastic movie,
the first scene of that movie is one of the greatest opening scenes
in any movie ever, and just that conversation
between Christoph Waltz and the farmer,
where he's saying all of this witty shit,
and the farmer's just sort of being meek
because of the position that he's in,
and also he's not hyper-educated,
but at the same time, you're relating more to the farmer's position,
and it's less like, oh, look how clever this character is,
although he is being clever.
It's more like, look at this asshole, right?
Look at how clever this guy wants us to think.
He's got so much power over this guy, intellectually, politically.
He's got every advantage over the guy.
So you kind of feel like, damn, this guy's the coolest.
I want to be with this guy.
That's the reversal of the usual,
or of the trap that I think two witty banter can fall into,
wherein have you guys seen that it's a comic,
but it's like a parody of social issue comics,
where there's two characters talking,
and one guy, he's kind of a smart, nerd-looking guy,
and the other is this sort of crudely drawn, big, yell-y guy,
and the little glasses guy is like, I have this opinion,
and the other's like, I disagree, and I hate you.
And then the glasses guy's like, I keep my cool,
and I'm the bigger man, and the other guy's like, not me,
I'm so fucking crazy.
The first panel is the smart guy being like,
I have this opinion, which I share with the author of this comic.
And the other guy's like, I have this alternate opinion,
that is contrary.
So they're basically just like completely straw manning
the other guy, the other arguments.
And yeah, you see that all the time.
You see that all the time in web comics and stuff.
You make a character that is arguing.
That's all of Tumblr, basically.
You make a character that you agree with,
and that you want the audience to agree with,
and then you have him try to look cool, and be cool,
and get one over on the enemy,
and say something that really cuts the meat that the other guy
obviously has no rebuttal for.
You know what the perfect example this is?
The author didn't think of what a reasonable rebuttal would be.
Are you thinking of Brian Griffin from Family Guy?
Because he's exactly that character.
But I mean, Brian Griffin is supposed to be full of shit,
because he's the stand-in for Seth MacFarlane.
And everybody who writes that show
uses Brian to make fun of what an asshole Seth MacFarlane is.
The episode where Brian tries to be a stand-up comedian,
for instance, is all about how shitty a stand-up comedian
Seth MacFarlane is.
Any time that Brian expresses a political opinion
like an asshole, that's Seth MacFarlane.
Right, that's true.
But yeah, the thing that those Tumblr comics remind me of
is fucking the Mac versus PC ads,
and how those made me want to buy a PC.
Oh yeah.
Because fuck Mac.
Yeah.
I always liked the PC guy better anyway.
Fuck that hipster asshole Mac.
Exactly, he's like this down to earth.
Are you guys familiar with the response ads that Microsoft did?
I don't know, maybe.
They just showed a bunch of people who own PCs
going off being cool people living their real lives
that don't have anything to do with computers.
And they're like,
Bravo, Microsoft, good job.
Exactly.
I remember people hated those commercials, too.
Like the tech sphere,
because I have to go on tech blogs all the time,
and everyone's like, these commercials are so cool.
And then the PC ones came out,
and they were so much more subtle and clever in response.
And everyone's like, these are gay.
They don't even show the computer.
Subtle and clever.
That only should apply to Whitty Banter,
but also PC users.
Meanwhile, Microsoft did earlier on
have an ad campaign that was very snarky.
Whitty Banter's become snarky banter.
Right.
Because Microsoft also had an ad campaign
that was very snarky from earlier on
during the height,
down the peak of all the hatred delivered at Vista
before Windows 7 came out.
I guess Microsoft wanted to come out with a campaign
to convince people that Vista didn't suck that much.
And from what I've heard from tech people,
I heard it was mostly like a hardware issue
on the part of Gateway and Walmart,
but I don't know.
But Microsoft had these ads where they had real-life
non-actors come in
to try out the new,
secretly fake Windows operating system
known as Windows Mojave.
And they interviewed people asking them
what they thought of Vista,
and everyone said, oh, Vista sucks.
Well, I'm a normal dumb person.
I think this sucks.
Okay, now let's try Windows Mojave.
And they tried it, and like, this is great.
I used it for five minutes, and I think it's really great.
I'm an unpaid non-actor person, real-life guy.
How much do you like Windows Mojave?
I love it.
Well, guess what?
Windows Mojave is Windows Vista
with a different name on top.
Oh, my God.
She was so wrong.
It's like, Windows Vista, you're an idiot.
Buy our products.
Like, who the heck exactly convinced?
Oh, that's great.
Vista, you're an idiot.
So, like, they pour it.
Oh, my God.
That's the meaning.
It doesn't say that.
Go on, Ben.
That's the meaning of it.
Like, they poured two...
Yeah.
They poured two tall, cool, refreshing glasses
of Windows Cola, and you drank one of each,
and then they asked you which one tasted better,
and they said, oh, this one.
Yeah.
This Cola is Mojave.
That is, like, a proven fact, though.
Like, people have certain biases.
There's a great episode of Penn and Teller's bullshit
where they're talking about bottled water,
and they go to a fancy restaurant,
and they have this guy be, like, the water steward,
and he, like, brings out all these different samples
of bottled water and, like, boxy bottles
and circular bottles and all these fancy bottles,
and, like, he tells them, oh, this is from the mountains
of the Himalayas, this is from such and such,
this is from such and such.
They drink it, and it's like, oh, that's got a very...
it's got sort of a metallic aftertaste.
Ooh, that's kind of minty, you know,
they're, like, making all these comments,
and then they just, they take them around to the back
where they've got Teller's just there
with a garden hose pouring water into all these fucking bottles.
They did that with food, too.
Fantastic.
They brought this back into a restaurant,
and they started serving them, like, Taco Bell
and, like, Walmart 99-cent shit,
and the same guy came out and, like,
trying to make it look all fancy,
and then tell them it was, like, this really expensive shit,
and they were all like, this is fantastic.
And, you know...
Presentation matters a lot.
True, true.
That reminds me of the one issue
in Biggest Problem in the Universe.
Most of the time I agreed with Dick,
but the one thing that I was totally on Maddox's side about
was his thing about expensive steak.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, expensive steak.
Dick Masterson swears that, like,
paying, like, $60 for a steak is, like...
I remember that.
It's just not comparable to whatever...
Or, like, $100 for a steak.
You know, Maddox kind of conceded.
He swears that there's some real tangible difference
by a really expensive steak.
There is. There is.
I've...
I mean, like, I've been wind and dined
at fancy restaurants as a member of the press,
and believe me when I say
that a really succulent cut of steak
that's prepared well is a lot better
than what you're gonna get.
Well, hang on.
How much of that is in the prepared part?
You know, how much of that comes into the preparation
and the presentation and the tenderizing
and all that stuff?
I think, like, 50%.
But, I mean, again,
that's what you're paying for at a fancy restaurant
is a chef who knows how to do that well
in addition to great ingredients.
But there's only...
There's only so good a steak can be.
Right? There's gotta be some point in which
paying more for a steak can no longer...
Oh, yeah.
I'm just saying, I went to the House of Prime Rib
in San Francisco,
which is like an $80 plate restaurant
where they only serve prime rib,
and I fucking came in my pants.
I came in my pants
in front of business people.
In front of God, Jesus, and the bear,
he came in his pants.
I came in my pants.
It was delicious.
It's one of the...
There was an...
There reminds me of an incredible drill tweet
from like a week ago,
where he says, like, yeah,
a pamphlet labeled MRA shit
comes tumbling out of my pocket
during my weekly Wild Wings J.O. session,
costing me the yo-play deal.
Drill's a legend, man.
Shout out to Drill.
I fucking love Drill so much.
Holy shit.
We're way off topic, man.
Yeah, we've gotten drastically off topic.
We can kind of bring the idea here
back to our witty banter topic,
which was, in fact, our topic,
in that it's...
The Wild Wings J.O. session.
It's not about...
You can't just dress up fancy shit.
Like, no matter how good
or how much action is going on in your movie...
Nice, silky smooth segue.
Yeah, thank you.
No matter how many billions you've spent
on making your scene look professional,
like in all your Avengers shit,
it's not going to make a lick of difference.
It's not going to impress people who actually care
about good dialogue and good characters.
Let me dial back to a specific example.
This was the thing that I think I was thinking of
when I suggested this topic.
And it's a webcomic that I don't hate it,
but I definitely don't like it either.
Well, I mean, you hate it because it's not yours.
It's taken away from your market share.
That's true.
That's absolutely true.
But...
Alright, so it's called Dumbing of Age,
and it's like a daily...
Yeah?
Okay, I guess you got an opinion.
It's like a daily gag strip,
but it also tells a semi-serious dramatic story
about a bunch of college freshmen fucking around.
I don't know.
It's fine and all,
but I really think that the structure of it
takes away from it because it's a dramatic story,
but it's told as these daily gags.
And so every...
Not everyone, but most of the beats
have to end with the joke.
So these characters' dramatic lives
are just punctuated by an endless series
of goofy gags
and snarky comebacks.
Yes, and one line is...
I'm looking at one right now
where the religious girl is talking to her gay friend
and she's just had a boyfriend
because he's dating her as a beard, whatever,
and she's realized that she can't keep doing this to him.
And she's like,
no, we've got to stop this.
And she says,
it's not right for us to be together.
You got to go back where you belong now
with your own kind.
Get out of here.
I don't need you anymore.
And then the boyfriend kind of
does a snarky expression and goes,
is that from Harry and the Henderson's?
Turns out this dramatic scene
is being undercut by some
goofy old movie reference
where he's got to let his pet dog
go for a while or something.
And I don't like it when this happens.
I think it is a disservice.
I'm pretty sure that they toss a gag
into that within two comics
of the scene where one of the characters
almost gets raped.
They do.
They have all these gag.
And a character will say something snarky
and nasty at the end of a panel,
but it doesn't necessarily disrupt the story.
You would expect someone to have
some reaction or response,
but usually the next strip just starts up
without any mention of it.
Not all the time, but a lot of the time.
This guy also does that fucking Tumblr thing
where every single character he disagrees with
is painted as basically Satan.
There's some of that.
I've been keeping up with it.
I don't know why.
You know how you get into a habit of
checking back with a webcomic after a while
and you just do it instinctually?
When you've read so much of it,
you can't stop reading it.
There's this character now
who's hyper religious
and she's trying to run
the trans girl
who lives in their dorm out of the dorm
by blackmailing the super,
which of course involves a lot of stupid
Mickey Mouse gags and shit.
She's the religious stand-in
compared to the other character
who it's Joyce who's heavily implied
is completely losing all of her faith in God
because her best friend's gay.
Yeah, that's her arc, right?
Her arc is she's losing her faith
and becoming a better person as a result.
Because she's not religious anymore.
It's so heavy-handed.
Part of the problem
is that this comic is from the guy
who wrote Short Pact.
Yeah, he does a lot.
He's very prolific.
He's very prolific,
and all of his comics involve the same characters
in different sort of situations
because he's never come up with a new character
in like 15 fucking years.
Yeah, that's weird.
It's weird, it's like the same characters later
after they've gotten married and had a kid or whatever.
Yeah, and his dialogue
isn't even good?
It's not.
But he's really trying to be clever
and get off gags.
He makes like,
okay, there was one I just read where
a girl at a social-
she's at church and she tears off her dress
and she goes, was that a Taraway dress?
And she replies,
is a Tara what you say?
That's a Simpsons joke.
That is just a straight up fucking ripped off from Homer Simpson.
Yo, I'm looking at that comic right now, Ben,
and it's pretty hot. That's all I've got to say about it.
Oh, he draws porn.
He draws porn.
He draws his own characters.
He canonically draws porn scenes.
Well, so does the greatest comic artist of all time,
Christian Westerchild, but we don't have that
against him to do it.
No, but this is bad porn.
In the comic itself,
characters will hook up and it'll skip to the next day,
but then he'll go and actually draw the section
and post it on Slipshine.com.
You can go to Slipshine.com
and buy that comic right now.
Things are gonna get slippery.
But the best thing about those
the best thing
about those comics
is when fucking
4chan gets a hold of them
and edits them together.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Oh, my God.
You see, that's where the magic comes in.
I don't want to get into a whole thing about this,
but I have really strong
but conflicted feelings
about creators like that who draw porn
of their own creations like that.
Really?
It really ties me up in knots.
I know I would.
I really hate it, but I really
Yeah, we know you would.
I really feel weird about it.
Is that so?
You know, webcomics.
But I also feel bad for feeling weird about it.
Webcomics.
I know a webcomic
that does not have snarky witty dialogue
is Cucumber Quest,
the only webcomic I've ever read
and it's still going
and all the characters
except for the main character
are kind of dumb
or not self-aware
or really impulsive and irrational
in hilarious ways.
The main character plays the straight man
to all of them, but he's not that strong-willed
so he just gets swept away by all of them
but he's always trying
to be like, wait, come on, that's a totally stupid decision.
No!
And it's hilarious.
The titular cucumber.
It's very relatable to any situation
you've been in in your life
when you were making a stupid decision
and no one was listening to you
but hey, it goes deeper than that
because as the series has been going on
it's been starting to come into focus
it's starting to be clear
that all the impulsive actions
of all the characters turns out to be
accidentally or unintentionally
more along the lines of what you actually
the point is he's not all right
it turns out that the actions that everyone has been taking
has a lot more
logic behind it than it may seem
at first and it's a nice balance
of, oh man
I was trying to say that
I was trying to get this point in for like 20 minutes
and the longer it sits in my mind
the more inarticulate it gets
my dialogue is not witty at all
so I think what the show
is what the comic is alluding to
is that the rational
thinking of the main character
in combination with the more
impulsive actions of all the other characters
put together
well whatever
the podcast listeners are going to be able to hear
in the podcast I'll be able to hear them
right
so it seems like
it's going to be the rational thinking of the main character
in tandem
with the more impulsive thinking of all the other characters
is going to lead the story
to a successful conclusion
and that's the kind of more humble
writing that I'm a fan of
like in the Lego movie where it has all of these creative characters
the ones you can just build
anything against the instructions
and at first you're like oh these are obviously the savants
they're the only people who can break
the system and be cool and awesome
and obviously all the people writing the movie
and making the movie are all fancy themselves
as the creative types but
toward the end it starts to suggest
that just being a wild creative person
isn't very good you got to be more
rational than that
and so the movie shows you got to have both
types it's a writer
sitting down writing a story
about how they're not the answer
and the solution to everyone's problems
isn't that interesting
now that is with
by do say so myself
wait what
what movie was that?
the Lego movie
the Lego movie yeah
cool
yeah go on Ben
okay
well first let me just make a side note
that control alt delete
is the ultimate webcomic
full of snarky dial
and two clever by half
bullshit
by the way
is also the sound of that face that they all make
that's true
that's totally true
the only one that I feel is a little bit more
of a shame is
XKCD which is inundated with clever
bullshit that I hate
and kind of ruins I can't read it much
anymore
sometimes the tone of XKCD
is really off
but sometimes it's legitimately clever
it lacks good punchlines
it can be a really clever comic
I love the math stuff
I much prefer Saturday morning breakfast cereal
and
I hate Saturday morning breakfast cereal
I hate cannot stand that
that's a fight for another day
I know I'm in the minority
and I really liked amazing
the power powers in gun show
before they stopped doing things
gun show is great
what was I talking about before you mentioned
XKCD
XKCD can be funny
but I don't think the dialogue is ever funny
I don't think the dialogue itself
is ever clever in a good way
I agree
the dialogue is never amazing
it's got really
snarky sometimes
I'm looking at some of control alt delete
and I'm immediately remembering
why I don't read any webcomics
it's because
you run out of jokes immediately
I tried to do a webcomic back when I was 16
I was going to do it
twice a week
I ran out of jokes in a week and a half
and I gave up like all webcomic artists should
just resort to random violence
I tried two webcomics
back in the day
but those more fell apart
because art is hard
and finding artists to do shit for you is hard
yeah
I
I wrote some good dialogue
I'm just going to say I wrote some pretty good dialogue
oh sure
maybe
statistically someone had to
I actually write a lot of stuff
I've got strong opinions
on the flip side of this
which is a whole bunch of people
complain whenever characters
are witty in anything
and they're like oh that's not realistic
and what they seem to want is
what we're doing now
the back and forth where everybody's
stumbling over their words and sounding like idiots
um
and that's
let me defend that position
because if characters are so
clever and so witty and have such great
good liners that it's
realistic and strains credulity
I think that's bad
I think that's bad too
witty dialogue in real life
I think that can be a legitimate
in real life battles
real life deathifying situations
can sometimes have witty dialogue
there was some sergeant or whoever who said
alright man there's two types of men
on this battlefield those who are dead
and those who are going to be move out
and that was spoken on Normandy
as it was going on
there was a couple of them who got a good chuckle
right before they got shot
right before they got a bullet to the neck
I don't think
that realism
is really ever
the goal
in creating a work of fiction
the goal is verisimilitude
the goal is believability
not realism
and
to an extent
if they're too witty that takes away
from it but to the same extent
if people are stumbling over their words
and using lots of filler words that sounds awkward
that's not something people want to watch
and that sounds fake in its own way
like a real
a real conversation
not improvised like somebody who
took all of this dialogue
and made people like all of what we're saying right now
somebody who took that and made somebody
rehearse it and deliver it
that would sound more fake
than if they cut out all of the fluff bits
and only
hit the salient points
and didn't have us dancing around the same points over and over again
and just had us
get to what we wanted to say
on the subject of
like you said, not going for realism
necessarily but going for believability
I agree with that and I like that
and I think that Tyrion and Game of Thrones
is a really great example
like his comebacks and stuff
are maybe
unrealistically good sometimes
but it's okay when he does it because everyone else
because he's
all the times he does stuff like that
establish him as being generally smarter
than the people around him
so when he is making one-liners
and being like too clever by half
it's kind of okay because you know
that he is this like larger than life
smarter than the people around him
dude
so even though it's not necessarily realistic when he does it
it works
that's what I have to say about that
haha
I was just reading some of these
SMBC comics
and noticing
the thing about SMBC is that
it's all the same
it all feels like the same joke
it's all some like
it's some science fiction
or like economic or scientific
economic was a lot of him yeah
his social concept
and then he just kind of presents it
and has like a kid
be like but dad
why don't we just you know
economic thing and the dad is like
no son because
you know other economic thing
take into its logical extreme
that's exactly the one I just read
since he became a dad
that's certainly more and more true
like he's
my issue is not that it's all about dads
and their kids it's just that
they all have the same like
cadence
wish fulfillment stuff for him though
that's like here's how I'd fuck with my kid
you know
if this situation came out
oh yeah every father just wants to fuck his kid
I'm with you brother
that's not what he said
haha
fuck god damn it
on
okay on the subject
of witty banter and someone getting off
one liners
I heard like a brief snippet of an interview
with Steven Fry the other day
and someone asked him
about the differences between
British comedy and American comedy
and what he said was interesting
and I'm gonna try and remember it
and I hope I don't completely butcher it
I don't think I remember it exactly but I'll try
and he said like American comedy
is very
focused on like the comedian is
like the hero and the comedian is smarter
than everyone else
and like you know kind of
gives them up for the fools that they are
whereas the British
comedian is the fool
and like life just shits on him
so interesting that is
yeah I think
I'm gonna try the example
I think the example he gave was like
if someone is playing a guitar
badly an American comic
might come and like smash the guitar
and everyone would go haha that's what I wanted
to do
he says what we're all thinking or whatever
the comedian would be the guitar player
who gets his guitar smashed
by some dick
yeah
so there's a thing I guess maybe
the witty banter
that irks me so much
is kind of an American thing
or like an America centric thing
could be it does feel that way
now that you mention it
did someone just leave
his audio is fucking up so he's
oh well I guess that's
is it as good a time as any to end?
probably
we've only been going for like 50 minutes
but I'm pretty comfortable with that
I will say before we close out
despite all of that
everything that we just said
there are times when I enjoy
and list witty banter as a guilty pleasure
sometimes
why don't you give some examples
of witty banter done
you know that's a good idea
I've been complaining about the concept a lot
although I acknowledge that it can be done well
well how about like anything
in the Avengers movies if you like those
I fucking love the entire MCU
I like Joss Whedon's writing
the Avengers is fun
that's the whole thing
I can recognize that it's stupid
but in the moment it's just like
I like it
I'm not a big fan
I haven't seen any of the Avengers movies
but I imagine people don't really watch them
for like intense character
development or stuff like that
I don't know
they watch the side movies
for that they watch the Avengers
for the big third act
climax to every single
other movie in the entire
franchise
that's what the crossover movies are
so there's no character development in those
there can't be
and it may still be guilty
of this
it may still be guilty of just making all the characters witty
for the sake of it but nobody seems to really give a shit
so you know at the end of the day
what really matters is if people are enjoying themselves
I mean
you know in a monetary sense so
fuck it
wait enjoying themselves in a monetary sense
no no they're enjoying themselves and
like the people enjoy the movie
so they're willing to go see it and they don't care
if the characters are consistent or any of that
whatever
I think that truly witty
not quote unquote witty
banter or dialogue
can only happen
when it's occurring in a way that's consistent
with like strong character
development and characterization
and if it's like
a witty line that's just
in there to be witty and doesn't
serve the purpose of the narrative
or the character or whatever
is bad it doesn't matter how witty it is
it's bad and it shouldn't be there
if it doesn't mesh
with everything else that should be going on in the scene
yeah like something like where
Sheldon walks up to Penny's door and goes
knock knock knock Penny
she opens door and she is a Penny
that's witty dialogue
that's real witty
that's the kind of thing I want to see
alright anyone have anything else
or shall we end it now
let's end it now
okay everybody
thanks for watching we'll be back next week
hope you enjoyed we'll see you later
bye
I'm an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
don't wanna do it
what the hell is wrong with me
I'm supposed to
be making money
I'm
supposed to be creating
creating
funny things
that the people
gladly will pay
for artistic
genius that's what
they came for
instead I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why
there's no heat and holes
in the ceiling
yeah it's
right the burden
it's a hard knock life
being a genius