Hello everybody and welcome to a Pro Crastinators Podcast. Nate's not with us this week for the
first time, but that's okay because we've got a special guest, friend of the show, Mr. Black
and Platinum himself, Nino. Hey, fuck all your, fuck all your favorites. We're SJWing the fucker
of the PCP. You people had too many white people, not enough PLC representatives. I've come here
to black up everything with my negronus, also the fact that I'm with my negronus. Yes, expect
this podcast to become 30% more urban and hip. You know, the demographics want more hip. We're
all just going to start rapping right in the middle of this one. We're all just going to start rapping.
Yeah. All right. Yeah, it's true. Me and Tom are the only true white people here. We don't rap.
I'm Digi Bro and I've also got with me Ben Saint of Patreon. Ben Saint of Patreon.com
and Tommy Oliver. Tommy Oliver was originally in this podcast, but his audio file got corrupted
and therefore I had to try to edit him out of it entirely. So if at any point it seems like the
conversation jumps around really strangely, that's because I was editing around Tom. Sorry if it's
weird. I forgot to plug my channel. Okay, guys, you can follow me at Anime Editorial Nino,
you know, N-I-N-O-U-H. Go watch my YouTube video. I'm not just a rapper and a black person. I actually
do stuff on YouTube. Yeah. They wouldn't have brought me on for any other reason. They brought
me on because they knew me and they knew that I did YouTube stuff. All right, thank you. No,
we needed someone to do a halftime show in the middle of the podcast. So today's topic, which
Nino suggested. Second topic I've suggested, by the way. Yeah, you suggested last week's,
or the one that was released last week. Yeah. This topic is, you introduce it.
Well, basically, the topic is our internet origin story. The story of how everyone on this podcast
or the people who are currently doing the podcast became familiar with the internet because if,
you know, everyone, if you're watching this, obviously, you know how to use the fucking
internet. Everyone has their own really intimate and personal way they use it. For example, let
me take you through how I wake up in the morning. Like, I'll get, I'll talk about how I've got to
this point, but I'll take you through how I wake up in the morning and use the internet. When I
wake up, I usually close out the tabs of N-Hentai I used the night before. I open up a new tab of
to check out all of the stuff, you know, to check out all the gaming news that is or isn't happening.
I go on 4chan, probably look at a few shitposts. I go on Twitter to see if anyone's been calling
me out today. And then I go into my discord and I start talking shit with all my friends.
That's how, that's how I use the internet right now. And everyone else has that you,
watching this, you have your own, the life of a troll. It's like some life story.
We've all got our, we've all got our own little internet fingerprint. We've all got a little,
a little internet snowflake, a little fractal spiral, spiral, you know, life, life pattern
of internet usage. Yeah. And basically, and basically the point of this podcast is now I've
shown, I've talked a little bit about where I am with how I use the internet. And this podcast
is how everybody got, got to where they are, how we got to this point, how we learned to torrent
stuff, how we learned to, how we learned to watch and watch anime online and stuff. Everybody
has a really interesting story. And I feel like everybody has a really cool way to express it.
So who wants to go first? Oh man. I feel like everybody, I feel like everybody on this podcast
has new grounds in their story at some point. No, not me. You'll be surprised. I definitely was,
I definitely was on new grounds for a while. I avoided new grounds like the plague because
as I understood it, that was the place where there were dicks. Oh boy. Like literal dicks.
For me growing up, I was like, all the seedy side of the internet, like I was afraid of.
Oh, you want to know, you want to know none of that. You want it to be all pure and just...
Well, I grew up, I grew up pretty sheltered from like both like violence and sex stuff. Like,
not out of my parents like actively sheltering me, but it was more like they kind of like,
I was very like, if my parents told me something was bad, my instinct was not to then seek it out.
It was to go, oh, it's bad. Okay. And then not look at it, you know. It's like, I'd never looked at
like stuff that my parents kind of said like, oh, this isn't for you. This is for adults. And I'm
like, oh, well, I'm not an adult. I'm a kid. I'm not going to look at that. I mean, I discovered
4chan and new grounds specifically because people told me they were terrible places full of terrible
things, which made me go seek after them. Yeah, I avoided them forever. I've only been on new grounds
like two or three times just to look at like Egoraptor's profile when I became a fan of him later.
You got some, there are some great, there are some legitimately great flash games on there. There
are a couple of real masters. Oh, you know what? I played Endeavor. Oh, I fucking love Endeavor,
dude. Holy shit. I fucking love Endeavor. Oh my god, I can't believe somebody else knows Endeavor.
Ben, we've talked about it before. I can't remember any of the names of them. I can't remember
any of the actual names of the games, but I played pretty much every possible side-scrolling action
game and every possible dating sim that new grounds had to offer, every single one of them,
all of them. I'm younger than all of you guys, so I found it particularly early when I was like
seven years old, but I'll get to my story. Tom, continue yours. Well, yeah, I want to know, Tom,
how did you find new grounds to end up with your... No, Jack's blade is a huge digi. Digi is a... Well,
no. Oh, no, no, no, no. A barometer. Are you going to say I'm a nigg whisperer? Exactly. I was about
to say, no, no, no. What I was about to say was, if you want to know what black people like,
measure up to what Digi likes to a certain degree, because he has so many nigger tendencies for a
white person, it's not even funny. I have, through talking to Digi, the nigger tendencies I've picked
up in him, he's one of the only people in the anime community next to Lou from Lou Talks Anime
that I can just talk to about hip hop for hours. We're just talking yesterday about a bunch of
rappers. Who's the one you recommended, Cakes to Kill Out? Yeah, we're just talking about a bunch
of rappers yesterday. I was telling him how YG is the bad end of Good Kid Mad City and Kendrick
is the true end. You know, but I feel like Lou is into like, white people rap music though,
because every time he recommends me something, it's always like a rap rock song, and I'm always like,
He's a fan of a lot of old school battle rap as well, so he is part of that scene as well.
I don't want to get too much into the rap stuff, so I'll get back to your internet story.
I gotta say, I only have a brief story for that period, because I also had Dial Up up until
2006, but I just didn't really know about internet video or downloading until around the time that
I got broadband or whatever. The only internet video I remember having that experience with,
of loading it all day, was AMV Hell 3, which is an hour-long AMV thing that I'm sure you've all
probably seen parts of at least. It was really big in the early 2000s, and back then the AMV
community was mostly file sharing stuff. People would make AMVs and then torrent them back and
forth, or whatever the old peer-to-peer them, or whatever. I guess that's what torrenting is?
Yeah, like Lime Wire. And so that's how AMVs were before YouTube, and then there was these AMV
Hell compilations, and AMV Hell 3 was this giant, epic, collaborative effort between all these
different people. It was an hour-long, and I don't remember what streaming host it used,
but it was available for streaming online, and I've watched it, and it would be like
me and Victor would watch it, and we watched it multiple times this way, and it would just be
this all-night endeavor, because you could load enough. Each joke was about 30 seconds long,
so you could basically pause the video and sit there for two or three minutes, and then maybe
play a little bit of that joke, and it would be just enough that you could get a laugh and then
wait some more, and it was literally all night. It would take to watch AMV Hell 3,
but it was so fucking good that we've fucking dealt with it.
I remember lying in bed on the weekends and waiting until I thought that my parents would be
asleep, so I could sneak downstairs and turn on my fucking dial-up internet and let the connect
the internet and hope that the fucking loudass beat it, didn't wake up my parents so that I could
get on the internet and jack it to pornography. That's my internet story.
Okay, the thing is with the whole issue of internet speed, because time progresses and
technology gets better, so internet speed is definitely a part of all of our internet stories,
but I feel like I've been uniquely affected by speed, because unlike basically everyone in
this cast, I didn't grow up in a first world country. I grew up in a mixture between Ghana,
Nigeria, and Togo, as well as the UK. I grew up in the UK to a certain amount of time.
The worst country of the world.
As well as the UK. I was born in the UK, I grew up there, and then I moved when I was very young
to Ghana, and I stayed there until, so basically my first experience with the internet was when
I was still living in the UK, and my dad would always say, Jimmy, we're going to the office,
because he didn't want to leave me at home, and my mom was also at work, both my parents used to
work, and my dad would say, we're going to the office, and I would hate going with him to the
office, because it's like all they have there are computers, and when I was a kid, computers,
don't suck! Who cares about computers? I want to sit at home and watch Dragon Ball Z, so he would
drag me over. I'm picturing you in that don't hug me, I'm scared when the computer comes to
teach you about the wonders of the internet. Yeah, who cares about computers? I went there,
and I sat down at my dad's desk, because he would never actually use his desk while I was there,
he would always be in a meeting or something, because whenever he would bring me, he would
always know that the only thing I would have to do was be on a computer, so all I knew how to do
at one point was play pinball on Windows 98, so I was just playing pinball all the time, then one
of my dad's employees came and said, oh Jimmy, let me teach you about this thing called the internet,
and I was just like selling drugs to children. Exactly, selling drugs to children. Let me teach
you about it, because this was, I think, 1999, 2000, I was like five, around there, five or six,
I was really little, so he then put on, I don't remember where it was, but he just put on the
website for, he was like, tell me what TV shows you like, and I was like, okay, I like, you know,
I think I said Sailor Moon or something, so he pulled up the website. And he shook his head
sadly and turned back to the computer. Yeah, exactly, oh no, but like, he asked me also,
how do you spell that, so he looked it up, and then pulled up the website for Sailor Moon, and he
was like, you can look at pictures of all the best shows you like, and I was just like, you know
what, this is something to do, I get to look at pictures of TV shows I like, so the internet,
the internet hadn't been sold on me yet, and it was not until like, a little bit later, about a
few years later, then one of my dad's younger employees, this guy was, I think, at the time,
I think it was like, 20, so he was, so this guy's an early adult, he's probably got an
anime blog, and we're probably all fans of it, so like, this guy, he comes like, Jimmy, let me
teach you about this site called Newgrounds, and that's what the doors got, that's what the doors
got blown over. Dude, you had some sick, sick ass adults in your life, dude. Yeah, like, oh man,
like. Yeah, you're the only person I've talked to who didn't learn about Newgrounds from like,
someone in middle school. No, no, no, adults taught me about Newgrounds, man, I was out,
no one in my school knew about the internet. I think the average person finds out about Newgrounds
some fat obnoxious white kid in your middle school, so he thinks he's really funny by repeating
everything you see in comics. By repeating all of those shit, but all the fucking lines from
Homestar Runner and all that shit, fuck man. Yeah, well someone who's gonna come up to you and describe
every Newgrounds video they watch, you know, and then Dick came out of the cereal box.
I remember, like he says, Jimmy, I know you like the Mega Man games, let me show you this one game,
and I remember the first game I ever played on Newgrounds, it was this, like, weird time attack
side-scrolling Mega Man game called Zero Race, where you controlled zero from the Mega Man X games
and you just had to complete time challenges, and I would play that, like, I would play that game
diligently for hours. So now, instead of, like, Jimmy, let's go to the office, it would be,
dad, let's go to the office, so I could go and play, I could go and play, like, you know,
whatever. And then I remember I started finding the other stuff on Newgrounds, and I know you've
completely co-opted Tom's fucking time to tell his story. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Tom, Tom, you can,
you can finish, I'll get back, I'll get back to the other stuff on Newgrounds when you're done.
Oh man, Shaw Shaw's part, man too, Shaw Shaw, man, I can't tell you how many fucking, like,
stick figure, like, stick figure stories. Oh wait, I know what you're talking about. Yeah.
Yeah, the super violent stick figure cartoons, right, and they don't always be sent to fucking,
to new metal songs. Holy shit, that takes me back. Oh my god, I watched a ton of those, because,
see, the era, like, my cousin, I had an older cousin, my cousin Boyd, who's like four years older
than me, and he knew a lot more of those, like, you know, flash cartoon sites and stuff like that,
like, the stuff that I avoided, because it was, like, too adult and stuff, but he would show me
tons of those violent stick figure cartoons, which are a fucking blast, because it's just,
it'll always just be, like, some extremely long, violent fight scene. God, what was the one where
it was like, the character was supposed to be, like, a beast? He had, like, Wolverine claws,
and it was like, some, like, they created some, like, genetic monster in a, in a lab, and each
episode of the show would be, like, some scenario where he ends up around all these people, and
it'll start playing a disturbed song, and he'll murder everyone, or, like, a slipknot song, and
this guy'll just fucking kill all these people, and it was so cool. Sounds pretty cool. My, my, my,
my favorite, my favorite was for the Shao Shao series, and the Shao Shao series is this, like,
long-winded, I think, at the time, when I stopped watching it, it got up to, like, eight or nine
parts, and the first one was so simple, it was just two stick figures fighting each other, right,
and they just had this really well-choreographed battle together, and then it just kept getting
progressively more and more crazy, where one of the most iconic ones is, like, their levels to,
like, a building, and this one stick figure goes through all, like, five levels of this building,
and murders, brutally murders hundreds of these stick figure guys in such, like, grandiose fashion,
and it was so crazy to see. It's such a thing, it's all detailed, right? Like, every punch and kick
is, like, is, like, unique and stuff, where it just, like, goes through this whole big scenario.
Did you guys have the same reaction to those that I did, which is to then draw
fuckloads of stick figure fight scenes? Yes, yes. Because I, I did a lot of, uh, flip books, like,
I would just take, I would draw, like, just on the bottom corner of the page of a book,
like, a bunch of stick figure fights, and just, and, yeah, I always wanted it to be like that,
where it was, like, every attack was unique, and the characters would do all these crazy moves and
shit. I drew lots and lots of, like, action stick figure comics in, uh, early 2000s. Because I feel
like that's part, like, because, aside from the internet, like, and aside from Sha Sha, when I was
growing up, my cousins were all, like, super, they were my cousins, a lot of my cousins were Otaku,
and a lot of my cousins were also really big kung fu movie nerds, and they would bring all of these,
and not just, like, the Jackie Chan Bruce Lee ones, they would bring all of these really obscure,
like, tapes from China, in the original Chinese with no subtitles, and would just sit and watch
for hours, just these absolutely insane, like, I remember we, one of my cousins had the flying
guillotine, and I was just like, this guy throws this thing, like, yeah, like, he, he, he, those
movies were great, so like, this guy throws the thing, and you just, and the, all of these fight
scenes were absolutely fucking great, so I feel like when I started seeing that, that kind of stuff,
that was obviously inspired by all of these, like, kung fu movies from China, like, in the form of all
these stick figure fights, that was one of my eight, my entryways into just being like, this is
fucking awesome, and that probably was also what later led me to being anime is fucking awesome,
but that's, that's, that's later on in the story, we won't get there yet. Tom, continue with yours.
Oh man, Lime Wire is, all of these things are flooding back, like, Lime Wire is another, like,
I feel like everybody's internet story, because of just how the internet evolves, and how it evolved
everybody has these topstones that just, like, everybody who was around in the,
like, I think for all of us, we've all been on the internet since the mid-2000s, and I know even
though you're younger than the rest of us, you started so young, whereas I think that, like,
for a lot of people your age who didn't get into it until like the 2010s, probably don't know what
any of this shit we're talking about. Well, yeah, a lot of my friends probably didn't get, don't
know what Lime Wire is, but man, shit, like, well, I want, I want to continue with mine,
but only after Tom's finished his, like, because I have a few things to say.
Not to co-opt, but I gotta say, this, I can, I think I remember that I, I, I,
Lime Wired the Fooly Cooly soundtrack. Everybody did.
I needed that. I bought the, I, I own the Fooly Cooly soundtrack.
Everybody Lime Wired the Fooly Cooly, I, I Lime Wired.
I painted it at a store and bought it. I remember Lime Wiring, like, pretty much
every single, every single song that, every single, like, different version of Charla
Hedjala that was ever done. Like, this was way back in the day, because I, I looked up
Charla Hedjala, because I, I, I grew up with the, with the English dub, and then I heard
the Japanese theme song. I was like, I love this song. Let me get on Lime Wire. And like,
18 different versions popped up. And I was like, let me get them all. And I was just like,
yeah, I just downloaded every single one.
Well, I got to talk about Lime Wire. Mine's different, because once again, I, I grew up
more sheltered. And I was familiar with Lime Wire from like, 2001, because my mom got into
the internet at around the same time I did. And she was a huge System of a Down fan.
Like, she was obsessed with that band. And she would like hang out in their forums and stuff.
And so she found out about Lime Wire as a way to download, like, System of a Down had
shit tons of unreleased music that was online, like all these demos and, and B-sides and shit.
And eventually they made, like they released an album called Steal This Album, which was just a
collection of like music that people kept stealing off of Lime Wire. And they were just like,
fucking here it is on a CD. But um, so we had, like my mom would download all the System of a Down
music. And some of it wasn't even them. Some of it would be like guest spots of them or just bands
that sounded a lot like System of a Down and people mislabeled it and stuff. Like the most famous one...
Yeah. Right. And the, the one that was the most famous is like, uh, A Legend of Zelda?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, it's, it's, it sounds like, it sounds a bit like Surge from System of a Down
singing this album. I was, I was convinced, I was convinced that it was him. But we had that on our,
our CDs. So she had all these burn CDs and System of a Down songs. But like,
I didn't know how to use Lime Wire myself. And I know my dad had been downloading like,
porn on there and shit. But uh... Oh, let me talk about porn on Lime Wire, man. Because I remember...
We'll get to it. But so what would ruin this forever for me though? And like, because again,
I never used it myself. But when I was like, uh, I want to say 12 or 13, I think 13,
my mom bought me a computer for my birthday. So I had my own computer. And that's another,
that's another important touchstone when each of us got our own personal computer.
Yeah. Well, here's the thing. It was ruined immediately because I got my own computer and
all I used it for was like, message boards, just like using the internet, you know, I didn't know
any other purpose for it and listening to music on there. But my cousin Boyd, the one I mentioned
before, he started downloading tons of shit on Lime Wire on my computer. He would come over to my
computer and download all this shit. So within like six months of me owning this computer, it became
just destroyed with viruses. Like you could not load up anything. It was practically useless.
So I couldn't even get online with it anymore. And we didn't know how to fix it. And I didn't
know how to communicate to my parents what the problem was, you know, so basically that computer
was good for about six months. And then it was never usable for anything but listening to music
again. And like writing, I would use it to write like poetry and listen to music. That was it.
Oh, oh my god. Oh my fucking god. Let me just let me just rant about that for two goddamn seconds.
Yeah, like when I was even when I up until maybe like two or three years ago, because like, you know,
since I graduated college, I've sort of been in and out of living at my parents house. Like I live
there for six months and then go away for six months and come back for a year or whatever and
go away for a year. Yeah, my dad was the same thing. He had the Wi-Fi on a timer so that it
would automatically go off after like midnight or something. And I was because I don't know,
he just didn't believe in me staying up past like midnight or whatever. He wanted to enforce
like a strict schedule. To this day, to this day, to this day, I'm not allowed to take my laptop to
my bedroom in my house that I can't live in. Oh my god, dude. In the house that I can't like,
that's the reason why I have to go downstairs to the basement to record because I can't take up to
my bedroom because they say, oh, you'll never come out your room and you'll never talk to anybody.
And it's like, well, okay. And like, oh, but you, and also if you take it to your room,
we don't know what time you'll sleep. All right then. But they still allow me to stay,
they still allow me to stay in the fucking computer room and be up until like 3 a.m.
So it doesn't even matter what time I sleep. And I have my phone in my room. So it's the same
exact thing. It's, but yeah, I understand. I understand technology. I mean, because like,
okay, should I pick up where I left off of mine now? Or if you want, sure. Yeah. So like, as I said,
at that point, I was on Newgrounds and I started finding the other stuff on Newgrounds and everybody
knows what the other stuff is. Dayton Sims and Hentai. Fun fact, I learned about Hentai before
I learned about what anime was. Like I had been watching anime, but I didn't necessarily know
like a term or like a what to call it or anything. But I learned what Hentai was in detail and understood
all the ins and outs of it long before I actually learned what anime was. So I was looking through
all of these like, you know, different things like just dating Sims as well as just game games that
I don't know how anyone could play fucking dating Sims on Newgrounds. It was it was it was again,
again, you have to understand, I was like seven or eight. I was a kid. I'd know I'd like free time
out the wazoo at free time. I was just following whatever I could want to do. So I started looking
at all this and it really just brought my mind really open really early. And it kind of made me
it kind of made me an outcast in school because I didn't because like I knew I wasn't supposed to
talk about it. I knew I wasn't supposed to actually like be interacting with other people about what
I'd been seeing on this weird internet site. So I kind of didn't have anything in common with the
kids with the other kids, even though like I wanted to it was it was it was you were like always
for a certain time, I really was always on you. But the crazy thing is I never went to the forums
here's another thing. I never had any internet exclusive friends up until about four years ago.
Like for my entire life, I never met anyone on the internet because I even though I was so free
to I was so willing to do whatever I wanted, I will the mind the mindset was don't make friends
with people on the internet because you'll get in trouble with your parents or they'll find like
it was it was the thing with that you said like except the only thing that took was don't don't
don't talk to people over the internet. Don't talk to strangers on the internet.
That's the that's the one thing that kind of stuck with me up until recently.
But yeah, so like the idea that then then came like when I grew a little bit older and I started
learning a lot more and then I start because the thing about what I used the internet for was games.
I played a lot of games on the internet. I was always looking for I was on mini clip all the time.
I was on new grounds playing all the new you see that new you know who just did a fucking review.
Oh yeah, I saw that was a trip. I was a trip. I looked at him. He posted a new review. That was
a trip when he was going through like that was I was seeing my life flash before my eyes as he
was doing that. So like I never even heard of mini clip before. Before you could see me. I want to
like because again, a lot of our viewers listeners might be younger and might not have lived through
this part of the history because what really is fascinating like I think the biggest change between
like 10 years ago and now is that 10 years ago you were always told do not put any personal
information. Yes, that is so true. Don't give out your name. So that's how that's why all of us
about anything. That's the reason why all of us have crazy weird names. That's the reason right
and I was actually about to get into that. That's how user user names are. Are you not still supposed
to put personal I don't think it's true anymore because I'm seeing you. Yeah. Facebook you can't
you literally can't use I mean you can but you're not supposed to use fake names on Facebook or
Google Plus. The way I see it now is people like us who are anime fans, who are nerds,
who are people who have like either internet followings or just do fun stuff on the internet or
like play a lot of video games. We all make up our own names and those identities are kind of separate.
Then we have our Facebook identities where we all use our real names and that's where you know
because our families see those which is why we'd never update them and like that's because that's
the reason why I quit Facebook because my mom is on it and like because so you don't you don't really
want to show that side but then because you don't really even interact with that side it's less you
but the side that is more you is the side where you're using a crazy weird internet name and that
kind of brings me I mean oh yeah like to compare now to then like right now we're in a podcast where
we've got Ben St and Tom Oliver and both of those are like not their real names but they're
halfway there like they're practically their real names and everyone knows that you're Jimmy
and most people probably know my real name but like 10 years ago no one would be using a name
that was anywhere near their real name like you would not be like you know using a name that's like
a vague version of your real name exactly which is why which is why like Digi Bro you know yeah
which is why like Digi Bro is so far off from Conrad and why Nino is so far off from Jimmy
because it's like I remember I was playing I wanted to the reason I got this Nino name because
everyone asked me this question and I like giving this like origin story like it also ties into like
the origin story because I would play a lot of games and one game one game that really typifies my
experience with the internet is the arctic games like the battle those arctic battle you know games
like the dragon the dragon fables the adventure quests or the the met quests never heard of
yeah I know you guys I mean you guys probably haven't heard of them but like I've heard of
adventure quests yeah those games those games are really big oh adventure quests oh god damn
fucking damn adventure quests holy shit just fucking shoot me in the fucking head dude
yes I knew you guys would have just shoot me starring David Spade god damn it yes like those
games were such an important like I don't like they're all shit they're all absolute garbage
but those games were such an important part of my childhood and my experience with the internet
but like dude thank you for reminding me about it playing adventure quests in high school during
study period and my fucking library computer you know what's what I would do I'm shocked that
none of us were runescape players I because yeah I hated runescape I because I kept hearing about it
I didn't like yeah yeah yeah if if we had hippocrite here he was a big runescape player
yeah because I remember okay so like like when I know comes from is I was trying to play adventure
quest and every name out because another annoying thing about the internet back in the day was
you're putting a name and it was already taken that's that still gets to me so then I was like you
know what I'm gonna make a name that's never ever going to be taken online again so I put
six letters that were absolute gibberish that could sound like a name together and that's when
Nino came from and I've turned it I've turned it in to the empire I've turned it in to me to the
massive to the massive identity it is today it's your brand now it's my brand so that whole
nine zero thing doesn't actually mean anything it's just your name the okay the nine the nine zero
that I add the nine zero because people always mispronounce NINOUH when they first hear it like
I knew that your name was you know like I just thought that there was some deeper meaning
yeah also because oh no nine nine nine zero is my like nine ninety is my favorite number
nine ninety and four are my favorite numbers those are my two favorite numbers but like it's
nine very interesting choices yeah well I have a philosophy I have a philosophical reason for
ninety but I'm not gonna actually get into that it's so weird it's I said it while I was drunk
one time I don't want to dig back in my brain for it but um like so playing these games kind of just
pushed me into understanding because that was one of my first brushes with anime because I would read
the blog of the guy who made the arctic games and he said oh we we use such as like I remember he said
I like to use the record of lotus war as a reference for this part of the game and something
I was like what is record of lotus war look that up on the internet found out what that was
and again I that was also another part of how I started learning today when I learned google
I would just type in random things and I would find them like I would just find
hours upon hours worth worth of just information and stuff that I could just read about and it
was the most interesting thing because I was like some like nine zero at this point I was like nine
ten and all that all I was doing was just on the internet occasionally looking at hentai
occasionally looking at like naked cartoons that I would you know I would watch on tv and then
and then I would also just be playing a bunch of weird obscured shitty 2d games online and
it was around that point that I started to actually truly discover anime because I was in school one
day and this was Naruto took my school by stone I don't know how but Naruto I was living in Ghana
at the time right so it was at home all of our internet sucked because Ghana and internet is trash
but our school had this really special router that made it a little bit better so if people
wanted to watch videos they would all just go and use it on there so we I remember everybody one
day I just saw everybody was on youtube looking at you know clips of Naruto and it was like what's
what's going on like what like what like why why why is everyone looking at this weird Chinese
cartoon or whatever so I would ask them oh so what is this oh it's Naruto go go go on youtube and look
up and I look I decided to look up and I was like oh Naruto isn't that cool but what really got me was
was when I found was when I like played this you know Bleach game on PSP at my friend's house
and then I was like you know what let me look this up on the internet because I didn't know Bleach
had an anime either so I looked up Bleach and I found Bleach on youtube and that's like from
from then on I just started watching it and watching it it's funny I was like in my head I'm like wait
Bleach was on adult swim and then I remembered you were in Ghana yeah no no no here's the crazy
thing here's another crazy thing anime on TV not a thing when you live in Africa when you grew up in
Africa yeah that's not that crazy I'm not surprised by that I'm pulling the slightest yeah like
but the thing is we had we had loads of TV shows we had like band 10 we had um we had pretty much
anime yeah we had pretty much every Cartoon Network show and Disney show like Tom's leaving
but I can't tell if he already took off did you want to take off the microphone still on or not
he said he said he said he said he's gonna leave the recording going in case he just wants to
drop back in I think he didn't mute his microphone I think you can mute him well no but what if he
comes back well someone someone type in the chat when you get back when you get back like you
on mute just will tell us or I mean I don't know it's weird um but yeah so yeah I did it okay okay
yeah um wait let me go back let me go back in time let me take you on a journey yeah to me
in high school home star runner oh man greatest of all internet I know I mentioned this and that
just like you did you like it and I feel like I I can't I can't let it go I gotta go back uh
yeah I was I mean I was kind of on Newgrounds a bit I didn't make a habit of going there all the time
but I uh yeah my one of my friends he was always quoting this he was always like quoting something
and some like love you puff my smell was like hey man what are you talking about and he showed me
home star and I was wicked into home so I bought a t-shirt I bought home star and a t-shirt so I
wore them to school all the time it was basically the best thing ever and you made online purchases
in the mid-2000s I guess I did I think I asked for them for birthday presents that's another thing
when you're like money over the internet was the is the most weird situation because when I was a
kid spending money on things over the internet was such an alien concept to me which is why like
people ask me jimmy you pay for a cultural account as well as you and you also still
torrent anime it's like because I can't get the torrenting like I can't get the download mindset
out of my head because when you when you live when you live in Ghana when you live in Africa
like and you're growing up you you're you're they don't ship to you they don't ship anything to you
like they won't do like there are there are pure like there are some pure boxes but here's the
craze the funny stuff I know you guys have heard the whole Nigerian prince thing like the whole
you know type of thing oh god did you know what Nigeria is?
guess guess what happens when you owe me 10,000
guess what happens when loads of people from your country make a bunch of scams and end up on American
news your country gets blacklisted and countries around you get blacklisted on amazon and a bunch
of other sites so to this day a bunch of my cousins and family can't order things on amazon
which is absolutely fucking mental so that's wicked fuck yeah so so but like you they can
still order through some means like they they ship it's it's it's much more trouble than it's
scorched earth policy yeah it's like the whole fucking country well I mean because okay here's
is a weird tangent because my uncle used to be one of those guys who used to scam people I'm sorry
I'm sorry like it's it's it's it's a real thing and like people really people really did it like
people he made a lot of money doing it but like my uncle used to be one of those guys who used to do it
and he told me stories about guys who he told me stories about guys who would like trick really
big business men into thinking they were ladies on the internet and like seducing seducing them
and telling them a bunch of crazy things and the other thing is they would they would then
seduce a bunch of rich ladies and then convince them to come to Nigeria and give them money in person
it was those these stories are fucking mental I know these kind because there's it's a lot of like
like uh like I've seen some of this second hand where it'll be like um like middle-aged women who
are like lonely at home and they start talking to like exotic foreigners from like Morocco and
yeah yeah you know and those those people have ulterior motives and they just want like a way
to get to the US you know which is why like which is why I feel like I have a being Nigerian also
being British what family Nigerian like I have this weird unique perspective when I see something
shifty on the internet and this has been instilled in me like from a very young age when I see
something shifty on the internet I I immediately call call you know call it on bullshit like
loads of people for example you know tinder right like the whole tinder thing oh I know a thing
yeah people didn't really catch like people in my college Ben well-laid patreon saint over here
but yeah um people didn't really know about the whole bot thing on tinder like until like yeah
people don't people didn't know that there were bots on tinder until like oh bots yeah I heard
but no I heard but sorry yeah the accent the accent guys I'm sorry I'm sorry but um yeah people
didn't know that there were like uh botted accounts in my in my in my college and I would I would be the
one to tell them no no like this is a bot because look all of them are pictures there's no description
and she's talking to you first it's a fucking trap like yeah it's a fucking trap so like I feel
like I was the only person who was able to figure that out purely because my childhood had indicated
and because the people I was raised with had indicated me into knowing like they had just
instigated me into knowing that oh yeah this is the you know this is how the shifty side of the
internet works don't trust it especially if you get really really shady friend you know friend
because on Facebook people people to this day don't understand that that's a bad sign it's like
it's weird like um last thing last thing about homestar runner when I asked my mom for for
homestar runner t-shirts and she she purchased me t-shirts for my birthday or whatever I remember
she said she was like Ben you know you should you should you should create you should make
something like this you should make content on the internet I mean she didn't use those words
but she was like this is a lucrative business here I am spending money
on these people that made some funny cartoon on the internet you should do something like that
and I was like haha yeah right mom not a damn shame I know right and now look at me now look at me
making content on the internet I want you to make I want you to make a t-shirt where Vincent is
vaping and like and like and like the the smoke the smoke from Vincent's vape just makes a logo
the vapors and then that's the t-shirt I I really need to sell a t-shirt even one t-shirt I just
need one oh you know what you know what I know I'll if you'll if you'll buy the first one if I if I
can pony up cash yeah definitely if I have one if I have one guaranteed sale it'll all be worth it
it'll all be worth it but definitely like done like a vapors t-shirt would be would be pretty cool
the digi bro t-shirt would be cool too I should fucking make it I can't yeah I can't I was thinking
I should make a t-shirt myself and I was like I can't put Huey Freeman on the t-shirt that's
copyrights since I feel like uh all of us are sort of getting towards the the like late 2000s
now in our stories I think I should run through my whole everything up to that point so I can
catch up with everybody so like so I got into the internet like pretty early like 2001 ish
maybe earlier well I mean I actually my parents for whatever reason and I really don't understand
why because they are they were not tech savvy at all until like deep into the 2000s maybe even the
2010s but like for whatever reason they just wanted to be like early adopters of new things so they
bought a computer because your parents are based as fuck that's why yeah they got they got a windows
me uh computer in like 98 see that's but the funny thing is like because they're not tech savvy at
all like they will get whatever the new thing is without having any idea if it's good or bad or
like how people feel about it they just because they'll walk into like Best Buy and be like
what's the the new computer and they'll you know Best Buy is just going to push whatever the fucking
newest thing is that's going to make them the most money see they bought a windows me computer
which uh historically is frowned upon as one of the worst operating systems I think but uh they
wouldn't have known that and I remember as like a little kid in the 90s I would I guess use like
lycos or uh yahoo or whatever like the early search engines and I would ask jeeves yeah I would search
I would I wonder how those ask jeeves guys feel like I want to just how they feel the fuck out
I feel like there's kids watching this like what the fuck is ask jeeves like who the fuck is this
jeeves man back in back in the day there was another search engine called ask jeeves and they
were going head to head with google guess who won yeah go yeah if you want to find out about ask
jeeves just google it so yeah in the late 90s like my first memories of what I would use the computer
for is I would search like beast wars and like I don't know if I was on like their official website
or whatever but they'd have like little like thumbnails of screenshots from the show and I
would just print those out like we had a printer like a color printer and I would just print out
all these fucking like a whole sheet of paper with just a little thumbnail like a youtube thumbnail
sized picture of something from beast wars because that was my favorite show and I thought it was
like so cool to have like all these and I had like a I had just like a stack of printed out
beast wars pictures in my room and then later when I got into pokemon I would spend a lot of time
on the pokemon website because they had like a full pokedex on there and at one point I like drew
all the pokemon from the pokedex and they had all this other shit but like at that point it was
just like you know website like I knew about a website connected to a show kind of like what
jimmy was saying earlier yeah and then like um I don't know exactly how I like discovered the
concept of forums again I think my mom was getting into the matter at the same time in 2001 but I
was really into yugioh and I found a yugioh forum um so I made an account there I think my name was
just like a string of ones like it was that kind of thing like I would forget my password all the
time because it would be something stupid and I just make a bunch of new accounts for the names
or just more ones um and then I would post on this yugioh forum and then like I was there for a
little while and then I think my cousin started getting into the internet around the same time
and he would like do use it for research on anime because we got into anime in like 01 and 02 and so
like he would start actually you know what this is all 2002 jump jump it forward a year uh he would
start like uh trying to find new information about anime and stuff and I think he found like anime
news network around the time he found uh he found he would find these different forums and so we both
became a part of a forum called otaku boards and I would spend all fucking day on otaku boards
like all I did was read and post there and um there were like a few other like anime forums but
otaku boards was my favorite one because they had more of like a tightly knit community where people
kind of knew who each other were whereas a lot of the other ones would just be like people posting
into the void um there was like anime suki forums I found that like a little bit later uh but yeah
I was like really big into forums because it was a place where you could like share your thoughts
on things and read what other people are saying and I loved knowing about like what what what people
are like into you know like all the anime we would watch would be like stuff that people were
recommending in the forums so like we knew about Eva because everyone would talk about Evan Gellion
and how it's like supposedly the best anime ever so like we went out and bought the DVDs and and
Helsing was really popular for some reason so like like yeah that was a huge part of me getting
into anime was through forums and then of course like I said he was using line wire and ruining my
computers um and then like I discovered the game FAQs forums and would hang out in there uh and
talk about Tales of Symphonia because like every game has its own forum on game FAQs so I got really
obsessed with the Tales of Symphonia forums and then from there me and a few people from that
started up like a freeboards thing where it was like just you know like 10 people on this forum
and let me tell you there is nothing in this world that is probably worse for a 14 year old
than being a part of like a tightly knit group of teenagers on the internet so so it just so
happened that we started this forum like right around the time that I was becoming like really
depressed uh my parents uh were fighting a lot like their marriage wasn't going so well um I I
we we switched I switched schools like we moved to the ghetto and this was when I went to a school
where I was like the only white kid there and I didn't make any friends so I would just hole up
in my mom's office because she was one who had a computer and I would sit on the forums all day
and we had the the fucking worst internet connection because we couldn't afford it at the time so like
it would take like two and a half minutes to load a page like of a forum so what I would do is I
would get into conversations with people on like this message board and like I would type a message
and hit send and then just sit there waiting you know and just and then I would reload the
page every couple of minutes until they would respond and just talk to people that way and
like I was in all these like everyone had like all these emotional relationships and stuff it's
like a bad anime like it whenever you see those romantic comedy shows where it's like everyone's
in love with someone else and the relationships keep changing like that's what it was like
were there were there girls in that group there were but I'm pretty like there was one girl in
there that I was like in love with and in retrospect I am convinced was a troll like I am 100%
convinced that they were running like a really high level trolling operation on me like I'm
convinced of it I don't have any evidence but like it just seems that way from like looking back on
it with what I know now it's like yeah I'm pretty sure this is like an extensive trolling operation
yeah I feel like despite despite everybody despite everything I said about not actually
making any friends on the internet and not actually talking to anyone there was this one girl who
wasn't necessarily she wasn't necessarily like someone I met through a forum she was like a
friend of a friend but yeah the only interaction I ever I've ever had with her in my entire life
is through the internet like he introduced me to her through Facebook and then we moved from
Facebook to MSN and I don't know if kids there's another thing kids aren't gonna fucking know about
back before Skype was a thing guys MSN MSN messenger was lit I was an AIM guy myself
oh yeah those AIM Yahoo MSN and fucking AOL Skype killed them all Skype murdered every single one
of them everyone in my high school we all we when we weren't in school we would talk through AIM
yeah like it used to be really segmented it used to be really segmented and then Skype came and
just wiped them all and now discord is slowly coming and just wiping off Skype so like it's uh
I remember uh I was I was really into fanfiction.net oh man I I printed out I printed out fan fiction
stories that I found of interest including some saucy ones uh many saucy ones actually I printed
out some uh a legend of Dragoon uh saucy fanfiction and I had a big thick folder I took it to school
and I showed my friends I was like look at these saucy fan fictions my friends uh well are you
are you not are you not entertained around that's around that period is when I was writing saucy
fan fictions and posting them to fanfiction.net I hope oh god I never found it did you ever
read Tales of Symphonia fanfics oh no never I feel like I feel like did you just like oh well
you know and that was my old stomping ground back in the day so so through those forums is how I
learned about like you know a lot of internet stuff like again fanfiction.net was a was what I
knew about and like mostly websites because like I never got into like the whole downloading and
shit just because like my internet was so bad and like online gaming was a total mystery to me
because that the idea of having a good enough connection to do anything like that online was
you know not a thing I feel like I feel like the more I now that I've moved to America and I'm
starting to look back on my life and my childhood I'm learning that more and more of my personal
gripes and grievances are very very tied into where I grew up because when I was growing up in
Ghana and like I would again Ghana Nigeria to go like oh I say grown up in Ghana but I was
growing up in like three different countries but it's weird like when I was growing up there
it was like I had a console I would play video games my parents would like I would never buy them
there but like my parents would always travel to like America or England and buy me video games
all the time and I'll be playing I'll play pretty much all the same games you guys played
you know had a regular childhood and everything but like I would never play them online every single
game I tried to play online the internet was way too slow for it to work I I could never like
actually spend enough time or actually like actively be you know concerned enough with the
internet to try and play games the types of games I liked playing would were usually single player
games so I gravitated away from online gaming so yeah so oh let me finish this a little bit
yeah sure go ahead like the the whole concept of online gaming to me felt really pointless and alien
for the longest time and up until now I'm seeing people say that online gaming is the only true
way to play video games like the fuck it is like I don't I don't I don't get the online gaming meme
why can't it die like that that should be please time travel me back time travel me back to that
fucking podcast online gaming is a meme that needs to die I think we actually did bring that
that part didn't we I don't think you did I had a bunch of I had a bunch of friends when I was in
I don't know how a teenager or whatever that played Ragnarok online and I went up and I and I
thought that the graphics looked really cool it was like it looked like online a little fancier
yeah it looked really cool and I really wanted to play it but like I couldn't fucking make it work
on my computer for whatever reason I actually I did event I did eventually get a final fantasy
it was 11 the online one yeah yeah I did eventually get final fantasy 11 it was like a big event me
and me and Nate both got it and we were both like wicked stoked to play it but like it was it was
terrible I mean it was bad for me I could not be asked to fucking form up a part I didn't want to
fuck around complicated ass game I just wanted to play it solo and build up a character and have
a cool looking red mage with a big red hat that's all I wanted but I did not want to fuck around
building parties and grinding and all that shit so I gave up I gave up online was actually the first
online game that I did play and that was in like 03 which is way before I knew how those things
worked but again my cousin was around and like we would get these I don't remember how I'm assuming
it had something to do with the anime stuff that we were buying but we would get these like free
trials for for Ragnarok like a seven day free trial disc kind of thing like in the mail I guess
probably with like anime magazines I don't know but um yeah I had like these trial discs for that
so I actually got to play that um like very briefly in those years and I thought it was the
by far the coolest thing that had ever happened in the universe like it was fucking awesome the
music alone in that game is incredible and I did eventually get to play it later because like
you know after this part that I'm talking about like for me it was like 2006 the internet opened
up massively because this was when we moved out of the ghetto we moved into a nicer house we finally
got like decent internet for the first time and it was like all at once uh YouTube started being a
thing and I found out about that through like again like people literally just linking videos on forums
I was like what is this thing you know um so I got I found out about YouTube then uh we had a good
enough connection that we started playing um World of Warcraft uh because Victor really wanted to
play it and he got my parents bought him for his birthday a mac book or not book but uh a mac computer
um it was like one of the first generations where they had the the computer built into the screen
so it's like a fatter screen than the ones they have now but it's not oh yeah yeah yeah I think
my aunt has one of those my aunt has one of those that they don't they don't actually have like a
standard cpu like tower they have just a screen and it's all in there yeah I remember those yeah
so she so he had one of those and they got it for him because like they told the people at Best Buy
that he wanted to like make like movies and stuff on it you know oh boy again again the mac is for art
meme the mac is for art meme it wasn't even the mac is for art meme it was that they showed my parents
like i-movie and garage band and my parents were in like photo booth which are like the you know
stock programs it comes with i-movie is like you can put clip it's like the windows movie maker of
no no no I have I've used i-movie i-movie is a it's like a tiny team to step up from windows
movie maker but it's still shit like well the the best thing about i-movie is that you could record
in the program and the mac they got him had a built-in uh camera on top so like a built-in webcam
so you can actually record directly into i-movie we made a bunch of dumb like action figure movies
that way and then uh it had photo booth which was like you could take a picture and do like all the
weird little distortion effects like the instagram type shit but that was enough that they showed
that to my parents in the store and they were so impressed with those effects that like you could
make you could take a picture and make it black and white it was like mind-blowing to them so they
bought this mac computer for Vic and he would play world of warcraft on it and uh
and then basically because my computer had again had been ruined so it couldn't go online at all
and what i would do is i would get on victor's computer while he was at school um and like
like he was in middle school and i was starting high school so like there was a two hour point
before he would get home after i got home and then i would also wake up early in the morning
and i'd gotten on to did any of you guys read megatocchio back in the day uh back in the day
i like megatocchio the website yeah the web webcomic oh the webcomic yeah i think i think
i did i think i've at least heard of it yeah megatocchio was a big webcomic from the uh like
2003 which i read a lot of those back i've read like all of sluggy freelance and all of megatocchio
and like a bunch of those old webcomics um but i was really into megatocchio back then and then
i got back into it in 2000 like late 2006 early 2007 and i started hanging out in the forums
because i figured out they had a forum there oh this is one of those OELs okay yeah it's an OEL
manga and it's like the OEL manga like the the first like big popular one um yeah my friend
who who does comics now he he told he told me about this yeah continue yeah um and it was
because the thing about megatocchio is that it was like it was an OEL but whereas most of those
are inspired by people who grew up on like DBZ and shit like that like the guy who wrote megatocchio
was a fucking otaku and like the biggest influences on it were canon and air the visual novels like
this is way before those had anime adaptations he would talk about canon all the fucking time
and like it wasn't until 2006 that that became a popular anime show you know like now everyone
knows what aclanat is but back then that was really obscure shit so uh so this dude was like
you know hugely visual novel influenced and um and as a result like the people in the forums
were like to this day like a lot of the biggest anime fans that i follow are people i knew from
the megatocchio forums and like through those forums it just so happened that like everyone
had an anime blog and they were all on wordpress and uh even the guy who was the admin of the forums
um the guy named omo uh who i still follow his fucking anime blog to this day um they all had
these anime blogs and i saw all those and i decided to make my own anime blog just kind of to follow
the crowd you know and it was through them that i found out about like both like internet streaming
of anime and that it was being subtitled by fans because up till this point i had only seen anime
either through cartoon network or through buying dvds and um i didn't know at all that you could
download it or watch it online so they were telling me like you know about all these shows that were
brand new that uh just started um in japan hold on i have to unmute tom real quick oh okay he's back
he's back hey tom he's back um yeah so so you so you caught up to like i won't say caught up but
like you were in on the front lines of the airing shows kind of thing fairly early yeah well i mean
for for a lot of those people in the megatocchio forums a lot of them were like older anime fans
who'd been trading tapes in the 90s like that kind of shit you know so they were just all so you were
so you just stumbled upon second boomers you just yeah i i somehow randomly managed to like the first
anime community i was really a part of it was like a good even split between people who were like new
like me who were just finding out about like new airing shows or had been into it for like a couple
of years and then other people who were like long time people who'd been torrenting for
fucking since it was a thing to torrent you know so like everyone in here like really knew their
shit and they were talking about these these new airing shows and like um you know i just found
out about like haruhi and i i watched all of haruhi on youtube in like probably 240p or something
like that and like uh because this was before copyright was oh man like that's that's that's
another that's another conjuncture point watching anime on youtube kids yeah remember when you could
watch anime on youtube remember what that was oh god yeah but um one two one three
with the stuff these guys were watching it was stuff that was you know it was only getting
fansubbed and no one else on the internet had heard of it so you really had to be someone who
like knew about these shows if you wanted to watch them but there was a site that had pretty much
every fansubbed anime on it it was if this was not the best streaming site in terms of like quality
of video or uh being able to full screen if you didn't have a paid account you had to watch if you
didn't have a paid account on this illegal website you had to watch everything in a tiny little screen
in like the minimum quality and it was like it was like especially small and you had to watch
everything that way but this website had every fucking anime on it get yeah guess what the name
were these the early days of crunchy roll this was crunchy roll in 2007 of course it was the most
illegal website in the world crunchy roll which had every anime ever on it so i watched like all
these shows that like all these obscure anime come yeah well that's the thing i think the reason
that crunchy roll was able to become legitimate so easily is because they had a pay structure in place
because even though it was illegal they you had to have an account to like watch stuff in certain
ways so i think because they already had like a system of paying for their content it was very
easy for them to legitimize it you know the point that really it's like something that happened very
recently that just fucked with my head i saw a television ad for crunchy roll while i was watching
it yeah with anamon agucci said yeah and i was watching awesome and then i was like watching like
stuff like sao and a bunch of shows that would that will never get on american tv in this ad
and i was just like fucking holy shit i saw that ad not on card to network i saw it on like regular
tv like my parents were watching tv and it was on and i was like what the fuck crunchy roll i think
it's for you for you you were there in the genesis of that shit like dude jimmy did you know that
crunchy roll is about to start doing dvds and blu rays like they're licensing now i think because
they said apparently they're gonna dub cabinary and release it on dvd oh man i just read that the
other day so yeah that's how far they've come but yeah so it was like crunchy roll and a few
other like wherever i could find the episodes of these shows um and then like everything this is
like the fire nation attacked moment for me like the moment because when crunchy roll started taking
out everyone else like no no no uh the the fire nation attack moment came later in 2007 so at
this point i you know i've learned about anime blogs i've made all these friends with these
people who know all this just deeper stuff about anime and like i think there's like when you want
i think all of us can generally agree that a big part of this is finding out about something and
wanting it and then having to go learn how to get it like you find out about oh there's anime
that's being fansub that comes out in japan right now and so now your mission in life is to learn
how to get it you know like for example like i was just talking earlier like before the podcast
started about watching about reading a bunch of comic books and like start getting into getting
back into comics and learning how comics worked like it was it kind of you know it was kind of
nostalgic because i was learning how to get into a thing i wanted to do that you kind of have to
jump through hoops for because you have to you have to you have to download a bunch you have to
download a bunch of fucking cbrs off the internet and if they're not in cbr form you have to download
image sets then convert them to cbr form and then put them on your phone or no then download
comic book readers a bunch of crazies i think that what what i think is the biggest difference
between what the internet is now and what it was in the 2000s and i think it was like i think the
internet continued developing in the same direction through the whole 2000s until the very end and then
in like 2010 it completely snapped and went in the opposite direction but this is what i think
people who are new to the internet won't understand is that nowadays the internet is all about
streamlining and putting everything in one place and it used to be that the internet was about
having to go fucking everywhere to find something exactly because yes everyone had their own website
for example for example who here used to who here used to read manga week to week on like you
know like maybe it would be bleach it'll be now it'll be whatever we had yeah in my school when
i was growing up we had like hardcore analytical arguments one manga lets you enlarge the picture
this way does this way no no no no no no no no no no no no no manga volume is the best thing
is like did she says there were so many places you could go to yeah like everybody had their
place to go everybody had their like there was anime advice there was anime like those
dude i gotta say this is not really related but the i remember the first time i ever saw an hd
video stream like when youtube first rolled it out and it was fucking um jizz in my pants by
lonely island like the official music video was like full hd and i remember seeing it and it was
like blowing my mind into pieces because it was so good looking the thing is i like when i when
they first rolled that out when they first rolled that out like the you know actually let me this
oh okay here's a weird dichotomy actually this is a weird part of my internet story my my trips to
america before i started living here that that's a very interesting part because every time it
will you know okay maybe i'll use mmo logic for this if i was leveling up regularly and grinding
regularly when i was in Ghana and that was the normal progression every time i moved to america
it was like free exp day because i would go there i would come here and the internet was faster
because i was already savvy on how to get around the internet my only big block was the fact that
it was fucking slow now i already knew where to watch all the all the anime i wanted oh you
you guys are talking about how yeah you guys are talking about how like you know you would never
you would leave videos on from morning till evening i told you this but i remember loading
eight episodes of shaman king before i went to school coming back and yeah i remember specifically
that with uh spaceship operators because the whole show was on youtube and i opened up tabs of
every video and left them running the whole time i was at school and then came home and marathoned
the show um and that was in 07 but like oh sorry uh yeah well to get through the rest of this uh
part of my story like through all those uh forums and stuff like through mega tokyo and other forums
like that i started to find like the best part was that people would always link you to some like
database somewhere like uh anime news network is like the reason i've always known so much
shit about the backgrounds of like anime people is because i would just go to anime news network
and like read the whole staff lists of shows and stuff because they've they've they've consistently
yeah consistently they like i don't like the staff and they don't like me no no the people who run
anime news network are terrible but they are generally a great encyclopedia site it's a very
good encyclopedia like they they they have very they have very do you want to know why because
they get a bunch of interns who speak japanese and they just like they just i will say that my anime
list is slowly catching up with their encyclopedia but anna is still way more useful in general but
but mal has pictures for everything and that makes it a lot easier to find shit but uh but
anyway um and then there was like encyclopedia metalum which like is a metal encyclopedia and
pretentious metal fans will always tell you that if it's not listed on that website it's not metal
so if you if there's some band that you think is metal and it's not listed there it's not metal but
they have thousands and thousands of metal bands is baby metal there is baby metal there uh i'm not
sure i haven't checked they probably are because they're definitely metal but like i would go on
there and just search like uh like the category of avant-garde metal and then just listen to every
band on there so like a lot of how i the reason i have such a like ridiculously broad like knowledge
with most of the stuff i'm interested in is that i would just go to these like encyclopedia sites and
then just look up everything and i wanted to have all the knowledge that's the reason why people
ask me like how do you know so much about tokusatsu video games comment books etc bro fucking wikis
man exactly just go like i remember when i was a kid go fucking research when i was a kid i would
open up wicked because the thing is i would do a lot of reading because that was the only thing
i could consistently do easily without because video was out of the question when you're when
you're living in Ghana video was it because it would take too long to load so if something had a
video that had to that to watch like i couldn't watch anime but i could read about a whole
ton of them like i could i could read about a whole shit that's why i like i it's so rare for
someone to name an anime and i've never heard of it even if i haven't seen it like i probably know
what it's about because i've done so much research but like so i would i'll just sit down and read
for hours like old comic book stories from like the 80s and that's how i learned so much about
the flash that's how i learned so much about spider-man that's how i read through wikipedia
like through wikipedia text the entire clone saga which i then recently actually read through it the
comic book version i'll read the wikipedia version if you want that story the comic books are actually
completely fucking terrible anyway to get back to how like chaotic the internet was at the time
though like when because when i finally got into fansubs like torrenting had you know it'd become
a big thing but there was a lot of fansub groups who had been around since like the irc days and
they were like they were like really like i remember um live evil which is i think they're
still around um they they do like obscure 80s stuff and like they had put out this video for
the first episode of kimigure orange road and they put in like this whole intro at the start
where they were explaining like how people used to like watch kimigure orange road like by
shipping tapes around the world and like you know like hard coding fansubs onto the fucking tapes
like onto the actual yeah people don't people don't people don't realize like back i man i've
said this so many times if i could if i had the resources if i had like the the know how resources
and people to know i would organize a giant long form no giant long form like documentary on the
history of fansubbing yeah that would be great like like if you've got otaku no video does a
little bit of it yeah it does a little bit of it but i want i want i want i want like fucking a
giant long form because this is guy that this guy otaku do otaku guy or something otaking
otaking he made a weird little like you know opinionated video on what was wrong with fansubs
in his brief slide and actually that does factor into our into our story because there was a point
in fansubbing where they would fucking sub the complete wrong way they would fucking add all of
the weird japanese text in and oh yeah see you know translator notes out the wazoo it was it was
actually a mess and now it's become a lot more streamlined because of sites like crunchyroll
who right well that's kind of what i'm getting to is like with that live evil group like they
would talk they talked about how that history and then they were like very adamantly like
you have to come to our irc to download our shows because to them there was like the sense of
community was like a big part of like why they did fansubbing and that was true for a lot of
fansub groups and so like in the 2000s there was this huge shift where because like everyone wanted
stuff faster so fansub groups were were trying to pick up their speed and get stuff out as quick as
possible and everyone was torrenting and we had sites like tokyo toshokan and nia torrents which
are still around which are where like the big anime resource sites didn't baka didn't baka bt come
around around that time as well yeah and baka bt has always been like the one that's like great for
archiving shows like they have lots of full shows from like like they'll have the full highest quality
version of the show and uh they always had a rule where if you're a member you have to have like a
good seating ratio or else you get blocked um which happened to me a few times but yeah uh so so
there was these different torrent sites and like because people would just go there because they
would have you know every torrent then no one would talk to the fansubbers and people kept
getting more demanding of the fansubs people would complain that they weren't going fast enough people
would uh you know not really care about who's doing it they just want the product and so
like fansubbers hated it they hated the speed subbing culture because it was getting away from
like what you know what they had seen it as but then one streaming showed up it just killed all of
it because there was no point anymore because everyone wants stuff immediately and so if it gets
simulcast on Funimation and Crunchyroll and like even if the subs aren't the best like because there's
a lot of people who hate those subs for whatever reason because they can't understand Japanese
well enough for it not to matter like I can but the show comes out on Crunchyroll and then immediately
gets ripped by horrible subs and immediately put on uh Tokyo Toshio and that's everyone's
gonna watch it yeah on yeah that's how but a crazy thing is that kind of reminds me about
something that's been happening to me recently because I've been watching this Japanese action
series called High and Low it's a live action it's a live action martial arts series about
delinquent gangs in Tokyo and the the only person you can fucking get this show from there's only
one person you can get the show from in English only one person translating it because if you go
to kiss kiss asian which is like the drama site for where they have all the common writer stuff
they don't have all of the second season there's only one person on the internet who subbed
everything so far and her name is Yuri or Stormichu and I found this person by a complete
accident and they run a little tumblr site where she lists she'll list of raw she'll list a hard
sub version she'll she just you know and she talks to you about the she even has a thing where
you can watch and she has like her like commentary in in sub form along the top of the series along
top of the show and like I talked to on face on on on twitter sometimes I send her messages like oh
wow this episode was great and I was like shit this reminds me of like back when I was a kid
talking to the fansubbers right this reminds me it was yeah it was a blast from the past I I mean
I had to I for me and I finally getting to that moment I mentioned earlier that I completely
didn't actually say what it was the big explosion moment for me was when I met my friend Donsan
who I talked about in the never going outside podcast that he was the most internet savvy guy
ever because all he did was read everything on the internet because he was a hikikomori so he
taught like as soon as I met him like I knew about torrents but I didn't know how they worked
something like he was disgusted that I was watching streams he was like he was like uh how can you
watch in low quality you need it to be HD which HD at the time meant 480p but I will I will never
forget that the first thing he taught me how to do I downloaded shakugan no shana and I watched all
of it in downloads and it was the most beautiful show I'd ever seen because it was like oh my god
this looks amazing and so I got really into torrenting and I would because I picked this up from him
that uh you know this was before external hard drives were really cheap but what he would do is
he would buy stacks of CDs and DVDs and just burn en mass like anime downloads onto them as storage
so like I I did the same thing I have like all these old DVDs of like you know like suku yomi and
like all these 2006 era shows that I downloaded and like burn to CDs and they're all sitting
somewhere I remember yeah I remember when I first learned how to use torrents right
like obviously the idea of that like when I was young when I was younger the idea of downloading
something sodding off to go watch youtube and like in 20 minutes it would be done was a was a dream
that was a dream what you would do when I was a kid you'd that you'd wait till everyone's about
to sleep start the torrent go to bed wake up and it's it's halfway done that's what torrents would
take me like days like if I was downloading the whole show it was gonna be a few days before I got
to watch it you were nurturing it it was like you were nurturing it it was like it was like a like
a little project like you're taking care of it took a long time for like it wasn't until really like
the last year that it got like way better for me because of the fact that as internet speeds were
picking up so too were the file sizes yeah exactly there was a time where one episode of anime was
like under a hundred megabytes and now it's like half a gig at minimum you know so well I mean if
you watch all everything at 1080 yeah it's half a gig but I sell for 720 because I do too because
most anime doesn't actually broadcast in 1080 like yeah it looks like a movie then you gotta I
remember when I fucking downloaded paprika and it was like 10 gigs and I was like what the fuck
like this is not possible there's no way oh man that's not that's not the really didn't care for it
oh you've expressed that on the show before but I haven't seen it it's been talking up 10 gigs of
my fucking hard drive for 10 years it's acceptable it's an acceptable no because no okay so where
everything picked up for me like was the late 2000s because I was in boarding school and again
this wasn't because of any friend this wasn't because of any like you know mystical otaku
otaku person who came into my life and whisked me away into a magical land of weird bonus like I
this felt like this was more because I was getting fewer and fewer friends I was being driven more
and more into the depths of the internet like because I was in boarding school and I hated everyone
and well I mean being friends with don son didn't take me out of the internet at all because we
only talked online like he was a hikikomori like even though he lived in my town we didn't hang out
as much as we just sat on yahoo messenger all day and like message each other and like and it wasn't
just that he took because he taught me a lot of different stuff like I threw him I figured out
exactly how to use IRC and I would use that to like download manga and stuff and at one point I was
part of a scanslation team uh you know with an IRC channel um which you just go through you just
go through all the motions of being a weird yeah the internet right I had I I was a I was a proof
reader for a group called rice ball issues where I would just take the stuff and make it sound better
in English and uh fun fact and this is before anyone had heard of anything that this author had
ever done in the in the u.s. no no no no I knew about him by this point I was the proof reader
and this is if you go if you go read this chapter online on any of the websites I've checked and it's
it's the one I proof read uh excel world chapter one reiki kawahara's excel world uh the guy who
would go on to make sword on your most your most hated fucking show of all time I I proof read
chapter one of that and I got you're bound by you're bound to him forever yeah but I want I want
everyone in the audience to know this if you've ever read chapter one of that of that comic like
they were telling me because I I wanted to write like a lot of swears into it like in places where
it made sense and like I did get like they let me there was like a punk character and they let me go
all out with making him swear like crazy but there's a part where the fat kid like uh he gets like
this lunch made for him by this cute girl and he's a piece of shit so he throws the lunch on the ground
and he runs away and the way the framing of the panel is the only translation that would fit there
was I'm so fucked up the shinji ikari and I really wanted that there and they wouldn't let me because
they said he wouldn't swear because his language isn't that like you know and I was like oh fuck you
so if you're reading that go read it and change it in your head make him say I'm so fucked up there
it fits so perfectly and I was always mad that they made me change that um let me tell a story
of my internet life this is the greatest story this is the greatest deed I ever did this is the
ultimate chapter of my life I'll never top this this is the story of how I bend saint uh like
saint george slaying the dragon uh slew slew the dragon kin I slew the other kin forums
oh what did you what do you mean by slew well I'll tell you digi I'll tell you how this went down
I was on 4chan in like probably 2007 2008 now I never got hugely into 4chan culture I was never a
big poster but it did expose me to a lot of the shit that was out there and I came to understand
the other kin and what they were and the the concept of the other kin filled me with more
intellectual rage than than anything had up to that point just the just the way that they would
play fast and loose with their definitions the way that they would twist their words to to change
their reality to be what they wanted it to be the way that they could they could just define
being a dragon to be whatever they wanted it to so they could say oh I'm a dragon I'm a fairy
it made me so mad so of course I had to go and be with them on the internet so I went and I found
the other kin forums and I logged in and I made a fucking manifesto of a serial killer and I and I
made and I made like a persona for myself I was I was an angel kin and I went in there and I told
them guys I think I'm an angel and they were like this is where ben saint comes from by chance
probably all wrapped up in the same sort of neuroses so I so I was like I think I feel like a
connection to heaven and stuff I'm an angel kin and they were like cool totally and so I I started
telling them stories for my life and and but I started I started making shit up I started being
like today today I close my eyes and I and I felt my phantom wings I felt like you know six wings
from my back and they were like cool cool and then I was like today I today I passed my hand over
the hand over my friend and I blessed him with knowledge and he got a 100 this is exactly the
kind of trolling that I think was happening to me with that goal like it was exactly this brand
of trolling that I was experiencing and and I just I just got more and more out there with that I
said today I closed I can I can see with my eyes closed I can tell the future I have legitimate
superpowers I was like guys I have fucking superpowers hold up for just a second hold up for
just a second I'm looking I'm looking at the first chapter of excel world right now and I'm seeing
this guy I don't see this character say Arita you pigly little bitch don't fuck around with me
that's how you know I translated that you pig like a bitch only I would have put that that's pretty
good oh boy I gotta say wait proofreader said that said that said that was that something
that was you all right all right all right all right anyway anyway the point is eventually I got
banned right because they eventually figured out I was a troll because I was just because I was just
a superhero I was just telling them an actual superhero origin story I see but I wasn't giving up
I came back and I had a new identity and this time I was a mind I was a mind flayer from Dungeons
and Dragons I had the soul of a mind flayer and the thing about that is that it's not a
mythological creature Gary Gygax just made it up in the 70s it's like totally invented from whole
cloth but I pretended that it had this big mythical backstory eventually I got banned then I came back
with another persona and this persona I was I was I was a Japanese kami I was a spirit but the
spirit was of what I was a spirit of fatness I was a guy who just who just loved to eat I was
just like yes I that would be a thing that would be a Japanese deity there's a god of everything
yeah I weigh like 600 pounds and I'm only gonna get fatter I love being fat I love how fat I am
I'm going to become more fat and I identify personally on a spiritual level with my fat
that would get you double that would get you double love from both the the otherkin community
and the and like the people who are proud to be fucking fat yeah yeah yeah yeah and they found
this very offensive I was I was banned for that too and I was I was just fed up I was like these
fucks these fucking assholes won't let me express myself these these these people just these people
don't care about truth these people only care about but they just want sit to be the way they
want it to be and someone comes in with a different opinion and a different viewpoint and it scares
them and they hate it so I went on 4chan and I don't remember how I did it but the point is I
whipped up people into a fucking frenzy and I had and I organized a raid and they invaded
the otherkin forums and they literally got the raid you yes I yes I and I have and I destroyed
their so I temporarily disabled their servers and it was it was the best thing that ever happened
I know were you a part of this other kid raid right it's one of those things that you hear about
that everyone talks about is like hey you remember when do they like no people say like they remember
when they went 4chan raided the fucking other kid no people will be like I remember I heard it back
when it might have happened more than once yeah I don't know if I was like did the only one yeah
no I want yeah I'm sure I'm sure you want the only one but like I remember this happened around
4chan does have a long memory they remember everything yeah fucking made a part of 4chan 4chan
I remember like I used to hear a lot during 2014 while the tumblr raid was going on those are like
well what so hey guys post your favorite raids that we've ever done and then someone was like oh
yeah the otherkin forum raids were pretty good oh yeah those those faggots couldn't even handle
anything we shut down their servers for a whole week I was like oh wow that's pretty cool it's
to hear that you were like part of one of those was is that what I want yeah I gave them I I gave
I had like I had like a jolly rod because I was wicked big into one piece I had a jolly
rod made for myself I gave them out and like had people like people were like spamming the
otherkin forums with that image oh man it was it was it was a truly a truly wonderful time to be
me the saint pirates beware beware of the heavens the heaven scribe pirates the heaven scribe pirates
beware if you were yeah I was a fucking yeah I was a fucking nerd oh man oh so like okay but
like one one again I didn't really finish the story but one thing that really changed my perception
was when I moved when I not moved to America but like moving to America did a whole another thing
but when I started coming over to America for vacation I would that was when I first really
got into YouTube and like before all I would use YouTube for was to watch anime like that was all
YouTube that was the only benefit it had for me it was to watch uh three days grace videos
AMVs and uh an anime that was all I wanted that was that's all I wanted from it just a bunch of
weird punk grace yeah really shitty punk rock anime and AMVs sometimes AMVs brought both of
those things together but like um so I would and then when I came to America I found out about the
it's kind of like I got the classical education in internet memes that was I feel like that's what
happened I like when I the first time I came was 2008 so I got no 2006 so I got a classical
education in internet memes that's when I got my Numa Numa that's when I got my that's when
I got my 2006 no no no no oh yeah it is yeah it is that all yeah that is star wars lightsaber
kid Numa Numa yeah all of all of that stuff all of that stuff like
fuck who's the the gay black guy song the one oh yes oh what what in the but what in the but
what what in the oh fucking hell man I got this is probably would have been like 2008 yeah this
all this yeah because I remember I came 2006 2008 2009 and those three specific years I would get
such a jump in knowledge about what fucking like you had a whole year's worth of new
yes oh yes exactly oh man fucking all of these shitty internet memes what drip fed to me I think
I think shoot the whoop is the old is the oldest meme that I ever knew I think that was the first
meme I ever came into contact with like
oh badger badger badger badger badger badger badger mushroom mushroom yeah yeah like then
unless you count lol cats as a meme I think and then even me on cut was one of the memes that I
fucking go into an education like from that era that 2005 era that I was saying I wasn't really
into internet videos yet I I forgot that I did have a phase of getting really into albino black sheep
because like everyone knew like ebombs world at the time and like new grounds I had always heard
that ebombs world was a terrible place and you get viruses and there'd be dicks everywhere but like a
lot of the content on like a lot of the best stuff on ebombs world was all stolen from other places
and albino black sheep was this place that uh that I don't remember the name of the type of uh videos
they did but it was um like they had a bunch of videos where it'd be like like almost like
magazine cutout look to it where it'd be like just a bunch of like random celebrities and funny memes
and stuff like in these videos and they were some of them were fucking hilarious there's one called
French erotic film that I recommend everybody look up it's just a fun little song about Colin
mockery uh and a bunch of memes and uh it's great but like yeah like I got really into
that for a brief period and that was also I think where end of the world came from which is an internet
classic uh you guys remember legendary frog uh no legendary frog was a fucking peat piece of
shit god damn it so terrible in hindsight I think uh I think the llama song might have come from
albino black sheep yeah I I mean I don't know I'm not looking like I'm not embarrassed to have
liked homestar runner but I am embarrassed to have like legendary frog do any of you remember a video
called gonads and strife yes that's from albino black sheep as well gonads in the lightning in
the lightning in the rain I remember I remember fucking uh okay like also the idea of going into
the internet and finding like just the deepest going deeper and deeper into some stuff that like
you know nobody else is looking at but you're just there being entirely enamored by it for example
this is something I no one's ever been able to relate with me on I was I was a I know I was a
giant fan of this weird flash cartoon about not about knuckles it was it was like not it was like
a sprite flash cartoon like it was a bunch of sprites they took sprites from the sonic games
and a bunch of other like scarpcom video games and they made like a giant series it was called
knuckles adventure in fact let me fucking look this shit up because it's I I I
I
eight bit theater Tom did you read eight bit theater back in the day
you know what that was the one about the final fantasy characters right yeah I'll I was so into
eight bit theater I fucking bought that guy's book I bought his novel and it fucking sucked
even as a kid I knew that I could I was reading his novel and I was like this is a terrible book
this is an incredibly poorly written novel Brian Clevenger fuck you Brian Clevenger
I had six volumes of mega tokyo say dark horse would release it and I fuck me with a stick it's
still fucking there everybody go look up knuckles adventure it was demote to
no like no way the videos are still fucking there oh here's mine here's mine along those lines
oh fuck I don't even remember the name of it there was a web comic that I was like super
fucking into it was a sprite comic and oh my god I can't remember the name of it it was like
it was like it was like a goofy comedy adventure type thing but it was one where like as it went
along the story you know got darker and more violent and serious but always while having like a sort
of tongue-in-cheek attitude I just remember thinking that like in terms of writing quality I always
felt like it was the best web comic I had found but I can't fucking remember the name I'd like
you guys just to just give a little bit of a look to this because I like I opened up and the first
five seconds encapsulate why I was so into it as a kid because I will watch the first five seconds
of knuckles adventure oh my god what am I in for oh my this is so it's so amazing it's yeah it's
amazing the one word for it it's so amazing it's got Inuyasha in it holy shit I would have loved
this this is the kind of shit I was so into as a kid I would have absolutely loved this I know
like this oh man this was my shit look at this I'm able I would have definitely loved that because
you could tell as soon as I saw Inuyasha I would have been fucking sore exactly because knuckles
is cool enough but like Inuyasha they all had special reasons as to why they were in the same
universe and they all had like personality quirks and different interpretations based on how it was
the fucking nut your shit man I'm just like now that I look back on it I'm probably one of about
like a hundred people in total who ever gave a fuck about this you know what I mean like
it this this was something that on the internet that nobody would have given a fuck about well
see I'm right like Jimmy that leads me well into a into a point that I wanted to make about why I
got into 4chan and like okay like for me it because like 2008 or so was like the height of my like
I don't want to say dark web but like knowing I think we should yeah you should stop I think
we should all talk about how we all got into 4chan because those are all interesting stories
I don't know that Ben or Tom is particularly into 4chan but uh yeah I think I already kind of
said like I heard that it was a terrible place for terrible people I checked it out and read it
like a bit here and there I never really got that into it although I did kind of get into draw fag
threads on tg I talked about this in my interview I would someone drew me my dnd character on tg
and it was amazing and I hung around there and would like do a little sprite art of other people's
characters for a while uh so yeah for a while t I would go on tg once in a while but that was
about it for 4chan um well for me like because I had I had a I had like a friend who was a big
time 4chaner but he was like a beatard and he was like a you know troll who like liked 4chan for
the the insanity of it you know it's like I was familiar with 4chan mostly as like a place I would
never want to go because it was all going to be pictures of weird gross shit and I'd seen like
little like I'd seen people who did like 4chan pilgrimages and what they came back with and I'd
seen tub girl and that haunted my nightmares uh which for those who don't know was like a picture
of a woman in a bathtub like shitting piss out of her ass and just just go to ask jves and type what
is tub girl and then yeah uh and like and like shitting dick uh the classic shitting dick nipples
um which is exactly what it sounds like so like I always thought of 4chan as being like that but
then like at some point I found out about the anime board and that it was just a place where people
just fucking talk about anime and what's what I have always loved about 4chan is that you can find
someone who's into fucking anything you can think of like no matter how obscure your taste is someone
on there knows about it and so like I remember there was a time it was it was when a certain magical
index was airing and that show wasn't that popular at the time that it was it was relatively popular
but my favorite character was last order which is like this little lolly girl who is uh like the
lolly version of misaka who's the well-known character from the show and like I just really
wanted like fan art of last order and I go on like 4chan and start a thread about her and like
every piece of it that was in existence got posted there like all these people who like last order
were there and I was like nowhere else on the internet will I get this in no forum in no social
media site could I like bring up like maybe now I could because I'm like famous I could like bring
something up on Twitter and people would know what I'm talking about but like at the time
that was the only way I could have a conversation about this obscure thing and like
was last order the inspiration for dark holy uh no not no dark holy actually
was before her uh before last order but it's my naming convention is the same type of naming
it sounds like the same kind of name yeah it's also a lolly yeah mine was more influenced by like
everything I like has stupid names like you know a lot of the anime I've been into is like
weird naming conventions but anyway uh the the biggest one that I got into on 4chan was there's
this character called bico b i k k o and she was like she had one arm and one leg and one
eye I think and she was always smoking and she could play guitar and like for whatever reason
that just sounds like you know that whole thing about you were telling me about aesthetic persona
yeah that just sounds like the most fucking obscure aesthetic persona I've ever heard of
she was like what the thing is that she was a character from this dojinshi by uh like just a
self-published comic not like a porn one but it was just self-published comic by this guy called
romantic fool 1990 or something like that and uh he had published this comic with this character
in like the mid-2000s and no one could find this comic because apparently he had sold all the copies
including the master copy so he did not have it anymore and no one who had it was like I guess
willing to break the binding or just didn't realize that it had become like the character was
becoming a phenomenon but for whatever reason people had found out about the character design
and like the vague ideas of her backstory and like there was a lot of like art of her like with
like uh like marijuana iconography for some reason I've seen this character before yeah
she became popular on like guru chan because she's like a you know sort of a gourd character I guess
and like uh and so like every once in a while there'd be a threat about her and like she ended up
over time getting like tons of fan art just because people loved this character idea so much
that there was like all this all this fan art of bico and like people imagining what her situation
was like and stuff but like pretty early into that when there was just like a decent handful of stuff
then there was a threat about it on 4chan and I was like hey what if we organized making our own
dojinchi about bico and like you know incorporating all the elements we know about her and just like
do a daily life story and then there will be an actual bico story out there and like I actually
got people organized enough that we made an IRC channel and we were like planning it out
and I was gonna like we we had all these ideas did I ever come to anything like it came close
because I was gonna draw storyboards and then there was this artist girl who uh like offered to do
you know was gonna do the art and like she had drawn a bunch of like preliminary sketches and
stuff which looked kind of cool and like I had sent uh she had like a very distinct like scratchy
art style which I'm of course into but it wasn't like great but uh I had sent her the storyboards
and then she just never ended up finishing a page but it was like kind of a like a lot of people
knew about it and like people would keep coming back to the because I posted about it on my blog
and people would keep coming back they're like hey is this still a thing and I'm like nope but
eventually years down the line someone finally scanned the be the real uh comic but fun fact
that I found out like much later along the line the guy who did drew that comic is also the artist
of izuna legend of the unemployed ninja like those games hold up hold up because I just looked up
I just looked up because when you say these things and this is the great thing about the
internet nothing ever fucking dies right I just looked up bico and right after the her twitter
account is my blog it's it's this is bico and you can help us bring her to life my sword is
unbelievably dull.wordpress.co holy shit so yeah this is why the internet is great like you nothing
ever fucking dies right but that character is so obscure that like you know that there's probably
10 people who knew about her and I organized them all to try to make a comic but it it didn't come
to fruition but now that comic is out there and she's become like in the time since then the
character has become way more popular like there's there's fucking hundreds of fan arts of her out
there on on the subject of web comics when we were talking about this a little bit oh boy one of the
well one of the biggest like like key moments I think in in in where I've come to be in my place
on the internet I think looking back was uh control all delete oh okay I thought I thought you're
gonna say something else all right they're gonna bring where you I think I think I know what you
yeah they are bringing a different web comic that we've all I am gonna it's related okay okay because
I came to I can't all right I was on something awful I would browse the something awful forums
for a while in like I don't know 2010 or 2011 or something seems like a lot of the internet
came from there didn't the entire concept of let's plays originate from something awful
I think they did I think well okay the the four chain guy the reason why was yeah the reason why
something awful and fortune are both like oh wait something awful used to be a really big deal and
I think I think when I was on there was a little bit past its heyday but still they had these long
threads devoted entirely to hating on control all delete and every time control all delete came out
with a new comic people would post the new comic everyone would just page in pages of shitting
on it talking about how terrible the new punchline was and how and how terrible the art was and like
rewriting it and reconfiguring it and just redoing the whole thing to try and make it a little good
try and see how the author fucked up and how they could maybe undo the terrible terrible crime
come back sorry I okay cool um anyway I would browse these threads all the time and just look
at this fucking asshole artist and then hate on him and people would talk about other shitty
artists and of course uh sonichu and christian western chairman always got into sonichu yeah
though those control all delete hate threads were how I got into sonichu oh man uh and
you know I guess that's the end of the story no but another the weird thing is the weird thing is
like like the reason why a lot of the internet came from both fortune and something awful I think
it's because for a long time when you know how everyone had heard of like new grounds fortune
something awful back in the day like everyone had heard of those places so because everyone had
heard of those places or a lot of the people who were inclined to be at the forefront of
dare I say internet culture were the people who perused these places so so not through well not
through the basis of the fact that I'll continue I was gonna say I guess because I think did you
said before nowadays the internet is all about places that aggregate constantly yeah so I guess
like before there were formal places like for that like youtube and and stuff uh and maybe tumblr
or something I mean for like forums like that and for chan and maybe new grounds and stuff
were places where you could go to find lots of stuff all in one place yeah that was that was kind
of that was kind of the thing so like and all the creative people who would happen to be there would
would end up making these things and those things would be shared aromatically and they would become
in in and of themselves like the troll face for example those things would in and of themselves
just become just like things that get shared repeatedly and just spread all across and it
was just some random fucking drawing some dude made for a thread sometime that I guarantee you the
guy who made the quote unquote troll face did not did not like think to themselves I'm going to turn
this into a worldwide phenomenon with this like he fucking drew a random ass weird like annoying
little face that he thought was funny and just posted it and people thought it was funny and
kept posting it that's I feel like that's the reason why that's the reason why the idea of a forced
meme is so annoying to some people because memes in and of themselves are supposed to be kind of
pure like that's another important part of the internet like a meme is supposed to be a thing
that just happens it's supposed to spark like wildfire like things don't just things spring up
out the ether and just now everyone's talking about it the the reason why I had to tell that
control alt delete hate thread story and like the the point of that is that like getting into
sonichu was like like sonichu and chris wesson channel it was like a huge it was an entire
chapter of my internet life like for like for like over a year I was on the sonichu forums like
or the on the sonichu wiki like monitoring this guy's life and monitoring all the developments
of the son I was of the sonichu fandom for lack of a better word like I was I was deep I was deep
fucking in to that shit oh my goodness gracious um I don't know I just I just had to say that
because I wanted people to know that like that's the point the point is that this was a full a
full chapter the I even tried I even I even got into amateur game development I started making
I started making an rpg maker game and I did tons and tons of sprite art for a game that I never
even got close to finishing that was going to be based on his life it was called christian
weston chandler's adult chronicles uh yep I definitely like that's a sad chapter of my
there's a big part of me that like really misses the the feeling of like going out in the internet
and finding something that was just not like anything else because like I think that because
we've centralized everything now where it's like you've got youtube facebook twitter tumblr uh you
know and then like a few other social media type sites like I think that on the one hand
it's allowed us to like perfect a lot of the content and like make stuff that's better than
it's ever been before but I also think it necessarily like pushes everyone to making
stuff that's kind of the same like everyone tailored to what that's kind of tailored towards
you know that's actually makes sense because one of one of my friends I think you guys know him
his name's Elijah uh like you know Elijah's a guy who just he's he's uh uh remember that video I
posted where the guy it was just a guy on the phone sending me a bunch of yeah it was that if
that's my friend Elijah that is that guy the guy with the really shitty opinions so I remember
Elijah was trying to get me into the anime world order podcast and they're a really great podcast
and I was explaining to him like why I had never gotten into them recently because I didn't read
them I didn't like listen to them back in the day and I didn't listen to them now because they're
not on YouTube and I told them that that's like that's exactly why I haven't started I've known
about anime order for 10 years and I've never listened to it because back in the day I didn't
know what a podcast was and like how to actually listen to it and then and like the guy I had
always I had always heard that they were like very like anti moe type guys you know and I was like
really into moe back then so like I was kind of like oh fuck those guys and then like over time
I was like man they're still going that's that's probably like one of the best anime shows on the
I'm willing to bet these guys really know their stuff more than anybody else these guys these guys
like no like I listen to I've listened to a couple of them ever since Elijah wouldn't fucking stop
telling me to go listen to them and to be honest listening to them has filled me with almost as
much knowledge as fucking listening to just you talk or like listening to what listening to
Elijah's or listen to some other friend Darryl Soret is a part of that podcast right yeah Darryl Soret
is like he's the head guy I mean Darryl Soret's a guy who for anyone or audience who doesn't know
about him not only has he been an anime blogger forever he has more knowledge about anything
than anyone else in the world he runs like a million panels at like at anime conventions like
every year at Otacon there will be like a ton of Darryl Soret panels and I make a point to go to
those because they are by far the most interesting panels there in terms of just like breadth of
knowledge uh and he also writes for Otaku USA he even knows about pro wrestling yeah he even knows
about fucking pro wrestling and it's crazy he writes for Otaku USA which is like the only
still running anime magazine in the US and he writes for like anime news network sometimes
he's really he's written articles for so many places and I was telling him that he's not on
YouTube yeah that's the craziest thing like he's not like I was telling Elijah he's not on YouTube
so I haven't listened to him and Elijah was furious at this concept because and it's it's
kind of based on what you just said earlier because Elijah is much older than me and Elijah's been on
the internet for a lot long well he's been on the internet as deeper than I have for a lot longer
and he is still in that mindset of there's a billion different places where you get a billion
different things and Elijah he can't fucking fathom why somebody would shut out another part
just because they're not on this site because he's like I mean
right yeah like I like I mean in fairness I have gone out of my way for biggest problem in the
universe like I go to the website and now both hosts have their own shows that I go to their
websites for that but like with anime world order it's also that it's been running for so long
that it's like it's daunting to think about the idea that like because you know even if it's not
a sequential podcast there's gotta be a million memes and inside jokes and stuff that they
talk about regularly well I've listened to a couple of them I've listened to a couple of them I
didn't really I listened to the one about initial D which has taught me more about initial D than
I've ever actually wanted to know right but like like it isn't really like that but I can I feel
like if I listen to a few more I definitely get that like for example if for example the first
person what if someone was picking this podcast for the first time will not know what well late is
yeah they will all teach them like oh yeah Ben could definitely teach them how to be well laid
or they probably don't get why we keep saying patreon.com slash ben saint or yeah
they don't need to know why they just need to they just need to go there and and pledge they just
need to repeat repeat it over and over again I think I probably am using oh why did you say
simultaneously all the time that's a that's a very inside meme that nobody really knows I think
that I am probably legitimately I think my life has probably been markedly worse all this time
because I haven't been listening to anime world order and I feel like it would probably improve
my entire life to listen to it but if I feel like it would like they are like they're a really good
anime podcast I think actually I think the real reason I haven't listened is that I'm afraid of how
stupid I'll feel for not having listened to them when I first found out about them in like 2007
and I'll feel so bad that I didn't know talking about talking about web comics and podcasts oh boy
here's an internet thing penny arcade definitely everyone knows penny arcade in my opinion it
kind of sucks and isn't very funny I agree but they have a podcast and sometimes when they're when
they record themselves thinking of the comic and they're like they're they're banter with each other
and their conversations about like what's going on in gaming news and like what's going on in their
lives as they're thinking of the comic and writing the comic is is awesome it's so great I can't
even though I don't recommend anyone read penny arcade but I highly recommend everyone listen to
the penny arcade podcast it is gaban i don't know gaban taiko are like two of my favorite dudes
to listen to because just wicked fun actually that's how she that's how she gonna suck they're
such cool guys they seem a way cooler than like because the characters in penny arcade seem like
total douchebags and like penny arcade is so much worse than them I don't understand because it
comes from that era it comes from an era when like web comic characters were usually thinly
veiled versions of the real people so you see those characters and you're like these guys must
be total douchebags but then they are not like their characters really yeah I think there is some
element of that like the format is just outdated but like it's just what they do so they're not
gonna change it it's the old is the old tim buckley control out delete style like fucking I mean I
I mean that's a whole another level I mean penny arcade is the worst web I'm sorry not penny arcade
control out delete is the worst penny arcade is just kind of mediocre and not very funny
but okay and that actually brings me to another chapter of my fucking internet existence I remember
one time like I was on vacation in Nigeria and my dad took me to Abuja which is the capital where
one of my childhood friends stayed and he was a huge fan of Tegua Tig that guy with the glasses
yeah I had sure and he introduced me to the nostalgia critic and he introduced me to a
bunch of other content creators like Linkara and you know just a bunch of that guy that dude in
the suede all all all of those people so I became a fan through him and I started watching a lot of
nostalgia critic and that that again was another like window into another chapter of the internet
like people people talk about Tegua Tig now like it was a weird otherworldly thing but people need
to understand it still seems like a yeah no but that like for better for worse for a long time
in internet content creation that was the that was the golden ticket that was the high water
yes and and I gotta say it's really lowered the bar for everyone yeah because of because of how
shit they are everyone else thinks it's okay to be that shit and the terrible thing is it's true
because that's what people accept because they were because they were the first big collective
to get to that point people have just been like oh if it's as good as Tegua Tig then I can I could
run with it they were the first ones to do it so they didn't have to do it well but that established
the go the standard as you don't have to do it well and then so then it then like another if you
can't tell I kind I kind of hate Tegua Tig oh no no no I think we all do I think it's like no no no
okay I think the PCP can absolutely go to war with Tegua Tig because I think we all hate them
to me to me is genuinely an actual personal gripes issue because I I really hate Jesu Otaku
like personal this is on a personal level me and her I mean me and him I think since he's he
him is now a guy it's complicated like it's I don't yeah like I despise that entire group
same as I know I know that Jeff was a big fan of of Jesu Otaku and like that inspired him to
make videos both of us both of us hate them both of us hate her now because she inspired both of
us she inspired both of us on how on to on making youtube videos my inspirations for youtube actually
were movie bob gigak who's now one of my close friends yeah movie bob gigak extra credits zero
punctuation and Jesu Otaku those are like the people those are like the things that push me on
how to make content now make content that's like nothing like I just want to say I know that like
I know that there was a time when Jesu Otaku was a big deal because of the fact that like
she was the she was the only person doing anime videos it was her and gigak it was her and gigak
who was the only person doing anime reviews on youtube and everyone liked the deck out the
glass of style but as someone who only found her later like I was you know it relatively early
into getting into internet videos someone like was like oh what about Jesu Otaku and like I watched
like her last like review and I was like this is fucking terrible like yeah everything I would
not want her attitude the smarmy attitude she had about anime the dismissiveness over like
yes fan service elements and sage who is the ugliest man who's ever decided to show his face
on camera and has the longest opinions in the world okay you see he was he was a guest in the video
that there's a there's a there's footage right you know who gigak is you know gunt right gunt went
to alcon which is a convention in england and a bunch of that guy with the glasses people were there
and sage was doing a live showing of his Evangelion review and the camera pans towards gunt and you
can just see the death in his like the death glare he's giving sage
i didn't see what's amazing for those who don't know sage is like infamous for the fact that he
really hates end of Evangelion and like has like he has this whole like position on it i guess that
is just like entirely wrong like he just and also doesn't okay okay so basically basically he is
when i say i like to use the term second boomer a lot right like did you's heard me say a lot
when i say second boomer i mean people who grew up who grew up on anime in the second boom which is
the early 90s where they got stuff like a quira ghost in the shell all the cool sci-fi stuff
and sage fashions himself he he builds himself up as that kind of person oh i only talk about
90s anime i'm pretty sure he's too young to even have been around yeah like i only talk about 90s
anime i only talk about like the action stuff and all that and power to you i like action stuff too
but the way he approaches it and the way he talks about modern anime as if there's nothing good
coming out now like he's he's one of those people yeah one of the that he's one of the anime stuff
he's a relic from an era like there was a point because this is what for chan was when i first
got into a for chan was constant fighting over whether anime was going to shit because there was
the whole like anime fans from the 90s and and early 2000s were really like genre fans like
there were people who were into anime because it was sci-fi and action and had all these masculine
things and so when anime became like they started having all these cute girls and stuff this is
where we get people like that anime snob who like despises modern anime even though it's just base
it's not anime has gotten no worse in terms of quality the problem is that it's just a yeah it's
different the genres are different yeah it used to be that there was a lot of sci-fi and now
sci-fi is not an interesting genre anymore because we all understand now now now we're in
now we're in the fantasy era yeah we're kind of in the fantasy era and like and so it just
so happened the genres changed and like so during the that the period where that change was happening
anime fandom was nothing but people arguing over whether anime was going to shit that's all it was
the whole late 2000s was just people arguing about whether or not moe was good or shit and
like i don't think anime discourse really made any progress at the time like that's why
like people look at someone like me coming out now and like my stuff seems so much more like
heady than most of what people have gotten because for so long anime has just been literally arguing
over whether or not something is even good not like explaining why it's good which is interesting
but you know just like arguing over the quality of shows because the old guard of anime fans feel
like has such a different taste in genres from the new and even i didn't i didn't necessarily
understand how to discuss that like this is a weird tangent but like we'll get back on top but
like i didn't know how to discuss that that's why i have this really odd video on my channel
called the importance of animation and it's a stupid video but one thing i do pride on my
younger self is that even back then i knew that we were in a wrong headed place when it came
to discussing anime like when every time somebody will talk about an action scene they'll say oh it
has good animation or it has bad animation fuck it talk about what makes it good or bad right talk
about talk about the camera angles talk about like talk about the aesthetic of it talk about what it
makes you feel talk about how justify your opinion like what this justify your opinion and like none
of that was coming through in any of the even of the people i really liked even of the people at
the time even though now i really don't follow their content anymore so guys like glass reflections
guys like uh jesso taku as we had mentioned earlier even though i used to be huge fans of
them back then they didn't fucking talk about any of that and they would just like give her like
look at how dumb this show is it's it's it's dumb it's not good jessel taku jessel taku every
now and then every now and then she would let her film school side she would let her film school
side show and she would get into a little bit of that like in her black cat review she talks
hold on jimmy we're getting too deep into your rules here
fuck okay okay so fine let me let me get back i think we should probably be wrapping this up
soon because i think we're getting pretty close to the end here's here's my here's my take on all
of this here's my here's my closing thoughts anime shit or not shit we'll have plenty of time to
sort it out after our after our beautiful white western god smites japan with holy fire and lightning
for the terrible sin of creating fully kooli too wow oh god we still don't i i i'm still like in that
denial stage where i don't believe fully kooli too will really happen like until oh it's happening
it's happening it won't it will it will because japan will be nothing but a smoldering crater
really because because the righteous a righteous god would not let you know the sad thing is that i
have now seen evidence that it will happen because i watched the first episode of the new berserk
anime and after that no travesty is too farfetched like i've been i've been i've been i've been
sending my righteous prayers my righteous prayers every night have reached his holy
oh by the way by the way before we get back on track like we need to do we need to do a week
are we being out on the fucking new season because oh yeah this this new berserk is gonna be is
definitely gonna be a point is gonna be a point to touch on but yeah okay back on my internet story
i'm gonna zoom through it now because i'm gonna go from the 2010s up until now all right so
2011 is an important year in my life one of the most important years like 2011 is like the
keystone in my life forever june 18th 20 june 18th 2011 was the day i first set foot in america
to start living here and at that point i obviously at that point i was i was about 16 so i was of
the age where i understood how the internet worked i nothing that i know in terms of how to maneuver
the internet has changed in that time but the one thing that has changed is my attitude towards
the things i see because now i'm much i'm much more open to interacting with other people
which opened up an entirely new dimension in terms of like just the internet in general which
like which could even be its own other podcast in terms of internet friends like that that i've
proposed to other people but like the idea of going on the internet meeting people talking to
them about stuff that you're into which is stuff that you guys had been doing much you know much
earlier than i did but something that i had only been doing up until like fairly recently within
the last five years and it kind of made me understand opinions a bit differently because
back when i was younger i didn't have like i would watch anime and i just i just be like i like this i
don't like this there was nobody who i could share that opinion with like i had no like growing up
in Ghana i had no friends who watched anime the closest i had were like this one dude who like
Naruto when i was in boarding school and my cousins who live in america who i would see like once
every two years and who know who i now live with but like my cousins who live in america made fun
of me for my name yeah i went over to their house for christmas one year and i and i put on like
tsunami or something i was watching raroni kenshin oh boy and they were like dude what are you
watching dude these these are just cartoons for japanese people or whatever and i was like you
you stupid baka gaijin scum oh you don't understand the majesty of the japanese animation folded a
thousand times longer and gaming and gaming oh that was me another important another important
part of how i've started to interact with the internet is torrenting video games because torrenting
video like torrenting anime was one thing torrenting video games is a new dimension man yeah like
the level to the level of video games i've played within the last five years has increased
exponentially not just because of stuff like that you can get on your computer through emulators
through like just a bunch of different means i've been i've played games because of the internet
i've played games now that i would have never been able to play as a kid because i had a pal ps2
i had a pal ps2 and ntsc games wouldn't work on them meaning games bought from america wouldn't
work on my ps2 so now i've been able to open up my entire i feel like i feel like how old people
feel when they're able to like when they have a bunch of money and they can just spend money on
shit that they couldn't do as kids right i feel like that oh yeah i feel like that now as like as
like an early that's how dude i you know my first console was the n64 and i never had a ps1
and i got a ps2 late so like everything before the ps2 era of gaming like i only got into because
of emulators like i'd never touched like a super nintendo and now i've played like probably 100
super nintendo games as a result of emulation that's another really important facet of the
internet being able to get stuff that you couldn't possibly have even come close to getting
in any other means while you're growing up that's one reason why the internet is like amazing and
another another really important facet of the internet is news like we get news now i get all
my news from twitter yeah what you guys never watch the news but i i usually find out what's
like if something's going on eventually like if it's something mainstream happening like
Guillermo del Toro is going to tweet about it and i'll find out about it from him because he does
a lot of like relief effort tweeting and if it's more like political than all the fucking uh
like liberals i follow will tweet about it if i if i see someone tweeting news i fucking mute him
i don't care because i don't want i don't want that shit in my life my dad my dad is a my dad's
an like i don't want to say this because it's gonna sound weird but my dad's an intellectual
right he's one of those kinds of people he he loves to read he he's written books that's not
weird that's that's cool yeah he's he's written books he's uh he's done he's done talks and stuff
he even has a TED talk online if you i'm not gonna tell anyone to find it uh but like he
what's what's it about it's about it's about the difference between it's about the inter-correlation
between uh activism and politics and political between political activism and political action
whether or not they're intertwined dude my dad's a politician it doesn't matter but like uh
he when when he was when he was uh when every time i would when i was living with him he would
always buy newspapers every morning every on the way to school on the way to school we'd always
stop by a newspaper stand and he'd always buy one and i'll be like why does that always buy
newspapers like why does he need newspapers all the fucking time and because he didn't have read
it yeah and then now that i'm older i i'm like the first thing i do when i wake up is i check
kamatsu for gaming news i check twitter for like my life for just stuff i have all other stuff i
check crunch roll news i check anime news network then i start perusing like youtube to see if anyone
was made in videos about current events then i start looking through the you know internet just
to see regular current events and i'm like fuck i have become my father yeah like through the internet
i have become my father i i go to reddit and i go to r slash the procrastinators to see who's posted
new shit and that's that's my news and then i'm done i i want to jump on something you said a
minute ago jimmy just briefly because you were talking about learning about like other people
having opinions and stuff and yeah like for me because like i said i started on forums which is
all about you know different people sharing their opinions and what eventually drove me off of forums
because i have absolutely no interest in that kind of thing anymore um is the realization that i didn't
care about anyone else's opinions and that other people didn't care enough about my opinions because
like we'd have a thread about a new show like a new episode comes out and like i'd post in the thread
and then no one would actually respond to my post everyone was just sharing their thoughts on the
episode and i was like well i wanted to talk about like my impressions i didn't want to just hear
everyone's impressions with no one responding to each other so then that's why like i got really
into my anime blog because if i wrote about an episode on there then the comments were only
gonna be about my reaction to the episode and like discussing the points i've brought up so
eventually i just felt like i wasn't getting anything out of forums and i was getting everything
out of blogging and that's why i just totally moved in that direction and never looked back
like i've never gone i think forums are fucking pointless now like even like you know somewhere
like our anime like they have halfway decent discussions but it's about uh like specifically
if it's one of my videos getting posted up there then it's a discussion of my video whereas
there's no way i would jump in on like you know new episode of the show is out let's all discuss it
because they have those posts on there and i'm like no i don't fucking care like it's too broad
you know i'd rather talk about my own opinions so yeah my sear my sheer self-centeredness drove
me off of forums and it drove you into making youtube videos oh boy like i mean the reason i
got driven like into using the internet for like content creation it was kind of because
well okay it was it was kind of because through internet videos i felt like i was learning how
to make them i was like i learned how not to make internet videos through that guy with the glasses
i learned i got my start on learning how to make internet videos with this one video that
gantt put out called oh so you want to be a content creator and he made he just gives
these really brief introduction i was like just write a script basically what it boils down to is
write a script record the audio find a video editor put the footage in there and release the video
and to be honest if you want to get into video making write a script record the audio put that's
that that is really the bare bones of what we do and that kind of is what like learning that kind
of stuff from the internet brought me to where i am today and it's it's kind of crazy to think
all the stuff i've learned every single part of the internet that i've learned is now kind of like
my little weird it's kind of like my little weird like background and you know education on how to
do youtube because all the stuff i've done like from torrenting anime uh look at all led us up to
this it all led us up to this point like using the internet to research information all that stuff
yeah we gotta we gotta start wrapping this up tom you said you had something you wanted a question
you wanted to present when you got back right yeah it's kind of crazy because we used it feels
and this sounds really like edgy if you if you want to put it this way but like all of us grew up in
the wild west all of us grew up in the wild west of the internet like it was it was not in any way
safe it was not in any way less like it was way more decentralized something that i have found
something that i found disturbing is like i'll find like i i tend to like content that's not
like you know like whitewashed right like i don't i don't expect to necessarily always even agree
with everything i'm seeing but like i enjoy a lot of stuff like musically right like music is still
pretty out there and the new releases will come out that are totally weird and abrasive and interesting
and like whenever i hear something like that i'm always like man you could not do this on youtube
like you could not have a career of making something that's totally out there because
no one will find you people will only like people come to youtube for very specific things and when
they click on your videos they have very specific expectations you want you want to know the crazy
thing it's kind of like to speak on that youtube thing like even though you guys probably haven't
been making content on youtube like you got you guys started a right like doing a bunch of pony
stuff right but and around that time yeah i'm sorry i'm not supposed to bring that up well i started
no no 2007 personally doing like weird videos but yeah so like but the thing is back back then to
make to get someone over i mean to get someone you know like a bet a bigger channel like to put
someone up you know at the same level you were to like promote someone else was a lot easier
because there were video responses if you if someone you're someone you'll subscribe to you see
what they're liking and you see what what they're commenting on other people's videos so then it's
like oh what is it what's he doing i want to see what he's doing now youtube has kind of gotten rid
of all that and kind of streamlined it so that only the people who are already big or can get big
easily based on very easily digestible content stay big and get shown which is kind of probably
you know is a kind of weird tom what's the rest of your question is there more we'll continue
to yeah i that's what that's what that's what fortune that's what fortune tries to be yeah fortune
tries to retain some of that chaos huge rubber banding effect where like because especially
for people who are making like the weird or stuff who are gonna start like being like i don't want
to be on youtube anymore and there are like a lot of audiences will follow you know i think that if
i think that um people who have large audiences when they migrate like they stand to lose a huge
amount of their audience but they will still bring a lot of people with them and they will those people
will move and they will change the way their attitudes are about stuff and i think that
like there's gonna be a point where uh you know like for me personally i have a a fairly sizable
audience but not nearly enough that i can take huge risks with it you know like i can post i can
post whatever weird shit i want on my digiroctor dark channel and people won't complain too much
unless i was to go on like some weird racist tirade or something like that most of the stuff i do
online is not going to have a major effect on me but like if i had a like a really huge audience
the kind where i could cut off 90 percent of it and i'd still be like like imagine if i had
10 times the subs i had now and then but i only need the amount that i have now then alienating
90 percent of my audience is no longer a problem and so as long as i feel like i can carry 10 percent
of it then i could go wherever i want and do whatever i want and i would feel comfortable with
that and i think that that's the kind of stuff that like if i got to that level and i wanted to
do something really different and i was like you know what youtube is too strict and what it allows
me to do i want to you know launch my own platform and do my own unique art that's not like what the
youtube formula is then i would do that and i would carry whatever small percentage of my audience
i can with me and go off to do this other thing and i think that we might start seeing that if
like if a channel with a million subs is like hey youtube is too restrictive and i want to do
something a little different then let's all go over here and you know enough people will follow them
i mean i don't know how long do you think it would take for google to buy it out
before what how long do you think how long do you think it would take before google buys it out
well i mean i'm not talking about like making a new youtube like i think we'll see more people
just making their own websites again you know like we'll go back to having a that guy with the
glasses collective or i mean a lot of those people they still have the website infrastructure there
like you know like john shran's group like normal boots you know like there's this whole
group called normal boots they have their own website with their own video hosting but
nobody goes there because everyone's on youtube but if those if john shran packed up his bags and
said i'm leaving youtube i'm going to post my stuff on normal boots fuck youtube then like
he'll lose a huge amount of his audience but he has so many viewers that he can still you know he
could still live off of it even if people like even if he was forcing people to go to another site
and like well i mean a lot i think i think someone like i think someone like yms that will happen
like when yms gets big enough because he's he's fairly big he's got like 400 000 subs if yms ever
got to a point where he was making enough money and had a big enough following that he could
justifiably leave youtube he would do it in a fucking heartbeat because he hates youtube and
he'd be will he'd be like oh i've got enough audience yeah exactly yeah
right i mean i've said this before all the time where like i'm like there's a lot of like i don't
care that much if my videos don't make it onto youtube because that's not where my money comes
from and like i've had times where like a video got blocked and i'm like all right well i'm gonna
put it on daily motion give it to my patrons and then you know fight fight the claim on youtube till
the video comes back but as long as i'm making the money it doesn't matter where it is you know as
long as my patrons can find it so i really think that is what's going to eventually
demit like when when youtube gets to a point where it keeps enforcing these new rules and like
in some ways youtube's getting better they're trying to they're trying to make copyright
better for people but i think that if youtube ever fucks us over everyone's gonna just fucking leave
everyone with a big enough audience is just gonna take off and go be a patreon somewhere
yeah that actually that actually does sound like a genuine like a genuine like uh evolution
evolutionary step that the internet is gonna take well i feel like we're a bit far off from it at
this point like because right now i feel like we are in the golden age of youtube it just depends
on if things get really bad like if the censorship stuff gets like crushingly bad then people will
leave if they start telling us that we have to release videos on youtube red or like content
creators if they want to make money have to release on youtube red that would be nah that like
i would quit then i mean i would i would love to be off youtube not even for any like particularly
logical reasons other than just i want autonomy like i really value that personally like being
able to have control over all my that's why i've never joined like an mcn or anything like that you
know i mean yeah that's another that's another thing i'm trying i'm trying to get out of my mcn
trying to get out of my mcn right now i'm trying to like leave but apparently something that they
didn't put in the fine print because they said you can leave anytime you want but then what they
actually meant was that you can leave anytime you want when your contract when your contract
runs out and they never they never tell you when your contract fucking runs out so what i had to
learn i sent an email can i fucking leave now and then not obviously not in those words because
i'm actually trying to leave i don't want them to like eliminate my account but like they'll like
they'll like oh yeah you can leave on december 30th and i'm just like wow fuck you like seriously
lawyer up dog don't you doesn't your dad know some lawyers or something you could get on that
oh man i don't think it's like a big deal i feel like it's not it's not that big of a deal right
now like i'll wait i'll wait till december and just leave them yeah like trying to file suit against
them would probably take at least well i mean i think like threatening to file a suit against
probably get them to just be like all right that's that's fair yeah depending on what network it is
yeah and uh yeah i've already fucked youtube i've already i've already taken my huge following
and just and just fucked right off to the black boy that is saintcomics.com and youtube will never
be the same and like youtube will never stop feeling that loss there's something to me is very
precious about like like precious and like like a legit not precious like in a condescending way
but precious like legitimately not precious like the movie there's something very precious to me
about when i get to go to like saintcomics.com or uh tom what was your fucking site called again
sorcerousloss.com what else would it be called well you barely ever update the damn thing so i
haven't had a lot of cause to i have gone there like five times and read through those same six
pages again but um i mean i mean i mean i'm always going to mspainadventures.com yeah i used to go
there you know that's the home of homes like there's no there's nowhere else to go for that you know
if i type the letter t into my browser then it either auto completes twitter or the biggest
problem in the universe or now i'm trying to convince it to send me to the dick show instead
because the biggest problem isn't a fucking website anymore and uh or you know the maddox network i
really like that i like being able to go to a website and it has its own feel and look to it
sorcerousloss is a beautiful website um it's weird because it's weird because it's it's almost the
opposite for me because i've been seeing all these content creators that i used to follow on
multiple different sites for example i used to follow movie bob i used to follow extra credits i
used to follow yatsi and now they're all on youtube now they're all i've never i have never
watched yatsi on youtube i go to the escapist i have it on my yeah i've had the escapist is like
the third bookmark on my bar because i watch it every single week for like because i because i
always remember that like i always remember that the escapist always was a they always recently
they let their youtube videos be a week behind but i think they let their videos catch up recently
i i i don't care about that it's just like a thing for me that like i've been watching it on
the escapist all this time and that feels right and i also sometimes would go and read like critical
miss or something uh while i'm on there but also something like a quick thing like i used to go
to the escapist and the entire weekly content schedule would be full now you go to the escapist
and it's just they fired everybody they fired everybody i used to while i was on the site i'd
watch uh yatsi i'd watch movie bob's both of his shows sometimes i'd watch jimquisition and like
those guys are all gone now but anyway i guess uh and they haven't hired anyone new yeah we're
wrapping up i'd run a week i'd run a weekly animation if i yeah no i thought about that i
thought about pitching myself to the escapist before back when i was like not sure if i wanted to be
uh indy forever um yeah but yeah so that's our podcast that's how we became net savvy i guess uh
and you should too i i guess
i'm a little bit concerned that in this world of homogenized information and everyone going
to the same websites that it doesn't teach people as much about how to like navigate the internet
and i i do like even though i think fourchan or a bunch of douchebags about their no spoon feeding
policy because they take it too too much of an extreme i do think it's a great lesson that like
if you go on fourchan and someone posts a picture and you say source then they're going to fucking
look at you like an idiot because you can reverse image search you just right click on an image and
click search google for this image and it will find you what that image is and like if you go on fourchan
for five minutes you're gonna learn that because everyone holds to it so strongly but if you don't
then you might never know and there's so much more faggot like i can find anything on the internet
because i've been given the tools and when i have people like leave comments on my videos that are
like how do i find this anime and i'm like google is right there just type watch and the name of the
show and you're done and it's like i've known that forever but some people don't even realize that
that it's that easy you know and so i worry that as we move towards everyone being on youtube and
everyone being on twitter that people will will not pick up these skills on how to find
interesting stuff on the internet and uh i value those skills personally
sorry that's it for this podcast everybody say goodbye
bye i have been i have been nine oh mr black and platinum yeah master of the master black and
platinum master of the magic arts wipe the floor with all the elite for using the magic yeah we got
it sorry all right later later see you guys bye