All right, two partner, uh, who's on top, who's on bottom?
Lighters are getting the fattest from the bottom.
That's not tough, that's not tough.
All right, and if you had to make an episode about Applebloom going to hell, what would it be?
What would that absolute progression be like?
Would it be like that time Homer went to hell and had to eat all the doughnuts?
I saw our parents applejack!
All right, guys.
Looks like we're all done, guys. We're all done.
They turn off the mic.
Hey, hey, everypony. Welcome to a very special episode of My Little Pony, Thoroughly Analyzing.
I'm joined by all my best friends in the whole wide world.
We've got best guy ever, also known as kegstandard.
I don't know who the fuck that first guy is, I'm kegstandard.
And welcome to another episode of TBBBAP. Take it, Phantom!
That's two best brothers bitch about ponies. It's me, your blue bitch here, Phantom Horne.
The only pony with the courage to defy social norms, ever.
We've got that.
And that's all you gotta say.
Is that give and take over there?
Hey, guys, welcome to ArmourTreeVul Act 7.
We're gonna be talking about homestuck today.
That's a banned topic. You know that.
No.
Trigger word.
Oh my god! Brody Curious is here!
I even look back! I did it!
I'm alive!
Yay!
Hi.
No longer a zombie.
No, I've been revived.
I'm glad to see everyone survived the whole cutie mark revival.
Have you been max revived?
We've all been max revived.
Yeah, that's right.
We've got the mage pony.
Yeah, Aurora Ignite.
Oh, that's the full name.
I knew that.
I'm a failure.
We've got the munchie with the tiny hats.
I don't know who that guy is, cause let me tell you.
Hey, PCP fans, he's the most recently acquainted best friend, Strawberry Milk.
Yeah!
Woven expertly into the grand tapestry.
That is my little pony, Fringe of Magic Analysis Community.
If you know what I'm saying, real cliff notes on my lore.
I love sex. I'm not like munchie. I love sex. I like the ERP.
I do.
I'm a toon fetishist, and I hate shame, and I hate self-reflection.
I just love sex. That's my character.
Don't wear it out.
We're peas in a pod.
We've even got a brand new friend joining us for the first time.
Our new friend, Tape Stack.
Hey, everybody. I predicted that this would be great.
Do you have tape in your mouth?
I was going to say.
No, I just don't.
I'm racist at all.
Excellent.
You see, we're appealing to all fetishes here.
I'm really into that.
I'm getting ready. I'm getting lewd.
The gang is all here, buddy.
Now, unfortunately, our seafaring buddy, Starboard Bow,
was busy off pirating today, so he couldn't join us,
but we will pour one out in his name.
Gotta get the booty.
Exactly.
Guys, guys, have you seen it? Have you seen it?
Have you seen the long-awaited fucking pony movie?
The cinematic events of all time,
of all the equestrian history.
Guys, let me tell you.
I walked outside one graceful night,
and I looked up in the stars,
and there was the solar eclipse
beaming down directly into my eyes.
And from that day onward, all I could see,
just directly into my red nose,
was the My Little Pony movie on repeat,
as thin as them.
And that's exactly why you should stare at the eclipse.
You know?
Because you get quality semina right in your brain.
You know, I've never really had
a religious experience in a religious place,
but while sitting on my couch,
watching the My Little Pony movie,
I briefly saw God.
Did you, Brony?
It was just wonderful to hear you say that.
I briefly saw God, too. All three of them,
before they were turned to stone.
You mean all four?
I can see you're rusty out here, Brony Curious,
but let's try and get up to speed, all right?
We're not running a shit show here.
This isn't like some bum-fuck internet pocket.
It's like the PCP.
This is...
It's better.
Get over it, you anti-Hazbright.
This is the PPCP,
the Pony Procrastination Podcast.
It's an alternate reality.
It's the darkest timeline.
Oh, it's the brightest from where I'm standing.
So, okay.
So let's just immediately dive into all the earth-shattering ways
this movie ruined the continuity
of My Little Pony Friends was imagined.
Should we go through it in order to chronologically
like the best internet shows and nostalgia critic?
Okay, hold on.
Let's go to where...
I think it's important because this movie
is so fucking earth-shattering,
and it just plumped us up.
It just plumped us up real good.
It just saddled us up and plumped us down real good.
All right, everybody.
As the creator of the My Little Pony analysis community,
I feel like I could lead this discussion
of the My Little Pony.
Wait, should we talk about our history first,
or is that whatever?
I'm going to talk about our history
and the movie all at once here
because I want to know who else watching this movie.
First of all, actually, more so than our history,
I want to know when was the last time
each of you watched My Little Pony.
I know Hippo follows the show still.
I literally haven't watched a full episode
since I stopped analyzing the show in 2014.
I watched, like, one episode from season 5.
Wait, that's not true. I watched a bunch from season 5.
Wait, Ben, didn't you watch all of season 5
and T-Bap it?
Yeah, we podcasted it.
Wait, you did the whole season 5.
Okay, maybe I'm thinking of season 6 then.
Season 7 is out now, right?
Season 6 is the one that...
Okay, then I stopped watching after the podcast ended,
but I watched, like, one...
I think I watched the finale of the next season
just to see if I was interested.
I keep forgetting I did watch half of season 5
before we went to BronyCon in 2015
just because I wanted to know what the fuck was going on.
I watched a couple episodes, I think, from season 6
because I foolishly made a list
of, like, four episodes I had to review
if big things ever happened,
and then I did some of them because I kept happening.
I got pestered on it on Twitter.
I was like, well, I guess I'll have to talk about them,
so I did.
I stopped watching right around
the midway point of season 5 weekly.
However, me and Phantom here
actually watched a few episodes of season 6 together,
and we should have been basically.
Wait, we did?
Yeah, we did.
Remember when we were going to do a thing, but we never...
Remember when we were going to literally do T-Bap,
but it never happened?
Oh, God, that was, like, forever ago.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
That's when I watched season 6.
What the fuck? I don't remember any of it.
Um, if I recall correctly, you almost cried
in an episode?
What?
Hey, nothing wrong with that.
Which one? Which one?
What the fuck?
The second episode of season 6,
you were like, that's really deep moral,
and I almost cried.
Wait, wait, what happened? Tell me what happened,
because I'm starting to...
Nobody actually cares.
I'm starting to form into memory.
Damn it.
It's like, I should listen to my friends.
What the fuck? No.
That can't be right.
Okay, let's get back to this.
I haven't seen anything since season 5.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that was the one where the evil,
where the evil got in her and made her be bad,
and I related to it.
Oh, shit.
God, I forgot.
I forgot this was the best show on the internet.
Mange.
Mange, what was the last time you watched
a new episode of My Little Pony?
Um, I'm actually up to date.
Who?
Oh, shit.
You're up there with hippo.
Number one.
She's a realer pony than any of us.
I'm not actually up to date,
because, um, the pony cast,
we've been having a bit of, like, seasick,
like, cancer, like, what do you call it,
scurvy, I see that.
Sea-sick cancer.
We have some sort of scurvy problem,
so we haven't been able to do any of those episodes
for a while.
So I'm behind on that.
But I, yeah, season 7 is good.
I like season 7.
No, here's the thing with season 7.
If you haven't watched the pony cast,
we discover that season 6 and season 5,
they're like, oh, whatever.
And then season 7,
they start introducing a new main cast,
sort of.
Yeah.
Like, that's, like, that good,
that good-
I have been,
I will say that I have been watching the pony cast,
and that's the only way,
it's been really surreal listening to that podcast,
because I can envision the episodes in my head.
Like, even though it's been so long
since I watched the show,
I spent so much time with it
that I know exactly what it's like.
And so, like, listening to you guys
discuss an episode,
it just brings me right back.
It's like, oh, yeah, this is exactly
what that would have looked like.
And here's what they're talking about.
And I can perfectly envision it.
And that was also what was trippy about this movie,
was that for the first, like, 20 minutes,
it's just an episode of My Little Pony.
Like, if you close your eyes,
because the visuals, you can't.
Like, if you just listen to the way the characters
are talking,
the things they're saying,
the sound effects, the music,
it's just the show.
And then it develops a plot,
and becomes really boring.
What would have been way better
if it looked like an episode of My Little Pony,
because this shit sucks.
God dammit.
Did anyone like the visual aesthetic?
No.
Yeah, man.
I thought it was good.
Oh, really?
It's like, you stood, I quite enjoyed it.
I never stopped.
I mean, it wasn't always terrible,
but there were plenty of moments
that were ruined by the way it was.
Oh, look at their weird big heads
and creepy eyes, though.
Yeah.
That is hard.
My Little Pony's never had big heads
and creepy eyes ever.
It's to the extreme, though.
It's definitely weird.
You'll let that turn up your game
if you want to cut it.
There's too much detail.
My ass.
I totally disagree.
I think the extra frames of animation
are great.
I thought the way that there was
more rendering detail and everything
was great.
My Little Pony's animation was never good.
They all looked like fucking flash puppets
and moved like them the entire show.
They were stilted and awkward.
Right.
And they were never good.
And it was great.
I loved it.
Yeah.
And everyone was saying they looked good
and were wrong.
But this was even worse.
No.
I thought the environments were
particularly really well done.
Here's the background.
The background was fucking good.
Dude, God, I have the perfect analogy.
It's about macaroni and cheese.
You might have macaroni and cheese.
It's made for kids, right?
Oh, God.
Made for fucking kids, right?
But then when you're like a late teen,
you're like, man, I still love
the fucking taste of this.
I could appreciate this fully.
But then once you get into your 20s,
it's getting more like, well,
I still like the taste of it,
but I do like other tastes more.
And also, I feel like cancer after eating it,
like 20 minutes later, I don't know why.
I can't relate to this analogy
because I still eat macaroni nearly every day.
Well, I'm talking specifically about
Kraft, specifically that box, right?
For all of us who aren't actively killing
our bodies and everything.
Right.
Yeah.
So fucking, yeah.
So that's the thing with macaroni and cheese, right?
So the same thing as the MLP aesthetic.
When I was, you know, when it first came out,
I was like, oh my gosh,
it's just so much good animation.
It's like hot colors and fluidity and timing.
But then when I look at it now,
I'm like, okay, I can see all the ones
and zeros in these fucking vectors, you know?
So basically this movie is like someone
handing me a bowl of Kraft macaroni and cheese
with bacon inside.
It's like, well, that's going to be tangy AF.
It's going to make me feel really gross after eating it.
You know?
It's going to be fucking, it's going to be weird.
But it's going to taste like really intense
and just very childish in that way.
So yeah, it's like people always think,
people always think that good animation
is always going to be better no matter what.
I actually fundamentally disagree with that
because you can't just ramp up the quality of something.
Like the fight scenes in this, particularly the one
where Tempest beats the shit out of like a random mook
in like that city.
I thought that looked absolutely beautiful
and I was like, now that's something that like
just enhances the quality of this thing in general.
Perfectly balanced.
That specifically sucked.
No, that specifically was good.
It was like the best part.
But you can't over-animate
just the scenes of people talking
and like looking at each other dramatically
actually makes it more boring and worse
because things take longer to do
and it drives things out.
Yeah, I completely disagree.
I think you guys...
Kill and kill is an inventive animation.
No, no, no.
You guys are two, you're two attached
to the style you've known forever.
No, I hate the style I've known forever.
I gotta say, yeah, one of the hardest things
about trying to go back and watch my little pony for me
is that the animation is dog shit in the show
and like every, I don't know how we...
This is the guy who watches anime.
I think we all somehow...
Like when you get into MLP
then it's like in the fan community
every unique facial expression
that gets introduced is a big deal
because the show by and large is just the same
stock shit over and over again.
As soon as you see like one face of new
everyone freaks out.
But when you go back and watch the show
like when you're not in the hype cycle
and you just look at it, you're like,
oh yeah, it looks like shit.
This movie to me felt like
lipstick on a pig.
I enjoyed the aesthetic
because I went into it with the right mindset.
Now you see the reason why I stopped watching MLP
right around season five
since I never got to answer that question
since everyone seems to always
fucking ignore me when we go round about.
I'll get over it later.
Anyway, I have a fucking pillow to yell at
so I'm fine anyway.
So after getting out of MLP
I discovered this thing called,
I don't know if you've heard of it, anime, right?
Now that's where like you have stuff that like
there's this one show called
Kill Law Kills Inventive Animation
and that's a really good aesthetic.
And then there's like this other show
called like the incredible pacing
and visual imagery of Sound God's To No Lion
by Super Eye Patch Wolf, the son.
That's a good anime I like as well.
With incredibly well timed imagery
I've had so much incredible aesthetic.
It's like how much more exciting
can a show be than Kill Law Kills Inventive Animation?
How much more fucking well
directed can a show be other than
Sound God's To No Lion by Super Eye Patch Wolf?
Like you can't have anything better than that.
So it really is like someone saying
hey man you want to eat some macaroni and cheese
with fucking bacon bits and maybe someone
will put some soy sauce on it.
You really, really milk in this analogy.
Yeah, well I love food analogies.
I'm not sure if I buy into it completely.
Who does love milk?
What the fuck is the boo?
The name is Tape Stack.
It's a set deck because that was somebody else's
Pony Osea and it's similar enough that it's
fucking out of my head.
I hope you guys understand what this podcast is going to be.
It's just going to be like eight people talking
all over each other all at once and then
long stretches of just DeVoo talking only.
So just another episode of the PCP.
I want to speak about
the artwork.
The animation.
Do it. You're the one with the most animation
knowledge.
You're a regular Bugs Bunny ancient.
Cowboy.
I'm going to plump you up real hard
and spread my necklace across your lip
in the second you're spread.
Oh my god.
Go on.
What the fuck, Strawberry?
Simmer down.
It's okay. He loves sex. I understand.
I came into this
seeing because I saw the trailer and it looked weird.
The pinkie was like
she's falling and her nose looked like
a weird pig nose and didn't look right.
Weren't caught in the movie.
The thing is
the trailer shows all the worst bits
because it just
Anyway
I thought
I would hate it because it was kind of weird
but I also noticed
it's like they're doing a Disney thing
with the pony thing
and I just sort of got used to it
and then I started to like it.
I started to like the extra frames.
I really liked all the moments where Tempest
was looking down at the camera
and she was the best animated
character in the whole movie.
She was good.
In the new art style, yeah.
Tempest was the best.
She was designed for it.
It's like Joachim's adventure.
What made?
Everyone shut the fuck up.
And everything on the water was great.
Yeah.
The new animation
really suited Tempest the most, I think.
All the rest
were kind of like
like I said, I got used to it eventually
but they all were very sort of like
still squishy and sort of
soft looking.
It's always been that way but yeah, definitely to a larger degree.
And you know how much I love soft looking things.
I think the problem is that
the MLP animation has always
had a really difficult time
dealing with extreme foreshortens
poses, like even in the regular show.
It's always like the thing, one of my
little pet peeves of the animation style
which persists in this animation swap
is that whenever you look at a regular
design pony from straight on, the muzzle
is never done correctly in perspective.
It just looks like someone slapped a shape on top
of a flat face and that's why when you get
that perspective shot with Pinky, it looks all fucked up
because I don't know how to draw that
from not a three fourths or profile view
it works even less well
in this more detailed style.
The point of the aesthetic is to add cinematic
to the MLP viewer.
That's exactly right.
It's often derided by being overused
but in this context it's, hey
TV show that looks really good
by its own standards, that's been going on for seven seasons.
Here, here's a cinematic version
because it's an exciting way to deliver
a little tight.
It's definitely hype to see it
that way. The problem is that I don't think
the character designs translate well to it.
When you see the characters
in three fourths faces
when you see that other eye
on the other side of their face
that just looks fucked up to me.
Some of the characters work better than others.
Twilight talking
to the princesses in the beginning
and I was just looking at her eyes
like why are they wrong?
And they also added detail to the eyes
like anime style.
The way that they made the shines
translucent.
That was the biggest problem for me.
Although I didn't like the detail in the irises
like how the irises are all speckled and stuff.
Yeah, I was cool.
I was never part of this whole analysis community.
Was this what it was like?
It's weird that none of the other characters have it.
How did you last it?
Just the main ponies have that.
I think
my impression of the animation
and of everything in the movie
was a constant series of
slugged.
You'd see sometimes
there would be a piece of animation
that's like, yeah, okay, that worked.
Or a joke.
I think Twilight showing
Celestia and Luna like the angles
she wants them to put the sun and the moon at the beginning.
I was like, yeah, okay, that's a good Twilight joke.
That's something she do and say.
The ghost in this movie
felt so fucking flat.
I can't even believe that.
Mage, mage, mage, mage, mage, mage.
Everyone shut up.
I don't understand why the princesses
didn't want to go with that plan because
why?
It's not much effort to do that
because when later the guy gets the staff
he just plays around with the sun and the moon
like it's nuts.
He's like, I have a great idea
for something you can do
and they're like, that is a great idea
and we totally could do it, but we won't.
Good luck.
The princesses have to stay in character
useless.
If they actually did something productive
I would have been totally unsold.
I am mighty and better than you.
I have something to say
when
Twilight's like, hey, I need this utility
so the concert will be cool.
They're like, we believe in you.
Don't worry, you're a princess too.
I'm sure you can do it.
I'm sure you can do it and she's like,
no, this is what I want to do.
You put me in charge and this is what I fucking want.
You're supposed to be able to do that.
I think the idea is that they're saying
we can't just fuck up the day-night cycle
of the world for one party.
There's other consequences of doing that.
I think they just don't understand math
and they were saving face.
But the Storm King does that later.
The Storm King fucks it up later and no, it's fine.
Everyone's fine.
Guys.
Guys though,
Twilight said that it was about the time
when the sun is supposed to be setting
and the moon was probably going to be rising
at around the same time, so all they had to do
was just hold it for a little bit
in the same place. Nothing was going to get fucked up.
That will fuck up people
who are looking at the sun and they're like,
why is the sun no here?
Some port sailor on the sea
is going to lose his way
because they're like a minute.
They know that the sun and moon are reliable.
You stop and ballot out there
right now.
We have to think of him.
That's how it is.
Phantom Horde.
The sun and moon
they're not just
over Equestria.
It's like the whole world's sun and moon.
I was thinking about this
the very day, when Celestia and Luna
fuck with the sun and the moon, is that just an Equestria thing?
Because only the ponies do that
It's like how America
is the world police.
These guys are the world sun
Like when the Sun and the Moon get fucked up are like the fucking cat people and like parrot people and like the hydro ponies and whatever
Are they all like, oh, I guess I guess the ponies are having a fucking war again
Equestria is like the America to that world where like all the third world countries get fucked every time we do something
The point I was trying to make simply is that if they hold the Sun and Moon in place it will fuck up for everybody in the world
And this is just for a party that's just
The Sun and Moon could be contextual, you know, it's like in Dark Souls now, since it's 2013 again
You might not know about the game called Dark Souls where the Sun is different in certain places
So just saying, it's an establishable concept
No, if it's 2013, then Dark Souls is exactly what we're talking about
I know what the Sun and Moon theory, the Flat Earth theory, this totally makes sense
Because they just go in circles, they move in circles around this, yeah, that totally works
Fucking crazy, get off the dark part of YouTube
All the new Pokemon they added were hard to get and I couldn't find them anywhere, they just had such a low percent rate
I just couldn't find any of them
You're missing the force through the trees, the point is that the animation, they all look chubby and scary, like vaguely like meaty
Like they have flesh, they eat their dumb, plump up cheeks, I just want to plump them up real high
I just want to lift up their stomachs real quick, real fast, real good, and just feel those shells
You're entirely correct, and that stems from a larger, I would call it a problem
And it's exactly what Davoo is saying
Who the fuck is this person you keep comparing to?
I'm sorry, a tape stack, my old companion in his beloved braces
He's a new companion, you fucking retard
Son
Yeah, exactly
So I'm looking right now at a screenshot of the princesses at the beginning
And they look normal and good
And then I go like one frame over to Twilight and then she looks all fucked up and weird
And that's the problem with this movie
It's everything that is involved with turning a cartoon into a movie I always hate and it's never been done right
It's like I said, the style sort of fits Tempest and she has sort of the same facial features as the princesses
It's that nose shape, you can't have the little bubbly nose because it doesn't work
It's not just the character designs either, this spills over into the narrative
Where A, they have to baby us by teaching us what all the characters do every time
Do
The beginning of the movie was just like, hey Rarity, you like fashion, right?
Sure do, bud, sure do
I knew who was going to do that shit
That seemed acceptable
I like how they established it's like X-Rarity even though that's completely irrelevant to them
I got it so irrelevant to the movie
The thing is, I don't think it was about babying us
This movie just contains every piece of information about my little pony in it
It's the people who haven't seen it before can just watch the movie, of course
Not even that, not even that, I don't think that's what they were going for
I think it's for fan service, I think it's so that everything they could possibly make
Every background pony is in just the opening scene
Every single named one, everybody makes an appearance
Every callback imaginable is made
I was actually distracted by that
To people who don't know
There's the end of the movie, everyone's having a good time
And then both biceps just shows up and no one who watches the show goes like, what the fuck is that?
No play
Why is that?
He was in the movie though, he was in the movie a number of times
Yeah, but that's my only point, it doesn't make sense that he was just a joke
I mean, no play didn't make sense to begin with
He was just a random sight gang
I was really distracted by Rainbow Dash saying three seconds flat, Fluttershy saying
Oh my god, when Fluttershy said two times
Yeah, when he said it's the first time I rolled my eyes
When he said it's the second time I literally hung myself
Alright, the worst thing about this movie, I don't know the worst thing
But one of the things I didn't like was the fact that most of the main six they got something to do
They either had a song or they were somehow helpful
Fluttershy said yay twice and did absolutely nothing
Just like the regular show, she was in character
I made an itemized list, I analyzed
We're going right back
What's up with this fucking cheesy Gornita Crunch is doing her shit
Well, there it is
Listen, I analyzed this film with a fine tooth microscope
And I determined scientifically that there were, of the main crew
There were a full three characters who did literally nothing in the entire movie
And it was Fluttershy, Rarity and Applejack
What about Rainbow Dash, what did she do?
I want to talk about Rainbow Dash
I want to talk about everything, that's what Rainbow Dash did
She is in fact a regular show
Okay, guys, okay, okay
This falls into the mean category
What I want to know, I called the police, called the mayor, called the president
What was with the weird insertion of the Sonic Rain Boom
The Sonic Rain Boom was never like a means
It was a band service, it was totally a band service
It was totally a band service
She just wanted to do it
It was really weird that she was so adamant about it throughout the movie
She keeps bringing it up, and I was like, why, she's not like that
Okay, wait, I've got it
In canon explanation, Rainbow is meeting a bunch of new friends
She's in a new place, she wants them to see
She wants them to see her cool things she can do with the rainbow
That's why she wanted to
That was in season one, it was so long ago
And you're like, gay was in season one too
Speaking of Rainbow
It was like beginning of the show memes
What's the deal, bro, what's up?
Entry level, basic bitch shit
Speaking of basic bitch shit
Did Rainbow really need another song about awesome?
I'm getting second verse
That song is literally, that song is my least favorite part
And I'll tell you why
Because when the pirates were being like, wait a minute
Let's cast off the yoke of the man and rediscover our true selves
I like the design of the pirates
And I really wanted to get excited for that part
Like I could feel myself almost enjoying myself
But then the song came on
And the song, it's time to be awesome
And I hated it
I hated the song so much that it ruined the moment
I was really hoping that they'd have this big song
No, because the whole reason they said
She's trying to get them to sing the songs
I don't want to get kicked off the ship
And I was really hoping they'd have this big moment of them being
Yeah, we're pirates
And then they fucking made them walk the plank anyway
Because they're pirates
Yeah, that's what I was thinking too
We've all been doing the opinions of this movie
It's just backwards
Here's what you do with a movie like this
You cooperate with it and reduce a point
In exchange for your cooperation
So as soon as the movie begins
I promise I won't have any food analogies
The movie begins to a parody of an 80's song
With a pony's lyrics inside
Wait, are you doing a mysterious Mr. Enter right here?
Is that what's going on?
Or are you being legitimate?
I thought you were memeing for a second
Well, I don't know, you tell me
Because mysterious Mr. Enter's thing
Is that he would start each episode with five points
And he would reduce or add them based on
Whether or not something good or bad
See, I never watched stupid videos
That is how I start my videos, they're great
I went into it assuming it was going to be bad
And then pretty early on I'm like
Wait, I wanted to talk more about the pirate
I want to say two things too
We have to get organized here
We've got to get organized here
Everyone was like
Everyone has to be in this episode
It's got to be the whole crew
This is good, this is what the people want
If we just analyze the fact for a second
That this podcast will mean
Literally nothing to like
80% of our audience
I don't give a shit, I want that
I want them to f-
If they don't know Peg, if they don't know Digi
If they don't know Phantom, if they don't know
Give them they don't know anything
The real point, the entire conceit of the PCP
I never told any of this
The whole point of it was to get people into
My little pony, 80 episodes of this shit
This is what it's all been for
I'm talking about of the PCP
This is like 80 episodes now or something
You fucking idiot
I tricked you
You're a brony now
Look down at yourself, that's the body of a brony
You fool
And what a body it is
While we're off topic, I want to
Pause it a backstory for
TapeStack, if that's okay
Here's a suggestion to be
The backstory of TapeStack
TapeStack is a huge
MLP analysis fan
Who has all of our stuff on Tape
He had everybody's analysis
On video
And he had like this huge collection
He put his VHS tape into YouTube
And recorded it
And then there was like a brony con going on
And he met all of us and was hanging out with the
With the group and he showed us his tape collection
We were really impressed and we wanted to be friends
And that's how we met TapeStack
So brony con is now canon to the
My little pony universe
I think though
Wasn't there actually a brony convention
In the show
In the show where Patton Oswald was there
Or something
That did happen
And they just made fun of the entire fandom
That is a real thing
I want to complain about the pirates some more
Because they made me really mad
I do want to make two points as well
You can go first and then I'll go
Okay first point
Alright everyone knows what a pirate is
And what a pirate does
Why would they think it's awesome and want them to continue to be pirates
That's stupid
Well I have an answer to that
It's because they're not actually pirates
When they describe their job as pirates
They say they're treasure hunters
They do not actually engage in piracy
The entire pirate conceit is fucking retarded
Because we get to the scene
And it's like oh we're being
Impressed by the Storm King
And she's like oh be pirates again
Does Storm King just do to them again
Whatever he did to subjugate them
Oh my fucking god
My first problem
How is that not immediately what you thought
When this scene came
Because that was all I thought
This makes no fucking sense
This is the least sense making thing I've ever seen
I was fine with Rainbow Dash
That was the moment the movie was dead for me
I was fine with Rainbow Dash convincing them to be pirates again
But then when Tempest showed up I was like
Oh okay she's gonna see that they've gone back to the pirate
And they're gonna get in trouble with the Storm King
No Tempest sees
That they've fucking thrown off their duties
And they've gone back to them and she doesn't even care
She doesn't do anything
The most cleverly written scene in the movie
Where it's like suddenly lunch
It's a funny subversion
It's a funny subversion of your expectations
It's a cruel way of establishing some world building
About how the fucking guy
Has been taking over the whole universe
Basic shit
You just get to know about their characters
And you empathize with them
And then someone goes
Hey, stand up for yourself
Stop being afraid
But apparently that makes no sense
People never have a point where they turn around
To realize they stand up for themselves
They never found that
So that's fine as they did
But there should have been consequences
If there were no consequences for them
Going back to being pirates
Then why did they start being different
They literally were just scared
They were totally consequential
No, they didn't
That's not because they went back to being pirates
It's because they were harboring prisoners
They didn't realize they didn't swap their costumes
They were standing right fucking there
What the fuck
That was a stupid thing
They should have immediately put their costumes back on
I would agree with that
I have to say something
I have to
Please give him please
Rainbow Dash was like
Hey, you guys should be pirates
But not because she's a good friend
Here's the headcan reason why
It's because she knows that she just wants to trick them
So she doesn't die
And then it's like
You guys should be pirates and they're like
There's no apprehension or anything
It's just like please be pirates again
Please
As Ben touched on
I thought that the point of the scene
Was going to be that the pirates were stupid
That like they were going to have this whole
Up like they're going to reform everything
And then the ponies after having
Like reformed the pirates were just going to
Skate or get like brought to somewhere else
And then the bad guys were going to show up and immediately
Subjugate the pirates again they're going to be like
Oh right of course how could we forget
That we are under the rule of the storm king
And we can't actually just rise up out of nowhere
Because he's more powerful than us
But like no
They just are characters now
And more than that like pirates
Are not necessarily good people
They really should
The whole thing of them doing the awesome song
Was completely out of self interest
That's why I say this script
That's why I say this goddamn script was
Babyfied there's this idea that like
Pirates are just like cool guys
The show is for babies
Dude you spent years talking about the show
It is not
You need to say something
Alright
You guys are all wrong in every aspect
You're not thinking
Let me explain to you what my little pony is
It is
A show
That's alright
But it has occasional flashes of
Oh that's nice
It's a show that's
Whatever and it's got a few little nuggets of
Cool shit
People noticed that there was cool shit
In a show about ponies and they thought
Wow that's really unexpected
And they formed a community around it
Everybody started analyzing it
And everyone's a stupid idiot
Pirates are cool
Airships are cool
I liked it
The whole movie was great and I can't believe
The continuity errors god damn
The continuity errors
I want to explain how I watched this movie
Because I did not go into this
Like
I think some mothers did
I went into this movie
I heard it was bad from Ben and Jackie
Or Phantom and
What was her equity
That's a genius name by the way
Let me quickly
Touch on the fact that walking into the theater
She was talking about her theater
At which theater soon
It's important to me
She got accosted by some guy in a pony shirt
Who was like
And right then the tone
Was bad for the theater
So a man asked her a question
And she was deeply offended
He was waiting around in the lobby
And I got the feeling
That he was waiting around to meet
His fellow bronies
And then he spotted too right before
But he knew it was time
His dar was on
Gibbon you liking something big
Big mistake
You're gonna get knocked into some pins
Come up your location about 5-10 minutes
Gonna knock you right down
Really soon
What we were talking about
Did you want to share your experience
Okay, okay, okay
Quiet the rails into like
Random nothing
Okay, okay, I have a story
I showed up to the theater with my posse
Of insane clowns
I just want to flip, I just want to flip so hard
Employees get sweaty, I just want to get plumped up
I'm gonna rough these guys around a bit
I'm gonna slap their lip a few times
And so
I order some pretzel bites
And I assume they're pre-cooked
Like anus wasters
But like I order them
What the fuck
And so
So I order them and the cashiers
Like alright you're just gonna come out real soon
And I'm like at the naive fool I am
I say like okay, I go wait by that side of the corner
With my friend Kyle, I talk about this couple for
Fuck you Kyle, he immediately starts
Jeering me most rudely
With his gnarled fangs and his angular
Visage and he's just eating
So we're gonna be late, I tell him please don't be mean
I'm just gonna be slapping around here
Real soon, right quick right now
The demon persists the clocks
To get down the minutes right before the movie
Get shorter and shorter, his flamboyantly hostile
Demeter rocks the very coal in my spine
He's like a furry freaky friend
But only worse and gay
Anyway I get the pretzels and
We weren't late for the movie but we were really close
Fuck you Kyle, stop being mean to me
And they were like
Yeah, there's a lot of bronies and stuff
I also got
My first movie
My little pony certificate, they had like these like
Certificates you could get out
What the fuck
Like all the five year olds who come to the movie
Like ready to get their cinema cherry popped
And I got the certificate
Is that like a Mew?
Write down your pony name, write down your pony name
Write down your date of birth and like day to day
And your movie theater like place
Is that like the promotional Mew cards
That you got at Pokemon?
It all ties together
The history repeats itself
The purpose was to like
Write down their first movie experience
But like everyone took them or just like 19 to 26 year old guys
And they just always wrote down
That this was their first movie they've ever seen
Wow
Awesome
So the reason I wanted to bring up my viewing experience
I had already heard from Phantom Inequity
That the movie was supposed to be really bad
I thought it looked really bad
So I was like I'm going to get drunk and watch this movie
And I didn't want to go out and pay for it
I was really resistant to being on this podcast
Because I didn't want to have to pay for the movie
We left you no alternative
But then the greatest bro in the world
Keg Standard
As he would typically do
Found an illegal download of the movie for me
That's right
So here's the thing
I watched this with my girlfriend
Who has never watched my little pony
She seemed like maybe two episodes of the original show
And completely avoided it
I thought it was like I don't want to be a part of this thing
This song
She recognized
All the autistic people she knew were into this show
So she paid a little bit
Such a significant other
Did you bro?
So
I went into this movie
With a weird mixed feeling
Because on the one hand I was expecting it to be bad
And I was drinking
We were both drunk when we watched it
But I also really
Wanted it to be good
Because I want to convince her
That I'm not a fucking
You're reminding me of my little pony
So
This is the wrong vehicle for that
In many ways
The early part of the movie
Was actually good
I liked the first 20 minutes
Because I thought it represented
What is good about the character interactions
In the show pretty well
Oh you're a fucking
I'm gonna knock you down
Lots of lines that immediately
Get to the heart of what's good
You get that Twilight's over
She's overbearing
She tries to prepare way too hard
You see the endearing qualities
Of Twilight in that early part of the movie
That was just to check off her character
Like oh she likes that
I agree
It was just checking off a list
You're watching if someone who's never seen
My little pony before is watching this movie
And you're checking off a list of all the
Best character traits of the characters
It's a good place to be
She was laughing at the jokes
And thinking
Things that are good about this
Yes see
Every time something would happen
That was indicative of something
I would explain it
Oh yeah Fluttershy is like this
Oh god you mansplained the entire movie
That's disgusting
Well the entire movie
Because then we got to the point where
They start introducing the plot
And it immediately starts going downhill
And I start explaining
Oh yeah well you know
Every time they would do a two-parter episode
And they'd introduce a villain
Those are always shitty episodes
Because it's not really like the shows about
And it's like
The movie was just like an adventure season finale
With all the problems
Exactly
How many times have we all railed against
Those specific episodes
Oh look at all these backgrounds
Look at all these side characters that have nothing to do
Here we go again
Not just MLP, any show in the universe right
What is the worst episode of any show
The episode that you try to show
To a new person that's a friend of yours
Who's not seen it before
Always going to be a fucking dumpster fire
Unless you calculate which episode
If it's a random episode
It's the worst episode
Right but it's just like episode one
To show it to a friend
The problem with the Nightmare Mooner
I smile for you because
My girlfriend has the exact same taste as me
My girlfriend has the same taste as me
And I show her everything
That I like
And she always feels exactly like I do
And I hated this movie
And she hated the movie
And it was
I felt like the first 20 minutes
Was a lot of me going
Ah yes, thank you movie
His name is strawberry milk, you son of a bitch
Thank you
My little pony movie
For proving that there are things about the show
That are obviously like interesting or good
So that it doesn't look like I'm insane for liking this
But then as it goes on
And there's so many songs
So many fucking piss breaks in this movie
The songs, the songs
The range from mediocre to bad
I've always liked all the songs
Hold on, hold on
You said that, hold on
Jackie was saying that too
I completely disagree
There were a lot of great songs in the show
We all knew the words of them
I know the words
I haven't watched MLP in fucking years
And I still remember all the songs
That were good, 20 minutes after
All the songs that were good
You cannot tell me that you don't like
Giggle at the ghosties
I can't tell me
You can't tell me you don't like the cupcake song
It's a good song
You can't tell me you don't like
The songs fucking
But here's the thing
Even if you don't like those songs
You remember them
They got good hooks and shit
I don't remember shit from this movie
None of them are memorable
I remember the second song
It was literally friend like me from Aladdin
There were no differences
That was the only song in the movie
I didn't hate so I guess that's why
Can we acknowledge the fact
That the songs were absolutely pointless
Because they established something
And then they take a few minutes
To sing about the already established thing
Oh hey Twilight
We're here, we're gonna help you
Now let's sing about how we're gonna help you
Oh hey, I'm the Swab and Colton guy
But no sings
Let's sing about it
Tempest or whatever her name was
With her song is that she's standing
In a room singing
As soon as that happened
I was like this is gonna be boring
But the flashback was good
That was the worst part of the movie
Every part of the movie
Every part is the worst part of the movie
I wanna address
Probably my biggest complaint
About this movie
Is how badly
It copies Disney movies
Every song
Is a ripoff version of a Disney song
Every new character
Okay, the main villain
He's literally Hades from
Our greed completely
I had that in my blue flame
He's all like I'm a
I'm this guy, I'm a funny guy
I love merchandise, I'm his yo
I love his rebranding
Is it that different from like discord though
I got the feeling they were trying to do like a discord
You're an unrelated problem
That I had with the Storm King
He's so much like Tyric
Yeah, that's amazing
Then you've got the girl
Tempest
All of her facial expressions
Are literally copy pastes
Of Isma from the Emperor's New Groove
And the placement of the
Bunga character is Cron
Isma was way more expressive
But all of Tempest's expressions
That she does have are copied from Isma
The fifth doll Tony was so upset
She should have personality wise
No, but the animation
A Tempest issue
Due to my past
Racial dysphoria
Which I have fully overcome
That's all in the past that's over
Due to those past unpleasantnesses
I was heavily triggered
I was heavily triggered by Tempest
And I was very interested
I was very interested in hearing her backstory
And I was so let down when I finally heard it
Because you can infer everything
That there's nothing to her backstory
Other than what you can see at a fucking glance
You see that she's a unicorn
And her horn's broken
What's her backstory is that she broke her horn
That's the whole thing
It's like she was betrayed by her friends
She was wandering into a fucking bear cave
And they're like oh we shouldn't do this
And she was like nah I want my ball
And then they didn't want to play with her
Because their horn kept shooting out death explosions
By accident
And understandably she's a little upset about it
She's a little upset
Her friends don't like her because she's crippled
That's the reason you come out and say it
Movies come out and say it
By the way I did want to point out
That Tyric
And his white legion of faceless goons
Clearly represent the disgusting white race
And diversity champions over them in the end
So uh
They only have black people
Exactly the human white mumkeys
Weird cat man
Whose design I hate
Why was he so black
Yeah he was
Dude dude you want you want
That's the point
It doesn't matter it's fine
It's not how it was
It bothered me that he was the only cat
It bothered me that there were no other cats
It's kind of true
I think it's weird that like
Maybe if everyone in the town
Like was black
It would make sense
But the fact that this guy is super black
Would nobody else
Dude put that aside because the weird thing is
The sea pony queen like clearly has like
That accent and then her daughter
Not even close
She's pinkie pie too
Cat bro is
Cat bro's animation
Is clearly based on the black guy
From uh well the black
Bad guy from princess and the frog
Whereas the song he sings is
Friend like me by genie
The whole movie is just cobbled
And the fucking stupid rainbow dash song
Is just everything is awesome from the Lego movie
Like this is just cobbled together
Ideas of other movies
Other better movies for that matter
That happens when you try to like it dude
I want to harp on
I want to harp on the similarities between the cat guy
And Aladdin specifically
Because he has the same sort of like uh
Like MC Escher uh lower body
That Aladdin has when he moves
He's in this desert type rule of setting
Which I hate by the way I'm gonna give that one to get to the location
In this movie but also there is this
Specific shot in that scene
Where he is like
Like he's lowering down a plank
Across two buildings for the pony
Which is literally a like screen
Re-draw trace
Of a shot from Aladdin
That exact same shot is set up and composed
Like an exact shot from Aladdin
Where Aladdin puts down a plank between
Buildings for Jasmine
During the whole pirate scene
I gotta think of a pony name for my
I don't know
Whatever pony she is
Big slut
The pirate scene
Was um
Very reminiscent of uh
Atlantis the Disney movie Atlantis
The design of the uh
The function of this movie is
If you're into the pony brony
Mindset then it's a hey
Here's an episode that feels cinematic
And if you go into it thinking oh man
I hope it wows me
Every single time something kind of good happens
You will juice every single ounce of juice
That you can get out of it and try to suck it up as much as possible
To justify the fact that you're trying to like it
And then every single thing that's bad will fuck you up
You know there's always concede
You have to like accept if you want to have a tolerable experience
The problem with your premise for me
Is that I don't like the show anymore
So it's not like if I just view it as an episode
That's cinematic then it's like
Why am I watching my pony
That should be the review, the review should be
Hang on, yeah it would be cinematic
I don't know anymore, it says why wasn't it the masterpiece
I want to say something
Since we're on the subject
Give or take
It's just like the writing of the whole thing
Was absolutely abysmal
I'm so disappointed in the writers
Like they couldn't even do a proper like
Chekhov's gun
I wanted to say this point a lot earlier
When we were talking about the rainboom by the way
This was the second point I never got to
Like the whole rainboom thing
I think that was their attempt
At like a Chekhov's gun
Like oh she wanted to do this but she couldn't
Then they mentioned it a second time
But she didn't and then eventually she got to do it
And that's like the worst
Application
She ended up being useless
Yeah that too
They're so incompetent
Like the main five
They made absolutely useless
But they were so incompetent
They couldn't even like
Divide the uselessness equally between
The main five
It's just like because
They gave Pinkie Pie all the reactions
And because they gave Pinkie Pie
All the reactions
She just kind of like
She's the mean one
But like she completely killed the tone
Every time the tension was up
She killed it because they gave her the reaction
They gave her screen time
And she killed everything
Even more than just the jokes themselves
Being bad which they all were
There was like one or two jokes
There was exactly one joke that was fun
And it was when the pirates are like
Let's do bad things
And one of them says let's scar them
And Rarity's like
Emotionally
That was great
That was literally the only joke
There was a bunch of jokes I needed honestly
I laughed at some of the Bunga jokes
Oh no
What the hell dude
That was a nice joke
Dude I'm gonna saddle you up
I'm gonna knock you right off your horse
I'm gonna knock you down
I'm not very critical of comedy
I liked the whole
Bunga was like surprisingly not terrible
By the way
Not terrible but not good
What I didn't like about him
Is that as the movie went on
I felt like he got progressively more retarded
Early on he didn't seem like just
An idiot he seemed like more of a
Like weird
Like he thinks he's a badass
Kind of but like also
It's just like a stoner comedy kind of guy
Kind of lazy
But then as it goes on
He starts acting like more
There's a lot of characters that seem kind of like
They're like done with improv behind the microphone
And it's uh it's it's competent
But it doesn't really fit the whole format of
DMLP thing so
I will compliment this movie
The fact that um all the new characters
Have better voice actors
Than anyone in the actual show
That is indeed true
Like they definitely brought in like real actors
Or something I don't know who any of them are
I didn't look it up but like all the new characters
Were like oh they are like voiced
Competently and not like a you know
Like a children's show
I have no problem with that
I really liked him this voice
That's Emily Blunt by the way
The directing of the movie was ranging from
Okay to pretty good sometimes
Because I was having a relaxed viewing experience
I could just naturally notice things for example
By the way uh it was a real
Okay I'm sorry
When the uh the assistant guy who was like
Cronk shows up right you see him come out of a ship
And you see him holding a box you can't see him
All you can see are his feet and I particularly
Thought out of my head oh by pedal
So it's you know going into this movie
You're thinking ponies ponies ponies ponies
Four legs four legs two legs
Contrast right that's why I like the whole
On an adventure thing it's like what the fuck is this
Disney cat I sure as hell
Feel like I we're not in equestria anymore
Right that's the whole reason I like that whole scene
Right of the contrast and also a nice
Directing technique that was so well done
You probably never noticed it
I feel like weird characters like that show up in equestria
Well the level of contrast
Was what I wanted out of a cinematic experience
Right so then the whole adventure
Up to the point that they get to the sea pony realm
They're going from left to right
The whole time ah nice you know
You always feel like you're going further and further away
Then when they go back they're going to the left
Again I went into it with ok episode
But it's cinematic it did the fuck out of that
If it just had good songs
And didn't have a stupid twilight fucks up
And everyone hates it for five minutes thing
That was the worst thing
That was hilarious
You took this win for my sales
I can't believe
I want to
Twilight would resort to fucking theft
That was the stupidest fucking bullshit
Conflict and it happened
I checked out of the whole movie
Hold on hold on
I want to challenge Davoo's premise
Of the fact that we were like
That we're watching it wrong by nitpicking it to death
Because Davoo but as you said
If we watch this it's just an episode of the show
And the question is why are we watching my little pony
So the only justification for watching
This movie is that we're going to do a podcast
About it where we bitch about it incessantly
That's the joke
That is why we're here
In the MLP analysis community
Are we going to all watch the MLP movie
And get into a podcast
And go well you know it was fine for what it is
And then roll credits like
Where's the podcast if we do that
I just think I optimized my fucking viewing experience
Well
I'm going to say that I did not
I was not looking for nitpicking
Oh do I like this thing properly
Just like it or don't
I'm going to record that I have a drag kicking and screaming
And coming up with an OC
Like refers to me by it
After I was
I'm sorry
We have been around for years
You just came out with it
You can't expect us to be on board instantly
You can't be dragged into this episode
I was like why do I need to be on this episode
I never did pony analysis and Nate was like
No you have to do it
I'm sorry
We're so fucking sorry that you had to be here
Alright who cares
Gib was saying something go ahead
I was going to say in responding to
Like the thing Davoo said about the cinematic
Camera movement
Directing
I actually remember like multiple moments
Where I'm like oh that's neat
That's a cool camera move
That's a cool special like
They did that very well
The backgrounds and the camera and the directing
Was actually really good the whole way through
The scene where the pirate ship gets attacked
They did like shaky cam for a while
That was interesting
It did really like
It's in a terrible part of the movie
It's when Twilight is sad and she's sitting on the rock
In like a mist
That scene looked really cool and was framed really well
I want to point out
I've talked about this in one of my videos before
But when you do shaky cam in animation
That necessarily means that they have animated
Beyond the parameters of the frame
And are shaking a camera through it
Which I always think is interesting
Because you think of it
As just they're shaking a camera
Then when you think about the fact that it's all hand drawn
It's like wait what is the camera pointing at
Oh right
And as we kind of know earlier
The scene where a chip
A horn kicks the shit out of that
One guy random goon
In the fucking town
And it's this awesome like four part single shot
Take down
That was a cool moment
Yeah I love Simba
I love
Tom
You're saying something
I just wanted to point out something
I thought it was really funny how this whole movie
Can just boil down to Twilight forgets
So you can teleport the movie
Yeah I was going to bring that up
She's like trapped in this fucking cage
And I'm just like bitch
Oh my fucking god
To be fair
There was some weird stuff going on
Where it was shown that the shields
Those guys seemed to be using seemed pretty resistant to magic
But you wouldn't use the magic on that
You just pop away
Maybe there was a magical field
What would be the comment
On Tom's video
Fuck you
Okay watching this
I want to talk about the most interesting aspect of watching the movie to me
Like completely
Unrelated to the actual quality of the film
What was the most interesting to me
As I watched this was I could see
All the fan art
I could hear the fan songs
Like I could hear the remixes
I could hear the lines that would become memes
There's the scene
I could see the porn
The scene where like a cake falls on
Like a, was it Twilight or Pinky
And like on Twilight and like all of its
Dripping off of her and stuff
Like all this white liquid is
You're projectively dripping off of her
Dude
There would have been porn of that scene
There would have been
There's the energy
I mean actually there might be
I haven't checked but like
If they weren't all herded into a room at Dashcon
And assassinated
I don't know how
Active the community is right now
But like I could hear
There was like one song that
Because as
Equity pointed out in the
What was the name of the
T.V.S.S.B.P
Two very special sunpony
As the very special sunponies
Pointed out
While I unlike Equity
Do like a lot of the songs of the show
They are almost the exact same song
They all use the same chord progressions
And there was a song in this movie that did that
And because of that I could hear the remixes
Like I could hear where the beats would
Fall and everything and it was really trippy
For me as somebody who consumed
Probably more fan content of MLP
Than any other human on earth
I'm willing to be forgiving of the songs
For being all pretty similar in structure
Because like this is MLP we're talking about
This is a kids movie that we don't need
They just were also not good
Because the hooks were bad
That's a separate issue
The good songs from old MLP
Were still simple
The way I've always seen the music
I mean this is just sort of the way
I listen to music in general
Is that I like the instrumentality
More so than the chord progression
I don't pay attention to what chords are being played
I like
The instruments being used
And the melodies that are going along
With them and it's like oh that's really cool
A little Spanish guitar bit
I like that in a thing
I liked all the songs because
Regardless of how similar
They are to other songs in MLP
They got good instruments
And Daniel Ingram is good at that
I think
Gibbon I'm going to shave you
I'm going to groom you
Hey let me tell you
My favorite thing about this movie too
My favorite thing was
When Twilight reveals herself
To be literally friendship challenged
So her friends were all
You know, entertaining
The princess or whatever
And it is in fact revealed that Twilight is like
Having Twilight be the princess of friendship
Is like hiring someone with Down syndrome
To be the head of Homeland Security
They could be a fine person
But they're just not right for the job
No justification for that scene
It's unbelievable
What are you talking about when she steals the ore
I can't imagine
Just like in Dungeon Crawlstone's soup
I'm just pointing out another moment
Where she forgets she could teleport
I'm just saying, I'm just throwing that one out there
At the very beginning of the song
She's trying to get away from the guys
The princesses just did nothing
By the way, they did not move
They did not say go away
How fucking annoying was it
When Derpy was the one that jumped in front of the bullet
And took the bullet to her
I was so confused by that
Did the rainbow swoop in the saber
Did she replace Twilight?
I guess that's what happened
I was very confused by that
Because you see Rainbow fly in and grab her
No, you cut away too fast
You see Derpy for a few seconds
Just before when it's zooming in on Twilight
You can see Derpy at the bottom left corner
Is she just behind her or something?
No, I remember specifically
It was confusing
But I did piece together that it was Derpy
Just because it cut away too fast
I knew there was a joke there
But I just needed one quarter of a second longer
To process what happened
But I cut away, fuck you, I'm not reminding
Speaking of that
Things dragged too long
There was weird, awkward, long transitions
Between scenes that really bothered me
Maybe it's a cinematic thing
I guess we kind of talked about this a little bit
But the fact that once again
The three princesses are fucking useless
This is the setting
To really show them off
And do something cool with them finally
But to be instantly again
Relegated to nothing
In the first 20 minutes
It's so fucking stock
And it pisses me off
Why the fuck is the villain so intimidating?
What is the basis of his power?
Because all he seems to have was the staff
That is established that fucking Tempest
Gave to him
Right
I guess he just had a really good marketing campaign
But don't you think it's kind of retarded too
The fact that this character Tempest
Like why wasn't she the big bad
Because her whole point is that
I don't trust anybody anymore
But then trust this guy to do what he says
So it just makes her look retarded
And she was right, she was right now trusting one
Because he didn't do what he said he was going to do
So she was right
That's literally the fucking story with Tyric
She is Discord and he is Tyric
And also like she's like way too competent
To be his underling
She did every single thing for him
She did everything
It's so dumb
There was some promise here
That all hinges on that he had the unique ability
To heal her horn
But no, anyone who had the staff
Anyone who held the staff would have had the exact same power
I don't think that's true because even though
Twilight has the staff at the end
She still doesn't heal her
I'm thinking that maybe that the staff
Actually let her do that
Because it gave him power over the sky
But none of the princesses have healing powers
Except Caden's
But that's the thing
This is the issue I'm talking about
Why would she agree to be his servant
Before he gets the staff
And then bring him the staff
If like he
Why didn't she just do it herself
That's very true
And very stupid
What exactly did he bring to the table for
I mean that's like that's the pain
I guess the troops
I guess he gave her the troops
That's the general bad guy logic though
Did she need the troops though the whole time
She just fucking steamrolls everybody
When she got in with him
Maybe he picked her up as a little orphan
Nobody likes you but I'll train you to be a child soldier
You didn't see him as established
Yeah
That's some headcanon there
That's some incorice territory
That's fucking way
Then what does it matter
Since we're talking about this
I did want to say
My favorite part of the episode
There's a brief moment during the assault
When they're raiding the place
Fluttershy
They're all fighting one
Fluttershy calmly
Acts like a psychiatrist
Or a psychologist to one of the troops
That's how she takes it out
That was my favorite moment
By the way
Who else felt it was a huge relief
When they did the
Like the discord balloon at the beginning
And that to me was a signal
He would not be in the movie and I was like
Oh thank god
Speaking about the villains and shit
So okay
Wait a minute where was he
Why didn't they fucking get him
The magic in this whole show is kind of broken
Phantom hard
Discord
Discord isn't in the movie
Because this script must have been written forever ago
Because Starlight wasn't in the movie either
And she's one of the main characters now
So they just kind of crammed everybody into the movie
I'm assuming this script was written years ago
Right after season 4
That's where I would say it takes place
In the timeline
I didn't even think about it
But the conspicuous absence of discord
Is like a huge fucking deal breaker
So here's what's happening
Canterlot was sieged
And now that's under attack
But the rest of Equestria is still fine
Why did that go on?
It's not like the entire population was fucking obliterated
They could go back to Ponyville
They could go back to fucking
Wherever there is
Go get your friendship nuke
Use the friendship nuke
Why didn't they use the tree?
Remember when there were Native Americans in My Little Pony
I do
Don't reveal the trail of tears
Even leaving didn't even matter
They could have finished
Solved everything right in the beginning
Because they go on this huge big quest
To get this orb that does nothing
And all they do is get the princess to help them
And she does literally enough to
In the end they just beat up the bad guys
It's really smooth
How do you guys all feel about the fact that somebody
Fucking died
Dude
I almost forgot
That was fucking insane
Has this happened
And then they play with this fucking corpse
I do
Guys
Guys though
Did you watch the credits though
In the credits
His eyes move so it implies
He's still alive
Are you kidding me
That ruins the only good part of this movie
I know
That's even worse
That's even worse because he's eternally
Severed
He's like that guy in Jojo
He's like that guy in Jojo that Josuke
Put in the rocks
Yeah
The show
Was anybody else actually like a little
Shook by that
That like a straight up murder happened
It was an accident
I was just thinking about
But the fact that an onscreen death
Occurred
I believe Sombra was killed
I think Sombra did die
It wasn't very graphic though
This was like
They show a shard
A shard of Storm King's head
Slide across the ground
I hate to bring this up again
But don't you think that's another
Disney trope that they ate
The villain dies
The villain dies by falling and it's not exactly anyone's fault
That's the funny thing about it
I kind of thought it was
inappropriate for the villain to
Die horribly in a My Little Pony movie
It was a little weird
A movie that has no mistakes
And where most of it
The villain's like a goofy dude
He doesn't come across as like
A violently evil
He didn't kill anybody
Friendship is magic but you
Cross your fucking dead
I just played
Cuphead
Which has me thinking about all the horrible
Fucked up things that used to happen in cartoons
And I want more of that
I want so much death in my cartoons
It's not that it was weird in this movie
Where like nothing that bad
Like in the case of
Sombra
I'm pretty sure he does die
Phantom
It's like obliterated
And he's like evaporated
But Sombra was a much
Bigger threat though than this dude
Sombra was just an angry
Evil guy who like
Turned everybody to crystal and was like
Another problem with the movie is that the
Stakes are already too fucking hot
The only way to have a movie that would actually be
Significantly more epic is if it was like
End of Iqwan Gelyon and where like everything's all abstract
I love that
I love that movie
What I was thinking about when I saw that
Was I really started running for my money
That's a great line
It all returns to Muffins
Coming down
That's perfect
Because it's a really inappropriate word
And that's exactly what a pony remix
Of that song would be
When that guy died though
My mind started racing about the board meeting
That must have happened where they were discussing like
What context is it acceptable to have a character
Actually die in
First of all he's frozen into stone
So that he can shatter and no one actually does
Anything to him too
He has to like be like Ben was saying
Anyone's fault
He dies exactly like Gaston
Like his aggressive action
Is what ultimately causes
Even though I'm sure Twilight could have easily
Fucking targeted him too on that hovering
Yeah
Like that guy he had no powers
He just had a staff
And then he loses the staff
Why did they just fucking kill him when he lost the staff
Had just random fucking bubble gum
God mode killer gum
That just turns people to stone
Like they are
Plus
Even when he had the staff that one time
She faces off with him head to head
And they prove to be like an even fucking match
Him with the powered up staff
What the fuck
That fucking obliterated everyone
And they did not even try
That incredible
I didn't even think about that
I wonder if you could do a cut
Of this movie where it's the beginning
Where he gets the staff
You cut the entire middle of the movie
And it just cuts to the assault
And nothing really of value would be lost
I'm going into head canon now
But maybe it's like breaking the horn
Didn't rob her of her power
Of the ability to control it
So her power is coming out raw
And unfiltered now
She loses magic all over the movie
Her tone works
It only works
For that one specific thing
Which is funnily enough
Her super special
She's Fizzle Pop Sparkle Butter
It was Fizzle Pop Berry Twist
Fizzle Pop Berry Twist
So I assume that her fireworks were going to be
Her super special talent anyway
So the fact that her horn breaking
Includes all magic other than that one thing
She was destined to be good at
It's pretty neat, but I guess that's just equestrian destiny
In action
Since we're talking about the staff
Why do the princesses in their castle
Have this one thing
Where you put the staff in
They can rob them of their powers
I don't fucking know
It was a slot for this staff
He had the staff
He brought the staff with him
Maybe they built that
In the week that they had
After the ponies
If you have to head canon away it wasn't written well
You mean three days canonically
Three days canonically
Maybe in three days they carved out the mystic sigils
Required for the ceremony
That you just said could have been so helpful
Over the years
If you have to head canon it's not good writing
That could have saved us so much
I just figured it goes without
Fucking saying
But every time you bring that up you get fucking shit on
So fuck you
Well head canoning is fun
It is fun, but it's fun
But it's not a defensive shit
Writing
I'm not sure we should really listen to anything that tall tales
Known denouncer and lever of the
fandom has to say about this
I never left the fandom
I'm still here guys
I'm looking for life
Alive and kicking
Here's what you don't understand about the storm king and his
His ilk
So immediately once he captured everyone
We learned about this guy named storm king
Never heard about him before
The princesses act like they don't know who the fuck this is
Then we leave Equestria and immediately
We're in his territory
All of these locations
The pirates are his control
And the hippogriffs are completely
Outrun and completely obliterated
The ponies are extremely nationalistic and isolationist
Don't you find it retarded though
That everybody's been fucked over
By this guy
But as soon
As soon as we're in trouble
We're gonna go get help
Yeah
That's exactly what I was thinking
First they came for the griffons and I did nothing
For the pirates
Then they came for me and there was no one to help me
But I could actually
Okay
Did you notice
The subtle, not subtle
Blading, racist undertones
Twilight explicitly wanted to establish an ethno state
Within this My Little Pony movie
She keeps saying we can't trust conars
Quote unquote
We can't trust pirates
Come out and say Twilight
You ain't furries
You're a pony just like me
Tempest, I don't understand why you aren't on my side
What's going on here
Did you find it a little bit racist
When Rainbow Dash is saying
This cloven hoove motherfucker over here
Oh my god
Is there some shit here I'm not aware of
Nothing gets my big blue
Horstic rock heart
Than pony racism
I'm not even joking
I love that
She just owns all this land
The hippo grips who
Was specifically saying to contact
Have been already overrun
So like what was the plan here
Not even overrun
Not even overrun but like it's been like
Who even knows how long
Since this happened
The city has been there a while
And Celestia didn't know shit
She didn't know shit
She's in character
Full disclosure I did not watch this entire movie
Oh my fucking god
After the sea pony scene
And then everybody getting mad
At each other and splitting up
That was where I started hitting the forward button
That's where I wanted to hit the forward button
But I watched about
I watched like a couple seconds of every
Five seconds of the rest of the movie
Because I thought there was a new video digi
That you made recently called Thoroughly Analyzing Ponyo
And you talked about how you don't
Like those kinds of scenes in movies
And I can completely respect skipping it
There yes
Because it was just
Twilight's trying to see the pearl
Was super obnoxious and as soon as the scene started
I went oh here we go
They're all going to be mad at each other
And here's what I predicted and I was completely right
They will not have to resolve this
It will just resolve itself
Twilight will be captured
And they'll all come to help her
It won't be that
They have to have a conversation about
What she did wrong or anything like that
She's going to get in trouble
They're going to help her and none of this will have meant anything
We just presume
We just presume that Twilight has learned
Something in all of this
There's no confirmation of that
And she would do it again
She says
Friendship didn't fail me
I failed friendship
Okay what does that mean
Shouldn't she be demoted
Shouldn't those wings go away
He should definitely have to go on a pilgrimage
How many times does Twilight get to learn this lesson
Before we just say you're broken
Your most popular video
Theories on
Alicorn Princess Twilight Sparkle
Your most popular video
You talk about how she earns her wings
In the episode where she didn't even need
To learn anything about friendship
She intuitively fucking got it
Now the rewrite for this lowest point
Scene would be simple AF
They do the song
Twilight's part of the song to the sea ponies
Great job convincing them
And then the queen is all like this is a fun song
But wait you're just trying to manipulate me
I hate you go away and then they're all
Super bummed because they thought they were being really nice
And they were extending a hand of friendship
And they got smacked back down
And maybe you could even have Twilight get a little bit agitated
That all of her learnings about friendship
Didn't work this time
And she could still have a little bit of a kerfuffle with her friends
Not really ideal but you can still
Wax it in there if you need it to
And that's it she could still be
A friendship intuitive as she was
And she learns that she has to
If she wants to do the job right
She has to steal and kill
Twilight at that point
And then she goes and kills the bad
Twilight at that point becomes a
She learns the lesson of becoming a race realist
And realizing that the race realist
Will simply not be able to
Understand her high level pony friendship
Because they are lower beings
That's awesome a race realist
It's a good one
And a new
A new race realist is born
That's a affirmed race realist
Fucking Twilight
Manipulates her friends
Straight out just like
Does not tell them the plan
She could just tell them
Her plan and they would like
Talk about like friends
Because they're not evil like Twilight
They're not smart enough
Like the prince of thieves
Wait no Aladdin and the king of thieves
These naive ponies
Still naively trust in the power
Of friendship when Twilight has seen
The error of her ways because the cat man
Would mean to them
With becoming the princess of friendship
She has now got an actual state position
And it is now her responsibility to look at
For the well being of the entire kingdom
She does say that in the beginning of the movie herself
That inherently puts actual friendship
On a lower level
That's not the fucking theme to the whole franchise
So now it's not her priority
It's not her highest priority anymore
I'm about to drop a bombshell
That's gonna completely hijack this conversation
For the next 35 minutes
I'm either gonna
I'm either gonna be jeered
Or I'm gonna be peered
I might be knocked down
I might be saddled up
I might be plumped up
Some of you guys might hold me like 6 feet above water
And boil me, steam me, break up my carapace
You guys might groom me
Twilight, can we
We've been out of this fandom
For God knows how long we've been
Can we please stop pretending
Can we please just be on for ourselves
Twilight being a princess was always a bad idea
And it was never cool
Can we please stop pretending that it was
I have always said from the very beginning
That Twilight becoming a princess should have been
The last episode of my movie
Agreed, yeah for sure
I mean I'm gonna disagree with that
Not to even bring up the fact that
It doesn't make any sense
I mean I think it's okay
I think it's cool but there's just a million ways
It could have been done better which I believe
I know Digi was pretty positive about it
At the time
I don't see any reason it can't happen
I enjoyed the episode
The logic behind it is totally fucking
Totally fucking opaque
I used to say
Even at the time that I think it should have happened
At the end of season 4
Because there should have been an arc
Like season 4 feels like
The arc leading up to her becoming princess
Like when you see the way
That people react to her the way she's not really treated
Like a princess that season
And the way people react to her is like
She's someone important now but not quite
There should have been an arc about her becoming like famous
Or like known as a problem
Solver and like people are coming to her
And as she solves friendship problems
Around Equestria she eventually
Is granted princess status
Maybe establish that that's a thing that can
Happen before springing it on you
Out of nowhere
The thing that I never liked about
The princess thing with the wings
Is that
Yeah it was Celestia and Luna
And that's it
And they were like super special
They erased the sun and the moon
And then you can just become one
And then there's Caden
This was my argument back in the day
They've become less and less interesting
And the lore becomes more and more convoluted
And it's very clear that being a princess
Doesn't mean you
Solved like you're very good at it
It just means that you're
Well that's something
My problem with
We're getting in some deep shit
I think it would have been
Easily possible to make
Twilight becoming a princess make sense
In the narrative and everything
I just think that it was not
It was jumped the gun because of the mandate
From Hasbro to Duke
To kind of work the series around it
And it's not until season 5 that it starts making sense
Where she actually is treated like a princess
It's amazing to think now
That Twilight has been a princess longer than she has
Not been
So my problem with Twilight as an Alicorn
Is that it means that the main six only has
One unicorn now
And look
That's my problem too
Right no no no
As we all know
This might be good information
The appeal of MLP is encased in autism
As you
I know maybe some people have heard of it
We all
You have to chip away the autism
To get to the My Little Pony goodness
I would say that there is
If you had a Venn diagram
Of autism and My Little Pony fans
It's almost just a circle
Right no no no
We are all
Dead in the middle of that
And we're the only ones
On the edge
I am in the middle of that
The main six, most of the ponies
They all have the same basic character shape
With some slight differences, different color palettes
Sonic the Hedgehog is the same
The sort of symmetry is pleasing
To the autistic eye
And two unicorns, two earth ponies
And two Pegasus high
Means there's this nice
Symmetry that's very pleasing
And it's really triggering my autism
That they changed it
I totally agree
If you read the
Very first analysis I ever wrote about MLP
My argument is essentially
That even though the show
Is all flash animation and stock stuff
That is the appeal
That it's so
Samey that it's such a clear
You can understand it
At a glance
And you can make your own
You can inject your own because it's so easy
It's such a template
It's so popular for autistic people
Because it's all
It's like
What the fuck
It's like you said
I'm seeing all the ones and zeros
In the show
When you look at the animation now
I think that's what we all kind of did
From the start
You like the ones and zeros
You want to play around with them
Autism programming
It's all a rich tapestry
We're all in the spectrum
It's all a rich tapestry that we use
To weave into a giant pressure blanket
That we use to get to sleep at night
I don't know if you guys feel the same way
But the locations in this movie
We're all fucking horrible
Like okay
And my little pony things are clean
And colorful
When they go to a completely generic
Dundadeth all one color
Brown sandy literal star war
Common fucking corporate
That's what they were going for
You know Munchy, I was really upset
Because
When they show that kingdom from the distance
It looks awesome
The image from a distance looks really cool
And I was excited because it made me think of how
The worst thing about
Episode one of season five
Was when they go to that town that just looks like
Shit, it's just nothing
And it was like the most unmemorable location
In the whole fucking show
And that had really bothered me at the time
Oh hey, it's like the art design that I expect from the show
And then they go there and it's just a generic
Um, yeah
Like bizarre and I was like oh it's one of these
It's all one color
It's all exactly one mid-tone color
You're not wrong
And even when they get to cool locations like the underwater area
And the last locations like that too
Well like the underwater location
The sea pony place sucked
Hold on
I'm talking about the top of the mountain
Was all gray
And then when they go and they're all sad
And they're like twilight, you're mean
And she's like yeah I am, it's all gray as well
It's all gray
That movie is weirdly gray
That is the trope of the breaking up the friend scene
Is that it's a gray place
Like if you watch all those Disney movies
It's always in a gray location
There was definitely an element
Of juxtaposing the pastelness
Of the ponies with like drabness
Of these other environments
Especially the ones outside of Equestria
All drab and it makes me want to die
Because it sucks
Wasn't the underwater place
Pretty cool
I don't know where the other one is
The throne room, you know
The throne room, not only is it that
It's just the throne room
But also that the throne room is literally copy-pasted
From the little mermaid
It's just the same place
Where's what you heard about the mermaid?
I liked the
The song montage done
When they were in the water place
Was enough to endear me to that place
I went to the bathroom to bring that song
Because I was sick of hearing songs
You watched the torrent
There's a pause button, what's wrong with you
No, I wanted to make
I wanted to not have to watch it
So I went, oh, they're singing
Great, let me get up and go get a drink
So that I don't have to watch it
Oh, that didgy brony
The integrity of all of your analysis work
Is now completely fucked
The word you say
You shouldn't have in the first place
I've never had integrity
That's why I put God's own channel
We've been glossing over
A part of the movie, which if you watched the trailer
You could have assumed it was a big part of the movie
But in actuality, it wasn't
That one celebrity appearance was literally completely meaningless
I was gonna bring that up
She only had like three lines
Literally just to trick people to see the movie
But it didn't work because I don't have no clue
She's just some Stacy
I like her hair
Okay, okay, her speaking voice
Her speaking voice is so soft
Genuine, you're not kidding anyone
We know you're mean, we know you're awful
Because you're a celebrity and they're all bad
We're not kidding anyone
We know you're bad, we know it
What she's famous for
Is that she's an anti-celebrity
No one knows what she looks like
She's like a hidden
She writes the biggest pop songs in the world
But she's never revealed herself
And nobody knows anything about her
Is that why her face was covered by all this hair
Yeah, that's actually what she looks like
In real life, she has the
Didn't you know the
Swinging on the chandelier song with the little girl who dances
And it's like the butterflies
Do you honestly think I have any connection
To pop culture beyond my little pony at all
Anybody know what the fuck this is
I watched the music video for
Tom, there's no way you haven't heard this song
Because it was like, I heard it
And I don't watch anything
Pop-related, but I don't know
You know way more about music than I do
Was it just like the ocean
Under the moon, you got the same
It was that
That's the one
That's Sia
I watched it
I watched certain that there was like a my little pony
Animation that allows this video
I watch Sia's cheap thrills music video
All the time because I love it
She's pretty cool
Wait, cheap thrills
Up with it, girl
Yeah, it's that fucking really gay shit
I don't know
Okay, let's not get too hung up on this
The point is Sia was in it, she's a celebrity
She sang a song, she was a character, she was okay
I didn't care
She's actually a pony and that was her face
Oh, whoa
Wait, wait, wait, this is the canon Sia
This is the actual one in the movie
The human version, it's just an avatar
She's communicating with the real world
Maybe we're all just characters
In a show that the ponies are watching
You guys ever think about that
It's like the Simpsons game for Xbox 360
But Sia, she's in the movie for no reason
Other than at the end
They get to have the big concert
That's like, yeah, now we've resolved everything
The fight gets to be that MC
Cause that's what he does and it's good time
I did not like it, but
I didn't dislike it, but Cheese Sandwich
Makes a cameo in this episode
And it just made me remember how amazing that was
The Cheese Sandwich episode
That's the perfect way to do it
The point of the Sia character
Is just so that's why I could have a thing
To talk about at the beginning, obviously
But I'm thinking, well, obviously
I thought immediately in the beginning of the movie
Well, at the end of the movie
Some sort of light show effect is going to happen
And it's going to be, well, not underwhelming
Cause I'm expecting it to be completely normal
And that's exactly what happened
Chip horn girl is like, I'm going to do
Fizzle Pop Man Twist
He does a fucking magic and I'm like, alright
It's going to be a firework, it's going to be totally normal
And everyone is going to act like it's exceptional
And they boop boop, totally normal effect
And I'm like, yup, okay, you guys did it
You guys had a couple years to make the movie
You could have like actually made something that was like really
Surprisingly artistic
Dude, they had, they had Trixie already
They could have used the fireworks
Yeah, they could have used the fireworks
This franchise has a long-stoyed history
Of ignoring Trixie's potential
And making new characters instead
That's literally what I said to my boyfriend
When we were watching, it was like
They could have just used Trixie for the fireworks
From the very beginning, Twilight could have
Just asked Trixie to do the fireworks
Trixie is in the movie
The name of the game in this movie is
Redundancy, right?
The name of this franchise is redundancy
I guess Twilight must have taken Trixie
Aside and been like, hey, I know
I know this was your bit, but just let
That Fizzle Pop have this, like she needs a victory
Right now, like
Dude, I would kill to have that seed
I could see that happening in the show
I could totally see like
Random background quality being asked
To step aside for someone else
That would totally happen in the show
And it would be hilarious
Speaking of scenes that were good
My favorite part of the episode was the Dr. Wolf reference
But other than that, my actual
Favorite bit in this movie
Was like, so there was
Twilight fucks everything up
The one who leads the charge
Telling her off and that she is fucked up
Is Pinkie Pie
Pinkie Pie actually filled
A leadership role in that position
As well as when they decide to go save Twilight
Because Pinkie is the one
That's because Pinkie
That's because Pinkie is the only written character
In the movie
It would have felt very strange
If Applejack, who makes more sense
To be in that position, suddenly had something
To do when she hasn't done anything
When you start up the movie, you have this giant box
Of conceits in a giant package of library
You got to accept all of them
All six of them are going to be there the whole time
And mostly it's not going to matter
That's just what it's for
That's the same thing that happens with all these adventures
That's always been a big problem
It's the Twilight show and her amazing friends
I think that there was space in this movie
To give them all something to do
Of course that could be
I think they gave
An exceptional amount of time to Pinkie Pie
Because she is the most popular character
With little girls and she's Pink
And that's what Hasbro wants
Guys, do you think
That in this situation of it being a movie
They could have
Permanently killed Fluttershy and Applejack
If they weren't going to use it
I was disappointed they didn't
They get caught in the crossfire
When the Thorn King falling
They do some sort of weird fusion
Applejack and Rainbow Dash become one character
And Pinkie Pie and Fluttershy
Also become one character
And the voice actors only have to
Have you ever noticed how
Rainbow Dash should have the element of honesty
And Applejack should have the element of honesty
Whoa
The blow in my mind
The elements are gone
Yeah, elements are irrelevant
They are gone
Did anyone else find it
Slightly amusing when
Rarity was like
I wasn't raising a barn
Sorry Applejack
I laughed at that joke
Okay, I guess there were two jokes
There were good jokes in the movie
Every joke in this movie
You just forgot because everything after the first
15 minutes
Those are the only two good ones
There was one joke that I found funny
It really surprised me that one moment
During the fight
Pinkie Pie
Gave a present
To one of the girls like surprise
And then he opens the box and she pops out
Double surprise
I wasn't terrible
I found it amusing
But then it's immediately ruined by the whole
Pinkie Pie throwing infinite cupcakes
With that stupid face on her face
I was fine
I liked when she threw the first cupcake
And they made it look like a blood splatter
On the wall behind him
See
There are good things in this movie
When the wind is whipping by
And the goons are getting hit with pies
It looks like they're being ripped apart
By shrapnel
The first thing I thought I was like
Holy shit
That's a very MLP thing to do
They've done shit like that
They always replicate
A serious movie but in a goofy fun
Kitty way
I have a very important question for everybody
Was this better than
Girls
Unequivocally
I don't know
How is this even a debate you guys question
But not better than Rainbow Rock
Just think back to that moment
At the end with the whole battle against demons
What's her face
Sunset
It was terrible
It was better than
Equestria Girls 1 but not as good as
Rainbow Rock
Can't they just both be undesirable
Yeah
So firstly I quite liked
The animation so I think
It's a lot better in the animation department
And cinematic stuff
I mean Equestria Girls looks like that
Writing wise
It's equally as bad
It's like the most basic fetch story
Quest without any sort of character arcs
In it and lots of stupid stuff
Just crammed in just for the sake of being there
It's such a poor writing
I completely agree
The fact that all the other
The songs
I think fail a lot more
Than any of the Equestria Girls songs
As much as I dislike some of them
They're at least earworms
And I quite enjoyed the villain songs
In most Equestria Girls movies
Which I mean in this one
Not so much I don't remember it as
Quite as well as the any other ones
I'm definitely not good at
Equestria Girls Rainbow Rocks songs
Were not the right type
Of rock music
There's not enough
I never saw
The other Equestria Girls movies
But based on
There's only two right?
There's a bunch of them now
They make one every year
The third one's bad
The second one's kinda good
The fourth one is like
In the camp
In like a
Concentration camp
I remember
I remember being
The guy who defended Equestria Girls
You fool
Pretty colors dude
Pretty colors now
I definitely regret
My position
I'm glad the history shows
I was right the entire time
Mostly because the movie
Is so insanely ugly
That I cannot look at it anymore
And I don't know the visuals
I just realized that
I don't know
I can't even look at the show anymore
I don't like
My little pony friendship
Can we talk about that for a second?
That's a point that I was struggling going through
The entire time watching this movie
And up to this podcast was that
I was trying to think of like
How do I enjoy this movie now
Versus how would I have enjoyed this movie
If it actually came out like six months after they announced it
Because this whole time
Experience in the fandom
From 2012 to like
2014 or 15 or whatever
I never understood why
I liked the show to begin with
I could never really quantify it in a way that made sense to me
And when I got out of it
I could never understand
How I even got so obsessed with it in the first place
Like it just feels
So weird to think about
How I even did that so much
I don't regret it
But I just feel like
The show is more than I loved MLP
And I never got into them to such a degree
I'm glad I did because I never would have met any of you guys
It was the power of the zeitgeist
Man, it was the fan
It was how active and fervent the fan base was
I got into it
Through the Newgrounds Game Story of the Blank
That was my first exposure and it really impressed me
Dude, I know
Guys, I know the exact
Date I got in MLP
For one specific reason
9-11, 2000
I got in MLP
I got into MLP
On August 10th, 2011
And I know that for a fact
Because that's the date
The Know Your Meme on My Little Pony came out
And that's how I found out about it
And much of it was refreshing that page fervently
Waiting for new memes to drop on that page
I got into it by my friend who was trying to get me into it
Showing me Captain Hook the Biker Gorilla
Rainbow Dash presents
With all these fucking loses
And I was like, that is my introduction to MLP
The most confusing thing ever
But I was literally sold on watching the show
Simply by virtue of witnessing how much effort
Would be put into a fan work
I thought, well, the show must be striking
Some sort of really deep chord
With some pretty deep specs going on
That's how I feel, definitely
I got into the show through TF2 analysis
Okay, since we got totally filmed again
Here's a question then
Do you think that none of us were
Do you think we were all just tangentially fans of MLP
And we're all fans of the MLP fandom
I will say this
The fandom wasn't even there when I started watching it
No, my enjoyment of MLP
Was sincere at many points
Yeah, no, I think there's a lot of good stuff
About the show
And it's a matter of
I didn't get into it immediately
I watched all of Season 1
And thought it was okay
It was Season 2
And I started involving myself in the fandom
And it was more like
Finding the good
The nuggets of gold was what was exciting
About it
Looking deep into it
And saying, oh wow, when you really think about it
That's an interesting idea
And so it was the analysis
That made me love the show so much
But then when you're not trying
To find all the great stuff
In it and you're just looking at what it is
I realized
That I got to a point with the show
Where I didn't start paying attention
Until three minutes into the episode
It starts
Like on my little pony episode
Opens with just characters describing
What the plot is going to be
For minutes on end, usually
I recently tried to go back
And watch Apple Buck Season
Because it was my favorite episode
And the whole opening segment is just
Big MacTosh going, you can't possibly
Get all these apples
And she's like, well, I can try to
And I'm like, oh okay
I don't need any of it
And I'm like, what's your favorite episode?
Huh? What are you saying?
Because you always said that's my favorite episode
But all your videos on it were like
I like it, eh, eh
And I was like, who had the best jokes?
That's why I liked it so much
It has by far the funniest jokes in the show
Okay, you're a good, you're a dry humor
I felt for a long time
Like certain members of this group
Lay it down for it, Keg, lay it on
A few members of this group
To me really seem to be making
Just actually reflective of their
Of their heart of heart opinions
Of the show and an attempt to distance themselves
And I get that
Some people might legitimately have been caught in the zeitgeist
And really now, they don't really care as much
I was probably
One of the most
Maybe, I was one of the most
Strident in my desire to remove myself completely
From the pony shit
Just not talk about it all, do my own thing
And just never reverence it or whatever
And that was only because I just didn't want
The same, like, perception of who I was
And, and, like, that fandom
Into my new shit, I just wanted to start new
And that's fine, but I am happy to admit
I go back and watch episodes of My Little Pony
All the time
Especially the, uh, the Diamond Tera episode
Is, is one of my favorite episodes
Of anything ever
And that's up against every episode of
Gurren Lagann, every episode of Stand Alone Complex
Every fucking episode of Fooly Coolie
It is one of my favorite episodes
Of anything I've ever seen in my life
Having seen it recently
It's really difficult, the thing is
My tastes have changed considerably
Since that time, like, when I went
Into My Little Pony, I came into it from
Having been somebody who was, like,
Literally anti-plot
Like, I thought that plot
Oh, you weren't anti-plot anymore, though
You're giving me that animation, I'm so much
Ammunition right now
Everybody knows this, I've said this a million times
I was literally, I did not think
I mean, I still feel that way, but, like
I literally thought that plot does not matter
And is stupid, like, when I was
Younger, I thought plot is
The least interesting thing about a show
And should not be paid attention to
All I care about is the characters
And watching them interact, all I watched
Was, like, cute girl shows and, like, magical
Girl shit, you know, like, and that's what
MLP was to me, was, like, a perfect
Representation of what I was interested in
But after MLP, really
At some point during the show, I got
Interested in plot-driven stuff
You know, through, like, Mass Effect
And then
I got really into sci-fi
And cyberpunk, and, like, if you look at what
I was watching immediately after MLP
It was all cyberpunk animation
That's interesting that you say Mass Effect got you into
Plot-driven stuff, because I don't know
I was way more into the characters than the plot
Well, yeah, that's how it got me in
After Mass Effect won, the plot was retarded
Okay, sure, but
What I'm saying is that it got me interested in, like,
World-building and, like, all these high-concept
Shit, like, I hated sci-fi
And I hated politics before Mass Effect
And now those are my two favorite jobs
I still want to do a Mass Effect podcast at some point
So, like, in the wake of MLP
The stuff I got interested in is, like
I don't know, I have, like, a much more adult
Taste, I guess, than I did even at the time
Like, MLP
MLP was indicative of the taste
I had at the time, and it is not now
And going back to watch it, it's really
Difficult to get through all the child-proofing
All of the, like, I, you know
All I want to say is people seem to forget
That there are episodes, like, putting your foot down
In my little pony
What the fuck is a foot?
Putting your hoof down, and how many fucking
Shows, at period, have addressed, like,
Assertiveness training seminars
Or, like, pick up culture
Or any of that kind of, like, like, nobody even
Wants to talk or think about that shit
Like, it takes weird-ass movies like Magnolia
To even bring up the idea of that kind of shit
And yet my fucking little pony
Makes an episode about it
I will never forget, I will never
End giving credit to that show
For making that shit part of an episode
I totally think it deserves, it deserves the credit
You know, I really, I really like, there's
Tons of, I still like suit of recess
I still think it's fucking fantastic
I still have all my favorites
I just, what I, it's weird
Because I don't understand, really, how
I got so obsessed with it, because I'd never participated
In a fandom at all, and never had any desire to
But now that I'm on the outside
I just have this weird feeling of awkwardness
Because, despite the fact that
I don't regret participating as much
As I did, like, I'm back to
Where I was before, and, like, I would never
Put that much time and effort into something
Like that
I will happily say that I was a bronie
And I will happily say
I met all of you people doing Mylepony
It was an incredibly great thing
That happened to me
Oh, absolutely
We will forever
I will just say, that was all
Things about the fandom that I enjoyed
And the sense of community that I felt when I was
In the bronie fandom, though embarrassing to say
Was pretty great, and there are a lot of things
I like about Mylepony itself
However, like, I don't know
Things change, bro
Things change
Things change, but sometimes we have to
Hashtag we have to go back
That's one of those sides
You grow up in your taste change, but also like
I mean, maybe it was always there
And I just wasn't seeing it, but, you know, at some point
At some point the tone shifted
And it became important to me personally
To get away from it
So as not to be lumped in with people like
KP and Dr. Wolf
It was important to my personal sense of identity
That I not be one of those
I feel like this is being like a big deal
Like, for us
Because, like, the bronie thing
Was such a big thing
It's a show that, you know
We liked it at a time, and now we don't
As much
There are other shows and games and things
That I have gotten into and then gone out
Of liking
And then maybe years later, I'm like
You know what, I might go and check that out again
It's not really any different
But the reason is like
We're making a big deal out of it because it was a fandom
Exactly
Mylepony is like your first girlfriend
Yeah, you'll date other girls
But you don't give a fuck about them
You only care about the original one
I always only care about her and want her forever
For me, with MLP
That's how it is
The thing that makes it weird is just that
It was the first show I ever had
Shout out to my girlfriend, by the way
Get fucked, Michelle
At the time that Mylepony came out
I was really grappling with the fact that
I didn't have a favorite show
I loved animated death
But I never had one thing
That I was like, this is my favorite
And MLP became that
And I think just
A lot of my love for the show was just
That I loved the show
Therefore I performed that
It's like a
Or a boros, you keep doing it
Because you say you do it
And then that keeps happening
And once you break out of that
Then it's like, okay, now that I've lost that
Now that I've lost the idea of
DigiBronie, you know
What is left
I just think that perhaps
I approached this whole thing
Because Ben and I never ever called ourselves
Bronies And especially I felt like that was part of
What I did
I really enjoyed the show
But I never really involved myself with anyone
Except people who were already cool people
Like all of the people here right now
They only associated with those people
Ben and I never liked at all any of that rift shit
Any of those other people
They were always trash and you could tell instantly
Except for Ben who loved it and was in TF2
And now his anarchy
My proudest moment
The height of my career
I figured out
Why I like my little pony
I figured it out
And you guys are gonna feel real fucking old
Because I was thinking about it
And the reason I like my little pony
I was thinking about it
It came on August 10th, 2011
I was born
I was
I got into it on August 10th, 2011
I was literally 10
I was literally 10 years old
I was like what
When I got into it
You admit older than that Ben
You're like 90
I've aged like 70 years
I was 22
Leaving the
Leaving the brony fan and really takes a toll
On your soul
That's probably why I liked it
Because I was a baby
The rest of us have no excuse
No excuse basically
I see
You get involved
Heavily enough and something like that
And it becomes a part of who you are
I know exactly why I liked it
It's the art style
It's very simple and cute and pastel colored
It's all the things I like
You're a girl so you're allowed to feel that way
I fell in love with it
I really fell in love with the show
When the winter wrap-up song played
Because I fucking love musicals
And I will watch any show that has music in it
God I just want to be a musical man forever
It's a great song
The thing that makes it unique is that
It is the cheap, chintzy, 5 year old girl's show
But done competently
Sometimes it's great
So you kind of sign waves right around
In the pretty good zone
And I believe I'm looking around
When it comes to western shows
With some poppy animation for girls
It's still probably the best one
And that has a unique position
And if you're going through a certain dark part of your life
Having something like that could be just the right thing
To pick you up and make you happy
And it's more of a time in place thing
And slap you down
For me it was definitely a
New thing and seeing all the world building
And just experiencing it for the first time
It's a great experience
And it was a great way to inspire lots of people
To make the fandom
People say, oh people just stuck it into the fandom
Well, the fandom became the kind of fandom that it was
Because of what the show inspired in them
And that just dragged it out
I feel like...
Everyone of us here who was inspired to create art
Through the My Little Pony
Analysis community or whatever it was
I feel like we all had that within us
Of course, that
Ability was inside all of us to go do the kind of thing
But I am just so grateful for the show
To being the vehicle that helped me develop it
I am such
Gratitude for it
I have nothing but respect for the show
And I will defend it
Because I don't want to look like
A fucking idiot for having like that
I really thought you were going somewhere else with that
Yeah, me too
Yeah, no
By the way, how long is this going to go?
I think we'll book this with a podcast with that anime snob
Whoa!
We're going to do just for that anime snob
This is
Jesus fucking crazy
How fucking telling is that?
The Digi Brony is betraying us
You're fucking anime snob
At least just bring him in
Bring him in
It's with the
Pause and select and all that
I'll make them wait
We're going a while longer
I feel similarly about like
The show giving me the confidence
To make stuff
Because I always wanted to make gaming videos
But I feel like if I had just
Like if I hadn't been
Part of the pony community and met anybody
Doing reviews and
Had a chance to test
You know my abilities
I probably would have ended up as like
I don't know, a cadichorus or someone worse than me
Like someone just okay
Not hundreds of thousands of subscribers
I honestly think
I'm not a subscriber cad
I think I would just not be as where I am
If I didn't have the community
He happened in the fires of the
Brony fanaticism
In the Brony sphere, think of it like a fucking tea tree
And there was one specific chemical
That all of us had that attracted us together
And then we forged our bond
In that realm and we had this
Ideological synchronization
That we're still riding on this time
I wasn't doing analysis videos at the time
I was following all of you pretty closely
Or at least some of you pretty closely
I never would have done anything youtube related
If I hadn't gotten dragged into this shit storm
So I'm grateful that
I was able to expand as a creator
Do more things and I definitely
Gained more confidence, more skills
And I have a ton of things that I've done
And can do now that I never would have been able to otherwise
So that was all pretty fun
I'm extremely grateful to the
Brony community for
Allowing me to take advantage of them
And launch my career
I would not, it was a very small pond
That I was able to be a big fish in
By being smarter than everybody else
Involved with it
You know
That's the Brony way
When I made my first Brony video
I told my friend Ghost Lightning
I can probably gain
Enough subscribers from this
That once I switch to doing games analysis
I'll have an audience
And that worked
And it was great because imagine if that hadn't happened
That would mean that now sitting
Pretty today in 2017 you'd have to look at the first year
And a half of your career making like
Video game and anime videos
And it's like you know that a lot of people would
Get curious and watch them and you'd be like
Don't but thankfully since they're all pony
No one's gonna go see them so you don't have to deal
With people seeing them
No one ever goes back to my like
The earliest videos that anybody will watch from me
Are already pretty good because I cut my teeth
On this other bullshit that nobody wants
To be involved with unless they already were
You can downplay your personal
Investment in this all you want did you
No no no I'm not downplaying anything
I'm just saying that my fans will
Not go watch those videos
And those videos are much worse than what I do
Now because I cut my teeth on them
Like I learned how to make videos
By doing pony analysis
When I watch sometimes I go back and watch those
It's really fucking hard to watch them
I think it's funny that
Digi Brony is using a teeth
I know I was thinking about that
I'm thankful
For the Brony community because BronyCon
What was it 2015 I think
Yeah I think so
The second year we were all there together
It was probably the best convention of my entire life
And I'm so glad I'm in all of you
And I'm really happy
That was really great
My favorite moment
In this movie is the first time
Celestia was on screen and I was said to my girlfriend
That's the voice actress I almost punched
In the face
Bitch
By the way hippo
I just want to say
I need you to apologize for my little pony
Right now you're a brick and I don't want to have to place you down
I don't want to have to place you down hippo
Please apologize for my little pony
I will never ever apologize
I'll leave you alone
I'm gonna have to push you down
It's just how it's gonna be
On record right now
I'm 10 to 15 minutes
I'm gonna push you down
She should have been the main character in this movie
If she was the main character then I would be screaming
I just want to say that we've had
We've had a real helpful discussion
A real nuanced discussion
About the pros and cons and the thing we like and dislike
And what it all meant to us
But I would like to just throw all that right out the window
Because I don't know about you guys
But I've had a couple too many diet code red
Mountain Dews and I gotta take a piss
And I'm gonna fucking do it
I'm gonna fucking take a piss on the movie
I'm gonna take a piss on the bronies
And I'm gonna take a piss
On everyone in the world
Can I personally say what
I'm literally sorry
I have to leave right now
Because that's why we scheduled this earlier
So that he could leave
Also I have double booked a podcast
I guess that's the way the wind is blowing
No, you don't understand
I'm peeing right now
Ben you wanna pee with me
You're my best friend
Strawberry milk and phantom horn
We're hitting on the MLP movie
Bloody fuckers, calculers, we're paying for a thousand years
I hear it
This is the best ASMR
Yeah, this should have been the ASMR cast
Oh wow, here we go
Do you wanna make your point?
I wanna say what I'm power
I love power
It's too much, it's overflowing
Get a new bottle, get a new bottle
I'm holding it in
Please at least stop talking
Fuck me, fuck unicorn
Fuck alicorn
Everything that ever was or ever will be
In the holy land of equestria
You're all pee
You're all pee now
Go ahead
You're so gross
I know
Well, now I can
I don't wanna be honest and stuff like that
Now that they're peeing
So liberating
I feel like we don't need to do questions
Jesus Christ
You guys can do questions after me and once you leave
Oh yeah, okay, bye
Bye, bye
You're leaving
Alright, we'll just say
Let's do a handful
I don't fucking know
Yep
I was just wondering who's leaving and why
Munchie's leaving because he has to go on a trip immediately
Like that's why we had to do this at two
Okay, understood
Go to it, people have to leave
Goodbye
Munchie get the fuck out of the car
I'm sorry
He was peed after he left
Yeah
I wanted him here
You want to make your point
The mood is run though
Okay, tell you what
We'll come back to that after some questions
Yeah, I want to answer at least one question
Before we all fucking
Before I take off to go talk to
Snob or whatever
Munchie was actually the one looking at the discord
If somebody else wants to pull that up
I'll take a look at it
Okay, cool
What do we got here?
No, that's shit, that's terrible
I don't know
At draw fill draw asks
Will there ever be a hashtag dad con
I guess where our dads go to a convention
I would assume
We'll have that con once Munchie steals all the dads
Yeah
We'll put them all in a bunker together
I'll send my dad along
In a package
Have we ever answered
Do you plan on having children?
I don't know
I think we might have on some sort of a podcast
I think on like a really earlier podcast
I definitely intend on having children
No, we have answered this
Because Nate gave us this whole rundown
Of what his kids are going to be
That's right, I did
Vincent and Charlotte, yep, that's right
I will never have children
I think it's retarded
I'm way too selfish
I would sacrifice my children
At the first possible opportunity
To advance myself
I've heard you talk about that too
I don't know what a child is
But I plan to have fillies
That's good
Because I'm still
Give us another question
I'm not finding any I want to read out
I'll just quickly answer the question while you're finding the thing
Sure, go for it
I don't particularly want any at this current time
Maybe in the future
But highly, I doubt it very highly
Don't like children
I agree, Paige
Well
In the Patreon chat
Crafty asks how long do you take to pee
And we just answered that live
You've got that on right here
Ascan asks
The biggest let down you've ever experienced
The My Little Pony movie
Yeah
Oh guys, guys, guys
When I said I don't like children
My cat mealed and came up to me and I was snuggling me
Yes, he is my child, I like you
Yes, they're good
We can control them and bend them to our will
Here's an actually great question
El Gringo Bandito
asks what's your favorite sword
That's a good question
I like a good bastard sword
A big
Hilt bastard sword
I just like bastard because then I could say it in class
And the teacher would be like I could say bastard
A pokey sword
I really don't know anything about swords
The one that does its job
No
That's like the weakest one
Folded a thousand times
Catanas are
Pretty cool though
Eek
Real
They cut the weak western steel
Are you kidding me?
My favorite sword is a specific answer
I like Stormbringer
It's a sword from the Eternal Champion Saga
The Elric Saga, it's pretty cool
It's a sword all made of black
Red runes etched into it
And with the sword it works
If you get cut by it, it steals your soul
And it's fucking awesome
The Storm King could have used that
It was funny
I was trying to remember the Storm King's name
And all I could think of was Stormbringer
I'm like it's not Stormbringer, he's not that cool
Fuck that shit
It's simple, but I've always really loved the Buster Sword
What can I say, the Buster Sword is dope
When I was younger I liked
The more ornately designed swords
But now I like big, simple
I really like a Sonosuke
Sagaura sword from Ruroni Kenshin
That he uses one time
Before he does
Fist of Cuffs
And also this
Zvihander from Dark Souls
It's kind of like a bastard sword
It's not from Dark Souls, it's from real life
That's a real sword
I like it because of Dark Souls
I think maybe my favorite sword is one of Zolo's
swords
You call them Zolo
I grew up calling him Zolo
One of Zoro's sword
Which one?
I really like the blue one
It's not even his best one
That's the cursed one, right?
No, no, it's one he gets later
As a replacement for one that breaks
Someone gives it to him
Because it's the best one they got lying around
Oh, that's really early
With the black sheath
The cursed one with the weird
Wavy pattern
In the cut of it
I really fucking love
Zoro's sword
And tragically, that one you're talking about right now
Is destroyed by a man with rust powers
And gets replaced later on
The blue one does?
That's right
But I liked it because
It wasn't like some Mary Sue sword
It wasn't like the best sword ever
It was an excellent sword
That someone gave to him because they felt he deserved it
And it fucking died
It suffered a tragic end
But it looked really cool
Zoro's swords have great backstories
Especially because the one he gets later to replace it
Is actually a sword used by this guy
Who was in one of Oda's previous works
About a fucking dragon slaying samurai guy
That's the dopest thing ever
None of the other questions are interesting to me
So I'm going to take off
You guys can keep answering it
Okay, peace dog
Bye, didgybrony
Get out, didgybrony
Tell us a tall tale, why don't you
I got a question from the PCP chat
It could be interesting
If the PCP were to form a band of any genre
What would the roles for each member be
And what would the first album be called
The album would definitely be gay and dead
Absolutely
Gay and dead too
I would be guitar boy
I want to be the designated band
Scatman
That would be what I would do
I don't know
Bye
Okay, I'm not down for this trickling away
We would instantly kick Davoo out of the band
Okay, let's
It's a musical difference
Alright, we're done everybody
Thanks for listening, this has been kegstandard
And this has been two best brothers bitch about ponies
Subscribe to our channel
Woo, fuck
Oh
And make sure you send us more questions
Ask hashtag
Ask PCP on Twitter
Or join our god damn patreon
Because we got bonus episodes
And with one dollar you get access to the discord
Where we just read a bunch of questions
That are frankly more likely to be read
And there's a great community there
Those people are dope, they're the best fans of the PCP
They're all fantastic
And I got a thing to plug
If you want to see
Really awkward first interaction conversations
With all of us
For the horse cast
Because that's what this PCP was before
I was never on the horse cast though
You fuckers
That's true
So fuck all of these guys, they're gay
I thought by that time we had made the PCP chat
Or something, I don't know
It was a long time ago
Also, the Procrastiners podcast
Is on iTunes and on Google Play
Just to alleviate some confusion
Because I've gotten some questions about this
Even though it's technically on Google Play
You have to go to the Google Play Music app
On your phone, not the Google Play store
It's really retarded, I don't know why it's that way
But you go to the Google Play Music app
And then you go to the podcast section
If you want to listen to it on your Android phone
Fantastic
Or you just go to the podcast app on your iPhone
Thanks, thanks Steve Jobs
What a great guy
You really dicked us on this one
Well, he's dead now, so we got to the last one
We've got some merch as well
There's some links below, yeah buy that shit
I don't know, whatever the fuck you want to do fam
I guess that's it
Thanks for listening everybody
Let's put your hooves together
And say goodbye
Bye
My little pony
I used to wonder what friendship could
Okay, I'm done
My little pony, I used to watch the show
But now I don't
Yeah
Yeah, uh
I'm supposed to
Be working
Right now
I'm supposed to
Be working right now
But I'm not
Working
I'm doing nothing
Why dick I'm
Drinking
Myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I got a
Deadline
Don't want to do it