1, 2, 3, sync!
And one more time. 1, 2, 3, sync!
I never got my apple juice.
Dab.
Sorry. Are you getting apple juice?
It's okay. It's okay. It's too late.
This is the first time hearing about apple juice.
Anyway, welcome to the Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Yeah, hello everybody. We're here. That's the episode.
What do you know? It already started. Who could have predicted this thing?
Welcome to the Apple Juice Cast.
Remember Apple Jacks? The cereal.
Here's my hot take. As a child, didn't much care for apple juice. I don't know why.
As an adult, I find it almost too delicious, almost too sweet.
I find the flavor of apple juice to be intense, and it's strange.
When I was a kid, I didn't like apple juice at all.
As an adult, I drink it and I'm like, whoa!
That sounds stupid, but I'm being completely genuine.
I'm almost on the same boat, though.
When I was a kid, I used to like the mixed fruit or whatever.
It was a 2D fruity something.
Wild berry punch.
No, no, no. It's mixed fruit. All of the fruits are together.
Right now, when I taste it, it's too sweet and kind of watered down.
So I really dislike it.
But apple juice, though. Apple juice is the god of the juices.
I love it so much. It's so good.
It's pressed apple juice. It's the most delicious juice of all.
I know. We're raised orange juice boys, and orange juice remains king of juices.
No. Orange juice has rained for too long.
I prefer orange juice.
I prefer orange juice growing up.
I think I probably still prefer it, but grapefruit juice is my thing.
Grapefruit juice is my favorite.
I also like cranberry juice. I guess I like bitter stuff.
Bitter is best.
To a restaurant for breakfast, I would say, excuse me waiter, please give me a,
please mix me a tall glass of two-thirds cranberry, one-third grapefruit juice.
Thank you very much. And that is my favorite.
Did you say bitter? Do you mean bitter or do you mean like sour?
Bitter. I guess it's sour.
Cranberries, I mean they're a little sour, but cranberries and grapefruits are both bitter.
That's a terrible taste, but okay.
No, it's good shit.
No, it's good shit, dog.
I've at the grocery store, and I buy orange juice now,
that I do not also buy a carton of grapefruit juice to make this exact concoction,
because it is transcendent.
Bitter is only worse than sour.
No, wait, yeah, sour is only better than the bitter.
Sour and bitter are two worse.
It's just a brainlet take to be like, ooh, some of these quadrants of food are bad,
just across the board.
Certain categories of flavor are just out of the question.
Exactly, they're banned.
Do you not like coffee?
Unless I put a lot of sugar and cream into it.
No, I don't.
Yeah, okay.
I mean same, I also cream and sugar.
Well, I splenda, but same difference.
I also cream and sweeten my shit out of my coffee.
I do like lattes, like caramel.
I've been drinking black milk straight for the last while.
The fuck is black milk?
Did I say I meant black coffee?
Only the blackest of milk for me.
That would definitely scare me to see my milk turn black.
Hey, speaking, we started this discussion with apple juice.
Do you guys ever confuse apple juice with piss,
as is discussed famously in Homestuck?
No.
Unless someone in your house pisses in cartons or bottles.
Well, of course, I've told you that in college,
I discovered that my roommate was storing piss bottles
in the bottom of the trash can.
There was a period of my life where,
due to stressful living conditions,
I did pee in bottles so as to not leave my room
to go to the bathroom because I would have to see
the people I lived with.
And after the cabin fever started to set in,
it was looking pretty delicious.
What, mage?
You guys and your milk proved being able to pee in bottles.
I don't, that's true.
You would just need a funnel, you know?
Just you need additional tools all.
No, I was joking.
Well, I don't condone what I did,
but I don't condone it, but I...
I won't apologize for what I've done.
I feel like I was really...
I was really, it was a rock and a hard place.
I only did it because of the high pressure situation I was in.
It's okay. You were a Hickamore.
You couldn't go outside.
It's not that.
It was that I was under threat of being
evicted from my apartment every single day.
And also, one of the guys I was living with
was this intolerable unmedicated bipolar
who was just...
Every time you saw him, he would...
50% of the time...
There was a 50% chance that he would demand
that you do some things with him,
some completely pointless, time-consuming tasks,
like moving all the furniture from one side of the room
to the other side.
He was like, we gotta do this right now.
Come on.
And he would expect you to help him with it.
And I would just crouch in my room like,
God, I can't...
I can't risk it.
I can't do it.
Not again.
Okay, okay.
Does that have...
Is that related to the whole evicting thing?
Because it doesn't seem like it's your landlord
like cruising around.
No, no, no.
That was not specifically related.
Well, because of the eviction,
the possible eviction,
most people had left the house,
so it was just me, that guy, and one other guy.
Okay.
But no.
No.
Fair enough.
All right.
Well, guys, I'm sure you've heard,
Homestuck 2 was announced.
No.
If it was.
If it was announced.
Homestuck 2.
Okay.
It says on the website, it's official,
and I believe it.
Well, Nate, thank you.
I think I do see that.
Here's my question.
Do you give a shit?
Absolutely not.
All right, cool.
It's all there is to say.
I never really got into Homestuck,
so no, don't care.
I'm simply curious.
I'd be curious to see if anyone disagrees
with me in the comments.
I read all Homestuck, you know,
was on the arm retrieval.
Good times, good times.
The epilogue came out.
Tried to read it.
Really tried.
It just felt to me like they were trying to...
It was like they deliberately didn't write
the full ending to Homestuck in Homestuck,
and now they're adding it back.
Like there are pieces just left out,
presumably to be filled in later,
as like this continuation or whatever.
I never mustered the energy to read the epilogue.
Do you just remember, just quickly,
there was that whole thing about like,
the Homestuck, the Fort Quadrant,
like the secret weapon that was used
against Cal at the very end.
We didn't really understand what it was
or how exactly it was found
or what the purpose of it was.
These things are somewhat explained in the epilogue.
I got to the point where at least that
made some sense, but then it just kept going
and I got completely bored, didn't finish it.
There was so much fucking text.
I don't have time for this shit.
I presume that it ended,
and I'm just flummoxed that there's Homestuck too.
I'm drinking a fucking blue Raz Rockstar X-Durance.
You know it's not even by Homestuck too.
I don't understand.
I'm just absolutely boggled that it's...
Wait, what?
I saw page one, it's got Dirk.
He's like a space pirate now.
Hussie is like the creative director of it.
Or this is what I heard.
It's like he doesn't...
He's like the Lauren Faust of it?
Yes.
You know, Lauren Faust had to approve every script.
She had to approve everything,
even if she didn't write every episode herself.
You know, I was happy to hear
what was that last episode,
that Hussie is engaging himself creatively
with his interesting fashion line
and is being a male Instagram model and whatnot.
It's not a fashion line.
He just dresses very cool and takes selfies.
That's totally sick,
and I totally support it.
It's kind of sick, yeah.
But frankly, compared to Homestuck too...
I don't give a shit about Homestuck too.
That is the most interesting creative thing
Hussie's done in a long time for me.
Yeah, I'm genuinely more interested
in Hussie being funny on Instagram
than I am in Homestuck too.
Although, didn't he help work on
Drill or Wint on Twitter?
He helped work on the book
that he made, that Gib bought.
I meant to buy as well.
Did Hussie help work on the sweet bro and hella Jeff book?
Yeah, he did.
Oh, I forgot it was a sweet bro and hella Jeff.
Whatever, you don't know what I'm saying.
Yeah, that's fine.
I haven't read it,
but if I ever got the chance,
I would thumb through it.
I've told you guys before
that my first ever exposure
before you told me about Homestuck was
just reading the sweet bro and hella Jeff comics
that we found online.
I should have stopped right there.
I had heard of sweet bro and hella Jeff
way before I ever heard of Homestuck.
Amazing.
Or at least I remember
reading Homestuck
they make reference
to sweet bro and hella Jeff and I'm like
wait, sweet bro and hella Jeff,
I've heard of that and then I go and find it
and I'm like, oh, sweet bro and hella Jeff
that's a Homestuck thing?
Like what?
I only knew about them as some sort of meme.
I still don't know their context.
I just know they exist and they're funny.
You should go to sweetbroandhellajeff.com
right fucking now.
But maybe I shouldn't.
They're fucking good.
They're legendary.
They taper off as they go.
Okay, they kinda taper off.
But the first half of it is fucking great.
I mean, they're legendary, they're great memes.
That's all there is to it.
Heavily inspirational to Gib.
Well, okay, he's not in this episode, but he's not.
Well, yeah.
Heavily inspirational to our country.
You're not wrong.
I had to quote Hussie, build that wall.
He really took his shit advice.
All right, there you go. Homestuck 2 done.
It's in the dirt.
Nothing else need to be said about that.
I opened up homestuck2.com or whatever
and I saw like, oh, Dirk on a spaceship
and I said, okay, and I hit that X
and I never looked back.
That's the way to do it.
If anyone has read it and it's good, just let me know.
I'd be shocked.
I'm very curious.
I wanna talk about an anime.
A single anime.
You have to listen.
Strap self into torture chamber.
I guess there's no law against it,
so I can't stop you.
It's called Ascendus of a Bookworm
and it's honestly one of the most pleasing
enemies of the season.
Or just like this year for me.
For me personally, it scratches
a certain itch.
It's like, I'm guessing you guys
at least watch Doctor Stone or Heard of It, right?
Of course.
I've read the first chapter of it.
He uses power of knowledge
to bring
science stuff
to the stone age,
so to speak, of the future.
Well, Ascendus of a Bookworm is sort of
a bit of an eseper. The stone age of the future.
I'm slightly confused, but okay.
That would be like a post...
What's the word? Post-apocalyptic.
What's the word that Preston Jacobs
uses to describe a period
of history wherein a society has regressed
from an advanced civilization to like a pre-space
or a per...
Oh, darn it!
Post-apocalyptic.
15 minutes from now, I'm going to shout out the word.
Okay, alright.
But yeah, Ascendus of a Bookworm is
a bit of an isekai, so like a girl
she...
Interregnum!
Interregnum.
That wasn't 15 minutes, but...
A period of time
after a society has achieved
spaceflight wherein they
lose it and enter a sort of like
intermediate dark age before we're
gaining it again. Does that happen specifically
spaceflight?
Well, I think maybe
in the context, George R.R. Martin used it,
whatever.
Ascendus of a Bookworm. Yes, like on Topic People.
I'm interrupting.
So, a girl dies and she gets
sort of reincarnated into a body
of like a five-year-old child
that actually just passed away
and she gets to inhabit her body
instead. It's really sad
and messed up when you think about it,
but they don't think about it and maybe
they don't address it.
But yeah, so she gets reincarnated
and she's like
all she wants to do is read a
book. She wants to read books,
but she lives
in a peasant household.
None of them can read or write
except for the father just barely.
He's a town guardsman, so he kind of has to.
But like no one knows what a book is.
So, her whole struggle
is her trying to find
or make a book
to read. Her comps, if you will.
Her struggle.
Fine.
Is to find and read a book or to
make a book herself if
their family cannot afford a book. Yeah, and she'll call it
and she'll call it my struggle
and she'll title it in her native German.
That's what I'm saying. No.
Continue. Can't fix that by the way, Ben.
Not struggle.
Wait, what?
I'm not sure, but I'm pretty sure
Kampf is battle, not struggle.
I've heard people say
that it means my struggle.
I could be wrong. It's been
like two decades since I had
German class.
Two decades, I'd say. A decade.
I'm not that old.
Anyway, what's really
satisfying for me is you get to see
how much she
works towards such a simple
goal and like all the little
victories she has are just so satisfying
and she has so many
troubles doing it and she fails
along the way, but also she brings a little
bit of knowledge from her own world
into this
medieval sort of stylish word like
medieval styled world
like she sort of
like invents shampoo in
that world because she needs to be able to
shampoo. Yeah, she creates shampoo
like a very basic sort of shampoo.
She had seen fight clubs and she knows how to make soap
I assume. No, not so.
Does she like make a lie out of ashes?
Uh,
No? Or explain.
Can you tell me how does she make shampoo?
I'm genuinely curious. Now, if I remember
correctly, like she used some
oils from a fruit
and then she added some
What was it? What's it called?
Not vegetables, not mint.
What's that called?
Uh, it's like some grass things.
Some bullshit in there.
Shut up.
I forgot the name. I forgot the word.
Herbs, there we go. Some herbs into that oil.
Okay. Herbs and oils
are not what shampoo is made of.
Well, she's unacceptable.
No, it's some sort of like basic type
of shampoo she used to make with her mother
back in her own world.
And it worked
fine enough in a world where there's absolutely
no shampoo.
Is this as detailed as like Dr. Stone
which is seemingly pretty scientifically accurate?
I think so.
You should play Dwarf Fortress
where you have to have your dwarves
make their own shampoo.
You have to like burn wood
to make charcoal and then soak the charcoal
to make lye and then process the lye
into bars of soap and then mix
and then put it in a waterfall
and wash your dwarves. That sounds so boring, Ben.
How could that possibly be fun?
Yeah. You say it's boring
but then you build your communal
showers and then like
50 dwarves a year end up like
getting sucked down the drains and dying in the
cisterns beneath. Choked with
dwarf bodies of women and children
like legendary swords and axes
and pieces of armor down there just waiting
for some enterprising individual. You call
that boring, huh? It's just hard for me to understand
how this could not be boring.
The fucking death bath house.
Okay, but back to the anime.
It is similar to Dr. Stone
in the fact that like, you know,
she explains all these things
and how she's making it and stuff.
But Dr. Stone has a lot of energy
and lots of
extreme facial expressions and stuff like that
and with this one it's
a lot more like slow
and tone down but it's also
like cute and it's still interested.
I'm surprised how interested I am.
I'm just loving the crap out of this anime
and I just want to see more. It's just
as much as that I didn't know I had
and it's great. I love it.
Fair enough. So I recommend people
to watch it. Okay.
I think I can understand the appeal.
It's like with most isekais
it's usually a power fantasy.
You sort of like you solve all your
problems with magic.
You're a super powered guy. You're the
only one. You're the chosen one.
You're the god of this universe. But with this
she's a five almost six
year old girl and she's so weak
physically that she can't even walk to
the edge of the
town. To the shitter. So she's constantly
shitting herself. No.
Acceptable.
It takes three months
of her to build up
her stamina just so she can
reach the edge of town.
That's how weak she is.
With that frail body
and her getting constantly
like fevers and stuff.
She's working towards
accomplishing her goal of just making a
book. So what is her goal?
To make a book.
Yes.
Why doesn't she just make a book?
It's hard. What's
standing in her way?
She has no access to
paper.
She starts off not knowing
the language of the land. She has to
learn to read and write and stuff.
Wait.
She has to
learn to read and write the language.
Then she has to get
trees and process them into paper on her
own. Probably
skin a cow and tan the
leather to make the binding or something.
I just may be at some point
but no. She tried to make papyrus
which didn't work. Then she tried to do
clay tablets which is
the last art we just did.
I appreciate
how ridiculously specific this premise is.
You said she was a...
If she liked books at all, she must
have been able to read in her original world.
She already
can speak that language and obviously
she didn't have to learn how to speak.
Is there some isekai thing
where she speaks the same language
she used to speak? Maybe
this world is different.
If I remember correctly, I think
when she first got isekai, she didn't understand.
I'm not too certain because I watch
so many enemies. I'm like how it's a verb
to get isekai'd.
It's a thing.
It's a thing now sadly.
My favorite thing about isekai's
my absolute number one favorite thing
is all these stories about
how you put
an average neat loser
with no skills, no abilities
into a world and they don't get anything.
I particularly like the power fantasy
of these gamer
skills I had as a worthless piece
or should gamer who achieved nothing in my life
I can now pretend, I like the fantasy
of pretending that those skills might have
some use in some other world
even though we all know they never would
and they never will. It's embarrassing
when they try. With her, she used to read a lot
of books so she's applying the knowledge from
the books. Well, that's fine. That's not
what I'm talking about. That's a-okay.
The only good isekai
that has ever been written
and ever will be written
is slime and punishment.
The story of phantom horn being
sent from his cozy, boring
existence in the real world
of Ponyville into the
fantastical wonderland that is
New Los Angeles City.
I'm not surprised. The greatest
isekai ever made
currently in its fifth season.
Six seasons in a movie, baby.
They just had a curiosity.
It seems like you're plugging
along towards the end. Is that close to ending now?
Are you getting close to the end? Well,
the main
story that I set out to write
is over. I did successfully
tell the story of their- But it's time
for slime and punishment, too, baby!
It's time to cash in! It's basically
time to go from the
story I set out to tell, and now I have
now- I mean, because Chris made
some- Oh! You know what I have
here? And this ties into what I'm talking
about. Uh, fuck. Where are they?
Where are they? Where are they? Where do I put them?
Uh...
Damn! Wait. No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Okay, well, I can't find them. Whatever.
The point is, Chris sent me
her, um,
custom-made cards
for Twilight Sparkle's secret
shipfic folder.
Uh, when they have- She sent me
the Arizona Slime
expansion pack. Did you
have to give Chris your address in order to achieve
this? Yes. Oh, okay.
Whatever. Chris is not protective of
personal information. Who gives a shit?
Fair enough. Fair enough. What's she gonna do?
Well, I just mean she might leak it
because she's a bit of a dunce at these things.
Yeah, because you're s- Why- Why?
Why would she do that? Well, I'm not saying
intentionally, but she's so flipping with
her own personal information. That's true.
Okay, whatever. Doesn't matter. Not important.
It's totally unimportant.
Frankly, I'm a fender that you even brought it up.
Indeed you are. Um, anyway,
uh, yeah, I fucking-
I'm holding them- I was holding them in my
hands. Um, I don't know why-
where- I- they- I-
Okay, I'm just gonna stop freaking out.
Oh, I used them as toilet paper because I was
running out. Oh, darn. Aw, shit.
Aw, not again.
Second time this week.
Uh, where the fuck would
they be? Where the fuck would they be?
Look, I'm with you, but do you need them
to make your current point, uh, at this jun-
I was gonna read off some of the text on them because they're really funny.
Oh, yeah. Okay. There's one- Okay.
She posted, like, screencaps of
all of them, uh, on Twitter,
but there's one in there
that is not that she never posted,
and I think it was, like, meant to be a secret.
Or maybe, I don't know. But it seems
like it's, like, directly addressed
to me. And it's basically Chris
Chance on it, too, wagging her fucking finger
out of the card, directly at the viewer,
being, like, be nice
to your OCs. Don't fuck
with your OCs. It's cruel
to be- to write bad things happening
to your OCs. Um, what- Chris wrote murder of his
OCs. They were horribly- Chris literally murdered
70,000 people in
New Los Angeles City. Oh, shit.
But those were the OCs, so it's okay.
Literal genocide.
Uh, hey, we can pause for a moment.
You can go look if you want. We can just cut that out.
Do you want to?
Well, oh, I see him.
Hey, alright, there you go. See?
Although, I mean, to be honest, I feel like I've already
explained everything I needed
to about him. Um, well,
yeah, do you want to just get the exact text
of that? I'm curious to hear it.
I want to hear it in Chris' own words. Sure.
Uh, where is it? Where is it? There's Chris Hold- Chris
Chance Ones, you're holding the Slime Podron,
uh, the- the
bicarbonate rain. Here we go. You got to give us
some pictures of this for the show notes, please.
Sure. The- the card is called,
and this is blasphemy,
uh, an endless war-free state.
So just like all the politicians of our
day, they're all calling for an end to endless war.
Bastards. Have they no shame?
Uh, so this is a goal card.
Do you- do you guys have any idea
how Twilight Sparkle's secret chip folder works,
by the way, because I don't? No. No, none.
This is- it's- well, I'll- I'll talk about it in a second.
I saw that there was a Magic the Gathering
crossover with MLP the other day. Now that,
I understand. Wait, like an official one?
Yeah, like actual magic cards
with like rarity the rare.
She's like a 2-2 monster unicorn
legendary. No, come on.
Celestia or something. Yeah. Yeah.
No. That's just real.
You're lying. I'll find a picture.
Stop lying to me. I'll find it.
All right. Well, um,
oh my god, IGN Magic the Gathering
reveals my little pony crossover set.
This is vile. This is truly vile.
There you go. All right, goal card.
An endless war-free state.
Win this goal when
at least three pony cards
who have been given the villain keyword
by card effects are either cleared
of the villain keyword or discarded
in the same turn.
Uh, and then there's a
parentheses 13,
and I don't know where the 13 comes in.
Quote,
and so the slime co-dilemma
and the endless war came to a close
in Dimension C197
on October 3rd,
2019.
When the moral being even the heavi-
No, sorry. The moral being
even the heaviest of hatred can be quelled
when we come together towards a common goal.
Also,
your OCs should be treated with kindness and respect.
Do not abuse them
or each other.
It's on a chew.
So, I got these in the mail
and I thought, damn,
this makes me want to get the game
and like play the game with these
cards in it.
Sure.
I don't know. I think Twilight Sparkle's secret ship
of photos seems like a kind of funny game,
I guess. I wasn't that interested.
But with these, maybe I'm a little interested.
But I went to go buy it
and it turns out you can't.
Literally,
the company is just out of business.
But you can kind of do it
and like the way that
okay, you can still get the game
but
you have to do it in the same way that Chris
made these cards which is if you go
to the Twilight Sparkle
official site
they'll be like, hey guys, we're out of business
but you can still
make the game the same way we did and they just redirect
you to like a custom card printing
site and they're like, here's the files
just give them the files
and like you can like have them make your own
set.
That's pretty cool, I guess. It's kind of cool.
It's kind of weird.
Don't you think that's fucking weird? I think it's bizarre.
It seems like they're like, even though our game
is technically dead, like we still
and we can't sustain it anymore. We just want people
to be able to keep playing if they really want to.
So here you go, folks. Here's the fucking
Yeah, I mean, I guess so.
Personally, I don't understand why they would
like do that.
Like, why declare yourself
generous.
Yeah, but why declare yourself out of business
when you could just be like, every time
you tell someone go make it yourself
you could just take
an order for it and do it for them
and like probably make a profit off of it.
Maybe they are planning
a resurgence one day. They had, like everyone
was busy. They had to go make their bread
elsewhere but they're hoping to come back
one day and they want to just seed the
world with as many of these as possible in
the meantime to spark
interest. I don't know.
I guess. Yeah, I mean,
maybe. I don't know. It's
weird. But
alright, I just want to say
that, okay, these
cards explain
these cards explain that
the bicarbonate
rainstorm did de-slime New
Los Angeles City
and put an end to the Endless War
and that is true, however
only in the alpha
timeline and there are
beta timelines. They are doomed beta timelines
like in Homestuck but they do
exist and they shouldn't be
written off as irrelevant.
Well, geez, you're really seeding
a lot of ground here. What makes this timeline
the alpha timeline? What's to say that one isn't
doomed? Why is that one so
legit? What are you talking
about? The alpha timeline is
the alpha timeline and the others are offshoot beta timelines
and beta timelines die.
But how can you determine
between a beta and an alpha timeline
at any given time?
I don't know.
Noby's got all kinds of freaky
dimension eyes and he can see weird shit
and he knows these things. I don't know.
Look, I don't know. I can see
into C197. I'm just reporting
what's going on there, okay? I'm not
the scientist, right?
I'm not the expert. I only report.
Well, you know,
on this subject, there was one other thing
that we wanted to discuss last week or that
I was going to bring up. We just forgot
or whatever. And it was that like, or rather
I was going to bring up more. I think we talked
about it a little bit. It was that when you
finished your Kickstarter, you got your
Yang 12K
yearly earnings. Yeah, 12K got my UBI.
My own personal UBI.
Upon seeing that, Chris just wanted
that money despite it being
specifically for a business venture
and it's just this
perception of Ben now has
that money. He could give that money
to me now. To be fair,
he could do that. He could. To be fair,
neither Chris nor MagiChan
has
mentioned that to me in a while now.
So they might have dropped it. I'm not
sure. Although
who knows? Like, they could come back
at me at any time.
It was mostly MagiChan.
They were
absolutely good cop, bad cop in me.
MagiChan was like the hard
ass, like, you better
pay what you owe criminal
scum. And Chris
acted as though that wasn't happening.
I can't hold him back that long, Ben.
Yeah, like, hey, listen,
I'm not responsible for anything my partner
does, okay?
And if you
really make him mad, he'll get Mewtwo on
your ass and you definitely don't want that.
That's gonna be way worse for you.
You think MagiChan's mean?
He learned everything he knows about
being mean from Mewtwo, okay?
True.
So, um, hopefully we don't have to
take it to that level.
I think there's something to be learned
about the nature of man in this little
exchange here. When money is there,
it just, everybody just wants it.
If you want to want it.
Yeah, well, um, too bad.
Suckers.
Yeah, go make your own Kickstarter, folks.
I guess that's all there is to it.
Oh, um, actually, MagiChan
asked me, it's funny,
he asked me like, he said
like, hey, you know,
you don't have to pay me that 300 bucks
if you will make a Kickstarter
for my,
did I already talk about this?
I think you mentioned it, I believe it.
If you make a Kickstarter with a goal of
$5,000, I'll waive that
$300 you quote-unquote owe me
if you run my campaign for me.
That's very silly.
I did not listen last week's episode.
Why are you quote-unquote
owing money to them?
I mean,
good question.
That's a great question.
Okay, it's a little unclear
of whether the reason is
because I
used Chris's
characters in the story
because I
used the comic
to attract attention
while running a Kickstarter
which made money,
maybe?
Or...
But the comic has nothing to do
with the Kickstarter, right?
True, well observed.
Or the other possible reason might be
because Chris used my characters
on her cards
and therefore I ought to pay
to have them made.
These are like three different reasons
that are sort of kind of interchangeably given.
The last one sounds like Chris should
be paying you
to use that.
So the Kickstarter had nothing
to do with the comic in which
you used Chris's...
Technically, the slime-oid stuff at the end
was related, I suppose.
Yeah, I mean...
I'm still angry
with you about that.
With me?
Well, it's okay because Tom and Hippo
both saved it.
Okay, good.
I haven't been on Twitter in a while, so...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, it was great.
I'm so glad.
I don't regret anything because it worked out so good.
Yeah, Hippo drew Red Man
saving it at the last minute.
And then Tom made a full 3D animation
of Izumi saving it at the last minute.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, we gotta go look at it.
We talked about extensive the last time.
Yeah, we won't dwell on it because we talked about it last time,
but you should check it out. They're both really good.
I don't know if these are two separate timelines.
I kind of wonder if maybe...
because the Izumi thing happened,
I kind of wonder if maybe
they didn't just happen in order.
Like, maybe Izumi
saved it from the pit.
And then, because Hippo then drew
a page of N7
showing up to fight Izumi.
So I wonder if maybe just in the battle,
like,
Uwupadi just accidentally fell back
into the vet anyway.
Like, the two of them were too busy fighting,
so it took Red Man to come in.
Where did I go wrong?
I've hit walk bottom.
And maybe then just Red Man came in
and scooped it out. I don't know.
My hypothesis is that these are both the same timeline.
You keep seem to be implying
that that was Red Man who saved him.
That wasn't Red Man. That was Suzy,
the slime girl O.C. of Gib.
Was it?
Yeah, go look at it again.
It's clearly like a girl. It's not Red Man.
At least, I think.
You know, we talked about this too much last time.
Hold on, hold on. Now, this is interesting.
Because
it was a little pinkish, wasn't it?
Yes, of course.
Wait a minute. Okay.
Okay.
I gots to make sure.
Okay, cut all this out.
Cut all this out. Just all of it.
It's all bullshit. It's all bullshit.
All of the podcasts, like making 0 minutes,
0 seconds.
Alright.
See what I'm saying? Look at those hands.
Those pink hands.
Okay. You know?
You got a point?
I don't know.
Look at the top of its head.
It looks like a smooth circle to me.
I mean, that could just be a curve
at the top of Suzy's
like, I think her name is Suzy.
That could be fucking wrong.
Her hair, head thing.
No, okay.
Right, though. Well, Red Man was wearing a suit.
But still, still, I believe.
Yeah, I assumed it was Red Noir
suit
version, Red Man.
I see what you mean.
Like, the one thing that I think is
supports the Suzy hypothesis
is the color.
Because it does seem a little pinker
than I'm used to seeing Red Man.
But the top of the head
to me looks like Red Man's head.
Please edit it.
Look at the top of his head.
I mean, in this moment.
What is that?
Oh, you wouldn't know, Ben.
I don't, so I guess you're right.
Okay, well, viewers,
let us know in the comments
what do you think. Do you support
the Suzy hypothesis or the Red Man hypothesis?
I need, like, a list
of Hippo's characters
and just, like, put them
next to that. Either way,
Hippo has made, like, big, like,
collection images, like, all his male characters
and all his female characters.
Either way, I still support the unrelated
hypothesis that both Rescue,
both Tom's Rescue and Hippo's Rescue
took place in the same timeline,
just one immediately after the other.
Um, but...
There are now two slimes instead of one.
But I can't prove it.
Well, because Chris said that if
Uwupati survived, it would be bad
for everyone. So I'm thinking that the one
in which Uwupati survived is the Beta timeline,
which the comic is now taking place in,
which has a frame and Nobi
are discussing the timelines, and they have
to come up with a plan to get back to the Alpha timeline
before the universe dissolves, right?
Because in the Alpha timeline,
all the slime was destroyed.
So they got to get back to the Alpha timeline,
but they got to do something about the slimes
because they don't want to go back and live in the Alpha timeline
if there's no slime. They got to find a way to bring
the slime with them. That's the plan.
What was this pink OC?
Huh?
What? What? What?
Look at the gross disgusting. Another show notes.
Oh, yeah, that's some...
Let's not go down this rabbit hole. Look at this image.
Now look at this image. Very cool image.
I'm not going down any rabbit hole.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I've never gone down a rabbit hole in my entire life.
Hey, Zenhuxible says he wants to join.
You want to just hop over to the other chat
and let him in?
Okay. I'm scared.
The answer is yes. Okay, hang on.
I've never been on the same podcast as a guest
as well, so I don't know. I'm scared.
Whatever?
I always purposely miss those episodes
so that the guest can have room to...
Purposely?
Well, we're low on people anyway, so...
I'm sick of you losers.
Let's get some fresh blood in here.
Done. How's it going, dog?
What's up? Hello.
I've been in a particularly
weird situation lately because
I work on weekends, right?
I'm in college right now. I'm in my senior year
working on my animation thesis.
It's been a lot of fun,
but the other problem is
I just haven't been having a lot of time
working on it because I've
been working on the weekends.
So I have two days free to work on it
and then I have class the other three days.
So what I'm thinking, because I've saved
a lot of money up because I also do commissions
and whatnot, so I'm thinking I'm just going to quit the job
because I want to...
This is what I'm going to be presenting to
my employers when I leave college.
So I want it to be the best thing
that showcases what I can do as an animator.
So I want to make the best product that I can.
I've got to leave the job.
I've got to come right back.
Fair enough.
This isn't really a dilemma that's in my mind.
It's just like, I'm explaining
where I am mentally right now.
I was actually supposed to go into work today
and I was like, you know what? No.
I'm not going to do that.
So did you just quit or something just now?
Yeah, I just quit.
All right, man. Deb.
Deb.
Truly we live in a post job society.
I have other money making
sources of commissions.
Exactly.
It's not like no liquid is coming in,
but you know,
that floor is coming under me.
Speaking of liquid,
are we hanging out on Halloween?
Oh, absolutely.
Nice.
It sounds like fun.
I saw Munchie and I was like, hey.
Maybe move to the real world for once in your life, Mage.
They tell me.
Munchie and Kazzy tell me
they've seen you once or twice around
and I'm like, damn.
I can't believe all these,
all my separate cinematic universes
are converging into one.
It's a really weird thing because the thing is,
I'm a real homebody.
So when I'm not at school,
I'm just animating.
Or watching Bojack Horseman,
which is what I was doing before I came in here.
Yeah,
the newest season came out yesterday.
Just in case you wanted to be extra set.
Right, exactly.
No, the new season came out yesterday.
I don't think
I ever was up to...
I think I watched the first season.
It was good though.
I think I watched four seasons.
Okay, so I missed one season
and I'm missing this one.
No, I just
I binge all my shows.
If you do the same.
Release the whole episode.
I did something a little shameful.
We were talking about
Twin Perfect last week.
Indeed.
They put out that four hour video about Twin Peace.
Oh my god, I forgot about that.
You gotta mention that.
I don't know if I'm even apologizing.
I feel like this is bad,
but I don't think I want to apologize for it.
I haven't seen the new Twin Peaks.
I watched the video.
I don't care that it spoiled everything.
Oh my god, this is a four hour video?
It's four and a half hours.
This is incredibly fortuitous.
Last episode I was bitching and fetching about
Where's Twin Perfect?
I brought up Twin Perfect.
Did you?
I think I brought up the song
for some reason.
I don't know, whatever.
It doesn't matter who brought it up.
I believe you, Ben.
I expressed some sentiment.
Where's Twin Perfect?
It's been so long.
It had been over a year since their last video.
They just released it.
I was like, what are they doing?
They're probably fucking around.
The biggest fucking video I've ever seen since that one.
Were we talking about cancel culture?
Or I think I wanted to talk about that thing
with Tom.
Tom Hewlett and the whole blaming him.
I'm sorry.
I'm still hung up on how you said Kovetching.
Is that like Northern European slang or something?
It's like Jewish.
I think that's Yiddish or something.
I probably got that from Seinfeld in my youth.
This is my estimation.
I've been watching some hot YouTube one piece.
I don't know why I said one piece.
Seinfeld's Kovetching.
It's basically the Seinfeld of Japan.
I don't know why I said one piece.
Two and one piece.
True.
Lucy, stop eating all the meat.
Sanji, fuck you.
I just want to sleep in lift weights.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Stop just getting upset.
Okay, so Twin Perfect.
The biggest video I've ever seen in my fucking life.
It's so huge.
Ben watched it. Cool.
I recently watched Twin Peaks Season 1 and 2.
I was like, okay.
I did a big glowing tweet of this.
I can't believe these guys proved me so fucking stupid and wrong.
I got to go watch the new season
before I watch their video,
which I'm dying to do.
I got to Episode 6,
and it took too much brain power.
So I had to slow down and relax.
Here's the thing.
I didn't watch the new season.
A couple of years ago,
I did watch Twin Peaks, the original.
I liked it.
It was cool.
I'm a big fan.
You know, I know the new season's out.
I hadn't seen it.
I don't know when or if I was going to make time to see it.
But I did see the Twin Perfect
review or analysis was out.
And I was like, I really want to see that.
I want to see that more than I care.
More than I want to see the new season.
So I'm just going to watch it.
And you know what?
I really don't.
I guess I'm just one of these people that spoilers don't matter.
I don't feel like I'll get less out of it
if I ever do decide to watch the new Twin Peaks.
That weighed on me.
That particular question
weighed on me heavily.
The funny thing is,
I got into Twin Perfect from the start.
They're some of my favorite YouTubers with their shit.
The real Silent Hill experience, whatever.
I got into Silent Hill.
You showed them to me a long time ago.
Yeah, exactly.
Their videos were the exhaustive,
incredibly in-depth reviews
of every detail of every Silent Hill game.
Yeah, it spoiled everything.
But you know what I did then?
I went and I played the games and I fucking love them.
I don't give a shit about Silent Hill.
I have no desire to ever play a Silent Hill game.
But I love those Silent Hill reviews.
They are good.
So was this a good video?
Did you enjoy it?
Yes, I did.
It is very much...
Twin Perfect have this mindset.
Twin Perfect really believe
that they can solve media.
They can find the hidden,
the meaning of it.
Which is very annoying and objectively wrong.
But it's still a funny exercise
to watch some of the...
That is their approach, though.
It is a fun exercise to watch them go through.
And they make pretty good...
Not fungo,
he lays out a pretty compelling case
for his interpretation
of what it all means.
It's good stuff, man.
That is a funny approach.
I don't think I would ever...
I suppose if someone
proposes to me an interpretation of a show
I really like for some reason,
and I find their view of it to be
dumb,
then I could say that that's dumb
because I really...
It depends.
What if they are picking up a small detail
that is there,
as opposed to
getting something wrong
that's clearly wrong.
Those are two very different ways
to view any piece of media.
One, you can counteract.
The other is...
I feel like
it's dumb to say
that this...
No matter how compelling
your reading of a story is,
I think that the one that Rossiter lays out
in the Twin Peaks
video is pretty compelling,
but no matter how good it is,
I think it's really stupid to be like,
okay, this is the right one.
I feel sort of implicit in the way
he lays it out is this idea that
we found the right one,
there is no other one.
That does seem to be the difference.
Come on.
It's funny.
He's got a bit of an ego which I like
and appreciate.
It's not about ego, I just think his critical approach
is very frustrating.
All his videos, they're all like
you're wrong about Man of Steel,
you're wrong about
Justice League or whatever the fuck it is.
I don't mind the ego or the attitude,
but
I just like to be right and I respect
people who are correct.
You know what I mean?
Indeed, I do. By the way,
I got into a little bit on the point
of watching it first or whatever.
When I put out my glowing tweet about
I was just shit talking to these boys.
I was proved so, so foolish.
I am ashamed as a content creator.
Wait, who are you talking shit about?
These people produce actual works of quality.
Who are you talking about?
On the last PCP episode,
I was saying, where is Twin Perfect?
What have they been doing, man?
And then they immediately
afterward come out with this.
I hadn't watched the video,
but I know the effort that Twin Perfect,
that Rossiter puts into these videos.
I felt assured this would not be
any... It's not as produced as
the Silent Hill ones,
but like... Really? Okay.
I mean, it doesn't have any songs
in it or anything like that.
Those were highlights.
Well, okay, fair enough.
But just the little editing they do.
For everyone who thinks that me and Major
are contributing a little too much in this podcast,
I'm sorry.
Apologize.
I gotta know my place here.
Yeah.
I would contribute, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
I haven't seen Twin Peaks or anything,
so I have nothing to say on this topic.
Fair enough.
Some of the shit from the footage
of the new season seems pretty fucking weird.
Let me see.
It's hard to describe in any kind of detail
the shit you see,
but it's just...
It really is me sitting there
on screen and I'm like,
what did he mean by this?
What did he mean by this?
Yeah, I guess.
It does feel, at this particular moment,
six episodes into this 18 episode
Season 3.
It feels too deep for me,
but I'm gonna work my way back.
Wait, was there a reboot of Twin Peaks?
Not a reboot, they just made a new season
that takes place like 25 years in the future.
You kidding?
Yeah, it's just straight up the same story.
I've heard nothing about this.
Like last year, or I think?
I don't know.
I gotta say, it was 2017, I think,
but the biggest thing that makes me sad
is they were not able to get,
because he retired from acting,
the original sheriff from the old two.
Him and Coop were buddies,
they were a team,
and what they have now is
they've got an actor who's playing his brother
also aged up,
and that character is in rehab
or he's off doing something else.
I don't know, it's unfortunate.
I miss that guy, but he's a retired actor.
But they got the log lady,
they got Coop, obviously,
they got the giant who I
suspected would be dead by this point,
but thank god he's not.
He looks like the kind of guy
who's got some kind of congenital thing
that'll kill him before 40.
Just like Tom, just like Tom.
Just like Tom.
Rip.
I think Tom was saying
he might have some weird, minor form
of gigantism of some degree
that's why he's got his finest shoe.
He says that because he's tall,
but he's not like freaky tall.
What if his parents were like four feet tall
and Tom is like six, five, whatever.
Although it is true that I think
that height does inversely correlate
with life expectancy,
like to a small degree.
Oh no.
That's why little dogs
live really long and big dogs live not at all.
Yeah, it's something I don't know
what it is, but like,
yeah, you're fucked.
Manlet master race
rise up.
Yeah, you fucking
manlets are going to have a real hard time
rise enough if you know what I mean.
I've been seeing like this weird
I don't know like how big of a phenomenon
it is. It might not even be a phenomenon,
just like business practices, but like
people who make quote unquote like high media
doing like low media stuff like
Francis Ford Coppola
he was like, you know,
shitting on the Marvel Cinematic Universe, whatever.
I could not give less of a shit about that.
But like people were like, dude, you directed
Jack, like that movie with
Robin Williams. That was like a fucking
joke. And I was like, huh.
Oh yeah. I wonder who else is like that.
And David Lynch, he was actually a voice
actor in the Cleveland show by South
McFarland.
That doesn't surprise me
too much. I feel like he does that kind
of thing. He'll just like show up on
somebody's fucking show or whatever.
Right. It's like a funny little guest
appearance. Twin Peaks can be
very non pretentious at times.
It's very like silly. Okay, but like this is the
guy who made Eraserhead, you know.
I've actually never seen Eraserhead, but
yeah, it's pretty good.
Eraserhead, I know, is from
in academia.
My favorite piece of
my favorite David Lynch piece of
media is
David Lynch cooks quinoa.
Oh yeah. Is that a thing?
Yeah, it's a
oh god, I think it's like 20
minutes or something, but it's like
some guy just goes to David Lynch's
house and films him in his kitchen
and David Lynch cooks
himself dinner and he cooks
some quinoa and broccoli and he tells
him his recipe. Okay. And then he goes
out on the porch and smokes a cigarette
and while he's smoking, he like
tells a little story about
like riding the train through Eastern
Europe and like buying some
weird soda.
Eastern Europe.
And then he like
you go slobby or something and then he
like goes back to finish his quinoa
and like that's it.
But it's really funny because like
the video, it's like it's edited
to be in black, like it's in black and
white. I've got it right here.
Very dramatic lighting and like
he'll make like a little hand gesture
and whoever edited it will add in like
a super dramatic sound effect like boom
like to go along with the story.
It's wicked fucking good.
It's a really good video. Is this
available on YouTube or something?
Yeah, it's in the chat there.
Beautiful. Yeah, I was right.
I think I tried to find this before but I couldn't
but I'm gonna go watch it because
I've always wanted to. Talked about it before.
That's the weirdest. I like that.
And which chat did you link?
It's in general. It's gross disgusting and also
in the general chat in our cinematic universe one.
Okay. That's cute.
Yeah, I like when like these
creatives make like appear
into their lives, you know.
Of course.
There was that like
Miyazaki like workflow documentary.
You remember that one?
Is that the one workflow documentary?
Is that the one where he says that anime was a mistake?
No, it might have been.
I never watched the whole thing. He actually had a new
documentary come out like last year.
I didn't get to watching it. I don't know why.
I just kept on putting it off.
He said something like that.
That got translated in that way.
I'm not even gonna touch it because like I know
I'm gonna get it wrong and then people are gonna give me shit for it.
But like, yeah, you know,
it's the one where it's like he's just like showing
how he makes ramen and it's not even like spectacular
or anything, but it's like, oh,
that's something I know now.
Hey, by the way, on your
subject of Coppola
and whatnot, talking a little bit of smack
on the Marvel films and whatnot,
I just want to put forward the possibility that
they would probably separate
their works that they've done
of ones that they would consider
cinematic quality or like true
cinema versus like Jack, which maybe
they themselves would say, oh yeah, that was just
some trash I made for money.
So they would inflate the two.
Definitely, yeah, that's definitely the distinction
they'd probably make.
Unless they're fucking loony.
Which they might be.
I don't know, maybe Jack is great though.
I haven't seen it.
Didn't Spielberg direct the North Pole
or the Polar Express or whatever?
That was probably
the Norm of the North.
Yes, with Tom Hanks.
Was that like the animated one
with the varying James 3D X?
Yeah, the weird CG Tom Hanks one.
Wait, that was Polar Express?
I think so. Oh god.
No, I remember that coming
on like ABC, like every
Christmas season.
I don't even remember watching the whole thing.
The Polar Express is a beloved, whatever man,
I'm sure everyone says, but the Polar Express,
beloved children's story, I liked in school,
whatever, it's fine, it's cool, who cares.
But then they add like, when they make the movie,
they have to add like action scenes
of the new, like,
worthless Tom Hanks character.
They gotta add like a subplot
where he wins his father's respect or something.
You gotta movie-ify it.
It can't just be boy goes to the North Pole,
which should be like a 15-minute film or whatever,
which is, but they had to make it
like an hour long, so I guess that's why they pat it out.
It's frankly amazing.
Have you guys seen Dumbo, the movie, the remake?
The new one? No.
I have heard all about it.
I have heard all about it. Why?
It just reminded me of how you said,
you can't just be the story, they have to add shit in.
And that's basically it.
That's my point, but they have to add shit in.
I heard that they don't even have the crows.
Yeah, they don't.
Yeah, they're middle-aged.
I'm sure they'd want to whitewash that way.
Whitewash it, know what I'm saying?
What the fuck?
They have a small girl that wishes to become a scientist.
Nice.
You know, I don't remember Dumbo at all.
Were the crows actually like an important narrative element to the story?
Yeah, they sing the fucking elephant,
I've seen an elephant fly song.
They give him the magic feather that makes him think he can fly.
Now the girl gives him the magic feather.
Terrible.
It's all about the girl now.
These fucking SJWs, man,
sticking girls in our stories about
proud, big-tow elephant boys.
I wouldn't even mind it so much,
but she gets so much attention
for no pay-off.
She's been right from the moment the movie started,
and she goes through no arc or anything.
She's always been right, she always knew what to do.
She's there.
Just like Applejack, I didn't learn anything.
But they also, I don't want to shit on a kid,
but the way she delivered the light,
she was just so bad.
I didn't like her actor.
If you got a bad child actor, it's the director's fault.
And she has a little brother,
and she has a little brother,
and he has even less purpose.
She's at least there to be like the play device, basically,
but the little brother just exists.
Why even have a little brother at that point, honestly?
I hear you loud and clear, Mage.
New thing bad, old thing good.
No, no, no.
I'm just complaining that the little brother doesn't have a brother.
Dude, we have to go back.
We have to make America great again.
Bring back the original Dumbo.
I just didn't like the child, the children.
I feel you.
It seems like perfectly reasonable.
Just talking about this stuff from a more holistic standpoint,
I was actually going to bring up the reason
as to why Disney is remaking all these movies.
And I thought, initially, it was because they...
It's got to be money, right?
I thought, and this is the viewpoint
that a lot of people were bringing up.
They thought that they were doing it to renew the copyright,
so it wouldn't enter public domain.
But apparently, that's not true.
I'm researching it right now,
and apparently, that's not the case.
Doesn't copyright last like 80 billion fucking years now?
No, it's like...
It lasts until the creator is dead,
plus another two centuries or some stupid crap.
It's something like almost 100 years for some.
Great.
Yeah, love it.
So I guess it is just straightforward.
It's just about the money.
Just rehashing these IPs.
Epic.
Like, I don't know, 5, 10 deep into these movies,
they would have stopped if these weren't successful.
Everybody hates them,
but they make so much fucking money.
Because it's Disney? I don't know.
It's just Disney again.
Look, here's the thing.
What I saw of the Lion King,
I hated it so much that, like...
I have not heard anyone say anything good
about the Lion King Remake.
I'm not even going to pirate it,
because I don't want to see any of it.
It looked terrible. Yeah, me neither.
It's like, I don't even...
Why translate it to this medium?
Like, with this weird CG crap
where it's talking like the Lion Turtle
from a fucking Avatar The Last Airbender, you know?
Like, that's how all the characters were talking.
It's like, oh, that just looks so weird in CG.
I heard they brought James Earl Jones back
to play Mufasa again,
but he's got to be old as shit.
He's not going to sound like...
I don't know. You know, whatever.
You never stop sounding like James Earl Jones.
I suppose. But you can sound...
Ooh, it's so sad when, like, they bring back
guys who are, like, they're playing the same character.
They're not supposed to have aged,
but we can see they've aged a lot.
Oh, like Jacques. Like Jacques the bird.
Like Jacques the bird, Ben.
Yes, and John Trun's hit new video.
I have not seen the new video, but I saw you
in Hippo speculating on whether Jacques
is getting old. I haven't seen that one.
This was fascinating. We...
Yes, so John Trun made a new video.
It was whatever, selling his merch.
You know, it's funny.
Just some N.U. John dog shit?
Basically, but the funny thing is
we call it N.U.
This is a fascinating concept, actually.
So, like, for the last many, many years,
at this point, probably most
of John's, like, YouTube career or whatever,
probably the vast majority of it,
John has not used Jacques for anything.
And that's because working with Jacques was, like,
hard and he, you know, whatever.
I get work with animals, especially a bird,
probably challenging and hard. I get that.
Nonetheless, this toy, as, like,
a big feature on the toy,
has Jacques on his shoulder
in the toy that's being sold of John.
So it's, like, I don't know.
I feel some kind of way about
we're remembering
the good old days of, like, the classic stuff
that we love John for the most,
but he doesn't do this anymore. Like, none of his new content
is of this style, despite us, like,
we're paying him
for the toy of how he used to be,
but he doesn't do it anymore. So, like, why would we support?
Like, I don't even dislike his character.
Oh, that seems like the whole
John experience in microcosm.
Like, it's just, I feel like
John today only exists
off of, like, momentum from, like,
classic John that everyone was so excited about.
You know, the weird thing about that, Ben?
And now when you see John, it's like, oh, that kind of
that kind of tickles that part
of my brain that used to get excited about
John back then. That's kind of true.
It sort of looks like him. Yes.
The weird thing is just the weird thing.
The weird thing is just how unbelievably
successful all of John's content is,
despite what I would consider
a pretty serious loss of soul.
They're so popular.
Like, 10 million views
per video, which he does every, like, month or two.
No, people love the spectacle, man.
That's all there is to it, you know?
Like, for some of his jokes,
it's literally just like,
I spent $1,000 on this
prop. Bam! I just destroyed it.
Ha, ha, ha.
I don't think there even is that much spectacle.
I don't know. I don't feel like when a new
John drops, it's like a fucking extravaganza.
It's just, I've only seen
a few of the newer ones, but they just seem
like the same old shit. Like, half of them,
he's literally just sitting on a couch.
You know, honestly, I want to give credit to John.
I don't even really dislike his new videos.
I've watched some of the new ones, and I have enjoyed them
because there's a lot of, like,
he does, like, practical effects.
To quote Mr. Plinkett,
I'd rather see them than blood in my
stool, but...
Well, I, true.
But, like, look, I, I, yeah, I, I love the guy
because, like, he would make video game things
that were really funny. I could, like, relate to it as an epic
game or whatnot. That's fine. That identity
is established for the guy. Now he just
makes pretty much more straightforward,
absurdist comedy or whatever. But he
re, you can really tell.
He is passionate about it, and he works
hard, and he has vision.
Even when I didn't like the videos, like, at all,
and I, we were all like, oh, why is he in this weird
set? Feels a little more natural now.
I, I really do respect
his work ethic and his, like,
dedication to the craft. Like, nobody
is putting as much work or effort
into his videos as John.
So just on that front, I, I am impressed.
You know, you know, it's, it's the funniest thing.
What do you mean he's putting work into them?
I mean, he's getting practical effects.
He's getting actors. He's getting, like,
skits that he's scripting out. He's
going to live action places in the real
world. Wait, did, did, did not think
he's putting work into them.
I don't know. I guess that's not your point, Ben.
It's something else. I've seen a couple, and I,
I wasn't, like, very impressed.
I mean, he's putting work into them, regardless.
Like, maybe the, maybe it's like, maybe
I haven't seen the right ones.
Like, the direction might be misplaced, but, like,
the work is definitely there.
They're, like, he did a video
for, I forget what it is. Let me watch this
jock exposed. Okay, fine.
Well, this one isn't particularly, it's
two minutes long. I want to watch it too.
Um, it's horseshit. Yeah.
One second and then it's horseshit.
Whatever, man.
No, but there's nothing good, nothing good
about this. Okay. In one of the videos, I
forget what it is. Oh, it was the goop
one. It was the one he did for goop. At the
end, he does this whole thing where he goes
into, like, is that recent? Yes, that was
the last, like, couple of months or something. Yeah.
Oh, found it. Okay, goop. Okay, there you go.
Like, skip to the end. He does a thing where
he, they've, like, produced an actual,
excuse me, fucking
a thing. He is literally
being a snake oil salesman.
Funny. That's a funny joke. He's being a snake
oil salesman. They set up in real life
across the street from an actual
practical goop store that he's
mocking. Oh, yeah, I saw that. He's hocking on the
street, like, he's in full costume,
he's got a script he's doing, and he's got
the whole snake oil, like, cart
set up. He's doing a Nathan Fielder. I am
impressed by that effort. That is cool.
Yeah, okay. I like that. See what I'm saying?
No, this is good. This is a good costume and set
all that. That's a good one. That's playing the Nathan Fielder.
Um, I don't care.
Like, who on YouTube is doing that?
I don't know many. You know what? You know what?
When you have as much money as John Tron does,
literally nothing you do is impressive anymore.
Right, but look, it's all in red. What do you mean?
What do you mean? Oh, you just get on the phone
and say, hey, pay someone to make this happen,
and then they'll do it for you. You have no
idea what's involved in writing. Yes, I do.
You gotta have the visions, like, make it come
together. I guess.
I guess. How much vision do you really need?
Just straight of credit, if nothing else.
It's bullshit.
You guys gotta, like, realize that this is
all in relation to, like, his old content,
which was, like, you know,
as tier, you know? So it's like,
in terms of, like, being a reaction YouTuber,
he's still, like, one of the best.
I think he is.
I respect what he's doing.
He's fine. I don't hate him.
I don't hate listening to him.
But I don't know.
You know what?
It's just, it's just...
I just... Die, John.
I don't know why. I don't have any desire
to fucking open up a John Tron video
anymore. Sure. The magic's
gone. Maybe it's me.
Maybe I'm the problem. I don't know.
I get what you're saying, because, like, you know,
I see the videos pop up on my feed and I don't click them.
Like, I... Me neither. Me neither.
Most of the time. Glad John's doing well.
But you know what? I did watch,
just recently, I went back and I watched
his Banjo and Kanzui
Mass and Bolts review. You know, this was, like, the video
that was, like, the most famous of his.
That made him hit the big screen.
You know, the big scene, whatever.
And it was... It was
very good. And I should keep in mind
I have seen it many times and loved it.
I'd call it, like, an 8.
I call it, like, an 8, currently.
I don't know.
Maybe I've changed. YouTube has evolved.
Is it fair to compare, you know,
things of that nature to what we got now?
I don't know. It's still a legendary video
where he waves and it deserves respect for that.
You know, kind of set the field for a lot of
epic game reviewers with editing
and goofy gaffy skits and whatnot.
So, whatever. I respect him on that.
It was a fun time. I don't know.
It was a good era.
It was a good era. It was a good era.
This is when him and John, or him and Aaron,
were, like, first forming Game Grumps, I believe.
It was actually, it was, like, after some videos
I thought were more recent, this Banjo one.
Whatever. I don't know. It was impressive.
We all know that was, like,
that was him being a gamer.
That was him tapping into his identity
for its purest, most,
I don't know, distilled,
gamerous cred and he was
capitalizing on.
You know, there's one other thing about
John that I must say,
I find extremely attractive.
And that is
his race, his realism.
Oh, boy.
It's like this
total
lack of need to work at anybody's
pace but his own.
And, you know, maybe just because he's so rich or whatever, he doesn't care.
He's got the leverage.
Of course he doesn't have to do anything.
But he was like that all along, you know.
He quit Game Grumps for that reason.
I feel like, yeah,
I'm just not a fucking bootlicker, okay?
That's, that's my thing.
Sorry if that's weird.
Who's boot am I looking here?
Oh, wow, look at this, wow, look at this incredible set
that he made. Yeah, he's got like an $800 billion.
He can make any set he wants.
It's not a challenge. Oh my,
you don't even know what it's financed. You have no idea.
How much do you think that card cost
to make, Nate?
Maybe, well, he probably
rented it. He probably didn't buy it, right?
Rent it from somewhere and then you deck it out.
Maybe a couple thousand tops.
Okay, but regardless of the price, it's a pretty neat card.
So what?
There's a bunch of things
that cost a shit ton
and look ugly as fuck.
Here's the difference between me and you.
I, I watch a Marvel movie
and I don't, like, or actually
I don't do that, but if I did do that,
I would, I would see, I would see some
CG and be like, it's not,
I would never be impressed by it, because like,
of course they have all this beautiful CG.
They paid like 8,000 people
to spend like two years a piece making it.
I agree, I agree. So my point
is that it's not impressive.
Look, the scale, I think
the difference here is the scale of
the point is that the Marvel has this
disposal versus John and his YouTube channel.
I'm not impressed by budget.
Well, that's not fair to the people who actually did
work on the CG and make it look impressive.
Right, a lot of people.
Right, you know, it's like, it's all these resources.
A lot of people can do the work, but it's like
you have to put someone in charge who knows like
what they're doing. So it's like, it's,
if you don't, if you don't care about the money,
sure, fine, you know?
Disney has a shit ton of money, but Lion King
still looks like shit.
Exactly, you have to put the right people in charge.
Even if this is like a gorgeous
card, even if you're like, oh my god,
I am living for this card.
I am here for it right now.
We will never know who made this card.
It wasn't John.
Dude, I couldn't give a shit about the card.
It's like, what context the card
exists in, you know? It's like, was the joke
funny? It's like, who could
have thought of that joke?
To be fair, I didn't watch the whole video
so I don't know if the joke's funny.
I don't believe it. I can appreciate
and sympathize with your point.
I really do. I just think that this joke
is funny and it's well
done. So I guess that's my main point.
It might very well be. I feel I can separate
the money issue, which I agree
is legitimate. I'm not saying
I'm not even saying fuck John for having money.
I'm just saying I'm not impressed by
the presence of like cool sets and
costumes because like, yeah, of course
he would have those things. Better than the set
costume is going across
the side from Goop
and being a snake oil salesman in real life.
Just that concept. Very funny.
What is Goop, by the way?
Goop is Gwyneth Paltrow's obviously
retarded, like, lifestyle
brand of stupid Goops and
Essences. They've got, they literally
have magnets that you're supposed to like
attach to yourself that are supposed to like
balance your chi. Like shit like that.
Shit like that. Maybe you should watch
the video before criticizing it then.
I'm not criticizing the video.
I'm just saying, I'm just
I'm literally just saying fuck you.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, that's all I want. That's all I want.
Okay. All right.
Well, agree to disagree, I guess.
God damn it. I had
another Rockstar, X-Durance
marshmallow flavor and I can't find it.
Give me 30 seconds. I gotta
check downstairs. That's not fair.
If he's going to get his marshmallow, I want to get
my apple juice. Apple juice?
Go for it, I guess. I'll just
fill time. Hey, I'll tell you what.
I actually started a website
recently. Yeah. It's
philip. S-O-S-S-O-U-R-T
dot com.
That's my art website. Put that in the links.
That's for all my
Well, it's for my animation ventures
and for like drawing and all that stuff
to have a place for me to
post your shit. Exactly.
Exactly. You know,
situate it all. But also,
I'm a big fan of puppets. I don't know
Okay, I'm back. I don't know when I got into
puppets. It might have been
just like, you know, going into Jim
Henson's shit, but like, I've been really
into it and I want to
incorporate it into my videos. I like
You're a man of many talents. I played
around with it a little bit for one
video and then I never did it again.
You know? Okay. I have a bad habit of that.
I want to see an R-long, not an R-long, an
R-low collab immediately.
Puppet Boys of YouTube.
It's time. It's the craziest stuff.
Um, yeah, I have like,
I just literally have
like, fur
halfway to the ceiling
next to me. You know, all these materials
I've just been stacking up and I just
haven't had the time
to do it because I've just been stuffed.
So like, the weekend freeing up for me
it's a blessing. I should have done it a long time ago.
So you can make these puppets for
producing in videos. For producing in videos.
Yes. Oh my god. I'm so excited. I'm so hyped.
You're filled with that. Dude, I'm so hyped.
You've always actually on YouTube been like a
Jon Trons spirit. You just do exactly what you want to do
exactly as you feel like it. Yeah. Oh my god.
At least that's how it seems to me. I've always thought that.
Yeah, it's so liberating, you know?
It's like, uh... I mean, now that I've made it my
fucking job, oh god, let me tell you.
It's a fucking bummer. Speaking of liberating,
I've done nothing on social media.
I've been sort of like, away
from social media for as much as I can
and it's been pretty liberating.
That's true. I feel so chill.
I feel so zen. I've played like
91 hours on Fire Emblem and Three Houses.
That's been fun.
Was this really an improvement in your life
is the real question? Yes. Yes, it has.
I've been so happy. I love
that game. I love my new Switch.
It's great. It's fantastic.
I don't remember the last time I've been so happy
with my life. Say you got a new Switch?
Sounds like a great investment then. Yesterday.
Wait, not yesterday. A few days ago
a miracle happened. So me and my boyfriend
we ordered pizzas for one for each
and they messed up one of the pizzas,
my boyfriend's pizza. So they gave us
that messed up pizza for free.
So we got three pizzas.
That's the story I want to hear about.
That's epic. One time
my people, we ordered
hamburgers, right?
My one friend Lorenz
he made the order for everyone,
right? And then we got the order,
right? And they messed up
like one burger, right?
Like one guy got the wrong burger.
I got the right burger. My burger was fine.
But he's like
oh, they fucked up our order. And he called them
up and he's like, he's just like, he's on the phone
like, yeah, no, these burgers are all fucked up.
No, he just gave us the wrong burgers.
And I'm like, actually, my burger's fine. He's like,
no, no, no, no, yeah, they're all fucked up.
And we just got a second burger. I just got two burgers.
It was great. That burger is epic.
I don't care.
I use kind of vague language if I was calling.
I'd be like, yeah, there's like some issues with our order.
I'd really appreciate it if you guys could fix it
and just like give us, you know, this is
what I like to do. I never tell lies.
This is the thing I do. But you can
talk your way around lies to effectively
lie. This wasn't me. I didn't do this.
I didn't do this because my burger was fine.
That's fair. That's fair.
I condemn this friend of yours. I disavow
he or she, I don't know.
They seem like they're a ruffian, a rapscallian.
I'll have none of it, sir.
That's all true.
You know, if we're still on the subject
of food, I've only been
eating one meal a day
and it's only been Burger King
or McDonald's.
I don't know if that's good or bad because
it's like, I guess
all the food that's going in me is bad, but it's like
I'm not eating the large quantity of it, you know?
It's counter balanced by the intermittent
fasting of eating once a day or whatever it's called.
That's my thought process
doing this.
I heal you. I heal again.
Sometimes we've been ordering pizza
every now and then. I only need to eat just the one
pizza that day and the next day
I've lost some calories.
It's really good.
I can have a
pizza diet.
It's beautiful. Well, no, you just got to do
what Oolulia does and degrease your pizza.
I mean, that sure would make
a pretty decent difference.
Well, you just take your napkins and you soak up the grease
off all your pizza. Okay, but what if my pizza
isn't all that greasy?
Then you've already degreased it. I guess you're in good company.
Well, you see, I don't actually
at the end of the press
that don't have anything, it's just bread. I don't
eat that. As a keto man,
what I recommend is
ordering a pizza, degreasing it
and then throwing away the pizza and just
eating the greasy napkins because
only the fat is good. Everything else
is poison and cause inflammation.
I can't eat the fat. Listen,
Jack Spratt could eat no fat. His wife
could eat no lean. Okay, here's the thing.
I got
was off keto and then
over the last couple days we've gotten back on it
and I literally went from
being fat to being skinny.
It's disgusting. The difference is
ridiculous. I can't believe
how absolutely heinous I was
four days ago and how
gorgeous I am today.
I was so distressed.
I was so distressed four days ago looking at myself
in the mirror like, God, how did this happen so fast?
And now I'm so euphoric
today, tips fedora
because like it's fixed, solved,
problem solved, no biggie.
Do you track your weight in there or anything?
I haven't been weighing myself lately, no.
Okay. For a while I was, but I haven't
counted calories. I haven't been counting calories
so in the last month I was like 3
kilograms or so.
3 kilograms? That's like 40 pounds
in a month here.
Wait, is that true?
That's like 100 pounds, dude.
What? That's not 100
pounds. No, it's just 3.
Yeah, it's like a thousand pounds.
That's like infinity pounds.
Oh man.
I don't exist anymore.
I haven't been great about my diet particularly,
but the one thing I have been doing, which is kind of more important,
I've been doing the W diet, the whatever
diet that I've advertised,
I've been doing it for like four months now
and I've lost like over
10 pounds at this point
and I mean that's a little slow, you could lose weight faster
than that, but all I've been doing
is counting my calories and all that does
is make me aware of what I'm eating
and so I can eat a little less of that.
Yeah, exactly, same thing. I've been counting calories.
I've also set a limit of how many calories I can eat per day.
Wise, yep, yep, that's the way to do it.
It's funny, when I went on
the pizza party
podcast
and talked about Keto
because I had gone
and listened to some like recent episodes
and I had heard Izzy
talk about how she was like doing Keto
and so I'm like
hey, uh, Izzy
I hear you're a Keto guy
and she's like, yeah
and I'm like, yeah, me too, awesome
and she's like, oh, she was like
I think she thought I was going to attack her for it
or something
like fuck you
eat some carbs, fucking asshole
put up those apprehensive shields
Yeah, yeah, she's right to be afraid
obviously
but in this case it was
unnecessary
Directly after gamers
it's the people who do Keto
Keto people
Indeed, that is how it
I couldn't find
I couldn't find my fucking
my fucking marshmallow
Rockstar Exdurance
Oh no, well deal with it
On the way here, I got two
I got, what, why is it like
fucking what?
This can is like smashed
I'm terrified
No, never
How does that stuff affect you?
It barely does
Energy drinks fuck me up, dude
I am like totally
immune to them now
My tolerance is so high
What's up?
Guess what day today is
Why is it special?
Is it your birthday?
27th
Daylight savings
Well, yes, but no
No, it's not
Daylight savings
It's National Black Cat Day
No kidding
Black cat day, no way
Yeah, I love that manga
You guys don't even know
what that is, I bet
I do
You probably know, you probably know
That's incredible
Happy day of black cats to my cat
because he's a black boy
Oh, that's nice
Happy black cat day to Luna
which is a hippos cat
Well, I hope you enjoy it
You know, my
My rotund little guy
My little baby dog, Sessho
He is black, he is a dog
He wants to be included
He has spent this entire episode
I've got a blanket around my legs and feet
He has been in that blanket
on my feet
You're like those fucking people
in October who draw digitally
and think you're right
Whoa, coming from my neck last year
You're gonna have a party
and you don't include everyone
That's like racist
Everyone wants a participation trophy
Sessho's a guest of honor
He's allowed, I am allowed
Okay, well thank you
Speaking of Sessho
Tomorrow, he's going to camp
He's going to camp for a couple of days
because me and Michelle
No, it's not fat camp
It's normal camp
We're going to visit
Digi out in Virginia
and we're gonna hang out with them
and Vic and Hope, presumably as well
Yep, gonna visit them for Halloween
and just, I don't know, maybe film some stuff
We'll see
We'll do
That sounds like a blast
Let me see, we'll be there
Today is Sunday
By the time everyone hears this
I will literally be on my way home
a little late for that
We'll probably do goofy stuff
Me and Zen and Munchie and Kazzy
will be having way more fun
than you
Watching Spooky Movies
Are we actually gonna do that
Because I've never watched Spooky Movies
I hate Spooky Movies
Watch Focus
Watch The Exorcist
The Exorcist is a great movie
I might consider watching The Exorcist
The only problem is The Exorcist is a little
It's like an actual
really good movie so you want to pay attention
which isn't great for like a party setting
or like hanging out with your bros
Watch Scary Movie 3
I don't know, that's more your speed
No
That's right
Is that the one with the 3?
No, never
That's for babies
That's the one where everyone makes fun
of the kid for being a virgin
Is that true?
Yes
That hits too close to home
It can't be happening
All these grown ass women
are teasing this 13 year old boy
for being a virgin
You see Bender
subverting the trope of
having the virgin woman
be victimized in horror films
by having it be a 13 year old boy
It's genius
Yeah, that might be true
That doesn't make it like
not super uncomfortable
I don't think they were actually teasing him
I think what they were doing was like
they needed a virgin for like a spell or something
No, they are definitely
You were actually
I do remember like
the spell or whatever
to summon them back in
The candle had to be lit by a virgin
or something like that
Everyone assumed it had to be
a female I think
and then specifically stated
ended up being lit by the boy
That's fucked up
Wild shit
I'm just saying, you can push a gamer
but one day you push a gamer too far
and on that day you'll learn to regret it
Veronica
Stacey, you'll learn
My people will rise up
It's tough out here for these gamers
Guys, I did it
I found my Marshmallow Rockstar Extern
You'll never guess where it was
In the refrigerator
You don't deserve any congratulations
It's always in the last place you look
Oh, you know what
I just reminded all of a sudden
Speaking of the last place you look
at the beginning of the episode I completely forgot
But now I can say it, it's that ladies and gentlemen
It's time
to head on over to patreon.com
PCP Minecraft
and join the PCP Minecraft server
Because we got it up and running baby
We're back in business
It's a thriving community, I know it took us weeks
but we fixed it seemingly every problem
Whatever, you get like a lag spike once or twice
It's an online game, deal with it pussy
This is it, Minecraft is alive forever
We'll happily take
all the money you've got
And also there's a slash
kit, sorry that you can claim up until
the 5th, I think of October
so it might be too late
So if you join now
November
Even if you weren't there
for the first part or whatever of it
you will still get this bonus sorry kit
and that's just a little present for most of you
Wait a minute, I think by the time this episode
comes out
this comes out on the first
this episode
So there's still some time
No time to waste folks
That's good
You'll get a really cool thing like a minors ring
which helps you mine faster
and also the sorry stick
which is a pickaxe
That's fucking sick
It gives you some light
when you're mining
in the dark
We've done all the work for you
We've solved all the problems
We have created for you
a thriving minecraft community
Honestly, I can't believe one
how many people sign up and two
how active the discord is
It's literally a thriving community
I just want to say thank you to everyone
It's been so fun
even while the server was down
It's just so nice
I love meming
I love when people do memes
It's so good
I love memes, I swear
They're so funny
I gotta say your enthusiasm
for this project is kind of infectious
It is infectious
SlimecorpHQ
rises higher every day
brick by brick by brick
crushing the hopes and dreams of the wage slaves of the world
Slime they had for mortar
brick and stone
What's the fucking bible quote?
Yeah, it's the original slime quote
I got it for you
It is
And they had brick for stone
and slime they had for mortar
Done
It's being constructed out of
a black concrete
clear green glass
and a beautiful marble
Oh, I can't wait
I'm gonna build 13 floors plus the lobby
for the 13th N members
Ooh, it's gonna be glorious
I'm gonna use my god powers to make an underground empire
Great idea
Has anyone seen
I've probably talked about
fucking the Yogscast
and like their
Minecraft series
You have told us many times, but they are
They continue to be fascinating
Exclusively Minecraft YouTubers, right?
Originally
They started that way
They branched off into other things
and now they are fucking like scary
evil capitalists that own everything
It's like
Ain't that just the way
Absolutely boot-shakingly terrifying
to like switch over
from doing like one video game
for your whole career
to just like wanting to branch out, you know
And like a lot of people can't make that jump
I mean, I think they started on
as World of Warcraft guys
Oh yeah, okay
I think they got popular among like wow
wow communities and then they switched to Minecraft
If you remember
the old fuck himself, old Dunkey
Remember Dunkey? I still enjoy Dunkey
I mean, Dunkey's still around
I don't know why you're talking about him in the past tense
Rest his soul, Dunkey
Good to run, but you know
He's gotten pretty fat though
So I mean maybe
He's on his way out
You know, not to me mean, because this is kind of like the high water mark
But like it's funny to watch
more and more like YouTubers are getting married
Dunkey got married recently as well
It's fun for me to compare them each
to PewDiePie's wedding
and see like how much
silence was off the charts
I mean, he's a literal millionaire
Obviously, I'm just saying
My wedding, whenever it happens
will obviously be nothing compared to this as well
I didn't watch PewDiePie's wedding video
How was it?
Well, his actual wedding video was like
an overdone, saccharine, like not funny
Like, oh I actually love my wife, lol
Idiot
Boo, don't want to hear about it, shut up
Sounds like a bunch of malarkey
It was a bunch of malarkey Zen
I post marriage and I post job
and I post life and I post food
I post all of this bullshit
Post existence
Exactly, I want to be pure energy
I'd be a millionaire too
God, I'm looking at this timeline
I just went to the Yogscast fan Wiki
Can you like it?
And I'm looking at like a timeline
of like all the different Minecraft series
they did
and like some of them overlapped
because some of them were running at the same time
Some people would have like YouTube
Minecraft series that were set
in like the same servers, right?
But sort of telling like separate stories
Man, there's so many more
than I've never seen
Like I've seen Shadow of Israel
is the big one that most people know
and then on top of like after that
like that transition into Duncan's laboratory
and then there was the Jaffa Factory
and Sipsco
The Jaffa Factory and Sipsco
I remember Jaffa Factory and Sipsco
they fucking went on and did it for years and years
and years and I will never ever watch
all this content but it sort of
makes me happy that it exists
That's cute, that's nice
It's good, it's good shit
Well, it looks like it ended around
late 2016 but I don't know
Maybe it continues
and this chart's just out of date
Yeah, please link that chart man, link the chart
so we can all cruise
I mean you will just, it'll just
be a bunch of names that you don't
understand because that's what it is for me
I can only
speculate as to the content of
Flux Buddies
or
Druids Downtown
Yeah, well, they sound enchanting
and I hope it's more than one day
I'm fucking charmed
Well, I mean we could go to voicemails if you want
I don't know, it's
talking about a bunch of bullshit
Yeah, we can go for an hour and a half
Yeah, alright, alright
Let's pull them up here, alright sick
You don't have a choice then, you have to
I am but a pretender
in this house
Okay, where does this go? This goes to the commander
Alright people, you know the drill, speak pipe
leave us voicemails, link below, click
play, record, there you go
Alright, first one, oh boy, okay
we're starting strong
First voicemails from I Need To Get Laid
Now!
Let's see what his excuse is
Go!
What's the quickest way to lose my virginity?
How do I execute Operation Pump and Dump?
Also, am I a bad person?
Yes
Zan, could you not hear that?
I didn't hear, I only heard him say hello
and I was making jokes about that being like his opening line
That's weird
I heard the whole thing
No, the sound was down
on the rhythm
Oh, okay, point was
Okay, Mage immediately
says to this guy that he is a
bad person because he just wants to pump and dump
There's nothing wrong
with going to pump and dump
It was mostly a joke, if both are concerning
to the act of pumping
No, of course
Listen to this fucking boomer
with consent
It's over man, get out of here
Post Consent Society
We're posting everything
Ban
Well, okay, listen
So the gist was, he has a girlfriend
Did you notice
he said something in there that was like
I won't be able to have a girlfriend
like in a year
What does that mean?
Maybe he's going to the military
Was I not paying attention?
No, you were not
He has a girlfriend, why doesn't he just fuck her?
I think
that's what he needs help with
Look, I've been there, you have a girlfriend
and you want to convert that girlfriend into
a girlfriend, but you are inexperienced
and you don't know how
The good news is
your hard work is behind you
You've got plenty of months, what you want to do
is in a non-creepy way, a totally nice way
You want to escalate physical intimacy
like hand touching
You just say, hey, I want to have sex
and if she says no, then you just leave
because you want sex
Ben's point is actually correct
Don't fall into the trap, I literally did this
You're absolutely right
You know what Ben? Rare moment
Ben's correct
I did it
If you have a girlfriend
and you want to have sex
and she doesn't want to
and that's it
You shouldn't be dating
Because that's such a large component
of the relationship
If you can't talk past it
If you're 13
whatever, if you want to fuck at 13
like a 16 year old
who's ready to go
who's experienced
or a 13 year old
I don't care, whatever
Don't encourage what?
Underage
I'm encouraging it
There's nothing illegal about that
No, nothing
Well, there might be a legal in some states
a 13 year old to fuck a 16 year old
because the divide between them
I mean 13's kind of young
I don't think it's illegal
Well, the premise there was a 13 year old
horn dog who wants to fuck
I mean, what are we going to say?
They're not allowed to?
I don't think it's not allowed
They can fight a 13 year old
As a general statement
not pointed to anybody
Practice sex
Condoms and whatnot
Do that too
Good advice
I'll go one step further on that
I actually am not
In my days
I've become a little bit revised on this point
I don't think having rampant sex
is really like a great way to live your life
I think pursuing people
who have a fellow interest in sex
who you could like have some kind of
reasonable relationship with
I just think will make you happier long term
having tried both
But get out there and meet someone who wants to have sex
as you do
and maybe your girlfriend does
You can't be pussyfoot around
She wants to have sex, just know if you
We're kind of scared of the actual question
His actual question is how does he lose
his virginity as quickly as possible
And I say that
I say that one
I mean, tell your girlfriend
you want to do that
There's a sunset on this relationship
And if she says no then pursue plan B
which is
get rid of her
I don't know
Ask around
Anyone for sex please
Use the Christian method
and bring a sign to school that says
Hello, my name is
whatever my name is, I'm looking for
such and such age female
so on and so forth
My name is I Need to Get Laid Now
as featured on the Procrastinator's podcast
with a link
Dude, how to get laid
Just tell them you were featured on the PCP
and their panties will hit the floor
Trust me
He already tried just being cool
and that's how he got his girlfriend
Now that you've been featured on the show
It doesn't surprise me at all
to hear him say that just calling himself cool
actually works
because that's just how simple human minds are
If you hear someone being called cool
even if it's themself
you will just learn the association
Oh, that cool guy
I've heard of this before
It's just that easy
Alright, there you go
There's your one-step program
Transparency is so important for our relationship
You just gotta be straightforward
I'll just tell the short tale again
of like I had a girlfriend in college
I wanted to fuck
It's obvious I was a loser and she wasn't into me
but like she pitied ATV basically
Yeah, exactly
but like, you know, would like try to push for that
and she would recoil because she wasn't into me
I don't blame her at all, 100% on me
So you know what you do?
And the relationship, if you're not into each other
and you move on, that's all there is to it
That's all there is to it
Alright, next voicemail
Here we go, we got the Northern Norway report
Okay, sick, go
Okay, so I listened to this previous episode
of the PCP a couple of weeks ago
and there was this voicemail with a guy
reporting on the autumn
and I start getting fucking pissed
because they look all around me
and there's snow
and there's winter
and he said he's gonna call back
three weeks, three months
Winter report
No, no, it's already winter here
Get your facts straight, you fucking retard
Also, related question
I woke up and there were some moose
shitting in my garden
and I got really scared
I waited until they got away
before I got out of the house
to go to school and stuff
So I have a question
Have any of you experienced
a similar incident?
Has a moose ever shitting
your garden back?
They have moose in Norway?
I'm trying to think
I thought those were North American
Landbridge?
I don't know
He said he was from Norway, right?
Yeah, Norway
I mean, I've seen a moose
when we went to Maine
I remember we saw some moose
Moose are fucking huge
by the way, moose are like
Do you guys know how big moose are?
They're huge
They're like fucking tanks
He's definitely right saying in the house
They could easily crush you
A horse
You see a horse in person
and you think, oh my god
I didn't realize just how big
a horse really is
and then you see a moose
and it makes the horse look like nothing
Okay
I thought they were a North American thing
but I'm not
too shocked to find out that I'm wrong
Anyway, they went over that damn landbridge
I used to see deer a lot
in college
because it was in a forest
that had a lot of deer around
and it should up its gamer cred
by ditching the leaf and making a moose
They're like national symbol or something
because moose are fucking sick
and they've got dope antlers
and they could easily crush a man
Do that
That's my recommendation
You ever read the Blue Moose stories
by Daniel Pinkwater?
Of course I did
Absolutely
For anyone who doesn't know, Daniel Pinkwater
was like a young adult fiction
I guess when we were kids
I don't know
That helped me out
That moose would eat and drink
one very specific thing
Was it like cinnamon?
Was it cider and chowder or something?
I just remember
the lodge that the Blue Moose
would visit
was known for
legendary chowder
That was their specialty
I don't even remember
anything that happened
I just remember there was a Blue Moose
who would hang out with his dude
at his fucking lodge in Maine
and they would eat chowder
and just fucking shoot the shit
by Stephen King
No, Daniel Pinkwater
Legendary
Let's go on to the next one
How many more?
18 more
We've got one
but this is good
It's Art Boy towards Chile
He's not dead yet
Maybe by the time you hear this
For anyone who doesn't know, the reason we're saying that
I'll make sure of it
The reason we're saying that is because he is from Chile
which is undergoing some kind of
fucking riot storm
Call it a revolution
It's all about the optics, Ben
It's a revolution
A workers revolt
I'm honestly not 100% clear
Oh, it's a litany of stuff
It seems like
I know corruption is a thing
They raised the price on public transport
but there was a lot more
that had happened before that
that had led up to this happening
Anyway, we should...
But also he had some health issues
Nexus continually
draws
This is so embarrassing that
there are men like Nexus out there
make me feel ashamed of myself
He just goes and he draws
and drops and just goes to the hospital
I don't know if that's something
to be proud of, honestly
Well, is it better
to burn out as a bright star
to slowly fade away into the
Why not
follow the middle way?
Don't burn out, just burn longer
The middle way is for pussies
Let's hear what Nexus has to say
Here you go
Oh, fuck
Hey, PCB
Nexus here from Chile
What a wig, man
Thing is, I found
a very sexy poster
I drew for the Ratcon Arena 3
that features Monty,
Egyptbro, Best Guy Ever, Tom Oliver
Give and Take
and that guy from the Kickstarter
So, I've been wondering
which one of you guys
would like to have the original art
of that poster in particular
There's a new post office downstairs
even in the middle of the chaos
in the city right now, so let me know
Oh, and by the way
this is a present, meaning
it's free
Oh fuck, no
I didn't say freedom, I said free
Oh, no way
That's even worse
Oh
So, okay
I think it's only fair that me,
an original member of the podcast gets that poster
Yeah, that's fair
I think as part of his severance package
we actually owe it to Mumkey
Um, so
I think this was somewhere
in the contract
Hey, remember all those good times we had without you
Here's a reminder, put it on your wall
Rest in peace, Mumkey
Oh my god
Listen, listen, listen
I have a PL box, you know the address, Nexus
Send it to me, I want it
I want it, I would appreciate it more
I bet it smells like ink
It probably does
You know, maybe we could in some way
have some sort of game of
Yeah, maybe no, cut it into 8 pieces
and send it to each of us
Damn, that's a good idea
When we all
like, unite, then we can
see the full image
Honestly, yeah, and then like we have
like at Radcon 4, we all come together
and like put it together like that
Ooh, that would be sweet
But Mage would have to get off her dumb ass
and get over to North America
No, you go, you come to England
Mage, how much money would it take
to get you to come for Radcon
Yeah, give us enough
Okay, Mage, that's 100%
Not only
How about 9,000 Nigerian dollars?
Mage, listen, listen
Let's just say theoretically
your entire trip was paid for
and let's just say for a crazy bonus
you also will get paid
$1,000, I'm keeping it trying
to be reasonable here
I'm just saying
Just an exaggeration, would you
come with that situation?
It's not about the price, having
the journey
Is it the bother of having to take the trip
and the babbling and all that?
I'm scared of traveling alone to America
America scares me, can you blame me?
Oh, it's always right to settle down
reasonably well at this point
I have a country with guns
I'm scared
Where's carrying guns around?
Here's the thing
You wouldn't be coming to the
gun part of America, you'd be coming to
Massachusetts, which is like as European
as America gets
Everyone wearing
scary cowboy hats
and guns all over the world
That's like the Ontario
of the United States, it's like its own
Ontario? Yeah, it's like a separate part
No one gets these Canada
metaphors you're using, no one understands anything about Canada
No, not Ontario, Quebec
Quebec is sort of its own cultural enclave
in Canada, I think
because they have a French peaking part
Texas is its own fucking beast
Massachusetts is the good part
I don't want to go to Virginia, fuck Virginia
We'll keep you posted
I got an observation to make
I got an observation to make about America
Mage, maybe you should be afraid
Listen, my personal life
I realized this the other day
my personal life has been kind of shit
ever since Trump got elected
and I can't find
a direct causal link
but it can't be coincidence
It has to be a connection, I know it
I know it in my heart
Ooh, when you got that
Trump derangement syndrome
it's tough to relate to your fellow man
Wait, what is that?
Well, that is the thing
You attribute everything
to what will happen to you at the Trump
When you're just so steam
that Orange Man is so bad
Is that a real thing? Is that like a phrase?
I mean, it's like a brain phrase
It's used to own the lives
Well, I better
I guess it's me
No, it's not me
That's victim blaming
It's not my fault for being mad
It's his fault for being bad and making me upset
That's fair
In addition to
being scared of Trump
In addition to Orange Man, yes
It's also like
I tend to fall ill
immediately after I travel
so I kind of don't want to be ill
in a foreign country
Have I talked about
what happened to me right before I left
to go to BronyCon this past year?
Much like Hillary Clinton
you have not yet told us what happened
Please do so
Again, okay
Before I travel
I'm kind of a homebody as well
I get very nervous
I get very anxious
and this was happening to me
I couldn't sleep, I was pacing around
in my house, I was sweating
I was sweating a lot
I don't know, that just happens
Something that I do a lot
when I'm stressed out is I'll cut my hair
or I'll groom a lot
a whole bunch of times or whatever
I'll take a bunch of showers
So this time
I'm looking at myself and I'm brushing my teeth
and I'm looking at my teeth and I'm like
Ah, damn these teeth
and I've got like
Damn these teeth
Get them out of my mouth now
No, I've got this tooth whitening gel
It comes in like a thing
So I might as well whiten my teeth
So I put this shit on my teeth
and I put it in my mouth
and I'm looking in
and the stick gets on my gums
and I have used it before
and it has gotten on my gums before
and it's been fine, like it has not been a problem
but this time it gets on my gums
and a little piece of my gums
just turns like chalk white
bone white, like swollen
weird looking, looks like cooked chicken
whiter than my teeth
it's just a little piece of my skin
it just turns white, I'm like oh my god
I start like, I go in to have a little fucking
attack, I have a little panic attack
about it, I get like
just distraught, I get emotionally distraught
I'm like weeping, right
I'm like, I'm rinsing my mouth out
like a whole bunch of it, after a little while
after a little while
it starts to go down, it just starts kind of
just turns kind of sore, but it goes away
and I'm like oh thank god, I thought I was doomed
I thought I was just doomed to have fucking chicken mouth
for the rest of my life
but for that moment
I was like, I can't go, I can't leave the house
like this, I'm a freak, I'm a freak
well
what was the point of that story?
I can't remember
oh traveling, traveling, fear, before traveling
or something, I've been using the crest white strips
a little bit, I've been a little lazy
I'm gonna try to use them like every other day or something
they seem, they're not bad
I haven't used my, that's the same kind of
I haven't used my, that whitening gel
since this happened, I'm too scared to try again
I don't want to have a chicken
it was very weird looking
and I've never, it was like
yeah, it was fucking scary, it was like
body hard
no, I'm sure, yeah
fucking yikes
well on this subject
perhaps one day
I wonder how much it would really cost us
to do like a rad con
in England
in London England, jolly old England
I mean considering you and
Gib and Mage wouldn't have to fly
but then like, you know, five or six
or seven or whatever of us would have to fly
so that's gonna be a pretty penny
but I don't know, I mean realistically
it would be me, you,
Munchy, Digi
Jesse, if he went
if he went, yeah
well is Tom just not coming
oh and Tom, well Tom definitely could
but I can't remember everybody
wait, that's like six people?
let's say six people, yeah it seems about right
assuming Jesse goes
I mean that right there, I don't know
I could easily imagine that would be like ten grand
ten grand? no
yeah, it's gotta be over a thousand dollars
for people to fly to England from Merrick
yeah, no, maybe you're right, yeah it could be
are the tickets really that bad?
no
you know what, we could research this
I think it's usually able to fly for less
we could get them for better
we could probably get around-trip tickets
for under a grand for each person
I'm seeing costs for like
I'm seeing costs for like six hundred
for round-trip?
for one person? oh not round-trip, my bad
maybe it is, I don't know
let me check
round-trip, yeah, yeah
round-trip, 633
okay
alright, hey, you know, that's not terrible
I mean still, for six people that ends up being like
that would be a large percentage of the budget
what airport would you guys use?
I don't know, Mage
I'm no London expert
no, no, no, I'm asking the American
which one you would use
wait, I have a lot of CVG
we don't need to go through the numbers right now
but you can use CVG
which airport I'd fly out of
to England
I would fly out of
it's Cincinnati
yeah, Logan Airport
she's probably going to crunch the
numbers right now
I'm trying to, yeah, just like, how do you spell Cincinnati?
we can do this later
we've got approximate numbers
if we raised, let's just say theoretically
if we raised like $10,000 for a ride
that's a pretty penny
but I think it's theoretically possible
for like a PCP in England or whatever
the things we'd want would be
air flight and then like
we'd need some sort of sort of like Airbnb
or some place to live while we're there
would $10,000 cover it?
probably, I think so
probably cover it
we probably also want Vic to be
cameraman too, that's another
expense as well
but I don't know, whatever
we'd have to fly Vic out and all his equipment
and his equipment too
maybe we just hire somebody else
to do it locally, I don't know
might make sense
you'd also have to make it worth his while
yeah, exactly
we also paid him last time
ideally, we're spending time doing this
I would like to get paid
I would like to at least not lose money
on the venture, that would be nice
which we have each time, but
I don't know, whatever, we'll see what happens
I, Radcom 4 man
Radcom 4
the Sonichi Lecture 2
is going to be a defining moment
I am like
I'm like
I'm creating history
right now
so that I can deliver it in
that's the way to do it, that's what God did
Sonichi Lecture 102
beautiful
this is what it's all about
speaking of lectures, this just reminds me
of a point I was going to say before
I avoided talking about this for a long time
because it actually bothered me and grossed me out
and I didn't like it
and it gave me lots of anxiety
so the final fantasy lecture
I did at Radcom 3
there's a bunch of issues with it
audio-wise, which is very unfortunate
it wasn't perfect, it wasn't good as the Kingdom Hearts one
that's fine, doesn't matter
but the main thing I had about that
I was very sad that the audio was dorked in the way it was
aside from that
I was very, very
worried, I was considering just scrapping the entire
video for one reason
and it was that
my, I had just shaved
before doing it, I was very concerned about
looking decent
I had just shaved and I was like
bleeding a little bit
I was like, you guys were downstairs
waiting for me and I'm upstairs
I had just shaved, I'm like, oh god
I'm bleeding, it's so gross
I don't want anyone to see it, it's so nasty
I hate it
you should have seen, as I was editing the video
Michelle was like, Nate, shut the fuck, no one cares
Nate, just post the video
you can't even see it
and if you look real close, you may be able to
detect some slight traces
but basically no one can tell
I mean, not one person
complaining about that, but like
me at fucking Radcon 3
Fat Ben, of course
Fat Ben, unshaven Ben
like, just like
not decrepit, but like
just like disheveled
disheveled, terrible
worst Ben
man, oh, I look so fucking
I look so fucking bad at Radcon 3
I'm on camera basically every week now
for Reagolas, but the real milestones
I want to get fit and get
better in shape and whatnot
so that for the next lecture, you know, the videos people actually care about
it'll be a look
a look that much better
we were doing voicemails
you're right, you're right
and let's get back to it and wrap this pony up
alright, this is
okay, watch out, brace yourself
this is an extremely scary voicemail
warning, ultra haunted
okay, so let's, it is the Halloween season
this will be like one day after Halloween
but nonetheless, okay, brace yourselves
so you're with your honey
and you're making out when
the phone rings
you answer it and the
voice is, what are
you doing with my daughter
you tell your girl and she
say, my dad is
dead
then who
was
phone
phone was daddy
daddy isn't her father
daddy is
the joke is well known
the joke isn't done, but
the production value was
worth the play
there's something you're misunderstanding here
a phone, a dad
is phone
I'm daddy
not father
yes, exactly
this is some new John Tron level
shit, I don't care about production value
next, next
alright, next voicemail, here we go
this is from the leader of the
PC partisans
okay, alright, good, go
greetings, PCP, this mission
if you choose to accept it
may very well change the entire world
around you, it's coming to my
attention, you're now all under house
arrest by the PC police
and may be subjected to gay
rape, straight rape
and even worse
but we, the PC partisans can fix that
we're leading a revolution
to stop them and need your help
the first 9-11 was so successful
they're planning a sequel, 7-11
we're on July 11th
2020, 11, 7-11
convenience stores, we're throwing
their 7 important towers by Nazi
vampires, hate off by the PC
police and their martial masters
this inside
job will be leveraged to give full power
to the Dark Lord and spell
the end for America
we can break you out
but if you do, you need to help us
I'll wait your response
but I NEED TO GO
what do you think?
oh man, man, is that guy in chili with nexus?
yeah, a lot of gunshots today
I mean, okay
I don't, you know
I wasn't gonna do anything
about the house arrest situation
but 7-11
I'm just so charmed by the theming
of this terrorist attack that I can't help
but get on board with it
you know, there was Homestuck
there was Homestuck 2
there was 9-11, then there was 7-11
and the rest was history
equally good works of art
okay, next one
we're in
we're in, we're fully on board
I'm comfortable speaking for the rest of us
that we will all die for this cause
no
no, no, your protests are in vain
I mean, I'm
putting distance between myself and this
concept
alright, next up, put mage on the front lines
strap mage to the front of the plane
I'm not gonna be there, I won't be there
alright, I think what he said
what am I gonna do?
we're gonna drive 7-7-11s
into
Nazi vampires
how are you gonna drive a 7-11?
I think we're going to
bomb 7-7-11s
on
I don't remember how the Nazi vampires
come into it
that's where I get my big gulps
I'm not bombing a 7-11
you can't make an egg with that
break into an obelisk
we'll go in
I'll buy up their entire stock
of cheeseburger bites
and then you can do what you want with them
that makes sense
they don't even have the hot deals
they don't even have the hot deals on
rockstar ex-durance anymore
it used to be 2 for 3 dollars
an incredible bargain
now what do you got like 2 for 5 for quake
fuck quake
die
next voicemail
we've got rustles
sorry, it's rustle
with name something scarier than a ghost
with a gun
I think it's the rustle
I think so
what's up guys
it's your gangoy rustle here
just calling in to let you know that a few months ago
I lost the only virginity
that's actually worth a damn
that's right
shooting a gun
a staccato p9mm handgun to be exact
so I just wanted to ask
what kind of guns have you guys shot in the past
and if none
what kind of guns do you want to shoot
no guns
I have fired a gun
on a firing range before
like once
was it like a pistol
one of those
wait have I
I think I have
me this episode
I'm scared to go to America because of guns
every single voicemail
I don't like guns
I don't like guns either
I've shot one at a range before
but I'm honestly now
what about like Boy Scouts
with the scouts I must have done it at some point
really
you did
what was that
in school
we were like I think secondary grade
we went to a police station
you shot at the school mage
we went on a little
tour to a police station
we were allowed to shoot
that's crazy
here play with my gun
it's only filled with hollow points
apparently shooting a gun isn't as
uniquely experiential
as I thought
a lot of you guys are like just an hour counting that you
shot a gun
you a frequent shooter
no I've never shot a gun before in my life
but um
it's just like
it's the kind of thing you would definitely remember
right exactly
apparently not
I would have been like a decade or more ago
so I'm like
I'm like 85% sure
I've also been to archery
you're not even sure if you shot it
that's how vague it is
maybe with these fools
I remember absolutely explicitly shooting guns
I have shot these exact guns
I shot BB guns stuff
like at Boy Scouts for the rifle rearrange
whatever
I did the shotgun shooting merit badge
which I achieved as with the BB gun shooting one
or the rifle shooting
so I had my shotgun shooting merit badge
it was fucking sick it was the best time ever
we shot clay pigeons I was so fucking good at it
it was absolutely dopey shit
and actually just the other day
Michelle on Michelle's
interest in the subject
she was like maybe we should go shoot guns
I was like fuck yeah let's do that
she would want to shoot guns
there we're in Ohio now baby
it's a wild west
that's right
so we haven't shot yet what we did was
we went to the intro to firearms course
and we were gonna set up for like a class
where they teach you more stuff
and then you actually go shoot pistols and real guns
on a range and stuff so we'll probably do that sometime
and I'm
super fun it's fucking sick dude guns are dope
epic
I'm way into it although they do
terrify me and I don't want them around me
I don't know if it counts but like I remember
like dad had a BB gun and I remember
like shooting some cans with a BB gun
but I feel like remember that time dad shot
the fucking rabbit in the garden
that fucking rabbit that psychopath
what the fuck dad because it was just
you didn't think it
I similarly remember my dad coming home
one day he came home and it's like
the first time he shot a gun and he like he had
like the gun range like
little sheet where you shoot it and he's like
he hung it up in his office I was like okay cool
in his office he's just like shooting across the room
yeah you're real badass dad
no no no like he brought it
he brought home the sheet that he shot
oh okay yeah yeah
we did archery
okay I've definitely shot BB guns
I
think I don't remember
if I shot a real gun at a range I've been to a range
it might have been an archery range
I feel like
we understand you exist in a state of quantum
having shot a gun
like disturbed by the fact that I'm not 100%
sure on this question
just go pick up a gun and shoot it
and then put your questions to rest already
alright let's move on here
couple more we got um
okay crates with pancakes
hashtag free secho
uh okay
no he's literally under my boot
deal right now my foot is on top of secho's body
push it down
push him
squeeze him out
the rates of dog incarceration are
insane
alright let's hear what he has to say
hey crater here
and Nate I'm calling you out
I was with my wife yesterday
yeah I got a wife what of it
and I see a dog on the corner of my
eye
I got out of bed after fresh plow
to the front porch
and here comes secho rolling his fat
dog ass over here
so I said
help me it's Nate
he keeps giving me fuel
and he just keeps feeding me
and feeding me
and he just won't stop
Nate
I contacted animal control
and they're on their way right now
oh
I think that's them
by the way can we please get fan art
a vorporn of secho eating
Nate please
oh no
it has to be in the furriard style
it's the only way
the only way to stop eating
is to consume that
which gives the
forces you to consume I guess
I can just imagine Nate
a big bag
of liquid fuel
you just could dump it out into secho's bowl
just slather it all over the floor
we hook it up to an IV
so he can't even not eat
you and him subsisting
on the same weird mineral
I pour it into the trough
and we both stick our heads through our respective holes
and we just lap it up
that's how it goes
we've been reduced to animals in this society
let's go to the next voicemail
ghost of
voice
the ghost of bad voicemails
okay
let's see what he has
there's a lot of those ghosts
it's gonna be an all-star one
go
who knocks at this time of night
ooh
it is I
the ghost of bad voicemails
I am a specter born
from the twisted souls
of those who died
in voice jade
ooh
and I have come
to kill you
what the fuck
I am the ghost
of bad voicemails
fucking
spooky
look
I don't know what the point of this is
I don't know what you're trying to sell me
I'm definitely not scared
there is
no point
you better start believing
bad voicemails
because you're in one
I was only pretending
to be an idiot
the twist ending
the ghost of bad voicemails
was no ghost at all
for he yet lives
he lives on in our hearts
this is a living breathing bad voicemail
before I take this very moment
alright well how many more do we got
that was good we got I think two more
two more okay here we go
we got another call from not even
clusterpunk can save me now
now the pc police
okay that's I don't know what that means
alright let's see what we got go
sir I'm sorry
don't want your damn excuses
I want best guy
ever's head
why didn't you illuminate him
there was an
unforeseen variable
we were attacked by a ferocious
frothing at the mouth giraffe
oozing with AIDS
he held back our main
a giraffe
a fucking giraffe held back
my main squadron
well not just a giraffe sir
there was also this rotom canine
that
any other pcp
members that you were successful in locating
well we're currently
researching this wacky place
called England for suspect hippo
after many failed attempts
at locating him in Africa
or any local zoos
we've also discovered through tireless research
that best guy ever has an older
brother named Ben St
we've never found the dumpsters in Boston
that Ben St can be living in
so it's only a matter of time before we dig him up
no I'm always on the move
very good
we may have had a misstep with that
ferocious giraffe and rotom dog
but soon
very soon they'll be making t-shirts
saying one of the reason why
the pcp are dying
oh no
what you gonna do
the pcp
the pcp police closed its grip
more and more every day
it's just propaganda
I'm not worried about it
they'll never find me
I'm slippery
literally like I'm covered in grease
yes absolutely
you are slime
oh so that's why you degreased the pizzas
to put it on yourself
I eat so much pizza grease
I sweat it now
we call it grease
first cousin of slime
it's related to ooze
and slime and sludge
you know I was actually curious
I don't know if you addressed this
was he dying that looked like a friolator
full of grease
no it is a chemical vat
this has been canon since the beginning
of slime oids
the way to kill a slime oid
is to throw it into a dissolution vat
oh I see
fair enough
now you can have multiple slime oids
in bottles
but before if you wanted a new slime oid
you had to go to the labs
and dissolve your old one
oh so this bottle thing that
is actually that's like lore
that was in there already
I had no idea
bottling slime oids is how you
I think you can have like three
pokeballs
in bottles
that's it
next voicemail here we go
we got fave chip
fave chip calling in go
question for y'all
do you guys have a
favorite
chip
that's it
that's the whole voicemail
I gotta tell you this was voicemail god
he had so many voicemails once again
I didn't play this out of pity
I like chips and I did want to talk about
my favorite chip
but he has so many voicemails
relax dude, relax
just make them on average better
what's your answer
what's your favorite chip
I think
I like
what are they called like new england style
like the really crunchy
cape cod chips
cape cod potato chips
I think those are my favorite
it's like you're breaking someone's spine
in your mouth
Tom sound familiar
it's great
yeah no I love those
you ever had
there's like a certain brand of potato chip
they come in a black bag
they look gourmet
and they have one kind that is like blue potato chips
made out of blue potatoes
and they have another kind
they have another kind that is like
it's like a mix of like
taro root and sweet potato
and like two other like different tubers
and they have chips at all
those are super good too
I really like those
I think I've had them but
mage, zen, comments
yeah
the thing that first comes to my mind is like
well I was listening
to this song by this rapper named young i may
and she's awesome gotta check her out
and she has this line in her newest song
she says pinky ring out the puddle
hot sauce under ruffles
and I was thinking
god that must be pretty tight
you know for you to mention
it in a song that must be pretty good
cause I like ruffles never had hot sauce on
indeed I might try it out
she's just shouting out ruffled potatoes
yep that's it
I feel like
I don't, I think I'm against
ruffles in principle
I kind of think they're overhyped
really what
they don't get that much acclaim
you see it on the bag
and it's like ooh ruffles
it's like a
point of sale it's like a selling
point and I'm like I just don't, I don't get it
oh you mean like the actual ridges on them
yeah
I like that texture
it's fine I don't know whatever it's a lateral move
I feel like it's a lateral move that gets overhyped
I
I usually like sour cream and onion
that's pretty basic I also like
um barbecue Pringles
yeah
but there was this one
I used in Latina and never again
because I could never find them again
they just disappeared off of the face of the earth
I don't remember what flavor they were
but like they were absolutely perfect
they were like sweet a little bit spicy
but not too spicy because I don't like too spicy
but a little bit of spice just a little bit
to get the little kid but they were sweet
and I just like when I ate them I just
I couldn't stop they were just so delicious
they were really next day to get more
because I just I wanted to know what flavor
it was to just like to just to get more
of it and they were gone and and like
what for as long as I was in Latina
this year they never again
stopped those chips wait what brand
what brand was it
I don't remember I don't remember
I don't know I'm
going to be tormented for the rest of my life
mystery chip that's how to get you
yeah
okay I have a question everyone
yeah opinion on
salt and vinegar
oh never been a fan
you know what
I'm surprised how popular
they are in England
byter loves them they're their favorite
when I was a kid I like
smelled like like I knew people
would eat them and I would smell it and think
it smelled disgusting and I was like
gross but then as an adult
I tried them and I'm like you know what I get
it so I've I I didn't
used to like them but I change my
right and I was not a fan
I used to hate them but now
sometimes a little bit is just
fine it depends on the brand
I think it's like the
it's the walkers I think
the UK version of them I feel like
I know that like some people are
against just like no it's
like some people just don't get salt and vinegar
but I guess we're all
we're all down with the strong yeah
I think we're all cool when I was young yeah
I've transitioned from the like childish
like it's gross I don't think it's gross
I just can't take too many
of them and I'm not a big fan
I like how it stains
your mouth
I like to over do it
with stuff like that
I gotta tell you a story
speaking of chips right I was eating
chips today but not real chips
because
somebody left
a monster energy drink
in my freezer
and it exploded
and then it froze to the edges
of the freezer
so I had to de-ice
the freezer but I noticed
that some of the ice
was green
and I was like this just seems like a damn waste
so I broke off chunks of this ice
frozen this and I tried it and I gotta tell you
it was it was delicious
it tasted like sweet
cotton candy
it was super good
this was the best ice
but then I was licking I'm like wait a minute
it wasn't a diet monster
these aren't keto ice chips
but it's okay
I only had a couple
anyway it was very excited
and I was like and like my friend
that same friend
who said that my burger was fucked up
even though it wasn't and he got me a second burger
he was there I'm saying like guys
you know you're not gonna believe me
it's frozen monster ice chips
it's actually super good
and of course everyone's like oh Ben
you're so fucking crazy
you're such a weird eccentric guy
just like when you said that watering down
your orange juice just gives you more orange juice
you're so crazy
but then exactly like that time
I got Lorenz to try some of this ice
and he's like it's actually really good
just like with the orange juice I was 100% right
fully exonerated
Ben are you aware of the product
it's a drop 50
which is just it's just
it's that they just took orange juice
they literally it's an ingredient
half orange juice half water
just half orange juice
why would you ever buy that
when you could just buy regular orange juice
for the same price and water it down
and get twice as much
because they're trying to pull the wool over your eyes
that's all there is to it
fucking cut your own orange juice with water dudes
with the samurai sword
by the way I sorry guys
double cheese is so good
double cheese delay like extra cheesy
flavors for chips are good
wait double cheese
I used to like those but
it's like the crazy like
flavor bomb chips they're too much
for me I can't I can't deal with that
sometimes I'll have too much
of one thing over like a two week
or you know whatever long
period and then like
I just have this aversion
do it completely like one time
like it was like Dr Pepper
and Domino's for me
and now I just cannot have it
at all anymore it also makes me sick
one time I got like a big I was a kid
and I got a big bag of salsa Verde
Doritos and I ate the whole
bag of salsa Verde Doritos they're kind of
spicy but they're pretty good and then
that night for dinner we had tacos
and then I woke up in the middle of the night
and I had to puke really bad and
I puked it all up and it was spicy
and it tasted Mexican
and the puke was like
I could taste the salsa Verde Doritos
and I didn't have Doritos for a long
time after that because real fucking nasty
makes sense
just my buddy Garf
my buddy Garf did the same thing with vodka
I think that's far more common experience
dude the thing about puking up vodka
is you get drunk on the way up too
eww
I guess
last voicemail right
you know I was going to say
that was allegedly last I lied
to you guys but there was actually one
secret final voicemail
brace yourself because this is the
one second voicemail coming back
ready here we go
so I haven't lived a voicemail in a while
that's it everybody
thanks for being here on another episode
of the procrastinators podcast
patreon.com
are you telling this is what you invited me for
for that bullshit
how dare you
how fucking dare you
hey if you give us $5 you get like 30 bonus
episodes that's pretty sick
there will be a new one out like tomorrow
when you hear this so look forward to that
and anymore and we'll just say
thanks appreciate that very much
what's going on at tpcrastinators on twitter
follow us you know what I'm doing
leave speak pipe voicemails
link down below quality voicemails
please or else I'll just kill you
like I'm gonna do voicemail god
none of this shit voicemails
quality ones in the future please
oh man I gotta tell ya
I'm gonna mock you a little bit voicemail god
voicemail god is getting so fucking cocky
you left a voicemail that I didn't play
that was like hey guys
what if we did a thing where like
ooh you don't know who I am
you don't know who the voicemail god is
try to guess who I am
who the fuck are you dude
you'll never be anything
you'll never make it in this business
who are you voicemail god
unless you're like an endless war player
of renown
are you investor
and then you'd have a dick
I mean is he someone we would know
other than as voicemail god
maybe he's like my best friend of childhood
and I just haven't recognized his voice
I hope that's what happened
I don't understand the game you were playing
is it
is he them snakes
shed his skin and reborn
that could be it
it's just I don't know
call in and clarify
and you may not get played anyway
so there you go
that's it end of the voicemails
end of the episode
drink your apple juice
and water and doubt
do that
I gotta go squeeze out my dog
squeeze the grease and pat down the
side of his body
absolutely
we'll see you next week everybody
water down your apple juice
water down lads bye
50-50