Oh, hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of the PCP Crogue Crastinators Podcast.
Oh, I fucked everything up. I don't know. I'm the best guy ever, though, and thanks for joining us.
Here we've got Tom Oliver over here. Yeah, I'm here with my robot body.
Indeed. The Davoo is here. Still just barely able to juggle the scheduling and in monetary conflicts
caused by having to do PCP responsibilities while hashtag saving the hamsters. They'll have robot
hamster bodies soon anyway. We've got Hippocrit is here. I identify as being a robot skeleton.
Good. And of course, Digibro. All I want is the Android dong.
Android dong. Okay, never mind. So, everybody, we're talking about... Oh, I got introduced
the show. So, this is The Pro Crastinators Podcast, everybody. It's a podcast of a bunch of internet
creators. We do YouTube stuff. Some of us do comics, et cetera, et cetera. And here we are
talking about various topics in this show here on The Procrastinators Channel. And today we're
talking about transhumanism. Today we're talking about transhumanism. And if you don't know what
that is, luckily our boys over at Urban Dictionary have you covered. Let's give it a read. Okay,
that's a long one. I'm going to do the shorter secondary one. Hopefully this will be good.
Okay. A postmodern theory that posits on the perceived benefit to mankind of having a
Cuisinart installed in your rectum. Oh, I don't even know what a Cuisinart... Okay,
then let's talk. Let's do the top definition. Okay, here's one of the little more details.
This is the top definition. Transhumanism. A movement supporting the use of reason science
and technology to advance and enhance human abilities and existence under optimal conditions.
Can be seen as an extension of humanism, but with much more emphasis on the future. Transhumanists
believe that we should try to overcome our biological limitations through the use of such
things as nanotechnology, cryonics, AI, mind uploading, spacetime engineering, Jesus Christ,
eugenics. Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay. And what not in order to become post-human. I don't understand
what that last part... I think that was a... The only thing I like about that list was the eugenics.
Oh, by the way, I just want to give a shout out to our heroes at Urban Dictionary to which the
PCPO is the entirety of its success. I just wanted to shout them out as their October 6th
word of the day was boy-splaining. Boy-splaining. It's mansplaining, but immature. That means that
mansplaining is mature. That means mansplaining is the mature thing to do. You fucked up, Urban
Dictionary. Isn't boy-splaining literally the entirety of the procrastinator's podcast?
I agree. That's a good point. So very relevant. So when transhumanism was brought up as a topic,
I was shocked that we haven't already done this, because I don't know about Hippo, but I know me
and Nate and Tom and probably DeVu are all very big transhumans. We all self-identify as transhumans,
for sure. Well, you know, we're not transhumans, but we're sympathetic to the cause. I don't think
any of us are augmented yet. You know, to some extent, I've heard people argue that human beings
as they exist now are semi-transhumans because we have our phones and stuff. Yeah, yeah. Well,
the thing I was going to say is I think we've already interrupted evolution, like the evolutionary
process of human time. Oh, no doubt. No doubt. So we're already off the beaten path. So I just
figured we might as well go full stop at this point. And I mean, when transhumanism gets brought up,
I feel like everybody imagines it as like robot parts attached to your body. But a lot of it's
way more than that. Of course. A lot of it's chemical. And we're all doing that shit. There is
nobody who is not ingesting some form of chemical that is performance altering in some way as to
how it's just caffeine. If you've got yourself kind of food, like actually, did you try to establish
smoking weed his new hobby as a transhumanist act? If you've got yourself a fly-ass, bomb-ass,
dope-ass hoe who you're nutting in regularly and she's taken that pill, that is her being a transhumanist.
That is her deviating from her biological intentions. So every time you nut in your lady,
just say, bitch, you're a robot now. That's what I do. That's the fact how I nut. I do. I feel like
I have to mention that I'm not really that into the future, the sci-fi. I'm more into the past
things, like aesthetically. But if transhumanism doesn't mean robot parts and it means all this
other stuff, then I don't know. Because I didn't know that. I always assumed it was like looking
way into the future to see all the cool stuff that was like, you know, flying cars attached to your
back. I know you're more into, I don't know. Well, you can be the surrogate for the audience.
We can dump our knowledge onto you. I think the reason I wanted to specify that, that it's not
far future, is because it's more interesting to think about the stuff that we can do soon,
you know, like the ways that we're already making progress. And a lot of the transhuman stuff I'm
most excited about is not just robot parts, but like, I don't want to have to sleep anymore.
When are we getting my anti-sleep pill, you know? Or when are we getting... Nate, I was glad you
brought up birth control, because I was thinking about this. I've been thinking about this all
fucking day about what I'm going to bring into this podcast. That I think transhumanism could
easily be mistaken as like a guy thing, because we all, you know, there's stereotype guys love
technology and we want to fucking have a robot android dong, you know? But I was thinking about how
there's already pills that can, for instance, make it so you don't have your period anymore,
and like fix PMS stuff. I feel like women would jump right the fuck on that.
It's in fact, it's far more common for, like, the whole idea of female birth control is like
deeply rooted now in at least western culture, but male birth control is like,
some movements actually oppose the very idea of it, which I think is sort of a play to like
keep the sexual power in the hands of women, but we can get into my red pillion over time.
Yes, so hippo, like I know you're more into the past, like pirates and shit, but in the future we
could potentially have pirates, but then also without polio ruining everyone's fun. So I'm
just saying, the future is really better for everyone. I know. I mean, I agree. I agree that
some things are bad about the way humans are and the things that we have to deal with, but I like
wood more than I like metal. That's just really what it comes down to. I like a pirate ship being
made of wood. I don't want to see pirates with guns get out. That's why apple wood texture
skimmed more quickly on everything. Wait, pirates always had guns. No, no, I mean, like, like,
modern day pirates are like, oh, the, you know, and I don't know. Like Somali pirates. Somali
pirates, yeah, they go on, they go on dinghies not filled with air and on ships made of metal,
with guns, get out of here. You know, I don't respect you because of that. If you had wooden
boats, maybe. On the, on the topic of just transhuman in general. Okay. So, so yeah, like,
I'm a gigantic fan of this. Like Ghost in the Shell is one of my favorite things of all time.
And I want to talk at least at some length and I'm so, it's so cool to me that you brought up
like male versus women just because Motoko is just such a role model to me and just represents all
these great things about like Motoko is like a technological wizard who is like ahead of the
curve. Everyone behind her is like a regressive piece of shit. But Motoko is always thinking about
how to like adapt to the situation she's in. And that, that is inherent to a character as like
the best cyborg user or like one of the best out there. But what I wanted to say about this was
there's so many people when you bring up this topic, like are struck with such a deep level of
fear instantaneously. And I feel this is one of our like, this is one of our like biological
carryovers from when we were, you know, beasts of the field. It's one of our, it's just like this,
this instinct to be afraid of, of, of change really and of the unknown because like,
whenever I think about this stuff in general, I think about like, okay, we're going to,
we're going to do extensive testing and try to like, okay, if we want to invent like a microchip
that lets us talk to each other, you know, not, not psychically, but through the technology
implanted our heads, which people are working on actively right now. If you bring up that idea,
people are immediately like, Oh no, I don't want something in my head. Like, oh, imagine all the
things that could go wrong. And like, that's entirely true, which is why we will before like
making that technology available to extensive testing and try to avoid the very things that
people are afraid of. Well, here's the thing. This is what I think. I think the problem is that
we're all influenced by popular culture and technology is the current boogeyman that we
all like to think is going to go bad. Like that's been the boogeyman for the last like 20, 30 years.
Yeah, you know, even dumb, you go that and it's like, Oh, Terminator 2, Skynet, all that's just
going to happen. And I just think back to like before that, you know, like, like electricity
was the boogeyman. It's like, Oh, you got shocked by electricity and turned into a monster because
we don't understand how this works. So like electricity, no thing like that's gonna be
so much art and like fiction has a hard time like grappling with the fear, but still great
potential of future technology, you know, so much sci-fi stuff, even if part of the appeal of say a
sci-fi movie is about like showing off this cool technology, the script just cannot help but
constantly preoccupy itself with all the fucking things that can go wrong and scarcely showing you
why people adopted technology in the first place. And again, Ghost in a Shell standalone complex,
the series specifically does a great job. Just really it's not it is even handed. It talks about
cyber brain sclerosis, which is like a disease that no one could figure out caused by a cyber brain.
You're fucked, right? But it's but again, the real villain just in that situation is the fact
that the corporation invented a cure for it, but didn't want to implement it because it would
impact their bottom line too much. Again, just setting up a situation where technology isn't
what's evil. It's it's the greed of men. That's the real evil here. So like that's exactly what I
want to see in a story like that, you know, right? Like and like, like actually, I'm actually watching
an episode right now, like earlier today. I also heard an explanation that was like, well, they
couldn't figure out why the cure worked. So it wasn't approved for that reason. I don't. Anyway,
like I even recently watched the Ghost in a Shell movie, you know, the 1995 one, and even that portrays
the whole cyberization thing with a little bit more attention and like fear, because there's like
a scene where Matoko and Bato are sitting on a boat just like reflecting on how like they they
sure they feel really ambivalent, really mixed about their robot body. So they're like, oh man,
we're like so strong and everything. But like, we can't swim in water without sinking. And I'm
like, dude, what the fuck? Like, I guess I guess it might feel uncomfortable. You might constantly
feel weird about yourself. But Matoko in the in the series just seems to have not really any
serious issue. You know, she has trauma over the accident that required the robot body. In general,
it's like, dude, this is fucking awesome. And like, that's the attitude I have for technology. It's
like, oh, the internet. Oh, yeah. You know, early on it caused lots of creepy killers to run around.
I mean, that's still a thing. It has all those sorts of weird consequences of anonymity, fake news
and all that shit. But you look at what came before all news was fake news before the internet
because you had no way of knowing what the fuck was going on in the world. They don't know Obama.
So that's why the internet is ultimately the most like incredible for society and same way
cyberization. Yeah, it'll have problems and people who do not fucking respect the difference in
quality of life from before that invention came around will continuously naysay it the same way
that like so much like I think fantasy fiction looks back on like the 1600s and like, oh, no giant
corporations, no fucking worrying about bills. Yeah. And fucking every plague that could kill you
any single week with no soap to help you. No one makes fantasy stories with that shit.
I think I think the these things kind of go in cycles as they kind of like permeate popular
culture. I think at first it's like awe and wonder and mystique, then it goes to fear and then it
just becomes acceptance. And like a great example of this, I think is Star Trek. Because I think
the original series of Star Trek was like, when technology is so crazy, it's amazing. And imagine
all these things we could do with it, we could travel the stars and get solve all the problems we
can heal people instantly. And but by next generation, it's like, oh, now we have the Borg
and like how technology can be used, evilly. And then like Deep Space Nine had a lot of undertones
of like technology being bad too. And I think now it's just kind of like a technology is just
like a backdrop. Like, you know, you look at the Star Trek films and stuff, and there's no statement
on it at all. It's just there. And it's a part of it. And like, I mean, there's plot devices and
stuff. It's interesting. It's interesting, the emphasis that gets played on stories like that,
because like, yeah, like in JJ Abrams' Star Trek, like, there's basically no cycle of philosophical
discussions beyond like the big like, why is the big bad guy doing this? Oh, no, we blew up his
planet. He's getting vengeance. Like something like that, which is just, you know, bog standard,
like action story shit. Whereas like Ghost in the Shell. So like the 1995 movie that's the most
famous is, I don't know if I want to say this, okay, it is sort of in tone at least my least
favorite interpretation of like the Ghost in the Shell series, entirely because it was by far
the most negative tone like the technology in general. It is a very dour like emphasis. Whereas
what I love about every single other iteration, including a rise to some extent, is that those
ones like like Star Trek, like actually the JJ Abrams Star Trek, they sort of just fully embrace
the change that they showed. Okay, this is just a world where like cyborgs live among us and it's
just normal. There's nothing weird about this. And that is honestly, that is fucking progressive.
That is super progressive in a way that I absolutely love that it's just like, yeah, like, okay,
so I don't like, I don't know, I hate all Muslims. I hate all black people. I hate Jews, whatever.
But I accept people who have fucking like gigantic like, but that's not of me. That's me
a fictional character. What I'm saying, but it just like, so if you if you hate like races,
but you like like someone with a robotic fucking body or like full of cybernetic, like augmentations,
like on the progressive stale, that's you on the progressive scale, that's you being like
way, way more accepting of someone different from you, you know, so I don't know where I'm going
with that. But yeah, I hate minorities. That's the slogan you're going for is get nanomachines
become a Nazi net progressive. I want to say about the the the presentation of technology is
scary. I think a lot of it just comes from like needing drama in a story. Yeah, of like, if we're
going to make a story about sci fi and the whole point is the technology, then the question becomes,
well, how do we create tension? Well, what could go wrong with the technology? And it's kind of
unfortunate. And I also think that people focus so much on the downsides of something like, for
instance, the self driving cars, which are now a thing that's just out there. There's people just
on the road with self driving cars. And of course, the second there was a fatality in one of them,
because of the cars failure, it was like a huge uproar. And it's like, on the one hand, yes,
it is still scary that they are not perfect. However, you will probably die in an auto accident
driving your own car anyways. Like you're talking like near 100% chance. I mean,
did you know that there that that the odds of you getting into an axe in auto accident
is that you will get in one once every 15 years? Well, that is how it's not you have a one in
whatever chance it's you will be involved in an auto accident at least once every 15 years,
no matter how so when you have when you have one accident with self driving cars, it's like,
what are we pitching about again? You know, it's once it's become so you know, that's that's the
whole thing of people like being afraid people are afraid whenever they put their like their power
in the hands of something else, even if it is like statistically more reliable. Maybe there's a
yeah, it kind of adds in a degree of people's people's like imaginations can run wild when
they don't actually understand what's happening. So like, there's all this room to conspiratize
about like, Oh, like, let's say like, I don't know, like an Asian guy gets in an accident. It's like,
Oh, my God, the self driving company like car companies are trying to wipe out Asian Americans
and purify the white race in our nation. Holy shit. You said conspiratize that like some sort of
porno about who did 9 11. Like, yeah, it's Alex Jones x Milo Yiannopoulos. It's good shit. Yeah.
I don't yet. People that's just an instinct. There's a major instinct that people have to
be scared of the stuff. And honestly, I am too. I definitely I think it's just a human thing.
And I would really like to transhumanize that away. I would love to cut that part out to say
the solution would be just to somehow augment our brains to get rid of this primitive limitation
that no longer applies. Man, if only there was some topic we could talk about. It was all about
that. What would you think about like, like that being implemented as like, Oh, a special gas that
makes everyone like technology and never question it. And that you just send that gas out and then
people are like initially like, Oh, no, I'm being gas. And then they're like, Wait, this was a good
idea. That is a very interesting question. And there is a Futurama issue that deals with that
a Futurama episode. Remember that episode where they get a new robot in the office and Bender
like hates it. So he gets a compatibility upgrade. And what that manifests as is one of the most
interesting episodes. It manifests as Bender like goes to the place to get the upgrade. He then
seemingly chickens out and runs away runs to an island where he like rejects technology becomes
like a wood robot instead of fucking metal. Eventually, like he comes back to land to lead
an uprising. And in the uprising, like he gets hurt and is going to die, except he's saved by the
new robot and is like, I love the new robot now, only to then wake up for the dream that this all
was in the upgrade center. And it was revealed that yeah, like this, this is what the upgrade was
for him, which incidentally is how I think about the way that I became compatible with making fast
YouTube content. I went through this whole rigmarole just to end up at the very beginning
where it was like, Yeah, make daily content, make fast content. That's, that's what you gotta do.
Oh, I guess, I guess that's the same thing. Yeah. So I mean, it wasn't an illusion. It was just
real life. That's that's the difference. It doesn't matter. The point is, like,
that is a very interesting thing. And if we could put it in those terms, if we could do things like
that, I like it. I think I have a handful of different because you know, due to you talked
about the whole a need for drama, but it's also need for drama plus lazy creativity, not being
creative enough and coming up with something that can go wrong without undercutting the entire value
of having that innovation in the first place, right? So like, for example, something with like,
like say post scarcity society, where we can simulate anything at any point forever. I had the
idea of like a, we like basically all of humanity gets together to make some computers that will
make more computers, it'll keep making more computers until they make one that is absolutely
intelligent, morally flawless, and will never betray humanity, right? So they make one, and then
they start expanding and colonizing the galaxy or whatever. So it's like 10s of 1000s of years go by.
And most humans don't even know about this because this post scarcity society is terrifying to most
people. So like, you can learn about it if you if you if you find out about it. And then like,
if you end up really depressed about that, they'll just erase your memories and put you back in some
other simulation, right? So people are put into countless simulations where scarcity is artificialized,
but everyone ultimately is happy. Everyone's given a life where they are given the illusion that they
could fail and end up succeeding, right? Maybe even with lots of stimulated humans, like fake humans
or all who are like dying Africans to make you value your own self, right? And so in the story is
that this AI that's like colonizing a pretty decent chunk of the Milky Way at this point,
finds some other some other fucking force that's like incredibly powerful at some other life form
that's beyond anything that we can conceive. And so the robot needs to figure out like how to beat it
and starts running specific test driven tests on humans to figure out like their behavior and
learn things from them. And maybe there's like one main human character in the story who talks to
the AI directly. You're literally pitching a full sci fi novel right now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And so
basically the robot has because like maybe the robot can't 100% simulate everything that the human
soul is able to come up with. And there's just things about this abstract entity out in out in
space that he can't understand. So he has to like investigate the human animal and like try to
he spends thousands of years, hundreds of generations evolving certain people to find
an outlier who can represent the same weird trait that this galactic force has. And that's the main
character. Someone would like this trait that no one could ever possibly have without specific
breeding. And I don't know if that's the fucking beginning of the story. Okay. Kind of sounds like
Neo. He was like kind of born with this awareness of the world. Yeah. My version of Neo, he doesn't
even just see the world in like zeros and ones. He sees the world in zero, one, two and threes.
Like he sees like all the fucking numbers. Whoa. Sorry. Sorry. Go on, Tom. You can go. Oh, that was
me. I was going to say to get to give us some structure here and to get hippo talking as well.
I'm curious about what transhuman thing each of you wants the most like what what do you want
a realistic one within our lifetime? Yeah, like what if like what do you hope? Let's say they can
roll it out and then let's say that we are in the technological singularity. So this stuff's
getting rolled out really fast, you know, like what what's the one you want to come next?
Hippo, do you have any like any things you would want to transhumanize like right now?
Well, it's it's always weird for me because I'm not constantly thinking of everything that
I do as a human being being like something I could get rid of or would want to get rid of
because I don't know what it's like to not have it. So I guess something that would just make
my job easier like the ability to write with your mind like you would think words and then
they would just type come up on the page ergonomic keyboard. That would be so perfect for me when
I'm fucking high because I can't write anything but I have a thousand ideas. Yeah, to make them
come out of your head and also to organize them in a way that's readable afterwards. Yeah, yeah,
that would be pretty great. That's important. I want to I'll go into mine just so I can sort of
lay the like let let you guys know more of what I mean. Though that was a good one.
Um, what I want out of transhumanism is basically autopilot. Like because I like setting I love
autopay for instance, like having my bills set to just automatic payments every month, having
everything just work automatically so I don't have to think about it. And I would like it if
something like like my personal upkeep could just be automatic. Like I don't have to worry about
for instance brushing my teeth. I've just got nano bots that do that or my teeth are just not
something that has to be taken care of or like, you know, my hair and beard are just set at a
length and like I don't I don't have to do anything basically. I can just do my job and not worry about
like constantly falling behind on personal upkeep because I'm too distracted by everything else.
That's what I want. Like first, you know, on on that front, you know how that when when you're
in a coma, they actually they sort of exercise your body for you. They stretch your muscles and
they move you so you don't get like bed sores as well as like keep you alive and able to function
once you come back. Like the exercising takes a lot of fucking time and a lot of concentration
and focus to do it right. But yeah, man, I'm totally with you. Like I mean, I know you can
there is a lot to be learned from working out like about self discipline and there's a lot of
good things that come from it. But like when you're in a position like I am where your life's
pretty figured out. And it's not that I lack the discipline per se so much as like I want to do
other things and I it takes up a lot of fucking time and energy, you know, and it doesn't always
leave you in the in a state where you can then perform sitting in a chair for the next eight
hours. That's an interesting thing about it's an interesting thing about that because like if
if things are just like easy for everyone to do, you know, the thing like having a perfect physique
or or whatever it stops being special and then everyone can have it and also like the discipline
thing if all these like transhumanist things are like, like, should they be expensive? Should they
be like this some sort of like you have to be a certain age or you have to prove that you're worth
all this stuff? Or is it just giving it to everyone? Like what's the moral thing? I think
I don't know. It's interesting to to the idea of like we'd all end up the same or it would stop
being special because that just means that the only people who are going to do it are people who
want it for like real like, I mean, everyone should be healthy because that's just better for
everybody. Yeah, it's not a hard decision, but still most people don't make it. That wasn't really
my point. I was just saying it, but like, like, I don't know. I feel like some people,
they don't, they don't all deserve all the like benefits of technology as like, I don't know. I
feel like there's some sort of a barrier to get into that. I think it'll make people better though,
like like people who, well, another thing I would really want is some kind of, you know,
we need ways to like control our minds better, I think. Like it would be nice if we had a
transhumanist way to, I don't know, alleviate insanity. Like I just feel like there is a risk
if like everybody becomes the same person or something. But like I feel like as we approach,
it would just be a change in like what we value. Like I mean, there was once a time where everybody
was healthy, you know, like because you had to be or else you fucking died. So like, well, okay,
maybe not, maybe help me like, yeah, I fit. Yeah. There was a time where there wasn't
fat slobs everywhere, you know, right? True. True. And it didn't, it didn't mean that
everybody has to do the same thing. It just means you can change your focus elsewhere. Like a guy
who, like there's some people who are way into fitness and that's their whole identity. But if
fitness was just something taken care of, they would probably just do something else. You know,
like that just wouldn't, it just wouldn't be something that is somebody's identity. But
something else might be, something that we didn't know we had time for. My answer to your whole
question about, about what you would, what you would do, what I would do, what I would want the
most out of like a quick rollout of transhumanism would be another way to do the same thing,
essentially, which is also an expansion of what Hippo said, which is just having a computer
screen I can see and control mentally, then I would never, I could just go for a walk all day
and get all my work done. That would be the tits. I love that idea. But for me,
like in all sci-fi stories, that is the thing I least can believe is like controlling things with
your mind, because your mind doesn't work that straightforwardly. You know, like at least my
thoughts, they don't occur in like a narrative way. It's not like, it's not impossible to control,
because like I've seen disabled people with like robotic arms that are controlled with like wires
into their brain. I feel like if we have the ability to control our, like our bodies to the
level of precision that we do, like just if you move all your fingers at once, like I'm doing
right now, like that's a lot of precise control that I have. I feel like it is possible. It might
actually take a lot of effort to do like as a person. I'm just wondering like if, let's say I'm
typing with my mind, is it going to only type the things that I want to be typed or is it going to
type every fucking word that's in my head of which there are thousands? The assumption is that you'll
get a little extra, a little chip, a little tiny bit of a little brain matter that will take care
of all that. Just like, yeah, just the same computer codes can now be thought. The way I would assume
it would work or that I imagine is that you're not like thinking a word like in your head the way
you would think a word now. You're imagining or controlling a pretend arm typing on a pretend
keyboard. Right, because when you're typing, you're still thinking of the end words you want to type.
So this is just taking those motor actions and translating them into the head screen itself.
You're using that same thought process like, okay, now I'm going to type this sentence after I've
thought about what it's going to be and instead of changing that into a physical motor action,
you're just directly putting it onto whatever this display is. But hey, ultimately we are talking
about fiction. I'm prepared to say like, yeah, we could figure that out. That seems fair to
you. Did you want to add anything else or can I go? No, that was it. Okay. Mine is a little bit
further out and possibly not even real or could be done. But what I want the most is I want the
ability to detach consciousness from the physical body. And that could mean either to like physically
body swapping so that I can be a big slut and fuck dudes. That'd be cool. Or like the ability to
sort of, and this is like next level shit, but like uploading your consciousness to the cloud,
to the internet. I don't know what that's like. If you could have an android body, if we could swap
our brain into someone else's body, would anyone in here remain male? Because I know I would not.
Well, not all the time, certainly not. Long term, I would want to remain male. I mean, I do like
being a guy. I would reevaluate what it even means to be male in a world with that where
that is the case. So would everyone. But I'm pretty happy being male right now. I would probably be
both. I don't see any reason why not to be both. Like at the same time, I mean, the body would just
both. Everyone in the future will just have a dick and tits and it'll be great. I wonder if after
you do the other one, if you'll be like, actually, it's not all it's cracked up to be. Like once you've
been it, will it just change your perception of it entirely? I'm sure it's gonna end sexism. It's
great. I'm sure it'll have an effect. You know, though, what this does make me think of a lot
is the I give brought this up a little bit. Like if this stuff gets implemented to some degree,
imagine the incredible gap that will develop between people who have this shit and people who don't.
I think that's probably the most terrifying part. And there are times when I'm always wondering,
like, do the super elite already have transhumanist benefits that we just don't?
Maybe, man. Maybe. See, I'm not afraid of that because I'll be in the transhuman camp and I'll
have a rocket launcher in my arm. And so if all the if all the proletariat are like, we're gonna
overthrow you because you fucking pieces of shit, I'll just be like, and kill all the more people.
Yeah. Classes and boys.
I think in order to be in that camp, you need more than 350,000 subscribers. I think the wealth
gap is a little bit bigger than that. Pewdiepie is gonna be the only robot YouTuber. He's gonna
go around assassinating the media. Yeah, and the media. He's gonna upload a video where he gets
some people in like a third world country uploading death to all flesh bags and he's gonna
gasp like, how could they say that? Indeed. I look forward to the racial slurs that develop
for transhumanists. It's gonna be fun. We're really talking about the boringest parts of
future novels. Like, oh, the despair. Oh, the weird weird words we come up with. Yeah, okay,
skip this chapter. Well, yeah, but like the whole like poor thing, like I assume if we have like
all this super technology, we'd get to a point like where there's no reason we couldn't give it to
everyone, but then my problem would be if we're still operating under that kind of model. Yeah.
If capitalism is still real, like why would we give it to them? And it's possible that like
nothing that someone who doesn't have these abilities could ever do could like get them to a
place where they can like afford to do this. I'm just wondering at that point, if we get to the
point where you can literally, you know, have a cybernetic body, we get technology to that
degree, like would we even have problems with like means of production at that point? Like I
can't even see capitalism. Those are separate issues. This is addressed in an interesting way
in a show that the first half of which is amazing. The second half is a dumpster fire called Cado
where an alien life form shows up on earth and he's trying to advance humanity as fast as
possible, basically. And so he comes bearing gifts and the first gift he gives them is these
little orbs that have infinite energy. And he's like, he's like, I want everyone in the world to
have this, but like the government and what's it called the United Nations are like, we want to
have control over it and have sanctions. So basically he teaches people how to just make them, like
how to make these balls, so everyone can have it. And he was like, what these people don't
the government's not understanding is they're worried about like this being an arms race or
a power struggle. But the fact is, if everyone has it, there's no need to fight over it. Like
everyone can have this. That's true and all, but it is possible. Like if everyone had nukes
right now, it's possible like North Korea, if they had overwhelming power would just destroy
everyone else. So that is a real concern to have. So I'm with the UN right now, but okay, go on.
No, that was it. That's all I had to say.
That show goes right. It doesn't, it does not continue to explore this amazingly interesting
situation it's created. It turns into a terrible action show.
Talking about that in regards to say like scarcity, right? For example, we're entering
a situation where more and more shit is automated and people are concerned about humans having jobs.
The thing is, every time a robot replaces a job, it makes living on the earth a little bit cheaper.
Like imagine we just have robots for like everything, we have robots that construct a house
and like refurbish it. And also the robots deliver the pieces of that house to the building site.
And also robots mind and cut down the resources from planet Earth to make those parts. So if
everything is done through robots, let's say even the administration of the business is done through
robots, then the only thing you're having to pay for is the energy spent operating the robots,
which the robots could themselves be mining for making even the obtainment of energy resources
really cheap. Meaning in a society where everything's done by robots, basically,
there's not necessarily much need for money if we just skip straight to the far future. But the
problem is that moving into that progress is sort of blocked or clogged up by like laws and social
standards that are in place to keep people from getting jipped out of work or finances. Stuff like
the minimum wage, like for all it does to help people not get fucked over, it also kind of
fucks over progress in a lot of ways. And yeah, you know, you're not wrong. It's a complex thing.
Yeah, transition to that. Everything about the way our system, at least in America right now,
is adapted for the current situation we found ourselves in. Well, I guess you got to actually
argue it's adapted for one like 50 years ago that we're still trying to catch up to right now with.
But probably even before that. But nonetheless, like you're entirely right. This getting to these
positions is going to be a very difficult struggle in a very, you know, transition period where people
are displaced. That's right. That's right. What if what if what if Rick and Morty was real?
Hey, Rick's got a robot body sometimes. That's pretty cool. It's pretty cool.
That'd be cool. Tom, you haven't answered this yet, have you?
I have not answered it yet. Right, right. I mean, I guess mine's just really fucking petty
compared to everybody else's. The one thing I'd want is to just like, I've always been disgusted
and ashamed in the fact that our flesh and blood bodies are so fragile. Like it's just like, oh,
like you have like, one heart and if it something happens to it, you're fucked, like we can kind
of hopefully stitch something in there, but you got to wait around and it's not a good chance,
like, like it just blows my mind that we can't just swap it out. So if we're going to do transhumanism,
what I think the first thing that should happen is either nanomachines that can
enhance and repair organs so bodies don't die and don't break down literally metal gear rising
nanomachines. Yeah, that's right. That's right. That's right. I mean, it just that just seems like
the most logical thing because like, I long term, I would like to have a fully synthetic body,
not necessarily like something out of like Deus Ex Human Revolution where they just literally
attach metal arms onto me after sawing off my normal ones because like Deus Ex is a great example
of like why that doesn't really work because like in the world of Deus Ex, in the original game,
they have nanomachines, like that's the current technology. So like the main character,
JC Denton, he walks around, he looks pretty much like a regular guy, but his entire body is augmented
with nanotechnology. The whole point of Deus Ex 1 is that it's like, oh man, you've seen
robot guys, but this is a guy who's robot just as small, he looks like a normal guy,
but then you're telling me the later Deus Ex games from the following century regressed on that
idea? Come on, it's twenty fifteen people. The other games are prequels to the first one.
Yeah, they take place, I think, twenty years beforehand. So maybe a prequel to a futuristic
story is a dumb idea. I thought it was actually really interesting. I think it worked very well
because like the idea in like the original Deus Ex is obviously it's talking about augmentation
and stuff in general, but it also has this interesting idea of like we have all these clunky
big robot dudes walking around that like at the time that was like the shit and what you were
supposed to do, but now like you can't, they can't get the nanomachines in the way that normal people
being born now can because they already hacked off the regular limbs. So there's this dichotomy
of like now they're second-class citizens where before they weren't because they can never take
advantage of this new technology the way that people now can. And then in Deus Ex Human Revolution
it's talking about the impact on current society of having augmentations becoming something in
the beginning. You could already see in those games the foreshadowing of like the nanomachines
technology coming because obviously the series has that in its lore already. So it's two different
kind of conflicts, but that's like I just it just seems to me the Deus Ex original game that's kind
of like the robot body I'd want or like the cyber brain robot body out of Ghost in the Shell. That
just makes more sense because I think it's just it's more advanced in general like I wouldn't
want to have this big giant fucking hulking arm because like the main character in Deus Ex Human
Revolution his tech looks really like slick and nice and shit, but that's because like it's the
most expensive fucking crazy shit they goodbye. Normal people walking around that you talk to
look like fucking Gundams and not in a good way. That sounds kind of dope, but you know once we get
once we get really deep into this shit like like remember in Ghost in the Shell how there was like
the president of one of the companies is just like a dude in a fucking box with like tiny little
like that's like the coolest thing ever. Dude I wanted to talk about this because you said like
eventually you want to disconnect consciousness from physical bodies and this is something I
think about a lot because I love transhumanism as a concept, but the thing that I always wonder
is like what's the end game? We're going to keep pushing this forward and forward and forward
and the end game seems to inevitably be to abandon physical reality entirely in my opinion. I think
that sort of or make the form that you that you sort of host in like it could be anything.
My my my thing is like what if you just existed digitally like what if you just there was no
like the physical because like no matter how much we like augment ourselves with like human
like like humanoid cybernetic bodies or whatever even just like non-human cybernetic bodies we're
still limited by being physical of having mass of taking up space and so like if you lived completely
digitally like think about it this way when you're on the internet and you go to a website you don't
have to travel from google physically to the next website you just go there what if like that's how
travel in general works like if you were just digital like first of all there'd be no need for
construction because everything could be made instantaneously because it's digital so there's
no worrying about resources resources are finite or infinite not finite anymore you're not dealing
with finite resources like oh someone needs a house just drop in the house.exe and it just builds it
so like there's nothing to deal with that. The thing with all that and this is this is like the
line I draw because digital enhancing your body so that you can do things in the you know in the
real world way better you know getting rid of the the need to sleep and all that sort of stuff
that's fine but when you start talking about living entirely as digital beings I'm like well a digital
being doesn't need a house he doesn't need anything he may as well have just killed himself.
Well no no that might my point is that when we get to this point of being a physical of being of
abandoning physical reality entirely if we get to that point well you have to actually wonder like
can our brains even cope with that because if you're not a physical being anymore and let's
why would you get in your car and drive to work why would you even have a concept of like buildings
and roads you would just you would just be like energy basically a consciousness that exists
and like could the human brain which has kind of obviously evolved to deal with the limitations
of physical reality adapt itself to a reality where I can't comprehend it of being just like
thoughts and math or like thoughts and consciousness that kind of just can
sift and move around somehow and interact with other things like I don't even know how to work
it's beyond clearing my comprehension. That's why I'm gonna actually lay down an actual like solid
like a die in the wall or lie in the sand prediction right you see people in the past be
like oh yes eventually computers may only be the size of two refrigerators by the year 2000 you
know but in some people who hit it right on the fucking money you know like oh man this whole
internet thing I think it's gonna bring us all together and it also isolate us and create weird
anonymous people right some people are out on the money so I'm gonna I'm gonna take my chance right
my prediction as I sort of alluded to but earlier is that when we inter-post scarcity be it because
we all become digital concepts or because we have 3d printers and intergalactic travel and
and we have like nanomachines that protect our bodies forever one way or another once we enter
actual true post scarcity it's only a matter of watching those rpgs rts stat bars on the galaxy
go up waiting for that resources to be mined from our solar system and other stars when we get to
that point my prediction is that people will have a mass exodus from actual awareness of lucidity
right of everyone will just go into simulations right be it actually constructing a simulation
and like living in it or just building a program you know like like 1950s american housewife.exe
boom you now think that's you your memories are totally altered and like once that simulation
of you version dies and you become conscious again you're like oh okay so now i'm gonna do this or
that we just come up with all sorts of weird fucking lives for us to have and you know and
we just exist like that forever and ever and ever and that's basically it I think that basically
works my my just feel like what's the point like why would why would any of that ever exist for
anyone my concern is that like if you upload yourself to the cloud then there is there just is no
more you you are just part of the cloud it's just well the cloud is just everybody it's just a
collective conscious because like you have all the information there is you know like if you
are a part of the information then like basically you know what everyone else is thinking because
it's all in the cloud you know like you've basically you're just a part of the the overall
partitions if you want there to be it's not you have to I mean they would they would have to be
heavy partitions for it to mean anything to a human going into the divisions between individuality
wouldn't be the access to information would be the interpretation of it because that's how
information works right now you can give two people the same information they can extrapolate
completely different results well okay you know i talked about like computer brains right so human
brains right now is a computer that is always running right is all even in a coma it's always
constantly going through its program loop right and whereas you know a hard drive or a program on
a floppy disk or whatever can just be inert right all the data is there but it's not moving so you
could program something on a floppy disk to be like oh man when i'm running i want to eat food
food.exe where the fuck can i get my food right but if it's just the floppy disk not being run
it's inert data not moving it's not alive right so presumably if you want an accurate if we're if
we're already assuming that we're having accurate representations of the human brain one prerequisite
is that we're already running right we're not just data on a floppy disk because then we're dead until
someone boots us back up right so if we are running then presumably if it's an accurate
representation of the human mind there is going to be a hey i need uh more of my fucking food value
can i please get my food variable please can i please get my human comfort variable i need it
right so for me it's i don't know i feel like that's kind of like a really obtuse
his hair here's my ex let me give you my expectation of uh my final form of transhumanism
that i imagine and even longer beard that the despair the disparity will be pretty massive
because even right now like think about the information disparity between someone who like
not only has a smartphone but uses it all day to use the internet to access all the worldly
information and like someone in like a tribal society in africa or something like the information
disparity is unbelievably i just imagine people in that tribe yeah well i imagine that people in
some tribes out in the world like literally have no concept of what the world is at this point
you know like there's no way to bridge the information gap that's at that scale so i'm
imagining that yes there will be a way to have a partitioned mind in a machine the people with
the partition minds they're going to be the uh Babylon like it's just people fucking around
like like people just my mind's in a computer and i can do anything now you know like my life's
going to be nothing but fucking sluts all day like that's that's the partitioned minds
then you have the people who join the collective cloud conscience who all mind meld into one being
and they're the ones who within like a year solve how to get off the planet and they fuck off
and they're like look humans y'all got a choice you can either mind meld with us and get the
fuck off this planet or you guys can hang out here until the planet explodes and we're all like
you know what giving up my individuality scares me too much so i'm not joining the
cloud i guess i mean i don't digi it's very it's very interesting digi that you refer that you
use the word babel on there because i think that is a very accurate word to use uh because you know
tower of babel on and all that and what this this whole discussion what we're what we're kind of
with our ape like understanding in our in our our you know crude human matter brushing up against
at the top of this is like where does what what lies above the consciousness that we now have what
happens when we all meld ourselves into a greater collective that has all the processing power of
the entire species and i like i that is entirely what the end of the you know of course the most
famous most successful ghost in the shell movie is all about because that's exactly what happens
with the puppeteer the puppeteer you know access if find some way to access like to basically upload
him herself itself whatever to like this network and motoko briefly briefly experiences what that
would be like and in both the manga and the anime in the movie rather like she basically sees the
face of god for a second it's it's it's portrayed in this angelic way and i think that is a fascinating
way to interpret it because i don't care about religion at all i think it's bullshit and god
doesn't exist but i'm happy to accept that what people think religion is and think god is could
just be some higher level understanding that maybe maybe in history sometimes people have tapped
into for brief moments it's it's possible in some weird way that i don't understand i mean the
point of it is i don't think to vote the point of it is there is a higher level of consciousness
than what we have it might not be anything like what we think existence or consciousness is right
now but there is something above it maybe it's even just so much consciousness and processing
power in a place that it makes like our like like her basically exactly like her where everything we
experience now is like incredibly slow motion and incredibly basic compared to what that that thing
can process and to become a part of that is to completely lose what you were before and to
become something just godlike yeah you know like okay so the whole thing about like the collective
right i'm gonna like really like like shit on the idea of a collective i guess ironically
according to the memes but like uh fucking what i understand about computer hardware i don't know
of anything i don't know like i guess there might be some big old fucking matrix somewhere in some
facility that people have been constructing i guess but like the the actual internet is not
like that at all the actual internet is just a bunch of different servers with a bunch of
different fucking wires you know there was one time not too long ago where some fishermen just
dropped a big fuck off anchor uh down to the ocean i happened to snap a particular uh ocean line
and like some random south american nation was without internet for like a couple of days because
they had to fix that right there is no like central place where everything is everything is like
like uh f to p or whatever no no it's like it's like torrents right it's just one thing
pure yeah peer to peer yeah one thing go into another thing go into another thing right you're
entirely right you're entirely right it's like what exactly would be this collective i'm not saying
you couldn't very easily construct okay here's just like a basic version the basic version of what
i'm sort of describing here is like okay what if you could just access the internet from your brain
at any time like that's like the first step it would be like okay now i just like know everything
now i just i know everything so this is this is different now i i am a different person than
what it was before i knew everything and that's just like the first time what if you could then
communicate with everyone in real time instantly in addition to knowing everything okay it's
essentially oh that's what you mean different essentially you already know everything on the
internet if you count flipping out your phone and then reading it into your eyes as knowing it
because essentially your phone with its access to the internet is essentially a memory bank that
just takes longer to up to to to get into your server than uh than just having it in your brain
directly would be yeah that's kind of an interesting thing how like the definition of of memory works
like that like uh i was actually thinking recently like if someone did like a like a memory swap thing
where suddenly you have like let's say a memory edition right let's say you like invade someone's
brain and you have all their memories and now you have control of them right i'm like would you
just suddenly you wouldn't have like the sudden moment where you suddenly remember everything
about their lives it's rather let's say you get up in their room right you look at your kitchen
you're like oh hey i suddenly know where everything is you remember each thing as you need it so
essentially being part of this that's how memory works yeah you just you just be able to know what
when you need to know it so you could very well still have a pretty big disparity of intelligence
regarding like how well you can like actually interpret all of that information so yeah okay
that makes a fucking interesting thought um i always imagine the cloud is like a beowulf cluster
of brains like at the end of psychopaths oh yeah like sorry i well i don't know it's usually just
down to the question of are you willing to just go into this unknown thing because nobody can
nobody in an ai digital form will be able to accurately explain to you exactly what it feels
like in the lifespan of a human they just can't do it so you have to just take a you know jump in
or just really interesting hippo because the stuff you're the way you're describing it is exactly what
the first episode of serial experiments lane is about which is where a character kills herself
so that she can be only exist in the cloud and she's basically like mass emailing people telling
them like you should come here because it's it's the most liberating feeling like it changes
what you are and basically lane ends up following her into the cloud based on sheer curiosity about
like what is it like to have that you know that's true i mean you know personally i i when it comes
to that question i am not convinced that it would be better i'd be terrified if my life if my life
was terrible and i was gonna kill myself anyway i would do it by jumping into a digital big old
computer thing right sure yeah that's like actually i'd like to like bring the whole discussion
over to that idea if we could is like let's think realistically like forgetting your ideology and
actually incorporating what level of fear or you know inertia you have inhibitions you have an
adopting potentially dangerous untested technology or not completely tested on the actual public you
know we live in a fucking note seven society here technology that you know could end up having
unforeseen consequences like what would you actually do as a preventative measure or like
how quickly would you adopt it based on the information i'll i'll tell you for me like
i even right now even though i made the case for why it's safe earlier i still would be
uncomfortable driving a self-driving car indeed the only way i'd be comfortable enough is if
most people were doing it basically i'm a fucking sheep is what i'm saying like i will probably never
be an early adopter no i'm not because i want it to be i want it to already be perfect by
the time i get there and agree it's a different thing to be an early adopter when like okay there's
a new phone out okay i'm gonna rush in be the early adopter as opposed to like my fucking car uh you
know that's like it's a different level of state partly partly it's because i will i won't learn
everything about it i want someone else to be i want it to be something that like because let's
say you you fuck up your smart car how many people can fix it you know like how many people
understand what's wrong with it do you know what's wrong with it you know even people who know cars
won't know what's wrong with it you'll have to go to tesla the google corporation you know if it's
if it was everywhere if it's gotta imagine the google algorithm oh tom you took the fucking algorithm
right out of my mouth yeah like and even with smartphones you know i didn't come in until
the fucking note three was like my first smartphone like i because it wasn't prolific enough that i
immediately understood it and it was only once everyone had one and i got what you could do
it was basically the day i saw somebody playing super mario 64 on a phone that i went okay this
technology has come too far for me to ignore it anymore you know right on the bell curve you're
like you're the you're the late majority slash laggard when it comes to things in general i would
say um i would say early majority of depending on what the technology is and what i think my
use for it will be like for instance if we start having optic implants you know my eyes i'm afraid
about my eyes like sometimes my eyes hurt for no reason and i feel like it would might be better if
i had specialized you know like if that technology if the technology gets rolled out where like some
people have augmented eyes and then now there's an entire new field of film that you can only watch
if you have specialized and and my favorite animators are working in that field like that's
where i'm going to start getting convinced you know you got to draw me in you got to make me
think that my life's going to be better than it is and i'm fairly happy with my life so like i don't
need i'm i'm definitely someone i'm someone who's more like willing to take a chance if like if
it intrigues me i'd probably do it i think the problem for me would be cost because i have no
fucking money but uh in terms of willingness yes the the interesting thing is like is there a line
this is a question i wanted to bring up to people because it definitely is for me is there
a line that you won't cross is there some if they is there some sort of transhumanism that you
feel like no i'm not going that far what is my life right now because if like hippo said if i'm
depressed and everything's going wrong fuck it throw me in the cloud like if my life is miserable
especially like let's say i became like a vegetable or something oh yeah do do anything to me like
fucking get me out of here like i don't need to be in this body anymore but like if i'm as i am now
where my individuality means a lot to me it's difficult for me to imagine just giving that up
for you know for the documented thing that people don't change that much once they're past a certain
age so even if right now i began to see like the entire population of the earth adapt to let's just
say i augmentations everyone's getting robot eyes to then to sell myself on the idea of going into
the doctor having him literally cut the eyeballs out of my fucking skull to replace them with something
else i'm just saying it would be a hard sell because i don't know anyone who's had their eyeballs
cut out of their fucking skull i've never seen it done like like it's gotta be because it's gonna be
an incredibly expensive procedure and if it's not expensive i don't want it because they're gonna
fuck it up like i want the best scientists in the fucking world uh augmenting my eyes you know
it better not be some fucking quack doctor yeah for me unless the technology is that easy yeah man
when you imagine imagine when this technology is finally out all the fucking my vision is augmented
memes that would resurface dude like so for me there'll be a whole new class of of memes you
could only understand with those eyes oh just like just like fucking uh what's that what's that movie
with the obey and shit they live it'd be a whole thing live meme scape there'd be reddit posted
everywhere it's about weighing the different levels of risk and weighing the different
levels of value so like you know if uh if they got nanomachines that make you swear hey if you
fall a 50 foot gap you come off with a scratch or get hit by a car you might have a broken bone
right and it's like oh there's there's like 10 reports of someone randomly dying from those
nanomachines every year i'm gonna go for that you know because life is dangerous never knowing
you could fucking fall on die right so i think i'd go for that assuming it's not too expensive
if there's something that's like a little a little dude you know that if if nanomachines came into
existence and like the death rate in the world dropped from like 100 million to like 10 people
be like oh fuck those nanomachines man they're killing people out there they're fucking killing
people that's humans for you that's humans for you yeah i mean the thing the thing that the line
that i wouldn't cross for me personally and maybe as if time goes on and technology gets more advanced
that our understanding improves i could be swayed on this because i'm i'm willing to say that could
be swayed on anything really if you present a good enough argument i know what you're gonna say
jewe technology i hear you know i cannot i cannot cross that you got me no um i is i would be more
than willing to have my my body augmented as long as i knew it was safe i would have the
willing to have my brain augmented if i knew it was safe the one thing i just don't i don't think
i would ever feel comfortable doing unless you gave me a really solid argument would be would be um
to have like my my consciousness copied onto a computer because i think i think that your you're
still alive in your brain so like you can enhance that as much as you want but as soon as you like
kill my brain like i'm dead a copy of me is existing so are you saying are you uncomfortable
with the idea of just like there's you and then they make a copy and then there's two of you or
this like you're transposed from here to there i'm saying being transposed is still right because
you will be dead you will die yeah there will be no transposition it's a copy paste and deleting
the original file the the only way i've been i've been thinking about this before the only way that
i'm at all like comfortable with that is that what's that ship the ship of thesius or whatever
like that model if we can if we can like plug in my brain to the computer and slowly piece by
piece we move little bits of me over so that after a while i'm like halfway on halfway off
and then we keep doing that until now i'm all the way on the computer even then it's kind of like
a hazy maybe you're still dead i think you're still dead right well the problem i don't have an
answer i mean i think that doesn't really come into the thing like it's you know if you're you're
just slowly being copied that's all this whole this whole discussion it's the same as teleportation
like like you're killing yourself and but you know you as you understand may i remind me it's
gonna be around when it comes to the teleportation argument i always have to remind everyone
that every seven years there is no same atom in your body that was there seven years ago
yeah you are literally a wholly different person every seven years it's the it's the it's the
continuity that people value that's what's mad and that's that's why i think the ship of damocles the
ship of thesius whatever it is that models whatever it is that sort of makes sense that to do it that
way as long as there's continuity you're conscious the entire time you're slowly transposed for one
body to another i mean it makes no sense i'm more i'm more willing to entertain that than a
than a snap cons copy yeah yeah guys yeah that whole discussion is based on a really stupid axiom
that oh you have to delete the original that's absolutely not a thing at all there's no reason
why you couldn't just copy it some people it's it's a whole separate issue though like yeah like
am i comfortable with there just being another me i would have to think about and that's that's
like a separate question i think it would be really funny just like just like in a homestuck with
little how the debu collective would be comfortable with oh yeah you wouldn't you fucking motherfucker
that happens in serial experiments lane and the alternate version ruins her life so you know it
can be scary well that goes back to the horrors of technology i would i here's what i would do i would
make a copy of myself in a robot body so that i could beat it up if it you know so that it's it's
for convents for self-esteem like fuck you dude i'm the no no what i mean is if it tries to
fuck up my life it still has a physical presence and it can't run and hide in the internet like it's
it's just it's just on a chip and if i you just keep it on a flash drive in your pocket you'll flush
it down the toilet as soon as it starts acting a bitch hey if fucking if fucking your clone is
not gay is beating up your clone like not violent is like self-flage elation you know what are the
laws here dude guys if i could clone myself like my brain i would like immediately start an animation
studio that's just me i would love to see debu collective videos about that every day i'm just
like man i just thought of a funny animation i could do oh fuck there's only one of you would
take two wait i could i could finally get a somewhat get what someone to do textures for me and do
all my video editing yeah imagine they'd be miserable but i'd pay them nominally we didn't
really think about that but imagine like the logical extreme of that what if like one guy was
like okay um i'm just gonna keep making copies of myself until i can fucking run everything
and then he just starts like and then like 90 percent of all people are this guy now he has to
have all the hard drive space oh my god it's shadow clone juicier and it's fucking bad and if the
worst part is fucking bad oh no no one's in the entire universe is never on time
oh get fucked man yeah the the whole thing would like having copies of yourself like if it was
like physical human clones then it would be weird like who you're a human being blah blah blah
but if you're a robot you're let you i can program you to not care about being the main one so i
can be the main one yeah i know but like um you can argue that i definitely am interested
and this is something like rick and morty explores a lot where he always makes like a clone but
there's something different and it's like usually they they just like he'll say you know this clone
doesn't have a sense of self or like it's not basically you can abuse this thing and it is not
a human rights violation because it's not quite human you know or it's not quite you and i always
find that really fascinating i always wonder what if i would use it like would i feel too bad
you know because like rick's always raising that like people you know other people who he
uh you know shows these clones are always like horrified and he's like yeah but you know it's not
it's not quite human i'm just saying you know i remember uh is rick smart enough to make an
argument that lets him basically do whatever he wants so he can find a way to justify you know
killing whoever morty just accidentally killed true you know i know like bill whittle a guy who's
like big into futurism and space exploration like he gets invited to like space x sometimes
stuff like that right and like he got invited to like some showing of some new robot like
animal thing it just like walks around on four legs but like intelligently reads the the terrain
in order to get around right and the guy and one of the engineers is like yeah it's pretty cool
bunk he kicks it like kicks it right in the head equivalent and like the and like the robot like
like like trying to like catch its balance and like steadily gets back up and bill was like
i had to restrain myself from getting mad at the man because i i felt like he had just heard
right i know and it's like i love watching videos of people beat up it's fucking it's
boston dynamics man boston dynamics the most evil people on the planet according to some robot
rights you know you know it's really it's it's so fascinating though because like it's it really
is interesting how we prescribe like uh moral consideration like that like it just because
it moves in a way that we've seen i mean things that we generally give moral consideration but
it was just like it was just like some random robot stiffly walking around even if it looked
more human it's someone knocked over like haha you know there wouldn't be any of the whole thing
about that to animals morality like the whole thing about like morality coming into the future
there's exactly one sci-fi fictional work that captures it perfectly duck dodgers in the 23rd
and a half century we're at the very end he's standing on this one tiny little fragment of
planet going i win that is morality in the 23rd century that sounds cool but i like i like what
gib was saying there we we we the the funny thing is people don't think about but like yeah we do this
to animals too people treat animals like they have quote unquote souls like humans do when they in
fact do not they definitely don't now pretty sure god addressed this directly in the bible uh but
none none of the less nonetheless uh the guy you don't believe exist is back in your argument well
yeah it's i use it when it's convenient sorry guys what a fucking blue-pilled cock
dude like okay so i was i was to answer finally the question i raised a while ago like how would
i adopt it right yeah this whole consciousness issue just cannot be fucking solved i mean maybe
there'd be some post singularity consciousness that could just convince the shit out of me
but then i'd be confused as to whether or not maybe it's just so smart it can trick me into
thinking it you know who knows but so for me the solution is pretty fucking simple like like i said
get like a body enhancing like body uh lengthening uh you know extensions or whatever and you know
try to and just try and do this now in my body as long as i can and eventually things might come
to a head and when there's no other choice then go ahead fucking upload me you know because i'm
going to die anyway whatever right yeah i think that's nano machines to body lengthen my penis
the sad truth here is that we were all born in leirang generation when it comes to this like
we can't like i really really hoping that i can taste a little bit of it when i'm like 70
well that's i mean i think we will all at least make it far enough for some augmentation but i
really want this exact same podcast to be done like every 20 years by a different like like the
next generation of us like our kids to do this podcast and tell us because our kids are all
going to be raised by us a bunch of fucking uh goddamn sci-fi weeaboos who are gonna like
rant about the glories of technology the whole time so i want to hear their opinions or they're
like oh yeah of course i'd be like we're going to they're all amish just like i want to know
they might be uh they're like oh why would i want my physical form like my ego is if anything the
only weakness i have i would i would love to be a part of the cloud you know like i don't i don't
know if this is likely to happen but i always kind of wonder if like what if uh will we hit a plateau
where people are just satisfied with a level of technology it's like where all your physical
needs are met oh why bother like i have another like prediction based on not really at the planet
but a prediction i agree based on different predictions that are right and wrong because as i
said you know you look at back in the past like you know 1800s people are like oh we think by the
year 1905 everyone will have jet packs who of course they will right um and like also let me see
what sci-fi there was like some sci-fi book from like 1870 where some guys go to the moon via canon
right and this was actually talked about in a book okay it was actually talked about in a book
about uh it was actually the art of game design a book of lenses by jessie shill but he was talking
about how at the time everyone kind of assumed that would happen or like like it's just sort of
made sense in sort of a pulpy sort of way because cannons at the time were getting a whole lot better
constantly right so the so really when you look at everyone who was wrong about the level of steam
punk that would happen by the night by the 20th century during the 19th century is because they
thought the same kind of rapid innovation steam technology you know machines and products and
stuff they thought that was going to just keep infinitely increasing and so the same thing with
that the same thing with uh the 60s right right right like lost in space like the year 1997 we're
going to leave earth and it's just because that's the whole space race was going on and like why
would that stop you know what it is i like that you brought the subdivided because i do sometimes i
lately i've had more and more doubts about computer technology actually advancing
because it doesn't feel like it's been advancing faster late right yeah exactly so yeah so like
like what i was saying before about like the internet thing right like we're computers in general
during the 20th century people thought like technology was going to advance more like with
machines or industry or something like that people didn't really see the whole computer thing coming
until it was too late and so one guy pointed out that they got like infinitely more powerful every
10 years so i can see everyone making the same mistake again which is that oh this whole progress
that we're making is just going to keep happening infinitely because that's our closed minded you
know primate brain assumption right but it could end up being something totally different it could
end up being just oh 3d printers fuck off 3d printers they just do everything now or it could
be something a fucking fidget spinners of course let's like hashtag 2017 they end up we end up in
like a post-singular society yeah we look up to the sky and the fidget spinners sun is just going
off and generating energy for everyone and we have like fidget spinners instead of hearts you know
oh you know what no i'm sorry that wasn't me me enough it's just going to be emoji emoji or the
secret to like all of life my prediction is that computers are going to stop the aesthetic of
computers and metal and sci-fi is going to get oh who cares and then they're going to go back to
they're going to make computers look like wood and then pirates are going to come back and i'm
going to be a pirate by the way give just hoping for a second dark age we can all just go back
yes a dark a dark age just aesthetic wise it looks like that but everything else is like
perfect we just turn all the lights off it's a dark age how's this how's this for a millennial
perspective when before did you said something like how technology needs to keep advancing people
won't give up because we need to get off the planet i was going to really say as a real counter
argument yeah well that didn't work for krypton now did it you idiot and then i thought for a
second i was like oh wait a minute well i was thinking what my train of thought went after
that is really we have to escape the universe because the whole universe dies eventually so
guys we've only got like six trillion years left we've got to do something exactly we're on the
we gotta rise above our three-dimensional limits and we have to
no incidentally that's what that show kato is about yeah unfortunately it doesn't explore this
we need to yeah you're right we need to break our 3d limits you may need to vibrate higher to
leave this earth of 3d to one earth of 4d or 5d going to the 5d is exactly what we need to do
yugioh 5d's was the answer all along here we go baby tom i want to just do everything on motorcycles
that's the solution i was really glad that tom um that you explained what you would do the same
way you did four years ago on uh on a different podcast because you really like i've thought
when i think about transhumanism i think about it in terms of what tom said about how like
all your organs and stuff can just fail and like that to me is what makes it feel urgent
like we could talk about this is like sci-fi concepts we all want but like when i think about
my fucking physical form and how shit it is and like right like my brother very fine dude my brother
and victor had to have his pancreas removed because it almost exploded but the pain not not the pancreas
i meant the um the appendix his appendix had to be removed because he got appendicitis and it
would have blown up and what happens if your appendix explodes is that it can damage your other
organs and kill you well what does your appendix do literally nothing the only thing the appendix
is there for is to explode and kill you uh so why the fuck have we not figured out like why is that
not just something we can remove at birth well because it's too dangerous to operate i hear that
every single time that the appendix is pointless that it can't be completely pointless it's that it
wants to have a point but it doesn't just like your tonsils like that's why if you get if you keep
getting tonsillitis they just take them out because they don't actually do anything we had them in a
time where we're like the air of the earth was different you know we're a perpetual transitional
form yeah there's so much there's lots of fucking design craft in our dna and it's bullshit did you
did you entirely right it digested plant matter i think i could be thinking the wrong thing whatever
it is it we don't need it because that's why they can just take it out like if you get appendicitis
they just remove the thing oh yeah and you you don't miss it oh and you guys zero cases of people
you guys know like goose bumps that's because it's supposed to make your first stand up on it
to make it look bigger that's right to make it look bigger to strength predators and shit
indeed indeed i did not know that incidentally yeah uh well does anybody have anything else
to say about transhumanism or do we want to move into questions because i got a bunch of good
trains humanism i like i want to be oh yeah i think i think the thing to take relish in is that
eventually we're gonna have to iterate on all this technology really fast because when the
technological singularity does happen and we have machines that are smarter than humans
we're all gonna feel really bad about it because we have fragile egos and that's when we're gonna
become i remember being in digi's kitchen one time talking about like a cgp great like one of
his episodes of the hello internet where he was like yeah you know guys like i don't know if i'm
really into like like a beyond human ai at this point because like think about it like yeah we
think they'll have our interests in mind but like they're more intelligent to us imagine if like
gorillas had invented humans imagine if gorillas made humans you think that would turn out well
and shade walked up behind me and said that all of them sucked
oh fuck i wanted to keep going but i just want to end on that no there's nothing i can add it's
better yeah it's pretty good um the most important thing about this is just this all needs to happen
before i specifically die absolutely the only thing that matters well they agree let's get a
move on to transition into questions because the first one is super relevant that i found okay um
from gray nine he asks scientists announce we will be in a post scarcity society by next week
what plans do you make oh fuck complicated uh i mean what i do is i quit my job immediately and
just start doing the content i want to do all the time i i guess that would be my first because
like i don't know what's gonna happen once it happens so i have to worry about all that
shit i have a really specific answer i would uh tell all those people who are uh poised to
adopt some of my baby hamsters no thanks man i'm printing myself some more cages and a bigger room
that's adorable i i would um spend i would forget about youtube because fuck it dude that's not
that important i would spend all of my time writing homes uh horse stuff oh yeah i would write
and i would make it twice as long as homestuck because i have all the time in the world so does
post scarcity society mean that none of us need jobs of course i think true okay yeah honestly i
probably stopped when we had to focus on other projects yeah i'm immediately off the internet
forever first of all um all i do is make really fucking weird shit with munchie that's my oh yeah
yeah all right right scarcity we'd all just got we'd no money yeah just hang out one place
does much still need to finish school in a post scarcity world i don't know but me and munchie
are just gonna hang out and like headbutt things like oh you know i'll make a whole like i'll make
a whole thing like other i don't even want to film this for myself i don't want to post this on youtube
i just want me and munchie to become so known for headbutting things that people start recording
us and like we get funded by like sponsorships and like movie deals you know on on that front
not the money funding yeah right on that front i would immediately go find a place for pcb hq
that's immediately what i would do fucking like man made island on the pacific bitch
wherever's appropriate i would be in the shape of the pcb it's just so it's really hard the only
reason i'm not doing that now is because of money i can't think of how to imagine the world without
needing money like i can't like doesn't it seem like the obvious answer is i'll just go fuck all day
like i'll just have sex and drink and smoke oh here i think there's nothing about post
post scarcity society that it's always interested me is people imagine like people frame it like
oh it's like going to be this utopia thing where there's no need to work or anything money is just
a me like the only reason people even really want money is because what it facilitates it
facilitates power it facilitates status yeah and like your desire for power and status does not go
away if you don't need money because you still have to have some way to obtain those things is there
no i don't think society is going to change as much as we all think it will just pull scarcity
mean that there is no scarcity of marijuana does that well probably 3d print it you probably
3d print that dude no like 3d print myself weed and watch everything ever you know you that's
what i mean already 3d print weed it's called planting it and growing it my friend he's not
he's not wrong but you know that that honestly does that does bring in an interesting question
because though the idea of like pcp hq it is a money making operation at the end of the day and
as tom said like that still will be necessary but like my plans for to get everybody here together
to do that do hinge on the idea that you guys will be motivated to make content you know to make money
and maybe that would change i don't know i see it in eight is that the difference between uh
priest scarcity and post scarcity pcp scarcity pcp is we all meet up in one place to make
the best content we've ever made post scarcity is we all meet up and we exclusively make the
blue glow like that's all let's play like all we do is let's play 24 7 because all we want to do
is play video games like so what i've come to realize now now that i've started playing video
games again um which i've been doing for the last like couple months i've been playing lots of games
and i realized that i have no real desire to do anything but play video games and listen to the
dick show because i feel totally opposed to that exactly we gotta we gotta no go ahead nate
oh okay but i was just gonna say i i know where you're coming from but but here's the thing
uh for most of my life i did exactly that i watched anime and played video games it's
it's only recently that i have felt the best about myself in my life that i ever have because
i'm finally accomplishing something but that's because made my life in a society where those
things are not helpful to do well but but that's no matter what we do humans are social animals and
we we want to have like i'm not i'm not afraid to say it like now that i have a little bit of
like power in society like i have an audience that respects me to some degree and people like what i
do and i have something to offer that allows me to have a little bit of influence it's it's those
factors that appeal to me inherently as a human male probably women too but for me for me personally
like a hundred percent of all the problems in my life are tied to my influence and talking to
other people so maybe that's why i'm going to the other regrets and perhaps i agree with either of
you my motivation for doing things is entirely because i feel like i have an obligation as a human
being to to to use my skills and my talents in the best way that i can the the only reason i want
an audience is because i need money and that's the best way to get it for doing the work that i
want to do and the only reason i bother doing like fucking gay youtube shit that can easily
generate money is because i need that money if i didn't need money i would do nothing that would
get me in that i would not focus on building an audience because i don't care about that i wouldn't
focus on money because it wouldn't exist i'm curious though i'm curious though doesn't your
top doesn't your work only have meaning because it has an audience yeah that's what i was gonna
bring up but for me i don't i don't think so at all well for me at least when i was younger
for the lirth for the first like ten years for the first ten years that i made things i had no
audience at all and i was right upset that i didn't but it didn't stop me from making it i wanted to
not because i want i mean of course you want an audience to see it but even if you had told me
tell me right now that like your project will never have an audience because i'm already working
under that assumption that's why i put so much effort now and trying to be more active on the
pcps i'm assuming this is how i'm going to make money and the content i actually want to do is
never going to get the level of success that would need to be my job but that doesn't i have no
intention of stopping to do it because that's like the only thing i feel that like gives my life
actual meaning about yeah for me it's i hear what you're saying it's just that specifically the
you're talking about consuming art though and like the the the use that art has in the world
is that people see it and then like enjoy it and stuff right so like isn't that just an inherent
part of the thing that i've been trying to talk about this whole time is is is that in the post
scarcity society people won't need huge audiences but they can all yeah like you know anything i want
to make right is for a few people i'm not yeah i want i want to make the horse stuck thing yeah
to impress anyone who likes home stuck and myself and close friends and if it's an audience of a
maximum of 20 people it wouldn't matter to me because that's all i was making it for i was
making for me and a few other people i agree with that it's like i don't be for everyone i'm not
saying i don't want an audience and i wouldn't like it i'm just saying it's complete the work
that i want to do i want to do because i want to see it exist you know it's you know it's interesting
that's why i want to go to to pcphq by the way is is is to hang out with you and the content made
like in let's play form can entertain a few people but the the the reason i would move is so that i
could hang out with you and it'll be like fun and i totally agree but this this is very interesting
to me this strikes me as a fundamental difference in what we're like what what our goals are because
my goal is specifically to communicate like my ideas to people and have them receive them which
is why like my my really primary goal is to is to package them in a way that both i enjoy
but that people will be receptive to so that they'll hear what i'm saying and like i think i'm right
so i want them to hear me and be swayed by my opinion so like that that's what i'm aiming for
the vehicle to get there is is open to me i think the difference between is because you're trying to
you're you're more worried you're trying to communicate your ideas like your videos have a
point like this is my opinion on something right right in order to make the the art i guess of that
you it needs to affect as many people as possible where like my like passion project is like telling
a story and like i don't need to prove it to anybody i just wanted to exist so i think because
the goals of those projects are different i totally get both of you because i there's like
when i make a video like here's this thing about anime that everybody's getting wrong like the only
real value in that is correcting other people's minds when i make like my music i don't give a
single fuck who listens to it like i if i have like one person buying it that's fine i just want
it to exist for my own sake because it's something that i needed to be off of my chest you know and
i think i would go much more down that road um if i had you know if i didn't have to worry about
yeah i guess okay like i guess i hear what you're saying specific plans if post guarantees announced
i would tell degi hey uh you know if you want to fucking have me edit any videos go ahead but no
schedule i'm not gonna write anything right i'm not gonna write a single video ever again if i
don't need money well i'll guess i'll just go watch anime occasionally and then also i think i'd
still i think i just spent all my time just making a game except uh it would have all the things i
wanted to be in a game rather than some of the things heavily censored that i'm planning on
putting it in my game well get what were you saying gib i was gonna say like in in this society
where it would be like all the artists are suddenly making what they want and all of the people on
youtube who are doing clickbait will die because they don't care about it oh yeah finally the art
landscape would change overnight you know what's fascinating i just watched like rice gums uh like
reaction to the to the roast of him or whatever and he was talking about like how this is what he
lives for he lives for drama like as a result of you know the content cop that just came out and
i was just like what kind of life do you live where you like this is your purpose in life to
respond to people talking whatever it doesn't matter i'm sorry go on gib the nothing else done
let me get our next question which uh dovetails pretty nicely out of that one uh vampire wait hang
on did you are these coming from the patron lounge yes these are coming how could you possibly
access such a place i need to know we're paying us for our amazing content then you would be able
to contribute questions to the show because uh you know uh fuck you otherwise um
what a great pitch vampire patreon slash best oh i was going to contribute to our personal
post scarcity society and give us your money yeah patreon.com slash the procrastiners okay there you
go which literally literally everything we just said about post scarcity will also become true of
our personal careers if the pcp made enough money to just be our day job it's very true very true um
vampire giffy asks a two-part question what is your best project that never saw the light of day
and what is the worst thing you've made that has seen the light of day
nate you could start us off if you uh if you want oh man i mean the the the first part things that
have not seen the light of day extensive work i mean i have not made anything that is good that
i have not released i was actually just talking to you guys the other day about how like i have
never completed a video and then not released it ever i i mean i don't spend time on things it doesn't
have to be completed let's just say like the best project idea that fell through you know
fell through i mean there's there's always a like that you've abandoned yeah like if there's a project
that you were working on that you feel like would have been amazing but it has not been completed
and i mean i'm well known to have taken a very long time to actually release my best anime ever
ghost in the shell which i but it will eventually but it will but there are several other projects
that i have not announced of that same ilk that like i know things about them and have produced
pieces of them already but they are there are ways out uh but in terms of things that got
dropped i mean there's always what me and ben talked about of the raise these bros which i actually did
make a song for uh for like it was going to be like the finale of t-bap or something uh but we
never that's what that was never got around to it yeah yeah that song floats around in my hard drive
somewhere all right oh and but uh in terms of things that are bad that i did release i mean
i think i generally make good stuff ben and i did a ice bucket challenge on t-bap a while ago
yeah that wasn't great that wasn't great though it did have a cool storyline where my glasses broke
or rather keg standard not me his glasses broke and uh that was very sad i don't know it's all
great everything i've ever made is fantastic i can answer it pretty quickly i mean maybe these
projects i mean i've had one idea for a song parody that would require like like a slideshow
animation in order to make sense and i've had it as an idea for like four years i've never told
anyone on the internet about it because i might still do it whatever i mean really the biggest
thing that i seem to systemically be unable to motivate myself to finish is like a big analysis
of the mario and luigi series because it's just overwhelming because when i really start to think
about it critically i honestly think there is enough there that's all original points that are
not redundant off of existing analysis videos of any game at all it's like it's like it's honestly
as dense with like things to talk about as like the star wars prequels so i mean not quite as like
culturally relevant of course not by a long shot but like it would just be a huge fucking project
that i could honestly spend a whole year on so i end up tensing up and just not caring enough right
if something reminds me about the current mario and luigi games that makes me upset it only lasts
until the afternoon and i just wasted like some hours typing up some shit on google drive or even
recording something so that's stupid talk about like the worst thing i've made i mean if you're
gonna be technical there's like a shitload of just boring tweets so just biggest failure in my eyes
was when i did a video on big hero six and like just has so many great analysis things to say but
i like that video yeah but i pushed it through so many stupid like misguided writing techniques
that it's like you really can't appreciate how much analysis is in it like when i was writing it up
until even when i released it was like months later when i went back to it and was like oh right
the audience hasn't all you say that's the would you say that's the worst thing you've put out or
just no one that is the most discordant from what it was yeah yeah yeah not all the worst thing of
course because like worst thing is a stupid thing to talk about when you're when you're an internet
content creator my right fellas but no that's the one where it's like i wrote it based on the idea
that you had just seen the movie twice and also taking notes like i was it's a stupid lack of empathy
with the audience like completely fucked up on and when i watch it back i'm like there's no way you
can actually appreciate my points oh and also i still was not even decent at audio narration too
so it's just hard to even listen to so when i think about it yeah the distance between how i
thought about it at the time versus now it's that one okay tom do you have an answer for this
i think the best idea that i've dropped and hopefully someday i'll come back to it when
i have the the skill to properly realize it because i think it's probably the greatest
idea i've ever had is uh it started out as a as a just a narrative story but i realized that the
point i was trying to tell would be way better as a game um i don't want to get too much into it
because like even to talk about the idea would spoil it and i do still want to make it someday
but it's a game that would have a dynamic art style and the as the art style changes throughout
the game it also reinforces the thematic points going on in it that's fucking cool damn um
it's got likes but that's cool it's it's oh god it's if i can that's the one number one reason
i want transhumanism probably need like another 70 years to get good enough to make this game
properly so get on it people um and the worst thing that i've ever released is everything
that was on my very first youtube channel that mercifully i deleted so no one can ever find it
thank god hippo um uh yeah i've i've got a thing uh the best thing that i never got around to
was an idea i had while listening to pink floyd and it was to animate the entirety of pink floyd's
the wall but replacing the characters uh in the songs with my little pony
i would i would imagine that's the best idea that never saw who is who is have a cigar about
who's the have a cigar that's not in the wall oh i fucked up it's the wrong oh god damn okay never
mind i also had an idea for animating uh the division bell uh to be about uh dick masterson
and and matters and that that whole thing not bad because a lot of those songs are like oh it
you can just imagine them talking to each other singing to each other like this
it's great but uh you know never ever gonna have the time to animate something like that
and also copyright would not let me monetize it afterwards so nope um but the the worst thing
i did publish was uh i don't know some why it's okay to clop you degenerate pony fucker
i've been on to you that's an okay no i actually like that video a lot i'm just mimin you i i i've
made like a couple like eh whatever sort of vlogs i guess i don't know i don't pay attention to the
my failures it's a bad idea i as a contact yeah you're going um i have no idea how to answer this
because i have so many answers for both like i have like gallons of unreleased content like
and and the thing is that these days i've sort of been going back through a lot of it and just
like releasing the concepts and shit like you know my my novel i wrote back in 2010 like for six years
that would have probably been the best thing that never saw the light of day but now i've gone ahead
and just released it unfinished under the internet um tons and tons of great story concepts my personal
favorite has always been um maho shoujo to henshin papa which is the the the magical girl and
transforming dad where separately a daughter and father the daughter becomes a magical girl and the
dad becomes a transforming hero and they don't they're not even aware of it but then eventually
they have to work together um but like i i just have like a thousand ideas i have tons of analysis
videos that have never been made album ideas songs that i have fully written in my head but
because i cannot perform instruments there is no way to translate them to um to the internet except
in acapella versions that i've released just as like proof of concept of their existence um
actually interesting you mentioned that digi i remember watching the diaries like the the
production diaries for uh that m dot strange guy he had for uh his third film and he showed this
production of like you can get a vst that um you hum and it takes that and applies it to any
instrument made the entire soundtrack oh my god i i need that badly fascinating that is the coolest
shit i've ever heard of yeah and if i can find it i will use it immediately that's always in the
back of my head of like if i ever start getting into animation for real and i need to do music
that's that's the way i'm gonna do it yeah and as for the worst thing i've made that's seen the
light of day this is equally difficult to answer because i've been on the internet since 2001
and like i've never deleted anything like there's some stuff that's set to private but it saw the
light of day at some point um what comes to mind first is the otaku sex hotline what what what i've
never heard of this i told i told this story in detail on a recent digi in may i think no on a
pub crawl a recent pub crawl i told this story but uh but to summarize i had a tumblr that was
supposed to be for people to like tell us about their like weird otaku-based sex hangups and we
would like give advice except the real reason it existed was so that i eventually could just post
my weird sex hangups and answer it myself and after after that happened which was probably
like the seventh post on the blog it completely died like no one everyone was just in abject
horror of what i had done what of anything you've released on the internet are you the most
ashamed of to think about right now if you want to divulge that well that was what came to mind
first oh yeah that's a good sign that or like just tons of writing about like otaku sexuality i did
that doesn't hold up uh back back in the 2010 or so um lots of youtube videos that are just
cringe worthy some of them are entertaining though like there's one digi bro digi digital boy cracks
open the double down where i just review the double down from kfc but i'm like so awkward and creepy
looking that it's like watching him like a murderer rapist eat a double down um there's just a lot
like there's tons and tons of content i've made because i've been on the internet for so fucking
long and most of it's most of it's cringe worthy i remember the time you pretended to be a pony and
you were running around that i'm very proud of that's awesome um i've rewatched that recently
because of victor being in that and just like that's what made it great poor poor guy i don't know
what the worst thing i've made like since becoming a popular youtuber is like there's a couple videos
i've made that i wasn't proud of like uh sort of infamously i had just hidden my um zanko notera
video because i thought it was so badly written um like there's been a few but not most of the
stuff i make has some entertainment value to it like even if it's not amazing there's something
good about it but if you go back through my history it's just a non-stop wave of infinite cringe so
yeah there's lots to choose from so my answer for both is everything i've ever made let's let's move
on to the next question um what loot will you drop when you die oh that's a good one wait who
who said who said that that's from dry bones god damn i oh i would definitely be a pile of sunglasses
a pile of sunglasses yes for sure for sure i'd drop like two mountain dews um a a pack of cigarettes
and uh and also sunglasses but of a different sort yes indeed i would drop uh basically economics
by tomas soul which you can't remove and you can't remove it from your inventory it's like
stuck in your inventory and it like takes up one weight and you're so pissed off at it forever
just like how it weighs on your mind that that forbidden knowledge every day to do
a yes i understand get what do you got i can't top that i can't fucking think of anything
you you'd uh it's just a hippo plush guitar uh yeah hippo plush that's that's or guitar strings
yeah that'd be good maybe a poof of hair that was good hey if we have any that's all the same
that's called cutting my hair or if we have that's your escape tactics you're like a wobba
we're gonna do any more just your hair we're gonna do any more questions you cut my whole body up
that was the true form doing any more questions i gotta go so i i guess i'll just leave now unless
we're done uh you can go ahead a little bit longer cool so i'm gonna i'm just gonna post in the
discord my answers to things by listening on my phone and if someone wants to read it out they can
yeah other than that i'll see you all right all right uh tom tom and you um i think mine would
probably be an unidentified stylist and when you go to identify it you find out it's cursed and now
you have good you have talent but infinite depression ah god damn i love the thoroughness
of that answer it's perfect oh man god damn bed would definitely be like a stylist in a vape for
sure for sure just the vape let's be real yeah you're right you're right it'd be a vape stylist
like two in one yes the ultimate combo i uh this one this one might be difficult but i thought it
was interesting because it's so precise duck chutney asks favorite character design oh jeez
full stop favorite character shadow the hedgehog yeah killer kills pretty good anime um i uh i
actually like ryuko is at near the top of my list for sure that's what i said ryuko doesn't very
ryuko in her um like her normal outfit is like extremely i like it a lot it's very good i also
like her transform because she does look like shadow it's pretty great um i don't know it's
going to sound lazy but i love everything about how kami looks you know i'm not really a big tattoo
guy he's yeah he's fantastic and the color design across the series unbelievable but uh i've never
been a big tattoo guy but just like this is not limited to anime by the way like it's any character
design that you right that's just where my mind goes i'm gonna come back with another answer
somebody else go uh oh i have a good one uh mind fang from homestuck i forget who that is
it's it's risco's ancestor the cool pirate's right queen apparently she's got that cool sword and
the in the coat yeah apparently i really like wants to shout out power puff girls z the anime
version power puff girls um what oh yeah those things were pretty cool i'm gonna have to give
my answer as the one character design that i've by far spent the most time obsessing
with which is remilia scarlet from toho of course yeah because i she's got everything immortal
lollies pink uh she's vampire i'm i'm into all those things and like just the way that even more
so than the character design herself the way that um artists will always draw her in like a very red
world like like like when you look at art of remilia the whole background is always different
shades of scarlet like and it's funny because it's her actual character design doesn't really
have much red on it but like it's just kind of interpreted as fitting into that world i guess
and uh i like yeah yeah um here's a grab bag just a couple uh i i love uh uh griffith i love uh the
way yeah griffith is dope um i just i i know it's expected but nia i just like nia's character
design is like so creative and awesome it's like unbelievable and uh and then finally uh her her
fucking hair like it's it's never been done before no one's ever had nia's hair and it's like the
best looking hair ever especially short nia is i yeah i love short hair nia with her with her pink
ass hoodie god she looks fantastic and finally uh ramza lugria in his second and third armor forms
not his basic bitch order of the north sky one that's for pussies there you go that's all right the
gobs asks what is your biggest pet peeve with amateur content creators um it's it's proceeding
proceeding a video it's it's proceeding a video with talking about how they haven't made a video
oh my god yeah dude fuck yeah or just like all the preamble the endless preamble up to the
fucking pretty much my thing is having to explain why you're making it having to like like just cut
just give us the content we don't need like the background of how you came about to doing it
you know because it's always the same story it's not like you did not have some unique epiphany
you just thought like it's almost always at first i didn't think the show would have much to talk about
but turns out it did and it's like yeah otherwise you wouldn't have made a video you know what honestly
i love those because now i just laugh when i see them i laugh the whole time like the the worst part
about those is that there's sometimes there's videos that i know are supposed to have an
interesting point and it bothers me so much i can't watch the video like i've had my cardinal sin i
still do that to this day i think i've recorded something today that has that in it you know what
it's not even a joke you know people have like and there's ways to do it fine like if you have a lot
of charisma or if you've worded well enough like it can be okay but like especially if someone's
stumbling through that it's just like dude fucking you had this in the editing bay you had time to
look at this and conclude it was not interesting you know the thing the thing i would suggest people
look at as like an example of how to do it good is because you know everyone likes to have an intro
or some sort of logo but if you watch tom scott's videos he starts his videos um just talking immediately
immediately about the point and he's usually on camera and always wears a red shirt his brand
is his face on the red shirt he doesn't need an intro he doesn't need a logo he just talks about
cool shit and everyone loves him he's a good boy so do that i agree um i and he's the only
fucking like like content every week youtuber i can name who does not stretch their videos at all
like they're always exactly he'll he'll fly to fucking alaska and only make a three minute video
out of it you know right okay yeah i remember that guy yeah he's he's good um i was gonna say i uh i
always am this isn't like a major criticism but people with just like very bad audio quality
that's just like a click off it's not like i hate them i'm just like okay i'm just not gonna watch
well you can't listen to it it hurts i haven't seen a video with bad audio quality you know
long time i i have but it's from it's not just the like clarity of the audio it's if you have
fucking noise in the background it's the fan noise if you got that if the noise is almost as loud
as your voice then it's like i literally can't listen to that you know but i just never i haven't
seen a video like that just like was trying i have some in mind but i don't want to shout them out
because i don't want to be mean um but there was uh like just like my hero trump instead of answering
this question i'm also going to answer the question that i wish i was asked and uh it's it's actually
it's the opposite of this it's what's what's something that annoys me about like too good
too pro animators and i will shout this guy out i don't hate this guy at all but like hold
in anime reviews i don't hate this man but what is what is baffling about his videos is the unbelievable
over editing and it's not like it is distracting visually how he will just say he'll talk for
like three minutes and animate every single word individually it's like i have to stop watching
because i'm like i cannot believe we invested the amount of time to go do this i've never made it
through that section of one of his videos before neither have i it's a brick fucking wall and i
don't hate the guy at all it's just like that just just like wow what what is this all right this one
i have no hate for you um gypsy ask oh and uh davoo's answer to that was complacency um gypsy
asks what's the worst recommendation you've ever given a friend um
my love fly across the country to come live with me i'll totally make vlogs you know davoo might
talk shit about that but but he grew he grew he that was a good experience for him to have i just
thought that'd be a really funny answer unfortunately he's not he's not in the call he's i hope he's
laughing his ass if he's listening still well it's edit in some laughs after this yeah uh
shit i i only give great advice i don't know well it's a recommendation so it could just be
like a show you told somebody to watch and they absolutely hated it i mean i've given a few
bad recommendations like that before hmm just where i didn't didn't i don't often i'm stumped by
this i don't often recommend things to people unless i know that that is their sort of thing
yeah but maybe as a so i guess i haven't really well as a kid i don't give a shit about stuff
yeah i'm like i'm really thinking back and i have pretty much stopped giving a shit what
other people do just in all aspects of life as long as it's not causing me a problem i'm just
too busy to worry about anyone or like you go figure out your life on your own go watch whatever
you want it's funny hearing you guys say this stuff because like i'm someone who is constantly
recommending things to everyone always like not just shows but like all i do is like try to
counsel other people on how to run their lives and i don't know why it's a compulsion of mine i
think it's based on my name because my name conrad it means honest counselor and i've known that
since i was a little kid and like tried to live up to it sounds like a calm to me so so like all
i do is try to like counsel people on how to run their lives and usually i give good advice most
people tell me i generally give good advice but sometimes i've given advice that has not led people
to a happier life sure i mean i'm thinking like my channel consists of a lot of recommendations
these days like recommending that uh takagi san anime it just that just comes to mind but that
that's great and everyone should read it i don't know yeah i mean when it comes to like youtube
stuff i recommend things that i like and i explain why i like them but i don't know how i can tell
whether somebody was like misinformed unless they tell me like i don't feel like people were
misinformed and they they actually didn't like it yeah based on what i said in my video by the way
this is the worst recommendation you've ever given a friend not just random strangers uh yeah well
yeah i mean i don't know i guess i could i i i know this is ridiculous for me to bring up but like
i tried because i love it so much i tried to get my friends to watch gurren log in with me in in
college and like god they were just not into it they just did not give you never like tried to like a
wingman for somebody and then the girl turned out to be shit like told someone to pursue
a relationship or like a lifestyle choice that just didn't work out for the ones who always
fucked up in those choices in those situations we're the friends though like they didn't just
go hard enough on whatever it was that i was demanding that they do tom you know like they
fucked it up or do if you're still don't talk to people in real life so this never happens
oh jesus our knees are also an aspect of me like i'm i'm never really the one giving recommendations
because i'm not the one talking to people i felt like when i asked that question if anybody had one
that would come to mind immediately like like that's the kind i think that guy was hoping for a real
juicy story but uh i think you're all anti social fucking peasants that just lock ourselves in our
rooms and make youtube videos so indeed let me throw out this question from the from the twitter here
from uh at this dorky guy oh great name dude uh yeah it's uh guys have any opinions on game length
does anyone feel like you're owed when you buy a 60 dollar game where this fashion comes from
this is twitter that's just twitter okay does anyone feel like they're owed a certain amount of
time when they buy a game of a certain price i hope the game is as short as possible even when
you pay like 60 bucks for i won't pay 60 dollars for a video game like oh that's just being idiot
just like monkey island told us not to way back in the day i live by that every day
no talking about i i don't like paying money so when a game is more than 20 bucks 20 pounds
i'm not i'm sort of like i really really need to i have me i need a reason to play this i'll you
know yeah i did yeah it's too much too much um 60 dollars never doesn't matter if it's like a million
hours of the exactly my favorite game ever i don't i don't want to spend that money so
how much was i think i got dark souls on sale i think that's the thing when it's on sale um i don't
i don't know i'm not thinking of i can't really think of the money and the length because dark
souls i've played over and over and over and over again so it has a lot of length in it kind of
and there's lots of different ways to go about playing the game so i guess what i what does game
length mean the amount of time it takes to get a hundred percent it's basically asking do you think
that a game has to be long in order for it to justify how much you paid for it
i i think i think um i mean it depends on the length obviously but i think
a game feels more cool when you it takes you know more than an hour more than a couple hours more
than a day i i on the other hand if it takes me more than two days then i don't care enough to
finish it like it's never gonna happen i think it definitely depends on the game and the mechanics
like i think every game has a set of mechanics and i think they all have a certain amount of shelf
life so yeah i think it totally depends on the game like i'm really just trying to think of of
like really short games because i generally don't like the idea of really short games it just feels
wrong yeah like i feel like they're for something that i'm done with if it's a game i want to play
over and over again like down well short for you two can like i mean it depends on the price
and probably like the platform and shit but it's not unreasonable to expect a certain amount of
game length from a game it's just a question of what that length is i will say metal gear solid
ground zeroes definitely did not feel like enough meat for what i paid for it that well it's that's
funny because like that game really is incredibly complex and has a lot of tons of details like in
this one level it is one level game and it takes like an hour to beat but then you can replay like
collect shit so like that's an interesting question is it worth 60 definitely not which is
why they almost immediately reduced the price because they were ashamed of themselves but yeah
i think i did buy it for 60 by the way it was only 40 when it came out in defense oh really
but it was not worth 40 bucks devu says he wants rpgs to become smaller and shorter and more about
the details of a world than the scale of it he also insists that he's got a lot of length in him
oh does that mean you have a big cock in you right now is that what you're trying to say to me
yo that's gay dude that's gay i i for one like i can remember i can't unfortunately i can remember
the last time i played paid 60 dollars for a game what i cannot remember is the last time
that i paid 60 for a game and then played it before it was dramatically reduced in price so
in other words i see no reason for me to ever buy a game at full price because there's no
fucking chance i'm gonna play it before it goes down that sounds like a personal problem i feel i
feel so like confused about i mean it's not like don't understand the question it's just hard to
think about price and enjoyability of a game based on the length at the same time you know i uh uh
like we could do a whole podcast on this i agree but the guy's question was specifically uh like
guys have any opinions on game length and i do have an opinion on it which isn't like a real
criticism but it's that so this is another great great chance for me to shout out my favorite game
of the year holo night which is a 10 out of 10 experience which with free dlc coming out on
halloween after the first free dlc thing and the amazing thing about that game is it is 15
fucking dollars and it's on steam it's going to be on switch at some point soon i'm just
shouting all this because everyone should play holo night it's fucking incredible i do plan
to playing it very soon excellent uh and like that game is it's a big metroidvania and it's got
lots of content just like if you want to beat it through the first time but it's got it's got
that classic thing i love about old uh metroidvania like uh egovania is what i was looking for where
it's got like true ending shit and all these secrets you can find that like add to the to the
gameplay styles you can do and the riches of the world like it's got so much content packed in it
for a $15 price tag that i think you can make some sort of relatively objective standard for like
amount of content available and quality of content versus price of the game based on that
i definitely think that judgment can be made um like i i totally understand people saying like
i'm not going to pay $60 for a five hour game um but for me it's like i won't do either one like i
will not pay $60 for a game period like i don't care if it has 10 000 hours in it because i won't
play a game that's more than 15 hours long like or 20 hours or so like um like devu says in the
comments uh a story based game i want the length to reflect the narrative mechanic centric game if
i can't get at least 50 hours of fun from it i feel i've wasted not only my money but also my time
there you go it's it's a mechanic centric game which is the only kind of game i play um i don't
want it to last more than two days i want to explore the mechanic and then go cool i get it like i
just played uh odin sphere um right which is five different narrative tracks and um you play as a
different character in each of the five but you play through the same levels and i beat the first
character's narrative in about eight hours and i felt satisfied and when i got to the second
character and realized i had to play through the same levels i went oh well i beat the game like
yeah right it's over i did it cool i only paid 30 for this because i waited years before buying it
or however long it took before uh the price went down on this game right so you know i felt like
uh i got what i wanted which was a video game to play for a couple days while listening to podcasts
you know i love what devu's say i love how devu's framing this though because like yeah like people
sometimes are annoyed at like rpg's being so long but that's just because you really are getting
such a a large amount of specifically story being being and it's it's framed as such so uh well i mean
a lot of the time it's that there's a lot of game between the story but parts that sort of padded
out like in a bad in a bad rpg i mean you can beat a final passing seven in like 30 hours if you
really hustle you can do that that's still a long time yeah i think that's all good that's why i never
beat rpg's is because at some point there's usually a point around the middle of an rpg where it
becomes more about the combat than the story um because essentially rpg games are too big for
their stories most of the time we're like at some point it gets into the third act and we're like
okay we know who the villain is we have to kind of get there and like that's when it gets a bit
more repetitive the battles get longer there starts being more and more fighting that's where
and that's where i'm like i don't care anymore at the end you've mastered the combat and you
now are getting an excuse to use your mastery you've you you have to use it on a thousand enemies
though i hear what you're saying i hear what you're saying it's not the amount of the combat that's
the problem it's when the combat system isn't as fun as the amount of combat okay that's sure
and something like super mario rpg where it's like timing based each battle can be really like skill
based you can you can try hard and you can win and you can dodge all the damage and stuff but like
in a in a generic bare bones like uh everyone's like a gay elf and the wizards and they go and
we're anime characters uh and the combat is the worst thing of all time and it's the same length
i hate it okay that's fair okay even if the story is one last question uh before we fucking head
out of here canith craley asks what type of content does youtube need more of um my answer to that is
irreverent shit like what i want less of is like cultural commentating analysis
reviews like or people just like responding to each other i want more stuff that's just
creative and weird and funny and like that i won't get anywhere else you know we need uh more
maximus thorns more maximus thorns a good example potion seller the guy who did that like uh or gmc
foe show like stuff like that where it's just like you know the youtube channel has an identity
it's one type of content but it's like something that is wholly unique to themselves and it's not
beholden to trying to be popular on youtube it just is a good idea you know well you know in
response to this specific question the answer might be uh nothing and youtube needs to die because
it's getting too corporate and is not supportive of this kind of content uh i just think i'm thinking
video content and yeah if you ask me what's the ideal situation we all end up skating from youtube
and everyone becomes way weirder because the we're not trying to pursue algorithmic success anymore
you know one of my favorite things about youtube is how you could like up to now you've been able
to just say the word fuck and it didn't matter you could see it at any time in any video one of the
greatest things about the entire fucking platform yep yep yep and now it is gone is gone yeah hashtag
demonetized uh tom hippo you guys got hashtag explode i kind of agree with you digi i think
there just needs to be more stuff on youtube and in the web in general that's less about trying to
game the system to make money and to just make cool shit i think we had that for a while i think
early youtube was all about that because there was no financial incentive in the mix at all
you know and i remember that that's how i found m dot strange and all this and i think this stuff's
fucking fantastic and it wasn't about make money it was just like cool crazy shit we need more just
yeah just like esoteric bizarre out there just like i want to make this as i wanted to exist
not because i want to make a paycheck yeah man now go to my patreon and give me money
so i could do that um davoo says he needs more of the channels that he's been trying to catch up
on to announce one year hiatus is well there you go yeah i was i was gonna say like if if youtube is
only like the really good shit there will just be less it'll it'll it'll result in less people being
able to make it on youtube but i think that would be better because uh some people just don't have
any good ideas the field is a bit crowded now though i wonder if it would put us in a situation
where the people on the top just stay there kind of like the uh you know like the the steven
colbert channels and whatnot are just like cementing their place at like the top echelons
what i think has right now what i expect to happen over the next few years if this kind of
shit keeps happening is that gradually a lot of the youtubers on like the like several hundred
thousand subs or even million sub levels will start vacating the site and all the you know all the
industry shit will still be there but the audience wants those other guys like the audience is here
for the homegrown youtube content once that shit leaves there's not going to be enough people watching
the colbert shit on youtube gotta happen that's my hope too either it'll cause youtube to shrink
and become just netflix 2.0 which at some point will just mean netflix will buy it and completely
change it or like you know wait was there an or or they'll just die yeah that's the other i think
they will become purely corporatized in time i think that's what they already work i mean they
have youtube tv that's exactly what they're already on their way to do and for what it's worth i i don't
even blame youtube entirely for this because like they're too big it was too good of a service for
us i think like i think this idea of fully democratized content as beautiful as it was
was doomed to fail because not like we don't have the server space for every fuck off to make videos
you know yeah like in the world at this point we need this post scarcity society to come along
and fix that but like it's interesting because like there's a new website uh bit shoot i don't
know if anyone's heard of that site yet but it's not yet it's it's it's a new youtube competitor
and it's peer to peer so it's all torrent based but it's you host your videos and then you like
download torrents and that's how you so they they don't have any server space to worry about
because it's all peer to peer i can easily see that being part of the the future you know like i can
see that yeah i was talking about that in the comments or in the chat earlier about how the
ethereum network i don't know if you guys know anything about that it's like a project right now
that's like i i don't know much about it i want to do more research into it but i the general idea
is that it's a peer to peer internet so the entire network basically is designed to replace the web
as it is now and it's all decentralized and peer to peer so there's no central servers hosting
anything thank god fascinating fascinating uh i can't come fast enough
well i guess that's about it everybody yeah any other i think i think i think we're good so
everybody uh remember most of those questions this time came from our private discord so please
go on over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators pledge a dollar or more and you'll be in there
baby boy and then we'll be able to see your shit and if you if you pledge five dollars or more you
get to watch the bonus episodes every month that we make that's the real shit that's that's what you
really want to be signed up for there's seven of them right now the last one we'll rape your ears
to death you want to be in on that uh everyone's commenting about like how uh that that like i've
seen some people being like is this a real episode is this a real bonus episode it's more real than
anything i've ever seen in my fucking life it is it is it is everything this is exclusively a dick
master said into a second bonus episode because uh most people love it i heard i heard one warrior
was like guys i fucking made it through somehow i survived all the way through i was just like
damn dude in fucking impressed shit i don't think i've heard a single bonus episode except the one
i was on oh yeah yeah they're um there's some intense shit i got a vision they're intense uh and
what else we got we got some merch you want to buy some uh pcb merch there's some links down below
uh oh ask us more questions use a hashtag ask pcb we read some twitter questions here as well
and i think that's it did i miss anything uh we are still on itunes and google play now itunes
and google play of course that's right everybody if you like itunes google play you want to hear
your shit there we got it it's it's real it's real it exists so go where i do i do we do whatever
we like a salad kind of lettuce guy you know i don't know what that means but hey that's life
that's living all right thanks everybody and we'll see you next week bye and i'll say bye from
davoo bye from davoo okay yeah uh
i am
you