I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello and we're back, it's The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Uh, we missed it entire week.
Or two.
Three, no three.
Three, oh my god.
I think we missed, yeah, by the time this episode comes out, we'll have missed three.
But that's okay.
Uh, anyway, we're back.
I went to America.
You were in America.
I forget what happened on the last episode.
I forget what happened the whole time you were here.
Well, I wrote down notes.
I'm not going to read them, they're just like personal, like journal notes.
Cause that's what I like doing.
I like remembering fun times.
So I flew to America into Boston to hang out with people I know and friends, and Ben St. as well.
Who has included new friends.
Don't you, don't you spin that.
Yeah, yeah.
Hang out with friends and Ben St.
That's right.
Gibbon and friends and Ben St.
I like it.
Yeah.
And then you were here for a million fucking years.
I was here for about three weeks because of a COVID incident.
It caused me to be bedridden.
I had to change my flight.
And that was, that was a whole thing.
I guess that's the cliff's notes.
That's enough information to understand what happened.
Yeah, it's, honestly, it was such a, it feels like a whole arc transpired during that time.
There was, there was the initial Gib is visiting arc.
Then there was COVID arc.
Then there was a,
Gib is visiting again arc.
Then there was post COVID scramble to figure out, Gib is scrambling to figure out how she's getting home.
And also let's hang out before she leaves again arc.
Yeah, basically.
It was a three act structure.
The second act was the darkest hour.
Just like Star Wars.
Just like acts.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
So, so.
Boston's really cool, by the way.
I like Boston a lot.
I think it's good.
It's a good place.
I think I'd only been in Boston during the winter.
Cause we were, we were, I was in Boston.
I think, I think the first time was Radcon 3, right?
That house.
Well, Radcon 3 was not, was in Sharon, which was.
Massachusetts.
Sort of.
So.
It's the first time in Massachusetts.
We might have gone to Boston once or twice.
Yeah.
Um, but yeah.
It was interesting.
I landed in Boston.
I took the train out.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So that makes perfect sense, actually.
Um, but yeah.
The other times was a arm retrieval con, which followed Radcon 3, which was.
More in Boston.
Right.
Or was directly in Boston.
So I saw sites, but it was like freezing cold.
Um, the other time.
There wasn't, there was another time that was, I don't even remember really.
Like, you know, well there's, there's, there's like maybe two other times.
I can't think though.
Uh, the one I'm, I'm remembering is the weird PCP meeting that was just sort of like between
name Trixie talking about how to do like, uh, uh, can't hear or something.
They would discuss the bizarre, the bizarre, the bizarre meeting that had to be in person
in which they discussed like, should I move here?
Answer yes.
And then it turns out they both moved to Virginia instead.
Yeah.
Eventually.
Genius.
Geniuses at work.
I mean, whatever.
I had fun during that cause I was just, I was just there to hang out.
I wasn't part of the meeting.
It was funny.
I think we called that rad con 3.5, right?
Yes.
That was in between.
And then, yeah, I bet.
All right.
I don't know how long that time was.
I guess we went out at some point.
I remember meeting econ.
I remember like Ukrainian Zagok.
Who's not actually Ukrainian.
I think just Zagok, the artist guy.
He was around.
Yeah.
Randomly.
And there was like, we had Chinese food at some point.
And Pokemon Go in the Commons.
Yeah.
Pokemon Go in the Commons, which was like God, like deathly freezing like, oh shit,
let's get inside and not enjoy the outside tour.
Yes.
I think that was that.
So it was not actually two other times.
It was three times.
Well, basically two times.
This time was June.
So it was nice and warm.
And it's beautiful.
It's really nice just walking around.
I love the architecture.
I love the architectural like variability.
I love the the the vibe of like the entire place is just like great.
I am glad you think so.
I also think so, but I'm afraid to say it because because then the West Coast people
will attack me for being biased.
I'll start.
I'll start a beef.
Well, I mean, I haven't been to the West Coast, so I guess I don't know.
I mean, me, me either.
I've heard it.
Is it is it just like?
Well, I've been to the West Coast, but I haven't.
Or is it like the whole West Coast?
Because it's lower down.
It's more southern.
Right.
It's I think the West Coast.
I think it's warmer.
Like, I mean, it gets cold when you go way up north.
But if even like Oregon is still like not that it's not not especially cold.
I mean, it does snow there.
I found I found the temperature in Boston during summer to be like warm, but not like
so warm that I am at risk of dehydration to a point where I would need to go to hospital
like like a one time when I was in Greece that happened.
And that was fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, you came at the right time of year.
The it does get it does get blisteringly hot sometimes, but it's not it's not there yet.
So.
Oh, OK.
It gets blistering, you know, in like late July and August.
Yeah, it makes sense.
This is this was nice.
This was like almost familiar.
It feels like that in London sometimes very rarely, but it's quite nice and hot today.
Hey, how's the weather over there?
Oh, that's the conversation we're having now.
Hey, what do you think of those clouds?
I like them.
They like them.
Thank you.
You know, did you did you ride the tea much?
I don't remember if we rode the tea.
We mostly took buses around.
Yeah.
Well, I wasn't with you the whole time.
I was staying with Munchie.
Yeah.
And in his apartment and Munchie loves the tea and we did take the buses to get around.
And yeah, I do like the trains that I rode the green line mostly.
And there was like a new train on the green line and it was shiny.
I have still I have still not taken I still not taken the new the new green line.
The one that goes up to the one that goes up like fairly close to where I used to live that I would have would have been pretty convenient for me at one point in time.
But oh well.
There's gonna I was gonna ride that train, but I didn't maybe maybe one day.
Yeah, it was it was so new.
It was like the buttons to like, I don't know, stop the train.
Didn't feel like they had been pressed by human yet.
He's like, wow, like brand new spanking.
I see.
The tea is great.
I had my Charlie card from that one time and it actually accepted my credit card perfectly.
So I could just I could just use it like a real Boston commuter.
Oh, man.
Sick.
Yeah, that's great.
I mean, I rode the I rode the London Tube once, but I didn't get a that strong of a sense of how it compares really.
So I don't know.
The main difference is that London is a gargantuan behemoth of a city.
And so right unless you are like a weirdo, you don't need to ever travel like 90% of it.
I frequent like two lines because one of them goes to the airport and the other one just goes north to south and it's close to where I live.
So I can I can get on one of those stations and go and it's like, um, I don't really ever need.
I mean, it's it's really interconnected.
The London Tube, you can go from any station relatively quickly to switch to like a line or a station, you can get to a station that goes to a different line.
And there's lots of like, what would you call them, not junctions.
Stations that have multiple different lines in them.
You can walk from.
Yeah, from.
Yeah.
So like if you're in the tube, you can get anywhere.
But it does take a while.
I think from from one, the Piccadilly line that goes to Heathrow takes like two and a half hours to go from like the train from the from the airport all the way to the end.
So it's a big long way.
In in Atlanta, they have a sort of like a T, but it's even smaller and it's literally just two lines and one goes north to south and the other goes east to west and they just cross in the middle.
Well, it's kind of cute.
Yeah, so an even an even more condensed version there.
I remember I remember writing we rode the bus home from that from that furry from that furry meet up in that in that.
Oh, yeah.
God, I forgot all about that.
That was so this is like so early on in the thing.
There was a furry meet up.
It feels like it feels like three whole active past since then.
Yeah, I I drew like silly little give drawings in a bunch of notebooks and sketchbooks.
I didn't know who they were.
Yeah, only one of them was quite a like renowned furry porn artist.
I didn't know that was just funny.
I know.
I know about that guy sort of.
I'm not.
I don't read his stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Heterosexual.
That's not.
He doesn't just jar gay stuff.
It's Brea Bravern.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's the name.
Yeah.
The pony.
Unbelievable.
Can you believe in real life?
He's actually a human.
No.
I always thought he drew with those hooves.
Just like phantom horn.
I love that video.
Just like phantom horn was little blue hooves.
Yes.
That was like, I remember seeing that for the first time on T-Bap.
And it was like, wow, you're really going, you're like making skits with props.
Yeah.
And there's like effort being put in.
These are effort posts now.
I thought they were just like, you know, kind of funny guys talking on YouTube.
And now they're effort posting and you started doing all these skits.
And that was one of the earlier ones, I think.
Yeah.
I peaked with that one.
I think I just, I don't know, somehow I just got it in my head like, hey, phantom draws.
What if I showed him trying to draw with this little, the little frost that it coos.
It was just too good an idea not to do.
It was really good.
Yeah.
The cool, man, the camera quality on that video is dog shit.
It looks like, it looks so bad.
But I mean, whatever.
It worked.
You can tell what's going on.
Speaking, a little bit of a change of topic and we can get back to other stuff if you want.
But speaking of shitty camera quality, I've been, I've been buying stuff lately.
I've been, I guess I would say I've been investing in capital.
That's not really true.
Yeah, sort of.
I've been investing in the means of production for, to make some, to do the, the alternate version of that thing that I was going to do while you were here.
You remember the thing people were calling my secret project.
Yes.
Which I don't, which I don't want to spill.
I still do not want to spill the beans on it yet because.
Yes, I was wondering if you were going to talk about it.
I do, I do want to talk about it.
The short.
The short answer is that my COVID meant that I couldn't go to it.
So it didn't happen that way.
And now I'm gone.
So.
Yeah.
The, what was it?
Oh yeah.
I made a post on my Patreon.
I did a Q&A like, like solo podcast, not, not.
What do you call a blog that's a podcast?
It's not a blog.
A blog.
Yes.
I did a Q&A post where I talked about the situation with that and I explained what it is more.
So I won't go into detail, but the short version is that the, yes, I had an idea for
what, for a thing to do while you were here and then COVID meant that it couldn't happen.
And so I have re, I have reconfigured the idea into something that I can do by myself.
And instead of, I was going to hire a guy.
I was going to hire a guy to do some work on it for me.
So instead of that, I'm just going to buy some stuff that's going to let me do it myself.
So instead of the sex tape we were going to make, it's actually just going to be Ben St.
Jack-in-off.
Yeah.
It's, you know, it's, it's less sensational, but I get to, but at least I own 100% of the
final product.
So fuck, fuck she's sharing the rights.
Yeah.
I've been buying, I bought a new microphone.
I'm not using it right now.
I'm still using the shitty snowball ice, but I have a real big boy XLR mic now on like,
not just that, it's on one of those like retractable mechanical arms that you can kind of manipulate
and move around.
Yeah.
So that's, that's pretty fancy.
It plugs into a real, what do you call them?
The boxes that you plug the microphones into.
An audio interface.
Yes.
An interface.
I was looking around for, I was looking around for recommendations on that.
I got one that everyone said was a good deal.
I was going to try buying a new camera, but I'm going to wait.
I'm going, I'm not going to buy a camera just yet because I think it might be doable to just
film with my smartphone.
Oh yeah.
I've never really thought to try making a long thing, like a video with a, other than
like, oh, this could be like a tweet or I just want to remember this five seconds, filming
a long thing with a, with a phone.
I always worry about like, oh, isn't it going to fill up with space?
Isn't the battery going to drain?
Yeah.
Well, it doesn't have to do that.
It doesn't, it doesn't have to be all one take.
So it's, it's okay if I like have to stop in the middle and like transfer the, the video
and then like start filming again, like afterwards.
I think it's probably better to just try to film with my smartphone and see if that gives
me like, like I don't need to film in 4k.
Like I don't care about that.
Like as 1080p is fine.
Yeah.
And I think it can do that.
And I don't, the alternative is to spend like $300 on a new digital camera and like,
I don't know if I need, why do I do that needlessly?
So it's fine.
Yeah.
Oh, my screen just turned off for some reason.
Anyway, it's been spending money, but it's good because in theory, I will use these products
to generate revenue for myself and that is, and isn't that what it's all about at the
end of the day?
Generating revenues.
Yeah.
Oh, I love that.
You know, speaking of generating revenues.
Hell yeah.
I don't want to get too into like the nitty gritty because it doesn't really matter, but airplane
bullshit because of the COVID and having to rebook a flight means that I had to pay for
a new flight and I had to pay for a new flight like soon at the time because I don't want
to like overstay my welcome.
I could have stayed even longer, but it would have gotten like weird.
Yeah.
So I got the cheapest available option in like, it was like 10 days or so after I had
recovered was when I left.
Yeah.
So it's quite a long, quite a long great trip, honestly.
Worth it.
Worth getting COVID.
But it didn't have to buy like a plane ticket close to like a plane ticket to London in
the summer close to the departure date is very expensive.
Did you end up getting, I was going to say you ended up getting screwed on the price,
right?
Because you had to like move the timetable up.
Yeah.
So I've been doing some commissions.
I made a tweet about it.
I'm doing like thin line, simple sketchy sometimes with color.
If you want to pay more, there's commissions art.
I'll draw for money so I can pay for that.
I've gotten, let me check.
I've got my spreadsheet here.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12.
So I've gotten like 12 so far.
And I finished one, two, three, four, five, five of them.
I got a few to do, but they are still open.
I'll keep them open for maybe a week or two.
Just in case people have not heard about it yet and will hear about it first time here.
I'm going to draw for you.
You have to pay me though.
That's the only catch.
What the fuck?
Okay.
All right.
Why didn't anyone think of this before?
I don't know.
I saw one you did of like a cat girl or a bunny girl who was white.
That looked really good.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
I saw, I walked in on you drawing that.
Yeah.
It's drawn on my iPad.
It was very, that one I think it was pretty good.
I think that's the only one that I've seen.
I posted some others to Twitter.
Nobody will ever see the other ones because I am doing not-safe work commissions as well.
Oh, sure.
And those are epic, but you can't see those.
Don't even ask.
You're not going to post those on Big Girl Squish?
I already have, but now they know where to find them.
Okay.
Whoops.
Excuse me.
Nah, it's fine.
It's not like a, it's like an open secret.
I won't mention it like all the time.
But yeah.
I think I did a really good horse that like a lot of furries found in light.
So that's pretty good.
Well, I really liked that drawing you did of Virginia.
Sorry, Vermont.
Yes.
This is a different universe.
You know, I forgot.
I had, I never posted your doodle in my copy of Lord of Ghosts.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I have it.
I have it here in my drawer.
I should take a screenshot of that and post it.
It's really good.
It's Phantom on Virginia.
I'm glad you like it.
I love it.
I was, I'm torn because part of me thinks it would be cool to take my Copics and like
color it in.
And part of me is like, no, don't touch it.
It must be preserved just as it was.
I mean, you could, you could like scan it in or take a picture and color it on, on the,
on the old computer.
That's, that's true.
Or you could like photocopy it and draw it.
I mean, that's obviously not the same thing.
I mean, I mean, yeah, the, the, the one, the one in the book is the, is the, is the real
one.
I don't know.
Uh, I should mention now that I have my copy, I should say on the podcast that the book
came out really nice.
Well, thanks.
And so did the red man zine.
I was actually, I said this, I told you this before, but I'll say it again for the record.
Uh, I was really surprised like that it's like perfect bound and like high quality.
I was picturing it being like a staple bound, like, you know, like, like a zine.
Yeah.
It's, it's because there's so many pages.
I couldn't do staple.
Yeah.
It had to be a thick boy.
That's the other thing.
There's way more than I thought they were.
The red man book is awesome.
Like it's, it's really great.
Uh, I'm pretty proud of that.
It's like such stupid subject matter, but it's really nice.
And a nice little product.
I like it a lot.
And the, the Lord of Ghost book is also, it's much bigger than I had like pictured it being.
It's quite substantial.
It was like a hundred, it's like a hundred pages or so or something pages.
Yeah.
It's really nice.
Uh, it's, uh, it's one of my, it's my, it goes in my drawer where I keep books that
I like.
I'm happy to have it.
Yeah.
Um, oh, in my pin, of course, my Lord of Ghost pin.
You know what?
I'll still wear it.
I was going to wear it for that thing that we didn't do, but I will still wear it when
I do it in the other way.
I, I hate being so cagey about it.
I mean, it makes, it's obvious that you're filming something.
I'm obviously filming something.
Yes.
So you can call it a video.
Yeah.
No, no, it's, uh, it's, uh, it's a multimedia, uh, it's a movie.
It's actually making a feature film starring me and a Lord of Ghost pin.
That's the only information you have.
I hope, I hope that doesn't, I hope that doesn't give it away, but you know what?
If it does, who cares?
I just don't want to talk about it because if I talk about it, then I won't have the
motivation to, to finish doing it.
And I just want to finish it.
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
That's, that's the, um, the UK mixam company that the printed those.
That's the one you were thinking of.
Which I might use for slime and punishment, which I am ashamed to admit I have still
not finished the footnotes for.
I have done like most of them.
I mean, you've, you've talked about like how in depth some of these notes are getting
like how many things you want to reference in each page.
Some of them are very in depth and some of them I have to like look up stuff and like
confirm things.
And, um, when they're done, I'm going to hand them off to some like old RFCK heads to
ask them like, Hey, can you like proofread these and like tell me did I miss anything
or tell me did I get anything wrong?
They're not that long.
I think I've written maybe like 16 pages worth of notes on them, which is not like a huge
amount of writing, but because I'm trying to be like scrupulous about getting the details
right and I have to do sort of like research on it.
It's a little, it should be, it should have been done, but it's not because I've had to
split my attention.
I've had to split my attention between there's that there's finishing the footnotes for the
book.
There was working on the video project and then working on reconfiguring the video project
into a new form once I had to change it.
And then gummy making, obviously gummy making is a high priority.
That can't be neglected.
I perfected, I perfected my recipe over this period.
I found, I found what I think is that is, I'll never call it the final recipe, but I'll call
it a final recipe that I'm happy with.
And I don't know what I'm going to do with that.
She was telling me that he thinks I should like offer it.
It's like a care pack.
He was saying something about trying to monetize it.
My idea was like, what if I did like a Patreon supporters, like quarterly care package or
something?
I think Tom does something like that.
I think I mean, Trixie used to do care packages care packages.
Like, I, I mean, I've mailed so many Lord of Ghost things.
I don't want to ever mail things again.
I want to post a box.
That sucks.
How could you do something like that regularly?
That's, yeah, I was going to, like I would not like monthly would be too often.
Quarterly would be okay.
And it would have to be for people who were pledging like 25 bucks or something.
Like it wouldn't, it wouldn't, it wouldn't just be for any old $5.
Shlub.
Because it is like actually quite, quite annoying.
I'm actually not even sure if you can send food in the mail.
No, yeah, you must be able to.
I think, I think you're allowed to send food in the mail.
It's just people will likely not, unless it's from a company and it's perfectly sealed.
You know, you send food to a random person and it's like just something that could,
could have been easily tampered with.
People will be like a priestess about it.
I think it might be liquids.
I think it might be like you might have to check a box and like pay a tax or something
if you send liquids in the mail.
Yeah, but you could lie though.
You could lie, you could lie.
Are there like stories of like, I don't know, YouTubers or whatever streamers having like
PO boxes and they open it and it's like, it's diarrhea.
Oh, who put diarrhea in the mail?
And that's why you don't have a PO box.
Bad idea.
I have to, I have to get a new PO box.
I think I may have mentioned that my old PO box expired.
My old PO box expired and I feel like it's almost certain that some packages that I sent
probably got returned in the mail and I'd never found them because the PO box was canceled.
And probably there are a couple people who never got stuff they bought from me.
And I will never know unless they tell me about it because I had no PO box to receive their
return to sendered, unsuccessfully delivered packages.
I had one person message me to tell me they never got their thing and I still have,
I just have to send his replacement still, but I will.
And I found like four other packages that had been returned before the PO box had expired.
And I did get those and none of those people like told me, none of those people like mentioned to me that they
didn't get their packages yet, even though it's been like four months, which is kind of surprising.
They forgot they bought it, but I'll get those recent as well.
Actually, the hold up there is that the packages have the real names on them.
And like, I don't remember whose screen name corresponds to what real name.
And I am like not, so I have to comb through like my PayPal transactions and my Twitter DMs
in order to try and find like who is who.
And I haven't done that yet.
And it's going to be really annoying.
This is one of those things I've in my spreadsheet I made to keep track of a lot of ghost things.
I made a point to like, you know, their name and their preferred name.
If I was going to like put their name in the back if they had like a different name to their real name.
And then like their email address, you know, just ways to contact this one person and then what they ordered.
So I can be like, okay, this person has messaged me on Discord.
Who are they? Oh, they're that guy.
It's made a lot of things simple, but some people like just never got back on anything.
So I just don't know.
I tried messaging on Kickstarter and that's all I know them from.
So yeah, like two people at this point.
Yeah, that's still one of them is going to supposed to get the plush and they just haven't messaged me still.
Oh, right. I got my plush. I've got the plush too.
Going to have an extra.
It's sitting up on my shelf next to my collectible Sonic the Hedgehog glasses.
Different topic.
I purchased an adapter for a PlayStation controller to plug the PlayStation controller into this USB adapter
and then plug the USB adapter into my computer to try and play games with it.
And it doesn't work and it makes me really mad.
It recognizes the controller.
But then when I look at the inputs, it does not recognize any inputs from it.
No matter what I do, I tried downloading all these different drivers.
None of them work or do anything about it.
In the end, I gave up and I just bought a PlayStation 3 controller, which supposedly works without any need for an adapter.
Wait, what controller were you using?
I was using an original PlayStation 1 controller with no DualShox.
Without the double twin sticks.
Because I just had one.
A family friend got me one for Christmas like two years ago, I think.
I was disappointed because that was the controller I wanted to use.
But oh well, the PlayStation 3...
It cost me like 15 bucks.
It's just annoying that the adapter was totally worthless.
I think I did everything I could with that too. I really tried.
I got the Xbox One controller for PC gaming, which is apparently a really good one.
The Xbox Series X controller is a bit...
It's fine apparently, but worse in ways.
That's a good gaming one I've heard.
The Xbox One, which is kind of old now.
I read online, sources that I looked up told me that to use a PlayStation 3 controller on your PC, you have to download drivers for an Xbox 360 controller.
And that's what lets you use a PS3 controller on your computer for some reason.
I haven't tried it yet, so I don't know if it's true.
But that's what I read.
I always go for Xbox just because it's also the computer people in Microsoft.
So they're supposed to work without any issues.
I guess that's true. I just like PlayStation better. I'm a PlayStation baby.
I grew up using it, so I like the controller.
That's it.
It's a good controller. I like the PlayStation 4 controller a lot.
I've gotten so used to Xbox for PC gaming. It doesn't feel right otherwise.
I was trying to play some games with the keyboard that were just...
You just can't...
Some games work, and other games it just fucking doesn't.
These were not working, so I was like, oh well, better invest in some hardware.
Since I'm already buying all this other shit, so I did.
The means of production. Are you going to make Let's Plays?
No! I'm not going to make Let's Plays.
Are you going to make Let's Streams?
No, the plan was not to stream, although I guess if I did ever stream again in my life and I wanted to play games,
you might as well use a...
Right? Right?
The stuff like the microphone, the camera, camera equipment, the tripod stuff.
There's this current video idea that I needed to make, but it's like, okay, but I'm going to have it forever.
I was thinking back...
I'm thinking back. I'm honestly pretty embarrassed.
It's pretty embarrassing that video that I made in like 2021, like more than a year ago, where I...
The Let's Read with Ululiliya's Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters.
The video quality on that is so garbage. The audio quality is trash.
Why was I not willing to invest like anything in making that video decent?
Like, well, I don't know what I was thinking.
I mean, I could imagine you were thinking, well, I'm not really a YouTuber, so I don't need it forever.
It's a big investment, usually.
Yeah, but I mean, what's the point of even doing it if I'm not even going to try to make it good?
And second of all, it's not that much of a big investment.
Well...
I mean, a lot of like pretty decent things have gotten very affordable over the years.
Yeah, I mean, the new... the microphone that I got was like...
It was like 70 bucks, but then there was like some other stuff.
You know, the stand and the wires and the adapter was like another maybe like 100.
So maybe like less than 200 bucks for a microphone upgrade.
The camera...
Well, I guess I would have had to spend a little more.
Probably another 150 would have gotten me at least an acceptable camera for that.
I don't know.
You know, the more I think about it...
Okay, on the one hand, that particular video would probably not have justified the cost of those things,
but I would have had them forever.
I would have then had like improved my production capabilities forever.
So it would have been fine. It would have paid for itself in other ways.
You got to invest in your future.
Okay, that's all I have to say about that.
I agree.
I mean, I've used this microphone that I'm using right now for a long time.
I don't actually remember when I put this.
It may have been something like 2017.
A lot of things I've recorded with this.
It's definitely paid for itself.
Econ gave me, or I think he sold it to me for very cheap, though.
This snowball ice that I'm using now.
And I mean, it's perfectly fine.
It's a perfectly fine USB microphone.
A little bit worse than like a Blue Yeti, but whatever.
You know, I forgot to mention there is another thing.
I think you might have forgot because it probably got lost in the shuffle of other things that were happening.
But do you remember that on the morning or the night before we were going to film the thing, my power went out?
Yes, I do remember this.
You stumbled in and you were like, I'm so nervous.
And my power went out.
I was trying to do stuff to like prepare.
And in the middle of it, like the power went out and I didn't have my computer.
And I'm like, my resources.
My means of production.
Yes, yes.
It was horrible.
It took me like a while to figure it out.
I did eventually figure out that I had a power strip with a long enough cable to run into the kitchen.
Which was only only my room and the adjacent room and the hallway had their power out.
The kitchen's power was mostly still on.
So I managed to use the outlet that powers the refrigerator to power not my whole room, but like I moved my table near my door so that it could power my computer.
So I could use my computer.
My lights were out.
My room was had to be like completely rearranged.
Anyway, this has continued to happen.
It has happened twice more since then.
So almost once a week since then.
My power has just died spontaneously.
And every time I have to complain to my landlord and then the next day the power comes up.
It has been a little while since, I think it's been more than a week since that last time it happened.
But boy, I hope it stops.
Although my computer table is still in the new position near the door plugged into the strip that's running from the kitchen.
Just in case it happens again so my computer doesn't die.
I have officially seen your place of residence.
Oh God.
Cringe.
It's not good.
I hate it.
I hate this place.
I vaguely remember you talking about trying to or like thinking of leaving pretty soon.
Well, actually my lease is up in only like less than three months.
Oh wow.
I actually, yeah, I was talking about like maybe just leave early, but like it's almost like too late.
It's too late to leave early, basically.
I just have to start looking for another place like normal.
Wait a minute.
Oh my God.
We're halfway through June already.
Yep.
Oh my fucking God.
June, July.
I've only got two and a half months.
This is a fucking nightmare.
Start Googling.
No!
You gotta do it.
Last time I started looking with only like with only a month.
I only gave myself a month to find a place and that was a mistake.
So I mean, I'm doing better than I'm doing better.
No.
Now I'm thinking.
I don't know.
I feel like it shouldn't be hard to like get this thing filmed.
I feel like there should be no problem getting this thing filmed and finishing the book and maybe even launching the Kickstarter in that time.
But like also when I think about all those things, I feel like so crunched.
Like I feel like I can't possibly do it all in only two and a half months, even though that's a long time.
Yeah.
And then also look for a new place.
Yes.
Exactly.
I mean, I would definitely prioritize a few things.
Like if you're going to do the film, you don't want it to be suddenly continuity.
Oh, you're in a new place now and I'm just going to finish saying it.
Yeah.
I mean, if I, yeah, I wouldn't, I wouldn't start filming it like the week I had to move.
I mean, filming doesn't take too long if you have everything ready.
No, I would expect it to only take, I might, I could probably film it all in one day.
Maybe I would, maybe two days.
Yeah.
And then once you've filmed it, editing can take however long it will take.
And if you need to put it in the back while you look for a place, that's, you know, that's fine.
What's taking a long time with it now is literally just waiting for all the like equipment that I bought to arrive in the mail.
And then once it's here, I'll need to set up like the shot.
And I don't think that will be hard to do, but...
Do you have a light?
Let's see.
Did you buy a light with everything?
I did.
I was thinking about that.
I did not.
Like I assume I would probably need like a good light to light the shot, but I don't really know what to get.
Yeah.
I don't know too much about lighting myself because whenever I did like skits for Hippocrite or whatever,
I would just use lamps that I had and then just point them around places and that did the job fairly well.
The best thing is just having daylight come in, which lights the entire room quite a lot.
Okay, but the thing about that is that then your shot changes as the day progresses.
Sure, but that doesn't stop YouTubers from doing it and nobody seems to care.
They just be like, oh yeah, it got dark.
So I'm just going to finish the video and then it's fine.
I mean, yeah, to a certain extent, I'm sure it's fine.
The point is having like a professional light or even just like a hobbyist light does a lot because it's not just the cool like lighting dynamic stuff.
It just makes it easier for the camera to see what is happening and it makes it look higher quality.
Like a good quality camera in low light will still look grainy and horrible.
Yeah, and I was thinking about it and I just don't, I don't know what kind of light I need.
And also like, I just don't have a lot of space in my room to like put up like a stand light.
I guess I could probably like fold it up, put it in the corner when I'm done with it.
I've seen like people use streamers and video people use like a donut light.
Like it's a ring, I guess it's called a ring light.
It's a ring light, it's diffused and it's like you can stand it on a table or on a stand.
And you put it behind the camera and it's like sort of diffused light shining straight at you.
I also...
The important thing is that it's diffusing because a direct light will be very harsh shadows.
Hmm, yeah.
Yeah, I should get something, I should just look into.
I looked into microphones, I found a mic that I thought was a good deal.
I looked into cameras, I decided I'm gonna try to do it without a new camera and try to film with my smartphone if possible.
I didn't look into lights yet, but I will do that.
I think I probably need one.
And then...
Shit, I was going somewhere with that.
Fuck.
Do you think, so the other thing you talked about doing the book and the Kickstarter for making the book.
Oh yeah.
Like you're trying to do all that in one month.
I feel like something has to go in the back burner.
Well, I think I could finish...
I feel like my plan was to finish the book and then send it off to a printer and then wait for the test copies to be printed and sent to me.
And during that waiting period was when I would do the recording.
Right.
I think that was my plan.
And I think it's still the plan.
And I think if I just finish the footnotes, that's like the...
I have to draw a cover.
I mean, that shouldn't be too hard.
It's a lot of work.
It is a lot of work.
Yeah, there's a lot of little things.
I feel like you should prioritize getting the new place sorted.
Because then if it turns out you get a good place, the video will be in a nicer location and you can do that then.
You know, that's true.
That's true.
The other thing, and this is...
I'm not sure if this is dumb.
This might sound dumb, but I was testing out my webcam to see if I could get my settings to look better.
And the answer is no.
The webcam sucks.
But I was looking at myself in the webcam and I noticed that in the webcam I could see a spot on my teeth.
And that really bothered me.
And I thought maybe I need to go to the dentist before I film this video.
Maybe I need to do that first as well.
So, I mean, go to the dentist has been on my to-do list for a long, long time.
And every day that goes by, that becomes a more pressing concern.
And I've let it simmer for a long, long, long, long time.
So, I mean, I do urgently need to do that.
Do I need to more urgently do it than everything else?
Maybe, no, maybe, I don't know, perhaps.
I would say hold off on the recording, the video stuff.
Get the book finished and have the thing said to you.
And then look for a new place.
Looking for a new place, the process of that involves sending a lot of emails,
waiting for replies, and then setting up dates to go and see places and visit people.
It's like a long process.
What I mean is in between waiting for stuff like that, you could be working on the footnotes of all the pages.
Because that will take a while, probably.
I hope it won't take me that much longer.
I'm most of the way done with it.
And I feel every day that goes by, I feel guilt and shame that it isn't done already.
No, Ben, you must feel positive vibes that your productivity will be better.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to do this.
I'm sorry to quote, to read you this quote, because it is from a Republican.
But I saw a really great wholesome meme recently.
Here, I'm going to read it.
I love this, but I almost retweeted it.
But then I was like, no, I'm not that cringe.
This is a great thing.
This is on Reddit.
I think it was a Reddit AMA.
The guy asks, this is asking Arnold Schwarzenegger.
He asks, I know this is pandering, but I've been depressed for months and haven't hit the gym during that time.
Mr. Schwarzenegger, can you please tell me to get off my lazy ass and hit the gym?
I swear to everything I hold dear that I will snap out of it and go.
And here was username GovSchwarzenegger's reply.
I'm not going to do the accent.
I'm not going to be that hard on you.
Please don't be that hard on yourself.
We all go through challenges.
We all go through failure.
Sometimes life is a workout.
But the key thing is you get up.
Just move a little.
Roll out of bed and do some push-ups or go for a walk.
Just do something one step at a time.
I hope you feel better and get back to the gym.
But don't beat yourself up because that's just useless talk.
It doesn't get you closer to the gym.
And don't be afraid to ask for help.
Good luck.
Yeah, I saw that as well.
That was very wholesome.
It's a great reply from Arnie.
It's so true.
The only good Republican.
Yeah, I don't know too much about his political governorship.
But I've always seen things he said as like,
oh yeah, you know, that's pretty good.
You're not just a meathead.
Maybe he's also that.
Yeah, I don't know the details.
I saw during the height of COVID, he was like pro-mask and stuff.
So he did that.
He made that post with the sword of Conan to be,
I think it was something to do with how we should all wear a mask or something like that.
Yeah.
He seems okay.
He's probably legislated some horrible stuff.
He's probably pushed some horrible fucking nightmare shit in Congress.
Oh yeah, sure.
Oh wait, he's not a Congresswoman, a governor or whatever.
He's probably vetoed some really cool shit, but oh well.
I remember this thing he did, because he's really popular in Russia.
He made a video to the people of Russia condemning the Russian invasion of Ukraine
and talking at it in a sort of even moderate tone so that he could get through to them.
And it was like, yeah, that's nice.
It's nice that you're trying to use your celebrity status to invoke change,
or at least change minds or open people to newer ideas.
He's saying the Russian media is lying to you and he's like, yeah.
That's a good post, Arnold.
Yeah.
He's a Republican though.
It's fucked up.
Some weirds going on there.
Maybe he just has a few backwards beliefs and they technically make him a Republican,
but he's not evil spawn.
I mean, it must just be that that's who votes for him.
That's where he could get the votes.
Maybe.
I don't know.
It's a mystery.
It's like that sometimes a person is like a cool person.
They just happen to be pro-gun and then they only get Republican votes.
Yeah.
It's like guns aren't that, I mean, they're bad regulation and all that,
but like guns are just things.
Like saying get rid of all guns is, I don't know.
Yeah.
Doesn't make you like an insane person to like guns.
Like the official Republican platform is like criminalized gay marriage,
set up the police state, et cetera, et cetera.
Prevent trans people of any age from getting healthcare.
Goes without saying.
I guess maybe they're all not 100% the same.
No.
I wouldn't ever expect it, but like, I don't know.
I don't know his views.
I just know that he makes holes.
He's wholesome and he gives good workout advice.
And for me that, and that gets in my vote.
And what he, and what he does to trans people after he's elected is their problem.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
It'd be really funny if he was pro-trans.
Like all of these things just pile up.
It's like, how is he Republican?
Like what, huh?
Yeah.
Maybe.
I don't know.
It feels like the sort of open-minded guy who would be like at least,
at the very least like lukewarm and not like anti-trans.
That's my, yeah, I would think so.
I mean, he's, he's a Hollywood star.
He's like straight out of the mouth of Mammon.
Like the satanic cult of like the Hollywood liberal elite is like where he came from.
So he must have been infected.
He must have been infected with liberalism at some point.
And it's eroding our national institutions from the inside out.
Anyway, I don't know.
The point is that's me.
That's me with making videos and going to the dentist and finding a new apartment.
You're beating yourself up.
And finishing my stupid book.
I'm always beating myself up.
Sometimes you gotta accept you can't do everything.
I try to, I'm always beating myself up.
And I'm always, I feel like I'm always in the like, God, I haven't,
I haven't done it.
I haven't done anything.
I haven't produced content.
What am I going to, I'm going to go to hell now.
Well, I feel like I'm always in the, I haven't produced anything,
but I have to do something like just let me just baby steps.
Like let me just do something.
Like let me do something today.
And then I'll like, you know, maybe write up like another,
another page of the notes or whatever, or I'll, or I'll go and,
or I'll go and I'll do the, and it's like, yeah, I did something,
but like I should really do more.
No, that's, that's part of the, that's part of the wrong mindset.
You should be, you should be happy.
You should be doing less.
You should be a forgiveful of your own, I don't know,
what do we call it?
Not reaching a certain standard.
If you don't reach it, just forgive yourself.
It's a good thing to try.
Speaking of, speaking of things that I did just to get them done
and feel like I accomplished something.
Uh, I forgot, I should have mentioned this first thing.
The podcast episodes are up on the apps.
They are up on the various apps, Google, Google podcasts,
Apple podcasts, Spotify, and on the website,
the procrastinatorspodcast.com.
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
I finally, I finally figured it out.
Good job.
Um, okay.
And then just today, someone messaged me just today.
Okay.
Apparently Spotify is now missing episodes one through 13.
Someone, two people have reported to me that since uploading
the new episodes, it's as though it hit a 300 episode limit
and then like removed the first few.
And that is infuriating.
It's not on every platform.
Like it's like the website still has all of them.
But I don't know.
I don't use Spotify and I don't look at the podcast apps.
I just, I just post them all through WordPress.
So I can't, I don't know.
I don't know.
I guess we should try to fix that.
I guess.
Yeah.
It's not, if it's not one fucking thing, it's another.
I mean, at least it's up on lots of things.
At least people can shut up about it.
Well, more or less.
Yeah.
I feel, man, I feel like, I feel a little bit like I've been gaslit.
Like I would, like it felt like, it felt like lots of people were asking me,
Hey, put them on the podcast apps, put them on the apps.
And then now that they're up, like, like three people are like, Oh, cool.
Thanks.
It's that classic, like the, the, the people who squeaky wheel gets the oil.
They only speak when they have something to complain about.
And otherwise they're just content and silent.
You have no idea whether they, they enjoy what's happening.
Yeah.
I really don't.
Hopefully, I mean the, yeah, I went and I checked just a minute ago and episodes one through 13 are still on the website.
Maybe they can be restored to, maybe they're just being hidden on Spotify.
They're not like, they're not gone.
They might, they might be gone from that particular app, which is fucking obnoxious.
Well, that would mean that there are 301.
Oh God, I guess I'll have to fucking figure out, make a Spotify account or something.
Maybe.
I mean, we don't have to, we don't have to pay for that.
To, I mean, isn't it, isn't that already an account that these PCP episodes are on?
I don't, I don't know because I didn't use an account.
It's like when you, when you post it to WordPress, I think Tom set it up so that you can check a box.
And if the box is checked, it will like automatically also upload them on the other, the other apps.
I didn't engage with anything outside of WordPress.
I guess we just have to look and see where they are from a user's perspective.
See that account.
I guess you could always like, like badger Tom about some, some glitch that's happening.
I feel confident that he will just tell me he doesn't know.
Yeah.
I mean, I could, I could, I could ask him.
If it's not immediately obvious from looking it up, then I guess you're worth, worth asking.
Okay.
I Googled, maybe I'm doing this wrong.
I Googled Spotify, the procrastinators.
And I looked at open.spotify.com.
Slash are like, there's one called the procrastinators, but all it has is the, the garling house track.
There's no podcast episodes.
What is this?
I guess that's like the account Nate made to post that as like the song that is what we made.
I mean, wait a minute.
I'm seeing that there is in fact another podcast on Spotify called the procrastinators.
One word.
So there's another show that stole our name.
Okay.
Here we go.
And this is, I know what I'm going to see.
I'm scrolling down, scrolling down, and I'm going to see that episodes one through 13 are missing.
So I don't, I don't, I don't know what, but I don't know what to do about it.
Maybe I'll just have to log into the Spotify account.
Maybe it's like, there's like an account thing being like, oh, these ones were blocked.
You have to like confirm that they're stupid or not.
And then we can put them back up.
Like they're unlisted or some, some sort of thing you have to do in the account settings.
I hope so.
I hope I don't just have to fucking repost them.
That would be annoying.
Whatever.
If for some reason you wanted to immediately, someone wanted to immediately go back and listen to episodes one through 13 of the PCP.
Well, you can no, you cannot do that on Spotify at the moment.
You would have to do it on a different app.
Oh well.
Get fuck spot if fires.
I guess I'll have to.
I thought I was done.
I thought I was done dealing with it.
I'm going to get upset.
I'm going to get upset thinking about it.
I just, I don't want to, I don't want to do it anymore.
I don't want to, I don't care.
I don't care about this shit.
Well, you don't.
I mean, it's the, like you said, it's just the first 13 on Spotify specifically.
I think you can leave that for a while.
But it will continue to be every episode.
This is going to keep happening.
Oh, is it every episode?
Yeah.
Clearly what happened is that by like posting the new episodes, it erased the old ones.
Oh, is that?
Oh, so like there's a maximum amount of things you can have on a podcast?
I don't know.
I mean, that seems, seems, seems that way.
Oh, so you posted 13 things and it's like deleted the first 13.
That's what people are telling me.
Huh.
Must be so, maybe it's a Spotify premium, something or other.
I feel like that 300 something episodes is a lot.
Sure is.
Well, if it's, if it's one through 13, then there's four.
Yeah, there are 301 episodes live.
There's, there's episodes 14 through 314.
That's 301 episodes.
Why would the limit be 301?
What's going on here?
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, I guess let's change the subject because I don't, I'm not going to, we're not going
to solve this by yammering about it.
Yeah.
Um, I guess, uh, I could talk about that I got a cool hat in America.
I got a cool sun hat.
Oh, you posted a picture of yourself.
Oh, I did.
For like the first time in a long time, I think, right?
Yes.
I had not shown my face since, uh, any Radcon 4 content actually.
I had not seen your face since Radcon 4 in any capacity at all.
And, uh, yeah, people said, said that I looked cute and that was very nice.
It was a nice picture.
It looked pretty good.
Uh, I was excited, I was just excited to see that you were posting your face and I thought
that was cool.
Thanks.
Thought about, about time, I guess.
I guess I don't post my face much either, but nobody cares what I look like.
So it's fine.
Uh, I look the same as always.
I hope I'm actually not sure if that's true.
Actually, no, I look old now.
My beard, I have more gray in my beard than I used to.
I did see, I just see your gray bits.
Oh, great.
Oh, I love that.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, thanks for telling me.
I appreciate it.
You're supposed to lie.
You're supposed to tell me the lie that I want to hear.
No, it's not true.
Anything.
No, no, no.
And you look, I didn't say you look old.
I just said I noticed the gray hairs.
You don't look like you're, you're, you're hobbling along.
You look good.
Oh, thanks.
Uh, I guess there's worse, I guess there's worse things.
There's worse things than gray in your beard, I suppose.
Yeah.
Whatever.
It's fine.
Uh, my teeth, my teeth look terrible.
Uh, my, my, my, uh, my hairline is gone.
My beard is gray.
I'm, uh, uh, I'm dead.
No, it's like a salt and pepper or whatever they say.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
It's cool.
It's a cool look.
No, don't patronize me.
No, I kind of like it.
I don't know.
Nothing.
I appreciate it.
Very nice.
It's okay.
I was, um, damn, I had a moment.
Oh, shit.
My headphone jack came out.
I said I was fucking around with my webcam.
And boy, I turned on my webcam and I got, I got the most disgusting, like, unflattering
angle of myself imaginable.
And I was like, I was like, Oh God, no God, why Jesus?
Are you there by the way?
Yeah, I'm here.
Oh, I don't know what, to what you're referring.
I don't know if I saw that.
No, no, no.
I just, I saw myself in the feed from my webcam.
Oh.
I didn't take a picture.
And it was, it was very bad.
Um, that was where I saw my, I thought my teeth looked messed up and I thought I need to go
to the dentist.
Um, but I don't know.
Then I, then I switched to the front camera on my regular phone.
I was like, no, I look normal.
No, I look normal.
It's fine.
It's fine, actually.
Uh, okay, okay.
I don't, I, I mean, you look good to me.
It's time for my weekly existential crisis.
It's time for my weak, weakly fucking therapy session about like, Oh God, I'm getting old.
I don't like my face anymore.
Hey, Ben, what do you think your skeleton looks like?
It looks bad.
It sucks.
My skeleton's so fucking old.
No, I'm going to make an ugly skeleton when I die.
I'm going to leave behind a shitty skeleton and that's the worst.
People are going to dig up my bones and they're going to laugh out loud.
They're going to fall over.
The aliens are going to dig them up and be like, ew, look at this one.
Oh, what was he thinking?
Um, what was he thinking growing his skeleton like this?
Wait, that reminds me of something.
What does that remind me of?
What is the idea of like growing your skeleton?
Remind me of.
Uh, drinking milk?
No, like, did I watch a video about like a horror game recently or something?
About like bloody skeletons or something?
I don't know.
Maybe I had a dream that I like don't really remember.
They just triggered like a moment of like.
You had a dream where you were looking at your own skeleton and you were like trying to do dark magic to make it look like the Chad face.
You know that the slow moving grayscale Chad guy?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The guy who is based on the new Pokemon professor.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You got the funny jaw on the, the, the shaved side of head.
He does.
They made the new, they made the new professor look like the giga chair.
You see the, the, I don't know whether this is real actually, but did you see the female trainer, female scientists, Pokemon professor, like vampire fangs?
Yeah.
She's got like sharp incisors or whatever that called.
Yeah, yeah, I did see that.
She looks like a wild, wild lady or something.
I don't know.
She looks like a tribal, crazy beast tamer or something.
I don't, a huntress.
I'm not, I don't know how to describe.
She'll bite you.
She'll, oh, she'll bite you.
That we can all agree she'll bite you.
I heard that sprigatito stands on its hind legs and that sucks.
I mean, don't most Pokemon end up doing that?
Yes, but it's bad when they do, when they do it with like Meowth and they make, they make us, they take a fucking cat and they make its, I think they did it with Litten.
I'm not sure if they did it with Litten, but they did it with Perloin.
They've done it with a bunch of fucking cats, like instead of just letting them stand like a cat, they make them stand on their hind legs like idiots.
It sucks.
There's Persian that doesn't do that.
Persian doesn't do it.
Yeah, I guess it is usually like Incineroar is the most obvious like annoying example of a cat that got ruined.
They got humanized too much.
I mean, he's not even really a cat anymore.
Well, obviously that's why it's so upsetting.
Like cat, Litten, and then Torracat look cool.
And then Incineroar, like nobody remembers Torracat.
I think I made a tweet about it.
I didn't even remember his name.
Google Torracat and it'd be like, oh, that's a cool.
I wonder what's next.
Just like, no.
No, with the switch to 3D models, with the switch to 3D models, they just made a bunch of, like the old sprites used to have them on four.
And now they stand, it's Meowth they did it with.
I think, no, not Glameow, but definitely Perloin.
I feel like Meowth standing is mostly because of the TV show, right?
Meowth being a famous stand, like he's specifically a Meowth that stands and talks like a human.
Meowth default does that, which is odd.
I could sort of understand it because that's the image most people have of Meowth.
I wouldn't like it, but I would understand it.
I don't understand having Perloin stand on its hind legs, like that's nonsense.
Well, how else are you going to have sex with it?
It's not fully evolved, Gib.
It's immature.
You can't have sex.
I press the B button.
They press the B button every, like, they're actually much older.
If your waifu is competitive in Little Cup, then I'm sorry, but you're going to jail.
No one in Little Cup.
No, I press the B button.
I press the B button.
No, you can't, listen, you can't have sex with an onyx.
That's a baby.
That's a baby because it needs to evolve into mega, mega steelics before you can fuck it.
God, does onyx have internal organs?
How do they connect?
Like, if you break it in half, does it bleed?
Yeah, I guess I've always thought of the body as just like a series of rocks and he eats a rock
and he's like a snake.
He's like the snake from Snake.
He eats a small rock or a big rock and it becomes his next segment.
But I've never really considered what happens if you just get rid of all the other rocks.
Is he just a head?
I feel like, no, I could be wrong, but I feel like I have a hazy sort of memory or a feeling
that the Pokedex entries describing rock type Pokemon pretty much imply that, like, they're not really made of rocks.
They're just kind of, like, have skin that, like, looks like and feels like and is similarly hard like rocks.
Like, he's still an organic creature, I think.
I feel like they eat rocks, though.
I guess, well, I don't know if things can eat rocks.
There's not much nutrients and they're hard to digest.
But, like, in a fantasy world, I guess you could say they just do that and they also have lungs somewhere.
But that means Onyx has a butthole at the end.
Yeah, he eats rocks and then he eats, well, here's what he does, right?
Here's how it works.
He eats, like, rocks and gravel.
Like, he takes big bites of, like, loose rock and then he, like, digested and processes it into one, like, big, solid rock poop
and then he poops it out the end of his tail and it attaches it to the end of him.
And that's how he gets longer.
Yeah, he's just made of his own shit, that's right.
It's just the most likely explanation.
I guess somebody's got to do it.
It's a living.
But wait, where does the butthole go? Does the butthole stay and then it's just poop from there?
Does he have a butthole at the end, the other side of his head? Like, where is his stomach?
He actually, every individual boulder that composes him has its own stomach.
And its own butthole?
And its own butthole, yes. That connects to the next segment, human centipede style.
Oh, and that would explain why they get smaller, because, like, as they go through more and more stomachs, they get smaller and smaller, like, dissolved or, like, chipped away.
Actually, each segment of an onyx is actually its own little geodude that's, like, just been human centipeded together.
Wow, well, it makes too much sense.
That's why they all live together in Mt. Moon, or whatever.
Do onyx live in Mt. Moon?
Yeah, very rare to find them, but they do.
Well, actually, I don't know.
We've learned a lot about it.
They must be catchable, because I remember.
I think they might be a different case.
I know the hikers have them.
There's a tunnel called Rock Tunnel.
There is, I think, in Gen 1, yeah. Or, like, Diglet Cave.
I don't know if Onyx is living in Diglet Cave.
There's a tunnel where it's dark, and you have to use Flash or something.
That's...
That's later.
That's after, like, the place where you can go north through the water to get to the power plant.
Isn't Diglet Cave in Kanto?
No, Joto. I meant to say Joto.
Isn't Diglet Cave in Gen 2?
It's in Kanto. It's like a shortcut you can take.
That's where you find Diglet and Dugtrio a lot, obviously.
What?
I just want to be it.
I know there's a different...
I think there's a sort of Diglet Tunnel in Gen 7.
There's a different sort of tunnel in Gen 2.
I don't know.
You know, I still have not...
I've had my new phone for a long time, and I still have not started playing Pokemon Go again.
I was playing it a lot.
I was playing Pokemon Go...
I mostly saw you all playing Pikmin Bloom.
Pikmin Bloom, yeah. I introduced Pikmin Bloom.
I think so. And then I got people hooked on it.
And now, like, a lot of people are playing it, which is fun.
I was surprised to seem like a bunch of you were doing it.
Yeah, it's just because, like, as we were there, we were walking around.
We were going on days out.
There was a lot of walking happening.
We didn't want to look at our phones playing Pokemon the whole time,
and Pokemon was kind of boring, honestly.
Yeah, that would be lame.
Every time we go for a walk, we set the flowers blooming,
and we put our phones away and we just hang out.
Yeah.
I was playing a bit of Pokemon Go during the COVID week
because I was bored to death of looking at YouTube videos.
I'm like...
I'm sure.
There's a poker stop in view, not in range,
so I could get items and I could throw pokeballs.
It was like, I guess I'm just going to collect some stuff.
I don't know.
But then, because of that, I'm like,
oh, look at all these tasks that have built up over the years of me not playing this.
Man, I could do some of that.
I could catch 20 psychic Pokemon.
Come on.
Easily.
Come on, get another psychic Pokemon.
Yeah.
Now I'm playing Pokemon Go again.
I had stopped playing because it's boring,
but now it's not boring, and I like it.
Because you can walk around again?
No, because I was playing it during COVID,
and I was like, oh, I just got hooked on stat going up and getting things,
and oh, look at...
What if I catch every Pokemon I see?
Think of all the Stardust I'll get.
You know, like stupid shit like that.
So I'm just...
I'm playing it now.
Well, not now, but like...
Next time I go for a walk, I'm going to do both at once.
I'm going to put on my flowers on Pikmin Bloom,
switch to Pokemon, catch everything I can,
and then reap the benefits of my...
Look at my phone all the time.
Mmm, the massive benefits.
Pokemon or Pikmin Bloom looked pretty neat.
Yeah.
Sending your guys out on like a long journey.
Like, didn't you...
You sent one...
You sent like a...
I sent a troop.
An envoy like back to the UK, right?
Yeah, yeah.
When I got to America, I was showing people...
We were sitting in the chicken place.
Yes.
An underdog chicken.
I can't remember...
I mean, I do remember, but that was so long ago.
What the fuck?
I remember watching you send that thing.
We got the...
What's that?
Cale slaw.
The Cale slaw and underdog chicken.
I think that's what you got.
I got like just the chicken wings.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I was showing people Pikmin Bloom,
and there was an expedition in the UK
since I had been at the airport.
It was like, you know, it takes a few hours,
a few...
Like maybe a day or so before something
that you can go on an expedition for
decides to not be there anymore.
But I could do it.
So I sent them on a journey
across the Atlantic,
and it took them 25 days.
Or I said it was going to take them like 25 days.
I think when I flew over them back,
I intercepted them,
and then it sort of went to zero,
and I got their thing.
So that's pretty funny.
Huh.
You just picked them up over the Atlantic?
Yeah.
They were like swimming over it with the thing
that they had.
They were rafts.
They picked it up.
They'd gone all the way over.
Picked it up, and then it was...
They had to walk all the way back,
and I scooped them up out of the water
as we were flying over them.
Nice.
But now,
I've got so many Pikmin from Boston.
When you do things with a Pikmin,
your friendship level with that particular Pikmin
will go up,
and when it gets to the maximum level,
you send them on an expedition
all by themselves
back to the location of where you found them
so that they can pick up
like a cosmetic item based on the location.
So like if you found them at a movie theater,
they might come back
and then they'd be wearing like a popcorn thing
on their head or something,
which is cute.
And I got a lot of Pikmin from Boston,
so eventually I'll be sending like,
I don't know, 40 little people
across the ocean,
and they're going to take a long time
getting there and getting back.
Will it be another 25-day journey?
I think so.
Like 25-day journey for each person.
That's delightful.
Yeah.
Sweet.
Yeah, I just...
noticed you and a bunch of people
blooming.
We're bloomers.
I should have bloomed.
Maybe I should have bloomed.
Oh well.
Too late now.
I'll just... I'll just bloom instead.
I'll just never bloom.
I'll just never...
You know what? Fuck it.
You know, I'm already late.
I'm already late.
Why bother blooming at all?
Uh, I mean...
Yeah.
Never do it.
True!
That's why I've never bloomed.
I've always liked it just because it's like...
it's a soft incentive to walk more.
Pokemon Go feels very easy.
That's why I used to like...
Pokemon Go.
Pokemon Go is very easy to be like,
well, I've done so much,
but like, if I want the next like,
progression thing,
I need to be very lucky with the Pokemon that spawn
and I don't feel like walking to...
for so long to find that one Pokemon I need.
It's like, you know what? Fuck it.
I'm just gonna find a Pokemon if I find it at a place.
But Pikmin Bloom,
progression...
the main thing is walking.
Everything is to do with how much you walk.
So it's like, the incentive to go on a walk
is a little higher.
And the stakes are so low.
And like, the things you can get are so...
like, basic.
It's not like anything is super rare.
If you want a Pikmin that has like a cosmetic
of like a barbershop thing,
which I've got a few of those,
like a comb on the back of it,
like a little yellow Pikmin or scissors.
Get it like a pick, like a pick sticking out of an afro?
A what?
You know, like a hair pick,
like stuck in an afro.
Yeah.
That's what I would want if I had a barbershop...
a pro barbershop Pikmin.
And so like, if you want to get one of those,
you just go to barbershops and walk around,
and then maybe you'll find like a seedling.
You can grab that.
And then when they're like fully friendshiped,
they'll...
you can send them back, they'll have one.
And it's sort of like, there's no...
there's much less random chance
than there is in Pokemon Go
for you to be disappointed on a day out.
You're always making progress by playing Pikmin Go,
just...
even if you don't turn on the app,
it'll like count if you have your phone on you.
And it's like, even in standby mode,
it'll be counting your steps through the Google Fit thing,
using the gyroscope or whatever.
So it'll be like,
you turn it on for the first time in like a few weeks,
if you've just been moving around and said,
you've walked like a million steps.
See how many levels you get.
And it's like, it's good.
It's low effort, low investment,
and very cute.
What I... yeah.
What I used to like about Pokemon Go
was that it got me walking around a lot,
like when I used to...
a couple years ago when I used to play it,
I was like...
that was when I lost a bunch of weight.
Part of the reason was because I was just walking like all the time,
looking for Pokemon.
And boy, did I ever find them.
Uh...
Yeah.
I don't know. Pretty cool.
Pretty fun. Pretty cute.
Okay, well, next episode...
Beth, the end of the episode of the podcast.
Well, Ben, what about the voicemails?
Are there like a hundred thousand voicemails?
There are...
about double the normal amount of voicemails.
I looked...
Okay.
So it's not as...
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, we could just start,
and I'm sure we'll think of things to...
I was gonna say it's only been an hour and a half,
and I feel like after such a long absence,
surely there must be more to go over.
But we can think of those...
The only things I would talk about
would be like specifics of what I did,
which is just like talking about a holiday like,
oh, and then we went to the thing and we saw this,
and then we did that.
Oh, you know what?
Here's one thing.
I got high.
I got like proper high.
No!
Yes, I'm corrupted.
If you want to talk about this, you had smoked...
Correct me.
Did you smoke for the first time at Radcon 4?
I think...
I think I had smoked like a tiny bit in Radcon 3,
and I didn't get high,
and then it was like said like,
oh, well, maybe it doesn't happen the first time.
The second time, though.
But I didn't end up smoking a second time at Radcon 3.
I just didn't feel like it.
At Radcon 4, I was like,
this time I'm going to get high,
and I smoked on that like stupid video
where it was like all green.
I think that's still up somewhere on the PCP channel.
Sounds vaguely familiar.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't remember the content of the video.
It was just like whatever, we're smoking,
and Trixie was talking about how she does bongs stuff,
and I was just being like,
I sure hope I get high.
I went outside, and it was sort of dark,
and I remember feeling a bit funny.
I remember being like, whoa,
this is kind of, whoa,
the sand dunes are moving a little.
I could feel myself being a little odd,
but not like I did this time.
Nowhere near.
You smoked before,
but you took edibles this time.
Yes.
I took edibles, and I had a bit,
I had a bit one night, and I didn't feel enough.
Everyone was losing their minds,
and I didn't feel like I was losing enough of my mind
for it to be worth it.
So the next time I took a little,
I took like a lot,
not like more than was,
I think I took exactly the same amount I took last time
when I didn't feel so high,
but I was still kind of giggly.
I took that amount, but like all at once.
So before it was like spread out
over the course of a few hours,
this time I took the maximum amount that I took,
same amount all at once,
and it hit a lot harder.
And I think also I was a bit like,
I hadn't eaten that much that day,
so it went straight into my system.
I have had the experience before of eating an edible
and thinking it didn't work,
and then it hits me like way too hard.
That has happened to me before.
Now I had a really funny time.
It was like the most hilarious thing in the world,
and I hadn't experienced like time dilation before.
So I was like very confused,
but like laughing about how confusing it was.
You mean thinking that like,
thinking it's been like half an hour,
but it's been like two minutes?
It was a weird experience,
because it's not like anything felt slower.
It was just like the gaps in between things that were happening.
Like retroactively felt like they had taken extremely long time.
Like a gap in a sentence.
Somebody would say something,
and there would be a pause
before somebody says something else,
and the pause would always feel like it went on far too long
for it to not be incredibly awkward.
And I would laugh at the fact that it was so awkward
when from other people's perspectives
it would sound completely fine,
except I laughed in the middle.
I know what you mean.
I hate that feeling.
I don't like it at all.
I, you know, it does get a little much.
I was like, but I think it was because it was my first time
getting that high.
It was just like such a new experience.
I was so excited that it was working.
I'm like, I wanted people to understand that I got it.
And I tried to explain it a lot.
It's hard to explain a feeling like that.
I think, I think, I put an explanation somewhere.
Let me see if I can find.
You wrote it in the discord group.
Yes, yes, that's it.
So this is how I described it.
Day after.
Before I forget, the experience is like two aspects
of my consciousness are experiencing time differently.
Like, I know what it feels like to move my arm at X speed,
but the feedback I'm getting says that I'm going at some other speed.
Thus, there is a contradiction of experience
and due to confusion, I can only laugh about it.
So yeah, that's, and then I do a little quote like,
what do you mean it took one second?
It's been ages, XD.
XD.
And that's how it felt.
I think it's basically what happens.
It's like, I'm expecting some amount of like stimulus,
like visual and audio feedback and touch feedback
for the things that I know I'm physically doing
and the fact that it takes much longer is like,
what's going on?
Like I'm just confused at everything happening.
But like, it was funny confusion.
It sounds about in line with my experience,
except that I find that sensation really stressful.
And I don't like it.
It stresses me out.
It makes me worry.
Well, I did feel a little stressed the next day
because I was so high that I stayed high
for basically the entirety of the day afterwards.
So we got high like in the evening to watch like funny videos.
I thought it took hours.
Apparently I had passed out in like 15 minutes
or like 20 minutes or something,
which is the negative of time dilation
is that I kind of ruined the night for everyone else
because I had like a million years of experience
in like 10 seconds and then I passed out
and everyone was like, oh, well, I guess we're going to sleep.
But I was high the next day.
Was that pre-COVID or post-COVID?
Fuck.
Oh, no, if that's the 6th of June.
Oh, that would have been post.
It would have been post.
Because you got COVID on the 23rd.
23rd of May, yeah.
So I was high like for a lot of the next day.
So like people were busy and I was still high
and it was, you know, there was a whole day of like
just try to like stay, like do something,
just try to occupy your time.
It was weird because like obviously during the time I was high
time was still dilating, but it was a normal day,
which means that people were just going about their thing.
But for me, it felt like it was hours
every time somebody left the room, not hours,
but like a really long time, kind of uncomfortable
to the point where I was like, do they hate me?
Are they leaving me alone for such a long time
because they hate me?
Oh, no, I've ruined everything.
I was considering being like on Discord like,
hey, if I've annoyed you, I'm really sorry.
And then I had to keep reminding myself,
I'm high right now.
Things are different.
Yeah, yeah.
And you know, people were reassuring about it.
So it was fine.
I ended up taking a key and walking to a local park
and just sitting under a tree and just sort of sitting there.
And that felt like it took a really long time,
but it was only like maybe an hour and 45 minutes.
Was it the one by the school,
the park by the school that I'm thinking of?
I guess there's a school.
I don't know, it's a small little park.
I've heard that there's a park there
and I've never gone to it.
So I'm not sure if I know the place you're talking about,
but even though it's like right near my where I live, LaMalle.
I bumped the mic.
Yeah, so I sat, I was just trying to like,
I don't know, like sweat it out of my body, I guess.
I just sort of waiting for it.
And obviously when time is dilating
and things take a long time from your perspective,
waiting for anything to be over is like, it's too much.
My patience ran thin.
Well, actually that was a weird thing.
I could experience, I felt like things were happening really slowly,
but it was odd that my fatigue levels were not like increasing
with the time that I thought was transpiring.
You know what I mean?
Like I didn't feel more impatient or more fatigued
as much as I thought I should be
based on how I understand myself to be.
So I knew it was taking not so long.
It felt like it was taking really long time,
but I wasn't really bothered by it.
I was just sort of anxious and I knew that it would be like,
oh God, how long am I going to be like this?
This sucks when it's not like fun and communal
and people are putting on funny YouTube videos to laugh at.
When it's just me with my own thoughts, it's like fuck.
I don't like it. I don't like too much of it.
Yeah, I understand.
Well, but we did get drunk that one time though.
That was a funny one as well.
We did get drunk that one night and that was great.
I vaguely remember a lot of silly things were happening.
I had these funny fake, like huge boobies,
these fake silicone breasts that I was like,
I brought because it would be funny,
but I didn't have like the inkling to use them
or pick them up or wear them at any point
until I was drunk and I'm like...
Use them for what?
Use them for being worn.
I don't know.
I see, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was like a drunk moment.
It was like, I got to do it.
Like inhibition is gone.
But you mentioned them and everyone was like,
yes, get them.
Put them on.
I put them on.
I don't remember who gave me the dress.
I was wearing a dress though.
I also don't remember.
I don't remember.
It must have been Kazi, I guess.
I think they would be the most likely one
to have a dress lying around to give you.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I got the dress.
I remember putting it on.
And I was on the floor a lot.
It was the sort of drunk where I'm like,
I know that I'm being silly
and I know I'm making fool of myself
and it's just amusing to myself.
Right, but it's okay.
Because so is everyone else.
Yeah, so everyone else.
And so it was like,
I was rolling around on the floor a lot
or at least falling onto the floor
but not like I'm accidentally falling.
It's just like I realize now
that it is too difficult to stand upright
and there's no problem.
Falling through glass tables.
Yeah, I get blood everywhere.
No, I was like, okay,
it'll be easier for me if I just accept
that I can't stand up right now
and slowly lower myself onto the floor
and just crawl around a bit.
Among friends who have never done that.
This will solve everything.
I just crawl around on the floor a little bit.
Right.
I like being like impaired.
It's so fun.
Yeah, it's pretty base.
Yeah, I like drinking alcohol sometimes.
Whatever, yeah.
So yeah, there was the drunk night.
There was the weed night.
And there's, I don't know,
we played video games.
Did you try, did they talk you into playing
Rivals of Aether?
They did.
I played that for a bit.
I tried to play every character.
I can't play with those guys.
We're just not playing the same game.
Like, what do you mean?
As in like, I can't play it on their level.
I mean, I managed to win one game.
I know this was like past the point
where they were trying to teach me how to play
easy on me.
I managed to win one game that was for player,
mostly by staying out of people's way
and then just having more stock than everyone else.
Yeah, sometimes I can manage a win
by like cheaply avoiding combat in a group battle scenario
and letting the people that actually know how to play
like whittle themselves down.
Even then, I freak, I freak,
I have won a couple games against Munchie
and I'm convinced that every single time
it's just because he's let me win.
I don't think if you were actually trying,
there would even be a contest.
So I've given up.
I've given up playing those games over there.
I mean, the one thing I feel works
when people know a game too well
or well enough that they're high-ish level
is when you suck so much at the basic...
You just mash and just do random shit?
You do random shit?
You do things that they wouldn't expect coming
because it would be inefficient or open myself up?
It's the sort of thing that's like,
oh, I can get a few extra hits in
because they didn't expect me to do that.
And sometimes I do well through that way.
Almost the time they beat me and it's like, yeah, whatever.
I only get mad at games like that
when I feel like I performed badly for my own self.
If I lose the match, that's expected.
But if I fall off three times in a row...
It's when you could have gotten back up.
When I could have gotten back up
and they weren't even edge guarding or anything,
it's just like I was bad doing the jump thingy.
Then I feel like shit.
And that only happened once, I think.
Yeah.
There was this funny one.
I think Craig is this rock guy and he's made of rocks.
And he has rock-based powers.
He stumps on the ground or he picks up
like a little cube, little square of dirt
and you can throw it or you can place it down.
And if someone else is Craig,
they can also pick up that rock,
changes it to their own color.
They can put it down.
But allows you, who now has no rock of your own color,
to make another rock and place it down.
And they can then pick up your second rock,
add it to their collection of rocks that they now have,
because their first rock doesn't delete
when they pick up a second rock from another Craig.
So they can't make a new rock,
because they already have a rock,
but you can make a rock,
but they can steal a second rock.
Yeah.
So there was a match where we were all Craig
and we were all building rocks to try and make a staircase.
And it was really fun.
That sounds pretty good.
Someone told me that Orcane in Rivals of Aether
used to be a Vaporeon,
like the guy had built that as a Vaporeon character
and then had just reskinned it for this original game.
And I had somehow misinterpreted that
to mean that the whole game used to be a Pokemon game,
and all the characters used to be Pokemon.
So I was sitting there trying to think to myself,
which Pokemon did all these used to be?
Which Pokemon did the one with the sword used to be?
But it turns out I was wrong.
They weren't all Pokemon.
It was just the one.
Yeah.
For those who don't know.
Did the bird used to be a Pidgey?
No.
Dude, Pidgey, my favorite bird.
Play Pidgey and...
When are they going to add Pidgey to Smash?
When are they going to add his own character?
This is his own character.
He's iconic.
What are they making a Pokemon game that is Smash Brothers,
but with all the Pokemon?
That shouldn't be difficult.
That's just Smash.
Wait, no, not with all of them.
Yeah.
Well, they made Puck and Tournament.
Puck and Tournament sucks.
Is that like an arena fighter?
Where you just like in 3D, you just go...
And smash them?
It's a 3D fighting game.
And I don't know how else to describe it than that.
Yeah.
I think I've seen like one second of it.
I know you can play as Gengar, which is awesome.
It's awesome that there's a fighting game where Gengar is a character.
That rules.
Yeah, that does rule.
I think I actually have that.
Like, my brother has it.
I think we played it once.
We're in like this in the middle of the road.
And there were cars who were presumably trying to get to work.
But no, there's a Gengar wrestling with like some other thing.
Yeah.
It's in the way.
And they're just getting punched and licked.
Very, very nice.
Very nice.
Again, fuck.
Ah, damn it.
This fucking Gengar and this Brakeson just won't stop like blasting the concrete.
What were we talking about before we got on Rivals of Ether?
We were talking about like stuff that happened.
Stuff and things that happened.
Stuff and things.
Oh, I went to...
We went to see...
I mean, you didn't.
But...
Anamonaguchi?
Anamonaguchi.
I was not there, yeah.
They had a concert and surprisingly, tickets were still available.
I managed to grab one.
And it was this really cool venue.
And they did these Scott Pilgrim vs. The World movie, the game soundtrack.
Because they made that.
Yeah.
And so they played the whole soundtrack.
Including things like the menus and like the level select screen.
They had like that on for a little bit.
And then it was sort of like a huge medley of the entire soundtrack where things would
move into other things based on the way you play the game level to level.
And they had like a cool like mishmash of like video game footage and like the comic
panels that are being depicted in the video game like flashing on screen at the appropriate
time.
And it's like, ah, I love Scott Pilgrim.
What was the name of the place it was at?
The big city place.
Okay.
Big Night Live.
I don't know if that's the venue, but I think that's, I think I remember that Big Night
N-I-T-E.
It doesn't ring a bell.
But it could be true nevertheless.
It is, it was in like Central Boston, like Metropolitan.
There were big buildings all around and it was quite a, quite a classy place.
It was actually really affordable for the venue it was at.
They had like a really cool like bar.
A couple months ago, Anamanaguchi did another show here, which I also did not go to, but
it was at a much more like low key venue that is like not that far from my house.
So it was probably a completely different experience.
Yeah, this one was like, I think it was just like so big that like, I don't know, it's
hard to explain.
They had like a little floor right next to the stage.
They had steps up to a larger area that was like higher up and back a bit to the left
and the right and the back.
And then even further back, there were like seating areas where if you paid for like a
seated ticket, you could sit in on a little couch.
And then to the side, there was like this big bar area.
And there was plenty of room to stand around.
It wasn't like packed or anything, just because the floor space was a lot.
And yeah, I got a cool t-shirt there, really expensive, but I think it's worth getting
a cool expensive t-shirt for a band I like.
Did I see the shirt?
I don't know if I wore it when I was around you.
It was like a navy blue Ramona wearing a shirt of something that says Anna Managuchi.
Wait, was it Mega Man?
Did it have the little Mega Man on it?
Yeah, it had a little Mega Man Anna Managuchi and Ramona Flowers was wearing that shirt on
my shirt that I have.
Right.
They got a, those guys got a poster of that design.
Yes.
Put it up on the wall.
Okay.
Ramona looked really hot in that picture.
Yeah.
It was really hot in that fucking shirt.
Yeah, true.
Actually, I couldn't even tell if it was Ramona or just some girl drawn in the style.
Maybe it's supposed to be Ramona.
It feels like it's pretty obvious.
I mean, she's got colored hair.
Oh, yeah, it's probably, yeah.
That's the tell.
Nobody else has colored hair.
A BRB, I just got a P.
Quick.
You know what?
Me too.
A few moments later.
You're back.
Oh, there you are.
Yes.
Okay.
What do you say we started on these voicemails?
Yeah.
Oh, I gotta get to the website.
I just had some, actually this morning I made some gummies with my new, my newly perfected
recipe.
They came out, they came out perfectly.
They're, they're just, just spectacular.
I should, people have told me that I should make a video about how to make them.
And I could do that and it wouldn't even be hard.
But genuinely the thing that's, the main thing stopping me from doing it is that my
kitchen is gross and I don't want anyone to see it.
Yeah, it was a little, little grimy.
Not, yeah, grimy and honestly, even if like I cleaned it, it's even if, yeah, even if
I cleaned it, it would still look not great.
That's why you gotta get a new place.
You gotta get the, you gotta get a photogenic area where you can do all that.
I mean, let's, let's, come on, it's, it's, have you seen the housing market these days?
Nope.
Well, nothing busting anyway.
It's bad.
It's pretty, it's, it's, it's pretty rough here.
And it's pretty rough.
Good live.
I could probably live much, I could probably live much better somewhere else, but I don't
want to.
I don't want to have to own a car.
I don't want to have to drive places.
All right.
How you doing on voicemails?
I got, I've got the site here.
Are you at the, the first new one is called what do you think of Arlo?
Yep.
I'm there.
I think, okay, there's no, there's no audio.
I think he, I don't know, he's, he's fine.
He's fine.
I don't keep up with him because he's like a, he's like a news guy.
Like he reports on like the latest news of video games and I don't care about keeping
up with that stuff.
Yeah.
He's, he's pretty like, like his takes are like whatever.
Like he's a, he's a gamer.
He is.
Whatever.
I don't feel excited to know anything about what Arlo says.
I am excited about his puppet and I've always felt like he underutilized the comedy potential
of it.
He's just a guy.
Yeah.
He doesn't really do anything with that, but like if I had a puppet, if I had like a little
red man, shit would go insane very quickly.
Yeah.
He doesn't, he very rarely like does anything with the puppet other than he just has it.
Like it's just, it's just there and like that's fine and all.
He doesn't do skits or anything with it.
Well, rarely he does.
I like a couple of his longer like specific, like reviewing a specific game videos.
Like, I think he did one about Breath of the Wild and he's done a bunch about Paper Mario
games.
I've seen those, but I don't keep up with him.
I just wanted to do a silly voice at the very least.
Yeah.
It's just like a little, little girl, little girl, little girl, little girl.
I'm Arlo and he like does like that voice the entire time.
It would be hilarious.
He would have to, if he had like a second puppet that was like a different character
than he did a funny voice for.
I appreciate that his puppet just has his voice because they're basically like one in
the same.
Like I'm okay with that.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
That's me in Phantom Horn.
Baby.
Yeah.
Who would win in a fight Phantom Horn versus Arlo?
Obviously Phantom Horn, he has a katana.
He does have a katana.
He'd fucking slice him.
Arlo had a gun though.
What if Arlo had a bicarbonate reign?
What if you had a gun, Adam Sandler?
Okay.
Next one is use probably don't remember the past topics, but three, two, one, go.
They know they are wicked, but even then easily hide their shame throughout history.
It is sadly said that even most well-circled families will spawn at least one for certain.
Sometimes you can't even tell which in a crowd they are until you see the mellies in their
eyes.
And the worst is that with every shower I see myself slowly becoming one of them.
This is not a critic.
This is a warning.
Ben St. Bows are not even people.
Don't become one.
But either way, if you dye your scalp pink, it'll be great rebranding.
It'll be a great rebranding strategy.
What are not people?
Bows are not even people?
I don't know what you're saying.
You put a word and I didn't understand it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I'm afraid I don't know what you're talking about.
Next one is called Unfoto Benic Saint.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben.
I know what it feels to think you look like a decent guy and then out comes your photo
and you're this hideous ghoul.
Just what I was describing before.
And I know part of it is narcissistic bias whenever they look in the mirror.
But I've had friends and other people telling me that I look pretty decent.
Unless they're lying.
They would lie, wouldn't you?
They're just awful.
Can't trust your friends.
I think it's just the lack of depth that makes my face look weird.
But just keep your chins up, man.
There's uglier people out there and I think you look okay.
Shucks.
Yeah, well that's what Gib said and Gib was just lying to make me feel better.
Yeah, I was lying through my teeth.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just use the front-facing, or use the rear camera on your phone.
Don't use the front-facing camera.
The front-facing camera looks really shitty.
It flattens it because of your weird perspective.
It looks terrible.
Never use that.
Never use that camera.
Okay, next one is...
It's a Japanese...
Oh, it says I'm a samurai in Hiragana.
Three, two, one, go.
That was a...
That says Shanisen, maybe.
Mm-hmm.
Konnichiwa.
Be no sento-san.
Sesha wa samurai-sama de aru.
Oroko naru waka-chan yo de wa nai.
You can't just speak Japanese.
Uso de aru.
Kore ga saigo no keikoku de aru.
I don't know what you're saying.
Sukuroru wo kaesu.
You gotta listen to the tone of his voice.
I'm skipping ahead.
What if he says something funny?
Oh, no, it ends with a...
Yo!
It ends with that one sound effect.
I heard Sayonara.
Okay.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one.
You know that whale?
That one, like, Kabuki Theater?
Like, yo!
Whale, kind of.
Yeah.
I did a bad job of impersonating it right there.
Okay.
Yeah.
Next one is Ben's Weekly Reminder.
Play Deltarune Chapter 2.
Okay.
Next one is Indire Need of Help.
Tread Hot Wiping at Mae Dot Boy Wife.
Three, two, one, go.
So, a roommate recently told me
that he puts powdered milk in his milk to get more milk for milk.
Which got me thinking.
I've been training my pelvic floor muscles on the daily in order to be able
to bust mad ropes more than once
when the blessed air get released from Valsal Dawn finally comes.
But seeing my roommate mechanize basic bodily functions
such as sustenance in an effort to maximize efficiency
made me do a double take
as I've been reading some French post-modern neomorphism recently.
Am I?
By pursuing the ability to experience multiple orgasm,
not also just trying to get more sex per sex in an effort
to appease some capitalistic motion of increased efficiency.
Am I not inadvertently reducing my sexuality and enter my body
which is imbued with the mechanics of life
to a mechanized object mediated by capitalistic bio power?
What do you think, Ben?
You seem like a small cookie.
What do I think?
But continuing to pursue the ability to bust fat fucking ropes
via capitulation to neoliberal hegemony.
I think that was the Stanley Parable guy.
I also think it was the Stanley Parable narrator.
Does busting fat ropes contribute to neoliberal hegemony?
Yeah.
Sure.
Of course.
I guess obviously it does.
The means of production.
There we go.
Speaking of reading post-neoliberal Marxism
or whatever the fuck he said,
I finally got that library book
that I put on hold weeks and weeks ago.
The one that I meant to take it.
The part of the deal.
No.
It's a book of essays by Foucault.
I'm going to read some Foucault.
I have started it,
but I have not actually gotten past the preface and introduction.
I haven't actually gotten to the Foucault yet,
but maybe soon.
I'll let you know how that goes.
Okay.
Next one is called Dentist.
Three, two, one, go.
This morning I went to the dentist.
Good for you.
God, I hate the dentist.
Yeah.
She showed me the needle and said,
this is going to feel long.
Jesus.
Then she slid that big pointy needle deep into my gums
and it took a minute, a whole 60 seconds I counted.
My eyes are watering as Rod is piercing my jaw
and she looks me in the eyes and says,
this wouldn't have happened if you'd have flossed.
Yeah.
That's how it goes.
And also she put her penis in my mouth.
Oh no.
Well, that's going to be me pretty soon.
If I'm good and I do my diligence and I actually fucking,
I won't take too long to complain about this,
but I had this feeling that I need to get dental insurance
before I go to the dentist.
So I haven't scheduled a dentist appointment.
So I tried to look for dental insurance and I don't understand it
and it all seems kind of like it's fake and it doesn't actually do anything.
I mean, I would assume that the whole point
is that you need some company to do it for you.
Because they don't want you to be able to be insured.
If you have a job and they have good dental,
it means that they have a way to get through the bullshit
and allow you to have dental insurance.
Yeah, but then shouldn't there be some...
There should be a private option, right?
Like if...
I mean, I don't know.
I would have thought so, but I can't...
I don't know.
Got to get YouTube dental.
Got to be a million subscribers.
You get great dental.
Maybe I need to like bullshit my way into a job with dental insurance.
Just to go to the dentist.
What if the dental insurance company doesn't have good dental?
That's the trick.
I just don't know.
Alright, that's something to think about.
I don't want to dwell on it right now.
Alright, next one is called...
This is going to be a long one, isn't it?
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, time to make a compilation of the Twilight saga.
I wonder how long total playtime is.
Let me check.
What do you mean 30 minutes?
And I plan on adding more context and explanations to.
And some visuals along the way.
Fuck.
Really? 30 minutes?
30 minute long video with visuals?
That's gonna take a while.
True.
Let's see.
Hold on.
I'm trying to keep these downloaded as I go.
Okay, got to download that one.
Got to download that one.
Okay.
Then I got to download this latest one.
Alright.
Next one is called...
I, Ethan Ralf, have fixed what you did to him, Ben Saint.
And then there's a really long email.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, we son, we're home.
You and I, father and son, Ethan Ralf Jr.
And his dad, Ethan Ralf Sr. Me.
That's how I talk to my son.
Ethan Ralf, son.
Ian, Ian, Ian, Ian, Ian.
Hey, we, it's me, Ethan Ralf Jr.
Reborn into a good old Christian boy.
Yes.
I have to tell you something.
Was that, son?
I have to tell you that I still hate Ben Saint.
And I'm gonna kill him.
Well, son, it looks like we might be able to
make an arrangement for that.
In America.
God bless America.
Man, like this game.
Ethan Ralf.
Ethan Ralf has grown on me.
Yeah, I was just gonna say, I'm starting out
as a Christian boy.
I'm a Christian boy.
And you have grown on me.
Yeah, I was just gonna say, I'm starting,
I'm starting to come around.
Maybe he's not so bad after all.
Wait, did I download that one?
Yes, I did.
Okay, next one is called just send funnysffs 321go.
Dan, the cringest thing about the PCP podcast is
definitely nicely trying to argue about shit like
You're you're literally hearing this show have fun and you bring
How been sent in a cycle before ever either way you wouldn't change
The body casters minds like so stupid
But anyway, like what's laborally that bad really
I
Next one is called can we just get this over with already three two one go
Then send Joe Salma. Can you show what style do you need for rad can do gin?
Maybe as United people that will not be fight it
We can find a person with a right style sooner than you will upload the episodes to Apple or play delta rune chapter 2
I I
Mean all you would have to do is look up Ed and you would see how he how he draws and that's the style
That I want to approximate
Kaiju might be drawing it after all again, maybe
I don't know. I've been talking to him a little bit. He says he might have some time
So that might happen. I found another artist on line webtoon who
What did not have like a ton of views, but whose style I thought was really good
And so I might ask them if Kaiju falls through again
But we'll see I
Don't know. That's
That's sort of progressing
Yeah, yeah
The next one is called finally speaking out against the specter haunting Twitter three two one go
I've come to make an announcement when saints a bitch as motherfucker
He's such a jealous bitch showing his ass and wanting people to talk about him and he pissed on my fucking boy wife
That's right
He took a soy boy Quillie gig out and he pissed on my fucking me to her boy wife
And he said his dick was this big and I said that's disgusting
So I'm making a call up post on my Twitter.com
You're a known harasser that has spent his last year of his life bullying a trans creator and you've got a small dick
It's the size of your online celebrity status except way smaller. Guess what here's what my done looks like that's right, baby
All points no quills no pillows. Look at that
It looks like the balls in a bond and it's almost as long as the time you want without lifting. Oh
Got ya
Almost as long as the time I went without what Wi-Fi lifting
No, my gains have suffered
Thanks to COVID and other things
That's okay. I'll get them all back. I'll get them all back and more. I'm just biting my time
Become even stronger. I don't like it like a Pokemon that waits to evolve so we can learn moves sooner
I'm just waiting to become strong until later so that I can be stronger in the long run
That's I'm gonna wait until my muscles are suddenly here for the until they're ready
Ali of the Ark until they're ready to start pumping up and then
It's there's a so there's more it's more art than science. Trust me
Did I download that one? No, okay next one is called. Yes, I am picking fights in the voicemail three two one go
I feel like you guys get too many voicemails of people asking for like analysis
Like can you please explain your thought process and motives for x event or opinion?
I can't understand if you don't give me a
hyper detailed analysis
Or just people asking you to explain
like
Years long events
like which the tricksy drama like
Bruh, you can't explain that in like a 15 minute chunk
let alone
In response to a voicemail
That's like do some research
Yeah, and maybe
like
Don't ask people to give like 30 minute diatribes on their opinions
and just
Like
Let it go. Don't leave a stupid voicemail. I don't know
It's it's it's a lot
Please stop. Yeah, uh, I can't I I've
Not don't think I'm
In the mood to answer such questions anymore. I've answered them so many times already. Yeah
Uh, I guess I agree. I I yeah, I mean when it comes to like
I don't know prompts that could spark discussion. I don't hate those
But a lot of the time
If it's if it's just remember that remember that post in the comments
I posted that was just like what happened to the other people on the podcast and it's like
Those sorts of things that bro first of all you could literally just see that you could literally just go look them up
And see what they're doing like why are you here asking this now like two years later?
like like it's just it's just not the
This is not how you get an answer to that and it's it's dumb. So yeah, I
Some sometimes I feel the way this guy feels
um
Okay, the next one is
Well, there's an image. So let me um, yeah, it's a pirate flag something
Uh, hang on. I haven't described pirates
Oh, no
Oh, this was my
Oh, no, someone found my uh, my old uh, like jolly roger my fan jolly roger that I made when I was like a kid
I had no idea
That's really funny
Where would it have been
Did you have like my maybe like my old facebook or something?
Yeah from like when I or maybe no maybe like my myspace when I was in like high school
Crazy, I was a fucking they do have audio in this voicemail
Yeah, so let's uh, let's give that a listen three two one go
An explanation skull is a symbol of lasting value in memory after a person dies
They leave behind not just a body
And in this way continue to exist in our own world in addition to whatever lies beyond
The skull represents this idea
Since it is the most distinctive physical remnant of a person who has died the feathers symbolize knowledge and morality
They are blue the color of wisdom and thought cherubim before the water baby
Symbolized wisdom and we're often portrayed as blue holding box
This intelligent shit gives the feathers their moral significance calm down spike the three yellow diamonds represent light
Not a constant radiance, but a more subtle gleaming signifying a semi-divine perfection reminiscent of plate on
Ideal forms the three individually represent body mind and spirit perfection of each of which can and should be sought independently of one another
So bad. Have you achieved perfection of any of the three?
I think body can be ruled out considering the dismal state of your physical exercise and hair
I
think
I might have written
I think some of this might be based on like I might have written an explanation of what the symbolism of the
Flag was supposed to be I thought that sounded
Like yeah, something a young ben may have written. I think that might be
Yeah, I wasn't they could have just been like speculating themselves. No, I think that was from a description that I wrote and
uh
No
The answer is no
I was I was um
I don't I don't know. I don't know what else to say about it. I was really I thought angels were really cool
I really liked the metatron
I learned who the metatron was and I thought he was the coolest
And I read somewhere that he was like the scribe of heaven heaven
I don't actually think that's true or most sources don't really describe him that way
But someone said he was and I was like, oh, that's cool. That's a cool title the scribe of heaven
um
So I made that my
Theme for my pirate flag
There you go
um
It looks kind of like the the the it's a clown head with blue hair
You know what I mean? Oh, I see I see yeah, if you took away the bottom parts of the feathers
That's the first thing I thought but then I noticed they will like continue
Yeah, I see what I do see what you mean. It kind of does look like that. Listen. I was uh, I was pretty bad at stuff
Back then still am some might say
um
Man, this is embarrassing. All right, let's let's move on. Uh
Uh
Did I download that one 752? Yes, I did. Okay next one is
um another image
I made myself in like a fucking
I hate this some of this freak this fucking freak just like went to my old like
You made that Facebook as a kid of like stupid shitty posts. I made as like a child of yeah, I like made myself in the south park
Please please leave me alone. Uh, whoever this is. Uh, that's all I have to say
Uh, I gave myself a gun. I thought shotguns were cool. And you know what? I was right. I stand by it
Um, are you in heaven? I wasn't heaven. Yeah, it was heaven scribe
Oh, that's that's the guy the scribe of heaven. Yeah, sure. Why not?
Uh, next one is called wait wait wait, there's there's audio. Yeah
Oh, I think that was probably my post
Whatever
I'm not ashamed. I'm not ashamed of myself. You know what? This was cool. I used to be this cool
You wish you were this cool as me
Uh, all right, I never made a south park of myself
Oh, oh, you're missing out. I've never been that cool. So, you know what?
Check's out. You're miss you're missing out. It's it's it's good. Shit. Okay, uh,
You can download that audio right there. Uh, next one is same guy from before
three two one go
Sorry, I'm leaving a follow-up voicemail, but I'm sevin
I
Like whenever you say like, oh, what did you mean like that? It's like if you're hanging with your friend
And you said, uh, I hate kids
Or whatever don't want to have kids and they were like, um, don't you realize but everyone was a kid once and uh,
Because you're a necessary party society. Can you explain what you mean by that? Like
No real human would say that
No actual human would respond like that
They would just go, oh, yeah, I like kids or oh, okay. Yeah, I get that like
Just
don't
Stop please. Okay. Okay. He's saying that the way people ask questions is not like
The way people talk to each other when they're having a genuine conversation. That's probably true
But I wouldn't I wouldn't really expect it to be I wouldn't expect a voicemailer to ask me something in the same
cadence as like
A friend I was just hanging out with
I get yeah, I think this guy has higher expectations for voicemailers than I do
Well, I guess it's sort of like a because not all voicemails on on podcasts are about like asking questions
Or like asking to explain things. They may just have something
to mention
That on on the pcp. They're often like
questions because
The we used to have questions and then we had voicemail and then we got answers. Yeah
Uh, I mean
That yeah, that would there there are there are there are people that get all
Inquisitive annoyingly inquisitive at you and those people are annoying
Um
Yeah, okay
The next couple voicemails are all
It's all just text posts and it's just a list of
Good good good pcp episodes. Yeah, here's here's what they say porn effort
commenter rules
Up internet upbringings fat fuckery wise stuff so hard circle jerk crying conventions
Irony and sincerity indie game development last brony con oops all guests kato any episode with a guest except shred it
That's a good list that is that's a pretty
Yeah, respectable
Okay, next one is called death note fun fact number two three two one go
Hey guys, it's me the death note fun fact guy. Here's the death note fun fact
Did you know that near and mellow l successors were originally intended to be l's twin sons?
Eventually the idea was shot down because the writer of the manga could not imagine l having sex
There you go, there's the death note fun fact c and x news for another actually fun fact actually is a pretty fun fact
It is a is a fun fact and I also can't imagine l
I feel like he wouldn't find it intellectually stimulating enough. I also can't imagine having sex
Myself because it's not intellectually stimulating enough
Uh, so me and l you mean you put the penis in and take it out and you just put it in again
Like what else is what's what's what what's the point? Yeah. Yeah, what what's there to what's there to write on my blog about?
with that
uh
Good fact good fact
Next one is just a drawing of if anime was real
and there I am
And I look I look great
Yeah, it's awesome
Love it a sword got a sword got a tattoo
It's it's it's more it's more of a
of a
plum
Oh, it's black sword. Oh, you mean like you mean like like one piece
something something black sword
Uh, no, not really
It's just that swords are usually light colored and this is like dyed the metal is has been dyed or
It's some reason not a light
silvery sort of color
There's a thing isn't that that's a thing in one piece, right?
Some swords are black swords
And that's good. So it's a it's a hacky thing. It's like uh the same way that if you have a hacky infused punch
Um, turn your hand your fist black. Yeah, and it'll make your
Visually like fist black
And some swords can be infused with hacky so that they are
Forever black and very powerful base. That's me
I did it. That's you
Uh, very nice
Next one is called I couldn't get to finishing page two. I cry
three two one go
Hey guys, I'm I'm not gonna be able to get the second page of that comic
I'm drawing of you done by tomorrow
Sorry
In the meantime
Or whoever the guest might be
Uh, did you think give give a kiss for me? Thanks
Nope
Oh, but late little too late dang
I'm not in the same cut train anymore. If only this person had sent this voicemail three weeks ago
Oops
They did the joke is they did send it three weeks ago. We just didn't listen to them until now
Uh, okay next one. I guess I guess briefly. Um, people might wonder why we didn't do live episodes
Yeah, uh, aside from me having covid it technically could have been possible
But I didn't really want like the stay to be like a work thing. I was just sort of
Having a break and traveling and seeing people having fun
Yeah, and it would have been a kind of awkward just I don't know
Pause all that and sit down and talk about stuff
We could have we could have done it. We could have done it, but uh, oh well
Like I think I mentioned
I might have mentioned this at the beginning, but like I could have recorded episodes on my own
But I just didn't
I just didn't feel like doing three Ben casts in a row
Understandable. Yeah
um
So I just so I just like ah fuck it let's wait let's wait until the trip's over and then the trip got artificially extended
By coronavirus
Uh, next one is called th versus f three two one go
In episode 314 oblivion four was posturing that the difference between the th sound and the f sound is the emphasis
Which isn't really true for me and might explain why it gets the mixed up
For me a th sound involves pretty much sticking out my tongue between my teeth
While an f sound has my tongue a bit further back in my top row of teeth by my bottom lip seems pretty different to me
Uh, it is you're correct. Maybe that's why oblivion can't pronounce it, right?
He doesn't know the difference
Don't know how to do it. Yeah, someone's someone just got to explain it in the difference and then and then it'll click
Yeah, so it's a logic uh puzzle. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
uh
Okay, downloading that one
Next one is called. What's your opinion on the english pokemon logo?
I think it is terrible at gmail.com. Um, do you mean do you mean like the yellow letters with the blue border?
What else could they mean?
I mean, it's
I don't know. It's it's it's pretty boring as logos go. It's just the name of the thing in a funny font
I I don't know. I've always I mean, maybe it's just due to supreme over saturation of it
Um, but it seems iconic
I mean it is now
Yeah, it is now. It's just sort of like well. I mean iconic. It's not it's not much of a cool and like unique
Maybe it isn't maybe it's very like early 2000s
I think it's not much of a logo
Really, it's just I don't I think it is pretty lame when a brand's logo is just a word in a font
Uh, I mean it's it is a print. I mean, I guess it's an iconic font. I guess it's somewhat unique
But it's not like
Yeah, I think I agree not not that impressed with it
You know, I've just realized that the the o's don't actually look like pokeballs, which is strange
Why not? Yeah, that's that's a layout
They just look they kind of look like eyes
Which is distracting
Yeah, they got a little moon they got the little moon in there little little moonshine like eye shine thing
Hmm
The o's are the o's are maybe the most unique thing about this font
But like to what end? Hmm
Yeah, it's not it's not much of a logo and then there's just this fucking the little uh, we the fucking uh comic sands gotta catch them all underneath
Oh, I'm not saying that uh some some versions of it have that included
And like typed in a pokemon logo japanese and it just just sort of looks it looks less dynamic
I prefer the english one to the japanese one of the same style. I guess
I think the japanese one looks fine
Honestly, I think I like a lot of japanese ones like the every time there's a new generation. They change it a little bit
It depends on the yeah, they do
They do I think I like the japanese more, but it's just because to me those symbols don't just look like boring letters
They look more interesting to me because I don't
Read them
phonetically
So that's that's not really a that's that's not really a
Praise it's just a me thing
It's just I mean for me like japanese letters because I don't know any japanese
My eyes glaze over it. I don't know where to start reading it
So it doesn't feel like I don't read it. It just looks like cool symbols. It just just well
I like it. Some people would say cool. Yeah, like me
I would say
Nothing gobbledygook. It's just like gobbledygook. It's mishmash
This japanese language is all greek to me
Next one is the superior ben saint and then there's this image
Of saint ben's senate
We strive to promote students rights and to aid the college of saint benedict in operating more effectively in the interest of students
Everyone go follow at saint ben's senate
right now, please
And don't tell them who sent you please don't
Okay, the next one is a drop box link
It's a png I think yeah
Oh, is this is this the artist from before?
Oh, fuck. What's his name a new?
Yeah, I think that's their name
Oh god. Yeah, new. Um
All right
Let me hell. Yeah. Oh, I'm so excited reading reading from the beginning. Let's do it
Uh, we got um, we got a tech tech tech. We got somebody running with the apple
Bottom jeans. I apple bottom jeans. I think that's me
That's somebody they they've got a robot arm. I think it's someone else
Uh, this the pig says recipes gummies
Nate that that's the last art mail art mail is a good word
I last part it is good. Yeah, we should call nef now on
Recipes gummies Nate and then I say that isn't even what's in the scrolls you fucking lunatic
Do you mind if I check respectfully? No, what the fuck let look at this this uh, this the forehead is so true
Uh next room 313 14 15. I said respectfully. I said respectfully. Come on
Fuck off psycho. That's what I sound like
Well, if that's the case then fucking die
I'm just doing a little sad about it a little sad face doing a little sad
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Ben's gonna fucking die. Oh, man
Okay
And then bang this robot girl
It's coming in with a the robot with a with a punch
This is his necklace. I forgot his necklace is snoop hogs robot girl. Thanks. Thanks for
Thanks for saving. Oh god the boobs the boobs. They've been bigger
Thanks for saving. Who the hell are you? She literally just saved her lives. They saved us you fucking big
How do I know?
Well, you aren't sure yet. Yeah, true
then
Oh, oh, it's error arari. Oh my god. Arari then give the natefuckers are coming
And we got to give them what they want. We got to get that bastard back on the podcast
Also, by the way, Ben my pronouns are she they so keeps
Wow nice pose with the the butt prominent
And the torso turned almost all the way around anyway, just to show yeah, they could have turned around their legs around
Um, uh
It's error arari. Yeah, who if you forget was the um
What the be be be be uh, be aware of the bear prepare prepare for the bear
Quick quick quick quick get wetty
Uh prepare for the bear, uh, and then the poems about fish
Also, they draw have you seen their art on twitter? I have I've seen their sort of like
Uh, they're abstract bionicle looking s like monsters abstractly sort of like humanoid figures of like made up of
Shapes and like almost robotic, but not exactly. It's very cool. Very cool stuff