I won't bless that guy. That's son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch. Son of a bitch.
We're son of a bitch. Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Hello everybody and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The only show where Ben Saint is here.
Actually that's completely incorrect, cause we were on something else.
We were on a different show.
Oh yeah, I wasn't gonna mention it because fuck those guys.
Okay, well I still haven't mentioned it.
You mean the pro and on. You mean the pro and on cast.
Make sure to bleep that. Make sure to bleep that so it's extremely secretive.
And people ask questions and starts drama and then people attack us in the streets.
They invited, they asked me to come on and I was like, okay, I guess.
And I was shocked to show up and see you and Tom there lol.
They had asked me. It was like sure.
Yeah.
But we talked on that show the day before we were recording this one.
And now we don't have anything to say.
Oh, I spent all my content.
I mean, I'll have to revisit all the same bullshit again.
Ugh, what a nightmare for everyone, but especially me reliving this the worst week of my entire life.
What was so bad about it?
Well, was it the worst week of my entire life? Probably not.
Okay, I'll complain. I'll complain about some stuff.
I got some, you know, you know, we're both working on our secret projects and I've been trying to work on mine and I thought I was ready to post a an update for my patrons on that.
Well, and that and that was like two weeks ago and since then I have like hit a point where I'm like it's not ready, but I have not made significant progress on it.
I feel I've been hitting my head against the wall and hasn't it.
It's it's at a point where like it keep it looks the same like I'll work for a work on it and then I'll look at it and then like it's the same it didn't change and I fucking can't stand it.
I hate it. I hate I've got I'm learning to hate it and it's very distressing.
Yeah, that feels like a lot of projects get to that point where the amount of work you put in does not anymore corresponds to the amount of stuff that is new that is that you've made.
Yeah, when you're first starting anything there's nothing there and then suddenly there's something the amount of difference is staggering but every second you add something else, the increases less and less impressive.
But I know what I want it to be and I know that it isn't that yet.
And what you want it to be is good.
Good. Good, good, good.
I was working on a little bit this morning. It's okay. It's it's fine. It's, I just got to get over it. I just got to get over my shit with it and just fuck it you know just fuck it.
I was feeling a little I wouldn't say bad it was just sort of like I needed a bit of a break from from my secret project.
Not that I was going to stop doing it but like I wasn't managing everything very well and you did like a time to like really thick because I jumped into a little too quickly and planned out everything exactly.
I took a week off near the end of February to like figure it out like figure out exactly what I'm going to be doing and now coming back in March it's it's a little more clear the path to victory is some feeling.
I stepped away from it for a little while and then stepping back I felt like lost.
Oh yeah I didn't what was I doing.
I didn't exactly step back from the project I just stepped back from creation of the project and went into like a pre production sort of like a like a like a research phase.
I was trying to like figure out it's hard talking about this without just explaining what it is.
Yeah.
I mean it's obviously a creative thing people can probably get all that and they can probably be like hmm well there's only so many things it could be.
These true true they'll figure it out and then I'll be like oh I can't I can't excite anyone anymore but that's fine nobody knows exactly what it looks like and I think it's looking fucking sick right now.
They're going to be like what.
Mine is looking.
What's there looks good.
It's just missing.
It's missing some things that I wanted to have and.
Are you are you like working like totally by yourself like no help at all on this.
Yes.
Hmm.
That seems like a recipe for having to learn new skills that you don't have.
No.
No I don't agree with that.
I mean everything easy skills are easy.
Well I mean getting to a point in a skill where you can make the thing that you want in the way that you wanted in a timely fashion takes a lot of time to get that skill.
So like it's easier just to get a group of people.
I don't have a make everything.
I don't trust anyone else.
Honestly I think that anyone else working on it we just fuck it up and I would just have to like undo whatever they did.
And and and tell them like no that's wrong do it again or else just like except their version of it and I don't want to do that.
I think it would make it worse and harder and longer.
So I'm just fucking suffering through it on my own and it's gonna be great.
It's gonna be great.
I mean maybe but like is an endless war sort of like mostly other people coded the bulk of it crack was like the backbone of the initial thing.
That's that's different.
Endless war was an organic thing and I had some ideas for it but I was fine letting it sort of become whatever it was going to be.
This is not like that.
This is like I know exactly I know exactly what this is supposed to be.
So the more I just have to keep hammering away at it until it is exactly that.
So the more important it is the less likely it will exist.
I don't.
I don't understand.
Like the less the less likely you are to accept help from others.
The longer it'll take to get made because it's not that it's it's not that it's more important.
It's just that my vision is stronger.
Yeah.
Yes.
Lol.
I was thinking about like Psycholonials you've played that.
I don't know how much.
Yeah.
Did you did you play it yet?
I bought it.
I played chapter one and I'm like it.
It's it's comfy.
It's like you know it's Hussey's writing style.
It's a visual novel.
Yeah.
And that's pretty good and it's like contemporary where it's no longer taking place in the infancy of the Internet.
And it's a different way.
It's like 2020.
It's in like coronavirus world.
And it's like dude relatable haha.
I know that what it's like to have a phone and look at it.
But it's it's looking good.
But I couldn't help but notice how shit the art looks the whole time.
Like it is like one or two moments where it's like oh yeah cool.
It's it's almost like like why would it why would I waste time making it look good when you're going to be reading anyway.
I just need the very barest essential features of this character to be portrayed and the rest you can figure out yourself.
And yeah I was thinking about that because it's like it is kind of like about it.
I think that's good.
It's like Hussey's minimalist approach to Homestuck in a way as well where like I don't want to draw all that shit.
I'll use a photograph and I'll like copy paste the cathedral and make prosper out of that.
Instead of drawing it and it works great because you don't need it to be drawn entirely by the artist in order to get the gist of what it is.
I'm like yeah thinking about that like how how he can do away with the visual aspects of of a comic.
When it's not necessary.
I'm like it's it's good.
It's it's good.
I don't know.
I'm really like Psycholonials so far.
I'm on chapter four.
I just finished the newest one.
And I think it's great.
I'm excited for chapter five.
I don't want to I don't want to spoil it though.
I don't want to spoil anything so I won't go into details.
It's not the same universe as Homestuck's far as I know anyway.
In fact, the main character is a like past fan or like a once was a fan of Homestuck.
Yeah.
She mentions it once or twice.
She's got a car cat on her wall.
There's a yeah.
I don't know.
There's there's still there's still mysteries.
There's still questions that get raised in in chapter one that I still don't have the answer to.
But I mean I mean yeah I didn't really bring it up.
I've been recommending it to people.
Yeah.
I didn't really bring it up to like talk about the plot or anything.
It's kind of interesting how like Hussey used to be like like way back in trying to make quote unquote legitimate comic books with like pages and like drawings and whatever with juggle whistles the clown was a pretty cool big thing that he was doing.
And then Homestuck rather MS Paint Adventures took it in a more like fast paced.
Don't worry too much about like what it looks like is you can you can make up for the lack of visual flair with like gifts and animations because that's possible with the internet and that's cool.
That's sort of that's sort of it doesn't matter if it looks kind of bad compared to like an incredible illustration is.
I don't know it's sort of inspiring away because I was awesome.
And you know I sometimes feel like that is kind of based in a few of the shittier panels where it's just cool stuff is happening and I like it.
And then when it gets to the ending animation I think I tried I was a bit too much of a try hard with making it look good.
I drew too many frames and took too long and the end result is like not worth the time investment I put into it necessarily.
It's still pretty cool way but like I feel that way about some things that I've made that I'm like why did I bother spending that much time on it.
I think I kind of feel that way about the Slime and Punishment finale pseudo finale video like I don't know I could have done that one faster but I also could have done it easier I could have made it easier on myself probably didn't have to take as long as it did.
And you know what I think shit I think this new thing that I'm working on I think that is sliding into the same territory of like I probably could have done this easier.
I just had a vision I just had it's got to look exactly like this and exactly what it looks like I might have it must be that.
Even though it won't be because it never is nothing you make ever looks exactly how you intended it to be.
Yeah that was my secret that was my secret ulterior motive in this discussion was to get you to realize that maybe you're working too hard on something that you could cut corners on new be fine.
My my plan I was thinking about this earlier I think my plan with it is to basically release or basically show patrons the like most bare bones version of it, which is almost ready.
And just think like anything that I could possibly cut like cut it all show the most basic version of it, get there like the reaction to it, and then decide like okay.
What what do I like need to add and what can I just leave on the cutting room floor and have it still be like a functional thing that is that people would still appreciate.
It's it's I'll spoil what it is if I go too much into like what things I have started to question like do I need to add that do I need to add that.
But yeah, sometimes I feel like my desire to make the Clarissa gun smoke comic.
I still sort of intend to finish that because I wrote the ending of it, but it being like a physical comic that you could print out in like an a for you know like normal comic book shape.
Yeah, you could have it and you'd put it on your wall and not on your wall and your shelf.
Like that is like a limitation that is entirely just because like there's no reason for it to be like that at all.
There's so many more formats that it could be.
I just wanted to do that because I hadn't done it yet.
And now that I've tried to do it.
It's kind of annoying trying to get it to fit even though it's like a cool skill to have to like make it work when it works really well.
It's like a few pages.
I'm really proud of how the how it flows where your eye move thing to thing.
It's good to learn those things but like I don't need it to be like an like a comic book shaped comic.
I could do it however I like.
I could make it a Twitter comic where there's just like a panel every day or something strange like that.
I could make it look really shitty.
I could draw it using a crayon.
There's no reason the lines have to be smooth.
There's no reason there has to be like a halftone little dots.
Those are all limitations for the print media.
If it's designed to be read on the Internet or if it will primarily be read on the Internet then yeah.
What's the point?
I mean I like the idea of printing it off just because the Internet feels.
It used to feel like everything would be on the Internet forever but as the longer I have existed the more I've realized that it only exists for as long as the servers are up or the website doesn't change.
The URLs are still functioning.
I prefer everything that I ever make to at least become physical at some point so that it can't ever be completely lost.
But of course physical stuff can still get lost.
It's just sort of everything's temporary and it sucks.
When I was a youngster I always thought things would last.
They don't.
I am really looking forward to after I finish this thing then I have a little bit more to do to finish Slime and Punishment and then I'm going to make a book out of it and it's going to look great.
It's going to look so good.
It's not even going to be that hard.
I was working on making like a Bill J. Book.
Yeah.
But it was just sort of like I don't know is this stupid?
Everything's stupid.
Yeah but like is it really stupid?
Like is it I don't know.
It's the same thing with like the time wasting like I'm placing all the panels in there and I'm like copying and pasting the things and making each page look nice and I got like 40 pages in.
And I was like this is looking all right but like who cares about Bill J. that much enough to buy a book.
I don't even know if I do.
It'll be cool but like it'll be cool if it exists.
I would probably buy one depending I mean I probably buy one for like maybe a joke for a laugh.
How many pages would it be?
Because of the gifts and the animation I think it might be like 200 pages.
I would buy one of the I would buy a book of it for I don't know maybe 30 bucks 35 something I don't know how much is not in the book costs.
Yeah I was looking at this like a while ago.
Like the type of paper to use for a paperback or hardback probably a paperback be much nicer.
Just like a you know a square Homestuck shaped book in the same way that Homestuck makes their book versions.
Yeah.
I could still do that there's nothing stopping me from doing that I am pretty preoccupied with my secret project.
Once my secret project gets to a point where I can announce what I was working on and then that ball could be rolling into the future and then I can sort of I don't know.
There's so many things constantly going on.
I feel like I can only work on one project at a time.
But if you would like a bail Jake book please say I would like a bail Jake book in all camps in the comments and I will see how many people.
I have been I've been I've been frustrated with progress on the thing.
And I can't even procrastinate with Noida anymore.
I don't even like Noida.
I'm sick of it.
I hate it.
It's just it's just frustrating.
So I guess I'm looking looking forward to streaming that on Wednesday like we said we would do.
Oh yeah.
I can't I don't know now like a couple weeks ago I would be like I don't want to work anymore.
I'm going to be naughty.
I'm going to play some Noida.
Now I'm like I can't I can't look at this.
I can't look at my work anymore.
I have to do something else.
I need Noida and I boot it up and then I'm like oh god but I hate this.
This is torture.
I don't even like this anymore.
I know the feeling where you've played a game for long enough that you're like I'm legitimately not interested in playing this anymore but I've made a habit of it and I'm booting it up yet again.
Yeah this sucks.
This sucks.
This is so boring.
I wish I was at work.
I wish I was working a nine to five right now.
Sometimes I wish I worked in 95.
It would just be it would just be so easy.
There would be nothing at stake.
You just clock in.
You fuck around.
You follow instructions for nine hours and then you leave.
Oh but I'd probably get COVID though because I'd have to go out into the world.
So never mind.
I don't wish that.
I wish I had a nine to five dig in graves.
Oh that's tempting.
That's tempting.
Oh god I wish I I wish I worked minimum wage so that I could get that fucking $15 an hour.
Timmy.
That didn't go through though did it?
No it didn't go through.
It didn't go through because those eight fucking demons voted against it including the only,
the first openly bisexual senator serving in the Congress.
Who was that?
Absolute girl boss.
Was it the lady who?
The one who did the cute little curtsy and the thumbs down.
The cute little fuck the poor.
No thanks essential workers.
Does she have an argument for that?
Would it be something like oh 15 is too much.
We should be 14.
No thanks.
To my knowledge no she made like a tweet that was like an image with like a paragraph.
Explaining like how much she cares about like the little guy.
But I don't think it explained like actually I think that we need to give subsidies to businesses instead of raising the minimum wage.
I don't think it had like a thesis statement or anything.
So it was just like pretending to be good.
Classic.
I think it was basically just like no guys no I do care though in spite of everything I promise.
It's funny.
It's really funny when legislation gets denied.
It's a very popular proposal.
I think it's like 67% of people supported but some fucking Congress people are like no.
Why is this allowed to I mean like I know like it's it's complicated getting people in office and out of office but I feel like if the majority of people.
Or like the majority of someone's who they vote for a senator or whatever for their place state.
I don't fucking know they vote for them and then they get elected and then they do something that the majority of the people who voted for them do not want.
And that's fine.
They can just vote in someone else.
But like for that one moment that they voted and they waited and then the senator they elected didn't do the thing they wanted.
That's not representing the people but they can't do anything about it until the next election.
The fucked up thing is that she and like most of the other or at least several of the other people that voted against it like we're on record like on Twitter and stuff as being like pro raising the minimum wage.
Like they said they were for it and then they voted against it.
Yeah.
So it's really fucked up.
Like if anybody voted for those people to get them elected on the assumption that they could get the minimum wage raised.
They've been lied to but they the voter has no power to like protest.
They can write an angry letter I guess but the voters pass have to wait until the next cycle.
They just have to they have to wait.
And then like OK are you going to vote against minimum wage again and it's like no I'm going to vote to increase it.
I'll do it this time.
I promise.
And then it doesn't happen.
They vote against it again or it doesn't even come up or something.
My favorite one of my favorite posters Posadas Trapgod got banned from Twitter because he told the senator cinema that she should jump into a volcano and that was against the terms of service.
That's that I mean that was that's just too violent.
That's just too like that's that's so abusive.
And you know she's just she's just she's just a simple bisexual woman trying to live her best life as a girl boss.
You can't go tell you can't go.
That's violence against women to tell a senator that she should jump into a volcano.
Have you have you seen the temperature of magma.
I mean what the fuck that's so high.
It's high.
Distressingly so.
Oh man.
That guy.
That that stupid piece of shit.
Dev Devtrospective a.k.a. the short fat otaku a.k.a. Sargon's Todi.
Oh you had a thing on with Twitter a little bit ago.
Like like like several months ago I think I had a fight with him on Twitter.
He was the guy who I correctly identified that he was like regurgitating Sargon shit.
And then he he's he wouldn't drop it.
He kept like laughing at me like haha you keep talking about Sargon.
That means that Sargon lives in your head rent free.
Yes in fact I am close personal friends with Sargon and I message him directly.
And I messaged him to tell him that haha Ben St. knows who he is.
That means he wins.
But it's you Ben in whose head he lives rent free.
You fool.
He showed up in the in response to me saying something disparaging to senator cinema to say like it was it was funny.
And by which I mean it was infuriating.
He was like haha rack up another L lefty and the strange part is like that guy hates Democrats.
He thinks that like the Democrats are bad.
So he showed up to laugh at the Democrat at Democratic Democratic voters like me or so he thought.
On the basis that the Democrats did what he wants because he hates the minimum wage and wants there to be no minimum wage at all.
He wants to lower the minimum wage not raise it and the Democrats did what he wants.
And to him that means that the Democrats have failed and are bad and he was there to make fun of them for it.
So I don't really get the angle there.
The angle is hate that guy.
The angle is haha I get to love but people who didn't get something they wanted.
He thinks the Dems are so despicable and yet he is more like them than I am.
They would he and they want the same thing.
So I don't know what I don't know why he thinks he's so fucking high and mighty.
I think he's just maybe happy that something triggered the left triggered the lips.
Something owned the lips and he was like haha now I like that haha I am not owned.
I make slightly more than minimum wage and therefore I will only laugh haha.
What a fucking bitch what is what a stupid what a stupid fuck I fucking hate that guy.
My blood boiled I saw I saw him.
I saw him show of my men cheese and immediately my blood starts boiling like this fucking mutant this fucking blight on humanity is back back to torment me from the beyond the grave.
It never ends.
Oh, I guess.
Okay, okay.
Speaking of Twitter.
I want to.
I want to talk about getting canceled for being racist.
Yeah, what the fuck.
I was very racist.
No, I don't think I was being racist.
But people thought I was racist because a guy actually I think they're non binary.
A person a black person artist on Twitter said if you draw.
Well they were talking about characters with like the big lips right characters that were like derived from.
Blackface right mostly in Japan because Japan's a little backwards I guess right well I mean.
I don't really understand because like it's it's not like it's only black people they draw this way like they draw Japanese people like the guy in the guy in what's it called.
I know the guy you mean the big boyfriend man.
No, not big boyfriend man.
There's like a show where there's a big Japanese man and he's like in lovey-dovey relations with this girl.
It's just a romantic cute show.
Oh, oh that one.
Yeah, that's not I was thinking of the editor from.
Oh, by the one with him.
Yeah, the editor from Bakuman.
Like he's not black.
He's Japanese.
But I guess okay whatever this this artist said like hey don't draw characters like this if you want to draw a fan art of them draw them different.
And then they showed like two examples.
One was basically just no lips.
And the other one was like Steven Universe lips.
And we're like here's two examples of how to draw them.
And then and then they showed like you know USOP draw in the way and I was like I think that's irritating because I don't know I just thought I just thought it was weird.
I think it's a weird reaction to be like the fan artists need to like do something about this like fan artists must simply simply don't draw the character how they appear in the media.
I don't know.
I didn't agree with it.
I didn't agree with it and I said it was bad and people said that's racist Ben and I said oh shit I shouldn't have waited into this discourse.
Well, I agree with your general premise that it is weird to expect that of fan artists because they're just drawing characters the way they look.
But the way you said you expressed your discontent with this like perspective was the cringe moment.
Yeah, I don't I don't blame anyone for getting mad at me.
I don't I think it was I should have expected it.
I was asking for it.
What I said was what I said was what did I say?
This is no ACAB ACAB includes art cops like don't be like don't be an art cop like you're being an art cop by policing what people draw.
Which was an inflammatory way of phrasing it and people were annoyed people didn't like it and like yeah, I get it.
I get it.
I was being a dick.
I was being a dick and so for like a whole day my men she's were just like but some some of those people were some of those people were just being unreasonable like the white people.
There were too many white people in there trying to trying to cape trying to trying to attack me for and fuck all those people those people were wrong.
And there were there were a few people saying like you need to pay money for this here is my cash app send me money.
And I thought that was funny and of course I didn't do that but I wonder if like that works.
I get several people were on several people were on some bullshit of like oh this guy made a tweet.
I'm gonna one call him racist and to demand that he pay either me or some black people I know.
And I like I want does that does that work.
Do you mean I guess if somebody says something like out and out completely racist and they mean it they wouldn't donate after saying it.
Obviously it would only work.
It would only work for people who slip up slightly on accident and then they feel bad and maybe they do that.
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
But I I never feel bad.
I can never be made to feel guilty enough to pay money for anything.
So it doesn't work on me.
They were very disappointed.
Yeah.
I think OK I've been I've been thinking about it since then and I think that the I can the original tweet I can interpret it in a way that I completely agree with which is just like as as advice or like how to avoid drawing a racist character design like you can simply draw them a different way.
And like I would say yeah you sure can and that's fine and good and thumbs up.
So there in that case there was no need for me to criticize this person.
And if I even if I interpreted in like the least charitable way even if I decide like oh no this person was saying nobody should ever draw like this and if you draw like that you're a bad person in your racist right.
Like even if they were saying that which they weren't honestly their tweet was like very polite and like pretty pretty moderate.
So it wasn't even like that.
But even if it were like that it's not like this person has any power to like make anyone draw anything any particular way so it still wouldn't have really warranted me like getting upset about it.
So yeah the whole thing was a mistake and stupid and I would not do it again if I could go back.
I would undo it if I could.
Well the only way to undo it is to pay up.
Pay all black artists.
So someone told me just pay every black artist.
OK.
How many could there be.
There can't be.
It can't be that many.
Twelve.
Easy.
Fifteen perhaps.
Well so that was a nightmare.
That ruined my day.
What was that like.
I was like last Thursday or something.
I don't know.
I eventually had to mute that whole thread because I just was like I can't keep.
I can't keep.
I can't keep dealing with this.
I can't.
I don't want to see any more of these replies and every time I see a reply I'm tempted to sarcastically respond to it and like that's only making things worse.
Yeah.
I must stop myself and I must stop myself.
You were going into like Bencinct Twitter mode sarcastically replying to a lot of the people who did not know who you were or what you were like and just thought based on what you were saying that this guy is a racist and doesn't respect doesn't believe like that.
I saw a lot of people who were like confused and they thought your use of ACAB was like disparaging.
Sarcastic.
They thought it was sarcastic.
Yeah.
Like I was making fun of ACAB.
Like no.
No I'm totally ACAB.
It was a very confusing moment.
Some.
All around.
Very.
Mostly me.
A couple of people saw the phantom horn.
Maga hat DC riot drawing.
That was funny.
That was pretty funny.
They were like oh my god this guy is like a he's one of those conservative bronies.
He's one of those Trump or bronies.
Like.
I wish.
That would be that would have been epic.
Unfortunately.
No.
Well.
So.
So you know these are.
So that's two things that were bad.
This week.
I'm sure I could think of more.
Nope.
Well that's not so bad then.
I guess it's pretty good.
I don't know.
How are you.
How's your.
I don't know.
Yeah.
The week has been.
It's just been.
Yeah.
I don't know.
God this sucks.
You know what.
I have.
I think.
You know I'm complaining about this rut that I've been in with the project.
But I think.
Like yesterday I finally started to climb out of it.
I think yesterday I actually got like.
I got more done yesterday than I had like for a few weeks.
And so I think and then again today I'm like okay.
I've made a little bit of progress again.
So I think I'm finally like.
Climbing out of it a little bit.
Wait a minute.
One last thing one last thing that's fucked up.
The hot water in my house is broken.
I have no hot water as of today.
I'm hoping that that gets fixed soon.
If it doesn't that would suck really bad.
But I guess we'll see.
I hope I don't have to like heat up my bathwater on the stove.
That would be that would be unfortunate.
How cold is it over in Boston right now.
Like outside.
I don't know.
It's pretty cold.
I mean the water is icy.
The water coming out of the showers just is just terrible.
Medford, Massachusetts temperature.
It is 37 degrees.
So a little above freezing.
It's chilly.
It's getting warmer though.
It hasn't snowed in a while.
I feel a little stupid.
Because like, you know, we come on the PCP.
Well, I mean, I yeah, you know, it's me.
But my last week has been very monotonous.
Regardless of progress I've made on my secret project.
It's like I work on that.
I was doing some stuff that I can't talk about.
Lamau.
Then at the end of the day, I checked the Bitcoin.
Bitcoin went down.
Oh, Bitcoin goes up.
Hmm.
That's nice.
Bitcoin goes up and down.
And then I look at it.
I'm like, huh, well, if it's gone down.
Hmm.
Well, it should go up soon when it's going up.
But it's going to go down some point.
Like that's every day.
My musings on Bitcoin is just one or the other.
And I'm just looking at it.
And it's just like I'm just living like a dull life.
Oh, are you are you like obsessively checking it?
Not obsessively checking it.
It's just sort of like a thing I've fallen into like at the end of the day.
I wonder whether it's done well today.
Oh, it has.
Oh, it hasn't.
Oh, well.
Oh, hell yeah.
And then like at the middle of the night, me and my brother will go downstairs and watch
two more episodes of Bovee the Vampire Slayer.
And that's been epic.
The last time I was, I had some Bitcoin.
I was checking it obsessively and it was really bad.
And I was like watching it constantly.
This time, it's not like that.
I've, yeah, I'd like, yeah, I've just, I check it like a couple of times a day.
Just look at it and like, oh, that's the number.
Okay.
And it's fine.
It's going to the moon.
Yeah.
Honestly, the crypto hype has worn off.
I'm not.
Yeah.
I'm not interested in what happens unless it goes really big.
And then I'm like, oh, I suddenly have a little more money.
That's nice.
But if it doesn't ever do that ever again, ever in the whole existence, then I'll just
probably not notice and I'll be like, whatever.
I'm going to, I'm going to be watching it for a little bit because, you know, they did,
they cut the 15 minimum wage, but they did pass the STEMI.
So STEMI STEMI checks are going to be going out probably in the next couple of weeks.
So I'm going to watch that.
I was looking, I saw people saying on Twitter today, like, you make sure you put all your
fucking STEMI into Bitcoin because that's going to the moon and fiat currency is a thing
of the past.
And I'm like, I'm rubbing my hands like, yes, the plan, the plan is all coming together.
I'm going to, I'm going to stick with it.
I'm going to stick with it.
I think it's going to work out.
Oh, it is at five.
It is, it is just hovering right around 50 K right now.
It is like just bouncing around.
Is it 50?
It is exactly 50,000 point one, right?
Oh, 50,000 even.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, it's going down.
No, it's good.
It's actually dropped quite a bit since the episode started, but it's been going up this
week.
So it's fine.
Uh, someone.
Oh, there was a good comment.
Uh, there's a good comment on last week's episode.
Now I got to find it.
Uh, it made me chuckle.
It was about crypto.
Was it like do the opposite of Ben St.
And you will make money.
Somebody said that and that's true.
Except this time.
This is the time.
Oh, here.
No, here it is.
Maric 24.
Ah, yes.
It's time for my favorite podcast, the pro crypto traders podcast.
I'm supposed to be trading right now, but I'm not trading.
I'm fucking crying.
GameStop is soaring.
Bitcoin is dying.
Uh, true.
Too true.
Too real.
Well, voicemails.
I guess so.
I mean, I, I, I feels like I, I could have had maybe more to say it was that, it was
that damn pro and on cast.
They, they, they, uh, let us dry with their asking of questions about stuff.
They, they let us dry, but also, I mean, I, I went on there to complain about Trixie,
which is something that I don't, I want to keep like limited a bit here on this show.
I don't want to do too much of that.
So if I, if I were gonna, if I were going to continue on that train, I, I guess I could,
but like, I don't want to on the PCP anymore.
Like that's fine.
I've said enough about it.
Um, so, I mean, I guess fine.
The, the interesting thing that, that episode they were talking, they basically had us on
to talk about the anniversary of Rack on four, which I think was then, or is at some point,
cause it's March now.
It's, it's this month.
It's sometime this month.
Is it the end?
Is it the end of March?
I don't even remember.
Well, I forget the, the exact like dates that we were here.
Um, but, uh, dumb, it's in March and it's been a year.
And I guess, you know, the things we said on that show, the same that we would say here.
More or less.
Which is, uh, please don't kill us.
Please.
We're trying to get the stuff out as fast as we can.
I don't feel bad.
I don't feel bad about the other stuff.
I don't, I don't feel bad about the stuff that we haven't released yet because it's,
I've said this already.
I, I don't want to delve too deep into it, but it's, it makes sense.
Like the, the, the final, the, the OVA, like it's got work, it's got work in it.
And like it's going to be, it's people are going to like it.
Even if people don't like it, people will at least nod and go, I understand why that took a year.
Um, oh, I gotta make a, I gotta make a beach background.
I gotta draw, I gotta draw a beach.
I tried and I failed.
So I gotta try again.
Did you use the wrong color for the scene?
It was piss water.
I, I just, I, I opened up like a, I opened up like a photograph of a, of a nice sparkly beach.
And I tried kind of like painting it and it just looked like shit.
And I just trashed it.
It was like, I'll, I'll try again tomorrow.
Uh, it just didn't look.
The water looked like goo.
I don't know.
Yeah.
What is hard to paint?
It is.
Um, I'm no, I'm no landscape artist.
I'm not like super good at painting like a sunset on the sea.
Uh, it's not really my forte.
Mmm.
But, uh, she just used, she's just steel photographs.
No.
It's just steel photographs.
Like, what are they going to, like, what are they going to do about it?
What's anyone going to do about it?
Um, they're going to say, no, it's not that it's just going to look worse.
Oh.
Yeah.
That would be bad.
Um, you say that, but I don't know.
And I say it because I mean it.
I don't, yeah.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know if my drawings would be any good.
I mean, I guess they'll be fine.
Thank you.
Good at drawing.
What are you saying?
My, my beach, the beach background on the radcon for poster.
It looks okay because it's like mostly hidden.
I went in and I, like, I took the figures out of the foreground to just have the background
only to realize that the only, like the very edges of the drawing are complete.
And like the middle behind everyone is just like smud, it's just like smudges and blotches
and it's just, it's like nothing.
It's like nonsense garbage.
And I was like, and I realized, like, oh shit, I don't, I don't actually have like a drawing
here.
I have just sort of, I just kind of worked around the edges to create the approximation
of a drawing of a beach.
Uh, now I have to actually do one.
Ugh.
I mean, it's not that hard.
It's just like you get a rectangle of sky and you get a rectangle of little thin, thin
rectangle of ocean.
You got a, you get sand on the bottom.
I was looking at a photograph and the, the line where the sand meets the water, I was
looking at it and I was like, wait a minute, water is clear.
What the fuck?
Like I can like see the sand through the water and like the only indication of the end of
the water is just like a very slight, like a white line.
But then it's sort of like the blueness kind of like creeps in as like you get a little
further from the water line that sort of mutates into blue very, very gradually.
And I tried to like approximate that.
And I think the end, it ended up looking like a lagoon.
Like the water wasn't sparkly enough.
The water was too like, just kind of look like thick blue ooze.
And I was like, no, this garbage trash.
You've got to look, I mean, it's an anime thing.
So just look at what anime does.
How do they get the limitations of having to draw it all?
You know, that's a way better idea than trying to copy like a photograph because it's supposed
to look like an anime.
Oh my God.
So it's so obvious, so simple and clean.
I'm going to Google it right now.
Anime beach.
Why don't I just, let's just steal this, just steal this.
What's even the point?
What's even the point of making anything original?
Literally, there's none.
No, yeah, I can't think of anything.
No, not a damn thing.
Some of these don't even look real.
Some of these, I'm sure these look fine like in a show when you're not paying attention
to the background, but scrutinizing them, it's like, that's not a beach.
This is a mere facsimile of a beach.
This is just colors on canvas.
This is just an arrangement of pixels meant to approximate an image of a vista one might
see in nature.
What the fuck is this?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Fuck art.
Fuck art is what I'm saying.
Voicemail?
Yeah, that's voicemails.
Let's fucking voicemail.
Hopefully some of them will distract us from this nightmare.
Okay, it looks like the first one this week is called, ass blast at last, 3, 2, 1, go.
The large samurai is right back.
Hello, American, hello, American conservatives.
My name is Genki Fujii.
I'm a Japanese journalist and an author of modern 70 books on international relations.
I know this.
There was a Japanese man who was part of the Republican something, CPEC.
President Trump fought against Chinese communists in order to protect the entire free world.
President Trump is a real American samurai.
I want to make US Japan alive and stronger.
I almost built a solid friendship with real American patriots.
This is some bullshit.
This is some...
Yeah.
It's like a Japanese man doing samurai moves and saying, I love a president to Trump and
then he has the Kawasaki scrolls or something.
Was he doing like sword moves?
Yeah, he was doing like the real American samurai or something.
It's like, okay.
Oh, wow.
That sounds pretty funny.
I need to crack open.
Republican samurai.
So like, I wonder if they're affiliated with the Kawasaki clan.
The Kawasaki clan?
God, I hope not.
If they were, that would explain why I ran away and betrayed them.
Next.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Ben is canceled.
Three, two, one, go.
Wake up.
Check Twitter.
Ben is canceled.
Yeah.
Good.
No, I'm uncancelable.
I'm uncancelable.
There was one.
There was one person, a white person, by the way, who retweeted me saying like Ben St.
is a racist and a homophobe and an ableist because he says the N word and many other slurs
in the tales gets trolled lecture.
And they tweeted the tales gets trolled lecture time stamped to when I talk about the words
of power.
And I was like, well, I've made my bed time to lay in it.
But it got like eight, it got like eight likes.
So whatever.
Did they know about your video beforehand or did they get mad about the Twitter drama
and then go watch your content to find stuff like that?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Like they would have had to watch like a full two hour video to find that.
I do wonder because it doesn't seem that ridiculous that somebody would like find somebody freshly
canceled or like freshly on the cusp of being destroyed online and then just click on their
social media links, look at their stuff for the purposes of like adding fuel to the fire.
I don't think that's like that out of the question for some people to do.
No, but but I would be surprised if they sat through a whole a whole lecture.
I yeah.
Looking for it though.
So I don't know.
And this this person was then like they they made another post afterwards that was like,
I didn't really understand it, but it was funny.
It was like someone just blocked me and I don't appreciate like I wish you would have
the decency to just tell me if you're going to block me because it's so nerve wracking
and it makes and it's so upsetting to me because I don't know why it's happening.
And I don't know like who blocked them or anything or even if it had anything to do
with that post.
But I thought it was pretty funny that they would that they would try and cancel me like
that and then get like so upset that someone they don't know blocked them.
I don't know.
It was a funny, funny moment.
I guess if you employ yourself in that sort of culture where people get like burned at
the stake online on Twitter that you'd be terrified if you were the one in the line of fire there
because you know what it's like to burn someone else.
I can imagine your own angry mob because you are one of another.
That person's avatar was hideous.
Just like very, very off putting for various reasons.
I just want to say fuck you your avatar is ugly stupid lol.
Okay, next voicemail is called Sniper King 3, 2, 1, go.
I completely understand not liking the idea of deeming some art unacceptable.
But as a black man and one of your likely very few, very, very few black listeners,
I will say that I am disappointed.
You can't call a black person an art cop for very reasonably asking people to not draw
characters with racist features.
That should make you very questionable.
It got worse when instead of apologizing for misgendering someone in their replies,
you just told them you'd never read a bio.
Come on.
I don't feel bad about that.
You keep saying that you didn't say anything racist,
but it's not your explicit words that made people think that.
It's that your reaction was to defend artists drawing racist caricatures,
which they should be smart enough not to do even if usops lips really do look like that.
Re-examine some shit, man, because that whole thing made your advocacy look just a little bit
on the performative side.
I partially agree with that.
And don't say Negro.
Okay, gotcha.
I partially agree with that.
I don't feel bad about the bio thing.
I didn't read that person's bio.
I didn't know they were non-binary.
I don't feel bad that I accidentally called them she.
I don't care.
Well, I think that in that instance, you didn't say the word sorry,
so they assumed that you were like...
I wasn't sorry.
I don't feel bad about it.
About misgendering someone accidentally?
I really don't.
Yeah, I made a mistake, but I don't think it matters.
It probably matters to them.
I think that's the point, isn't it?
It doesn't matter to them.
They were there.
This was that same person.
This was that same person with the ugly avatar.
Do you think it really hurt their feelings that me,
who they were there to call out for being racist,
didn't know their gender?
It's not that in any individual situation,
maybe somebody doesn't have a problem with it.
It's just the idea that as a rule,
you should probably do it just in case they do have a problem
or they would feel sad,
because some people feel very strongly about that.
I should have just said nothing.
I do agree.
I do agree that calling them an art cop
over the not wanting people to draw racist characters,
I do agree that was foolish of me,
and I don't stand by that.
So I'm with you there.
Yeah, I guess that's it.
Thanks for your voicemail, sir.
Sorry.
I feel pretty stupid about the whole thing.
I hope not too many people made voicemails about it.
I can see one that might be about it.
Okay, that's cool.
Next one is called Kringus Bingus 6.
Three, two, one, go.
Here he is.
It's me, Kringus.
Back after your little break.
Hi.
My fate, my Kring this week is that,
I think two weeks ago now,
Ben mistook some random voicemail color
who just happened to say Kring and Bing for me,
and it wasn't me.
He didn't sound anything like me.
He did outside of the single thing,
my Kringus Bingus,
and it made me very offended that Ben did not,
Ben thought that someone else was me,
because I thought me and you were very good friends, Ben,
so I would like you to apologize,
and I will accept your apology,
and we will continue to be friends.
Oh my God.
Sorry, Kringus Bingus.
What I've been binging is,
I've been binging the Sopranos,
the HBO show from the 2000s.
It's actually pretty good.
That's a pretty good one.
It has a lot of emotion and drama,
and it builds this web of these characters
who all lead very intriguing or dangerous lives,
and it has a lot of heart,
and it's about family,
and it's about obligation
that people think that they have,
and it's a very smart show.
I would recommend it to anyone.
You can torrent it.
You don't have to have HBO.
Okay, yes.
Kringus Bingus is out.
Goodbye.
Okay, goodbye.
Thanks for recommending the Sopranos,
Kringus Bingus.
I am so glad to know that it's good.
It's got a good intro song.
You listen to that,
and you're like,
well, I want to listen to that again.
The episode itself is like,
whatever.
Tony Soprano going,
hey.
Yeah, yeah, that's my shit right there.
Okay, next one is
Kringus Bingus bonus episode two.
Wow.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, it's Kringus Bingus with a bonus episode.
But how do I know it's Kringus Bingus?
He says he says he's Kringus Bingus.
I've been thinking for a while,
for a few weeks, actually,
that I've been thinking about
is everything that Trixie is doing,
everything Trixie is doing right now,
not only did you take all of her videos down
from her channel,
and she didn't give everybody
a lot of time frame
that she said she was going to give them
to do it,
and then a lot of people didn't have
videos that they wanted,
so everybody's mad about that.
And also, not releasing the Burning Recture,
you can just give it to the backers
as backer content,
or you could just release it.
It's whatever you want to do.
But I think that you should put it out there
because even though it wasn't explicitly
promised in the rag-con for Kickstarter,
everybody expected it,
and you didn't make it clear
that it wasn't backer content.
So I think it's weird not to release it,
and you should release it
because everybody wants to see it.
I agree 100%.
Kringus Bingus out, goodbye.
Hey, that was a pretty good bonus episode,
Kringus Bingus.
I like that one.
Was that two crings and no-bing?
Was it just one cring?
That was two crings.
I think it was multiple items
under the umbrella of a single Kring category.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it was just a Kring,
but a fairly broad and robust Kring.
Okay, next one is called...
Oh, yeah, this is gonna be great.
This one's called Racist Ben Strikes Back.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah, I knew it.
Ben was racist the entire time.
I'm sorry.
I feel stupid.
I'm stupid on Twitter, lol.
I see that there's another one coming up
called Sniper King 2,
and these were all released on the same day.
So that one's gonna be great.
I hope that one doesn't make me feel even worse about
the things I said.
Okay, next one is called...
Bort Coop.
This is Ben's weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
Number four, three, two, one, go.
Nah, but in all seriousness, though,
Ben, you're totally right on Twitter.
It's a shame you're getting ratioed by these absolute brainlets.
I'm not totally right.
What do they expect to do with their claims and shit?
What do we do?
Just not draw Usopp anymore?
Just because he looks racist?
It's a racist caricature or something?
No, that's literally bullshit.
Anyways, it's your weekly reminder to catch up on one piece, Ben,
if you haven't already.
I know it's been soiled a little bit, you might want to say,
but just do it, fam.
No, no.
No, I actually...
I always knew Usopp was racist,
and that's why I liked it from the very beginning.
Oh, no.
I like Usopp. He's my favorite.
This is stupid,
but I always associated myself with Usopp
just because he has curly hair, and so do I.
Yeah, no, I didn't see that.
Somebody asked me,
what did I say?
Was it on the PCP that someone asked who was the best?
No, it was in my Discord.
Someone asked me, who was the worst straw hat?
And I said, probably either Nami or Chopper.
You know, these days, probably Chopper,
because he has become entirely a mascot
and with no interesting anything,
and it sucks to see.
It's not Chopper's fault, but he's been relegated to a cutesy face
that does nothing.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
So I guess that doesn't change.
That was the case back where I left off as well.
I guess Nami does some stuff.
Nami has like remotes.
Chopper's probably become worse than Nami at this point.
Nami had her joke,
well, the straw hats have their joke,
and Nami's was like, I love money.
I'll do something for you,
but you have to pay me a lot of money.
And that got boring,
and that seems to have been dropped as a thing she does.
The other characters have funnier jokes that have stuck,
like Zoro constantly losing direction.
And you know,
I don't even think Chopper does the hiding
on the wrong side of the door thing anymore,
which is upsetting.
That was like his whole thing.
It's his best trait.
I mean, he still does the thing where,
what's his thing?
It's that if you compliment him,
he gets shy, but also gets really rude about it.
Yeah, he's really aggressively bashful.
Yeah, aggressively bashful.
Well, I have like a year's worth of one piece to catch up on.
Is it good? Am I going to enjoy myself?
Yeah, there's lots to love.
I'm really enjoying it right now.
Would it be spoiler to ask, are they still in Wano?
It depends on where you are in Wano right now, but...
I was like pretty early on in Wano is where I left off.
Okay, I mean, Wano was built up to be a big arc,
and they're still in there.
Okay, okay, I thought so.
Oh, I want to catch up on one piece,
but I want to finish my fucking thing.
But we're finishing my fucking thing is so hard, and I hate it.
But if I do anything else, I'll hate myself even more.
Do the thing, Ben.
Okay, you're right.
Just got to do the thing.
Next voicemail is called PCP Adjacent Discords.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, just wondered if you know of any PCP Adjacent Discord servers
you could tell me about that aren't Endless War,
and that I don't even care if they're hidden behind a paywall.
I joined this art community because it had a really active voice chat,
but everybody always treats me like I'm crazy.
Like I ask like, hey, do you guys think Loomis is a meme?
And like a roomful artist just sound baffled.
Like what the fuck is Loomis? You mean the truck company?
No, the construction method.
Like I'm sure Ben knows what Loomis is.
Of course they know Loomis.
Yeah, I need friends who know what I talk about.
That's well, okay.
A good one there for art specifically is the Quickdraw server.
That's pretty active.
The Quickdraw Saloon.
I mean, I haven't looked at it in a while.
Is it still active?
Yeah, people post their art and respond.
Tom posted something quite recently actually, that's pretty cool.
A little 3D model.
But yeah, it's a pretty thriving community of artists
who can talk to each other about cool shit,
and it came from the PCP drawcast.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, that seems probably like exactly what this guy is looking for.
So I guess I'll just second that and say
the Quickdraw Saloon is still around.
Just being itself.
Okay, here's the one I'm dreading.
Next one is Sniper King 2 Damage Control.
Let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
I realize my last voicemail may have been too hasty, too harsh for what this was.
It's been a rough year for my people, you feel?
Shit is touchy.
If a character is in black or black coded,
it is reasonable to say that even if they have those same features
that are reminiscent of black caricatures,
they are divorced enough from that context.
That's whatever.
I still think with a character like Usopp,
it should be on anyone who draws them to know that that shit isn't right.
I don't care if that's his canon appearance,
people should be smarter than them to draw his lips like that.
I love listening to you guys, keep just being cool.
Hello, my favorite podcast.
Right after the Pizza Party podcast.
Nice.
Okay, I guess I'm just curious then.
I don't even disagree that the way that Usopp looks is kind of racist.
I think that, yeah, it probably is and it makes sense.
But I mean, I'm assuming that if you don't want people to draw him that way,
that would it also be good if Oda stopped drawing him that way?
If Oda redesigned him, maybe that would be good.
But also, I know it won't happen.
So, I don't know.
Maybe that's what people should...
Okay, like I said, I don't feel like I was completely justified in getting all huffy about it.
I feel, you know what?
It's very awfully, awfully considerate, awfully considerate of this guy
to even be like, hmm, maybe I was too hard on Ben.
I don't think you were.
I don't think you were too hard on me, my guy.
But thanks.
Yeah, it's touchy.
You know, Twitter drama aside, the idea of fan artists drawing characters that are inspired from a artistic style that is racist
is an interesting question because it's not an obvious like, just don't draw them.
Because like, I don't know if I see a fan art of Usopp.
There's nothing about that that leads me to the conclusion that the artist is a racist person in any way.
And I don't know whether like, one piece is overwhelmingly popular.
But it's not about the artist.
It's about like, you know, if this...
It's about the depiction.
And if the depiction is based in this like stereotype.
Okay, well, I guess...
Well, that's why it's an interesting question because like, one piece is extremely popular anyway.
I don't know if people, like there's that much of a backlash against Usopp in general by people who read one piece.
There's some.
Maybe.
I mean, obviously there's some.
I don't know.
Like, you can understand the racist roots of that, the lips and stuff and still like, I don't know, talk about it.
Not that anyone who was getting mad at you was like in the wrong for getting mad at you.
But like, there's a, I don't know.
I feel like there's more than just a don't draw Usopp conclusion to this.
The original post.
I mean, the original post went even further and said like, don't even draw like Japanese characters with lips like that.
Because it's like still based in the same like depiction, which I mean, I don't know if that's true or not.
I don't know the history there.
And then they also said like, but it's okay if the character isn't human.
And then they showed like Feebas, the Pokemon who has big lips.
Yeah.
I was a little confused about that because like drawing lips that have a like an outline.
I think the understandable way to describe it is like a lips that have a consistently thick outline all the way around.
Like they're not like, they're very cartoony and not realistic because lips have like a in the middle.
They're the thickest and the edges that thinner.
Like that doesn't necessarily have to come from a racist black character caricature place.
Just because that did exist.
Like not everybody who draws the that lip on like a Pokemon necessarily thinks of that as the way to draw things.
You know, it's like maybe it's it's more complex, but like I totally respect anyone who just doesn't like looking at that.
It makes me it makes me sad.
It probably makes lots of people sad that like Usopp has this like his depiction has this kind of like sort of connotation to him.
Like that's a real that's a real drag.
Yeah.
I don't like it.
Oh, it makes me want to just makes me want to just makes you want to do a colonialism.
Real bad.
Just like a lot of realism.
You should finish.
Psychologials.
I want to talk about Psychologials.
Yeah.
I'll get put up.
I don't know if I have that much to say about it.
Other than just that I like it and I'm looking forward to more of it and I'm not sure where the story is going.
There are some things that I are funny that I would like to point out with interest and go haha did you notice this later.
But I don't know your own chapter one I think it gets pretty cool from there.
I was I mean I was already into it by chapter one at the end I was like end of chapter one I was like oh I didn't expect to go here.
But it did.
I've told people that I'm reading it and I get a lot of a lot of skeptical replies that are like oh how's he thinks he's going to tell a story now after what he did I don't think so.
You're like oh there's no way that how's he can keep up with a release schedule.
And I'm like I said that you weren't the only one though you weren't the only one.
But I think I think he can.
I think he can do it.
Well definitely now seeing it being like oh this is just like like very low key like.
Like I feel like he probably put together the entire thing himself aside from the music.
Yeah.
Like coding it and everything because it's very simple looking very simple feeling.
But it's it's writing and he's good at that.
Yeah.
Oh you know one thing one thing about it that I noticed is that Z is she looks like punk because she wears a purple dress and she has black hair.
And she does look a lot like punk actually.
Yeah.
She I feel like this is this is like maybe it was definitely an irrational thing because it doesn't matter at all really.
But every time somebody has a character design that is even similar to one of mine that I've already made.
I'm like shit.
I call my lawyer I get my lawyer on the phone and I say how much can we squeeze them for.
It's not it's not that sort of angle it's like shit I've I've I've sat on this character design for too long I didn't become famous yet.
Now people are going to think they came up with that idea first and I'm a copycat they're going to think that I'm copying this Z character.
You.
Okay.
All right.
Here's what you do.
You get screenshots.
You get receipts.
Right.
You show like oh I posted I posted bail jpe in you know summer of 2019 or whatever it was.
A year.
17.
It was a while ago.
Maybe actually no no.
2018 probably.
So it's like I posted it before.
And you know.
Cycloneos is clearly just a bail jpe rip off and I want my fucking royalties.
It's it's like I don't know.
It's not that it's worth like bringing up but if any people see see this first and then find like if I don't know bail jpe gets big.
I use punk again.
Then they'll be like this reminds me of that thing and I will have to be like either explain like actually I could have thought of it first.
I thought of purple.
I thought of putting I thought of putting a girl in a purple shirt first actually so.
It was a purple dress with like black tights which punk has.
It's the case.
It just is the case.
They're going to say you just are.
I had a girl in purple back in 2018.
You're insane.
You're crazy.
You don't you can't you can't remember the past.
Let me gaslight you over it now.
There was never there was never a girl with a pumpkin head.
That's ridiculous.
Like who would even I don't remember any such thing.
You imagined all that.
No.
I made bail jpe.
And then and then you post that one fan art you did.
Yeah.
And I was like this came out like years before you were born.
I was like no this can't be the truth.
But yet it is.
Okay.
Next voice mail is called your name is spades slick three two one go.
I hate to moral coward one who lacks a manly spark.
I just detest a man afraid to go home in the dark.
I always spend my evening where there's women wine and song.
But like a man I always bring my little wife along.
I'm a member of the midnight crew.
I'm a night out and a wise bird to home with the milk in the
morning singing the same old song.
With the sun early to bed and you miss all the fun.
Bring your wife and trouble it will never trouble you.
Make her a member of the midnight crew.
Thanks for the voicemail.
I like that.
I've never been singing it though.
Eleazar make those all line up so it doesn't sound like shit.
Thank you.
Please.
Next one is called Lou three two one go.
In my talents I shaped me.
Fucking him as I.
Around me is a burgeoning empire of silicone.
For my phone lines have come Korean into the skies of her.
My winds will become lightning bolts that devastate me.
Out of the chaos he will run and whimper praying for me to end his.
Anarcho capitalism.
I'm drunk with this vision made me fucker.
The title suits me well.
Yeah.
Nice.
There should be an earthbound about the Nate fuckers.
Like.
Like you play as a group of four Nate fuckers on your way from region to region to fuck every Nate.
No, no, no.
You play as a group of Nates and the Nate fuckers are all the enemies.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I feel you.
It's like Yoshi's.
Yoshi's Island with all the Yoshi's, but there's just Nates instead.
What's the Nintendo 60 like Yoshi's story where you can lose the Yoshi's and you can't get them back?
Yeah.
The one where you collect fruit and it goes in like the border all around the screen.
It'll be like that except when you lose a Nate, the Nate gets fucked.
Oh, yeah.
So really just want to lose all the Nates as fast as possible.
That's how I thought you won.
Next voicemail is called meaningfully content.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So I've...
Voice Grail.
Wait.
He can't voice grail something just because it was surprisingly terrible.
He fucked it up so bad.
Okay.
Next one is called name my...
Name my poo poo fart noise.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello.
Regarding Golden Witch's new name, I got to say Digi rolled up the tongue really well because it was like a nice little two syllable thing.
And while just mumbling the name, my brain came up with G Witch.
G-Wee.
Doesn't that sound like a lot more...
I mean, she's got Trixie for the short and sweet way to say it.
We've been saying Trixie.
Like, I mean, yeah, if she'd always been Trixie and she changed her name to Digi, you'd say, oh, but Trixie just rolls off the tongue more.
Oh, this new name is so awkward.
G-Wee.
No, I'm sorry.
No, it was a good try, but in the trash.
Yeah.
Trixie or Bee.
I don't...
Those are easy to say.
Beatrice Bee.
Yeah, they're fine.
Okay.
Next one is called League of Blankfuckers, Incorporated.
What could it be?
Three, two, one, go.
Please, please, please suck my dick.
Okay, I will.
You know what?
I fucking will.
Yeah, it doesn't say Nate, and there's only three S tricks.
It could be Benfuckers.
Oh, they're...
Oh my God, you're right.
There is three Asterisks.
No, there can't be.
There can't be another League.
That's too fucked.
There's only room for one League of Fuckers in this town.
The Rowdy Fuckers.
That's right, the Rowdy Fuckers.
The next voicemail is from youtube.com slash user slash DG Valentine, who...
I don't know who that is.
Three, two, one, go.
No, that the era basically is over.
I've been wanting to ask about DG slash Trixie, sorry.
Yeah.
What did the...
Did you ever heard of DG Valentine?
And he has a YouTube channel.
He also did like video games and anime and whatever.
You heard of him?
No, never.
Okay, I'll go kill myself now.
Okay.
I have started up a video.
Okay, talking about nights into dreams.
Looks like the last upload was like five months ago.
So this is a real Nate.
This is a real Nate style YouTuber you might say doesn't upload.
No, I don't know.
Whatever, similar names.
Haha.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Mingus...
Mingus Sweepgus.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello and welcome to video games.
I have one million hours in mind.
I've played it all throughout university.
My first shitty job and my second slightly better job.
90 to 98% of the time.
The game gives you perfect information to progress unhindered.
It's just a game of attention span and slight logic work.
Each number represents the amount of minds around it.
Nothing more, nothing less.
I'm going to boot up a game right now.
It was very cringy to hear you talk without authority and criticise.
I admitted it.
I said this as much last episode.
There will be moments where you're forced to do a 50% shot,
but it's a minority of the time in the long run.
Those are versions of the game that eliminate that entirely.
My personal favourite version is the one on mobile phones called Polish Minesweeper.
It's icon is a nice little slick mine on a soft black background.
It's got satisfying animation and that's nice. Goodbye.
Does it have ads though?
I don't like mobile apps that are free that have ads.
I delete them immediately when as soon as I see an ad.
Oh god, I just started up a game and I don't want to play it.
Oh god, I hit a mine.
Why would you play this game if you just leave hitting mines?
We should definitely do that thing.
I can't remember.
Like a Minesweeper race or competition to see who can...
Oh bonus episode?
Yeah, that was the bonus episode idea.
You're right. We should.
How do we know who wins? What are the rules?
We'll play Minesweeper and whoever wins is a base and whoever loses is cream.
Okay.
It scores you, right?
Like, yeah.
Oh no, there's a timer.
Yeah, like how fast you can do it and then how correctly you do it, I guess.
I feel like it should keep track of how many spaces you clear
because the winner should be the one who clears the most spaces before dying, right?
That seems...
Maybe. I haven't looked into it, but we should definitely do something like that.
But it doesn't say... it doesn't keep track of that.
It seems like the easiest way to judge who's the best Minesweeper.
Yeah, we should do that.
Okay, next one is called Trixie.
Hey, by the way, I want to say Persona 5 is great.
Three, two, one, go.
Lol.
Is he like running away from a dog?
I don't know, maybe.
Whispering like running away from a dog.
Okay.
It's too late. It's too late.
The videos are private. The views are gone.
Comments are gone.
It's all been said in motion.
Next voicemail.
I'll email you my suicide note after.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, my name is Jebediah Brickinson.
I will kill myself if BGNA slash Trixie will remove her channel.
Goodbye.
Well, I mean, the channel's still there.
It's just called something different.
Yeah, sorry.
And the videos are gone.
You can't do it on a technical...
Sorry, you technically can't kill yourself.
Whoops.
Next voicemail is called Knock Knock Joke.
Please play along.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey.
Okay.
So you saw the name of the voicemail.
I'm going to tell a knock-knock joke.
And old boys for you guys to respond.
And it's going to be really cool because it's going to sound seamless-ish.
And it's all going to come together.
And it's going to be really good.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Sam.
Sam who?
Konnichiwa.
Samurai.
Faka-yu.
Meno-shintou-san.
Samurai-6.
Beno-san-0.
Faka-yu.
Okay.
Until next time.
Sayonara.
I, well, I've been, I've been got, I've got that one.
Oh no, the tricky, tricky Samurai has...
The war, the war continues and the weapons only get more technologically advanced.
Yeah.
Devious even.
Next one is called Bill.
Three, two, one, go.
Based, based on what?
Yeah.
Nice.
Based on, on like science, you know, like acids and bases.
Based in reality.
Oops, there goes gravity.
Based on alkaline.
Won't not get mad at you.
The liquids and the test tubes and the phosphorus pipettes and titrations.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called Hey Quick Question.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, so I barely graduated high school because of my math grade.
I became a custodian about three years ago.
I cleaned toilets at a fucking elementary school.
I work 12 hours shifts regularly to keep up with bills and other payments.
Sure.
I don't know how I will ever move out of my parents' house.
I want to make comics, but I'm not going to drawing yet.
I have very little free time.
I have a turn to edibles and alcohol as a form of escapism.
Am I missing something?
Or do you think this is my lot in life?
Thanks.
Why do you have bills if you live with your parents?
Maybe they're asking for rent.
I guess so, sure.
I mean, you sound young, so I wouldn't say that's it.
And if you have an idea to, you want to make comics, it'll just be a matter of time.
If you put the time in to learn how to draw.
Yeah, I mean, that's what I would start doing if that's what you want to do.
I mean, I hope you're practicing if you're thinking of doing something like that.
The definition of insanity is trying the same thing over and over again and expecting a different result.
I don't know, man.
I can't tell you what's going to do it for you, but you got to try mixing your life up in various ways.
And just see what happens until something sticks that is maybe a little better than what you got going on right now.
Sorry, I can't be any more specific than that.
Everyone's journey is their own.
Everyone's journey.
If you don't have a lot of time, you don't have no time.
So you should just allocate time to the practicing.
And over time, you will get to a point where you can maybe make comics.
It really is like, you know, the pathway is always the same.
It's just like difficult depending on your situation.
And if you have no time to do it, it's more difficult than if you did it when you were at school, but you can still do it.
In the meantime, try and, I don't know, I'm surprised that you have to work 12 hour days to pay your bills while living with your parents.
I don't know, maybe you could find like a roommate situation that would be cheaper and then you could have more free time.
I don't know.
Think about how to keep costs down so that you can get away with doing less labor.
Maybe you already, maybe, maybe you already did that.
But if you haven't thought about it, I'm sure you have.
Never mind.
Fuck.
No.
And no, actually, you know what?
Give up.
No, just give up.
That's that's what I would say.
Okay.
Next one is called Oreno Sad Stonks Monogatari.
Three, two, one, go.
Since we're all still talking about our stupid stock stories, I guess I'll talk about my own.
Please.
A couple of years back, I started investing in this company called Billy Billy, which is the parent company that owns a game called Azure Lane, which is basically just another mobile fap game.
And I wanted to invest because I knew they were going to make gangbusters someday.
But then I saw some others thought called Aurora cannabis and they were really cheap.
So I was like, yeah, let's let's put my money in there instead.
And so you can guess what happened.
Billy Billy is now like 120 something dollars last I checked when it was like 17.
I was going to go in and meanwhile my weed money is just floundering and not doing anything.
So stocks are fucking stupid.
Just don't do it.
Why did you change course so much?
You could have diversified instead.
You you went all the way in on someone else.
I guess maybe you didn't have a lot of money to throw around.
Yeah.
Yeah, like buying.
If you keep if you keep buying and selling, like you're more likely to come out behind because like.
Like every transaction has fees associated with it.
Like, you're more likely to do well buying and holding.
I mean, unless the stock you've got is just like, you're sure that it's going to tank and then sell sell sell sell.
This from this reminds me the talking about the FAP games reminds me.
Did you see, do you know Grums?
Nope.
Grums is a guy I I guess he worked on World of Warcraft.
I don't know what his deal is, but I see him on Twitter every now and then saying some really stupid shit about the culture war.
And this week he made a tweet that was like, you could never sell you could never sell Conker's bad for a day today.
Like they just it couldn't make it today.
Totally oblivious to the fact that literally you can buy it right now.
And I hate it.
You couldn't sell that today because nobody plays platform games.
I mean, people bought ukulele.
Well, not that many people.
It was a Kickstarter hype thing.
And then oh, I just looked again and now two hours ago he tweets three days later and people are still upset at me for making a video game tweet.
Get over it.
I fucking hate this guy.
I fucking hate him so much.
You should just admit you were wrong.
You said a thing and it was wrong.
And you come back and you're like, huh, people are mad at me because I said something that was wrong.
Get over it.
I hate you.
I fucking hate people like this.
What a piece of shit.
Oh my God.
I don't know, but like, I don't know.
A lot of people commented like, you can like, what do you mean you couldn't sell Conker's bad for a day?
You can you can buy porn.
You can buy porn games on steam.
Like shit hasn't been censored.
It just hasn't.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't get it.
I should stop looking at Twitter.
I've probably said that every week for like two years now.
But maybe this week I'll do it.
Maybe this week I'll finally quit looking at Twitter.
Maybe you could make maybe you could make like a stupid game of it and see like every week.
We'll check in on Ben saying see if you've been on Twitter.
There'll be a corner of the show has been saying tweeted.
Has he been on that Twitter?
If you see me tweeting or liking on Twitter, send a voicemail saying.
Fuck you saying, oh, you fucked up saying, oh, you're an idiot.
Don't actually do that.
That would be really annoying.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called hi Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
We need to get Nate to go into Trixie's computer.
Hack it with his elite programming skills.
That baby release the lecture.
I agree.
Nate should go on a fucking secret mission.
Nate should go on a matrix.
You should get the he's got the sunglasses.
He just needs the trench coat.
Nate should send Michelle in as a secret operative to distract the residents of the Trixie house.
And then sneak in behind the scenes and extract the data on a disk drive and upload it into directly into the main frame is what I think is what I think should happen in my opinion.
Next voicemail is called hi Ben two, three, two, one, go.
Also is Davoo still alive?
Yeah, Davoo's still alive.
Yeah.
Do you not follow her on Twitter or davoo.com?
She has a website.
Yeah.
She's had one for years.
She's been making posts on it occasionally about her games and stuff.
I think she made, yeah, she did.
She made a video game instead of a vlog.
It was like a blog.
She called it, which is an update, but in the form of a interactive experience.
So if you want to know what Davoo's going on about, check that out.
This is not.
I don't think it's Davoo.com.
Okay, there is a website called Davoo.com and it is a game developers website, but it's like definitely not.
Yeah, I remember typing Davoo.com and getting that.
I was confused.
Whatever it's the Davoo.com.
Yeah, this is it.
Last updated February 9th.
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't know what they were working on.
I guess they're making a new game.
That's kind of cool.
The last one, did you play the one that was like a little puzzler?
I did.
Yeah.
That was pretty good.
That was a purple one.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
It's pretty short.
Hex game.
Yeah, that was, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, Chamber of Hex.
Chamber of Hex.
Hex game is completely different.
Autonomous was really good.
Chamber of Hex was fine, small.
I'm okay.
I guess the new game is called Chiro?
Chiro?
It looks like another walk around.
I don't know what genre you would call adventure game.
Wait, what are you?
Where are you looking?
I'm looking at thedivu.com.
Oh, yeah.
Finally, I asked the game Chiro, Chiro.
I've been working on.
Did it.
Played a trailer.
Oh, yeah.
It's called something.
No, wait.
Something stuff about the game is called something city.
Oh, this is Chamber of Hex.
It's going to be top down adventure game.
You must explore two realms one peaceful realm of colorful losers and another dangerous realm of chaos and madness.
Why does this look so awesome?
I love it.
I like the vu style.
Yeah, me too.
I've always liked the funny little drawings she would put in Digi's videos.
Yeah.
Hang out in my house, Glog number one.
Free to download on itch.io at thedivu.itch.io slash Glog dash one.
Okay.
Well, I won't watch any more of that right now.
I might check that out later.
Next voicemail is from Ritsu Zizix.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
I wanted to know your guys's thoughts about NFT and crypto art, because you've been talking a lot about Bitcoin and Ethereum and stuff.
And NFTs have been really big lately.
So what do you think?
Will you sell any?
Thanks.
Those are, as far as I know, NFT non fungible token and crypto art is it's like a token that is a token of authenticity.
It's the only one of these that can exist.
And they are assigned to things to give them a seal of this is the image.
And if you copy paste it will not have this token.
So if you want the genuine article, then you have to buy it from me.
You can't copy paste it.
I think that's the idea.
And people are making a lot of money selling things art, I guess.
But an image is just data.
Can't you just copy the data?
Well, I don't know.
I think the token doesn't allow for you to just copy it.
That's why it's like that.
Okay.
Some sort of technical wizardry.
I'm just saying.
I mean, I can kind of understand how you could make a token that is linked to something like an image say that is, you know, non fungible, I guess.
But like if it's linked to an image, like to display an image, the computer has to be able to access its data.
And therefore that data could be copied.
So I don't know, it just seems like a stupid gimmick.
It is a stupid gimmick.
Like you could absolutely just copy whatever it is and you could display it and it would look exactly the same.
But if somebody checked the metadata for that thing, it would not have the token.
It wouldn't be fungible.
Yeah, yeah.
Awful.
I think it's just terrible.
I don't know about, I've been hearing that crypto, I guess, is really terrible for the environment.
And I guess it's because like the mining process now is complicated enough that mining a new Bitcoin takes like astronomical amounts of energy.
Yeah.
In computing power.
I've heard that as well.
And so this, I don't know whether this, like, I guess it must, if it's making people upset about that.
It must be generating additional, like aside from cryptocurrency, it will be creating additional waste of energy just to make this stuff, these tokens.
I guess so.
So yeah, I despise it.
It's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
And if it's bad for the environment, then there's all the more reason to not like entertain anyone who has these things.
But people are stupid.
So that is not a surprise that is making money.
Okay.
But I mean, crypto would be okay for the environment.
It's just that our sources of energy are bad for the environment, right?
Like it's because we rely, it's that we rely on like non replenishable like fossil fuel that makes it bad.
Yeah.
Screen house guesses are the end result bad reason for using energy.
But yeah, we're not at a stage where we're totally carbon neutral.
Yeah.
But if we were carbon neutral, then crypto wouldn't be any worse for the environment than anything else, I think.
No.
Like if we could just harness the power of the sun, like we could put a cryptocurrency machine on the sun just uses the heat energy of that somehow.
Dyson sphere.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Just get the bitcoins sent through space to us.
That would be the day.
Imagine all the bitcoins we could mine if we could harness the sun.
Harnessing the sun and all you do with it is just mine bitcoins.
You put like solar panels all the way around the sun encasing it completely blocking out the energy for everyone else and light and everything and the entire solar systems becomes dark.
But you're rich.
Nice.
I mean, that's that's what it's all about, right?
That's that's what I'm in it for.
Oh, someone just told me.
Someone just told me to stop being racist on Twitter.
But it wasn't in response to that other thing.
What else did you do?
It was because someone was complaining that it's a what the fuck it's someone said that it's gross to call.
It's gross to call Senator cinema a bitch just because she voted against the minimum wage.
And I called them a piss rag.
I called them a sopping wet piss rag.
And then someone replied to me to say stop being racist.
Which, you know what?
I don't I don't know if I can take this person entirely seriously.
Lol, because that was a white person.
That was a fucking white person that I call the piss rag.
So I'm good.
I'm solid based.
Next voicemail is called there is a spider in my rectum.
Hee hee.
Three, two, one, go.
Previously on the procrastinators podcast.
Fuck you.
Ben no sentosa.
And now it's really conclusion.
Fuck you.
Ben no sentosa.
Okay, until next time.
Sayonara.
Thank you.
Wow.
True.
Sad but true.
Next one is called sincere engineer.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, if you like girl emo music.
Check out the band sincere engineer.
They're pretty new and super cool.
Okay, I will.
Okay.
Wait, I'm going to Google them.
Oh, no, they're cringe.
Sorry.
What?
How'd you know?
No, I, if you, if you don't know, then I can't explain it to you.
I'm sorry.
I went on on Spotify to look them up.
Oh, so if you saw an image, I didn't see it.
I see some images of a girl who I guess is the band.
So there we go.
Cringe though.
Should I reply to this guy?
She's got a Dave Grohl smile.
Dave Grohl?
I don't know why.
Something about that cheek combination makes me, reminds me of Dave Grohl smiling.
I kind of see it a little bit.
Should I, is it worth responding to this guy with a bunch of question marks?
I'm going to do it.
This guy told me to stop being racist.
I'm engaging.
I'm going to give him six question marks in a row.
Oh my God.
There we go.
Yeah.
Deal with it.
How could you do something so controversial yet so brave?
Good sucker.
Okay.
Very based.
Next voicemail.
Okay.
Error Array.
Bear and the Cluster Punk Orchestra present.
Hashtag rip RIPCP.
Three, two, one, go.
I am supposed to be drowning right now.
I forget.
Was that like the theme?
I think I heard the theme in there.
I guess so.
Did, did we leave off where they were, cyborg was drowning?
I don't, I don't remember.
Someone give me a refresher.
Someone give me the cliff's notes for the bear versus cyborg saga.
Next one is called Error Array and Bear's Missile Maelstrom Catastrophe.
Three, two, one, go.
Konichiwa, guys.
I'm supposed to be drowning right now.
But I'm not drowning because I'm floating.
Bear and I are currently stranded at sea.
Someone from the voicemails left us here, Teehee.
Join us for a PCV mystery.
Because when we find them, it will be a Cluster Punk Missile Maelstrom Monopoly.
Uh, yeah.
Hey, you heard Doft Punk is, is exploded.
Doft Punk ended.
I heard that, that goodbye video they made was actually, uh, like from something.
Like it wasn't an original Doft Punk.
Like, like it was, it existed before the, the announcement.
I didn't know that.
I was just saying this guy could probably do the voice of Doft Punk.
He could bring him back.
We could, we could, we could weekend at Bernie's, we could weekend at Bernie's Doft Punk.
If we were dedicated enough, but we're not based.
Next voicemail is called ETFs and index funds.
Three, two, one, go.
So an index fund is just a pool of money that follows an arbitrarily defined index, which can be the S&P 500.
It could be wheat stocks.
It could be cryptocurrencies.
It could be just about anything.
So when people tell you to invest in index funds, they usually are telling you to invest in indexed S&P 500 ETFs.
Right. So an ETF is an exchange traded fund.
So that's something you can trade as if it were a stock.
Right.
So, you know, just keep in mind, like you could, you could be a part of like a mutual fund and you could be putting money into your mutual fund and that could just be an S&P 500 index.
That's, that's not good because mutual funds tend to have very high fees relative to ETFs.
Boring.
So if you want to be like a very conservative long-term investor, you usually just want to make sure you put your money in, in those low fee ETFs since they're going to give you the best long-term rate of return if you're just like a passive investor.
It sounds like this doesn't even have any like, any like non-fungible tokens attached to it.
Yeah, where's the funny coin at?
Where, where's the silly, where's the silly number?
Where's the memes? Where's the memes at? I can't do it unless there's a meme attached.
I don't, I don't even want to make profit unless it's, unless it's either funny or edgy.
I don't want to make profit unless it's funny. Okay.
It's like, if, if, if at the end of the day, if I can't laugh about it, then, then, then what was the point?
I say throwing my money into the sea. Yes.
Maybe I'll listen to this again after the show when I don't have to pretend to be too cool for financial information.
Next voicemail is called more like what the fuck bang three, two, one, go.
I know mukbang is a loanword from Korean, but why do we have to keep it in English?
It occupies like the same space in my brain as bukkake. It sounds like a gross porn word.
It's about like eating. It's supposed to be about eating food on the stream.
Oh, it's cool. But no, it has to have a word that makes me think of like the Pokemon muk and come at the same time.
And it's just gross. Just stop. Why just come say eat food stream.
Um, I don't think of when I think of the word bang, but I can see why you would.
Mukbang definitely sounds dirty in more ways than one.
I agree. I kind of agree. I don't see why we couldn't just have our own word for it. That's like less, I don't know, ugly.
I only recently learned what it was, actually.
I didn't know until I happened to click on the right opinion video about that guy, that one guy who does it.
The never ending nightmare of Nico Avocado, I think.
I don't know. Maybe you've seen that one floating around the recommends.
The only one, I don't even know if this counts as mukbang, but it's one munchy as posted multiple times because it's really funny.
It's this guy, extremely fat white guy eating a like a sloppily eating like an entire chicken.
That is not mukbang. That's some weird fetish shit.
It's very, very gross and he puts it in rhythm all the time.
Mukbang is like, I mean, people are eating, but it's mostly about talking, right?
It's people talking and eating, either they're talking to each other or they're talking to you or something, almost like an ASMR video, right?
I thought it was mostly about the eating.
I feel, I don't know. I thought that the eating was sort of like incidental.
Maybe you'd show up and it'd be like, hey, I'm going to eat all these tacos or something, but like, yeah, they're eating the tacos, but they're like, it's not just them eating the tacos.
They're also like engaging you, talking to you, having a conversation or whatever.
Do you mean that the primary thing is just like a feeling like there's a person that you're hanging out with?
Because I feel like that's basically all streaming.
I guess so.
Like, I mean, it seems like the Nico Avocado video made it seem like all of his mukbangs are like, it's him like dishing.
It's him basically dishing the drama about all the other mukbangers.
Mukbangers.
Like, it's like, come for the food, stay for the-
The cum.
Stay for the cum.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a weird word. I don't like it either.
Okay.
Next one is, it cut me off at the end, but I made my point also was drunk.
Three, two, one, go.
So I'm here replying to a previous voicemail I heard before regarding how one should measure their recipes.
And while I agree that weighing by mass as opposed to volume is the superior method.
It's going to be more accurate.
A lot of American recipes seem to be piecemealed out via a volume instead of mass.
Yeah.
Which creates kind of a catch-22 situation, right?
Like, if they are measuring my volume and giving you instructions by volume.
How can you accurately measure by mass?
Most recipes that I find online do measure in volume.
How do you know the volume they have is accurate?
How do you know?
It seems like it's imprecise and dumb.
Okay.
And it's a weird thing that we shouldn't have.
But at the same time, historically, cookbooks aren't like perfect things you just follow.
You know, if you go and you do some research into the cultural context of historic cookbooks,
you'll see that a lot of them were kind of assuming you had a base level ideas and they were to give you inspiration or alternatives or various things.
You know, they weren't expecting you to know everything.
Yeah.
I feel like I've noticed when I look up for a recipe online for something, if it's an American website,
it'll be confusing to me because they say things like cups.
And I don't know what the fuck a cup is.
Do you not use cups?
Well, no.
We use accurate measurements like grams and stuff.
Cups are perfectly accurate.
Sometimes there's like, use a teaspoon of this because it's not that necessary to be super accurate.
But like, I don't know what a cup is.
What is a cup?
I mean, it's a conversion.
There's a simple conversion from cups to milliliters.
What's a cup and a jug and a mug?
A cup and a jug and a mug and a like a tanker.
Okay.
It's true that most recipes that I find online are measured in volume.
That's no excuse for me.
That's really no excuse for me because I'm like, I was making up the gummy recipe on my own.
I could have been using mass if I wanted to and I just was sloppy about it.
The cup is, I don't know, it's like if you like, if you like cup your hands together and you kind of scoop.
What if you got really big or small hands?
Then you're going to want to drink more.
So it works out.
Large hands doesn't equal large stomach fluid.
It does.
It does, actually.
Statistically speaking.
Small hands doesn't.
What if you have small hands and a big appetite?
What do you do then?
You just starve?
Yes.
You just, you weren't, you weren't designed to survive in this world.
It's funny that they mention like historical recipes.
I feel like I watch, I watch the occasional like old food recipe from the old and I watch, sometimes I'll watch a Townsend's video.
And sometimes I'll watch a tasting history with Max Miller.
And it's really funny that old recipes like don't even like say what you're fucking doing.
Some of them are just like, they'll just say like, yeah, take some milk and like mix it with some flour and like squeeze it until it becomes goo.
And like, that's it.
Like that's all you get.
Yeah.
Like just throw enough sugar on it that like you think it looks good.
And it's like, okay, I guess I will.
They use rumors from the time that only they would have known.
Yeah.
Like, you know, like Jerry down the road, like, like if you could like, if you cut him in like to 32 pieces, like that's how much milk you put in.
They don't even, they don't even specify though.
They'll literally just say like, yeah, take some stuff, like add some.
A pinch of this, a punch of that, a slap of this, a scrape of this.
Fuck, a fuck of a fuck of ooze and a dollop of tea, a stir and a sip of gravy.
I don't know.
Just put everything in a bowl and hope.
Boil it.
Put it in a pot.
Drink.
Doesn't matter what it is.
That's just every recipe.
That's how you make sure, that's how you get optimal nutrition and you make sure that you don't waste anything.
Because then it all goes into flavoring the broth.
And then you're good as gold.
What did I try to do?
I tried to make some, oh, I tried to make a cucumber, not cucumber.
I tried to make zucchini chips.
And I tried to like, sort of brine them a little bit.
Like I cut a cucumber and I put salt and water in a vat.
And I just kind of slosh the cucumber slices around in this, in this salt water.
Then I bake them and it was too salty.
It was way too much.
And I crunched it and I said, but then I ate all of them anyway.
Yup.
Because I had to use my zucchinis because they were starting to get moldy.
Anyway, last voicemail is called P Court P Prologue.
Three, two, one, go.
Please remain seated because we couldn't afford the sound effects for the honorable judge-judge.
Case 69, nice.
The PC people versus the shipy.
He has been charged with impersonating a voice graver.
Impersonating a voice graver is a serious claim to shipy.
I have to send you to Tommy J.B.O.
However, this is a court draft order.
The court is with PC people.
The morning meeting of jail voice mailers shall be given a court.
This
could you understand that?
No, also tear down the wall.
Tear down the wall?
Was there a wall mentioned?
I was-
No, no, it's it's, you know, the the ending of Pink Floyd's The Wall.
You know, that's the album.
Oh, by Doug Walker.
No, yeah, I've never seen either the original or the Doug Walker version.
Well, you listen to it because it's an album.
Yeah, but there's a movie.
Sure, I've never seen the movie.
I've seen bits of it.
No, I've never listened to the album.
I mean, I've heard songs from it.
But yeah, the the end of the court and there's the big fat guy and he's like,
I am the big fucking judge and I say tear down the wall.
That is, you know, the thematic wall from the album.
And it's like, everyone's like, oh, we should do that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, OK.
And chat goes wild and they tear down the wall.
It's it's it's the Twitch chat went went crazy when that album dropped.
Boy, OK.
Well, I'm sure whatever decision this fucking too deep
to understand Judge Maid was great.
He's it was it was the the emperor from 300 Spartans.
But that guy Persian Empire, man.
Xerxes, Leonidas said, this is Sparta, but you didn't say to that guy.
Oh, yeah, yeah, he's like, you are the perfect man.
Oh, Leonidas, I will fuck you and your men.
And I said, not today, not today, foreigner shot him.
I remember that, I remember.
OK. That was the last voicemail.
The end. We're free.
We should do the fucking bonus.
We'll do my super bonus.
We'll do my super bonus soon.
We'll release some fucking rad content soon, hopefully.
Well, I have done a fucking Shekels for Heckels Noida edition
this week on Wednesday.
If you're listening now, you missed it, you nerd.
Send us a voicemail at speakbop.com slash PCB voicemail.
Subscribe for bonus episodes of Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Anything else?
No, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing.
OK, thanks for listening.
Thanks for listening.
Have a happy week of March.
Goodbye.
Well, I don't know why you're saying it so strangely.