Today we have a Ushipalooza for you.
Ushalooza.
Yep, an Ushalooza.
These are brand new.
So right here I have Marvel Series 2 packs.
We have DC Comics.
Ooh, very nice.
And we have Disney packs, which how awesome is that?
Very cool.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It is the day of the chosen battle destiny.
It's the big fight time every day.
I'm the best guy ever.
And we've got Endless Jess.
Yep, here for the one topic that I'm sure nobody else on the internet has ever talked about ever.
I can't wait.
Oh, Munchy is here.
I'm a prisoner.
I'm an Alcatraz.
I need to tone for my sins.
This is the only time I've been allowed to be on the internet because I'm a prisoner.
I am a war criminal.
Check this out.
Munchy, Mumkey Jones.
Oh, fuck.
Yo, Danny Phantom, he was just 14 when his parents built a very strange machine.
He was assigned to view a world unseen.
He's going to catch them all because he's Danny Phantom.
When it didn't quite work as folks, they just quit.
Then Danny took a look inside of it.
There's going to be a crash.
Everything can change.
His molecules get all rearranged.
Look at that shit.
Didn't Danny Phantom like shoot up the supermarket the other day?
Yeah, that's why I'm singing it.
He fucking shot up the supermarket like two days ago.
God damn.
Wait, what?
What happened?
Some guy who was inspired by the Danny Phantom character, Ember, and he has many fan fictions of him and Ember shooting up his high school just went and shot up a fucking supermarket and killed himself the other day.
What a fucking hero.
Okay, we'll have the podcast in celebration of his exploits the other day.
And lastly, we've got Mr. Tom Oliver is here.
Yeah, we picked a great day to have this discussion because Adam West died today.
So in his honor.
What?
Oh my God.
Danny Phantom shot Adam West.
Yeah, it's really bad.
Jesus Christ.
He just went to the supermarket.
He wanted to get some avocados, but you know.
Is that for real?
He was 88.
Like that's pretty old.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Who's going to play Adam West on Family Guy?
Seth Meharrow is.
Oh my God.
The impersonation of Adam West, hooray.
Yes.
I think they wouldn't do an impersonation.
I think they would just retire the character.
Hard to say.
He's a pretty popular character.
Well, we'll see.
Any case, folks, our topic today is Marvel Baby versus D.C.
That's it.
That's the one.
What is this?
I don't know, dude.
I really don't know what any of this means.
I think it's a bunch of nerd shit.
Is this like an episode of the panel cast, but not the panel cast?
Pretty much.
This seems like a panel cast sort of.
I don't think most of us are that deep into comic book lore except for Jesse, of course.
I think most of us will be commenting from our experiences with perhaps the animated
universes and, of course, the new movies.
The one in particular contention today is that most of us were able to go see the new
Wonder Woman movie.
With that, that really does change the game when it comes to this balance, especially
in the cinematic universe.
For reasons I'm sure we will get into.
I was just too much of a misogynist to go see it.
By misogynist, I mean poor.
It changed the game by not being completely terrible, so now the favor is totally the
balance is way in favor of DC now, because for once they made a not bad movie.
You know, it's really the prodigal son effect, you know?
They were so shit, and to make one that's actually good is like everyone falls in love.
Munchie, what are you saying?
You know, I have to say this right off the bat.
Gal Gadot killed two children while in the Israeli Defense Force, and she is a murderer.
She's not to be in the United States movie at the Hollywood business, and please boycott
this movie, please do not support Zionist propaganda, and please, please God, do not see
Wonder Woman.
Well, that's Wonder Woman, ladies and gentlemen.
Symbol of love and truth for all humanity.
I will say, of all of the DC movies so far, Wonder Woman is my second favorite to feature
the Wonder Woman character.
Who's the first?
Batman v Superman, dog?
That movie's the shit.
Batman.
Hell yeah.
You know, that movie's pretty good, but I mean, Suicide Squad really just blows it out
of the water in terms of sheer quality writing.
See, you take what you assume is my sarcasm, and then you return to the sarcasm.
I wasn't joking.
Batman v Superman is actually pretty great.
Oh, well, looking for you, we've got the world's biggest fan of Batman v Superman,
Endless Jess right here on the podcast to agree with you on that, right?
Awesome.
We can agree together.
I mean, yeah, it's okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
You're supposed to be the angry man, Jesse.
I forgot, Jesse is always irrationally angry about stuff.
That's correct.
Well, okay, so I just wanted to say, overall, I thought the Wonder Woman movie was very good.
It was a little shorter than I expected it to be, but I found like the...
Really?
It was like two hours and 20 minutes.
Well, see, I didn't get that, but the various shots of her in the different locations,
thinking about what...
And then she eventually comes to that climactic moment at the end where she realizes it was
milk that she forgot to write in her grocery list.
Oh, goddammit.
That was really good.
That was really an impressive character.
Now, Nate, when you say you saw Wonder Woman, did you see this in a theater,
or did it pop up in your YouTube subscription feed?
I watched it yesterday in the theater, and today I watched it again on YouTube.
I preferred the YouTube version of the cinematic one.
It was pretty good, too.
Those fan supercuts really do make movies just so much better, you know?
They really do.
Okay, so let's just say, so the Wonder Woman movie was great, and there's mostly one reason
why, and it's because it wasn't a fucking abysmal, depressing piece of shit that made
me hate every character in it.
Wonder Woman is by far the coolest superhero in like the DC Universe right now, because
she actually is a real hero.
She really wants to help people.
She's not going to cry.
She's not going to stand there.
While her father says, no, Clark, just let me die.
Don't help anyone ever.
Let everyone die.
Stop my invincible son.
Yeah, no.
Just don't involve yourself in this situation.
Watch me die, son.
That's what I want for you.
Man, fuck that.
That movie was kind of okay, but that was like the worst thing I've ever seen in my entire
life.
But no, Diana is a fucking hero, and I love her, and she was the kickass, and she beat
up all the bad boys, and she shielded those bullets.
They had the cool moments.
They had the slow down things.
Yeah, so the movie was a lot of fun.
Well, you know, it really is.
I think it really is a lowered expectations thing, because I actually saw Guardian to
the Galaxy 2 last night, so I saw Guardians after I saw Wonder Woman.
I think most people probably saw it before, but like, I walked out of Wonder Woman thinking,
hey, that was a pretty good movie.
But then I walked out of Guardian to the Galaxy 2 thinking, no, it fucking wasn't.
Yeah.
The Guardian to the Galaxy 2 is a good movie.
Wonder Woman is a fucking okay movie.
It's the best DC has done so far, but the worst Marvel movie is still better.
I don't know.
I really hated fucking Thor 1.
I thought it was an absolute garbage.
I wouldn't go as far as saying Wonder Woman's worse than Thor 2.
No, nothing is worse than Thor 2.
You're all right.
I take it back.
You know what?
I will totally grant you that.
I haven't seen either of the Guardians of the Galaxy movies, but I hear they're great,
and I believe them.
And Wonder Woman, I definitely did not like love it.
I thought that especially the male lead guy was, he was capable, and he was fine,
and he was cool, and he fucked, you know, Diana, so that was cool.
But he was kind of boring.
And then it felt so, I don't know if Marvel does this really consistently,
but like the whole crew there was so like, uh, milk toast.
Like they had like one character trait each, and they're just like, yeah, we're going to go on a super quest.
I would say they didn't have a character trait each.
And none of them had any characters.
Well, I mean, the Indian guy was Indian, and the one guy who was scared of stuff was scared of stuff.
The dude with the fez was okay.
I liked all the characters.
I thought they were all cool and likable, and like I liked the little bond of friendship they all had.
I liked the guy who wanted to talk.
It was weird how like the Scottish guy had this arc of like he's afraid to pull the trigger,
but he didn't actually ever get to pull the trigger.
He never took the shot.
It's like a literal Chekhov's gun that never went off.
I felt like that was like literal cut content.
Like all the signs were there to resolve that, and then they just didn't do it.
So it was really bizarre.
That's the DLC that's going to come out two months later.
Exactly, exactly.
And then you see some paths.
Yeah, the fuck it.
By the way, for context, for my enjoyment of, I've only seen the movies, and in fact, I hate comic books.
I'm not only have I haven't seen any comic books in my redness.
I don't like them.
And I don't like superheroes.
I don't like Marvel.
I don't like DC.
But I like, I thought the movies were pretty good because they were movies.
I'm in the position where I'll read an anime book because it's in black and white.
But when you pick up a colorful comic, it does something to my pea-sized brain where I can't really
function and understand what the fuck is happening.
Exactly, exactly.
I just can't read it.
That's odd.
I'm a legitimate issue now because I don't get it.
I read a lot of mangoes.
I feel like most people are the opposite way.
That the black and white is a turn-off and they like the color better.
I know Jesse would argue that he misses color in a great way when he reads mango.
There's just too many colors.
It just overloads your brain.
There's too many things to keep track of.
There's too many colors.
When you look at a beautiful painting with a ton of different colors, you just get too overwhelmed.
I want to have black and white only contrast, no hues whatsoever.
Crush the blacks and whites.
There's just too much information, you know, Mumki?
There's just too much information.
I mean, he might be being sarcastic, but I actually feel that way.
Okay, fair enough.
Yeah, me too.
Well, okay, but let's get back to the point here.
Marvel vs. DC here, okay?
So, Jesse's the foremost expert on this.
So, Jesse, why don't you just give us your overall impression here?
I mean, you're coming from the comic book world a lot, but then of course you've seen probably more of the films than any of us.
So, where do you lie on this issue?
Yeah, the same place that everyone else lies on it.
I can't explain it in any way that's new or exciting to people.
The DC movies are just a clusterfuck.
They tried to introduce too much too fast and they're kind of dark and miserable,
whereas the Marvel movies are like actual fun superhero movies.
And that's it.
That's the whole thing.
Really, this is like a 10-minute podcast.
I think the way we can go through these is each one of us, you know, from both Marvel and DC,
we say, what's our favorite movie and what's our least favorite,
and then we can, that's a good excuse to talk about why we feel these ways.
Okay, sure.
That's true.
Well, it's ironic because, I mean, the whole, I mean, that's the complaint is what I just said,
is that the Marvel movies are actually superhero movies and the DC movies have been sort of miserable
and monotonous and tedious and shitty and DC doesn't seem to know what they're doing.
That's the movie side of it.
When it comes to the comic book side of it, it's literally the opposite.
The DC comics are all great and fun and everyone loves them.
And Marvel comics right now are all miserable and shitty and the clusterfuck and everyone hates them.
So it's weird that, like, they're both equally good and equally shit,
but they can only be good or shit at one thing at a time, it seems like.
Well, I feel like the reason that this has happened, at least in the cinematic movie,
I have no idea what Marvel's doing with their comics right now.
It's other than, like, being awful.
But I think it's just because, like, they're trying to capture the lightning in a bottle of their first successes, respectively, right?
Because, like, Marvel Studios' first, like, movie was Iron Man.
And Iron Man was a fun, light-hearted, kind of, like, you know, it was a good interpretation of a comic.
It's not as light-hearted as you might be remembering it being.
He spends a lot of the time in an ISIS cave.
Well, that's-
I'm a light-hearted.
There's-
I'm not, like, the character is very much like-
The movie makes a very favorable depiction of ISIS.
Yeah.
They come out as the heroes.
Oh, they're the real stars of that movie.
Yeah.
But, like, all of the movies that came out after Iron Man, I think very much are trying to capture, like, the underlying tone of Iron Man of, like-
Sure.
This, like, is a serious story.
It's, like, a very comic book-y story, but, like, the characters are fun.
There's a fun, kind of, just, like, overall tone of the movies.
Whereas, DC's big thing was the Dark Knight trilogy.
Right.
That wasn't even so, like, as- I don't know if this is just me, but I felt like the Dark Knight trilogy, as it went on, became less Batman movies and more like Christopher Nolan movies.
That's true.
They've been- I felt they became more disconnected from the canon as they got darker and he took more liberties with the character and all that kind of stuff.
Which was fun.
They were still fun movies.
But it was- you can definitely tell that when they came up with Man of Steel, they're like,
Okay, we're gonna make the Dark Knight Superman.
That's right.
And they've been running with that ever since, really.
Except maybe for Wonder Woman because I haven't seen it because I'm just- I hate women that much.
But, um...
No, you're right, Tom.
The Dark Knight trilogy is the worst thing that ever happened to the DC cinematic universe because they're all trying to do that again,
but they're failing because they're not Christopher Nolan.
They finally realized, though, with Wonder Woman.
Or at least it seems that way.
They're moving in the right direction at last.
They understand that that's not what you want to do, especially with a character like Wonder Woman.
That they did what, like, guys like the Red Letter Media guys have been talking about for a long time,
of, like, no one knows who the fuck Wonder Woman is or anything about her or, like, any of her origin.
No one fucking knows.
So now is the time to, like, set all that shit up.
Yeah, that's part of what I've wanted to say about Wonder Woman, I guess.
Is that, I mean, I've seen everyone praising the movie.
And everyone's praising it from either a movie fan's perspective or from, like, a feminist perspective or, you know, whatever.
But I've seen very few people talking about the movie from a comic book fan's perspective.
More specifically, my perspective, which is the only one that matters.
Right.
Which is that Wonder Woman is a shit character and always has been and I've always hated her because she makes no sense.
And anyone who says they're a fan of Wonder Woman prior to this movie was a big fat fucking wire.
Right, for sure.
Nobody, the character, it just isn't, like, relatable.
Her origin doesn't make any sense.
She's, like, made from-
She's literally not human, she's not even human.
Yeah, like, nobody in the world, and I think even now, even still after the movie, nobody can tell you what Wonder Woman's powers are because nobody knows.
Dude, what were those, like, weird blasts or something she can do?
I don't know, they never talked about it, she just does it sometimes.
She's a god or something?
I don't know.
Can anyone in the world answer me this?
And don't, because it's rhetorical, because I know you can't.
Is Wonder Woman bulletproof?
If she hits it with her wrist.
Yeah, I mean, I would say no.
Because Wonder Woman, I mean, they portray her as being as strong and as invulnerable as, like, a Superman.
Like, she can get hit by Doomsday in the face and she can get up and be fine from it.
But she needs wrist gauntlets to block bullets.
If she was really as strong as Superman, she wouldn't need those.
So, just, everything about the character makes no sense, but that's what I liked about the movie, is that they actually managed to somehow succeed.
In making Diana, as opposed to Wonder Woman, an actual fucking character that I can kind of relate to and see where she's coming from.
So that, I think that was the biggest strength of the movie.
Diana?
I think the worst parts of the movie, sorry, but the interruption.
No, go ahead, go ahead.
I think the parts where the movie was the weakest or faulted were actually the more superhero tropey parts.
Like, how she has to have a big superhero battle at the end with Aries that made no sense and was totally unnecessary.
Like, the whole point of the movie is that Wonder Woman is realizing that there's not like a turn off switch for the evil in the hearts of men.
She's like, sort of losing hope and that's losing hope in the idea of fighting.
She's learning about mercy and love.
That's why she hasn't fought for like 100 years by the time Batman v Superman happens.
Like, that's the plot of the movie.
They could have done that without a big superhero god battle.
That was totally like counterintuitive to the whole point of the film.
Yeah, it was a little weird.
Like, yeah, oh, there's nuance.
I killed the guy and it should still happening.
You didn't kill the god of war.
It's me, the god of war.
I make war happen.
Kill me and it'll stop.
I'm the god of war.
But then she does and it doesn't stop.
Really, there really should have just been no Aries.
That would have been the right way to go.
Does it make sense?
Are they implying that World War One was actually caused by Aries?
Why was he there?
Like, he's there to make it like a little bit worse.
Yeah, like he says, he says like,
I didn't put evil and fear in the hearts of men.
I didn't start this war.
I just, you know, tell them to make bombs and gases and make it worse because I'm an asshole.
And it's like, okay.
That could have just been a guy.
That could have just been the actual general.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, that was dumb and, yeah, as you said, was kind of counterintuitive to the point of the movie
and just served to let there be a battle at the end.
By the way, I wanted to say that, like, that British dude as the Bat-
Spoilers, by the way, fuck you.
You know, the British-
He got shots, Tom.
He's so jarring.
The guy with the mustache being Aries at the end.
Like, you know that shot where like it shows like his origin and like we find out that he's the guy
where he gets like smote down by zoos.
He's down like in the Hades dungeon and he still has the gay ass retarded mustache.
It's the goddamn British fucking mustache.
What the fuck?
The God of War has been wearing for like thousands of years.
It's like, dude.
I thought he was in disguise, but no, that's how the God of War actually looks.
Little weasel face to mustache.
And it's like, fuck.
And his motivations don't make any sense because like at first Diana thinks, well, he's Aries.
He creates war because he loves war.
He's the God of War.
He thrives on war.
That makes sense.
But then she meets Aries and he's like, oh no, that's not it.
I just hate humans and I want them to all be destroyed because I hate zoos.
But it's like, wouldn't him just liking war make way more sense?
He's the God of War.
Like, how do you mess up that?
That's a weird thing.
I know he's the God of Truth.
Jesse, God of Truth.
That doesn't make no sense.
No, he's not.
He's the God of War.
That's a lie.
I think that is a lie.
I was confused.
And the ancient Greeks always said, I have three gods.
One for lies, one for truth, and one for wisdom.
And the wisdom.
And then, so like, he's fighting Wonder Woman and he's like, fine, then I'll just destroy
humanity myself.
If that's what you wanted to do, why weren't you doing that before?
He apparently wants to destroy humanity through war, even though he's just as strong as a
God and he could have done it at any point by just beating people up.
You know what?
Wonder Woman's a really shitty movie.
And you know what?
All the DC movies are shit.
I take back anything good that anyone has said about Wonder Woman.
You know, I totally, I usually hate this, but I'm definitely one of these guys liking
the movie a lot more because it's just such a change of pace.
Yeah, I mean, that's my point.
It's just that all of the, a lot of the movie was stupid and totally fell apart at the end
and didn't make any sense.
But the reason that you can still sort of forgive it, at least for me, and say, well, it was
still a pretty good movie, is because as a comic book fan, at least they made Diana good.
She was, God, her naivete and her like sincere desire to do good for the world and her like
steadfast belief that like, I'm an Amazon, what we do is we help people, we save the
world.
That's what I'm all about.
Just so, so good.
Yeah.
And I actually found myself relating to her a little bit, a character who I have never
been able to relate to at all before because she's been weird and obtuse and hard to understand
and hard to grasp.
But I really could relate to her frustration at realizing that human beings are just bad
and broken and most of them will just do horrible things for no fucking reason.
No, Jesse, you've missed the end point where she realizes that she's going to keep fighting
because she can still help, she can make a difference.
That's wrong.
Where is the Amazon island thing?
Where is that?
Munchy, that's not important.
Don't worry about it.
It was like off the coast of that German base, but it was like hidden in a mystic aura.
I, yeah, so like in the Mediterranean?
It certainly wasn't in Amazon, I don't think.
Did she, did she, well it's not in the Amazon, yeah.
Is that, is her of accent Gal Gadot, is she Israeli?
Is that what her accent is?
Yeah, she killed two fucking children in the Israeli defense force, you fucking faggot.
Well they were probably asking for it, Munchy, did you ever think about that?
They, we've got to get our land back.
That was an attack force.
Did anybody else feel like Wonder Woman up until the dog shit ending was, it was like
watching a Marvel movie?
I felt like I was at a Marvel movie and then they had to force their DC tropes into the
end fight.
It was really desaturated and that was annoying to me.
Not because I'm against the grimy ascetic, which I am, but I just love saturation so
much and I just feed off that saturation.
Munchy just saying too many colors are a bad thing.
I think he was making fun of me.
Yeah, I was making fun of Monkey, my favorite thing to do.
Yeah, Wonder Woman's outfit is just a little desaturated and it's like, okay, it's like
they're afraid to go full color mode with these costumes and shit, which I guess I understand
because they look silly, but whatever.
Yeah, let's talk about the comedy in this movie because I was actually pretty on board
with most of what they were doing.
We're totally diverging, we're going into this movie deep, but hey fuck it.
Were there jokes?
I don't remember any.
Dude, how could you forget Munchy?
How could you forget the epic joke where she's looking at his penis and she's like, what
is that?
And he's like, uh, uh, uh, oh my watch, it's a watch.
How could you forget that all the jokes landed, I thought the movie was pretty funny, none
of the jokes failed to make me chuckle.
And even things that weren't outright jokes, they were just sort of humorous, like when
he wraps her truth thing around his wrist to prove that he's telling the truth.
It's a lighthearted kind of fun thing, it's not necessarily a joke, but I still got a
little chuckle on it.
I really had the fear going into the movie that all of the humor would be like, oh, the
world of men is so regressive, here's men and I don't like them, which to me is the
opposite of what Wonder Woman should be, shouldn't the whole point of her be that she's enamored
with the world of men and like enamored with sexes living together because she's been sheltered
from it her whole life.
She shouldn't be like walking around like thinking she's above it all.
Like I was really, I really felt like this movie would come out and just be like a really
bull dyke-y like fuck all men movie.
And it really wasn't like, there's, there's no feminist agenda shit in the movie at all
already.
I fucking loved just how like it was all about just like humanity, brotherhood, you
know, men, women, everybody, we're all in this shit together, don't fucking worry about
it.
Yeah, like she learns about like the world of men and she's like, yeah, cool, I've never
seen a man before, your penis is really big, is that the biggest penis?
And he's like, yep, it sure is.
And she's like, wow, cool, I think that's cool, I am a girl, let's sleep together and
cuddle on my boat.
And he's like, okay, and then she has ice cream and she's like, well, this is just
the bee's knees right here.
And they had the opportunity to make the cheapest, dumbest, pro-feminism joke possible when
he says, Chris Pine says, oh, Wonder Woman, you can't go in there, that's no man's land.
I thought she was going to say, oh, no man.
I could feel it coming and thank God they didn't say it.
They didn't do it, it's like they set us up to expect it and then they subverted it
and it was really, it was beautiful, it was wonderful, I might say.
You know, I did want to say, I have to give the movie a couple of minus points for never
having the line that really was, who was that wonderful woman just now?
I don't know, I'm really wondering about her, I'd really like to know.
Wonder Woman, we serve like a Wonder Woman.
Yeah, yeah, we got, are we some kind of Wonder Woman?
Holy shit, it's Batman versus Superman, the dawn of justice.
I remember that line.
That was the greatest one.
God, okay, so we're pretty much all in agreement that this movie was great and, well okay,
not great, but it was definitely a positive move for DC, the best they've done in their
whole cinematic universe yet and hopefully they'll continue this way and they won't
fuck it up anymore, they'll just improve from here.
Alright, one last thing to say about Wonder Woman, I hate Nazis but not the kind you're
thinking about.
Alright, so here's the reason I like Wonder Woman.
There were no Nazis in World War I and not World War II.
I hate World War II, it's fucking played out and it's gay.
Yeah.
World War I is sick as fuck, a ton of people died, a lot of people got their fucking asses
blown up because they were stupid, they didn't realize that guns are real and they thought
that guns were fake and they weren't real.
That's actually true.
World War II is cooler than God and God is Godder than God and that's my review of
World War I, it's pretty good, Wonder Woman saved World War I, it was a shitty movie before
then and World War I got a shitty review on Ron Tomatoes because it didn't have a lot
of humor, it was pretty desaturated, but then Wonder Woman came in the last couple minutes
of the movie and it saved World War I and I like World War I, Dr. Poison is my waifu
because World War I is cool.
My question is, how did Gal Gadot manage to make every single scene sexy as fuck?
My question is, how did Gal Gadot manage to kill two children rather than your family?
I mean, one's bad enough, but you get two in there.
Oh no.
Munchy, please, that poor woman, she suffered enough.
Just judging by the way she looks, I would probably jerk off to footage of her killing
those children.
Oh no.
Yeah, me too.
Are you jerking off to the kids dying under the woman?
You know, it's a healthy mixture.
A little bit of column A, a little bit of column B.
So, okay, let's do what Munchy was saying, I mean, Munchy was saying, and let's all talk
about maybe some of our other favorites or least favorite ones, just to get the sense
of how this whole thing's panning out.
Munchy, why don't you tell us some of yours?
Is your favorite Guardians of the Galaxy 2, is that what you were saying?
No, but I did say, I do think that's better than Guardians 1 for sure, although they're
both like nine out of ten stars in my book.
I want to go back to my opinion that Batman vs. Superman is fucking awesome.
And you were complaining like, oh, the problem with DC is it's all sad and depressing.
I'm like, nigga, do you know who you're talking to right now?
You know this Mr. Monkey Jones?
He's into that kind of shit, baby.
I want to go feel like a piece of shit watching Batman mope around and be all sad, and Superman
stand there in a courthouse while it blows up and everybody fucking dies.
That's my kind of movie.
So I had a great time at the theater, I saw that one twice, and I thought it fucking kicked
ass.
Dope dog.
What's your least favorite, though?
Suicide Squad.
I would rather kill myself than watch it.
Suicide Squad's cool, dude.
I'd rather have to be part of a Suicide Squad.
Not a joke.
Suicide Squad's cool.
Horrible.
It's fucking cool.
It's funny.
I don't know, dude.
Suicide Squad is one of the greatest films I've made.
It's awesome.
Yeah, Wonder Woman is getting credit for being a more lighthearted DC movie, but Suicide Squad
was lighthearted, and that sucked a lot.
Yeah.
The United States Marines embodying one character, the greatest show of, like, a love letter
to all of our armed forces, Rick Flag, the greatest DC character of all time, Rick Flag.
He's a Marine, he's from America, he's sort of gruff, but he's got a heart of gold, Rick
Flag, United States Marine.
Doesn't he betray his platoon, because he wants to fuck a witch?
United States Marine, Rick Flag, American, Carnate, Fights for Liberty, American Flag,
Rick Flag.
Same thing.
It's like the American flag, it was an extra G. Rick Flag, American Patriot, Patriotism
Incarnate, Rick Flag, Fighting Batman, fuck Batman, Batman's not American, he's Israeli,
Gal Gadot killed two children while in the Israeli Defense Force.
Rick Flag tried to save those children.
Rick Flag, American Citizen.
I think I can already see the comments on this episode.
They're going to say, Munchy was good.
Good job, Munch.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I try my hardest.
Everybody, forget 1-1-1, post a good job, Munch, in the comments.
Yeah.
Good job.
You know, none of these guys really touched on the main issue at hand, except for good
old Munchy.
Bring it home once again.
Good old Munchy reminding us all that Gal Gadot killed two children in the Israeli Defense
Force.
It bears repeating, dude, it bears repeating.
Welcome to the Gal Gadot Killed Two Children in the Israeli Defense Force podcast episode
1.
What about you, Jesse?
Jesse, what's your favorite Marvel movie?
Oh, yeah, Jesse, go ahead.
Well, you know, it's not part of the Marvel universe, but I still have a soft spot for
old Spider-Man 2, a true classic.
That's cheating.
It's everybody's favorite.
It's cheating.
I know it's cheating.
I'm sorry.
There's something deeply wrong with me.
You know, I think Iron Man is like a really rewatchable, just a classic film.
The First Avengers is great, but you know, I really think walking out of Guardians 2
last night, I just felt like, wow, they fucking did it.
It was like the best movie ever.
The best movie ever.
I've never seen that shit.
I saw Guardians 2 with Digi, and when the movie was over, it wasn't even like a, yeah,
that movie ruled.
It was like a, huh, how in the fuck did they make such a good movie?
Yeah.
It really boggles the mind, especially since the first one was so good, and the second
one is even better.
Do you agree with the idea of Guardians being like this generation's Star Wars trilogy?
I've not heard that before, but yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel the same way.
Yeah, I mean those movies are ironic considering there's a Star Wars trilogy coming out.
I have a Russell Wall, it's the decayed pictures of Russell in my room.
I really like Kurt Russell, I really like him.
I like how that implies that the new Star Wars movies that are coming out are no generation
Star Wars trilogy.
Even the prequels were at least some generation Star Wars.
Well, I mean the idea of it being a good thing.
Yeah, I mean it's very imaginative, very excited, and you don't even really have to
know anything.
You don't even have to be up to date on the Marvel universe continuity at all.
The movies stand on their own as their own series.
That is good.
Yeah.
It's a good strength.
And how about your least favorite, though?
I mean Thor 2 is not, like it's almost like a meme that everyone hates Thor 2, but it's
just like of all the Marvel movies I've seen, I remember nothing about Thor 2.
It's the most forgettable thing that I've ever seen if I've seen it.
I don't even remember, that's how forgettable it is.
I remember one shot where Loki becomes Captain America, and then also I guess Loki killed
Odin at the end, and that's it, and everything else is out of my mind.
Oh yeah, I wonder if that has been like dropped, or if it still matters, because no one remembers
it.
No idea.
It'll probably come up in the next one.
My favorite movie is Iron Man 2, and my least favorite is Guardians of the Galaxy Breakout
Mission, the rather-replaced Hollywood Tower of Terror at Disneyland, California Adventure.
What?
That sounds amazing.
What is happening?
We need to inject this podcast with some juice, brother.
I need to bring in some controversial opinions for everybody to argue with.
I think Tony Stark is a shitty character, the most boring thing to ever happen to the Marvel
Universe.
Now see here, sir, you've crossed the line before, but this time, you can't possibly
go back.
Comic books!
Oh god.
And no!
So you guys excited for the new Spider-Man movie that's coming out?
No!
That just looked pretty good.
I'm super hyped for that.
I literally like it.
Um, I think it looks like shit, actually, and I'm not excited about it, but it does look
pretty good.
I'm super hyped for that.
I literally like it.
Um, I think it looks like shit, actually, and I'm not excited for it at all.
That's something we can talk about.
I've never, I've, I never would have imagined I could be this unexcited for a Spider-Man
movie.
Yeah?
I don't care about seeing Spider-Man be a fucking, a 14-year-old baby in high school.
I've seen it before.
I can understand that perspective for sure.
Do you ever think this looks better than Amazing Spider-Man 2?
Oh no, it looks a thousand times better than Amazing Spider-Man 2.
You know what?
My least favorite Marvel movie is Amazing Spider-Man 1, so bad I didn't even see the
second one.
Those movies are fucking shit.
They're terrible.
That's not that kind of Marvel movie, though, because it was like, fucking Peter Parker
in those movies is like a weird school shooter on a skateboard, fucking, he's, he's not
even like a nerd.
He's just like a fucking weirdo.
He like, I don't like him.
I don't, I'm not, I'm not a fan.
And also those movies were made like while the Marvel Universe movies were going on,
but they still couldn't get them in there, so like what was the fucking point?
To make Sony money.
Just Sony to make money.
Did you guys hear that Sony was trying to make their own Spider-Man cinematic universe
and they even had plans for like fucking Aunt May was going to have her own movie?
What?
Yeah.
Well no, they're still doing that.
What's that movie called?
Titanum.
Titanum's coming out.
Yeah, she's telling the story of how she met Uncle Ben on an ill-fated ship back in
1912.
No, Aunt May is like 30 now for some reason.
Yeah, but yeah, but that's not part of the Sony cinematic universe.
We're talking, that's Marvel.
You know, you got a good point.
No, I'm telling you, like they were, they said that was like amazing Spider-Man 2, they
were going to, amazing Spider-Man 2 was meant to be their Batman v Superman, where they
launch it off into eight different movies.
You're going to have a Sinister Six movie, Aunt May, they're still doing Venom, Venom's
coming out like next year or something, isn't it?
But I don't think it's going to be related.
It's actually going to be good though, I think.
Because as soon as they got rid of Andrew Garfield, I think that whole universe was
going to be gone.
Well, no, because they just announced a little while ago, they announced who's playing Venom.
Yeah, but that's not part of, I'm saying it's part of a contained universe.
Dude, that's going to be great.
That's Bane.
What's his fucking name?
I can't remember his name.
Tom Hardy.
Tom Hardy's playing fucking Venom?
Yeah, man.
What?
Cool.
It is cool.
It's not a bad casting choice, I'm not going to lie, but no, that's like Sony is, I guess
like the weird thing is that like they have the rights to all the Spider-Man characters.
So like they can't, all of their Spider-Man movies that they're going to make won't have
Spider-Man in it, but they don't have anything to do with the Marvel Cinematic Universe.
It's their own Spider-Man, Sony Cinematic Universe minus Spider-Man himself.
I'm not making this up.
It is that stupid.
Awesome.
Yeah.
And so it's great and licensing deals are the best.
And it makes everything good as we can clearly see now because we have this Marvel Cinematic
Universe without Spider-Man and the X-Men because why would we need those?
You know, I mentioned this.
Poor X-Men.
Oh, the poor, the poor X-Men.
They all died.
They're all gone.
What about Logan?
I thought Logan was pretty fucking sick.
No, no.
That's, yeah, that's what I mean.
I mean, I mean, in the continuity of Logan, the X-Men are all dead.
I was just kidding.
No, Logan was a great movie.
Yeah.
And I, yeah, I forgot about that.
Logan, yeah, Logan was as good as Guardians 2.
I think I might like them equally now that I think about Logan.
That's what's pissing me off about this Wonder Woman shit is people saying, oh, it's the
best superhero movie in 10 years when it's not even, it's the third best one this year.
Yeah.
Dude, that's not even close.
That's the feminist agenda in action.
They got to say that.
They're trying to cover up the fact that Gal Gadot killed two children in the universe.
That's what feminism has always been about.
What the fuck?
Ever since the creation of feminism in like fucking 1917, it's all been about covering
up Gal Gadot's murders.
So you're saying that feminism is the next scheme by Ares to cause strife and horror
in the world?
It does cause it.
And Wonder Woman 2, 3, a.k.a. the third sequel, like the third first sequel, Ares is going
to come back and he's going to start a Neo-Gamergate, but this time like with the real people and
it's going to be great.
Looking forward to it.
Feminism has started the most bloody, the bloodiest war of all and that is the internal
war inside me as I struggle to decide how much of a cool feminist I truly want to be.
The bloodiest war of all.
The period war.
Is that a period piece?
Yeah.
It's a bloodiest war because women will be fighting in it.
Jess, since you actually read the comics, are there any comic storylines that you think
should be adapted into film that haven't been done so yet?
Shit.
Yeah.
A lot of them.
One of my favorite Wolverine stories, which they couldn't do now because the whole Wolverine
story is over, but it was like a Wolverine story where you just get introduced to him
as this woman's neighbor and she doesn't know anything about him but she gets kidnapped
and it takes him six issues to even pop his claws and then he just slaughters an entire
camp full of kidnappers and it's the coolest thing ever.
So there's tons of stories like with the X-Men and the Marvel Universe at large that you
could never do just because the film universes aren't connected, like there's a story where
Wolverine gets brainwashed by Hydra and kills everybody and has to fight all the superheroes
and it's the coolest story ever but they couldn't do it because yeah.
That's cool, bro.
Why are we doing that?
I'm sure there's a bunch of Batman stories that they could do except they only ever want
to do the Dark Knight Returns over and over again.
Honestly, I think Batman the Long Halloween would be fun to watch.
I really like those comics.
It's a great story because stories like that where you get to see Batman's entire rogues
gallery of villains over the course of a year in the Long Halloween or how cool would it
be to get a spooky director like Guillermo del Toro or something and do Arkham Asylum,
Haunted House on a Serious House on Earth or whatever.
Just the story of Batman being trapped in Arkham for a night and running into all of
his kooky villains and it's like a trippy scary, like a horror movie with Batman.
That would be a way cooler standalone Batman movie than anything they've done recently
and I think that's what they should focus on more in general is more standalone movies
because a lot of them get bogged down and kind of new.
They're kind of doing not new animated films but it's just it's not the same thing.
I really like Lego Mr. Freeze.
It should be Lego Batman movie.
Oh shit.
Wait, holy shit.
That's a good idea.
Did that come out this year too?
There was a Lego Batman movie.
Yeah, it came out this year.
That was last year, I think, right?
No, that was February this year, dude.
Oh, so Wonder Woman is the fourth best superhero movie this year.
Lego Batman was fucking awesome.
Lego Batman was fucking sick as fuck, dude.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, does that count?
Can we count?
Oh, of course it does.
I didn't even...
Okay, okay.
I forgot all about that.
I didn't even see that one.
Wonder Woman is the first one and I really like Mr. Freeze's level because there's ice
cream in it.
Nate, I hope you have a lot of questions on Twitter ready for this episode.
Oh, you know it, brother.
Okay, that's actually...
We've been building this episode up amongst ourselves for months and it turns out we have
nothing to say on the subject.
Everything really is like super obvious, Marvel's better, DC still sucks but the comics are
good.
That's a good idea, Tom.
We should all put it to a vote.
There's five of us.
Hang on, hang on.
Before we launch away, okay, are we decided that we're only talking about the cinematic
universe?
Is that the whole...
We're talking about everything.
Yeah, the comics.
No, okay.
Well, forget the comics because there is one area where DC is unparalleled, un-fucking-paralleled
and it is the animated universe, is the animated shows, fucking classic animated Batman, fucking
Justice League, Justice League Unlimited, the Superman fucking cartoon, all absolute gold,
all gold.
I hate Man of Steel so much because I grew up watching that animated Superman show and
to spit on that character so badly, just like maybe fucking livid, is the...
Oh, god.
I think I did a video about that.
You guys don't like the Spider-Man cartoon where Drake Bell is the voice of Spider-Man?
You know, I really like the original Spider-Man from the early 90s and the X-Men.
The X-Men cartoon holds up.
It's really good.
It's really funny.
This one's for you, Morph.
Yeah.
Marvel had good cartoons, too, but yeah.
The DC animated universe is like supreme and awesome and great.
I really love Batman and beyond.
I know that it's like kind of like the redheaded sketch, huh?
But it's so good.
Dude, Return of the Joker is one of the finest animated, you know, fucking comic book films
of all time.
There's just so much fucking, fucking good shit coming out of DC's animated show.
The killing joke.
I love the killing joke.
That was...
It was so good.
Oh, dude.
No.
Okay.
I always wanted to watch Batgirl get fucked.
By Batman.
Come on.
Her tits.
Harry Strong sucks.
Ouch, God.
I'm wearing my Brony shirt right now, as a matter of fact.
How dare you?
The fucking extended universe stuff, like related to Batman and Beyond.
I always bring this up.
It's like my favorite episode of any of that shit where...
I know.
I know what we're going.
It's great.
He's grown up more.
He's grown up from the Batman Beyond days, and he's looking around.
He's like, what's my deal?
Why am I fucking Batman?
And he does a bunch of research.
And here's the story of what Batman was like and why Batman's a real fucking hero.
It's the whole scene.
Here's it from Amanda Waller, like Batman's nemesis when they were young.
And they fucking talk about this one time where Ace was fucking going apeshit and was
destroying the city, and Batman's like, yo, I'll take care of her.
They're like, Bruce, but she has to be fucking killed.
And he's like, I'll fucking handle it.
Shut up, you gay ass bitches.
I'm on this shit.
And then he fucking storms in there and gets in and Ace, who can read minds and shit.
And she's, you know, fucking up the city.
Everyone's going to die.
And she's just like, hey, Batman, I can totally fucking read your thoughts.
And he's like, yeah, what of it?
And she's like, yeah, I know you're not going to kill me.
He's like, yeah, what of it, bitch?
And they just have the fucking heartwarming moments where they sit together and he's like,
yeah, I'm not going to hurt you.
We're just going to sit here.
I'm going to be with you while you're dying.
Because I know what it's like to lose your fucking childhood.
That is the greatest Batman moment of all time.
It's so fucking good.
Nothing beats it.
Oh my God.
It's, yeah.
I mean, like, that's like the kind of like heart and like soul of these characters that
like defines them.
And yet it's so fucking missing in these, these DC movies.
It's just like, we're just going to have everyone be like really angry.
Well, that's why Justice League is going to save us, dude.
Justice League is going to fix all the problems in the DC universe.
Man.
I'm ready for it.
I'm so jealous of your optimism.
When I went to the movies yesterday, the Justice League trailer came on, I was like, okay,
time to get beer now.
It feels like DC can't stop making really obvious mistakes.
Like a couple years ago, Ben Affleck was going to write and direct his own Batman movie,
which would have been cool because he's actually a good writer and director and also a good
actor and he was actually really good as Batman.
Like he was the best part of that movie.
Oh, for sure.
But now he's not directing it anymore and they're like rewriting the script.
And it's like, why would you do that?
Why?
I think that like he was trying, but like, you know, the executive meddling was just
too much.
Studio interference fucked it.
Okay.
Well, here's a question then.
Like, do you think that the reason, because like, here's the thing.
We had Fox and Sony doing all these Marvel films for a while and they were okay.
They have like their hits and misses and then DC did their thing and they have their hits
and misses and they're missing more often than not.
But the reason Marvel's doing so good is because like there's like one guy ahead of
the show who's who's like in charge of everything.
And like, there's like a very like, cohesive vision for what the Marvel Cinematic Universe
should be.
I forget what the guy's name is because I'm stupid, but there's this one guy who's like
that guy.
He's in charge of the whole show.
And like, I really feel like that like very clear sense of direction like one dude who's
like knows his shit and can make it all happen is why Marvel's doing so well, because there's
no there's no equivalent on the DC camp right now to keep any of this shit coherent or
reign it in and like make those like executive in like someone to stop the corporate meddling
is like, no, like we're going to make something good if you want your fucking money.
So it's just like, I don't know, I feel like that's a huge part of why it's not just like,
oh, Marvel understands it or Marvel has better characters or whatever.
I think it's because like there's a very clear like power hierarchy in terms of how Marvel
Studios is set up and you can make executive decisions like that that trickle down through
the rest of the production, which like DC clearly doesn't have their equivalent at this
point.
And incidentally, I'm becoming aware that like most of the stuff I really love from
DC was like a decade ago at least.
So yeah, let's talk about the actual best DC movie Batman Returns where he fucking he
fights the penguin and the penguin is gross.
He like eats a bird eats raw fish, Michelle Piper is really hot in that movie.
Everything is all weird and cookie because it's Tim Burton.
He goes, I played this thinking city like a hop from hell and then fucking that movie
is good.
The end.
This is a good movie.
What about was it Batman and Robin?
The greatest Batman.
Oh, shit.
That's a good one.
How can we forget the best nipples on the suits?
The fucking, hey man, even the Adam West Batman movie is pretty great.
It is very, it's very, it's more comedy movie, but it's very funny that scene is trying to
get rid of the bomb.
He can't get rid of the bomb.
The ducks are there.
He doesn't want to hurt the baby ducks or the baby people.
He just can't get rid of a bomb.
That's great.
Good movie.
Tarot Tarot was such a cool ride.
Why would they take it out and replace it with Guardians of the Galaxy?
It's like not.
I don't know, dude.
Guardians of the Galaxy is even that popular.
I mean, Tower of Terror is fucking iconic.
When you go to California adventures, you have to go on the Tower of Terror because
it's just so cool.
You, you know, the Twilight Zone is such an interesting.
Look, they decided that instead of just having a single Tower of Terror, they're going to
terrorize everyone there by taking it away.
You know what?
Speaking of Guardians of the Galaxy.
Right now.
Again, let's talk about something that needs to die and I'm sick of it and I hate it more
than anything in the world.
Baby Groot.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
That too.
Baby Groot was annoying.
Yeah.
And thank God that he is only a baby for that movie and won't be a baby again.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
They really pushed the marketing on Baby Groot a lot and it got a little oversaturated.
I don't see any minions vibes from it.
Yeah.
Oh no.
He didn't ruin any scene he was in at all.
I mean, he worked in the movie, but just like the marketing and like the hype surrounding
Baby Groot himself is pretty obnoxious.
He was there for the normies.
But yeah, I was going to say the post credit scenes need to die because Guardians of the
Galaxy 2 had like seven post credit scenes and they were all completely worthless and
didn't mean like, oh, here's a Captain Marvel thing maybe and here's a fucking, Stallone
has his own crew now.
And here's like teenager Groot and I'm like, they're doing something with Captain Marvel
now.
Well, like it annoyed me in particular with Guardians of the Galaxy 2 because the movie
was so perfect and like every character had an arc and they all coalesced at the end.
And there's like this really emotional moment and the movie ends on this like emotional
point where it just like, you know, the close up on rocket and he's and he's crying and
I'm like, wow, this really fucking touched me.
I can't believe.
And then there's like a bunch of fucking post credit scenes with like teenage Groot jacking
off in his room and coming on Peter Quill's fucking face.
And it's like really, you couldn't you couldn't just let it sit on that image of rocket being
like all emotional like making me, you can't just make me, you can't just be content to
let me feel something.
You have to throw like teenager tree jizz in my face.
They had to make me feel uncomfortable.
I'm totally with you.
I'm totally with you on that.
That fucking sucks.
But I would argue even worse was the fact that now that those are a real thing, I sat
through the entire fucking ending credits of Wonder Woman like, of course, it's going
to be a fucking end thing and then there fucking wasn't.
I got played like a god damn fiddle.
This is what you do, man.
You got to as soon as the credits start rolling at any movie you're in, you always got to
take your phone out.
Remember before you go there, like, is there an ending credit scene?
Is there a stinger?
There's no stinger.
You just book it.
No, you have to respect the people who made the movie and look at all their names on the
big screen, dude.
I don't fucking care.
I'll respect them by pirating the movie later, if I get help.
That's how I'll respect them.
Iron Man 2 was fun because when I watched it for the first time, I ate some mozzarella
sticks and then after I watched Iron Man 2, I played Super Mario Sunshine for like all
night and I 100% of it.
That sounds like a great evening, not gonna lie.
Iron Man 2 was the first time I realized a movie could be filler.
Yeah.
Fuck, not grown-ups, too.
Fucking Jack and Jill, you know, just a filler movie surrounding a bunch of advertising.
Jack and Jill's a classic.
A dunk-a-dunk-a-dunk-a-dunk-a-dunk-a-chino.
This must never be seen.
What a legend.
I think Al Pacino wants to play Twisto with your sister.
With her sister.
That line deserves 100 Oscars.
Jess is making it funny.
Jess should have been in the movie because now it's funny to me.
Okay, here we go, folks.
Let's just say...
Okay, I'd say we want to make any final points about this.
Jess and Jill.
Let's wait on this issue.
The greatest movie ever made.
I think we should just go down the line and vote and, you know, we'll have a vote.
That sounds good.
Marvel wins.
Okay.
Let's start with...
Okay, I'm looking at the alphabetical order here.
Okay, Jess is up first.
Jess, Marvel or DC?
Who wins?
Marvel wins.
Bumky?
Who wins?
Marvel.
I don't...
Next is Nate.
No, you don't fuck them.
They got rid of the Tower of Terror.
Fuck them, DC.
Who wins?
God could kill...
No, no, God could kill...
Kill the Israeli defensivists.
This is Sophie's choice.
Both are nightmarish answers.
I have to kill myself.
I'm going to use my park ride and one of them killed children.
It's the only way.
Okay, so Munch is an abstention on this.
I'm going to go with DC just because I'm not that into the Marvel stuff like everybody
else seems to be and I do love all the old DC stuff.
So just because I like old DC, I'm voting DC and Tom...
Are we talking in general or just the movies?
We're talking all told.
Everything.
Dude, that's too hard.
I guess I really...
We can abstain.
I don't want to abstain.
That's a bitch move.
Yeah, it is.
You're a parody.
You know, I guess I'm going to have to go with Marvel just because I'm watching the movies
more than I'm reading comics or anything right now, but in terms of just nostalgia, nothing
can touch watching the Batman Superman adventures.
That was my fucking jam.
As much as I love the 90's Spider-Man and stuff, that was so good.
Oh man, the Superman show was just...
It made me like humanity and if I go back and watch it now, I'm like, oh yeah, there's
good in the world.
So fuck.
You know, we didn't even talk about the Marvel Netflix shows.
Those exist.
Yeah, it was the black guy, right?
I watched four episodes of Jessica Jones and I hated it.
Does that count?
Really?
Yeah.
I thought it was pretty good.
Is that because you're a saganist?
You hate women?
No.
If the character was a man, I would probably hate it even more.
Hmm.
Why's that?
I don't like watching men have sex with huge black guys.
Well, you're the only one in this podcast you could say that.
Well, Jesse, what do you have to say about those, Jesse?
You think they're good?
You think they're great?
You think they're the coolest?
What about that green arrow show?
Anyone want arrow?
Oh yeah, DCF shows too.
No one cares because they're bad too, I think.
How retarded is it that those have nothing to do with the cinematic universe they're
building now?
Now there's going to be two flashes at the same time.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess I didn't have anything to say.
Daredevil was good, Luke Cage was okay, Jessica Jones I liked, and the other one I didn't
watch.
I did not watch Iron Fist.
Luke Cage.
Black Panther.
I like that one.
Luke Cage, that's right, that's right.
I like him.
I'm thinking of the Black Panther movie that's coming out, I keep seeing ads for it.
Oh yeah, that guy's like super, like that guy's like even more black than Luke Cage.
He's just even blacker.
He's an African king.
He was Kang.
Dude, that guy's so fucking black.
He was Kang's, dude.
Yes.
He is Kang's.
I think they get so black they can't get black anymore.
They get even more black.
It's really wonderful.
It's the gift that keeps us coming.
Luke Cage better find a new thing to be other than black because he's been out blacked.
It's true.
Okay, let's go to questions, right?
We answered, I think we're good on this shit.
Okay, here we go.
Here's some questions, folks.
Here's, at Ichipan asks, we heard Ben and Nate's in Nate's interview, but tell me
other members of the PCB, what are your favorite movies?
What's some favorite movies here, folks?
Forget Marvel and DC, they're all garbage.
What else you got?
What are some top picks here to recommend to our viewers?
All right, here's the three best movies ever made.
In order, Back to the Future, Inception, and The Neverending Story.
There you go.
You're done.
Don't watch any other movies, just those three.
Pretty good.
What about Bridge to Terabithia?
Never seen that.
Yeah.
I like all movies.
I like every movie is great.
Anyone who gives any movie a bad review is wrong automatically, for any reason.
That sounds right.
Munchy, I bet you love yourself some movies.
Munchy, Escape, or, no, no, no, sorry, Number One Favorite Movie, Big Trouble in China,
Number Two Favorite Movie, Escape from New York, actually no, Escape from LA, and then
Number Three, Escape from New York.
And then my third- Fuck Escape from LA sucks, dude.
Escape from New York is a thousand times better.
Escape from LA is as fucking sick as fuck.
And then my fourth favorite is Chinatown.
So Kurt Russell, your big Kurt Russell guy.
This all seemed very related.
Big Trouble is good, but Fucking Escape from New York is like a cinematic fucking masterpiece.
10 out of 10.
Hey, speaking of China, the actual best movie of all time is The Legend of Drunken Master,
and also Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 1, and also Muppet Treasure Island, and also Friday.
Those are the actual best movies.
Yes.
Agreed.
Is that the movie where they say bye, Felicia?
Yes, it is.
Oh, okay.
It sure is.
Oh, oh, oh.
I learned something about black culture.
The Kirby anime movie.
Right, of course.
As to be seen in an upcoming episode of The Pleeve and the Weave, stay tuned, folks.
Oh, yeah.
The audio on that, by the way, Jesse, are you going to, or are you just gonna keep it
as is?
Um, man, I think that's probably gonna have the least editing of any episode, because
I'm just gonna let you fucking go.
Yeah.
Tom, how about your favorite movies, dude?
What else have you got?
Oh, god.
I'm terrible at answering these questions, because I always remember things.
What's your favorite?
Just what's some good ones?
Vampire Hunter D. Bloodlust is fucking amazing.
Yes.
So good.
I really like Heart String Marionette, which probably no one has seen, because I could
buy an industrial...
I like the one you heard, Bruno.
Yeah, that's a super fucking cool movie.
What's the third one?
Just round it all out.
Oh, shit.
Spider-Man 2.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Questria Girls.
We're gonna take you back to Equestria Girls.
It's the theme song of the show.
I'm just gonna say, I'm just gonna reiterate Reservoir Dogs.
It's the greatest film ever made.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, also Interstellar 5555.
Ooh, that's a good choice.
Yes.
Yeah, it's a good choice.
I watched that only last year.
I hadn't watched it until last year.
It was very disturbing.
Yeah.
It's the best.
Okay, next question.
We'll see what we got here.
Inglourious bastards.
Yes, we are.
Not as good as Reservoir Dogs, though.
No, it's much better than Reservoir Dogs.
That is a meme.
I don't know why anyone thinks that.
It doesn't make any sense.
I don't know why anyone thinks that any Tarantino movie is better than Kill Bill.
It's the peak of all cinema.
Reservoir Dogs is the tightest package.
It's got the best characters.
I'm not a tight package for you.
It's small.
I think it goes to show that since all three of us have a different opinion on the best
Tarantino movie of all time.
Tarantino must be pretty fucking good.
Yeah, I definitely agree with that.
Well, what was that, Tom?
The best superhero movie of all time is Mighty Morphin Power Rangers The Movie.
That was...
That's...
Yeah.
Who could forget Ivy News?
That movie traumatized me in a deep way.
I told you guys about the story about how I had a ridiculously high fever and almost
died and I dreamed that I was the ooze boy.
That was the coolest shit.
It was terrifying.
I wish I had dreams like that.
My dreams are always really one day and just like I went out and got a sandwich or something.
Well, all you need to do is almost die.
Which you do frequently.
It's true.
I just...
You know, guys, this has been the most agreeable, you know, podcast you've ever done.
Nothing has been...
No opinion has been contested, even the ones that contradict the other ones.
It's true.
This is the most I've ever liked any of you in a podcast.
This just goes to show why we need to do this.
We need to do more topics like this and not any actual issues or philosophical notions
or ideas ever.
This talk about...
This is the only time I've ever liked Nate in general.
Is it wrong that Gal Gadot killed two children on an Italian festival or was it just a father?
Hey, if we want to do a podcast about like a philosophical topic, is it wrong?
I mean, really, those kids died so that DC could have good movies.
Isn't that a reasonable sacrifice?
I'm looking forward to the PCP-Palestinian conflict coming up to a week of some time
soon.
The next bonus episode.
Yeah, that'll be the actual most agreeable episode we've ever done.
By the way, I was re-watching the Dignation video the other day and one of the questions
along the Great Journey was you were just asking...
It was just like you forgot where Palestine was or something.
And then I described the entire history of the Israeli-Palestinian conflict as the Israelis
came in and were just like, fuck you, dude.
And then immediately we were just like, yeah, yeah, that's how it happened, yeah.
Oh God.
Okay, let's...
Before we get too deep into that shit, okay, here's another question from our buddy a zombie
ninja cow who's not my buddy, I don't know this man, he's a stranger to me.
And his question is, do any of you do art that you don't release?
Like a craft that you like to do but don't think you're skilled enough at to make public?
That's an interesting question.
Who isn't a basket weaving but is ashamed of their basket weaving around here?
Aren't we all ashamed?
I mean, I would say that most of my art I don't release because it's mostly all I do
is write faster than I can edit videos, so most of them never get seen.
That's interesting.
You know, it's funny, this might be, I don't know if everybody does it like this, but I
release almost every single thing that I make, even through channels that are inappropriate.
One day I was just making a fucking, I just decided to make a shitty webcomic that was
very poorly drawn and I released it by adding a link to it on Imgur in the description of
the video that I happened to put out around that time.
There's no vehicle I had to deliver that shit, but I actually, I'm fairly non-prolific
in general.
I'm changing that recently, but historically, it's taken me a long time to produce things
because I just will think of a thing and just work really long to make it happen and
then release it or whatever.
And you know, I've got a bunch of stuff like in the works, but I all plan on making it,
so it's not like I don't plan on releasing it at all, but yeah, so I'm like the opposite
of this.
I release everything.
Yeah, I'm in the same boat as you, Nate.
If I waste time making something, I'm gonna throw it out there and see what people think
of it.
Yeah.
What were you saying, Munchie?
I'm like really good Meeze.
Oh, Meeze, as in the Nintendo cool boys.
Oh, Wii video game, yeah.
The best characters in Super Smash Bros. for Wii U and 3DS.
Yeah.
Most of them are black people, so it's easier to make them look bad.
Too soon, dude.
9-11 just happened.
Too soon.
Dude, I could have just killed black people.
We was just Kang's.
Tom, do you have any, I mean, I know you make a lot of stuff that, I don't know how much
you've released, but I feel like you're in the same boat of like you're planning on
releasing it, like your 3D art stuff or your comic?
Yeah, I'm doing like, I do a bunch of stuff.
The problem isn't that like I don't want to release it, it's that I hate it and then
I can't bring myself to release it.
So I have a bunch of stuff sitting in limbo, but someday.
Didn't you restart that and make it like a novel thing?
I've restarted it like seven times.
I don't even think it exists anymore.
I think it's just like this weird interdimensional, it's like been seeping slowly out of like
the Berenstein universe or something and I keep like getting it in flashes.
I don't know what it is.
You should make a documentary on the making of chapter one of Sorceress Lost or whatever.
I just start doing, I remake that like seven times, it's not even worth it.
Tom, evidently, I've been posting on Twitter that I'm working on this Elliot Roger Diary
of a Wimpy Kid book and I've been posting art from it and I don't know if you-
This looks great by the way.
I don't know if you like to-
I'm incredibly excited for that project, not gonna lie.
Well, here's the thing though, Tommy boy.
I don't know if you liked one of them or if you retweeted it, but some Jackass retard
in my comments said, oh, I can't wait for this Elliot Roger book that Tom Oliver is
making.
Oh no!
I thought, is this motherfucker stealing my idea, the son of a bitch, but I'm guessing
you just saw it on Twitter by accident.
I would never, that's your realm my friend.
Yeah, so I assume you liked it and then Twitter feed said, oh, Tom Oliver liked this and the
retard thought you posted it.
Well, yeah, I can't control stupid people.
Okay, I forgive you for what that guy did.
Thank you.
Okay, here's- no, that's a shitty question actually.
Here's a good question from our good friend at British Ninja Zero.
He asks simply DC or Marvel.
I don't know if we have time to go into that.
I don't know if we have time to go into that one.
We did not announce this topic or anything, so these people just want to know.
No, that question sucks ass.
I'm just gonna read this one.
I don't know if it's good or not, but I'm reading it.
At El Great Gonzales asks, do any of y'all ingrates know how to bust a move into club
or anime goth rave?
Oh, you know it bro!
I bust a move with my anime dames all fucking day dog.
Oh, okay, actually here's an interesting question.
At Dark Gold Game asks, is the human instrumentality project good or bad?
So we're talking about Evangelion here.
So is it a bad idea to turn all of humanity into an orange goop and have them all just
hang out in a primordial ooze again?
Well, I think the ultimate moral of the film is that it was obviously a good thing because
if you're cool enough and important enough, you can just come out of it and then you get
the whole world to yourself.
So basically it's good because it weeds out the shitty people.
Yeah, it's good because everyone dies but me.
We would never have to see Ben singed again.
Ben is the kind of guy who would be totally chill hanging out in the primordial ooze.
Yeah, he'd be like, hey man, come back into the ooze.
We got pizza in here.
Imagine, it's like I don't have to pay rent at all, this is the best.
Exactly, there's so much freed garbage around everywhere I look.
Hell yeah.
Oh, fuck you Ben.
Here we go.
Oh, no, that's a shitty question.
Oh, okay, here we go.
At WhattaThings asks, what is the best cheese?
What is the best cheese?
Pepper Jets.
Yeah, Pepper Jets.
Which is pretty good.
I have access to.
That yes.
What cheese is best is cheese that is closest.
That's very philosophical.
Also nacho cheese is pretty good.
Cheese touch bro, cheese touch.
I'm going to have to say the best cheese is that episode of Chappelle's show where he
goes, I wonder what Arsenio is up to right now and it cuts to Arsenio Hall and he's eating
cheese at a fancy party and he goes, this is some good cheese.
That's the best cheese.
That's good.
I'm just going to go on the record and say an extremely sharp cheddar is the best cheese.
I cut my mouth on some of that one time.
It kind of hurt.
Yeah, man.
Yeah, good joke.
God damn it.
Fucking hate all of you.
Oh shit, there was a relevant one.
Every episode this shit.
Look, you just fucked it up.
You used up your bad joke quota with Wonder Woman, all right?
That was good for like a month.
That was a good joke.
That was a masterpiece.
Wonder Woman is the best joke I've seen in a long time.
Get to a shitty joke makes it a funny joke.
Okay, here we go.
I guess we can just reflect on this again.
At Mr. No Name 2001 happened to ask, ask PCB, any thoughts on the passing of the great Batman
at real Adam West?
Let's reflect on this.
Adam West was a cool ass guy.
He was a cool Batman in the movies.
I liked his voice.
He was fun.
He's a funny, fun.
You know what?
He was also pretty fun.
He really did have a great voice for Batman.
At least for like the detective aspect of the character, he always sounded right.
And it's a shame that sometimes he's disregarded as more of a campy version of the character.
But I mean, his voice sounds way less campy than anything Christian Bale ever did.
Absolutely.
Well, here's the thing.
Back when that show came out, that really was a pretty decent representation of what
the comics were, because comics were way sillier back then, so it was really fucking cool.
Obviously, the entire Dark Knight trilogy is starting to feel just as campy and dated
in its own way as the Adam West version.
You got an Adam West Batman.
Everything's going according to plan.
You got yourself a Christian Bale Batman, and everyone loses their mind.
That's the greatest.
That's a good name.
Actually, you know what was like the coolest thing with Adam West ever was?
It was to go back to Batman the Animated Series.
It was when the Great Ghost episode, the Great Ghost episode, was the coolest fucking shit
because I grew up watching the Adam West Batman as a little kid, and then I graduated
to Batman the Animated Series, and then they collided, and I didn't even realize until
my dad was like, that's the old Batman.
I'm like, what?
And I'm like, fuck my shit.
Tommy Oliver, the 70-year-old boy.
Yes, you got me.
It's me, Adam West, I'm the ghost now, and I enjoy your podcast.
Hey, thanks, dude.
What do you have to say about your whole death situation?
Well, I'm glad it was me who died an old man.
If I had to see two children, for instance, die, the head of the son is really a bitch.
It is really a bitch that I'd probably go living.
So I'm glad that, you know, I got to live my life before I was seriously killed by Galgogo.
Oh my god, you know what this means, Adam West actually is the gray ghost now.
Oh my god.
He is the gray ghost.
Did Galgogo join the female ghostbusters?
Speaking of the best Marvel movies, how about that female ghostbusters?
Is that actually affiliated with Marvel?
Are you fucking stupid?
I certainly hope not, because that will mean I'll have to watch it.
I don't know.
That means I'll have to shift the whole grading.
Okay, here we go.
Last question, here we go.
Here's a fun one about current events in some of our lives.
At WhattaThings asks another question, and it was best and worst things about Digi becoming a nomad bum.
Well, I'll say the best thing was-
He's never around to film my fucking podcast.
That's true, that's true.
Fuck you, Digi.
The best thing was when he came to visit me and we hang out and had a great time,
and I'm going to start editing those videos soon and they'll go up and it'll be a big, fun thing.
Fuck Digi.
It was good.
Yes.
The best thing is that he's doing what he wants.
The worst thing is that he usurped my idea.
He should be doing what I want, god damn it.
Well, you know.
I make 60 bucks a month off that podcast.
I need the fucking money, Digi, you son of a bitch.
Digi, give me that money.
This is, this is, this is Monkey's Sandy Hook right now.
This is a rat.
He's been standing next to me the whole time, laughing.
Tell me what he said.
Fuck you.
Fuck Monkey.
I'm not doing his podcast right now.
No.
The whole time he's been here, the only thing he said is,
I'm not doing Monkey's shitty podcast.
Consistently.
But that was Digi's idea.
It was his show.
You know, we've got the DeVue Hydron Collider.
We've got Digi decompression.
I'm going to start the Monkey Fuck Digi Chamber,
where I just talk shit about Digi for an hour.
That sounds like a good one.
I think the people will love it.
It's going to go up the day after this comes out.
The Digi degradation chamber.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's it.
I was going to do Monkey's Suicide Perch, but it was too sad,
so I'm going to do this instead.
Suicide Perch?
Okay, you know what?
There's one question here that has to be addressed.
This will be our last one.
Okay, it's at XGUpload asks,
Are chads overrated?
And I would have to say no.
Chads are underrated.
Chads are underrated, for sure.
Everyone should strive to be as chaddly as possible.
Yeah, it worked out great for Ziz.
It did.
I mean, what better way to go than dying in a Burmese brothel
or something, like an Armenian brothel, one of those things?
Yeah.
You know?
If those two fucking kids were just more chad enough,
what would have been fucking swooned by their physique
and, you know, social skills?
It's their own fucking fault they died.
Gal Gadot would have dropped her gun or drone device,
drone controller, and been like, my god, their beauty.
Those chads, I can't do it.
I can't do this to them.
If only the world had more chads,
there would be peace on earth as long as.
Nobody would get bullied.
Gal Gadot would account for like 50% of the fucking murders
in Palestine.
It's half Gal Gadot, half the Danny Phantom kid.
Yes.
That's right.
Okay.
All right.
I guess we're done, folks.
Remember to send us more questions at our Twitter's at tpcrasnairs,
but just send them any time using the hashtag askpcp,
and we'll fucking answer them.
All right, everybody.
Thanks for listening.
Okay, this is a short episode.
This guy.
It's the last time I've seen combat so I can kill you.
I can't eat the food.
Oh, shit.
I forgot I was a prisoner.
I said that at the beginning of the episode.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
Subscribe to Monkey Jones.
Let's go kill myself now.
All right, bye.
Pledge to our Patreon, everybody, for the bonus episodes.
Oh, yeah.
We got to say, we got to say, we got a new Discord
just for the Patreon-y people, right?
That's right.
Of course, that's right.
Guys, we got a new Patreon.
Perk, if you pledge.
I think it's any of us.
I made that.
It was me.
It was me who made it.
Just for the patrons.
It's a cool place to be a cool boy,
and we kill everyone there who's not a cool guy.
Yeah.
It's a good place to be.
So, everybody, go pledge.
Pledge a dollar.
Pledge five to get the bonus episodes.
The last one was a Chuck E. Cheese versus Five Nights at Freddy's.
World acclaimed masterful podcast.
It was indeed.
Thanks a lot to the presence of our friend,
Munchie, where's Tiny Hats?
So, thanks, everybody, for listening.
And we will see you next time.
God, I need to give you last surprise.
Killed me.
Bye.
There you go.
Bye, everybody.
Bye.
Waiter.
Get the fuck out.
Subscribe to Monkey.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Skalkado.
She's the one who killed me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
She's gay.
Bored.
Yeah.
Boy cut Wonder Woman.
Oh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.