I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Oh yeah, it's pretty based, alright.
Yeah, but I do plan on watching that documentary, or is it a behind the scenes thing?
It's a behind the scenes, I guess you could call it a documentary, it doesn't really have a story or anything.
It's documentary style footage in a sequence.
Yeah, I'm definitely looking forward to it, it's always interesting to see pre-gamers tavern PCP lore.
Yeah, I don't know, do you want to just start recording like now, just go?
I've already been recording.
Okay, well I had Craig, but now I'm recording. Did you watch the doc Gibb?
I caught some of it while I was premiering, yes.
I was there, I was there the whole time in the chat.
Okay, let's sync real quick, on the count of three, say sync, one, two, three, sync, sync, one, two, three, sync.
Right, we're talking about, right until the documentary just came out yesterday, I put it out, it's up.
The premiere was fun, there was like a hundred people in the chat, it was a good time.
What else is there to say about Riot Country?
Oh, the commentary, Gibb, you and me did the commentary, and I think we...
I liked our conversation while we were commentating that...
Yeah.
I thought we had some good insights and some good stuff to say about the goings on.
It was nice to watch and remember, even if it was bittersweet at points.
It's very bittersweet, it really is, because it...
Yeah, I'd imagine so.
It was, I should mention, right, the commentary track is for patrons, it's in the master post, it's listed as a bonus episode on the Patreon,
so you can get our commentary of the uncut version with all the language intact.
You mean it's a PCP patron?
Yes, where else?
Anyway.
I don't know, I thought it was going to be the Trixie patron.
Never, never!
I lost patron, I thought.
Right, because it was very fun at the time, and it's like, oh, the good old days, the golden age, whatever you want to call it.
And it's also the like, oh, remember how the people used to talk about PCPHQ?
Oh, this was going to be the future, this was going to be forever.
What happened?
What happened, man?
And now look at us, scattered to the winds, broken on the rocks.
But when you say people, you really mean Trixie mostly, right?
Mostly.
The idea that we might all...
And the PCP was never like each individual person's main thing, it was all just sort of a side thing that we were doing in conjunction with our own creative endeavours.
So like we're scattered to the winds in podcast world, but like we're doing stuff.
In hindsight, it's a little silly, like the fact that like, you know, like the fact that me and D'Vu did in fact move into Trixie's house, the three of us live there and the practical benefits of that were minimal, right?
Because like, D'Vu doesn't need to live in the same house to edit the videos, I didn't need to live in the same house to do nothing related at all, right?
Yeah, I think she...
Nevertheless, this idea of the HQ persisted.
Yeah, I think she mentioned in one of her videos that you took forever to do her art stuff.
Yeah, she mentioned that in that one video, she complains that like, Ben Saint, I had to pay Ben Saint to do art for me and he took a while to do it, whereas Mint Salad draws whatever stupid shit I tell her to for free.
My new friends just work for me for free.
Yeah.
The thing she neglects to mention in that is that she didn't pay me up front, she said she wanted the art, the channel art, and then I did take a while to do it, but I didn't get paid until after I had done it, so whatever.
It's true though, I did take a while.
It sounds to me like you're a worse Mint Salad.
Aren't we all just a worse Mint Salad in our own way?
That's a good point.
Anyway, the PCPHQ is a bit, in hindsight, it's kind of a silly idea, but the idea persisted and it was a nice thought for a while.
It was a cool idea.
I feel like it was almost entirely watching Red Letter Media and being like, wouldn't it be cool to just hang out in a place where you make videos?
And also the Game Grumps Super Studio where they had all that Let's Play stuff in their recording room and they're like in walls of games and Amiibo figures and like, dang, that's the dream.
It's really just like, what if we had an office space?
That would be it.
What if we...
Lots of stuff.
That basically is the dream.
What if we had an office space?
It was the set.
It was the plebenweeb set.
I feel like it was the actual draw of PCPHQ, the set that we all used to do the lectures and stuff in.
I think Victor built it.
Yes.
That's the Red Letter Media set, but then also on top of that, she had the idea like, well, everyone should move into my house.
Everyone should move into my parents' house with me.
My parents gave me this house to live in.
Everyone's just moving here and then we'll be like the PCP, but they're all in one house.
And then that didn't work.
The parents eventually were like, okay, we actually are selling on that house.
You gotta move.
And he's like, hmm, well, okay, maybe we can't all live in the same house, but we can all live in Boston, right?
We can all live in the same area of Boston, but then, you know...
And then we sort of did, but then still nothing happened.
Like me and Munchy and Tom and Trixie and...
I think that's it.
We did all live in Boston eventually, but we still didn't do anything.
And again, it's like, what benefit does being geographically near each other really give to the specific stuff we're doing?
We're not even really working together on anything anymore.
Maybe we could have if we'd done another...
Well, I would imagine the main benefit would be that you could do more lectures.
Yeah, yeah, maybe, possibly.
And you wouldn't have to organize kickstarters to meet like the Radcon stuff.
Yeah, I feel like that was part of the pitch.
Yeah, you know what?
That's true.
We don't have to spend a lot of money flying people around.
That's good.
That actually is true.
Not for day-to-day stuff, but for what would have been stuff we would do at a Radcon.
Yeah, that's true.
Sure.
Yeah, it would have been interesting if the lectures just became a regular thing you did as opposed to just like a yearly or every couple of years kind of thing.
Especially since the lectures were real popular.
They were real popular.
It's a bit of a conundrum, actually, because they were real popular.
Some of the most popular stuff any of us ever did.
But we could only do them together as a group.
So we only did them at Radcons, and now the group is shattered.
I guess there's nothing in theory stopping us from doing something like that on our own, but who would we do it with?
There's no equivalent group.
I guess it would be possible to put one together.
Maybe you could put one together with all the guests you've been having.
I saw actually a comment.
There was a comment left on one of the PCP videos.
I don't remember which one.
It said, Radcon 5 stretch goals should be to get Cybershell and Gamerstaven in person at Radcon.
So I guess that's an idea.
Yeah, Cybershell live.
Where do you live, Gamerstaven?
I think Cybershell lives in like Washington, Seattle or something.
I was going to say that.
I have the same sense, and I don't know where I got it.
So that's probably true.
Don't you live in the Midwest or one of the Dakotas?
No, I live on the East Coast.
Let's just say I live to the south of where you live.
Okay.
Alright, fair enough.
Would not be unfeasible, I guess.
I guess it wouldn't be impossible.
I'm going to have to talk to everyone about it.
Anything is impossible if you put your mind to it.
Sure.
I want to say Radcon, but I said Gamerstaven.
Radcon 5 with you, me, Cybershell, Oblivionfall, Gamerstaven,
Cheesy Manfredo, Simsie, I don't know.
Tectonic Improv, Crack, the gang's all here.
Yeah, that's basically everybody.
The Merlogic, of course.
We could get Merlogic as like a trap and then kill him.
Oh yeah, I forgot about that guy actually, but I just remembered who he is.
We could get some baseball bands.
It'll be like the big video that we make.
Okay, the new Handboy Winter War will just be us actually killing Merlogic in real life.
In Minecraft.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was talking about, there's a tweet that said the skeletons are not really scary,
but they're kind of used in video games a lot.
It would be a lot scarier if like a nervous system just walked up to you without any bones or anything.
Like in Watchmen.
Have you read Watchmen?
Yeah, I've seen the film where they take that for a second.
Yeah, I watched a movie.
Oh yeah, I guess it happens in the movie too.
It's just like one scene of when Dr. Manhattan is trying to reconstruct himself
and for a minute he comes back and he's just a brain and nervous system.
I saw a picture of a person's nervous, I assume a real person's nervous system
like displayed in like a museum or whatever.
It was preserved and it was like, it was sort of like a rayed out like held up
in like a position that it would be in the human body, but it was just the nervous system.
So like brain up top, spine coming down, tendrils like coming down the arms and legs.
And it's like that's your whole like mind and stuff in your body.
Just take the rest of it away.
Scientific like illustrations and diagrams of the human body, the central nervous system,
the blood vessels, capillaries, the fucking arteries and stuff and the skull
and those like sort of medical, here's how to learn about skeletons, the human body books.
That stuff's like real body horror.
I don't know why people think they need like Junji Ito or like like scary things
when the real actual stuff is the stuff that makes me faint.
I open up a thing and I see like a liver and it's like this is what a liver looks like
if you sliced it in half, I'm like, oh no.
Why would you do that?
The scariest things were in us all along.
I can't believe we're so fucked up.
The scariest thing is just the horror of your own existence and how fragile it is
and how like a simple, such a small disruption to one's physical body
will just end your pitiful existence.
Something as flimsy as like a single bullet that just happens to pass like in one eye socket
and exit the back of your skull.
Something as small and random and pointless as that can just kill you.
I mean, if you pick up any given thing anywhere near you,
you could probably turn it into a weapon that can like kill you.
I think about this, how easy, how many forces are arrayed around us at all times
that could kill us?
Like for just my go-to example, trains go everywhere.
They're so big and if one day you ever happened to be in the path of a train
as it was going, you would be torn to shreds in an instant.
I live on the first floor of my apartment building.
It's kind of a big brick building.
Think of how heavy that building is if something gave out.
There's so much potential energy stored in the bricks of this building.
If it came down on me, I would be crushed and smothered
and smeared across my floor underneath all of that.
Another one is outlets, electrical outlets.
The connection in an electrical outlet represents an electric potential drop
that is akin to a cliff that you could walk through in terms of potential energy.
If you just stuck the right thing in there, or if you just touched it in the wrong way,
then suddenly that potential energy would release and go through you
and just burn you to a fucking crisp.
You don't have the super safety plugs.
I thought we do have the super safety plugs.
Maybe you do have some of them.
You have the shitty ones.
No, no, no. We've got the three-pronged plug.
We've got three pronged plugs.
Well, you copied us then because we came up with it first.
And I say we because I want to assume the smarts of people
who are somewhat generally associated with me by nationality.
And I did it, actually. It was me.
The glory of the British race.
You want to bask in your racial heritage.
That's not the only thing that Americans copied from the British.
Quite a lot of those things, too.
Transphobia.
You know, slavery?
No, of course, slavery.
The British didn't really do slavery.
No, we did slavery all over the place.
We did slavery better than everyone else.
We were the best at slavery.
You didn't really have like slaves in England, though.
You kind of traded them elsewhere.
We made a lot of money as a country by occupying foreign lands
and taking their people and using them as slaves to sell to other places.
It was really fucked up.
British Empire, one of the worst.
What was it like?
You get slaves in Africa, and then you trade them in the Caribbean
for molasses or rum or something, and then you trade...
There's a triangle, right?
Sugar and...
Sugar and rum and stuff.
Slave sugar, rum. Slave sugar, rum.
And you trade in a big triangle.
And I think the triangle...
The triangle was like slaves from Africa to the Caribbean
and sugar from the plantations back to the UK
where sugar is hard to make.
And then from the UK to Africa, weapons to sell to African tribes
in exchange for people.
I think that's the general idea.
It sounds like capitalism to me.
Yeah, of course it was.
I saw a Stefan Molyneux tweet that I had never seen before.
It was just a screenshot of it.
It was the most insane thing I had ever seen.
The tweet was like...
Okay, if I remember correctly, it was like,
who's worse, the drug user or the drug dealer?
In the context of slavery, whites were the users, blacks were the dealers.
Okay.
That's an interesting way of looking at it.
I guess he's probably specifically...
He's probably specifically referring to the fact that
we did trade weapons and rum
and whatever other commodities to the tribes in it.
We did trade for the slaves.
Some of them were just kidnapped, but there was trade.
We did obtain them.
Maybe that's what he means. He means specifically that.
We bought the slaves in some capacity.
But we also had military might in order to take them if we wanted to anyway.
Right. That's true.
And also in this metaphor...
It is interesting when you think about it.
In this metaphor, the black people are also...
They are also the drugs being smoked, I guess.
Which kind of muddies the metaphor a little bit.
It's like if the dealer was dealing you the drugs,
the drugs they're selling you are cutting off their own arms and body parts
and giving them to you.
And that's the deal.
And then you're asked, what do you think about that?
And you're like, I don't get it.
You say...
Who's the real villain?
I say, chopping my arm off.
It's probably best not to think about it.
That's how these things work, right?
You just have to accept them without thinking about them too deeply.
That's what I say about roles in society and colonialism.
Because as soon as you start thinking about it, it kind of doesn't hold up.
I just thought that was interesting.
Very funny.
So is that everything you wanted to say about the documentary?
Oh, let me think if there's anything else to say about that.
Just the footage, it's not a documentary.
It's sort of a documentary.
It's not a very structured one, but I mean it is one.
It doesn't have enough of a narration through line.
Like every so often Victor will point the camera at somebody and ask,
so what are we doing today?
And then we would say it and it would usually be not that interesting
until the Pleeb and the Weeb starts and then the documentary ends
because Victor was busy and he couldn't film anything.
Yeah, it ends because Pleeb and the Weeb started in earnest
and Victor was always filming that and he was no longer around.
Is the documentary of the fucking around leading up to Radcon 2 basically?
Yeah.
Which is the most memorable part for me.
I can't even really remember what happened day to day.
I don't know how many days it was, I guess that's one of the things.
I could look at my old vlogs because I remember making a vlog
at least of Radcon 1 where I was trying to make sense of everything
because there was a lot of stuff going on.
It did look like a lot of fun.
I watched some of the episodes of the Pleeb and the Weeb and not all of them
and the main one that I keep remembering is the one with Munchy
and Victor B stuff and the N-word counter.
Munchy, I'm sure he hates that.
I can't remember if he said that outright.
But he was so embarrassed of how he was acting.
When I made the Blu-rays, I think,
okay, I saw those guys a little while ago and there were some people visiting
and I gave some people had bought, they had back the Kickstarter.
And I was like, hey, since you're in town, here's your Blu-rays, LeMau.
And they were like, lol, cool.
And someone suggested like, hey, let's put on the Blu-rays.
Let's put on Pleeb and the Weeb.
And Munchy was like, I don't want to see my episode.
No, he does not like it at all.
Honestly, I can't really blame him.
We were going through, we watched through the uncut version and it's funny.
Like, he's not the only one, he's not the only one, but he does do it a bunch of times.
He makes these, the remarks are, they're obviously meant to be uncomfortable.
Like they're meant to be like off-putting on purpose and everyone laughs.
Everybody always laughs whenever he says it.
Because it's shock humor.
We all have a good laugh, but it's shock humor and we all laugh.
But I think sometimes more than others, it's an uncomfortable laughter.
But I think that was the point, right?
I certainly laughed.
It's kind of weird, but it's pretty funny.
Yeah, so it was...
I like the kind of weird interview with Jesse at the beginning of that episode
and he keeps cutting back to that interview about it.
Oh, you're talking about the actual Pleeb and Weeb episode?
Yeah.
I haven't rewatched it.
The only thing I remember of that one is that Munchy is so full of energy and so talkative
and he starts pacing around the room just talking while Trixie and Jesse are sitting in their seats
and they are sort of slumping down and being like,
I remember him being...
I don't know what to do anymore.
Munchy's completely bowled us over.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember him being like just beside himself about like,
I can't believe we're watching Kirby Flight to the Finish.
My favorite show.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's definitely a big ball of energy.
You know, he's a pretty...
I think he's a pretty talented performance artist and he got like a lot better since that time.
Yeah.
So he's pretty cool.
He's a funny guy.
He's a cool guy.
I guess I don't really have that much else to say other than we did have a lot to say during the comment...
I won't rehash everything that we brought up during the commentary.
If you're a patron, check out the commentary track.
I think it's cool.
That's it.
What else?
I guess we already...
I guess you probably don't want...
You probably don't want to discuss the conversation we just had.
No.
Okay.
I'll say what.
We did have a talk in...
Nate wanted to talk about the Blu-ray situation, which is fine.
We had a little pow-wow.
I think he called it a pow-wow.
And Jesse actually showed up, which I was surprised about.
That never happens.
But we did get into it, which is fine.
And we've reached some sort of agreement about it, I think.
Which is fine, I guess.
But we don't need to get into the specifics of it.
But that's an interesting thing that happened, I guess.
I don't know.
So I guess everybody is happy after all?
Oh, yes. Everybody's ecstatic.
Jumping over with joy over the moon.
Everybody's over the moon about how everything has shaken out.
I couldn't be happier.
It's good to hear.
Instead of that, Ben, talk about your game and comic.
The Slame Phantom's Revenge.
Well, sure.
I've been drawing...
I think I have 35 pages drawn of...
Right, because Phantom's Revenge, the game I made for a year,
I spent a year making it, that is done.
It is out for my patrons, not PCP patrons,
patreon.com slash ben saint patrons.
My patrons have played it.
Oh, really funny...
Okay, remind me to say the funny thing that happened with the game.
You know what? I'll make a note.
I'm going to make a note right here, so I don't remember.
Forget it.
Marriage. The note is marriage.
So the game goes with the comic, so I've been drawing the comic.
I need to draw...
Slime and Punishment ended with the video called S. Revert,
which was sort of the S. Cascade of Slime and Punishment.
And now there's some...
And now I have to do the Act 6.
Everybody's favorite.
No, it's much shorter than that.
I have to do just a little bit of story to explain what happens right after that,
to get Phantom from there to the game,
and then I have to draw what happens after the game and the end of the comic.
So I am currently...
I've drawn about 34 panels,
and he is most of the way from there to where the game happens.
I think I probably have to draw maybe like eight more.
So I meant to do that yesterday,
but I ended up spending a lot of my day doing a PCP channel
and red con documentary related stuff.
But oh well.
So yeah, I've been drawing the comic.
That's basically all I've been doing this past week or so.
So the game is finished?
Yeah, the game is finished.
On my Patreon, the last post,
there's all the different versions of the game that I released.
There's the first version,
which is...
Well, there's an old post with the demo,
and then there's three versions of the game that have more and more features added.
And actually, the final game, as I will eventually do the full release,
does have a few graphical changes.
Specifically, I added them.
I made it so that the damage numbers change size,
and they shake depending on how much damage is dealt.
I feel like it makes it a little more impactful,
but it's purely a visual change.
Other than that, the game as it is on my Patreon right now is the final game.
But a really funny...
What are you waiting on for the final release until you finish all the comics?
Yeah, the comic.
And you worked on the game entirely by yourself,
or did you have any help on it?
Yeah, I did it all myself, except for...
I stole some assets from other games.
Just a few...
The only sprites that I took were explosions sprites, animations from Secret of Mana.
I stole all the music from...
I think we talked about this because I was looking for a game to get music from.
The game I ended up settling on was Front Mission 2 Gun Hazard.
I took all the music.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, like I said, I was vaguely familiar with the Front Mission series.
I had played Front Mission 3, and I had liked it as a kid.
I had never played Gun Hazard, but I like the music from it a lot.
I stole some sound effects.
I used a couple sound effects.
I made some myself, like the sound of a soda can being thrown on the ground.
I just did that myself.
The phantom's voice sounds, like when he says stuff and when he burps and stuff,
that's just me, that's just recordings of me.
I got some sounds from YouTube, like sounds of horses galloping,
sounds of a sword being drawn and sheathed were from YouTube.
Some sounds were from Mega Man X, Secret of Mana,
and Mario RPG for spell sound effects and stuff.
Menu sound effects.
It's pretty cool.
I'm going to get a lot of references when I play it.
You probably will, yeah.
It's mostly those three games.
Four games.
The last feature that I added between versions 2 and 3 was weapon marriage.
I added the ability to anoint to your weapon with a podron to increase your weapon skill,
and when you increase it high enough, you can marry your weapon,
which increases your skill even further.
And when you get married to your weapon, there's a little like wedding ceremony.
And I was looking for...
That's nice.
Yeah, it's lovely.
Phantom Horn finally ties the knot.
No more migtail life for him.
But he...
I was looking for a pixel, like a 16-bit sounding version of the wedding march.
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
And I was looking around and the only one I could find, or the first one I could find,
was from a game called Libble Rebel,
which I had just happened to hear of recently,
just because Tim Rogers goes on a long aside about Libble Rebel in action button reviews Pac-Man.
And I was just like, wow, what a coincidence that this game I'd never heard of before,
but only recently heard a bunch about.
This just happens to be the easiest, the most readily available 16-bit wedding march sound.
What system is that game for?
I believe it's on the Super Nintendo.
That's interesting, I never heard of it.
And I'm kind of the Super Nintendo expert.
It might have not been released outside of Japan?
I mean, I'd never heard of it.
I'm not like an expert, but I'm a big Super Nintendo fan.
And I'd also never heard of it.
I would have thought of trying to check the Harvest Moon games for a sound effect like that,
but I don't think any of them actually do have that.
It would make sense if they did, though.
I have no idea why it's in Libble Rebel.
I haven't played it.
Libble Rebel is a game about controlling a line and drawing a rope around posts
and surrounding little monsters on a field with a rope.
And I don't know why there's a wedding in Libble Rebel.
You're tying the knot.
You're trying to ensnare them into a relationship.
You know what they say?
They say that marriage is kind of like a prison.
And life...
What was that great quote by that philosopher?
Life is like a box of chocolates.
No, I mean, life is a cage and death is a key.
That's what I meant.
It's funny.
In Phantom's Revenge, because the mechanics are based on Endless War,
I used in-game text from Endless War when you use the data command to get the data on yourself,
or on Virginia, or when you use...
Yeah, when you get text responses from Endless War,
like when you try to attack but you don't have enough slime, for example,
I used the same quotes that are in Endless War when you try to do those things.
And the ones related to marriage are all very cynical.
It's very funny. I think Munchy wrote them, which is funny.
But they're all about how when you get married,
it's all kind of regretful and resentful of how the good old days have passed.
Like now, we've settled into our boring married life or whatever.
That's amazing attention to detail.
Yeah, I didn't end up implementing weapon divorce,
because how much is it really necessary?
Like, there would be no possible strategic value to getting weapon divorced in the game.
So I was like, ah, fuck it.
So I didn't add divorce to the game.
The divorce ones are like, to go through the...
You have to endure all this shit about how marriage is a scam and stuff,
if you want to get weapon married and weapon divorced.
You have to go to the dojo.
Who hurt Endless War?
I bent the rules a little bit, because in Endless War...
Endless War's the one who says it all the time.
Endless War was married.
Yeah, he...
You know, there's...
We were talking about in the last art contest, Matt brought this up.
We were judging Endless War art entries,
and Matt was reminiscing about a post that we both remembered.
It was drawn by someone named Gabe, who has since deleted all of his social media posts
and all of his art.
He used to be a big Endless War artist.
He did a lot of great stuff.
And apparently a lot of it's deleted now, for he had one of these...
He had one of these episodes that so many people seem to be prone to,
where you just say, everything I ever did needs to be destroyed,
and you just like leave the internet forever and delete everything for some reason.
And he did that, as many people do.
But there was a comic about Endless War and this spirit woman in space.
It was supposed to be a prequel.
It was before...
Oh, yeah.
It wasn't a factual history.
It was something like a little Kirby.
It was like a what if.
It was someone telling a story.
The little Kirby before they had a real character design.
And they made a comic.
Yeah.
I didn't know that was deleted.
That's pretty good.
It was good.
We all remembered it fondly.
And it might be that the only record of it that exists now
might be in that art contest, in the lore contest,
where we judged it as a contest entry.
That might be the only place to see it.
I think the idea in the end was it was...
In the end, it's framed as Gabe just like...
He's like drunk and he's like telling the story at a bar or whatever.
So like who knows if it's true or not.
But supposedly like this spirit woman is like Gabe's mom.
Because Gabe is like this...
He's like a Kirby star child from space, you know?
So he's this cosmic...
Endless War and this spirit woman are like these two like cosmic entities
that like met in space and Endless War came to Earth.
Got divorced and came to Earth afterwards.
So yeah, maybe that's why.
Maybe that's why Endless War is so bitter about marriage.
Because it didn't work out with what's her name.
Well you know what they say, marriage is an endless war.
I hear that every day in my heart.
You hear that endlessly.
Kind of like a war.
What was...
What were we talking about?
How did I get on this?
Oh, the thing that I wanted to say, a funny thing was...
I had added in the weapon marriage system
and the weapon skill system, the anointing and the marriage.
They changed your weapon skill.
So they do increase your weapon damage.
And so it was an open question about whether it could be worth it to...
Do you spend those podrans leveling up so you can then get married
and get that damage boost from the weapon skill increase,
or is it better to keep the podrans so you can crunch them
to get the slime from them and also increase your level,
which does increase your damage,
but also that increases the cost of your attack.
So it's a bit of a trade-off with leveling up as well.
Also, leveling up is sort of like a hidden mechanic.
Like nothing in the game tells you that you can level up.
You sort of have to like find it yourself,
but now everyone listening knows that now.
Actually, I think Chrono Cross did something like that.
In Chrono Cross, you don't see what level your characters are.
They just gain stats every once in a while.
Really?
And it's not extremely obvious what increases your stats.
I mean, if you look at guides online, you can eventually figure it out,
but in the game itself, it just seems totally random.
Yeah, I ended up taking information out of the game.
Before, I had it so that when you beat the game
in any of the prior versions,
you would get an end screen that would display a bunch of information.
And that information was useful for me.
I wanted to know how many times were people leveling up,
where were they leveling up,
how many times were they attacking,
how many times were they being attacked,
how much slime were they entering the final room with when they won.
So that was info for me.
And then for the final version,
most of that stuff is not interesting to the player.
I think the player would care about certain...
What's the word I'm looking for?
Game state things?
Whether Phantom's horn broke or stayed intact,
whether Virginia was killed or stayed alive,
whether you ended the game married,
and your stats...
Not what level you were, that's not really important.
It doesn't really matter in terms of your state at the end of the game.
But I added stock trading.
So there's a mechanic that's totally unrelated to everything else in the game.
It means absolutely nothing, it doesn't interact with anything else.
But you can trade stocks in every room,
and then in between rooms, the stock values will fluctuate
according to a little routine that I came up with,
which may or may not be possible to game for maximum profits.
A little dancing routine, I imagine.
And so at the end of the game, it tells you your net worth.
Like how much money did you make?
You can find out if you become Jeff Bezos at the end.
But it was an open question whether getting married was useful at all.
And I tested it out, and I decided,
okay, I actually think that spending the two potorins to anoint your weapon twice
and then getting married...
Spending those two potorins is actually too costly,
and it actually makes it impossible to...
Well, not to win, but to get the good ending,
because there are things you can do that will let you win,
but will give you the bad ending.
So it's actually impossible to win and get the good ending and get married.
And then Prince Isolation, the same...
But just like real life.
Yes, and honestly, I was okay with it.
But then Prince Isolation, this is the same guy who sent that voicemail the other week
asking me to explain who Cold Corona is, which is very funny.
He tested the game out, and he just completely, at random,
I think just lucked into a combination of moves,
and strategy that actually...
He found the one way you can actually get married and win and get the good ending,
which we had all thought was impossible, but he just found it at random.
And I was like, yes, yes, it's strategic depth.
And actually, it's funny because doing so involves making what I had already considered
to be the optimal play in a situation where you have decided
that you are going to sacrifice Virginia to preserve your own...
Your health, to preserve your slime.
And if you do it...
If you make that play that I was aware of as being statistically optimal,
if you make that play, it actually does work.
You can get to the end and you have...
And Virginia has been destroyed,
or not like destroyed, destroyed, but she's been reduced to her heart.
And then you can get to the end and you do have just enough that you can eke it out.
And if you spent the potions getting married, but it's okay,
you have just enough that you can beat the final boss.
It's always cool, I'd imagine, if you're a game creator,
to find out when the people playing your game come up with strategies
you never thought was possible.
I was so excited.
I was so excited to learn that the possibility of space in the game
was just a little bit wider than I had even realized.
Just a tiny little bit.
There were a couple of new options in there.
I think maybe, I'm not sure if this is the case,
but I think for Smash Bros. Melee,
I think maybe the creators didn't know you could wave dash.
Yeah.
And then that completely changed the entire game.
I don't really understand what wave dashing is.
I mean, I've heard of it.
I don't really know how it works, but I know that...
Oh, it's when you go with the controller.
I know that Melee is full of shit that the devs didn't intend.
It's kind of a broken game, but that's what makes it...
It's like there's a whole other game.
There's a whole other game there that developers had no idea about.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's what people have been playing all these years,
basically, is that other game.
You know what?
I'm willing to admit that Phantom's Revenge is not as strategically deep,
and it does not have as many systems interacting
to create beautiful, spiraling, intricate webs
of potential player interactions as Smash Bros. Melee.
I'm sorry.
That's just a small game, you know, so...
Yeah.
I couldn't match Nintendo.
Maybe next time.
I have to say, as somebody who has tried making a game in the past,
it's pretty impressive you did most of this yourself.
I watched a tutorial.
I found some tutorials from a guy called Game Maker Rob on YouTube.
He had...
Because I knew that I wanted it to be...
I wanted it to be built as like a menu-based JRPG turn-based combat,
so I looked up some tutorials and I spent...
I think it took me like a week or so to follow this guy's tutorials
to build a menu system.
And it's funny, at the time I was like so confused,
but I was just like, I'm just gonna follow the steps,
I'm just gonna follow the steps and like figure it out
and like hopefully when it's done,
when I've followed all the steps, I'll have something that I can use
and I don't need to know how it works.
As long as it works, I can build on top of it.
And now looking back, I'm like...
I was thinking about this on the bus the other day.
I do feel confident now.
I didn't set out to learn anything.
I hate learning.
But I do think that if I tried to now,
I could just do what he did like off the top of my head.
Like the way...
At the time, the way that he was setting up the menu system,
I was like, why is he doing that?
I have no idea.
Whatever, I'll just copy it.
But now I'm like, oh yeah, I understand.
You had to set up like the way the in-game object
sets its states.
And basically the menu is a collection of states
that tell you what is the menu active,
which state of the menu or which sub-menu are you currently in.
And it draws the options here and there and wherever.
And I understand it all and I could do it.
I could do what he did now
because I've worked with that fucking thing for like a year.
I probably could have at some point gone back in
and remade it from scratch
and maybe it would have been better and easier to work with.
Instead, I just kept the like kind of fucked up and broken
and not broken, but messy,
probably needlessly complicated menu
that he had like basically given me in his tutorials.
It has all these like unnecessary states
and these unnecessary options that are just not available.
Like they're in there.
Like there is a magic menu in the game
that just has like two spells that don't do anything.
Like that is in the code.
It's just not accessible
because that was how that was what the tutorial told me to put there.
Maybe with all the stuff you've learned,
you can rebuild the game and make a sequel,
you know, instead of actually rebuilding the first game.
I think even with real developers,
that's a lot of what happens.
They make a game, they learn a lot from the experience.
And then when they rebuild everything,
they just make a sequel that's better in every way.
I wouldn't make a sequel
because Phantom's story is,
well, I mean, I guess there could be more stories
with Phantom Horn in New Los Angeles City.
It wouldn't be impossible, but like,
the story I wanted to tell with him is over.
This is the end.
It could be like a spiritual successor kind of gameplay sequel.
If I made another game.
If I made another game, I would,
I probably wouldn't even use,
I might use some pieces.
Actually, I used some pieces of that old, the champion game
that I made, like the text boxes in Phantom's Revenge are,
they use a lot of the same assets
and they're built of the same code that I used
to make the text boxes in the champion game.
With some added stuff, like I added code in there
to make it so that the text does not like,
type out like half a word before realizing
that it doesn't fit on the line
and then it jumps the word down to the new line.
That's actually a fairly common issue I see
with a lot of indie games.
It, yeah.
My, the early versions of my game have that in there
and I always intended to fix it.
I was just, I didn't really know how
and I was like, whatever, this isn't the final version.
Fuck it.
When I eventually got around to like,
okay, final version,
actually got to fix this like shitty text wrapping issue.
It actually wasn't like that hard.
Maybe it took me like a day.
It was funny.
Crack, I think Crack was complaining at me
about the text wrapping issue and I was like,
I know, I know, I just, I haven't gotten around to it.
I know it looks ugly.
And then I did it and it worked.
And he, and then later he sent me a video,
or no, he sent me a tweet thread from some code person
who was like, a big problem in indie games text shit
is that it looks like shit in this particular way
and it was like, you know, the line,
the word jumps midline.
And the thread was like, here's how to solve it.
And it went through like a very particular step
of like, first you do this, then you do this,
then you do this, and that solves the issue.
And I looked at it and I was like,
and it made me really mad
because the solution that they gave was way worse than mine.
But they presented like, this is how you solve it.
It's like, and I'm like, see,
I feel like if you know anything,
if you know what you're doing at all,
you don't need someone to tell you, here's how to do it.
You just have to think about it for like a little bit
and come up with something
and you can just fucking come up with something.
And that's what I did.
And it was so much better.
This person's solution involved like taking every,
you would take the text string you wanted to write
and then you would break it up into words
and then you would break up every word into like letters
and then it would do like a word count
and it would create like a new string
out of every individual letter
and then it would add the strings together
until it exceeded some value.
And then it would, mine doesn't do that.
Mine just like every time the string writes a space,
it counts characters until the next space
and then it adds that number to a value in the text box code
and it compares like, okay, will this exceed the horizontal space?
If so, insert a line break into the string
and then continue writing, otherwise continue writing
without adding a line break.
Mine is so much more efficient.
That sounds pretty elegant, pretty elegant solution.
Thank you.
It took me a little bit, it took me like a day to figure it out
and make it, because it did have some problems where like certain screens,
like certain instances of text that had line breaks already in them
would get confused when they needed to add a line break
and it would like insert like infinite line breaks
and that was bad obviously.
But that's not good.
So I needed to flick futz with it for a while,
but in terms of like, yeah.
I tried programming a few games like 15 years ago in C++
and I would always have trouble when I stopped following the tutorials
that I had online.
And when I had to like think of how to do things on my own,
I always kind of had those issues trying to come up with solutions
and common problems.
Well, I have a lot of respect for anybody that can actually do this kind of thing.
I was lucky to find that tutorial because it gave me,
like even though the menu system that I ended up building by following it
was maybe not exactly suited to what I wanted,
it gave me a framework that from then I could just be like,
well, he gave me, you know, attack items magic
and I'm like, all right, well, I'll just, I'll cut out the magic system.
I'll just cut that menu off, but then I kind of want to add in another thing.
Like, shit, what's another, what's even, like a data one,
one that you can like get a data reading on your enemies and yourself.
So I'll take that magic menu and I'll copy paste it
and then I'll just say, okay, what do I need to change about the magic menu
to make it into this?
Okay, well, I wanted to take out any battle effects
and instead insert sort of a, like a pause in the menu
and then it inserts a basically a text event.
And then I just need to create all these custom text events for each enemy.
But then the command is just like, it's just a menu command that leads to,
all right, run a text event, reset the menu to its initial state.
Okay.
And like, and every, every new thing I needed to add to the game
just became a matter of being like, okay, what is already in the game
that is the most similar to it?
Okay, take copy paste that into wherever I need it to be
and then be like, okay, what do I need to change about that
to turn it into this, right?
Right.
So that's probably how you started out,
but as you get more experienced and confident,
you can just kind of do your own thing eventually, I'd imagine.
Yeah.
If I were to do it now, I would, I would not have any trouble
making a menu system from scratch.
I wouldn't need to like follow tutorial for it anymore.
And you made everything in Game Maker, right?
Yeah.
Game Maker with GML.
I tried using Game Maker years ago, but I think back then it sucked.
So I kind of just stuck to C++ and later on when C sharp came out
and was new, I tried C sharp.
And then there was also like XNA, which was for like Xbox Live games.
This is quite a long time ago.
Wait, Xbox Live had its own like programming language?
It's not really like a programming language.
It's like an extension library like SDL.
So XNA is kind of like an extension of the C sharp language.
So that just means you have a bunch of pre-built functions you can use
for game making, which makes game making easier.
So I tried all that and I sucked at it.
I never really, I never really fully programmed the game,
but I made a few shoddy prototypes.
And now I think C sharp isn't used anymore.
I don't think anybody...
People use C++.
Yeah.
There's like a new C++ now.
C sharp in the music.
That's all I got to say about that.
All these numbers and letters is confusing.
Ben finally reached the meme status of learning to code.
Yeah.
I used to be a trucker, but now I've learned to code.
Yeah, precisely.
Yeah.
Is that a meme?
Yeah, learn to code is like...
It's a funny thing that tech pros say.
It's like, oh, technology is going to displace our jobs.
All these truckers are going to be out of business once self-driving cars become a thing.
Oh, well, they just need to learn to code.
They just need to learn to code and then they'll have jobs.
I used to create products, but now I code instead.
In the future, everyone will just work at a fucking data center doing data entry
in a fucking spreadsheet.
In the future, everybody can just be writing programs all the time.
That's the future.
The future is Ben St.
I remember reading a short Isaac Hasimov story where kids were thinking about what they were going to do after they got out of school
and that the only jobs they were talking about were all different types of programming jobs.
There's just different genres of programming.
The idea of building stuff and having other things is like, what's that?
What is this ancient thing?
What is this book?
Will you open it?
I mean, that sort of funny story.
In a world where automation is at a point where physical manufacturing, where you could just fucking 3D print literally anything,
what would you need?
A craftsman, a physical...
What would you need a carpenter for?
It makes sense to me.
Sounds cool.
I think automation is good, actually.
I think we need less jobs, but also we need communism.
Wow.
We need both of those things, and then it's good.
No jobs with no communism is bad.
And communism with jobs is maybe bad?
Is that like...
Oh, everybody works in the mines.
That's also...
Or whatever.
But both together is good.
Communism has lots of different flavors and culturally confusing historical examples,
which are not really actually communism or dictatorship.
I thought it was all about a way to gain power.
Wasn't it all about labor?
Yeah.
I mean, in theory.
In theory, yeah.
If you remove labor from the equation, doesn't that change things a lot?
You give them...
Well, I mean, the idea...
It's like in Kropotkin, right?
In Kropotkin, he talks about how agriculture...
Even when he was writing, agricultural technology had come so far that the productive output of land
could easily exceed the need for people to actually work producing it.
And this is as a type of automation.
You could construe it in the same way as like, oh, well...
We need less labor to get the same amount of stuff done.
So what should happen in a functioning communist society, what then should happen is,
okay, everybody needs to work less.
Everybody can get the same amount of stuff, because we're still producing the same amount of stuff.
Everybody can still get what they need, but we all just need to work less.
Whereas in the trucker self-driving car situation,
it should be a good thing that self-driving cars mean that these people don't have to spend their lives
doing the hard work of trucking freight across the country.
It should be good, but it's like, oh, no, but my job, though.
But my job?
Well, I gotta do something.
I gotta work.
Sure, this labor is no longer necessary, but I must work at something for its own sake.
Otherwise, I do not deserve to feed my family or whatever.
It's like on paper, it sounds good to most people to say...
Wait, no, not on paper.
What am I trying to say?
I'm trying to say the responses to communism, you say, you won't have to work as hard.
And it's like, well, how's that gonna work?
It's stupid, actually.
The idea that you'll be given everything you need, but people always default to thinking like,
oh, so we'll be like peasants.
We'll all have the same amount of dusty dry bread and nothing else.
Right, right, right.
We'll all be given rations.
We'll all wear denim jumpsuits.
And it's like the idea is that capitalism makes sure that that will happen unless you work.
And on the communism, on paper, you can live...
But you don't have to work.
You can live in a nice way.
On paper.
Yeah.
It's hard talking about it because I'm stupid and I'm not like a video essayist.
It's definitely...
In theory, the thing about automation should reduce the need for labor.
Seems like a slam dunk.
Obviously, that's true.
The nitty-gritty of implementation or whatever is like...
That's a lot.
That's a lot of stuff.
In the future, Utopia, when nobody has to work, they'll have more time to listen to the PCP.
When all the labor that ever needs to get done is completely automated,
well, I guess then you need people to maintain the computers or whatever that run everything.
But maybe even once that's done, once that stuff's all self-sustaining,
once all the work is done of like, well, you know, our fucking AIs,
they do all the work for us, they make everything we need to have made,
they build the houses for us, they make the food for us, they take us from place to place.
There's no more work that needs to be done.
There's a lot of science fiction that takes that idea and makes it sound scary.
And I sometimes buy into it because it's like, if everything has been done by the robots,
why do they need us anymore?
We'd just die out and they'd kill us and they'd destroy us
and we wouldn't have any way to fight back because they control everything.
It's very like...
It's like, I guess that's true.
It's just like, I guess that's true.
I guess we would like, if human life is less necessary to sustain everything,
maybe less people would exist.
It's a very like...
The idea, it's like, things can't be good.
Anything that seems really good must actually be bad somehow, right?
There must be some hidden downside to removing the need for humans to spend their labor.
Or whatever, right?
It has to destroy the world somehow, if we were to do that.
Because otherwise it would just be like a really, it seems like a really good thing
if there's less need for humans to work.
Seems like good, but it must be bad because if we're good, shouldn't we be doing it?
But we're not.
There must be a reason for that, I guess.
I don't know.
I was thinking about this in the shower.
This is a real shower thought.
I was thinking about human beings invented capitalism.
And I have to wonder, is that like somewhat ingrained in just normal human behavior
to want more, even if we have what we need?
Naturally, the reason we've taken over the planet as the number one species
is because we've been wanting more than we needed to literally survive.
And so we built capitalism as the way a society would run
if we were an individual once more than they need
and they don't want people to take it.
So they start like othering people and, you know, I want to be the rich guy at the top.
Everyone kind of feels like it would be cool if they were that guy
if they don't think about like the ramifications
or they otherwise don't care about the people who get left behind.
And it's like, yeah, I guess capitalism isn't like a problem.
We can just say, all right, no more capitalism and nothing bad would happen
because human nature has some sway in the way these systems end up happening.
So it's like, how do we actually do anything about this?
What do we need to do to the human?
You're going to have black market capitalism in this communist utopia, probably.
People would always want to be on top because it feels cool.
There'll always be markets.
And yeah, I think it is a thing of like, I think most animals,
just animals in general, yeah, they'll take more than they strictly need
because like it's useful to have surplus, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, something like capitalism or whatever,
or even like an oldie system like feudalism
that is about like one guy's hordes at all
and everyone else just has to deal with it.
Yeah, it grows out of that animalistic hoarding instinct, right?
That feeling that one must accumulate for survival,
for one's own survival benefit at the cost of, you know,
you got to choose between whether you want to hoard
and increase your own survival odds
or whether you want to collaborate, share with the tribe or whatever.
Humans are a social species, right?
Humans' survival is more guaranteed by their harmonious teamwork.
This is something I was thinking of.
The survival of the group is more guaranteed
if everyone in the group like mutually collaborates with each other,
benefits each other, shares with each other.
That's more beneficial than keeping everything away from the group for yourself
because then if you're not working with them
and they're not working with you,
that's the most beneficial thing that humans have going for them
is their ability to collaborate.
This is the thing I was coming into my brain in the shower.
It was like the reason we are like safety in numbers, social animal
is because that's a good way to survive,
but it's not because we care about each other necessarily.
We feel like we need to be part of a larger group.
We don't want to be outcast and we want to be safe and secure
because cooperating does that,
but at a large enough scale,
you're cooperating with a group that is competing with another group
and so you don't actually care about other humans necessarily.
You can and many people do because it's just sort of,
oh, it's a person, that's part of my species, cooperation.
But it's very easy to, if you feel like your group is under threat by another group,
to suddenly not care about them and their livelihood.
It's like it doesn't come from a place of real wholesomeness,
it comes from a place of survival, our instinct to collaborate.
I mean, yeah, that's how it is for me.
I know that it's just a better idea to not fuck people over.
It's a better idea to collaborate when it's possible.
To have people on your side is good.
This is the Ben St. philosophy is to use everyone around you to your own benefit.
I mean, you could phrase it like that.
I think most of my Japanese anime would call it the power of friendship.
So I mean, I guess it's all in how you want to look at it.
It's no matter of perspective.
Sora is such a fucking sociopath, right?
He's always telling Riku, my friends are my power.
Oh, so he's just using Donald and Goofy for power?
What a sick fuck.
He just, just so we can power up his damn-
All he needs to do is press-
Just so we can power up his damn Keyblade.
Yeah, it's kind of like a naive, deep thing.
We don't actually care about each other, it's just mutual benefit.
Wow, love doesn't really exist.
Pog.
Oh, I'm just like Light Yagami, I'm a creature of pure logic.
Yeah.
Speaking of using your friends as power, did you guys talk about Riley leaving Trixie's Yig thing?
I think you did.
I may have mentioned it on the last one.
There he goes.
There's really not.
Well, it is-
I mean, do you have anything to say about it, Chrono?
I just think it's kind of ironic that Trixie basically burned every bridge with everyone
and ruined her career just to be with Riley, to work with Riley.
And now he's gone, you know?
It made me remember the old-
It's been taken down now.
I saved a copy, cleverly.
I think it was called Introducing Yig Video, where she sits there wild-eyed,
like leg jittering or whatever, looking off camera,
reading from a script for some reason,
and talking about the future of Yig, I think it was called.
And she explains, like, yeah, we're putting red borders around the people movies
and the cartoon movies or whatever.
I remember that.
And movie movies and music movies and cartoon movies, which-
all that shit.
And then she-
whatever talks about them.
And then at the end, there's the part where she explains,
oh, and also here's why all these other people don't want to work with me anymore.
And she explains it very diplomatically.
She's like, I allowed myself to be fired by the best guy ever from Cantet.
He did not want to work with me or Riley or be involved in any of the things we're doing.
Okay, moving on.
And it was like, hmm, if there were a few more, there's like that.
And then this one in the latest video where she's like, oh yeah, by the way, Riley is not-
Voidgazer is cancelled, Riley is gone, he's not involved with Yig anymore.
Okay, moving on.
If there were a few more of those, like, just like three or four of those in-
two is not very enough.
But those two form a symbiotic circle.
What happens to one will affect the other.
You must understand this.
I don't know, it was like poetry.
You know, it rhymed.
Two things happened that were similar to each other.
She sure put a lot of eggs in the Riley basket, and now that basket's not there anymore.
Well, that basket has gone home to roost.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it.
The eggs have come home to roost.
I think it was talking about this in my Discord a little bit,
and I think a few people have made the observation that like,
that whole, yeah, that whole Yig, like introducing Yig like, oh, Yig Studio is like this new,
bold production company.
I'm taking things in a whole new direction.
I'm doing this with Riley, I'm doing this with Bird,
and we're making a whole anime with Mint, and it's gonna be great.
And like the entire next year was just like the slow dissolution and walking back
of everything that that video said Yig was going to be,
and everything that, like, Void Gazer, now Void Gazers,
and more recently the music reviews and other stuff before that,
all that stuff was gradually taken off the channel and put on some other channel
only to get like 30 subscribers and then be completely forgotten about and pretend it never happened.
Yeah, it's pretty surreal when you think about it.
And she's, you know, when Yig started it was like, you know,
fuck, fuck, fuck Digi Bro, fuck the whole, that whole thing.
You know, I'm moving in a whole new direction, I'm doing a whole new thing.
Yig Studios is this whole new thing, it's totally different.
And then of course, and now it's like, well, everything that,
okay, but everything that isn't, everything that isn't me talking about an anime,
take that off the channel, hide it, pretend it never happened, everyone,
the whole group has fallen apart, nobody's working on any of it anymore,
I'm just making anime videos now, actually.
And then those anime videos get like, they're getting like 8,000 views,
the last several videos she's put up have gotten like under 10, they're all under 10k,
the last three, which is very funny.
Low, even by my standards.
Well, it's still better than my stuff, so.
Well, it's all about the ratio.
But anyways, at the very least, I guess you can commend her for finally having the humility to kind of,
I guess this is kind of her way of admitting that she was wrong about everything, I guess.
Wrong, she doesn't, she'll never admit that.
She'll just never acknowledge it.
All that other stuff goes to another channel, I'll never acknowledge it.
I'll continue, I'll just keep making YouTube videos and then pretend that that was actually,
actually that's kind of what the plan all along.
Actually, I never said that I wasn't going to stop making anime videos,
so the fact that everything I said I was going to do in the Introducing Yig video,
the fact that all that is canceled and was a waste of time and I just made it all up.
No, this was the plan all along, actually.
She'll know she hasn't admitted any faults, she'll never will.
Well, this is like her, you know, not actually admitting it,
but her actions kind of tell a different tale if you get my...
Well, sure, I mean, sure, if you're paying attention.
Yeah, it's obviously, she's walked back all the other stuff.
Where's Lorent Witch? Where's Lorent Witch?
Yeah, I'd sure like to see that one.
I was this biggest fan.
I guess she must have gotten evicted.
Can I, can I just, can I just bring up the fact again?
Can I just bring up the fact again that in all seriousness,
in complete sincerity, with no trace of like irony or sarcasm or anything,
Trixie and Riley and Mint all sat there on stream and said,
yes, Mint has drawn thousands of frames.
Mint has drawn thousands of frames of the Lorent Witch anime.
It's coming, it's getting there, thousands of frames.
And then when they showed the animatic, it's like...
Maybe like 20 frames.
And what they met...
In one video, she showed a little bit of one.
It was like a couple shots, a couple sketches of like the witch
by like a wall talking to some like cats on a wall or something.
There were, there were a couple of drawings, there were a couple of rough sketches.
I think Riley might have tweeted some.
Oh, that's long gone. Riley deletes his tweet, his Twitter all the time.
But I think she did show some at some point.
But the point is, it was like a handful of drawings and like, and it became clear.
It dawned on me in hindsight that what they meant, what they meant by thousands of frames
is that, yeah, it's only a couple drawings, because it's just an animatic.
But it goes on for like, you know, 30 seconds or something.
And 30 seconds, you know, at 60 frames per second.
That's like 1800 frames.
Mint has drawn 1800 frames of Lorent Witch.
That's what they think things mean.
They just don't know what things mean, yeah.
And it reminds me...
It reminds me of how Trixie would have talked about how she bought a house.
She would constantly say she bought a house in Boston.
Seemingly unaware that renting is not buying?
Like, seemingly not even understanding.
Did she actually say that?
Yeah, all the time. She would say she bought a house.
She said she was married to Mae. She says Mae was her wife.
It's like, like, seemingly not understanding that like, two things are not the same thing.
20 drawings of Lorent Witch, a dozen drawings of Lorent Witch,
it displayed in 60 frames per second for 30 seconds, is not 18,000 frames of an animatic.
But whatever. Never mind, yeah.
By the way, you know, since you brought it up, did you send Mae her Blu-ray copy?
Mae didn't buy a Blu-ray. She did buy Road to Radcon.
She backed Road to Radcon and she did...
I guess that's what I was thinking of.
She had me send it to her parents' house.
So I did not send it to Ralph's house. I sent it to Mae's parents' house.
You're a very fine, upstanding citizen.
I know, I know. I would put it that way, for your information.
Hold on, I need to grab another sparkling water.
By the way, did you know that the Flat Earth Society has members all around the globe?
I did know that. I think I've seen that meme, in fact.
Where, like, that was said by an actual Flat Earth Society.
As like an advertisement on like a wall.
Yeah, that's pretty amusing. Pretty amusing, those Flat Earth guys.
Gotta give them credit, you know. They have a lot of passion for what they're doing.
Flat Earth has become a worldwide phenomenon.
Oh yeah, you missed a little joke.
They're talking about it all around the globe, you might say.
It's a very common meme.
Well, it's easy. Simple and clean.
I actually wanted to mention something.
Speaking of like pony games, you know, you made one.
Like Phantom's Revenge, yeah. The famous Brony game.
I don't even, can I just say, I guess it is a Brony game.
I don't consider it to be that, although I guess you could call it that.
Like the fact that it has, the fact that it features-
I don't think it's a Brony game, because Brony's specifically will not find anything interesting in it.
The fact that it features a pony as its protagonist,
and the fact that Ponyville features in the comic
is almost completely incidental.
It just happens to be the case, but it's not like, it's not really that important.
It's not about that, you know.
Well, in any case, I actually discovered a pony game that I thought you'd find interesting,
because it combines Mega Man and my little pony two things that you're known to like.
Bro, I know. Are you talking about Megapony?
Yeah, exactly. I guess you already knew about it.
Bro, me and Keg, Phantom Horn and Keg Standard did a whole Let's Play of Megapony back in the day.
Back on T-Bat plays.
Oh, wow, really? I didn't see that.
The soundtrack, Megapony has a great soundtrack. I have gushed about it before.
The Megapony soundtrack is made of these gorgeous, gorgeous, 8-bit mashups of classic Mega Man video game music
mixed with leet-like motifs of well-known MLP songs.
What's that one from, that one that the cadence sings when she's in jail or whatever, mixed with the wily theme?
That one's great.
Yeah, I guess I need to watch the LP you guys did back then.
You could, if you wanted to.
This looks pretty cool. I saw some gameplay previews of this game and it actually looks like something I want to play.
It's good. Yeah, it's a whole new, it's got its own levels. It's a whole Mega Man game. It's a whole Mega Man fan game.
It just so happens to feature ponies in it, but whatever.
Yeah, I'm not a big fan of the pony stuff, but I do like Mega Man.
You could play it as just a Mega Man game and the fact that it is pony-related is just a funny quirk, just a funny graphical quirk.
Yeah, I love Megapony. There were a bunch of really good, this was one of my favorite things about having a pony channel on the side channel,
getting to play and bring what little attention I could to some of these.
Yeah, there was ponyvania. Ponyvania was pretty good. There was a little bit incomplete.
Megapony, Legacy of the Pony was a really good one that I think was based on a Metroid, it was based on the Game Boy Metroid, I think.
There sure are a lot of these pony fan games.
I mean, the hype was huge. You could make, if you made anything at all and branded it as pony stuff, and it was good at all, people would lose their minds about like, oh, it's Metroid but with a pony in it.
Oh, it's Dubstep but with ponies in it. People craved it.
And it was great. It was a whole little self-sustaining culture.
Yeah, it sounds a lot like the Sonic fan community which Cybershell is well acquainted with.
Yeah. I mean, there's so... Yeah, it is actually. I guess the Sonic fan of has basically never waned, has never died.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it. Yeah. I mean, it has changed. It has changed its tone.
Yeah, it changed much like War has. Like never? Sonic and War both have a lot of common.
Wait, War never changes? Doesn't... Wait, one thing says War has changed.
I was referencing Metal Gear Solid 4, I think.
Metal Gear says War is always changing. Fallout says War never changes.
It says War has changed. War has changed. I think that's Metal Gear Solid 4, right? Is War has changed? Or maybe even earlier than that. Maybe not.
It definitely in 4 because that's when like, you know, all the weird technology shit starts to really fuck shit up.
Have you ever seen wacky game jokes for kids? The animated series by Hot Diggity Demon?
No, but it sounds interesting.
Probably have seen it. That sounds familiar.
It's the thing he did before the Pony.Mov series.
Is it like kids? It's like kids with blue hair. One girl has blue hair or something, right?
The girl is June and she has blue hair. She's a gamer girl. And then there's a nerd kid and they're making YouTube content about wacky game jokes for kids.
And there's this other guy, Mickey, who is forced to be part of the YouTube show for some reason and he's like a real dick.
And that's the joke. And it's a really fun series actually. Really well animated.
Anyway, he makes a point about the war is always changing and war never changes thing. It just reminded me of that.
I check that out. I think I like that guy's stuff if I remember correctly who he is.
Here's...
Yeah, Max Gellardi.
Here's a question. Here's a question. I don't know what to do with about this.
Somebody whose name I won't say for their privacy sent me, I just got a PayPal. I just got money from someone on PayPal.
It's got $16. Someone just sent me $16 and attached a message that says upload the podcast on Google, you cuck.
And people have been telling me that the podcasts have not been going on. I think Tom has been busy.
I think Tom, because Tom is the one that knows how to do that. I don't know how to do that.
Like on Apple podcasts and Google and whatever.
So this guy just sent me $16 and I...
Okay, I thought maybe because he included there is a shipping address here.
I'm wondering if I should now send him Road to Radcon. I feel like this looks like he was trying to buy Road to Radcon, but he...
$16 is... No, that's $20. I think... Why $16?
I think he was trying to...
It sounds like he was just trying to get your attention.
That's a possibility.
You didn't need to do that. He just wanted to give you money for something that you weren't doing.
I don't know. I don't know what to do about this.
You should probably give him his money back because this isn't even your duty.
I don't think I will. He gave me this $16 fair and square.
Guy, if you're listening, if you want Road to Radcon, send me five more dollars.
Otherwise, thanks.
Otherwise, hit the road.
Otherwise, hit the road. Jack and Tom, please upload the stuff to... Upload stuff, wherever.
I heard someone say... I think Tom might be driving somewhere.
I heard someone say that Tom is traveling somewhere, driving somewhere. I don't know.
Maybe not. I don't know anything that's going on.
Tom's an enigma.
Tom is an enigma.
Tom has been in a state where people think he's moving for two and a half years now.
I know he hasn't because I saw him recently.
I don't know if I mentioned this. I hung out with Tom.
It was surprising. He showed up at Munchie's house because Sixton was there.
Three weeks ago because Sixton was there and Tom wanted to see Sixton.
I think that was what...
Oh, that's the meetup that I would have been at.
Yes.
Tom was there.
We have invited Tom to stuff and he has never...
He has come a couple times, but he...
I got him out to my house like two years ago, maybe like twice,
and then he never came to anything ever again, but Sixton showed up and Tom was like,
okay, well, in that case, I got to go.
I was like, okay.
And you know what? Fair enough because Sixton's really good at music.
So it makes sense, I guess.
True.
Tom really needs to put his...
Go check out Sixton's music. Go over on Sixton.com.
I don't know what their thing is.
Slamrarn.
They have a band camp.
Their band camp is Slamrarn unless they've changed it.
It sounds like Tom really needs to put his back into things more.
Mmm.
Very has so much to give.
Very funny.
In the documentary, when Tom shows up to Radcon too, we're asking him how he is,
and one of the first things he mentions that he recently threw his back out,
grim portents of the future.
That's some grim foreshadowing.
Exactly, exactly.
There's a lot of foreshadowing in that documentary.
Yeah, that's true. I guess a lot of it is.
I think people were like leaving comments about that while they were watching.
I saw in the premiere.
Yeah, there was.
A lot of people being like grim foreshadowing.
A lot of people being like, damn, kind of...
Sad, seeing everyone having fun, knowing what would eventually happen,
and like, lol, true...
What else?
Was Jeff in that one?
He is.
He was.
He actually...
It reminded me...
I hardly talked to Jeff when he was there.
Same.
I think Jeff was basically there to talk to Digibro.
Because Digi was bigger than Mother's Basement,
and it was a networking opportunity for him, I think.
Not that he was rude or anything,
but he was there because his colleague had invited him to participate in a collaboration.
An anime-related collaboration.
I did talk to him a little.
We went on a car ride.
No, no, no, this was not...
There was a car ride where apparently DeVue and Jeff got in like a political argument,
because, you know, Jeff, Hillary Stan, still with her, Libguck, DeVue,
only like six months ago, was like...
I think Trump was kind of bad, actually.
So, you know, I could see how they might have had this agreement.
Apparently they got in an argument.
I don't... I wasn't there for it, so I didn't see it.
I definitely was in the car at one point with Jeff,
but I don't remember talking to him about hardly anything.
I think he was there. He had a one-track mind.
It's pretty interesting to see that.
Wasn't he like a member of the PCP at one point?
He was.
This was... Yeah, this was back...
He was at that time.
This was back when Mother's Basement was a smaller channel than the Digi Channel.
So, it was a...
And it's really funny to hear in the documentary when they talk about...
Trixie is like...
Jeff, you know...
They're talking about like making good videos.
Like, you gotta make good videos.
Like, oh, you gotta shill more.
Like, oh, well, you know, hey, I'm making good videos, though.
They're like talking shop and like...
Trixie is like giving advice and stuff.
It's like, you know, another like...
Weird to see that knowing how things shook out.
Apparently, she should have taken her own advice more, I guess.
She really should have. She really should have.
She used to give kind of good advice.
She kind of knew what she was talking about,
but it was sprinkled with like, dumb shit that's like...
Obviously, this is just like survivorship bias.
Like, it wouldn't work for anyone.
It just happened to work for you.
This isn't real advice.
But, you know, making a thumbnail and titling a video...
You know, I guess she had that down.
She really attributed her...
So much of her success to like knowing how to make a good thumbnail and title a video.
When like, that's actually like so simple.
Like, it does not take a genius to understand that like a big, appealing face as your thumbnail
is like an attractive thing that will make people want to click on.
It's really not just a matter of knowing that.
To make the difference between success and failure.
Yeah, there's a little bit more to it than that.
Yeah, she talked about it like it was.
It was just little tricks like that that were like the reason...
She just knows all the tricks.
The reason why she's successful is just because she knows all the tricks.
There was no luck involved or anything.
That's why they call her Trixie now.
She knew all the tricks.
Ah, true.
But it's crazy to see how...
I think Jeff now has over a million subscribers or something.
I looked.
He's got like 1.25 million, yeah.
It's more than I thought.
So he started out as being smaller and Trixie probably looked up to her
and now he totally eclipsed her.
So it's pretty interesting.
Yeah.
I guess I could have been Trixie if she just kept doing what she was doing.
She...
I mean, it wouldn't have been exactly the same, but...
Okay, you know what?
I feel like Trixie's content was always a little more niche
because of the personal angle.
I'm gonna say...
I don't know too much about what Jeff's content is like,
but it seems more like wider, appealing, but less emotionally interesting
from a review or analysis perspective.
Trixie could have gone a different route and ended up much more successful.
But it's not like Yig was like the end.
It's not like everything was going great and then Yig was like,
oh, she changed her formula, she changed her name, she changed all this stuff.
That's what ruined it.
It was already...
I mean, how they marketed was a big failure.
Yeah, I noticed there was a decline before the Yig stuff.
There was a big decline and then it led to stuff like the rants, right?
Stuff like the rants are her basically being like,
okay, my channel is floundering, like my numbers are stagnating.
So what I need to do to make money is to lean more into the niche parasocial element of it,
which I'm not saying that it's wrong to do that,
but it's a sign that my metrics, my pure numbers are not pulling the weight.
The crazy thing is the rants were really successful.
She was getting more of them than she could have even done.
They were.
Looking at her Patreon, it's funny.
I'll bring up the graph.
The graph I always look at.
I cleared my cookies now and now I have to reload every page.
I think every page that I've loaded is broken.
I remember she stopped doing the rants because she was getting so many of them.
She had a hard time working on other stuff.
Yeah.
So it was a very lucrative business.
It's her peak.
We looked at the timeline while we were doing the commentary, watching the documentary.
That was in January of 2017.
A few months later in May 2017 was when she would switch from the per video to per month Patreon model.
That was when her number went up from 1,300 to over 4,000.
Then it dipped for a while and then I think in around mid-2018 it starts going up again.
It briefly rose even above that initial peak in March of 2019.
It hit almost 5K.
It hit 5K but it was right there.
I think that was the rant era.
That was when she was making the most money ever on Patreon.
She was deep in the rant era and then that continued for a few months.
Around February 2020 is when it completely falls off a cliff and now we're at 500, 600.
She shouldn't have stopped doing those rants so soon.
I'm sure they would have eventually dried up but she should have just kept doing them for as long as they came in.
The numbers don't lie.
That's super easy. Those rants are the easiest things to do.
I made a post on Twitter about the incredible ratio of 300,000 subscribers on that channel to getting 7,000 views.
On a main upload, on a real upload that's not an updated video.
Like a real video. 7,000 views.
I've seen YouTube channels with worse disparities than that.
I struggled to think of any. Maybe there's some.
I've seen a few.
A YouTube channel that had a super viral thing or two and then didn't have any good ideas for years after that.
They get a couple thousand even though they got hundreds of thousands of subs.
That's what we're talking about.
I think the rebranding and stuff she did also killed her algorithm performance or whatever.
I think there's something to that.
It probably did.
I think at the end of the day, it's just that people don't like her anymore and don't want to watch her stuff.
It's definitely part of it.
You could be as fucked by the algorithm as possible but if people want to watch your stuff, they're going to watch it.
You can't just blame the algorithm for everything.
At the end of the day, you're responsible for making stuff people want to see and being someone that people want to watch.
What was I going to say?
I had one other...
I was talking to Mimeori, the Among Us girl on Twitter.
We were talking about the rebrand and how stupid it was.
I wrote a reply and it made me think.
When she was talking in the Future of Yeg video, she was talking about all these projects that they're going to be doing.
Then I think in the I Hate Digi Bro video, she's talking more in the past tense.
It's what she wanted to do.
She kind of reiterates it again.
The idea is I want to live in a truck or a trailer or an RV, live with my boyfriend, go around, meet people, make stuff,
and then just go from place to place, meet up with people, make work on projects.
The way that it sounds to me is that...
And the way that she describes Yeg as her crew.
When she says her crew, to me, it doesn't sound like she's talking about a one-piece Nakama.
It's like a production crew.
They're there to work for her.
They're there to set stuff up,
make connections for her.
This is consistent with how Riley presents himself.
Riley says, I'm the producer.
I have the connections.
I'm going to set it all up for you.
I'm going to bring in professional people.
I want to make Radcon 5 happen.
I'm going to make it a professionally hosted event, like a catered event or whatever.
It's going to be a real rap show this time, not like whatever bullshit you were doing.
When she describes them as a crew and she talks about the things they're doing,
it sounds to me like the goal here was to become...
And she talks about how she wants to be the director.
She wants to be like the director of a studio.
I really think she just wanted to get these friends that she could just tell them what to do,
tell them to make stuff, and they would just do it and make stuff and put it on her channel,
and they would do shit for her, and other people would make shit,
and she could just get to take credit as the I'm the director of this studio.
This is all under my umbrella.
I don't have to do anything. I don't have to do any work.
I can just smoke weed, and other people will make shit for me.
And isn't that the capitalist dream?
I think so.
She never quite puts it in those terms, but that's my read of when she describes what she wanted for Yig.
I think that's what it is.
She just wanted to be able to step back and have a self-sustaining content machine
under her branding, under her control, that she could just profit off of, live off of.
I don't know how accurate that is, but it does seem like...
That's just my opinion.
Her creative drive to make stuff is sort of gone.
I mean, she was writing Kusomega, which was like a light novel,
and she seemed like she was really into it, and lots of people were like,
oh, this is cool. You should really make this a thing.
And I felt like she was going to, but I don't know what's going on with that.
For Nanarimo.
She sort of stopped.
For November last year, for Nanarimo, she said at the beginning of the month,
she said she was going to write a novel, maybe three, like maybe two or three.
And then the whole month goes by, and literally all she does,
she writes like a one and a half page short story about...
First of all, she asks people, like, give me an idea for a short story on Twitter.
Someone suggests, I don't know, something about a robot or whatever.
She writes like a one and a half page short story about a robot, and that's it.
What happened to the three novels you were going to write?
That's something that's been the case with her for a long time.
She starts a lot of projects and doesn't finish most of them.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that's always kind of been true.
But it's sort of been held up by her work ethic.
She was able to make lots of stuff, even if a lot of the projects didn't go anywhere.
The human content machine as like a gimmick.
I don't know why that has also gone with Yeeg.
She's not interested in making stuff on like a large scale,
because I think that's a lot of the reason why she remained and became so big as an internet figure.
But she did used to...
Just the amount of stuff she was able to produce.
She did used to have a pretty good work ethic.
Not all of it was the best.
I think it's...
Because from my perspective, I don't really have a say in what an internet person does for their internet job.
If you don't want to make your videos or create things anymore, then whatever.
I don't care.
That's your prerogative.
That's your life.
But if we're talking about her as like a person,
I don't know why she thinks letting go of the work ethic is a good idea
if she wants to continue the internet stuff with people doing the work for her instead.
It just seems like it's not going to work.
It seems like it hasn't.
It has not worked.
I mean, at this point,
I think she said in the I Hate Didgeridoo video that if the views continue to only get the amount of views they've gotten,
she will eventually quit.
And they've only gotten worse since then,
which is very funny.
The video is, I think, why I was saying before that.
It does seem she has a little bit of humility about what's been happening.
I don't think you're...
Maybe not as much as she's showing, but...
I think that you see what she's saying,
and you feel, you rightfully feel,
wow, this is embarrassing.
She does not feel that way.
She doesn't understand.
She does not recognize that a failure has occurred publicly
and that she ought to be humbled by it.
She is frustrated.
I think she's noticeably frustrated in that video.
Compare her attitude in I Hate Didgeridoo to her manic energy in The Future of Yig.
It's like night and day.
I think she's frustrated that the outcome has not been what she wanted,
but she's not like,
I messed up.
I made a mistake.
She's just explaining, like,
here's what I'm gonna do.
It's gonna work.
Okay, bye.
All I'm saying is, at the very least,
she's admitting the outcome is bad,
whereas before, she seemed to just completely...
She acknowledges that the numbers are low.
She acknowledges the numbers are low.
So, like, good for her. She can count.
She notices that there's less money in her bank account.
Before, she wouldn't even acknowledge that there's a problem.
She would kind of, like, censor all mention of it on the channel.
People would post comments saying the views are bad or whatever,
and those comments would be deleted.
Yeah, the dislike ratio, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course, of course.
Uh...
Uh, well, I was gonna say, um...
Yeah.
So, she's...
I understand her motive,
even though her creative verb or whatever,
her enthusiasm for it seems gone.
Like, she seems checked out, frustrated,
unengaged in, like, the...
I hate Digipro video, and again,
in the recent one, the, like, best-looking anime video,
the one where she says Riley quit.
She just doesn't seem happy to be there.
Uh, she's gonna...
But I can understand keeping at it,
because even now, even after, like, losing most of everything,
she still has, you know,
she's still making, like, 600 something on Patreon a month.
Just, that's just free money forever that will never go away.
Uh, she still...
She said she, like, has, like, put more, uh, ads on her videos
or her channel ad revenue,
just on passive old views and old videos,
is probably making hundreds,
maybe over $1,000 a month, just by existing.
That's just free money forever.
So, like, in a sense,
she is kind of making a living at it,
even though, like, not really.
It's more like a passive living was already made,
uh, and it will just continue to be the case.
I think the, um, the thing about it is,
it was lucrative for a really long time,
and she believes that it can become lucrative again,
but I don't think she realized quite how much luck played a part
in her, her rise.
Absolutely.
And so she doesn't realize what needs to be done to rectify it.
This is what...
In the state that it is now.
This is what I was saying about how she thought,
she really believed that it was just her own genius.
She taught, like, remember at Radcon 4,
she was gonna give us all, like,
she was gonna give us all, like, uh, like advice, right?
Like YouTube career advice.
She wanted to take us all aside,
talk about, like, the state of our,
the state of our, like, careers or whatever,
and, like, give us personal,
like, a personal advice program,
but, like, here's what you need to do to, like,
to, like, supercharge your career.
At Radcon 4?
Yeah.
I remember that.
She didn't, she didn't really end up doing it forever.
Like, she never did it with me because I wasn't interested.
I think she might have done it with one or two people,
but she was talking about it.
Like, this was a thing she wanted to do.
It was like, I want to take everyone,
maybe it was gonna be filmed, I don't even remember,
but, uh, that was,
she was talking about that at Radcon 4,
and she, she really just attributes all of her success.
This is, you know what, this is a thing of, like,
lots of people, lots of rich people are like this.
They attribute all their, all their successes
are due to my own genius,
my own good decisions,
my own skills and abilities.
All my failures are bad luck.
The market, the market was against me.
The, the, uh, you know, the, you know,
just something happened that I was out of my control.
It was an act of God, you know,
and nobody could have predicted this.
Yeah, all her, uh, successes kind of got to her head
and gave her a big ego.
We got kind of, uh, a little bit conceited.
She's not that special.
She's not particularly smart.
I, she's not, I wouldn't say she's,
I wouldn't say she's even a good writer.
What she was is a prolific writer.
She wrote a lot, and that's not nothing.
That's something.
Uh, and she had a weird personality
that I guess appealed to a certain niche
and it wasn't well served in the anime YouTuber market,
and I understand the appeal there
and how it led to her just hitting,
striking the right chord
with a certain demographic of people
and it got her popular with those people.
That all makes sense.
But it's all, also,
pretty much just complete happenstance.
It all just happened to work out that way.
I do think she does have some, some genuine talents,
maybe not as much as she thinks she has, but
she kind of...
I'm not saying she's...
She had a pretty good ability to like talk about stuff
and make it sound more interesting than it was.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Right.
I'm not, like, I'm not, I'm not saying she had...
I'm not saying there was nothing to her at all.
But she, she really thought it was...
What I'm saying, Gabe's right, there was a lot of luck involved,
but she doesn't see it that way.
Yeah, I agree with that.
She just thinks that, like, she just was such a,
such a marketing genius or whatever.
It's definitely...
I don't know.
There's some truth to that.
There's a lot of luck involved in YouTube success, you know?
It's, it's sad but true.
We have, we have now turned this into
the Bitch About Digi podcast that Trixie says,
the pod, that Trixie says the PCP now is.
Which is, it's fun.
I feel like...
It's fine, it's fine.
I feel like this is, this is fine,
if only because we're largely talking about
the Red Con 2 documentary.
That's true.
That just came out.
In, in that context.
And we're reminiscing, in a reminiscing mood.
Yeah.
I think, I, you know, I've never really, like,
DM'd her about my thoughts on her channel direction
or what she could do.
I don't know whether she'd appreciate me doing that now.
Didn't she, like...
I could just tell her.
What do you think, what do you think she...
Just make more stuff if you want to get big again.
Why would you want to help her?
I don't know.
Didn't she just burn her bridge with you,
like, everybody else?
I mean, she's, like, whatever.
I'm not, like...
I'm not, like, terribly, like, hurt and, like,
betrayed by her, as I think you feel been.
I still don't like her.
I, but, like...
I, I hate her.
I hate her and I want her in the gutter.
That's literally what I want and I'm not ashamed of it.
But it's a very, um...
Yeah, I'm not quite there.
It's a very saint core thing to say.
And you know what?
And I'm a good person and I am full of light.
I am Kingdom Hearts because she deserves it.
And evil should be punished.
I am the good guy.
And I mean that and I'm not joking.
Yeah, that's exactly what a good guy would say.
This is what a good guy would say!
Listen, I think she...
I don't know.
In my opinion, in my opinion, the karmic scales of balance
are out of whack.
And she, and even to this day, even now,
she has so much more than she deserves.
What she has now, you know, maybe like $1,500 in passive income,
just money that she gets just for breathing,
that's so much more than so many, than most people have.
That's amazing.
An incredible blessing.
She doesn't deserve it.
Literally, she's a bad person.
Literally, she deserves nothing.
So if, you know, fucking a fire at Internet headquarters
occurred tomorrow and all the servers went down
and YouTube died forever and Patreon died forever
and all that money was gone and she was back to zero,
I would laugh and I would say good.
This is what should have happened.
This is just a good thing that's happened.
Justice has been restored.
And that's where I'm at.
And I will always be there.
It sounds like YouTube is the UBI we fell to make.
Why didn't everybody, you know,
if everybody had just started making YouTube videos back in 2015,
everyone would be rich, just like if everyone had just bought
Bitcoin back in 2014.
Exactly.
Everyone would be rich.
Stupid.
Duh.
It was the solution to the economy,
but everyone who just didn't recognize it at the time
is just too stupid and they deserve to be poor.
Yeah.
Duh.
Precisely.
But anyways, speaking of RVs,
did anybody catch the RV joke in that video I did like months ago?
Yes, I did.
I did see that.
I can't remember the joke, but I've seen the video.
I forget what the video, what was the title of it again?
I posted it in the chat.
It's the Astros Playroom review that I did.
I'd never heard of Astros Playroom before.
It's a PS5 game.
I caught the RV jokes in there.
This wasn't a real review.
It was just kind of like a joke review kind of goofing around.
But I did do a real review of Metroid Dread.
I don't know if you guys saw it.
You know.
I did see that, yes.
I don't think I did.
I'll just kind of link it in there.
As well, if you want to put the link in the description for anybody listening to this.
Of course, of course.
It's like an actual serious review.
I did that recently.
I've done many actual video reviews, have you?
You've mostly been on your website.
Yeah, this is my first attempt at a real video review.
So people can check that out.
You can kind of imagine this like one of my website reviews, but with video to accompany it.
And also, I did a podcast with Cybershell a couple of...
Oh.
That's also a little while ago.
We talked about Sonic 06 and gaming stuff in general and that kind of stuff.
So if you like Cybershell, you should probably listen to that one.
Wait, did that just work?
You know what?
I do like Cybershell, actually.
Maybe I will listen to that.
I'm almost finished.
I've almost caught up with Animorph in time.
Oh, really?
So, yeah, almost.
I'm a few episodes behind still.
I listened up until the one where they say that I'm sexy.
That's a good place to be.
That's episode 39.
That's book 39.
So that's three episodes behind where we're at.
Yeah, they say I'm sexy.
Oh, wait, no, actually, I think they've probably released like two more since then.
So, yeah, I just wanted to...
I will give a listen to that.
I just wanted to plug this stuff to kind of give you guys an idea of what I've been up to.
Yeah, it's been a while.
It's been a little while.
And I'm working on a major secret project that maybe will come out this year,
hopefully in, you know, 50 years from now.
A major secret project, huh?
Do you want to...
Do you have any hints about it?
It's just a video, but it's probably going to be long, like maybe 40 minutes to an hour long.
And it's a new idea, but it incorporates some of my old trademark humor.
Because, you know, back in the day, I used to do those pun LPs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I just...
That's what we knew you from.
I just figured out why not take that kind of humor and incorporate it into a video
that people might be more interested in watching instead of it just being a let's play.
That sounds like a good...
That sounds like a pretty good idea, yeah?
Makes sense to me.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
So I'm hoping to see if people will like that.
Well, let me know when that's out.
I'll check it out, whatever it is.
Yeah, I'll definitely let everyone know about it because it's going to take quite a while.
Good, good.
I see.
Well, it's not good that it'll take a while, but interesting.
Well, it's just going to take a while because I'm really slow at this kind of thing.
Well, same.
I was hoping that I'd be done drawing the Slime and Punishment by now.
Almost halfway through February, and I would say I'm probably more than halfway done with drawing, probably.
It's hard to say.
I was hoping to be further, but...
So you're basically just finished with the game and you're just waiting for the comics, right?
Yeah, and it's a bit of a...
I was actually...
This sounds wild.
I had actually intended not to release the Sonichu 102 lecture until I had finished this game and the comic.
I'm well aware of that.
Really? Yeah, okay.
Well, I was going to release them all at once, but then that other stuff happened and I was like, now's the time.
Now's the time to release.
That was kind of a bad idea in retrospect.
You mean holding on to it?
Yeah, it was.
I'm sure when you first came up with the idea, it sounded cool.
I didn't think it would be like a year.
And it probably would have been cool if you didn't take as long on the game.
Yep.
True.
But I did.
So if nothing had happened on that front, I would be saying, yeah, I'm about to release the game and the comic and that video.
But you know, game development takes a very long time, so I'm not really surprised that it took you so long to put it together.
You know, well, the game, the little game that I made for the champion, it took me less than a month to make that.
And so I thought this game would be maybe a few months, but it ended up ballooning out.
A lot of people don't know how much hard work it is to develop a game, even if it's small.
Because you kind of, like if you go back and you look at some of those old games on Genesis and the Super Nintendo, you know, like Mega Man X, for example.
A game like that, it's only like around two hours long, but it took the development team like maybe a year or more to make it.
Yeah.
You know, and it's, they had to do a lot of testing and polishing and bug fixing.
They were pretty serious about bug fixing back in those days because there were no patches.
Yeah.
The, the, uh, yeah, it just, I didn't expect it to be quite, I knew it would be a big undertaking, it was bigger than I expected.
Oh well. But the, the, so what I'm saying is I feel a little stupid, a little bad about holding onto the game when it's done.
And I'm like, this is kind of like what I did with the lecture.
Like, am I, should I just release the game?
But like, I don't think so because the game is not something that anyone like knows about or is expecting outside of like the small circle of people that maybe follow me.
Uh, I don't think it's not like something that has like a broader, much of a broader like appeal.
I think kind of whenever, whenever the game comes out will be basically the same.
Like there won't, there's no real difference in releasing it like this year versus last year versus next year, like whatever.
I guess there's the other weird thing about all of this is that you're, you're working really hard on something that has like very limited outside appeal.
It, I, I, to, to finish my last thought, I just, yeah, I hate holding onto it, but I don't think it will suffer very much from being released later where like, the, the, the, uh,
I mean, it's so, it's so tight in it, the, the, the lecture is kind of its own thing.
It's not really part of the same thing.
It's related, but like the, the game and the comic are based, are literally one in the same.
So I feel like, okay, it's okay to, it's okay to hang onto this for another month or whatever.
As long as you don't take another year.
I am hoping, I hope that the game is, is cool and good enough that maybe it will make a little bit of a splash.
Maybe it will get seen around a little bit.
Maybe, maybe indie game fans in some circles might talk about it a little.
Maybe it'll get seen.
I hope, I kind of hope that like some new people maybe just find it because it's a game and they like games and maybe some people pass it around and comment on it a little bit.
Uh, that would be cool.
I would kind of like that the most, actually, more than like, you know, fucking God, fucking Sonichu fans, Chris Chan fans.
I hate those people.
I don't, I don't want them to play the game.
Fuck, fuck them.
Kind of the worst.
Yeah.
It would be nice if it has like a wider appeal because you did work very hard on it.
It's, um, I mean, I don't know.
I guess I don't know that much about like the indie game scene, but you know, I made it to be, I made it to be a game that's fun and challenging.
And so I hope that it appeals to gamers.
You know, I hope it's a good game that stands on its own as a game and people appreciate it in that way.
That's my hope for it.
If it does appeal to other people, it might get them interested in all the other stuff connected to it.
May, that's, that's what I, that would be what I would most hope for would be my optimal.
You know, maybe somebody will play it and then be like, I wonder what all this stuff is about, you know, and look up the comic or whatever.
That's what I hope.
That's what I really.
It could be like a marketing tool.
It's a, it's a thing that I made and I hope it gets seen and it ties into some other stuff I made.
So maybe if it gets seen, it would get that stuff a little more seen.
Kind of, it kind of reminds me of how like back in the day, they used to have those cartoons to market the toys.
You know, I think that was the case for transformers.
Hmm.
So this, you're saying this is the new transformers?
Yeah, basically.
Hmm.
Yeah, it's, it's very similar.
It's very similar to transformers.
It's just there to sell the toys.
I mean, I mean, what would you do if Hasbro came to you and said, Hey, we want to buy the rights revenge.
More like they would cease and desist it.
Because it's an OC.
They can't do anything.
Hmm.
It's just a parody.
All right.
Well, I would say I would take their money.
But it's not a very interesting answer, but expected.
What else?
Why?
What would you do?
No, I would sell it as well.
Yeah, of course.
It's funny to imagine like toy, like little toy phantoms revenge or like Hasbro-ified family friendly versions.
You have to imagine what happens after you sell the rights.
What happens after I sell the rights is I just have some money.
I don't know.
If they, what would they do?
They would, okay, in this ridiculous scenario, they come to me.
They're like, wow, we love your game.
We're going to make, we're going to make our own, we're going to remake Phantom Horn on the, on the switch.
We're going to, we're going to make a whole series of like comic books about him.
We're going to have a whole, it's going to be tied into like the G5.
We're, we're going to, we're going to make some changes though.
We're going to make some changes with the character.
I would be like, sure, whatever.
It would, it just wouldn't matter.
Will they get the rights to TBAP?
Will they get 50% of the rights?
It just wouldn't matter that much to me because like, they could do all that if they want to.
Honestly, like it wouldn't, even if like they did that, it wouldn't, it wouldn't change anything.
It wouldn't like stuff that, it wouldn't change what I think about the character.
Like just none of that would be canon in my mind.
Like it just, there would be a, there would be a line between like the stuff that I made,
like the stuff, the story that I wrote about this character and all that shit.
And like, and, and then like I sold it and then they did some stuff with it.
I'd be like, whatever, they can do whatever they want.
You should, my story is, my story is still my story.
This is my story.
And you're not part of it.
You know, you should just.
God, if they, if they wanted to put me in charge of like, I mean, yeah, I would definitely, yeah,
I would definitely take a job like that.
No question.
Yeah.
Okay.
In that case, if I'm like on the project, I'm like working on it, then yeah, sure.
Well, I take, I take that job.
And I, and I, I'll have, I'll have the project decision to take.
Yeah, it is easy.
Get your OC and like the, but the backing and funding of like a large studio company to like make stuff.
Of course.
If I get to say what I want.
You sold out Ben.
You used to be indie.
Just, just imagine if that happened to Christian was a sonic shoe.
People were saying, someone was saying in the comments of the last video that I guess Christian was going to be on smiling friends.
Oh yeah, I saw that.
Christian was, was, was going to be the voice.
I have, I still have not seen smiling friends with Christian was going to be the voice of the puddle.
Yes.
I guess.
I saw this clip.
Too expensive.
It was, I don't know, they didn't get into like why that it's expensive, but they said something like,
you can't just get one person to do one line and one thing.
You can have one and they got like a chills the number 15.
Yeah.
They got that guy.
But like, if you want Christian to voice characters, they need to be in multiple episodes.
I'm, I don't know why that costs more to have them only in one voice clip.
Something must be like, I don't know.
Was that actually true?
Some sort of workers thing.
Well, that's what Zach said.
And there was a clip he was talking about why they couldn't do it.
So that the show's budget, the show's budget wouldn't allow for it.
And they didn't want to have Christian on multiple episodes because it would have been a nightmare to get her to do things.
Yeah.
I guess it's kind of like trying to get a dog to do something.
I mean, yeah, she would, it would be incredibly.
Wait, is that really the reason just like they were like, it would be hard to work with her?
No, no, no.
Well, it's more complex than they explained.
But the gist of it is, is that the budgetary reasons mean they couldn't really do that.
And then later, like, I don't know.
So it's not that she's expensive is just that having her on the show.
No, it's not that Christian has like a high price tag.
It's that the way that they do like a hiring people would have made it more expensive beyond the budgetary thing.
I guess because you've got to compensate them for using their voice in a small part rather than like a larger part.
I don't really get it.
I have no idea why that's the thing.
You can't just use them for free like, you know, somebody else might.
Well, you'd have to pay them something.
But I don't know why it would be more expensive for just a bit part like one line.
You can't just have a crew of people work for you for free.
It's just like the thing we were saying before.
Yeah, has absolutely no relation to anything that we've discussed previously.
What, smiling friends?
No, I just made a comment about, don't worry about it.
Yeah, don't worry about it, Ben.
What's going on?
Anyway, speaking of working hard, I've been working hard on my secret project, I think.
That damn thing.
So there's two secret projects.
I was saying, you've been saying that yours is getting close to being ready.
And it's, and I'm like, I was expecting mine to be done.
Shit.
Oh, no.
I was sure it was going to be done this month.
It's still, I still might be done this.
I think I can still do it this month.
I don't see why not.
But if you, depending on if it's like this week or next week or the week after, you might beat me.
I might beat you.
I can't say for any certainty.
But like last year, I was hoping that I could wrap that up.
And it turns out no.
Okay.
So it became more clear that it would take a few moments, but it's been a few moments.
And we've got, well, it's got closer.
I'm very excited to be able to like say it's coming out and all that.
But because I've been working so hard on that, I've sort of fallen behind on like fulfilling Lord of Ghost Kickstarter things.
Mailing stuff is expensive and confusing and scary.
And I actually got like, I sent a few of them out and I got like somebody telling me that there was a gash in the, the envelope.
And the red man comic had fallen out.
Everyone's supposed to get a red man comic.
They only got the Lord of Ghosts.
Did they like, they cut the envelope open?
I don't know why it came with a gash.
I'm assuming customs cut it open to look inside because customs is customs.
Customs is customs.
Customs is customs for sure.
And they didn't seal it up or something because I kind of imagined they'd be delicate.
It's a postal service.
They don't give a shit.
Yeah, that's the issue.
It's not first class.
You're located in the UK and I think the majority of the fans are in the US, I would assume.
It's, it's weird.
It's not like, I guess it's a majority coming from one country, but like there's quite a lot coming from other countries.
Yeah.
There's a, it's like 60, 40 US and other.
So shipping to other countries is pretty expensive, I'd imagine.
It's expensive.
I've been like looking at like prices and been like, is it cheaper to go through this?
Which has tracking and, but I don't know like how reliable it is or is it cheaper to go through this?
Which is probably more reliable, but doesn't have tracking unless you pay a lot more.
I'm like, how important is tracking?
If the parcel arrives with a, with a fucking hole in it and something's fallen out.
I don't want that to happen more than once.
So I'm like, I'm not sure really what to do with all that stuff.
That's why whenever I saw stuff on eBay, I just sell it to the US locally.
I hate having to deal with shipping stuff overseas.
Yeah.
I mean, I think part of the reason it's stressful was because I didn't know the, the cost of sending all these things would, would be so high.
Um, because of the weight of the comics.
I, I tried not to have like the comics have too thick of paper to keep down the weight,
but even at like a normal, like, oh, this is a normal page and it's not too thick and it's not like flimsy thin.
Um, it still weighs quite a bit and it bumps the price up.
Yeah, paper is a lot heavier than you'd expect.
I have a, I have a bunch of old issues of Nintendo, Nintendo Power Magazine stacked on top of each other.
And one time I tried lifting it and it was so heavy.
I couldn't lift all of them at the same time.
You know, that was, I was back before I worked out.
Now I can lift them just fine, but you know, they are pretty heavy.
One little finger.
Oh, I just haven't worked out in over a month now.
Oh, almost we're going on two months.
I'm getting, I'm nearing the two month barrier.
So I've, I've been losing weight though.
I've been losing weight.
So that's cool.
That's good.
So I'm doing something.
Yeah.
But have you been losing a muscle weight or fat weight?
I could, I think I'm losing fat weight.
I don't think I'm looking a little skinnier.
I'm probably, I mean, I'm probably losing muscle too because I'm not working out.
So that's bad.
I could stand to lose a little more.
You know, not all weight is bad.
It depends on the quality of the weight.
Yeah.
The weight is in the boobies.
That's great.
Nah, get it all out of here.
Cut it all out.
Scoop it out of me and dump it in the trash.
Speaking of boobs.
Hey, you seen February?
February?
I've seen a little bit.
Actually, I do have something.
I've seen a little.
Something that relates.
They're here and there.
And it relates to that.
No, I just started saying my thing.
Well, I guess the only thing is to say, go check out my tweets.
I'm posting daily boob art on big girl squish.
All right.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Pretty good.
I've been, I've been, I've been seeing a little bit.
I feel like, I feel like I need, I need to like actually try to improve my, my skills.
It's, it's one thing to like keep drawing every day and get a habit of it.
But it's another thing to like make the drawings count for more.
You know, I want it to be both a funny thing, a habit building thing and a skill improving
thing.
But a lot of the time I get to the end of the day, work it on secret project.
And I'm tired.
And I'm like, fuck, I'll just draw something.
There we go.
Put it up.
And sometimes it's great that a lot of the time it's just sort of a little doodle, not
to it.
Yeah, it's hard to like do a bunch of different things at the same time because you, even
if you have the time to do it all, you kind of spend all your energy working on one thing
and then you're exhausted to, you're too exhausted to work on something else.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to the secret project being done and I can focus on sending a lot
of ghost things and then don't know what I'll do with my time.
But I think the lot of ghosts is going to take a while.
I still got all those doodles to do, still got all the lot of ghosts, plush costumes
to make, which shouldn't take too long.
I just need to cut out the bits of fabric.
So on the fucking funny buttons on the, on as the eye holes.
Yeah, those, those bushy things look pretty cool.
And I noticed you changed, you changed the design.
Did I change the design?
Well, yeah, I mean, he doesn't have buttons in the comic.
Well, no, it's just like a, I feel like if I tried to cut holes in a little sheet and
then put like a black bit of fabric behind them or leave them open, that's a whole lot
more like stuff.
I thought, I assumed I thought it was just like drawn on with like a Sharpie.
Well, I didn't want to go that.
That would have looked terrible.
Yeah.
But like, isn't that like the, the point that like it kind of looks terrible?
I suppose, but like, there's a part of me that wants it to like at least be durable.
And, and like, I don't know if like Sharpie will wash off if you try to scrub it or if
it gets dirty or whatever.
Oh, I mean, I feel like a little, a little so Sharpie would probably be Sharpie would
be a bad choice for that.
Yeah.
I could probably find something, but like, where when in real life, when fabric is like
ruffled and something's drawn on it, it completely distorts it to the point where it
doesn't look like anything.
So just like a, like a black smear, I feel like a button is cuter and does the same job.
And I have some buttons.
So it's fine.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I'm satisfied.
Well, I do have something that's kind of titillating, I don't know, it's kind of related.
It's kind of weird.
Yeah.
I've seen this, if you're like into anime stuff, I know this might have a reputation.
I linked, it's called a Keiko Kamin.
I've not seen this.
You know, you can read the Wikipedia entry on it.
It's kind of, it's kind of weird.
Kind of weird.
Maybe it's supposed to be funny.
I don't know.
Maybe somebody, some people find it funny.
It's a weird Japanese thing.
Have any of you ever seen it before?
I'm reading about it.
Teachers are something, something, misadventures of a student named Mayumi Takahashi who attends
a boarding school.
The teachers are constantly looking for ways to torture or humiliate the students and from
this teachers derive sexual satisfaction.
And then there's a superhero involved, I guess to kill the teachers.
Yeah.
It's, it's kind of weird.
I encountered it recently and it's like a hero, a female hero that doesn't wear any
clothing for some reason.
It's pretty, pretty interesting.
Oh, I thought she was wearing a white jumpsuit.
Oh, she's naked.
Yeah.
That's her costume.
You know, I don't know.
I don't know who came up with this, but it's pretty, pretty weird.
And they made a surprisingly large amount of like media out of this.
She's got, she's got nunchucks.
Did she always use nunchucks?
Is that like her signature weapon?
I don't know.
I haven't really watched this because, or read it because there's like a, I think there's
a comic book series and there's, maybe there's an anime and there's, I think even a live
action show.
So I saw a clip of the live action show, but I haven't seen any of the other stuff.
It doesn't strike me as a work of quality, but it's definitely interesting or funny in
an ironic way.
I'm reading the plot.
Okay.
First year student, Mayumi Takashi, attends a junior high school called Sparta Academy
where the penalty for any student, usually girls, making the slightest mistake is being
sexually humiliated by the perverted, corrupt and misogynistic teachers running the school,
the principal being a demonic jester like villain named toenail of Satan.
However, before the teachers can take their sexual advantages too far, Keiko Kamen steps
in and delivers a sound beating to the teachers and usually performs a finishing attack by
jumping into the air and landing crutch first onto her opponent's face.
Yeah, that's some, you know, Yosuke from Yu-yu Hakushoi has the spirit ray gun thing.
And I guess that's what, you know, this Keiko Kamen has, you know, her own special move.
You can call it that.
It's pretty special.
This entire thing is pretty special.
If you say so, man.
It's just a really weird.
Is it good?
But is it good?
No, I don't think so.
It's pretty terrible.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
It's just, it's just kind of amusing from like an ironic perspective.
You know, I saw, I saw somebody review this on like some bad movie review blog.
So, I just thought it was so fascinating that something like this actually exists.
You know, that's, that's the thing about like anime and, and all the, all this Japanese
media is that it's like almost every idea that can exist does exist.
You know, no matter, no matter how horrible it is.
Yeah, I mean, there's nothing, there's nothing new under the sun.
Every idea has been done before.
This doesn't seem that strange for Japanese, like anime weirdness, like all this perverts.
And there's a girl who beats them up, you know, funny costume or, you know, lack of
costume.
Says a lot, says a lot, says a lot about society.
Yeah.
Well, it says a lot about us.
I guess we brought this in or that I brought it in.
It's you.
This is all you.
No, it's, it's your guys is fucked.
This is your, your weird show.
I guess we, we invited you.
So I guess it's sort of our fault by extension.
You're, you're corrupting the Gamer's Tavern brand.
Just like that one.
Yes.
That one.
So long ago.
Yes.
We've turned you evil and edgy.
We've turned you into an anime knower.
You know about anime now.
That is pretty unforgivable.
Yeah.
Actually, I thought about trying to do some anime content, but it doesn't seem very
appropriate for, you know, Gamer's Tavern.
For Gamer's.
Yeah.
I can't think of anything that I, anything less, that I'd less expect a Gamer to like
than anime.
Yeah.
That's, that's a good point.
Well, just got to do an anime game.
You got to make a video about an anime game and that'll bridge the gap.
You got to do that as like your, your, your dues, pay your dues.
You got to make a separate channel called the anime algorithm and then, and put all
of the, the anime stuff in there.
Yeah.
That's probably, that's a good idea.
And then I can collaborate with, you know, famous anime YouTubers like Trixie the Golden
Witch.
I thought it was really funny.
You know who replied to that, the tweet that I made about her, her terrible ratio was Shade,
the younger Collins.
Oh yeah.
I saw that.
Shade, I was, I was, I was surprised.
He replied just to say that like, yeah, can't, can't ride those coattails anymore.
Yeah.
I'm didn't, didn't work before, but now I can't even try.
I think that's what he said.
And I was like, wow.
I mean, true.
I mean, it's just true what you're saying.
I'm pretty surprised that that was his attitude about it.
I, I guess it doesn't really, I guess it doesn't surprise me.
I mean, it, it's a fair attitude.
I guess I, you know, I guess it's like his, his mom, Trixie's mom and Shade's mom unfriended
me on Twitter, unfollowed me on Twitter.
Oh really?
That's pretty sad.
Yeah.
We were, we were Twitter followers.
We were, we were Mewchies because we were both Bernie supporters and Trixie, I guess,
I think this was when Trixie had moved back in with her mom.
And I got to assume that Trixie said, nah, Ben's mean, Ben's mean to me.
And she said, oh, well, I'm going to unfollow, I'm going to unfollow him on Twitter then.
Like, I won't follow such a bully.
And I assume that's how it went.
Yeah, I'm sure that's how I played out.
So it's exactly how, how else.
So she unfollowed me.
So I guess I had just kind of assumed that by making an enemy of Trixie, I was making
an enemy of her whole family, but maybe not.
There was actually, there was a video that Victor did a while back, or kind of recently,
I think, where Trixie was sort of in it towards the end on the Vic and Hope channel.
Yeah.
And she just kind of pops in towards the end of one of their, like, I think they were
playing Bloodborne or something like that.
It's like a, you know, that's really weird.
It's funny.
I didn't hear about that.
That's interesting.
I guess it doesn't shock me too much because I do know, I did know that they're living
in Virginia again.
So I guess they could do that.
So I just brought it up because I figured this means that, you know, Vic and Hope, you
and Trixie are on good terms, I would have imagined.
I would never imagine, I would be shocked to hear that like Vic was not on good terms
because Trixie has spent like her entire life like bullying him and he has just been fine
with it.
You could see it in the, you could see it in the, in the documentary, Trixie like snaps
at Vic several times for no reason at all.
She just like snaps at him and treats him like, like, like shit.
I wasn't, I wasn't aware of that.
I guess I should watch, watch that, that footage.
There's one or two moments in the documentary that left me.
It's like, why, why are you, why are you talking to him like that?
Yeah.
I mean, it's not, I mean, it's not all the time, obviously.
It's just, it's just sometimes it would take, I feel like it would take a lot.
to make Vic be like upset.
Well, I wonder what his opinion is on the whole Yegg studio thing, because he doesn't
mention it in that video at all.
And they don't talk about it.
I would, I would imagine that he takes the common sense approach, which is, well, my
sibling had a pretty lucrative career and that's pretty much down the drain now.
Same one, same one, Shade took, and also just the factual truth.
Well, then I wonder if Shade is going to be cut out of the family or something.
I very much doubt it's so serious.
Yeah, Shade can do what they like.
Shade can do whatever they like.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, what are we talking about?
Shall we get to voicemails?
Oh, God, fuck, I forgot about voicemails.
Did you forgot about voicemails?
Hang on, I get, I get a pee.
I will go to the, I'm going to go to the bathroom and when I get back, we will
hope there's not too many.
Now is a, now is a good time to do our routine negative Ben St.
talk.
Nah, I think that joke's played out.
Yeah.
Now it's for real.
It's no longer a joke.
Yeah, exactly.
We've got to.
I hate Ben St.
Gotta get all the negativity.
So mean.
He's real, he's real mean on Twitter, you know, he has a big, mean, mean issue on
Twitter, big, big, mean streak.
He's a beast on the internet.
He's a ravenous beast and he'll bite you and suck all your blood out and he'll
laugh about it.
No empathy or, and that's not untrue.
And he would, he would agree.
No empathy or compassion.
Pure logic.
Light yagami.
If he had a death note, he'd use it on you.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, I don't know what I did.
We just use it to make more money, you know, because less people on the show
would mean more money going to him.
Now, if I think of the draw, think of the give and take draw, I'm a lucrative
brand.
Yeah, that's true.
If it was just him, probably viewership would sink to an all-time low.
Would sink to zero.
Everyone's here for me.
Yeah, that's a good point, you know.
99.9% are Gibb fans.
That's the, that's the last holdout of the PCP fan base.
Okay, speakpipe.com.
We're just saying lots of really great things about you.
You're the, you're the best.
Yes.
Well, we should change.
We should call you a best saint from now on.
I think so as well.
Shit.
Fuck, what's the password?
123 PCP, you remember?
Yes.
Thank you.
All right, sorry.
I'm logged out of everything.
I got to, what's the...
Just say the password to your bank account on the recording.
Oh, got it.
Oh, there's too many.
Okay, it's not, it's not that bad.
Only an hour, you think?
I, let's try and get through it in less than an hour.
I got, I got, I got comics to draw.
What?
Why is it taking you so long to download?
Two second long, okay, whatever.
All right, the first one here is called, is, is called, it's another voicemail.
Wait, sorry, I skipped one.
I skipped one.
Actually, the first voicemail is this image here.
I will post it.
Was this my one?
I think they're criticizing your, your, your Minesweeper play.
Notable only because Gib died at one hour by flagging all of the spaces in green
and then clicking one of the magenta spaces.
This is from, this is from the, is it the, is it the Minesweeper bonus episode
or the Minesweeper Picross bonus episode?
Yeah, yeah, it must have been.
I don't think we did another one of those.
No, we only did one, but it was, it was combined.
It was both, both games.
I must have, I must have missed that because I was rushing to try and completely own you.
I can't, I can't imagine playing Minesweeper for over an hour.
That's crazy.
I came to appreciate that it is actually, I came to appreciate more of the strategy involved in it.
Once there's a strategy, once you understand that it can be solved and it's not just like good luck.
It's not, it's not just clicking around.
Yeah.
Then, then it becomes like, you know, with every click, more information.
It's like a tiny little extra puzzle every time.
Yeah, I'm pretty horrible at Minesweeper.
It's very engaging.
I can't last even a few minutes.
You know, I'm pretty bad at anything involving Mines, you know, Minecraft, Minesweeper.
Any other Mines related games?
Uh, Mastermind.
Mastermind's great.
Very similar to Whirtle, as I think I said previously.
I've been killing Whirtle, by the way.
I've been playing on hard mode and I've been getting into like threes.
I've been getting threes and threes.
Oh, I've always played for as it sucks.
I've gotten a bunch of threes lately and I feel I'm on top of the world.
I feel like quite a lot of my forums could have easily been threes if I just so happened to choose a different letter.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Which is, I had most of the word there, but oh, it's another word ending in ight.
ight?
Okay, the next voicemail is this one that I posted here.
It's called is another voicemail from DoidGazer.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi, it's world-renowned webcomic artist DoidGazer again.
And I'm just calling in to let everyone know that I am opening up tryouts to be my new best friend.
Requirements are you must be less successful than me.
You must be able to smoke weed at a similar rate as I, which is a lot.
We smoke a lot of weed.
Also, you have to enjoy birds cooking and yeah.
So less successful.
Be my friend.
So yeah, apply on my Twitter at DoidGazer.
Thanks.
Head over.
We should all head over to DoidGazer on Twitter.
I'm not a big DoidGazers fan personally, so how do you recommend somebody be DoidGazer's friend?
I do recommend anyone that has not seen it.
Check out DoidGazer's comic about, I'm in it.
They made a little comic about, you know, about Yig.
The comic is real.
I thought that was a joke.
No, they did draw a little comic.
I'll check that out.
Just Yig things.
I retweeted it.
Yeah, check them out.
Okay, next one is a Vokeroo.
I guess it doesn't have a title.
Three, two, one, go.
My conclusions that I would draw is, I hate Big Mac.
I hate cross-tresses.
I hate transchangers.
I hate transsexuals.
I hate trans.
Everybody, everybody sucks.
Fuck you all.
Yeah, that's agreed.
Absolutely.
Back in the base era of the PCP.
What happens?
That was a T-Bat episode that me and Jesse were on, I think.
Remember that?
We were talking about Big Mac, an episode where he dresses up in a dress.
Was that before or after the PCP existed?
That was after, I think.
I don't really remember.
Wait, that was on T-Bat?
Yeah.
It must have been a T-Bat podcast, one of the later ones.
Yeah, one of the later ones.
I forget about those.
I think my angle, it made for a bit of a laugh.
But I think in terms of analyzing the episode, I didn't know what I was talking about.
I remember you having a better take on the episode itself.
What about it?
I don't remember at all.
I just remember being like, yeah, I don't know what I'm doing here.
I'm just talking about horse.
I also don't.
God, I don't fucking remember.
I remember he puts on the dress to impersonate someone
or to get into the women's bathroom so that he can molest people.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't remember anything, but I definitely agree that my take was better than yours
because I'm really smart.
I'm positive that's true.
Okay, next one is further voice grail reparations.
Three, two, one, go.
For their contribution to sweet, freakin' memes,
y'all should put doigazers in the voice grail.
Also that Ben St. Biocomics was pretty great.
I think doigazers deserves voice grail at this point.
Yeah, I agree with that.
You haven't done that yet?
No.
They made a whole album.
They did.
I'll give it to you.
Yeah, voice grail.
Voice grail for doigazers.
Reparations complete.
Equality achieved.
Next one is flipper.
Three, two, one, go.
What's that flipper?
And Saint?
He can deadlift five times his own body weight?
That's true.
Oh my god.
That's absolutely true.
Why is flipper telling him this?
And why is flipper screaming like a horde of girls?
It's very exciting, you know.
It's nothing.
Five times a body weight?
You're just as strong as an ant.
Easily.
Stronger even.
Okay, I'm trying to load this next one, this next image.
It's a whole image album.
Best rival reason.
Yeah, this image, this Imgur album.
It's the same thing twice.
Oh, why is it the same?
Yeah, okay.
Best rival reason anime, Sasuke and Naruto, Goku and Vegeta,
Guts and Griffith, Ben Saint and the Golden Witch.
It's just true.
Yeah, that's my favorite one.
Nothing more.
The Golden Witch.
My favorite rivalry of all time.
I would say it's better than whatever stupid Japanese cartoon
other people might nominate.
Alright, next voicemail is called Voicing My Opinion,
Tee Hee, 3, 2, 1, go.
Local feminization is cool and all,
but doing it requires you to confront and deeply think about
the physicality of all the muscles in your throat.
And if there's one thing I hate doing,
it's remembering that I am in fact a physical object
that exists in the real world and as such can be destroyed.
Each fold of muscle or vein of blood is just a vulnerability
that will eventually cease to function and rot away.
I don't understand how anyone can watch a Transvoice Lessons video
without feeling like their vocal tract is full of existential horrors.
That's definitely something.
That's definitely something I feel a little bit.
I don't feel like body horror, but I do feel like,
if only I wasn't born, then it wouldn't be a problem.
Things were so much simpler.
Things were so much simpler back in the pre-existence era.
Okay, next one is
whether it be a no-nate episode or a solo Vencast.
There it is. 3, 2, 1, go.
Aw, shit. This is not going to be on episode 300.
I'm fucking with you.
Anyways, do all you PCP heads out there.
The best episodes and moments of the podcast
come from the topic of friendship is magic.
No buts, all fans.
I would say that's largely true.
Wait, what do you say the best episodes of the PCP come from?
Or come from conversations about MLP.
I mean, we're all pretty well-versed on the subject.
I think the last big one was like the My Little Pony movie,
like the Disney-looking one.
Oh, sure.
I thought the best episode of the PCP was the yellow one.
I remember if that episode had, like, good stuff in it,
aside from the one, like, explosion.
I understand why people were into that one.
I get it.
I still have to go back and listen to a lot of those old episodes
that everybody is clamoring to say are the best.
People just go wild.
People go wild for that yellow episode.
Next.
What?
Hold on.
Why won't it...
What?
Okay.
Oh, Jesus.
All right.
This next voicemail is six minutes long,
and it's a vocaroo link.
I think you missed one.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry.
Okay.
158 is called Don't Know How to Feel.
Guess I'll Just Cringe.
Three, two, one, go.
Months and months ago, before the falling out with Trixie
and everything, I left a drunken, fairly cringe voicemail
taking some easy pot shots at Nate Bestman,
making fun of him for being a dork-ass nerd
who doesn't understand fuck about shit.
And I was embarrassed, although it was funny
how it triggered Trixie on the podcast.
And I thought it was past me.
But then, low and behold, episode 298.
Oblivion Fall sampled that random-ass voicemail
as a lead-in to a beat.
And while I am honored to have been sampled,
I don't understand.
Oblivion Fall, you're not on this episode probably,
but I know you're listening and I know you're in the comments.
Please explain why does one of my moments of cringe
have to be prolonged and live for even a second longer
than it had to in the consciousness?
I don't know, man. I don't know how to feel.
It makes me feel weird.
Wasn't that voicemail one?
Didn't Trixie get mad that, like,
I don't know, some shit about, like,
you should say it to Nate's face?
Oh, Trixie was like, don't...
Nate's not here to defend himself or something like that?
Where did she say this, exactly?
No.
I don't know. He mentions that Trixie got triggered
by this voicemail that this person left criticizing Nate.
And I'm trying to remember which voicemail it was.
I don't remember.
Where did she, like, voice or distaste for this voicemail?
She was on the episode.
So you mean this is on an old episode of the PCP?
It must have been...
It must have been, like, her last appearance ever or something.
This person says months and months ago.
That must have been, like, a year or more ago.
Maybe, I don't even remember.
They're just quite a while ago.
Yeah.
Okay, whatever.
Anyway, this next one is fucking...
This next one is six minutes long,
but let's give it a shot.
Uh, what does that go...
What do I have to do here?
You can just open the Vocaroo link
and just play it in the browser if you want to not download it.
You got it?
Yeah, I have it.
Okay.
Alright, let's see.
Three, two, one, go.
The show's dark now.
Everybody cries.
No more funny times for a kind, funny man.
It's dark and depressing, but that's what makes it good.
It's Kyle and Funny Man
in space.
Alright, calm down.
Don't shit yourself.
Don't fucking cry.
Don't slobber all over your keyboard
and fucking circuit yourself into oblivion and die.
Okay, we're still in the dark arc, alright?
But this episode is a special musical episode,
so you might enjoy that.
Just watch the episode, alright?
It's like five minutes long, longer, maybe six.
Who knows?
Listen carefully and get emotionally invested now.
Huh, sigh.
Oh, man.
I came to this weird, freaking wacky jungle planet
to go on a crazy adventure,
but instead I'm sad and confused about my place in life.
Same.
And this is all because of last week,
I had a huge falling out with Funny Man,
and he went to have his solo episode where he goes to therapy.
It's a deep psychoanalysis episode,
and this is my episode where I go into the woods and be sad,
and that's a recap of the storyline.
So, yeah, I don't know what to do, man.
I'm just feeling sad, and I guess I'll self-reflect
through song?
I guess that's something I would do.
I can hear the music.
I can hear the backing track.
I remember when we first met.
Funny Man broke into my ship.
I thought he was a space pirate.
Did he come to rob me blind?
Oh, then we went on crazy adventures,
and everybody loved it.
We had fans, but now we hate each other.
It makes me so sad.
It makes me want to shit.
How can you just leave me standing
alone in a world that's so cold?
Maybe I'm just too demanding.
Maybe I'm just like my father too bold.
Maybe you're just like my mother.
She's never satisfied.
Why do we scream at each other?
This is what it sounds like when Kyle cries.
Oh, man, I'm so fucking sad.
Wait, what is that?
A spaceship landing on this planet?
This remote-ass planet?
What's going on here?
Hello, Kyle.
Mr. Funny Man?
You're here?
But...
Yes, I had my epic episode where I did psychoanalysis,
and I worked through all my issues, and now I'm here.
Back with you, because I realized what was important was
you, Kyle, being with you, having fun, going on adventures.
That is what Kyle and Funny Man is all about.
None of this deep stuff.
It's all about funny, referential jokes to things,
especially PCP memes, and that's what's so important around here.
We need to have more funny, referential memes, Kyle.
Oh, my God, Kyle, I totally agree.
While you were gone, I had this episode where I was stuck in the forest
on this planet, and I was going crazy,
and I did like an epic psychoanalyze as well,
and I did like a thing where I sang a song, because it's a musical episode,
and I sang a song, and I compared myself to my father,
and yourself to my mother.
It's kind of fucking weird, Kyle.
It's kind of weird.
I think a psychologist had a field day with that one,
but at least we're back together, finally.
Yes, finally, the iconic pairing, Kyle and Funny Man.
We're back together, and we're going on new, sweet, fucking cool adventures,
and it's going to be the best.
Oh, my God, this is so good.
And we went through our entire emotional arc in just like three or four episodes,
so we still have like 17 episodes left of fucking sweet, juicy-ass content.
Oh, my God, the future's looking bright.
Well, Kyle, since you did say this was the musical episode,
how about we end this episode off with a sweet musical performance?
Oh, my God, Funny Man, you're so on the money, so correct,
and I think I got the exact right song.
Oh, yes, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Yes, it's a song the people have been clamoring for.
We haven't even heard it in like two episodes,
and we're finally going to bring it back.
Let's go, yeah.
Oh, say can you feel safe by the dawn's early light?
That was very heartwarming and touching performance.
It took me through the whole range of human emotion.
It started out in the depths,
and then it swelled to triumphant heights in its darkest hour.
I especially like the use of the music they use
for when somebody's about to be voted off of a competition on television,
and then they cry about it, and like, I tried my best.
That was my favorite part, too.
Pretty good.
I don't know.
Kyle and Funny Man for Voice Grail?
Are they already Voice Grail?
I don't remember, actually.
Whatever.
Well, fuck them.
If they're not, no, chuck them in there.
Chuck them all in there.
Ever in it.
Well, that was a, what more can I add?
What can I add to the experience that was that voicemail?
Honestly, kind of justify that slide.
I can't believe it.
Six-minute voicemail?
Didn't even mind.
Wasn't even bored.
Crazy.
Good shit.
Next voicemail is, it's a, this one is called
Red Man Comic Impression?
Three, two, one, go.
Here is my review of Rayman 2.
Wow!
Rayman!
What the heck?
Nine out of ten?
Based!
I remember that.
The little Red Man Comic I did.
I don't remember that.
It sounded just like I imagined he would sound.
He reveals, reviews Rayman 2.
Bangs, pups and pangs together.
That's totally forgot, totally forgot about that one.
You'll find it in the Red Man Comic once I send you.
I can't wait!
I can't wait for my copy!
I remember telling you that one of my favorite things you did was a Red Man Comic.
So I'm quite pleased to see that you're turning that into a physical item.
Yeah.
I can't wait to have mine all snug in my clutch to my bosom.
Next one is a image.
My Norwegian aunt posted this on Instagram.
I don't think she knows what Family Guy or Final Fantasy 7 is.
What does it mean?
Peter, I told you you have to stop.
You must stop doing push-ups.
One like.
This reminds me of like, did you guys see, we probably know when the Final Fantasy 7
like porn thing was played on the Italian...
Oh, I heard about that.
The Italian Senate, Tifa.
I heard about that.
That's great.
This, if you didn't know who Cloud or Peter was, I would see this and I would just think
that it was like a fit guy being like, you did too many push-ups, bro, to a fat guy.
If you didn't know who Cloud was, you'd probably be like, what the heck is he wearing?
That's a really weird get-up.
Yeah.
I think you'd go to the hair first.
That's the more unusual part.
I just don't...
I don't see what would be funny about this if you didn't know.
She must know...
They must have Family Guy in Norway.
How could she not know who Peter Griffin was?
I would imagine she at least knows Family Guy.
I mean, if I take...
I guess I'll take this guy's word.
I'd be surprised if she didn't know who Peter Griffin was.
And if you don't know who these people, either of these people are, what's the joke?
I don't get it.
Yeah, I can't explain it to you.
My dude, I really can't.
We know at the very least that Ben will never have this problem.
He can never do too many push-ups.
I can push...
I can do push-ups ten times my body weight.
Shit.
The next one is called...
Shit, where did I put it?
I think it's this one's 62.
Sorry, I'm looking for it.
Alright, 62.
Here we go.
One, go.
Hey, Gib, have you read the manga versions of the Ace One Piece novels?
It came out a few months ago, and it's...
The art's done by a Boichi who does the art for Doctor Stone.
It looks really, really good.
So if you haven't checked it out...
I have seen those. There's like a...
Firefist, Ace, Adventure, bit, and...
Manga chapters.
I don't know how much there is.
I've seen a few of them. They look very good, yes.
They sort of depict the events that are not shown fully in One Piece itself.
It's like a side story.
So they were mangas made about...
Manga chapters. I don't know about full-blown...
Maybe like two or three big chapters.
Did this guy say that they were based on novels?
Did I miss you?
No, it's just part of...
Like when Ace was on Whitebeard's crew.
Or like how he became to be on Whitebeard's crew.
And stuff relating to Blackbeard and...
Fucking some other stuff.
So that's Canon?
Technically, I think yes.
I don't know if all the characters would be considered Canon.
I don't know if Oda invented them or not.
But yeah, I have seen them. They look pretty good.
Well, that's pretty cool.
Okay, next one is called...
Keep the Momentum Going.
Three, two, one, go.
Alright, Ben.
You've already made approximately five million dollars of sales
off of the Plebe and the Weeb Blu-ray.
But you must keep it going.
Ben, you must create Plebe and the Weeb Season 3.
Kickstart it now.
You can get new guests with watching new, sweet anime or whatever.
Maybe just review comics.
You got to do it, Ben. You got to do it.
I got to do it.
Plebe and the Weeb Season 3.
I got to do it. It was on the Kickstarter.
You got to do it.
If I watch some anime, I can be a guest on that season.
You'll be...
Yeah, we'll do a guest episode with you.
We'll have Cybershell on one.
We'll have Living Fall on one.
To Snake on one.
Minerva.
Who's the guy who did Frog Fractions?
Shit, what's that guy's name?
How do I look like that guy's name?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, he has a real name.
He has a real name. Jim Storm Dancer.
Jim Storm Dancer. That's it.
You might have to change the title of the show.
It could actually work because
every episode only had, I think, around three people, usually.
So...
Yeah, it's easy.
No, it'll be easy. We don't have to change anything.
In fact, we can just recreate all the original episodes, word for word,
just with new people.
That saves us on writing.
Right, exactly.
We can arrange that for you.
He's got connections. He's got big money connections.
The next voicemail is...
What is this called?
I missed the 300th episode voicemail, so here's 301th.
I wish I had 12 hours of PCP instead of heavy machinery at aah.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Congratulations on your 301th episode, guys.
Thanks. Is that Solaris to say?
Thank you. Thank you.
And good night.
Yeah, 300.
Cool.
We did it.
Next one is called...
Urgent Message from Wong Chan.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello. It is I, Wong Chan, calling you from China again.
I have urgent message for the man known as Tom Oliver.
You can send this message for me on behalf of the Wuhan Town in China.
Please, thank you.
There is a message I need you to send to the man known as Tom Oliver is.
Hello. How are you?
Thank you. Wong Chan, turning out.
That's a very important message, so you better deliver it.
I don't know about the deliberately super racist Chinese voice.
I'll be a little honest, I zoned out. I sort of don't remember what he said just there.
At least it kind of wasn't paying attention.
At least he didn't say it a N word 43 times or 46 times.
Sure.
I think there's a difference of like...
Because the obvious parallel is like, oh, Samurai Samma.
But Samurai Samma just felt like it was...
Samurai Samma and better.
Was an accent, but it was not about the accent.
The joke was not how racist stereotype voice.
I think this Chinese thing is entirely that.
And it's like, yeah.
Not as good.
Are we going anywhere with this?
No.
Okay, next one is...
Oh, we got another image here.
Let's just see about that.
All tiggers can't get enough of that malt extract.
The malt thing is a racist stereotype.
People of stripe surely enjoy their malt extract.
Just say otherwise would be an erasure of their rich culture.
I don't even know what this...
I mean, I'm sure this is like, some sort of...
Okay, I don't know what...
I don't know why it's malt extract of all things,
but sure, whatever.
Just trying to make a statement about like,
black people in watermelon or something.
But they're using tigger and malt.
Maybe something like that.
They're making a statement on like,
the ways to react to a racial stereotype.
Like the dumb thing is to say, ha ha, the stereotype.
Then the next thing up is Winnie the Pooh normal,
saying it's a racist stereotype.
And the apparent enlightened,
whatever you call it, this version of Winnie the Pooh,
the tuxedo and the funny eyebrows.
I like that Winnie the Pooh, he's just reading,
just reading, just some light reading on critical race theory.
For race theory.
For Winnie the Pooh.
He's so smug about it, he loves it.
It's like to deny the stereotype is in a ratio of their culture,
which is not even a thing that is said.
People of stripe, people of stripe.
So it comes off as like, I don't know,
dumb the whole way through.
I think...
Isn't that what makes it funny?
I feel like maybe I could try and read something into this
that might be offensive.
Maybe I would disagree with something,
but I don't feel like it's meant that seriously,
and I'd be missing the point if I tried to take issue with this meme.
So I'm just going to say...
Listen.
Funny joke.
Listen, everything...
It's funny that Winnie the Pooh is reading a book.
Everything is funny when it's ironic.
Yeah.
People of stripe.
Okay, next one is called New Plan.
Posting.
But that's what Trixie is going to do very soon.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, comrades.
Nikolai decided not to invade Ukraine,
and Nikolai instead is going to invade PCP headquarters.
That sounds good to you.
Good luck finding it.
Yeah, good luck finding something that doesn't exist.
Wait, was he looking for PCPHQ?
Yeah.
You got to have to go to the realm of...
The realm of dreams.
That's where the podcast is.
Where's the podcast?
Where's PCPHQ?
The realm of dreams.
Yeah, also, this is still just Digibro's anime podcast.
Now that...
No one is...
No one's...
Now, Chrono, no one's saying this isn't Digibro's anime podcast.
However...
Nothing.
Okay, next one is called...
End of Otatwai 3.33 You Are Not Otaku.
Crunchyroll Awards.
Three, two, one, go.
Main character, Eren, won antagonist of the year.
That isn't what antagonist means.
Star Wars vision, zero nominations.
Attack on Jujutsu, Demon Titan, Slayer, Kaisen, Socks.
Done with anime.
I'll taco no more.
Good.
I don't...
I don't know.
I guess I agree with all of that.
It's good to be done with anime.
I like...
Finally, you're free.
Chinese cartoons.
But Chrissy was done with anime, but she appears to have gotten back into it.
Here?
Wait.
Oh, did I?
I think I forgot one.
Never mind.
This next one is called...
Wake Up.
There we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, wake up.
The accident wasn't your fault.
What do you think Gibb is called?
Gibb?
It's because she's your id, Ben.
She's your id.
It doesn't make any sense.
What does that mean?
What?
Id?
Like the youngy and psychology thing?
I don't know.
Considering you do...
Because it's a B backwards?
Whatever.
Considering you do these shows now really early, like 10am, you do need to wake up more.
I do need to wake up.
But I always do.
Okay, next one is new character, WREE, wree, wree man.
Three, two, one, go.
Anyway, what do you think about spiders?
I think they look pretty aesthetically pleasing.
There's so many different kinds.
guess I mostly don't like them I mostly think they're unsettling and I
wouldn't want to be around one or even look too closely my favorite spider is
spider-man because he's a man and I also hear he's a good web designer I like
spider-man because he's a man and I'm a misogynist yeah whatever spider-man
what about what about spider woman where spider man what why is he white
though spider-man what about spiders what about spiders what about man spider next
voicemail is called the Nate had theme song from no Nate yes watch at dusty
dumps.com 3 2 1 go oh Nate Nate the reason I breathe is you but you're not on
the podcast oh best guy ever there's nothing I wouldn't do listen to the
gamer zone I'm coping show me Nate best man just put him on the PCP with no click bait
my naveless is killing me and I must confess I still believe when Nate's not
here I lose my mind my ass is primed get Nate on here one more time my ass is primed
well that's about all the shit I can take I tried to stick around but this was kind
of a fuck you to the fans comment by jig lover for 06 on PCP episode 300 I saw that
once in Nate head forever in Nate head never stop complaining always no Nate no watch
hell yes yes that should be the the intro to this out that's a good that's that's great
you get a voice I saw that comment I this guy's already got voice group mood to send
who's already got voice grill if he doesn't already we definitely definitely I saw that
comment I thought it was really funny that like this is the like what this this is the
this is the straw that breaks the camel's back I don't know if you want me my ass is crime
gamer zone that's true that's true I'm still I'm still waiting for my light because I feel
like you know it's the gamer zone so I should be on it on the gamers never huh opening in
seven minutes okay hold on this some weird shit is going on with my downloads at the moment this
is a very good time for that okay I'll just I'll skip that one for now whatever okay next
one is called my official PCP nostalgia critic impression contest entry I don't know why this
one's a minute long three two one go okay this is my entry for the official PCP nostalgia critic
impression contest here we go hello I'm the nostalgia critic I remember it so you don't
have to why top 11 because I like to go one step beyond okay now I will be performing one of the
iconic scenes from one of his reviews okay let's go we need more victimization there are no good
teachers oh god my accident we need more stuff to rebel we don't want to help you we just want to eat
your blood please I don't want to listen to this whole thing our education systems broke wait maybe
it's the other way around I don't know I got a high school education nostalgia critic the height of
comedy be like hell remember the one teacher who seemed cool he wasn't it's all part of the plan
hey who cares all this bitch and sales remember that one teacher who seemed really kind and give
candy well oh well we gotta another hit in the wall oh god it's so obnoxious so
well so school sucks grow a damn pair of walls I don't have any original thoughts about this I
just agree with everything that Dan Olson said in that one video it's so it's so irritating so
so fucking bad okay well thanks for that thanks for that I guess geez okay next one is Prince
Annihilation announcement three two one go what's up Ben since last week's 300th episode was jam packed
with guests and banter assuming that this one will have to rebound into a solo band close enough
totally accepted 301 the dawn of a new age we have to face it on our own so as an avid
enjoyer of the endless war of slime and punishment and a phantom horse revenge I've recently had
the realization that perhaps in being so busy with working on the conclusion to these older
storylines you might not have had the time to be as up on the newer events in lakakam so with that
in mind I figure since you seem interested why not give a little report of some relevant news
and current events in the city and the server so I'm here by announcing the slime and times weekend
update as I cram my lore down your little throat honestly okay goodbye yeah uh yeah okay I remember
the slimes I remember I wonder if Prince Annihilation is is aware that there was a news and a real
a real and in-game newspaper called the slime times slime times was great
uh wish they'd kept it up but I mean it must they made a bunch of them they sure it was a lot of
work that's pretty cool uh so a game that you created has all its own lore that its fans are
coming up with that you might not even know about it and you're you're the creator of it
yeah I can't I can't even keep track of it um I'm I'm not super like active over there I pop in
every every so often uh for for one reason or another um all right uh well let's do the next
one then I did find I did get that one that was having trouble downloading but we'll do the next
one it is called uh it's gonna take 10 seconds seven six five four three two two one okay uh
the next one is called slime times weekend update number one there you go three two one go
top of the morning tally ho welcome to the first installment of the slime times weekend update
straight from the beating heart of neo milwaki in this week's news a killer by the name of
ungin got arrested for having a rowdy alt named splat cat when rowdies became suspicious of the
imposter and asked for discord screenshots to prove that splat cat was legit the alt reportedly
claimed they needed time to clean up their servers first because it was quote 50 furry porn
ungin's official statement on the matter after coming clean we do a little trolling in other news
wordless taken over nurses office and the hunt for relics of the olden days is still in full force
some rowdies and killers have even allied themselves to more expediently solve the riddles
leading to the relics we'll see how long that lasts that's it for this week we hope to see you next
time and remember the slime time is the best time right the the the in-game uh sort of a meta or
lore at the moment is that they're uh right they're hunting for uh ancient relics is kind of a
is the current uh the current uh thing that's happening just like uh the plot of every 90s j rpg
uh yeah uh thanks for that uh prince uh good uh keep keep me updated if there's if there's news
that's a pretty cool feature um it'd be nice of uh you continue doing that
yeah um okay the next one i'm this is the one it's called crypto enjoyer volume two three two one go
hello it's the uh unironic crypto enjoyer trend episode 300 uh i've changed my setup a bit so
audio is a bit different also i'm a little bit sick so explain so that i was sick i got boosted
i got my booster and it made me sick for a day i need to expand my my thoughts a little bit for you
it was like having cove it all over again ethereum and these in these mostly gpu mind
um cryptocurrencies are really bad for the environment right don't tell me about proof of
stake use they take up so much power um for the hash rate that they get and because you have to
clock up the speeds um they're pretty much worthless once you're once you're done mining
on them so you have to basically either throw it away or sell it to some poor soul for way too much
money now that crypto i was talking about um so so 300 manero okay it's actually cpu mind so you
just mine it on the cpu that's already in your computer um do you have a clock then ruin what that
does basically is lower power consumption because there's been a focus on increasing efficiency
for cpus for quite a while because they're used in laptops and stuff like that and um cpus aren't
very sellable um um you know aftermarket stuff so basically uh once you i mean you can still
use it after you've done mining it it's basically the same yeah but it's still using energy that
otherwise would not be being used okay this this is all okay i get all right this is this is this
is just a more you're telling me that there's a more efficient way to do something that i still
think is bad the core idea here of cryptocurrency is and the blockchain is it's just bad and i would
rather not even if it were free even if it took no power at all i would still say sucks don't do it
uh that's that's the core that's the core disagreement we have here i don't see a reason
of making a distinction between the cpu and gpu because uh you know i don't really get that either
i have no idea basically just a cpu that's dedicated to graphics processing you know so it's
not really that different hmm that's yeah i don't i don't understand that at all
uh okay next one is called confirmed question mark uh there it is three two one go
i saw that elias are in and live in fall are under the this episode's procrastinators thing
in the description does that mean they're new procrastinators confirmed hell yes no more new
procrastinators no never never unpaid interns only it's all about uh unpaid labor that's uh
ben saint uh the communist champion that's that's that's exactly that's exactly right um
that's what i'm talking about uh next one is called speed run from how do i pronounce this
name is it it's friggin friggin i'm gonna say friggin okay uh three two one go
hey ben you mentioned last week watching commentated speed runs which remind me of
of all things a homestuck fan comic called spurb done quick in which two players the entire game
in just 81 pages the only text is a speed run commentary explaining their exploits that sounds
really cool the whole thing in maybe half an hour might be worth checking out that actually sounds
awesome that does sound good because my favorite one of my favorite things about homestuck is uh is
the um yeah is the the actual the mechanics of the game are the most interesting part
and then like that all gets dropped and like after like act three and no one cares anymore
speaking of speed runs uh anyone remember those races you guys used to do like the Kirby race
of course is there is there more to that thought or i don't know i just i watched one of those
videos recently i just wanted you to feel bad that you don't do anymore okay i remember i think i
watched the Kirby race and didn't you win that one i did i did win that one you're pretty uh
experienced Kirby player you're kind of a Kirby master yeah oh no that you should yeah i would
i would say so definitely you should have said that that's what you should have that would have
made more sense i'm the top racist i just won too much i won too much and nobody wanted to uh to
race me anymore uh the the uh did you see and did i already talk about the um the yawn measly
video about homestuck i haven't seen it i don't think you talked about it um well you know yawn
measly is that one guy whatever i won't i won't explain him again uh he did have a homestuck
video it was like a patron reward for passing a backer goal patron uh and he was gonna do the
homestuck video and he i i thought the video was pretty good it was okay it was decent he
doesn't like homestuck but that's okay because he the things that he says are good about homestuck
and the things he says are bad about homestuck are the same things that i think are good and bad
about homestuck uh so like i guess we're in agreement he just waits them differently uh
i don't know it was kind of a bummer it was a bummer hearing him be like homestuck's bad and
here's why and i had to be like yeah true he's right yeah but if he says it's bad he must surely he
must be wrong only only a bad person right he's he's his reasons are actually that's a weird
coincidence because i was just watching like an old pcp episode where you guys talked about homestuck
and i think jesse he mentioned he said homestuck is bad i don't know if he was being serious or
not he i'm sure he was being serious yeah he because we talked about a lot and he read like a
little he started to read a little bit of it and he got like frustrated with it or he didn't feel
like continuing which i mean there was a lot of a lot of people feel like there's a lot of friction
on that episode yeah i remember getting pretty annoyed about it so the ben versus i remember a
line where it's like you ben said of jesse making fun of homestuck despite not reading it you you
said you're having fun but you're having fun at homestuck's expense and that's what's upsetting
yeah i thought that was fun because it's like it it is often the case it was like
it's funny to just be flippant about something um yeah you know because whatever who cares it's just
a thing but no it's the end of the day it's just homestuck yeah but it's homestuck and i'm like
i agree i i wanted him to like it but whatever i wanted i wanted him to like it i it's not that
i actually think it's like a problem for you to trash talk homestuck if you hate it but like
yeah i think what i was getting at is like you're making jokes i guess if if anything jesse says
is a joke who whoever knows um but he he his yeah the the the crux of the joke was like
homestuck is bad people shouldn't read homestuck and i'm over here sincerely believing that no
people should read it even if i can acknowledge the homestuck is bad on some days i would probably
agree that on the whole yeah homestuck is bad i thought i still think people should read it
so so when you when the the the the sediment behind your joke is homestuck bad no one should
read it i can't i can't get behind it uh so that's what homestuck is is like the simpsons uh people
talk about it being bad uh but there's still a lot of good stuff in there and people of new
generations should look into it there's a lot of people who don't know the simpsons because it's just
yeah before their time now just like homestuck you're just like the simpsons with homestuck you
should just read you should just read the first the first couple chapters i was gonna say uh
and maybe you should only watch like the first 10 seasons or so yeah with homestuck you should
you should react one if you like it you should continue on to read probably definitely till
act three probably through act five and then nobody should read past the end of act five
under any sort even if you liked it and you want to know what happens just don't just don't do it
yeah um okay next one is called good job ben very okay there we go uh three two one go
ben it's been an honor watching the rag con two documentary with you but one problem
you missed the fucking slur you god damn idiot i i will fix it i will fix it you did what was it
uh there's um there's a there's a soft there's a soft a n word and there's another one that is uh
it's harder to hear i i i i shouldn't have missed it but i know why i did because it's kind of spoken
in the middle of a bunch of other people speaking and i and i missed that it was there uh so i will
i will scrub those out i sure were a lot of n words back in the pcb's history and that's uh
that's for sure i i mainly got them but i didn't get them all but i can i will fix it uh
i feel pretty stupid uh i messed up but i'll so i'll fix it um next one is called jumping on a
three month old topic there it is uh three two one go in episode 283 there was a conversation
about whether we should bring back media from the future to the past or i guess the present or not
and ben said that he wouldn't bother with it since that just lets people experience it earlier
which is all net neutral which is frankly dumb as fuck people die ben people die before art they
would have liked gets released yeah okay well i mean if you really want one specific person
to experience one specific work of art i guess uh is that really that important i guess it has
potential to be important if the right person with the right sway in the way the world will move
going forward reads homestuck in like 18 or more yeah you see if if if adolf hitler only played
megaman x he wouldn't have done the holocaust would would someone in 1804 even be able to appreciate
anything about homestuck maybe they can read the words they i mean they could probably
i don't think that i don't think they would appreciate anything that makes homestuck special
like yeah they could probably could understand you know the idea of these kids that are friends
that communicate through this messaging system going on this fantastical journey and you know
aliens from another world and alternate realities and stuff i'm sure they could get the gist of that
but everything that makes homestuck special is like its format and the way that it is sort of made
for the internet of its time and that just wouldn't mean anything well okay to a person of the era
maybe that wouldn't but i'm just saying you bring the right thing to the right person maybe they'd
get inspired and write a like a book that's like way ahead of its time that influences other things
you don't know what's gonna happen maybe but like okay i don't like like art is kind of the same
story over and over again really there's not that many different stories that you can tell
what makes a particular work special and what makes a particular work like gain traction and become
you know renowned and a classic in its day you know when it's made is that it speaks to
something about those people at that time and so i think it would be a really weird to think that
like oh this work of art this classic work of art that exists here at this point we need to bring it
back in time to a different era that can't really appreciate it or it would be it would be like
really it would be a really weird thing for like one work of art to like hit
better and make a more splash and be better suited for like a previous time except in the
way that it might be prescient of things that hadn't happened yet which i guess is true but
then that's not really about the art that's about like oh we got to warn people that world war two
is gonna happen and stuff like that right we got to prevent anyone from making the first blockchain
uh it's so on and so forth it's like i said if you just uh gave hitler something to idle his time
away with he probably wouldn't have he would have become a he he would have stuck with his art he
would have become a webcomic artist so we never would have had uh the nazi party exactly you see
he just had too much like there was like similar like uh political people who at the time would have
taken the place of adult hitler i don't know if exactly the same thing would have happened but like
the it's not just him like germany was completely normal and nothing was going wrong until he
decided to change everything and alone he managed it well i guess uh we can't know that for now you
know it's uh all in the past even if hitler was in his room playing super mario uh land
i this gameboy uh color all right i i think i feel like i've explained my reasoning for why
bringing art from the future isn't like it's not i don't i don't think other other than like the
fact that with it comes like technology we've never seen before that it would give us insights into
the practical realities of the future i don't think there's anything artistic that would blow
minds about future art it would just be art from a different context that we are not really suited
to appreciate that's what i think um anyway next one is a an imager link
artistic interpretation of what ben thought give looked like before yeah why have i got like the
swedish flag because i because i said i thought you were like a like a blonde nordic oh i i thought
i thought that was like the fallout uh you know like like vault suit for a second not like that
not like that fat i didn't picture you as being that fat i thought maybe i would have drawn you
with like long hair like kind of like kind of like kind of like shoulder length hair or like
long ish i don't know this was just my mental image based on almost nothing it's funny how
this is exactly opposite aside from the blue eyes yeah which i kind of a little bit like gray blue
eyes hmm uh i don't know just uh i'm just so stupid i'm just so dang stupid is all is that
is that what some people think mage looks like no it's what ben thought i this is this
i i've seen mage this is exactly what mage looks like yeah in real life
in case you didn't know yeah um so they're uh slavic blonde so you know whatever uh okay next one
this is the last one unless there's a last minute please no more yep this is the last one need an
answer from tgt lormaster ben i'm not that much of a lormaster i haven't even read the new pages
three two one go so i saw this comic about shadow breaking out the time prison his bro uh he spoke
his bones and his heels every time he moves and it's very funny yeah when he's in style all of
task controls but i read all of taggill's throat and i never saw the sequence i'm pretty sure it's
an edit where is it then i'm pretty just like an extra panel from laser but i can find it anywhere
be famous meet the origins of this comic strip you probably saw it it's all around on twitter
yeah it's a it's a it's a strip it's a strip about uh shadows like i just came back from the
whatever like time void i lived there for 10 000 years i never died i never went to sleep
uh i just i couldn't move except by breaking my bones so i just broke all my bones over and over
again until they healed themselves and began my body is pure scar tissue i'm like i'm a i'm invincible
you know i'm so powerful that i'm just constantly breaking and re rehealing all my bones whenever
i move or whatever i'm pretty sure it's a it's an edit of a bunch of panels of tails gets trolled
that have been put together i don't know what the dialogue comes from or why it exists uh but i know
the one you're talking about well if cyber show we're here probably he'd be able to answer that
because he's not only the sonic lore master he's also the the tails get strolled lore master
and just like the meme guy in general like i'm sure he knows he probably knows exactly where
that meme comes from and who made it and why and what it's referencing uh and all that master of
many lures i found out uh from this is from the know your meme page the meme of uh putting
the two the smiling friends guy guys in front of something and him and say like uh you know
i know we're supposed to help this guy but if he's a lost cause you know he's already made
up his mind why don't we just get out of here and cut our losses i guess cybershell was the
first guy to put that image in front of something yeah i saw that or at least the first one that is
that is known or at least he's credited as the first one on know your meme which i just thought
was i just thought it was interesting quite a quite an obvious meme template to do yeah
yeah i guess so like it might have happened inevitably it's still funny that he was he's
i guess was the first one to do it he's the first one to do it and therefore he owns the copyright
to it he owns the copyright of putting one copyrighted thing on another copyrighted thing
just like sonichu it's a parody baby uh you could you lawyer fair use um yeah there you go well
that's it that's the last uh okay that's the last one hooray no more cast no more podcast i'm sick
of this bullshit uh do we have any final notes do we have any final notes uh stay tuned for
the secret project revealed should be the next few weeks or like early march i guess i'm not entirely
sure but i will be talking about that a lot when it happens yeah i can't i can't wait to discuss it
with you can't wait to see it yeah it's it's it's it's people are gonna be excited about it uh
stay tuned for my not secret project uh fan of revenge and the end of slime and punishment
uh coming very soon don't know exactly how soon but within the same general time frame probably
still within the month of february uh i think probably i it should and that's it uh become a
patron at patreon.com slash the procrastinators uh check if you want to see the commentated
uncut commentary on our commentary on the uh the the right country documentary here are thoughts
about all that uh this is a good time um and i guess that's it don't forget uh don't forget to
check out my stuff at uh gamers tavern dot com and if you if you have not checked out gamers tavern
check out gamers tavern uh what's what's your what's your latest video was it the metro dread video
yeah i've uh been dreading that video for a while now so yeah it's youtube.com slash
gamers tavern show for um latest youtube content definitely definitely check out gamers tavern
um all right if you check me out i'll check you out cool uh all right that's gonna do it
end of the episode we'll see you next week and um peace out every time we see you later everyone