Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Entertaining you with all the weak snooze that makes you snooze, I'm the best guy ever.
And we've got Ben Saint over here.
Pretty fucking good. Hey, hey.
Thank you. On the top of my head.
On the top of your head, pretty good.
He guys heard about this British indie pop band from London, England, consisting of vocalist
Sarah Midori, Perry, and producers and multi-instrumentalist Gus Laban and Jamie Bullard.
And all their songs are about meat and butter.
That sounds good.
They're called Keto Keto Bonito.
But thank you, thank you.
I do shows, I do interviews, I'll do speaking gigs, you can contact my agent.
Is that a real band?
No, it's a Kero Kero Bonito joke.
I was hoping you'd say a London-based pop rock group, Sleep Tight, featuring two unnamed collaborators.
But let's get to one of those.
Give and take.
I mean, Sleep Tight's more like a Pacific or Atlantic ocean.
I forget which one, because it's like me and Munchie and we're like,
if you take the mean, the median average point, we are based in the ocean.
That's like the Atlantic somewhere.
Yeah, it's representative of the downfall of Western society, let's be honest.
And there he is, Tom Oliver.
Yeah, I'm ready to go see Joker and shoot up a theater, because I guess that's what we do now.
I do want to see that real bad.
Haven't gotten to it yet, looking forward to it.
I've actually heard pretty good things.
Well, you know, you hear a mixture of things, depending on who's talking at the time.
I haven't heard everything nowadays.
There's two versions of everything.
I haven't heard red-letter media or Yomo Yusaku's talk about it, so...
The only people who matter.
Just like everything.
There's two versions of everything.
There's the Dimension 1218 version and there's the Dimension C197 version.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, pause.
Which side are you on?
Pause. This is important.
There is a completely polarized society that we live in now, especially with social media.
Is that evidence of the dimensional merge?
Is that why there's such a polarized social conversation?
Because this is actually the two dimensions coming together?
Tom, literally anything you want to be is evidence of the dimensional merge.
So, absolutely.
You want an evidence of the dimensional merge?
Look at my boy Joker crossover with Jeb right here.
This is everything I've been waiting for.
So good.
Now that's proof of anything.
Now that's pod racing.
God, I fucking love Jeb.
Okay, let's...
Why is he not running again?
What a travesty.
It's pouring out for the dimension we didn't get to experience, the Jeb dimension.
Quick update, everybody.
Jeb will rise again.
Lisa Simpson for president 2020.
Quick update, which is just...
So, I'm sure everybody saw.
So the PCB Minecraft server rolled out since we last spoke.
I mean, you had already heard it when the last episode came out.
But almost like 75 people have already joined.
It's an active community.
There's always people playing in there.
People have been building stuff.
I'm building Slime Corp HQ at this very moment.
No, guys, get in there and stop him.
You can't get away with it.
There's mining and crafting happening literally right now.
It's insane.
So, hey, $5 pledge, patreon.com slash PCB Minecraft.
If you want to play, come play with us.
It's going to be a good time.
Link down below.
When are we going to get a cameo appearance by our boy MC Fit?
He needs to bomb into the new hotness.
He should.
That would be pretty cool.
He showed up in the stream briefly.
Did he?
Oh, cool.
I tried to beg him.
He did.
Yeah, he did.
He did just for a moment.
I missed the first one, but I want to.
There will be many more to come.
I want to get in there.
Yeah, I want to get in there.
I need to.
I have to install a Minecraft.
Hey, we should go back to Bufalantopia.
You know what I wanted to do?
I was thinking to start a stream.
We do a goodbye stream at Bufalantopia.
Yeah, a goodbye stream where we have mage.
We all cancel all the zones, and then we just burn the whole thing down.
Oh, that sounds like a good idea.
Yeah, if we could make it.
We burn the sign.
We watch the sign burn.
We return the land back to the land.
Back to the Bufalant.
We release all the Bufalants into the wild.
What a great idea.
All right, look for that.
Look for that soon.
So what else is going on?
I mean, that was the one quick update I had.
Well, I have one.
I have an announcement.
As of right now, when you are hearing this, well, as of recording, the Vapors 2 Kickstarter
has $1,000 left to go to hit its stretch goal.
We hit the first stretch goal, which means everyone who pledged gets $15 and gets a dollar
back.
We did communism.
I made communism real.
Everyone's getting a dollar back.
I'll put a dollar bill in your fucking thing.
I will pay you, listener, to pledge to my Kickstarter.
And then if we hit $10,000, which as of right now we're $1,000, I don't know when you're
listening to this.
I don't know how close we'll be.
There'll be a free pin, a new third free pin that everyone will get $15 and everyone
gets a third pin.
It's the St. Heart.
Everyone thinks that people seem to really want this one.
I really want to make it.
Anyway, Vapors 2 Kickstarter, kickstarter.com slash projects slash Ben St. slash Vapors
2.
I'm, you know, I don't want to count my chickens ever, when before or after they hatch.
Even once they're hatched, I'm not entirely convinced of the reality, but I'm feeling pretty
optimistic about this next goal, 1,000 bucks left.
There's always that spike at the very end of most Kickstarter's film.
Last time there was a pretty significant spike at the end.
Will we have this one?
Only time will tell, but if you're listening to this right now, this is the last weekend
that you have until April.
So there's like two days left as they hear this.
It's time for the spike.
Make the spike real.
Go, go now.
The night of Sunday the 13th.
I did my part.
Have you done yours?
Yes.
It's the last night.
I've had my first Kickstarter ever with this one, so I'm just saying that's an endorsement
if there ever was one.
Remember, the most important thing is that the more money the Kickstarter makes and the
more people who buy the book, the more money I get for drawing the thing in the book.
Indeed.
Yeah, I'm giving all the guest artists, which I will get you a script soon, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was going to bring it up.
That's my passive aggressive way of bringing that up.
All the guest artists will get, I'm giving them like a percentage basically, and yeah,
the more it gets sold, the more every guest artist gets.
They're already past last time.
Past last time.
Last time, we had 212 backers in.
This time, with a week left, we've already up to 236.
I think at this rate, I think I would need between now, like in the next seven days,
and when we're recording, seven days left, I would need at the average pledge amount,
which is like just under $40, I would need like 25 to 30 people to pledge at the average
at like a typical like $30, $40 amount, and that would hit the goal.
Seems doable.
So if you were, hey, viewer, you're one of 25 to 30 people.
Think about it.
About $40 of expendable income.
Okay, cool.
That's my piece.
Hurray, hurray.
Very exciting.
So what's the word in the world, everybody?
What's going on?
I've also had a fucking crazy week.
Why don't you tell us about that, Ben?
You want to hear?
Okay.
You want to hear about that?
Well, God, what even happened?
Where was this at last week?
Because the developments have been astounding.
I think the last time it was just you were doing a comic, and Chris Chan was just saying
it was cool and canon, and we were talking about how that's pretty funny.
You were hoping to not spook him away with 9-Eleven jokes and stuff.
You were talking about how you needed to bring Nightstar back in to reel him back into the
interest.
Oh, yeah, I was saying that Chris was like, not really.
Chris was like kind of there, she wasn't liking all the tweets, but she was still definitely
reading.
A lot has happened since then.
A lot has fucking happened.
Okay.
I mean, you know, we did 9-Eleven, right?
We all had a really big laugh, it was great time, everybody had a good time.
Okay.
The order of events here is really important for context, but I genuinely don't even know
the order of some of these events.
Well, at some, okay, so...
I think it was like you made it so that Phantom Horn saw the big green eye, and then...
Incredible artwork by the way.
After he died.
I loved that.
Thank you.
Yeah, I had a lot of fun drawing that.
I didn't make it that way.
That's what happened.
I saw it in C197.
Oh, really?
Of course.
None of this, I'm not doing it.
I mean, I'm just reporting on with the truth.
Are you that green guy in the, well, he died, right?
I mean, who are you in this?
No.
That was just a random juve.
Okay.
Are you the cop killer?
I mean, I...
You need to understand your dimensional, your fucking dimensional ontology here.
Clearly.
Right?
Okay, there's 1218, that's us.
I am 1218 Ben.
Just like there is 1218 Christine Weston Chandler.
There is an alternate version of each of us.
So then there is C197 Ben, who is the cop killer.
And then there is C197 Christine, which is Comet Christine.
There is HumbleJuve.
What about that?
Right, I was gonna ask about HumbleJuve.
HumbleJuve is not...
You would think HumbleJuve is an alternate version of me.
No.
HumbleJuve is just a guy who looks exactly the same and has the exact same name.
He is technically just a very similar person by coincidence.
Gotcha.
He is technically unrelated.
And then Phantom Horn is not an alternate version, he is an OC, and that's distinct.
And I am...
I could correct me in the comments if I'm wrong about this, but I believe the distinction
is that a alternate version, when the dimensional merge happens, the alternate versions will
merge like if they are well attuned to each other or something, they will merge into one
entity, whereas OCs will simply come into, you know, our newly created gestalt dimension.
Okay.
C119, whatever, it's like a combination of the digits.
So you will merge with the cop killer when this happens, is what I'm hearing?
Well, I would under certain circumstances, which Chris claims are no longer the case,
but I mean, let me just skip to the end, right?
Yeah.
This is like the movie where you see the end of the beginning, it's like the second season
of Breaking Bad or whatever, when you see what's his name floating in the pool, and it's
like, how did I get here?
And then the season is the story of how we got here.
Well, you know, as of right now, we got people, we got propagandists in Quickville spreading
the rumor that Slime City is slimeless, has been de-slimed, and that the cop killer has
been beheaded, and that his head has been taken into custody under Quickville with Chris,
Weston Chandler, and Magichan.
But this is false.
I can tell you, right?
I've looked at the other dimensions, this is false.
Endless War is saying, Endless War says that is a lie, that's propaganda, they just painted
a watermelon purple, Endless War provided photo evidence that that's true.
So I-
I haven't seen that yet.
Okay.
It's on Twitter, Endless War tweeted, it's like, do not believe the lies.
Okay, I'm gonna try and give like a succinct-
It's just like Arrival, by the way, time for Nate's movie lessons, Saw Arrival, Time Loop,
there you go, that's all I have to say.
Okay, cool.
I'm gonna try and give a succinct summary, okay?
So Chris, oh man.
So Chris-
Started drawing the, they're like, at the moment Phantom Horn was beheaded and they
died.
Yes.
Chris Chand took it upon themselves to start drawing what happens next.
Basically, yeah.
And Chris decided that what happened next is night stars, and there are drawings of this,
and there's like text dumps of this.
And most bafflingly of all, all of it is chronicled, not in a comic, but in the form of images
and flavor text on an expansion-packed set of Twilight Sparkle's secret shipfic playing
cards.
This is the format that Chris decided was the best way-
Is that what those are?
I thought it was-
Yes.
That's what the deal is with the format.
All right.
So there are cropped images of text on cards, because all of these were, this is a 15-card
Twilight Sparkle secret shipfic folder expansion-pack, and yes, and they detail how nightstar gets
Phantom Horn and strawberry milk to send her a sample of the slime.
She does tests on it, and then she sends Chris Chan Sonichu, like, you know, comic Chris
in Sonichu form.
Along with the other forces of Quickville, like lots of flying Sonichus, I don't know,
just a whole bunch of them, and nightstar determines that slime's weakness, something
that can wash slime away, is a mixture of water, sugar, and bicarbonate of soda, which
I believe is baking soda, but I forget.
So they create a storm of this and rain it down on Quickville, and their story is that,
oh yeah, this washed away all of the slime city.
Not Quickville.
Did I say, oh, did I say Quickville?
Yeah.
New Los Angeles City, aka Neo-Milwaukee.
So they say that, yeah, they rain for 24 hours, wash all the slime away, the city's no more
slime.
No more slime.
The implications of this are staggering, absolutely staggering.
But it's fake news.
It's fake news because, you know, the city's still there, the city's still running, and
Los Juarez said its propaganda, the rain did happen, and the death toll is counted
at about 70,000, and this is confirmed by Chris herself on Twitter, who says that 1%
or 99% of the population of Arizona survived, meaning that 10%, 1% died, population of Arizona,
about 700 million, so 70,000 people died in the bicarbonate rain.
This is, she did not back off from this, she confirmed this to be true.
So 70,000 people were killed when called out on this act of literal genocide.
Christine said that all those people were, that was just the bad ones.
Just the bad ones died.
And I believe, there was something along the lines of like, I mean, hey man, to make
an omelet, you gotta break a few eggs, I mean, these things happen.
That was Christine and Magi Chan's stance on the issue, is that it was just the bad
ones that died, and it was for the greater good, so don't worry about it.
That sounds like, I don't know, that could be approximately the population of Slime
City, I mean, they would be the ones to die if anyone from, I mean, these numbers may
be loose or who can say.
Me and Chris agree, we agree that 70,000 people died, but the population of Slime City is
above that, it was a terrible, terrible holocaust basically, but we're still here, we're still
here, we're queer, get used to it.
And so that's happening, you know, Chris claims to have, or, word on the grapevine, is that
they have the cop killers head in a jar, it's just a watermelon, I've seen it, don't worry
about it.
Yeah.
I'm filled with comfort by that.
Yeah, same, man, so, oh, I forgot to mention also at some point in this, Chris joined Endless
War, tried to play it, died a couple times.
Made up a couple of her own fake commands, like exclamation point, infinite revive, and
exclamation point, moxby dash, and then declared, so died a couple times, declared that like
game sucks, games over, Slime's fake, there's no more Slime, games over the end.
And then when it made these cards, making it so.
I spoke to someone who had in their possession, the medallion of Chris, stripped from their
neck.
I forget who that, but that's like a real thing in Endless War now, it's an actual item, someone's
carrying around.
There is a medallion, one of the people who slant cab.
Possibly one of the Endless Rocks.
Cab and dupes.
Perhaps.
I think they each got one kill, they both scalped her, so, and then there was complicated
series of trades that I won't get into.
The cop killer now possesses both of Christine's scalps.
And unlike this claim about the head and the jar, the cop killer can provide photo evidence
that this is the case.
I can type in exclamation point inventory right now, concrete proof, undeniable.
So that happened, the mayor of Quickville joined the server died.
Man.
I remember looking on Twitter, there was Phantom Home and Strawberry Milk.
I like how Chris Chan's interpretation of Strawberry Milk was very accurate.
It is.
It's shockingly self.
Strawberry Milk is always thinking pervy thoughts and talking about sex and it's really funny.
Yeah.
She kind of got to be like better than I did.
I was talking to Munchie and I sort of realized that like, you know, I kind of wrote Strawberry
Milk basically exactly like I would write keg.
I was thinking the same, I was saying to everyone that we all know Strawberry Milk is just a
knock off value brand keg standard, trying to fill the role of a greater character.
And I think, yeah, I wrote him to Broi.
I was talking to Munchie and he says that Strawberry Milk is really not much of a bro.
He's just like a gross perv.
And I was like, hmm, shit.
So I don't know.
You got to introduce keg standard into this narrative.
So Chris will draw a keg standard.
I mean, there needs to be a nod.
There needs to be nods to him at some point.
He's absent in the narrative.
It speaks volumes, Ben.
It speaks volumes.
I would love for Chris to draw some more, but, you know, I guess we'll see.
Dude, I want to fucking, I understand now, I don't want to undercut you, but Chris has
made certain demands of you to fund certain projects that's what I'm getting to.
Okay.
So Chris makes these cards explaining, you know, what really had quote unquote really
happened.
Yeah.
And so, you know, it was propaganda to propagate among the citizens who all love Twilight
Sparkle Secret Chip and Folder, literally the best way to get news out is to create
an expansion pack of Twilight Sparkle Secret Chip and Folder because everyone will read
it.
Nobody reads it.
It's an untapped market for sure.
Yeah.
That's basically, that's the Twitter of Quickville is Twilight Sparkle Secret Chip and Folder.
So Christine makes these cards and then she's messaging me, you know, she's been saying
like, she's been saying like, love your work and stuff.
Like we've been DMing a little bit and then, you know, she's very complimentary.
And then MagiChan, no, she says, I'm going to send you a copy of the cards.
And then MagiChan messages me and MagiChan says, hey, Ben, so, and I tweeted some of
these screenshots.
He's like, hey, Ben, so, hey, don't appreciate the greedy way you've been using our characters.
Don't appreciate the greedy way you've been profiting off of our something.
You know, I want you to contribute to the production of this card game, this expansion
pack.
So I expect you, and this is after Chris has already said, like I'm sending you like a
copy of the game of the expansion pack.
And I expect you to put a generous donation of $300 or more into Christine's PayPal account.
Here's the link.
Okay.
Have at it.
So is this like MagiChan?
Or like it's like Oral, it's basically it's like Oral's like, it's like a vague threat,
but there's no actual like, it's a threat that like, if you don't like, you will, like
everyone will know you're a bad person and like,
Well, Ben, you know, you know, you have to do, you know, you have to do, you have to
$13,000 stretch goal on, on the Kickstarter.
Oh, send Chris, they're, they're deserved earnings, they're fair share of the profits.
I mean, all my, I mean, even if, I mean, all the money from the Kickstarter is going directly
into slime coin.
So that's, I can, I really can only pay in slime coin, you know, I told her all my
money's tied up in slime coin.
That will continue to be the case for a foreseeable future, especially with this whole rain ecological
disaster.
Now, like the economy is just so clogged up, there's just, yeah, it's, it's, it's slime
coin or nothing.
It's slime.
It's really a slime coin or nothing to think all this could have been avoided if someone
had just given Chris Chan exclamation point diplomatic immunity and none of this conflict
would have even been started.
That's true.
I was so nice.
I was in the red carpet, gave her a custom role, did some custom artwork, a celebrating
the new alliance between quick fill in new Los Angeles city and what, and she responds
with genocide.
This is what I get.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't, you know, I'd love it if we could reestablish diplomatic relations,
but the way she's behaved, I don't know if it's going to happen.
Who's the troll now?
When you think about it, all this complaining about, oh, you're just fucking trolling.
Christine's the one who bombs into your server commits mass genocide and then it tries to
extort you for money.
I don't know.
It's like, I want a hundred percent agree with you.
It's like going into the ocean and saying, oh, oh, fish, let me take care of this pesky
water for you getting in the way.
Let me just get that out of here.
Yes.
That's, you know, what a great, what a great, yeah, yeah, yeah, like, it's like, oh, hey,
what's all these fish jumps in water, oh, oh, it's wet, hey, water gone, don't worry.
This water's gone.
Problem solved.
Welcome Moxby Dash.
What's the, I need to sever your addiction to this water.
I know better.
You can't be relying on this anymore.
You have to be set free.
My favorite, yeah, Chris just decided that like, oh, Slime's evil.
Actually, no, Slime's evil and fuck all of you.
I would really like to know, Ben, how you felt like the, like, initially it was just like
Christiana has drawn phantom horn and strawberry milk at last, and then realizing that she's
like, like trying to destroy Slime.
Yeah.
Talk about the monkey's paw in a fact.
Indeed.
Exactly.
I knew, I knew what was going to happen.
I, like, Chris had been, every time Chris had mentioned Slime up until it had been in
a negative context, like, I, I already knew, like, I knew where it was going.
I just didn't know how quick it was going to get there.
And it ended up being, like, three days from when, like, the first card was published when,
you know, phantom horn was on the card, and I was like, oh, my God, phantom horn, oh,
my God, New Los Angeles City, Chris Druitt.
And then, and then you, she releases the last cards and it's like, okay, yes, this is Slime
Genocide.
I was like, I knew, I knew exactly what was going to happen.
My favorite thing about-
I had hoped that it would be left open, like, because I, this really, this is what's really
frustrating, right?
Because I haven't, there is an ending in mind for the phantom horse robbery milk comic.
Chris doesn't know what it is.
I've told her there will be a happy ending.
There will be a happy ending, but it is not the happy ending Chris envisions.
Of course.
But Chris just decides that, like, okay, so obviously at the end, obviously what needs
to happen, this is so fucking annoying.
Obviously the phantom and strawberry come back to Equestria, leave the city, the city
is destroyed because it's a bad, evil place.
And also phantom horn gets his horn, after all, he gets a magic horn.
Fuck you.
Like, no, never.
I mean, it's, it's so sad.
It's just cheesy writing there, Chris.
It's just cheesy writing.
It's just, it literally just, like, you know, honestly, I felt a little bit personally attacked
by that one.
So that's completely unacceptable.
Not canon.
Phantom will never have a real horn, a biological horn.
Fuck you.
Never.
Never, never, never.
No.
Besides, that's how you know.
That's the smoking gun that lets you know that this is all fake news and propaganda.
For no other reason then.
I mean, if we, if we give phantom horn a quote unquote real horn, aren't we undermining the
reality that he does in fact have a horn already because he identifies as such.
So there can be no distinction made between phantom horn now.
It's ridiculous.
It's all, hey, you know, you know this, you spent your whole life, your whole character
arc, learning to accept yourself despite what you see as your physical shortcomings.
How about at the end of that, oh, but here, here it is, though, you don't have to learn
any, I didn't learn anything.
I can't believe you would criticize Chris Chan's stellar storytelling that there could
be any way that it, yeah, underlines character arcs or undies.
Nightmare, nightmare, nightmare.
Anyway.
I do feel like this is a really cool arc, though, like this is Lord of Ghost levels
of destroying the city.
We've got a, you know, really powerful enemy now, exclamation point war, you know.
Yeah, there, there is, there, in the game, there is like the bicarbonate reigns, Magix
Rampage put them in the game and they are now a hazard in the game that can kill you
and your slime lids.
Well, the good news is, N8 and Slimecorp have been reaping incredible profits from umbrella
sales.
Yes.
Bicarbonate proof umbrella sales.
That is also a thing in the game.
It's been one of the literally, mechanically, it's there.
The day, the day that I woke up to all of this like slime destroying storm sort of bullshit.
I read all of the tweets.
I was like, holy shit, I got out of bed and I immediately started drawing like more of
the red man noir comics so I can lick it into having the rain in it because it's so inspiring.
Are there more of those red men?
I hadn't seen them before, but like yesterday I was just on Twitter and I, or maybe the
day before and I was like, what is this red man?
What is this like?
What is this fucking noir?
What is this red man?
Okay.
Yeah.
Red man's character design has changed.
He's now like a detective.
Slime alteration.
He's rouge man.
He's like red man noir.
Sure.
I mean, it's the next logical step.
That last explosion Robin of all was blood.
But the thing that started it was Kip, like typed exclamation point harvest and nothing
happened.
That endless war chastises you because harvest is not a command.
He says harvest is not a command you fucking idiot.
So I was like, oh, is that changed?
And I typed harvest and then endless war yelled at me and not Kip.
And I was really upset and I was like, how are you doing that?
I copied Kip's text exactly, posted it and endless war yelled at me again.
So I was like, okay, there's some secret going on here.
Please tell me.
Kip was like, no.
And then red man donned his trench coat and hat and like interrogated Kip.
And that's when I drew red man, the detective.
And that is his goal.
He's trying to find out how to harvest without getting yelled at.
Wait, red man is or Kip is?
Red man is.
Kip will not like tell him the truth and this is the story that started and then it started
raining, slime destroying rain.
I'm like, let's let's tie this in.
Let's make this like a real narrative thing.
That's very noir-esque.
Yes.
Heavy rain outside.
Yeah.
Right.
It works.
It just works really good.
It's really fun.
I really hope that we can have some, forgive my, forgive my coom brain right now, but sexy,
you know, noir-esque damsel in distress or just secret agent gun girl with like fishnet
stockings in the size.
Leggy damn.
Oh no, your lipstick and like Jessica Rabbit from Who Shot Jessica Rabbit or whatever that
movie was.
I love that movie.
You know what I'm talking about.
So that's where the Chris Chan drama stands right now.
I'm sure it's not over.
No doubt.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see.
Neither Chris nor Madge Chan has yet to respond or they both have yet to respond to Endless
Wars declaration that, you know, the head, the head, the rumors about the head of the
cop killer are false and I mean, you know, obviously with this rain continuing, tensions
between the city are growing, you know, this keeps up the alliance is definitely going
to break down, you know, there may be war on the horizon, but you know, thoughts, thoughts
and prayers.
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
I guess.
I'm getting rowdy.
Not in the good way.
But fucking cool, cool news and this is pretty cool.
I am the article of the now on the quickie.
Ben, it's actually pretty good.
It is pretty good.
I read through it.
It's not bad.
It's not that, I mean, it's missing some stuff and it gets a little wrong here and there,
like it's pretty mostly accurate, pretty neutral, like the only thing I don't like the picture
they use because they use that fucking picture of me at Digi House.
Yeah.
That I hate, but like whatever, God, I really wish, I really wish it were the, they could
get the picture of me in the in the Chinese pajama pants squatting next to the fire hydrant
saying vaping is not a crime.
Can't you edit a wiki?
It seems to be like lockdown.
Really?
I didn't want to do it, but like people were telling me that like they were trying to like
make accounts and it's like you need permission or something like I don't know what the deal
is.
Disgusting.
Cowards.
Cowards all over.
Can I have a link to this, this article?
I got it right here.
It's.
All right.
You gotta dig through this shit.
There you go.
That fucking picture, you know, like it's fine.
It's fine.
You know, it's just like, it's okay.
Overall, I'm pretty good with it.
I'm pretty good with it, but like that fucking picture will haunt me for the rest of my life.
Yeah, probably.
It's not even like a bad picture.
I don't know whatever.
It's pretty okay overall.
It's fine.
It's a silly expression I guess.
There could do.
I mean, I could do so much.
It could be.
Yeah, at least it's not fat band.
Oh, at least it's not fucking fat band.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
It's just now only in the annals of, well, I guess the lecture and, and T-Bap resurrection.
And there is, um, there is a screenshot of Chris dying an endless war on here.
You know, it's good stuff.
There's good stuff.
Everyone should definitely go check it out.
It is interesting.
And I mean, it's a, what a culmination of a, of a career spent in,
Here we go.
Crystorian life.
Information.
Name Ben St. also known as the cop killer, Phantom Horn.
There you go.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's canon.
Legendary.
Amazing.
And I can't believe you, Ben.
You yourself are the feature of the update.
And this is the not so good news we've just heard about on the web.
It's you, Ben.
It's you.
Update.
I'm article, I'm article of the now.
My article is now tagged forever that it was once article of the now that is a distinction
I will take to my grave.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, this is very, very exciting.
What a life.
You gotta update your Twitter bio.
Gotta, gotta flex this article.
Article of the now on the.
Hey, not bad.
Not bad.
Yeah, maybe.
That's great.
Maybe it will.
That's, it's, uh, not everyone can lay claim to such a distinction.
It's true.
Okay.
I was thinking about something on this subject.
This is, it's a slightly more serious thing.
I don't, it's not a big deal.
It's not anything crazy.
I just had a thought and I was curious what you think about it, Ben.
It was just that, okay.
Yeah.
Because obviously some people have been arguing with you about like Chris Chan's, uh, pronouns
and identifying.
Oh my God.
I know you've been, you've been getting into some arguments about that.
I'm, I understand.
I don't, I hate these people, Nate.
I get it.
I fucking hate these people.
They're such fucking dicks about it.
They're such, uh, aren't you, aren't, aren't you a hypocrite?
Aren't you a hypocrite for insisting that we not misgender someone while you make fun
of them for unrelated things?
You like, no.
No, no.
You grow a fucking brain.
I've been saying that that's consistent.
Grow a fucking brain.
You're fucking moron.
Okay.
I hate them.
But I, I, I get the, the kind of idea they're getting at and I, I had this question to say.
That's okay.
I get the idea and it's fucking stupid.
It's the product of a fucking diseased mind that can't think, that can't make logical
connections from one thing to another.
I thought I had one interesting point about this, which was just that, um, okay, so we
all know that, like, so this idea of the dimensional merge, right?
That was like planted by the idea guys or whatever.
And it's, it seems, it seems to be the case.
Okay.
It was, it was, it was, I think it was, yeah, more or less.
I, I had heard, I had heard, you can correct me if I'm wrong, again, I'm, I'm gonna just
take Chris at his word.
I don't, it heard or worried.
It doesn't matter to me.
I had heard that this idea of being trans might have also been planted sort of by trollish
people.
And I was just thinking, if that is in fact true, and I think it, it could be true, then
does that change the dynamic of like, you know, what would the multi-dimensional, dimensional
merge thing that's planted by people who are trying to fuck up Chris?
That makes it worth like, okay, I mean, should we question it?
If this was also like planted in some way, should we, is it then, you know, something
similar to question in some way?
Okay.
All right.
Let me tell you what I, let me tell you what I said on Twitter.
Someone said something similar.
I was like, okay, I get what you're saying.
What did, what did I say?
That seems to me to be the only reasonable case of like, why you would have a, well,
here's, here's, here's what I think about that.
Okay.
So this is what I said on Twitter.
Someone made a similar argument and I said, here's why I disagree.
There is no way to look into some, I don't know why I'm, I don't know why I'm quoting
myself, but I don't feel like thinking about it.
I really said, there, there is no way, there's no way to look into someone's head or whatever
and say if they're quote unquote really trans, the only criteria we actually have to go on
is if someone says they are.
So if someone, anyone, even Chris, right?
Chris doesn't know anything, right?
Chris doesn't understand gender theory, doesn't matter because I understand it and, and they
don't need to get it.
They don't need to be, they can be wrong and I still want to be right.
Sure.
So if someone tells you their pronouns, there is nothing to appeal to as an argument for
why they're wrong.
Interrogating someone's reasons for why they say their pronoun preferences are what they
are is just missing the point that the only reason that matters is their preference itself,
right?
I don't know.
I guess what it comes down to, there's no higher authority.
There's no like, there's no like scientific truth of the matter.
Like this is literally just like a language thing.
And so if they're, if they say like the only, the only act, the only fact of the matter is
what they say and that's, that's it.
So if they say, if they say female pronouns, please, it's like, well, what, what, I don't
think there's nothing to appeal to be like, oh, well, here's why actually you're wrong.
Like, no, no, you can't, you just, you just can't do it.
It is unassailable.
It's, it's like, like somebody saying, you know, I have this opinion and then someone
else going, well, I disagree that you have that opinion and it's literally the same level
of objection.
Yeah.
So you are, I agree.
I think you're correct.
However, just let me put this example forward.
Let's just say theoretically, so one of these trolls came forward and said, yes, here was
my experience.
I was talking to Chris, I trolled Chris, but they were secure in their male identity.
Then I came in and began convincing them they're female.
This was my work.
They did not believe before I did this.
Now you're still correct.
We didn't do anything, their opinion is of their opinion, but if we know they were like
manipulating this way, are we doing the right thing to, to not in any way object?
Well, I'm trying to paint an example where we know it was done by an outside force.
Yeah.
Okay.
If we know it was manipulation, then does that change anything?
Yeah.
Like what, like such like, like everybody's manipulated, like, like the, the idea that
manipulation is different from just learning or like hearing about this new idea.
No.
Cause like, all right.
It's the context in like a macro sense is different.
But like in terms of like Chris's own head, it's the same thing.
I mean, I agree.
I agree.
Which, which it's unfortunate, but it's also true.
Well, I don't know.
Like, yeah, like we're all, I don't know, we're all, we've all, we've all been manipulated
by like the, the, our circumstances of existence.
The thing, the thing is like some people, um, you know, only say they're trans after hearing
about it.
And if it, you know, when trans things were like nobody ever heard about them, nobody
ever talked about them.
It was like, you know, years and years ago, I didn't even know that that was a thing.
Um, but like if people hear about it and then they say, like, oh, that's me, then are they
being manipulated with new information?
Or is it just that now they have an, like they have a word and a, like an understanding
of the thing they've been going through.
I don't know whether Chris was like, you know, maybe he was easily manipulated into that.
But like if he likes it or she, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I get it.
It, we're talking in like past and present tense at the same time.
Yeah.
It gets, it gets really confusing and people have, uh, I think lightly tease me thinking
that I've accidentally said he, when I've actually been talking about Magi Chan, cause
like when I talk about Magi Chan, you gotta, I say he, and like, you know,
It's a whole other layer to the, because obviously they are in every sense of the word
distinct individuals.
Um, and Magi Chan is not just an alt that is being used to try and squeeze money out
of me.
No.
Literally Magi Chan is like the fucking good cop or the bad cop to Christine's good cop.
Like Christine's all nice to me and stuff.
And then Magi Chan is like, Hey, give us that fucking money, by the way.
Uh, thanks.
Uh, I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting.
Um, and if you don't, um, I will come, I will come to you in soul form and obliterate
you.
So, all right.
So Magi Chan.
All right.
In terms of like, uh, that's one of Chris's accounts.
And like to type that Chris Chan had to type it.
Is it canonically that Magi Chan, like types through Chris Chan?
No.
It was that way for a while.
Canonically, um, as part of like the ongoing merge, um, okay, first, and this was sort of
like when I was kind of getting clued into what the, was the goings on more in Chris's
head.
Um, it was, uh, uh, Chris and Magi Chan had swapped minds.
We talked about this on another episode.
We did.
They had swapped minds.
So for a while, Magi Chan was in our dimension, but in Chris's body, like inhabiting her form.
Then they swapped back, but Magi Chan actually did like make the physical transition.
So canonically, Magi Chan physically exists now in our dimension.
And there are some screenshots.
I've seen those.
Those are incredible.
YouTube videos.
Oh, it's just one frame cause he's so fast.
You can see Magi Chan.
A and Y pony appears.
I mean, Chris linked like that one.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here it is.
I just found it in one fucking frame at 4535 in this fucking video.
Okay.
I'm getting the link right, right here.
Wait, wait, wait.
In like two frames of that video, Magi Chan is there behind A and Y pony and like, there
he is.
There, there's, you know, you know, the funny thing was, the funny thing was I went to this
video, I watched it through at that moment.
The damnedest thing.
I couldn't see Magi Chan.
It was weird.
I mean, I mean, you would have, you would have to pause at the exact right frame and
like, what are the odds that anyone could do that?
I mean, with the speed of Magi Chan, I mean, we know that like a computer, a camera only
renders it most.
It's going to be like 60 frames per second.
That's way too little time.
I mean, with YouTube compression, it's really not, it's no surprise that you're, you couldn't
pick them up even with frame by frame scrubbing, you know, obviously going to be between the
frames.
Did A and Y pony turn around that he'd like, oh, what's on my shoulder?
A and Y gave no sign of, of noticing, but just that fast because he's been touched on
the shoulder.
If Magi Chan didn't want to be noticed, he wouldn't be.
What's that command?
Spin dash away.
Exclamation point.
Mox speed dash.
Yeah.
Magi Chan totally Mox speed dashed right out of there.
This whole Mox speed dash is bothering me because in Sonic, there is an upgrade called
the light speed dash.
And the fact that Chris didn't go with that is mildly.
That's worse.
Mox speed dash is so much worse.
The second one is really.
Yeah.
Just looking straight at the camera.
Magi Chan.
That was at 3210 in the video.
Incredible.
Oh my God.
I love that it appears on an A and Y live stream.
Dude, I wonder, I wonder if Magi Chan is going to appear in this PCP episode.
Magi Chan went so fast, not even in the video at all.
Oh my God.
You're right.
He might be in it.
He might be here among us right now.
He's probably visited all of us, like while we're on here, just to make sure that we're
not slandering his and his wife's name.
It's kind of terrifying.
We are not.
Praise the God.
What is it?
Exclamation point, infinite revive, exclamation point, goddess protection, exclamation point,
goddess healing.
Is there any irony in the fact that it's a live stream of them discussing the God Delusion
by Richard Dawkins?
Is there some symbolism involved in this particular?
Is that true?
Is that really?
Yeah.
They're reviewing the God Delusion.
That's fucking rich.
By the way, I just want to point out, my favorite, this amazes me that one of the panels that
Chris Drew is Chris Chan Sonichu holding up a slime podron, the one that Phantom Horn
mined on his first mining.
He holds up the slime podron and he discusses it, and I forget his exact wording, but he
calls it a podron.
He says a slime podron and he says that it can be used as a healing crystal with minor
slime side effects, which is absolutely true, and literally what it does in the game, or
one of the things it does in the game.
He knows what's up.
He literally says this thing is good, this is a good item, and then he says, oh, but
slime is all evil and he tries to obliterate all slime.
It's funny to me how it attentive Chris Chan is.
The fact that he was attentive enough to, she, fuck, getting confused, talking about magic
Chan.
She's attentive enough to talk about the podron and call it by its proper name.
The fact that enough care was put into it, enough consideration was given that she learned
the word podron and used it is like, oh, that fucking is like success, mission accomplished,
we got her.
By the way, Ben, so Chris was on your case, and okay, I loved some of these tweets about
like, hey everyone, just letting everyone know that it's also ugly is going to be financing
this expansion.
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
Incredible.
And everyone will love the fact that Ben is going to be paying for it.
I love that fact.
I really do.
Why would anyone else care about that?
I could not be going to put that social pressure on you, Ben, you know?
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
That's what it is.
It's like, it is like a weird like sort of like social bullying kind of thing.
It's like, well, now I got it, now I got it, because she said I will.
I think that was the intent on Ironclash.
It's absolutely, absolutely that was the intent.
Okay, but be amazing.
So, not only is Chris literally like kind of extorting you for this money, but also
like talk about, in a way, in a way, not exactly, but they're whatever.
Any normal person did this, we'd be like, well, this is fucked up.
What the hell?
But like beyond that, Chris is getting on your case for using her OCs and like, you
know, cloud chasing and whatnot, and yet is making, is using phantom horn and strawberry
milk and endless war rampantly in her own work.
I mean, the hypocrisy is off the fucking charts here.
She literally, you know, that's funny.
I didn't even consider like, it's actually even worse than it sounds, because she
literally does the exact same thing.
Exactly the same.
That she demands that I pay her for, like we both do the same thing to each other.
And then she says, okay, well, now you have to pay me for both things.
It's, you have to pay, you should pay me.
MagiChan literally says, the two reasons are, like one, because Chris made the cards, you
should pay her.
And also because you use the characters, you should pay her.
Yeah, exactly.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You're you, and then Chris is using the setting, you should pay her.
You know what it is?
I feel a little bad because I know, and I have had interactions with these people, there
are some like, there are some real, there are some real fucking like weird kids or something
that like, Chris thinks are her friends that are like, and like, this is, this is their
influence, I think, like I think, I think some people that Chris, that have tricked Chris
into thinking they are her friends, they're definitely not, they're very, very not, very
much not, I'm sure.
But I don't know, I think these people are telling her to do this.
So I'm maybe not as mad as I would be.
I feel like, I mean, she shouldn't do this, but also someone else is telling her to, I
don't know.
It sucks, and I don't like it, but there's nothing I can do.
If I, honestly, I wish I could get rid of these people, like literally for Chris' sake,
I wish I could get rid of these, I don't know, weird pseudo trolls slash white, and I don't
know, a lot of them seem to be pretty, they're either like really, they might be kind of
sick people themselves, honestly, like they seem unhinged.
Just on that one grilling of you on that live stream doesn't speak too highly.
I think it's like they put themselves forward as if they were white knights, but clearly
some of them have ulterior motives that just like fucking with Chris, but they sort of
shield themselves with people who do care about Chris.
I think a couple of them genuinely think that they do, like there was that one girl who
seemed genuine, and then all the other ones were just like, yeah, make it interesting
though, yeah.
Yeah, that one.
Hey, we're gonna dox you, hey, give us your, give us your, give us your, send, you better
send Chris all the money from whatever, from the comic that you're putting for free on
Twitter.
Indeed.
And then, I don't know, just, and there's like, there's like a weird little cabal of
people that are all associated with this person who is like sort of Chris' internet boyfriend
or something, and they all seem like, there's something wrong with them, I don't know what's
going on, I don't like, I don't like thinking about them, and I don't care, like to me the
least interesting part of the Chris thing is like the real life antics, like my favorite,
my favorite Chris stuff was Alec Benson Leary who made Asperchu, and which was, you know,
which was like a comic, and, and, and liquid Chris, which was basically just like an extended
role play thing, like these, this was like, these were like fake, these were basically
like fake story arcs that people just invented, and that's just like, that's so much more
interesting to me than like, I don't know, what if we made Chris shove the medallion up
her ass?
Yeah, like that's fucking lame.
Or like destroy their PS4, PS3 or whatever was, I mean, there's a certain amount of hilarity
in there.
Oh, okay, well, I mean, that was a little funny.
I mean, yeah, when, when, when you get Chris to do something herself, that, that, like
that's what's funny, and, and the, the, I don't know, I don't, I don't, I don't care about
that stuff.
I kind of like that to think about it, but I guess it's, I guess it's all interwoven
now.
Some people have compared, like me and the, and the Nightstar comic to like Alec Benson
Leary and Asperchu, which I'm flattered by that, because that's, that was a good arc.
I would, I would, if I were, if I were, if I were, if I were, if I were remembered in
Crystery as another Alec Benson Leary, I would say Mission Accomplished, great job.
I did everything I wanted to do out, that was a good, it was a good arc, boys.
Yeah.
Anyway, so that's, feel a little bad, feel a little bad for Chris being manipulated,
but also like fucking, get the fuck out of here, this $300 bullshit.
I mean, well, we all know Chris is not a perfect individual, many, many character, personality
flaws, et cetera, et cetera, but I mean, yeah, I feel bad for anybody who's being taken advantage
of.
I mean, I guess you could say that, like, your involvement makes you somewhat part of
that, but I mean, not, not, I don't think it's fair to give you the, the, you know,
I haven't done anything.
I haven't done anything wrong.
I'm adamant that everything I've done.
You've really only drawn a comic at the end of the day.
That's really, and yeah, it's involved with Chris and Chris is a long time ago.
I've just drawn a comic and if Chris's reaction to that involves some like weird psycho shit,
like I don't think that's on me.
I really don't.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe the criticism would just be like to get involved with Chris period and openly
invites these sorts of things and they're inevitable.
So there's, you know, some.
Victim blaming.
No, it's not.
Well, don't, you're blaming me.
The victim.
Uh, well.
How short was that skirt, Ben?
Perhaps you, uh, deserve.
Uh, good.
You know what?
Good point.
Okay.
Touche.
Um, boy.
What a fucking week.
Okay.
I think, I think that's everything.
How close are you to the end of Phantom Horon's comic?
That's a good question.
Well, we're in the sewers right now.
Uh, I'm not going to say exactly what's going to happen, but I think where it's probably
maybe two thirds.
I think I've been saying for a while that like it's almost done.
It's almost done.
Um, but it's, it's getting there.
It's, uh, I know.
Well, like acts one, two or three.
Where are we?
This is, uh, this is probably late act two.
Okay.
It's cool.
Yeah.
This is like, this is late act two.
Well, I'm very interested to see where it goes.
I'm not sure what it's going to be like, but it is interesting to note that like when
you're waiting for a Ben, uh, you know, like Vapors chapter, it's like, uh, Skeleton sitting
at computer waiting for the update.
But with this, it's like, every fucking day, there's like, basically every, basically every
fucking day.
Yeah, it's great.
It's, it's wonderful.
Well, I think it just speaks to the nature of the distribution of the product.
You know, when you're working on the Vapors, you get no short term, uh, response.
But with this, you're getting feedback and like engagement every day.
It's got to be addicting.
I mean, just a positive feedback cycle of, you know, people, plus you're contributing
to something bigger than your own work, something that you've been following religiously for
years.
Yeah.
And like this.
There's like, I'm getting constant feedback about it.
It feels really good.
And also the sense that like I need to strike while the iron is hot on this.
Yeah.
If I, if I left it, it would be a big missed opportunity to let this go cold.
So it's, um, and also I'm just really excited to, cause I have a really, I have a really
an ending in mind for it that I really like.
And it's just a, a story that I really want to be out there in the world.
I'm just saying, Ben, wouldn't it be amazing if at the end of this, you also somehow in
another way released this in some physical medium that one could put next to your other
Ben words.
I'm thinking about it.
And at some point, I would love that all the custodians would buy a copy.
It's Christian.
At some point, that's, that's when you'd have to give Chris a $300.
Oh, he's right.
He's right.
I mean, it's like 120 or 140 pages long at this point.
So, well, like pages, I mean, panels, right, right.
But you know, Twitter size images, but like, yeah, no, it's long enough to be like a little
mini book.
So, um, yeah, honestly, at some point, I think I probably will do that.
Ooh, I look forward to it.
I want that too.
Yeah.
I've been thinking of like the potential like, and maybe when I do, maybe, maybe like
I make a bunch of money off and then I'll maybe I'll send, I'll send Chris $300.
You are using his OCs.
I did.
I did you.
I did use your OC in this.
I did do that.
And as a show of goodwill, here, here you go.
Here you go, friends.
I've been thinking myself about like making like book comic things and like whether Bale
Jap would, would work because there's a lot of panels in that, there's a lot of text.
It would work probably the same as like, uh, like a problem sleuth where the gifts would
be just, you, you, Dave wouldn't be animated a series of images, but like that's technically
possible.
For sure.
But I don't really feel like, I don't really feel like getting into another Kickstarter
before like, I know like the viewer base is big enough, at least the finished project
though.
I mean, you know, it already exists.
It's just a matter of do enough people want it to be on print and willing to buy.
Maybe like when you finish like the next work or whatever, or have that started, that'd
be a good time.
Well, give, you don't even need to run a Kickstarter.
You could just put it on like KDP on Amazon and just have it be a print on demand book.
And if people want it, they buy it.
Is that a thing?
Yeah.
Now that's what we're looking into.
Like I would design the entire like PDF of it or whatever and then you just upload it
and people order it, they buy it.
How did it all work with like covers and then hardback and paperback and the size of the
book?
They have like, you know, they have templates and you download and you format the templates,
the book to the templates and stuff.
I mean, people self publish all the time.
That's how it works.
You just upload it and people can buy it.
That's our, I'll look into that.
What was it called again, Tom?
It's just on Amazon.
You just go to Amazon Kindle Direct Publishing and you can do whatever the fuck you want.
And then you're on Amazon.
So could you do that with like a fully like illustrated?
Yeah.
People publish comics through Amazon all the time.
Okay.
Man, I wonder if like, because I have given absolutely no care at all to like color formatting.
It's all just, there's a gradients all over the place.
I feel like, I feel like physical printing would probably run into problems with the
colors on a lot of my pages.
I mean, Amazon has decent quality.
I mean, it's going to be easier to print through Amazon that would be to like busting
out a laser printer yourself and like grinding through it, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, probably.
So yeah, I had thought about this.
Like, I'm like, this is like, this is like approaching book length almost.
And yeah.
I definitely like the idea of having physical comics.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Like manga collection, Lane, there's too many of those, like too many volumes for
each manga.
Like comic book collection is just the coolest thing ever.
The only comic series I really want to own is One Piece.
Other than that, just to have it all there to look at and appreciate.
But other than that, like I just kind of want stuff that like has particular value, like
all year guys' work I would love to have and, you know, that kind of stuff.
I mean, I wouldn't want to collect like huge series of stuff, because then it becomes like
unmanageable.
But like, if there's like one to five volumes of something that I really care about, like
that's fucking sick to just have on the shelf.
Indeed.
Oh yeah.
Speaking of that sort of stuff, I recently just purchased the original black and white
Scott Pilgrim volume one to six box because I have just finished reading it for the first
time.
Really?
Yeah.
You never read the whole thing?
What'd you think?
I did not.
I always meant to.
Never got around to it.
It's pretty solid.
It's really good.
I like something like it like seeing the movie and knowing that it's cool and stuff.
I always felt like I should, but I'd never got around to reading it.
But it's it's surprisingly like, I was not surprisingly way better in terms of a lot
of things.
It's different.
The movie's good.
But like so much of like how the story is structured with all of the seven or something
evil exes and the amount of like the volumes are all like each is a self contained like
part of the narrative.
It deals with a different aspect of romance with Ramona and the evil exes related to that
and everything that happens in that volume is related to that sort of thing, that sort
of problem.
And it's like, it's really clean.
It's very clean as they say.
It is very clean.
So there is, I did reread it a couple of years ago and I was struck with the feeling
of like, yeah, a lot of this stuff in the middle.
I can see why they didn't make it in the movie.
I feel like it's a little bloated in the middle.
Like in the one that sticks out in my mind is the, okay, you know, there's the vegan
guy Todd, right?
Is it the vegan guy?
In the manga, there's like an extended sequence in like the third or fourth book or something
where like they, they had the part of their battle is they have to do like a race through
this one Canadian like chain store and like the challenge is that they keep being blinded
by all the deals.
Okay.
That's funny.
It's like, oh yeah.
I didn't understand that.
No.
Yeah.
You'd have to be, it's just like a really stupid joke that only a Canadian would find funny.
And even then I think they would probably, it seems a little eye rolly.
I don't know.
It's funny that it's there.
It's like, it's a little charming that it's there, but also like, I can see why they skip
this.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a lot of like stuff in like the middle.
There's a lot of like extraneous other characters that come in that are like really tangential
and tertiary.
I mean, I can't think of too many that are like pointless.
Like that thing with Todd in the supermarket was like pretty pointless, but like.
There's like other girls that show up.
There's like another, like Scott's old classmate shows up and he like wants to fuck her for
a while, but she just goes away later.
Yeah.
But she plays into like the thing that he's dealing with with Ramona at that point is sort
of like a, like a rejecting her, like staying true to Ramona was like a thing that allowed
him to do.
I can't exactly remember.
Yeah.
I don't either.
Like I can't analyze it off the top of my head, but I felt like that it was all like
properly put there.
Like it was very deliberate, very goodly done, but most mostly what I really love about Scott
Pilgrim is just sort of like, yeah, why not like feeling to everything?
Yeah.
That's true.
It has a lot of attitude.
It has like a just a really good fun attitude to the way that it's just like, it's great
and it's like reserved.
It's reserved in the fact that it doesn't go ridiculous and it only goes ridiculous in
the places where it would be like most, you know, beneficial emotionally for the reader
to, for it to go that ridiculous, like near the end and all that.
It's just, you know, it can do anything, but it doesn't do everything, which is great.
I just, I just really appreciate it.
It's an instant classic.
Obviously, lots of people already knew this, but I, I finally, I finally read it.
And if you saw my Twitter, I drew alley-oop in the style of Scott Pilgrim and people like
that.
The debate rages on about whether the black and white versions versus the color versions.
And a lot of people say that the color adds a lot, which seems to be, it seems like it's
a pretty high quality coloration, but the fact that the black and white was the way
it was originally published, just, I don't know, it gives it a sense of like, this was
how this was, this was what, like historically, this is the work that got popular and then
it was changed later and given color.
And just something about the fact that like this was the product as originally delivered
that had that impact, that made that impact, that became what it eventually did, just gives
it like an inherent value to me.
Same with like one piece, which has a colored version that exists out there, but we all
know that the black and white was the, it's, it's hard to imagine because I, I, I read
it like illegally on illegal.com and I saw the color version first.
I read all that, but I decided to buy color version online, like, uh, I don't know how
good it is in print, but like the scans or like the, the PDF, whatever it is, it's perfect.
It's really, really good.
I mean, like perfect quality, but like, um, the coloration is like, it's really good.
Like I can't imagine it having no color.
And so that's why I'm buying, I'm buying like the physical, uh, colorless one so I can read
it differently.
And you know, Ben, on the subject, I actually gotten probably cost a lot less to, it probably
true.
Yeah.
Each color one is like 26, like, uh, buckaroos, but like the black and white is like 15 for
the whole set.
So I definitely get in that.
That's, uh, that, that's fucking, that's good value right there.
Yeah, for sure.
Indeed.
Uh, so yesterday on my stream, uh, somebody asked me a question that was like, we were
talking about like subs versus dubs a little bit and I, I like, I had made a point in my
last we Agua that was like, whenever something exists that is like the original, but like,
okay, you got your traditional, you got your anime, obviously it's in Japanese first.
Um, my, my thing I want to do, I don't hate all dubs, but I always will want to hear it
in the original version first.
That will be my preference, all things considered, because it's obviously going to be the closest
to like the base artistic, you know, vision of the creators who are Japanese, even something
like, like space dandy, for example, was simultaneously produced in Japanese and English at the same
time and released that way.
But nonetheless, by knowing the fact that the guys like are Japanese who made the show,
that just makes my brain think that the Japanese one is like, there's things that translate.
It's kind of hard to capture everything in Japanese and English and like cultural differences.
I mean, if the dialogue was written by a Japanese writer, then I guess you could say that like,
even if it was simultaneously produced, you know, it was still like written in, in Japanese.
It's just like the time it was, which I imagine it was.
I feel like though, like space dandy is one of the, the closest it comes to have the English
version just being like almost better, like, like it's at least equal.
I did like the dub of space dandy a lot.
And like, if there's a choice, I mean with language, it's different from like color versus
non color.
Experience whatever I feel like, and that'll be my initial one.
And then I can make a judgment later.
I don't have like a preference for what was originally intended necessarily.
But with language, I guess I, I don't really have a, I guess it's just usually whatever
I click on first.
I was watching Karakana and I initially started watching the dub just because like, you know,
maybe it's good, I don't know.
But the, the, the boys like character voice was like super deep and like chocolatey and
like that didn't fit as like character design at all.
It was like too old, like, like a 34 year old man and like a teenager's body didn't work.
So I switched to Japanese and it was immediately incredible.
So like, I always like to do a little bit of testing the waters because I, I don't assume
all dubs are worse.
So I might try them, but sometimes I just forget to try them.
I just, I, I want to get the original version.
I don't know.
I already said something about that.
Yeah, I need to.
I feel like I'm getting, when you watch the original original, it feels like you're getting
the historical context in a way that you're not getting as much with like an adaptation
or a translation or a remaster or whatever.
That were both released simultaneously.
Oh, I mean that, yeah, then I think you, well, you know, that's, that's closer to the original.
You know, there's a thing with that because like with video games, remasters and emulation
and remakes and stuff, I would generally like them, the earliest version of the thing, but
I think realistically in the, in the, in the ways that as like consoles break down and nobody's
making these old consoles anymore, these old games on these old hardware is going to be harder
and harder and much more expensive over time to play.
And so it's like,
Like an emulation.
Yeah, but that's the thing.
And emulation is not always the same as how it plays on the original hardware on like a
CRT television and stuff.
Like it's designed for that kind of television.
It's designed to be played in a certain way with certain hardware.
And if you don't, if you can't get the hardware, you may as well just judge it based on how
emulatable, like how the emulation works, because getting all of that stuff, like if you,
I mean, I was thinking about this when I used to review things.
What is the purpose of reviewing the original version of something when somebody would need
to like invest so much money in order to play it properly?
When there's the emulation, there's like worse.
So like, do you review that as the game or do you not, or do you review both?
You know, it was a fascinating example that did you once brought up years ago,
which was that during design of games for the Game Boy Advance, I don't know if he knew this
for sure, but it seemed to be his impression that like when designing for the Game Boy Advance,
which did not have an inherent backlight or anything, they deliberately seemed to
artistically choose really bright colors for the games that they were designing,
because they had to make up for the fact that there was no backlight and they were playing
with like, you know, whatever light was in the area.
So brighter colors and whatnot would stick out more and be easier to register on the screen.
And now if you're just playing that on an emulation on your fucking TV,
it can look like fucking neon crazy shit.
I mean, sometimes it's a little too much.
I'm so used to how Fire Emblem seven and eight look on my Game Boy Advance
SP with the little weak backlight that had.
And then emulating it is like, it's too vibrant.
It feels like a different game or like a lower quality version of the same game,
where like you just up the contrast and now like there's no nuance in the colors,
even though, you know, the original is the emulation.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, that even happened during the Game Boy Advance's lifetime itself,
because you had the original Advance, which had no backlight.
Then you had the first SP, which had the side light, like the side lit screen.
So kind of wash the colors out.
But then they released the actual backlight version, which changed everything again.
And then that was like super saturated.
Which one was the folding one?
Like the laptop one?
That was the SP.
But like they released two versions of it.
They released another one that had an actual backlight.
Oh, I didn't know.
And that like because it was backlit, it was way more saturated the colors.
And it looked like super over.
I think I have the side light SP because.
If you can turn the light off and still play it, it's the side light one.
Maybe not.
With the actual backlight, you turn it off and the whole screen turns black.
Game Boy Advance SP, little laptop, adorable case, folded up.
Backlight for the first time ever.
Oh my God.
And essentially a fucking charging cable so you can play forever and never have to stop.
The SP was a life changer.
What a revolution.
Like the best thing in the world.
Incredible.
I can now play under my covers with the lights off, except my Game Boy.
Oh, I used to do that all the time.
Fucking based.
Same here.
How many of you.
I wondered why I was so tired.
How many of you with that Game Boy Advance SP power would hide it from your parents by
closing the screen, saying, good night, I'm going to bed now.
I'm going to be asleep.
Oh, of course.
Then you turn it back and flip it back open.
Love that.
Yeah, those.
Those fools, those naive fools.
They didn't understand technology and I did.
I am the new generation.
Exactly.
Yep.
You didn't.
There's a literal intellectual stratification going on between you and your parents at this time.
They couldn't even comprehend what was going on before their eyes.
My parents grew up playing fucking Pong.
Pong came out like the first shoot ever on my mom's when she was a kid.
And now we got fucking SP.
Now we got Pong too.
Insane.
Yeah.
Now we got Pong too.
There's no going back.
He's being a Pong.
I saw, you guys know the channel Ahoy?
Nope.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Okay.
It's a really weird channel and it has like two or three really good videos and one is on the
history of Polybius, you know, like the fake video game.
Yeah.
I know that.
I don't know.
And they just released another or this guy.
I think it's just one guy or maybe he's got a team.
I don't know.
He released another one about like what's the first video game.
And it's like, you know, he goes like space war for some computer.
That's there's it kind of tennis for two, right?
Tennis for two on the yeah.
He talks about all these.
There's there's a couple other ones that are like contenders that I had never heard of.
It's good.
I really like these two like history videos are great.
The rest of his channel is dog shit.
It's amazing.
Like really?
These videos are really well researched, well written, well produced, great content.
The vast majority of his channel is complete shit.
It is like.
How so?
It's like he'll it'll all be some of them are talking about a specific game and some of them
are talking about he has tons of videos that are just a like exploration of a of like a
particular weapon like a specific like the talk about the rocket launcher.
And he'll just talk about like every game that's ever had a rocket launcher in it.
So I guess like the history of the rocket launcher, the history of the AR 15, the history.
They get a lot of views.
I'm seeing like millions of views.
They get millions of views.
They suck.
They're so bad.
I've seen a couple of them and it's okay.
And it's just why are they bad?
They're bad because I tried watching some and they all feel like I'm not learned.
It's not really learned.
Like maybe he'll talk a little bit about the gun itself.
It's like I don't really care about that.
But like fair enough, that's relevant to the subject.
But like then he'll go through, he'll elaborate about the gun each and it's literally just like
it just feels like each one is just like a five second blurb where he like talks about like
in this game, this gun is really good.
And here's like, in this game, this gun really gives you a fucking punch for your money, bro.
But in this game, it really was felt like the dog shit and was bad.
And this one, it really captured the way that the fucking bullet comes out fast and makes you go, ah!
I hate, I was so amazed by the disparity in quality between these two videos that I love
and everything else he has, which I hate.
Those strange like 107 facts videos where the number of facts dilutes the
interestingness of every fact.
Yes, yes, you watch, like you start one of these videos and it's like
two minutes into the actual knowledge, you're like, I'm over it.
I'm so over it.
I don't need to hear anymore.
No more, please.
I noticed that this guy went seven months without a video since this new video game
one just came out two days ago.
Well, I mean, I hope that means he's pivoting towards making stuff like this,
because like this and the Polybius video are really great videos.
Super good.
The Polybius one is like, I've watched it like four times.
It's excellent.
Damn, it's an hour, eight minutes long.
All right, well shit, I gotta check that out.
Link in the description.
That reminds me a little, you know, the guy I talked about who is crossing Wales,
the country, the country Wales is not a whale.
Yes.
He crossed it in a straight line, you know, he finished that series,
but the rest of his channel had up to that point been GeoGuessr videos.
And, you know, like, basically he goes into a thing and he's like, hmm, well,
you know, he's very good at GeoGuessr.
He can guess the countries pretty accurately by looking around.
What is GeoGuessr?
It's a Google Maps based game where it plops you in a random location
and you have to look around for a bit and then guess where you are in the world.
And you can use like road signs and like language things and like environmental clues,
like figure out where you are.
And he's very good at it, but they're very boring.
They're just the sort of like, it's a let's play show.
And it's like, if you don't really care about it.
Yeah, you know, like doesn't sound gripping.
So like he does that and then he does this walk across Wales video.
Most incredible video series on YouTube this year or like the last five years probably.
And then he's finished.
And then he goes back to GeoGuessr videos and like obviously nobody cares.
Like you could gain so many subscribers and they all are like me included.
And we're like, oh, what a shame.
Can you do that thing?
You thought you'd found a big well of new content and then you dive into it and you're like,
like maybe he may in the future do.
I mean, he's talked about doing another one.
It'll probably be like four years or something.
And then, oh, there it is.
I don't want to watch these videos in the meantime though.
But you know, I guess he has to make money.
I just, you know, that's probably how most people feel about my channel
and how it's got the two lectures that they like.
And then all of a sudden like Pokemon Nuzlocke bullshit.
Yeah, I imagine someone makes these incredible life changing anime reviews.
Then they just churn out these shitty vlogs every week.
I mean, geez, what a disappointment that would be.
I mean, I get the feeling because I feel that way about Ahoy
and I'm sure people feel that way about me.
And I don't know, what are you going to do?
Yeah, yeah, what are you going to find out?
That's all.
You separate your content, separate the content into different channels
so people can subscribe to one or the other.
But YouTube doesn't like you to do that.
So they punish you for doing it.
Yeah, they sure do.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, what good does it even do to have a channel?
I mean, I guess it's easy.
But like if you have it, let's say you have a channel where you just post
like these amazing walk across the world videos and everybody loves them.
But you only post once every year, maybe?
I don't know.
Is that good?
Is that better?
I don't know.
It's obviously not better for him as like a business.
He, you know, reaps an audience.
I mean, people are very, very used to a content creator existing only
if they upload every day.
And if they don't upload every day, the people forget that they exist.
And they're like, oh my god, you're alive?
Like, lol, that was a joke a while back.
People still say that.
They do.
And it's, I mean, it's what they really feel.
Like you basically are dead to them if you stop posting for more than like two weeks.
And I've always, I've ever since like this happened to Igoraptor way back where like
animations were taking a long time to come out.
People would go to his like comment section, like on his channel
and just complain that he wasn't uploading frequently enough and they would unsubscribe.
And I never understood-
Oh, how we paid for that mistake.
I never understood the, like the problem there because if you're subscribed to something,
it's not like that you're paying money.
It's not like you're doing anything.
You just said, I'd like to see the next thing that comes out.
And if it takes a while to come out, then you'll be notified for it later.
Then you would maybe hope.
But like, why would you unsubscribe?
They put in the hard work of clicking subscribe because it's not putting out content fast enough.
But if the, yeah, but if the content that it is putting out, even if it's infrequent,
like if it's still stuff you like, you don't lose anything by being subscribed to a channel.
I mean, I don't think people do that anymore.
But like the way YouTube works now, it definitely plays into that because
you're just, you're just nothing.
You're nothing.
You have no money if you don't post every single second.
Yeah, you gotta, I mean, you should be posting daily.
Everybody should be.
Like that's the ideal way to do it, which is disgusting.
But what are you going to do?
I put a one second video every day of like-
You just, you just got to like make an update video every day.
Just you basically just have to become like a life blogger.
Just be like, yeah, I'm just going to vlog my entire-
All right, here's my new project.
I'm going to record-
You have to be a new storyteller.
I have to, I'm going to record a 365 second long video.
Oh yeah.
And every day for one second of that video will be uploaded.
That's a good idea.
You know, literally you should make a new channel and do that and like see how it does,
you know, like see if people are interested in-
What if it just algorithmically crushes?
Like who knows?
It could, it could.
There are other things that don't seem like they're going to be-
I mean, there's no watch time because like I'm not going to get anything from it.
I guess that's true.
Like 17 million videos and a one second video is like-
You'll just, you'll just please the algorithm.
It'll just be like, it'll just be like a sun offering-
Please just punch.
The algorithm to favor you.
Just think about this.
What if before, forget the watch time.
What if before all those watches, if it gets a lot, you, you have just one ad,
you know, just one ad before it.
Financially, I mean, it could do well.
It posts every day.
You have like a 15 second ad before each of your one second videos.
Exactly, exactly.
Why not?
And an ad afterward.
Yeah, and then no, you have a one second of the video and you go,
hey guys, thanks for watching.
This video is sponsored by Skillshare.
It'd just be like, hey guys, thanks for watching.
Oh, I mean, it's a really funny idea.
I wish someone would do it.
If, if not you-
I mean, I may as well.
Why not?
Like who gives a shit?
Yeah, you should.
Take a day and schedule them all.
Put them up on, I don't know, some, some monetized channel.
I'll just put it up on Gibbentake.
Oh, actually, that's not, that's-
Gibbentake 2020.
Gibbentake is like completely demonetized forever,
so I can't do anything on there.
What?
Yeah.
Why?
Why is that?
I don't know.
I, I appealed it twice and just said no.
So like, I don't know why.
Obviously they didn't tell me.
I think I've explained this on the PCB before.
It's got it.
It's just sort of like fucked.
So I can't put it on there.
Maybe it's like-
They really didn't like your My Little Pipe.
Yeah, that's probably it really.
It's just like-
Clopping is not okay, Gibb, and you need to learn.
Oh, no, you're right.
Whoops.
That's not family-friendly content.
I do, I do have a few videos where I say fuck.
At, even in the title.
Are you crazy?
Including this one where I just said fuck.
I don't, I don't, I don't pretend.
I don't pretend to understand how the algorithm works.
It's beyond me.
Me either.
It's praise be.
All right.
Bullshit meta art piece YouTube things.
I remember Jay Bauman had a YouTube channel,
or still does under his name.
All the thumbnails and titles are him talking about something or other.
But then the content of the video is just a static shot of a candle and a book.
It's just they're completely out of order,
all these different puzzle piece videos.
You click on a new one,
you think it's going to be Jay Bauman talking about something.
And it's no, it's more footage of the candle flickering
and the wax melting slowly for like 20 minutes.
And there's nothing, I don't get it, but it's cool.
It's-
Is it the thumbnails?
Are the thumbnails a joke of some kind, perhaps?
Well, I think the joke is that you think that this is just some sort of stupid video bullshit thing.
And it's even funnier than that.
It's nothing.
It's just nothing.
Perfect.
It's just what I want.
Imagine that.
Yeah, it's kind of cool.
I remember looking at that and wondering what the heck the deal was, but it's good.
Just his sense of humor.
All right.
Well, we could just get to the voicemails now if you want.
I have something I want to bring up, but it is in the voicemails,
so we will get to it inevitably in time.
Wasn't there- Tom, didn't you have something that happened?
He did, Ben, but that's within the voicemail.
It's the same thing I wanted to discuss, and we will get-
I will say that I'm working on DevTober.
It's going great.
I posted a video showing the work in progress of the boss fight.
It's great.
Give me money so I can keep making the game.
I also added a new thing to my Patreon yesterday where I'm going to have rants for a dollar.
So you can listen to me rant about shit for a dollar.
Wow.
You know, I also, incidentally, added something similar to mine,
which is just if people pay five dollars in my monthly video or whatever,
if you're at the $10 one, then I will also just answer whatever fucking question you want.
So there you go.
We were both had the similar of one month.
So I have the $5 podcast where people can request topics for podcasts,
and then for $1 you get rants, which nobody gives me questions for.
I just do it whenever I get mad at something.
Because I'm too much of a bitch to put them on Twitter and get the blowback.
I don't want to deal with it.
So I just put them on Patreon instead.
Yeah, makes sense.
It's great.
So, yeah.
Those people are already invested in that.
Those people will give you the benefit of the doubt.
Exactly.
I can have a conversation with people who don't want me to die.
In fact, they want me to live.
Hence, they give me money.
Rare, rare privilege.
Indeed.
I have also been doing monthtober,
which is where you do something every day for a month during October.
So I've been drawing.
It's the same as last month, basically.
Yeah, it's doing the draw streams and stuff.
Are you still doing the streams daily?
Is that still a daily thing?
Yeah, every weekday I do a stream to a wrapped audience of seven.
And that's pretty cool.
Well, I mean, the end result is these noir red man comics, which...
Boy, I've got fucking excited when I saw those.
I saw those on your Twitter.
I was like, oh my...
Okay.
Yeah.
You're going to make more?
I'm going to maybe make one tonight.
Because I haven't thought of an idea for today what I'm going to draw,
but the more red man is good.
I'm going to be...
I'll probably continue streaming myself drawing more of the Phantom Horn comic,
because that's pretty good.
I think people like that.
Pretty epic.
Maybe I'll get trolled some more.
You never know.
God, I hope so.
God, I wish that were me.
All right.
Well, let's do it.
Let's go to the voicemails.
We got them right here.
Speakpipe, people, link down below.
Speakpipe, link, whatever.
Leave us voicemails.
And I've got to say, so we're getting there a little bit early today,
because there's just a fucking bunch of them.
And they've been of higher quality, and they are good, and I enjoy them.
I'll be the judge of that.
So we'll spend a little longer.
Yeah, well, you can let me know if that's true or not.
Oh, I think there was one.
This is like the classic pre-real start of the voicemails.
This is just kind of a life update one.
So let's see what the PCP Shadow Puppet Master has for us today.
All right, get to it.
Go.
Okay.
Secretly, I am the PCP Shadow Puppet Master.
You may not realize it.
I might sound familiar, but here's the thing.
I originally submitted a voicemail a few weeks back, calling for more voicemails.
And what happens?
That's not true.
More voicemails come in.
That's kind of strange coincidence.
It might I say the quality of them has been higher.
I knew you could do it, PCP audience.
I am grateful for you because I too have submitted many fucking voicemails that have
all gotten in.
Okay.
This is what is up.
If you guys have noticed that quality increase of voicemails,
you might want to thank me, PCP Shadow Puppet.
Master.
Well, there you go.
Like I said, thanks for all the voicemails.
My dude, you did.
I don't know if he's the PCP Puppet Master.
He's more like the voicemail.
He's the PCP audience master pulling their strings and yanking their chain.
Pulling the strings that connect to his own arms and legs.
And their vocal cords to elicit dulcet tones for us to respond to here.
Let's thank you Shadow Master.
Let's get the next one.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Next one is from BradoSanDakoku.
Okay.
Great.
Go.
Like what the hell bros?
So like there's this chick, right?
And I said that she was fat, but I still fuck her.
Right?
I'm like, she got some piss at me.
Like what the hell is her problem, bros?
I need some opinions on this, especially of mages on.
Like is this a compliment or an insult?
I mean, I'm pretty sure it was a compliment.
Yeah, no, no, for sure.
It's a very, no, it's a very funny insult.
And I think you should continue to do it.
It's yielding results already.
So just stay the course I say.
We got a great voicemail out of it.
So we all had a lot of laughs.
Keep it up.
Keep up the good work, my dude.
Yeah.
I have no further commentary.
I'm gonna stay the course.
The problem is clearly with the children, not with you.
No, it's the children that are wrong.
Well, there you go.
That's all there is to it.
Excellent work.
This is great, by the way.
These are great.
Okay, no, no.
Get ready for this.
Because we've got an actual five-star chef,
not a joke on why we're all wrong culling in.
So, okay, let's hear it.
Sweetest chef.
Okay, what's up?
I'm a real actual five-star chef.
I've worked in a couple of famous hotels,
like the Jefferson and Richmond, Virginia,
and the Omni in Charlottesville.
I'm a culinary school grad,
and while I was there,
I cooked with a bunch of celebrity chefs,
including Guy Fieri, oddly enough.
Jesus Christ.
I'm here to settle the score on Hello Fresh.
Here's it.
Here's it in a nutshell.
Ben is both correct and a massive retard.
Nate is just a retard.
Munchy is a little baby boy,
so he gets a pass, but he's wrong.
I made it at the best.
What I think Ben is trying to say
is that the biggest problem with Hello Fresh
and those Amazon ready meals or whatever they're called
is that they teach you recipes and not techniques.
And in order to be a good cook,
recipes are literally not worth the paper they're printed on
because they don't teach you things like knife skills,
searing, sauteing, blanching, flavor bases,
how to season things properly.
So here's the difference between you and me.
We could both be given one of those ready meals
with the same instructions,
the same pots, pans, and stove to cook it on,
and mine will come out better 100% of the time.
And that is because I know these foundational things.
So if you want to learn those,
you need to check out Tim Ferriss as the four-hour chef.
Tim Ferriss is a guy who wanted to be a post-food boy
and hated cooking and decided the best way to do that
was to master cooking.
So it's written for people exactly like you.
So yeah, learn some techniques.
Peace.
Sounds really cool.
And that was a quality voicemail.
Yeah.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
It's almost like when someone has experience,
they can speak on a subject with some sense of intelligence.
I'll put that...
It's very rare on these parts.
I'll put that guy in a voicemail for dropping genuine...
Any of voicemail?
Am I crazy?
Oh, come on.
I didn't even get one giggle, one goofle out of that.
I learned...
But I gained knowledge.
I gained...
We didn't do the category.
It's the voice braille.
It's not the voice comedy award.
I disagree with the distinction.
The distinction without a difference.
I definitely agree with him, by the way.
From my dad, I've learned a lot of cooking techniques.
And so I know what you're supposed to do with steaks
and when you're frying and how to do this and that,
and how to chop onions properly.
But I don't know any recipes at all.
But when I Google something, it works out.
So...
That's all you need.
Now, okay.
Sure.
See, I agree with his point.
But I will say, I will say,
that I think he's coming from a different perspective.
Yeah, a perspective of knowledge, as opposed to ignorance.
Okay, because here's who I am.
Here's who I am.
I'm a poor orphan boy on the side of the road saying,
Papa, please, sir.
I need something that tastes at least kind of decent.
I'm dying of hunger.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Why is like a ready...
They were literally free.
They did not pay for it.
Well, this is important.
That is important for you.
That makes all the difference.
The voicemail guy did direct you to a book thing that would...
A resource that I'm sure you have.
That is from your perspective of a guy who wants to be post-food.
Intellectual elite, five-star chef coming on and saying,
like, Nate, you need to go to school for five, 10,000 years
before you can cook a meal.
That's not what he said.
So just die of hunger, Nate.
He said, read a book by Tim Ferriss.
Just die of hunger, Nate.
I'm hungry now.
No eating until you read this book.
I'm going to McDonald's.
And that's final.
I'm getting a Big Mac.
He also said you're a retard and you're proving it right now.
You keep getting McDonald's.
I'm going to have to kill you one of these days.
I'm just...
No, I'm for McDonald's.
I'm pro McDonald's.
McDonald's is one of the better.
McDonald's isn't even keto.
It is if you do it like me.
Dude, $3 for two McDoubles.
You just take the buns off.
And it's four beef patties for $3 and you just eat them.
And it's great.
It seems...
It's great.
Are they, like, good, though?
Yeah.
Like, those patties are kind of...
Honestly, I highly recommend it.
It's keto, keto, bonito.
Bringing it back to the first thing I said.
Bring it all the way back to the beginning.
All right, we're ending the podcast right here.
Good night, everybody.
All right, what's next?
Oh, oh, you know what?
There was another call from the five-star chef.
Now, I thought he was good.
I'm tempted to just skip it because it's...
Okay, it's the five-star chef one last time on why I subsist on...
Why I subsist Huell, which I think was a typo.
I think he meant, like, resist or something.
And I'm afraid this will bring his average quality of voicemail down.
But, okay, now I have to play it.
Yeah, I want to hear it.
I want to hear what he has to say.
All right, let's hear what he has to say.
Here's the second one.
Beware of the tipping point of cooking.
Once you reach it, you will never be able to eat out again.
Because even if the food tastes good,
you will always know that it could be better.
And as a result, it ruins the experience.
This is why it's a great way to become a post-food boy, however.
So, this is...
And another reason to bother to learn it
is when it comes to impressing dates, you're done.
You're set.
That's true.
Impressing your significant other.
You never have to buy a birthday present ever again.
You just make them standing rip roast with some fucking mashed potatoes
or some other shit like that.
Bitches love that shit.
Some rice pilaf and some salmon.
There you go.
You're never obligated to buy a present
or pay for an expensive dinner.
Literally ever again.
Well, I don't know about all that.
Bitches still want that diamond, that rock.
Just put a gold bar in the pie.
Yeah.
I love this idea of the best way to...
Like, if you hate cooking, if you want to be post-food,
you must acquire the knowledge necessary to defeat it.
I don't understand this point.
I love this.
What am I missing here?
It's like to be a post-food boy, you learn and you cook.
Because if you can't cook for yourself, then you are a slave.
You are a slave to others' ability to feed you, right?
To cook for you.
I think the difference here is that...
You no longer depend on others.
The more you understand food, the more freedom you have.
The more leeway you have in how much control...
Once you become a fucking elitist about it,
you're not just going to go down to McDonald's
and get your two McDoubles and just eat the four patties.
Because you're going to look at those patties
and see how disgusting they are compared to what you could do
with your own two hands.
So you'll get higher quality ingredients.
No, that will always be great value.
Value is one thing.
Quality is another thing in time.
Value is eternal.
Value is undeniable.
All right.
That sounds very capitalist of you, Ben.
I really feel like you could get an equivalent amount of meat
for less than going to McDonald's for it.
What's less?
You're saying that McDonald's is not valuable?
The four, whatever you said.
Two McDoubles for $3.
I feel like you could find an equivalent amount of meat
like of an equivalent.
I go to Walmart and I get 20 patties for $8.
So I'm pretty sure that's...
That's pretty good.
...that balances out much better.
Okay, I defy anyone to find a better keto deal than two McDoubles
for $3. Throw the patties away.
You just buy the meat from a butcher's.
I just said 20 for $8.
You buy the meat from a butcher's?
20 for the patties for $8.
But it's pre-cooked.
You don't have to cook it.
Okay, but we're talking...
That's part of the value you want to offer here
is that you don't have to prepare it.
Yeah.
Is that you just get it.
I suppose that's true.
I mean, okay.
If I have to get in my car, drive down to McDonald's, order the food,
spend the gas, take them apart and put them back together
versus buy them once and then just throw them in a pan.
Well, I'm with you in making the trip as a nightmare.
I feel like the scale at some point starts to balance in my favor.
Well, you know, we're not...
You're on the road and you're just McDonald's right now.
You just buy a cow and then you cut it in half
and then the other half grows back
and you can get another cow again.
You can do this all day and day.
Just take a bite out of your arm.
It'll grow back eventually.
All right, let's move on.
We've got a thank you five-star chef.
Are we putting them in the voice grail?
Put them in the voice kitchen.
Yeah, that's there.
There you go.
That's where he belongs.
Your honorary PCP cook.
All right, we got...
Where we can extract the most value from him.
Jade Murrow sounding dumb is the title of this.
I know.
Okay, Jade.
All right, Jade.
Sorry I haven't given you that script yet.
One of these days.
All right, go.
Seeing as you all are different ages,
how do you think you all would get along
in a timeline where you're all your 20-year-old selves?
Now, I thought this was an interesting question
because we have to age up, munchy,
and age down most of us and see like,
what's that going to be like?
What was I like at 20, you know?
We wouldn't get along...
Me and munchy wouldn't get along
because I would be dumber and he would be smarter
and then we wouldn't be on equal intellectual footing.
I mean, I was like...
I mean, this is before Nate's journey to the East,
you know, the famous story.
So, I was still a little bitch boy.
I mean, well, I was 20...
This is an incredibly difficult question
because you're talking about changing our ages,
but like, it's also like,
are we going back to like what we were at the time
or are we in present time now?
This is like, what if we are all of our 20-year-old selves?
Because we all have different levels of experience
at that age.
So, it's difficult to say.
I mean, I think munchy would just be bored all of us.
If we all grew up at the same time,
we would all probably be on similar levels
in terms of like cultural and like just ideas
because like we've all come to the same conclusions
as the culture has...
A 20-year-old munchy will still be in college.
He'll still be a nascent pupa of a nothing boy.
But he's done so much more than I did at 20.
He's done all these internet things that we've now done.
Right, but the reason he's done more things at 20
is because when we were 20,
all this stuff was just starting to emerge.
But I think we...
I think it's still fair to like give munchy that up
just because like it's...
He just started earlier than us.
He just did better earlier in life.
Right, he started earlier because the culture allowed you
to start earlier, became more of an accepted thing.
There is that aspect, but not everybody who is munchy's age
is like munchy.
So like munchy is exceptional even among his age bracket.
The thing that ties us all together right now
is that we all have similar value structures.
So if we were all the same age,
I feel like we all would still be pursuing
the same kind of things because those are reflective
of our values combined with our modern experience.
When I was 20, I thought I was going to go on
to get my like PhD in physics and become like a scientist.
I thought that was going to be like or become a professor,
I think was what I wanted.
But then it was as like the world continues,
like as things happen to you, right?
And you experience new things.
And look at me now, falling.
And that changed you into who you are today.
Yeah.
So like, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, it's complicated.
We get it, old man.
You're just trying to justify your decrepit body and soul.
I mean, yes, I guess, sure.
I'll cop to that.
Hey, well, how is the, what are you saying?
Like, how is that an argument against?
I mean, Tom's point is making a fair point that like we,
Munchie has had many advantages by simply existing
later in time than we would have had slightly earlier
because the development of, you know,
things like YouTube online businesses,
I mean, a 20 Patreon didn't exist.
What would the fuck would we have all been doing,
you know, without Patreon?
And Munchie will have that at 20.
That's okay.
According to my YouTube channel at 20,
I was like getting tired of the compilations
and I was thinking about making a pony analysis channel.
Okay.
So that's where I was.
Interesting.
Sad.
I was, I was a nothing man.
I was the nowhere man of being the same.
I was still in college and I was sad
and I was making comics and trying to get them self-published
and trying to, making my huge mistake
of networking with terrible people
and they're dragging me down.
And I swore off humans for like three years after that
until I got into MLP and realized that friendship was magic.
Oh, ironically, what happened?
Cramp.
Okay, it's fine.
No, don't worry about it.
All right.
Speaking of decrepit old man bodies,
a mere laugh drives back to the ground.
Can I tell you, I have a story about my decrepit old man body.
I've been feeling, I've been having, I've been suffering.
I've been just waking up or like, just like,
my back's been hurting, right?
I've just been like, and like, there's nothing I can do.
Like, no matter how I sit, it doesn't help.
I can lie down, it doesn't help.
It sucks.
And exercise help with this?
Not really.
I hate to tell you, but that's how my back problem started
and I'm getting surgery in two weeks.
Well, I mean, I discovered, well, I mean, who?
Yesterday, I discovered that like, it actually helps
if I just fucking like, jam my knuckles into my back
and just like roll it around.
That's probably a massage.
Yeah.
And I, yeah, I've spent my entire life
saying that massage is fake and a scam.
And so now, so now I found the solution
but I can't use it on principle.
Yeah, that's fair.
I've been thinking of going to a massage parlor,
just the idea of like, you know, seeing what it's like.
And then.
No, massage is fantastic.
I swear by it.
I don't do it nearly enough because I can't anymore
because if I lie down on my back for more than two minutes,
it breaks in half.
But before that, it was fantastic.
Huh.
I mean.
Interesting.
You know, when I was at Dom, maybe there's a little something to it.
At my, at my last job, you know, my programming job,
actually like once a year or so, fairly, there was like these
every week, there would be like on Wednesday,
there'd be like a get little take a break.
Everybody hang out and kind of like chill for a few minutes.
But, but really, you guys can get back to work.
You got things to do.
But as part of that, once every like six months or year or something,
they have like a masseuse in the area,
come to the place and give like little like 10 minute
promo massages of like what she could do at like her actual boutique.
So she would just come in and do like free massages.
She probably got paid by like the company or something.
But as a result, every once in a while,
you could just sign up for like a free short massage at my job.
And pretty, pretty, pretty sick.
Man, what'd you leave?
It's good.
I can't, I don't know.
Cause I'm an idiot.
You had it all.
He threw it away.
It was a, I mean, like I said,
I could have done that job the rest of my life
and been pretty happy.
And maybe I will when things don't go well on YouTube.
We'll see.
You know, when Ghost in the Shell finally comes out
and everybody turns up in here.
And nobody likes it.
Yeah.
Oops.
Well, there I go.
I'm the Ghost in the Shell of my YouTube career.
Oh, don't you know that show is made by white supremacists though?
And you're like, ah, damn.
Is that true?
Probably, right?
Statistically, it's likely.
I can't wait for next year, April, 2020,
when Ghost in the Shell finally comes out
and it's an April Fool's joke
and it's just Scarlett Johansson movie review.
And you prank everybody and everyone mass on subscribes.
Oh, would that be epic?
All right.
Let's, let's move on to our next question here.
Erdek's call.
This is from Autism Quantified.
And I think it's a little quiet.
Oh, Digi's calling him.
Yeah, indeed, indeed.
All right.
Let's, let's go here.
I heard there's a new way of categorizing autism.
My therapist cocks an eyebrow.
He says that I seem like a well-adjusted guy
and that there's surely nothing to worry about.
I respond that I like to make sure.
She nods and asks what kind of media I typically consume.
The usual, I say, I read and I'm quite partial to anime.
Her brow furrows.
The answer clearly concerns her.
She writes plus one on her notebook.
My neurotical divergence increases by six
and my communication stat plummets.
Do you have any hobbies like sports or languages?
Yeah, I'm learning a language.
Her face lights up.
Japanese, I add.
She winces and increases my score by one.
Conventional, I think, is increased by minus eight to three.
I also write fanfiction.
She skips straight to four.
My alcohol tolerance and degeneracy increase dramatically.
Two adder all appear in my inventory.
Oh, and I write for a dating son.
She seems more scared than anything now
than I'm on the notebook reads six.
I gain the ability to communicate through Pepe's
and lose the ability to communicate in any other way.
I elaborate that in the dating son,
you romance a group of niche account artists called the PCP.
She stutters that she doesn't know what comes after seven.
As I take the notebook, she gulps.
I write the number eight and rotate it by 90 degrees.
We both die instantly.
A happy ending.
Fuck, what was the last thing you said?
I missed it.
I think I should, like, everyone dies or we both combust or they die
is the implication.
Great.
Great storytelling on our own.
PCP is infinite autism.
That's pretty funny.
That was that was a great creepypasta voicemail.
Didn't see it coming.
The twist.
It literally sounds like Creeps McPasta
who does creepypasta narration, so.
I did that joke.
Great job, dude.
Sorry for you and your therapist lost, my dude.
Yikes, big yikes, big oof, effin' chat.
We'll see you next week.
See you right.
Next voicemail.
This is from, wait, what is this?
What is, I think I linked the wrong one away.
Let me get this again.
Oh my god.
Okay, it's One Piece and Munchy Extravaganza.
Okay, let me re-type this, play, and okay, go.
So hello, PCP.
I have a story to tell.
So one of my friends is retarded, okay?
He says that he does not like One Piece at all
because there's nothing going on in either manga or the anime, right?
Oh, okay, I see.
He's saying like the Luffy character,
he was supposed to become the pirate king, right?
But he's still not a fucking pirate king,
even though it was a billion years, right?
And I know that he's wrong because you guys are right, right?
That's right.
But I don't know why he's wrong.
Like, what is really going on in One Piece?
Well, do you read it?
Also, just a quick side note, I found everybody in PCP
through Munchy, through arm retrieval.
It's just a fun fact and nobody cares.
But I'm pretty sure I'm the only person
who was a Munchy fan before anybody else's fan.
That's not true.
Fascinating.
There is a class of people, a lower class of people,
who found arm retrieval through the Homestuck subreddit,
which I wonder if that's where you found arm retrieval.
But I know that some people found it through the subreddit
and discovered the PCP through that.
I think, pretty wild.
Fascinating.
Yeah, there's a number.
I don't know how many of the people who are arm retrieval big fans
knew about the PCP at all before.
Like, I don't know, like this...
You could maybe say, does it count to be a...
Like, if you got in through the Spirit Science lecture
or the other lecture he did, the Deagle-Mation...
If you got in through the Spirit Science lecture,
I think definitely, Deagle-Mation.
Deagle-Mation, thank you.
Yeah, that would count.
Then you hear through Munchie, for sure.
Yeah, agreed.
I wonder how many people found the PCP
through the Christian lecture.
I mean...
Gotta be some.
It's gotta be some.
I've never...
It's funny, people say...
Gotta give a straw poll going.
I hear people say, I found it through Munchie.
I've never heard anyone say, oh yeah,
I found the PCP through the Sonichu lecture.
But numerically, there must be people like that.
Guys, in the disc, yeah.
Guys, viewers watching, type where you found the PCP from.
Who did you find us?
Don't bother Digigi.
I don't care.
Yeah, just delete your account and kill yourself.
Oh, only?
Yeah.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
T-Bat.
Oh, what was the guy's question or something about?
Oh, and the question was just like,
my friend says one piece sucks,
because Luffy didn't win yet, and he isn't the pirate king.
It's a series designed to go on a long time.
Every...
There's been progress continuous.
It's not like Naruto.
It's about the journey.
It's about the...
It's not like Naruto where we can't gauge
how much progress is being made other than just beating certain guys.
They are making literal, linear progress
towards the end of one piece every time they move islands,
and they do things.
I mean, I don't know if the guy...
If only there was a podcast you could listen to
that broke down in excruciating detail.
Imagine that.
The moment-to-moment greatness that is one piece.
If only.
But such a thing just sadly doesn't exist.
Well, it does, actually.
This is called the Podicast.
What?
It sounds good.
Where can I find this incredible resource?
youtube.com slash thepodicast.
It's hard for Google to type it in,
and people say, you mean podcast?
Like, no.
No, idiot.
You got to force Google to bend to your will.
And that's the only way you can find.
There's some marketing issues there,
but we can work on that, I suppose.
Anyway.
It wouldn't be a PCP adjacent project
if it was just totally algorithmically dead right from the get go.
Oh, wait.
I forgot.
It's actually the Podicast Pirates is the full URL of that one.
Oh, okay.
But like, yeah.
We're the reason projects are dying.
Like, I don't know whether he reads the manga
because he says he knows his friend is wrong because we're right.
Does that mean he doesn't read the thing?
Because clearly, if he did,
he would understand how to refute that and say, just because...
I don't think he does.
Like, the ending of the, you know,
when Luffy becomes the Pirate King,
that's when the series will end and it's not over.
That's all you really need to say.
Yeah.
I mean, and you hear people who aren't big fans,
or maybe they've even read it,
but they gave up because they're like,
I thought Luffy was going to win.
Why, you know, what's happening?
It's just like, but every arc is like, great.
And like, there's always progress.
I mean, Naruto didn't become the Hokage until the end of Naruto.
And if Naruto...
No, not even within Naruto.
It wasn't what's Hokage at the end of Naruto, I don't think, right?
It kind of implies that he was, but...
No, in Boruto, he's Naruto.
And there's like...
In Boruto, he's Naruto.
Tell me more.
Hokage.
Damn it.
Yeah.
But like, Kakashi's Hokage by the idea of hashtag spoilers.
Does he become Hokage offscreen?
I think he...
Well, because like, after the narrative ends,
literally, Kakashi becomes the next Hokage.
Yeah, Kakashi is Hokage at the end of the show.
And then after that, Naruto then later becomes...
I don't know, I don't remember what happened
in the literal last chapter of Naruto.
I think he's not Hokage in that, but I could be wrong.
No, he isn't.
I watched Naruto Kai earlier this year.
Does it end with Kakashi as Hokage?
Well, there you go.
He doesn't become Hokage, but we all know he does eventually.
But it's implied that he will be after Kakashi.
I got it.
That's unsatisfying.
But like Boruto exists, he is Hokage in that,
so I guess it's fine, whatever.
It seems like he's Boruto, isn't it, Boruto?
I fucking guarantee you.
Luffy will be pirate king at the end of One Piece.
He's already the king of the pirates in our hearts,
and that's all that matters.
Yeah, that's true.
It's just people see, wow, this year's been running for like 22 years.
Jesus Christ, what's the deal?
It's all been good.
People just can't wrap their mind around that it's actually good,
and it's the journey is valuable, and progress has been made.
You're totally right, but I think the problem that some people have
is just that this is, it's like when you watch a movie,
and it sets up the stakes and the conflict,
and you're there because you want to see the resolution to it.
I can understand some people being like,
I want this question to be answered, you know?
Yeah, that's fair.
But like, you shouldn't ignore that that question comes up
like every arc and is addressed,
and everything they're doing is moving towards it.
You just can't forget that everything they're doing
is in pursuit of that goal.
Some people is just dumb.
Yeah, that's, yeah, you know.
And you know what?
I don't even blame people who are like, Jesus Christ,
20 years, like I'm out.
If they don't want to be on a journey for that long, that's fine.
Well, they don't need to be,
because it's already been going for 20 years,
but it takes a lot less time to read the thing
than it does to write it.
Well, that's true.
That's true.
But you get people, like even Michelle was like,
Jesus Christ, by the time I read one piece all the way,
like I'll be done.
But it's like, no, you can read in like a month easily.
Here's the...
Well, not easily, but pretty fast.
I understand.
If you spend a full work week,
if you commit 40 hours a week to reading it maybe.
There's like one thing, like Game of Thrones,
I will only read that when it's finished,
because people have been waiting for a long time.
But like, I don't...
I love it, but...
Just because it's been taking a long time to get written,
I don't make a judgment on it being like shit or anything.
Like, I don't understand people who would make judgments
on things based on how long it's been coming out.
I could see why people,
I think a lot of people just make an assumption,
because it's been going on so long,
they assume it must like not be getting to the point.
It must like be stagnating and not being good.
One piece really is that rare exception.
It really is the one that was designed with this in mind
and has not failed to do so,
unless you just need a story to get to the point faster.
But it...
If you need a story to get to the point faster,
then you can just watch like a movie.
I mean, absolutely true.
And one piece is literally a series about how...
Like one of the main points is
that it's about the journey, not the destination.
The destination matters,
but it's about the fucking journey
and boy has it been a great journey with purpose, with intent.
I feel like if you're asking this question,
like why hasn't he become pirate?
Like you can't be like a fan of the series.
I think that the caller here,
I don't even know if they have not won,
but you just have to like adjust your perception of it.
You're kind of looking at it the wrong way.
Well, this person's on your side.
Like why do you think he's not a...
I think, I'm not even saying they're wrong.
I mean, it sounds to me when he says,
I know you're right.
Well, I think what he's saying is I agree with you.
I just can't put it into words and explain it.
I was thinking that he was saying it like,
look, I listen to the PCP, whatever you guys say,
I know is true.
I mean, I hope that's what it is.
And it's possible.
Yeah, me too.
And you know, if you want to be truly right,
you got to go over to patreon.com slash...
The podcast, no, the podcast pirates.
The more you play as a writer, you are.
That's the formula.
Exactly.
Like we give the true secrets of knowledge
to the big patrons.
We actually, we literally do have a stratified patron of,
let's see, there's just the one piece discussion,
then there's Marie-Joy, then there's...
Raftel.
Raftel or Lafts Tale.
And then there's the actual crow's nest,
the treasure vault, the commander's lounge,
and finally the empty throne for those gods who...
Ooh, that gives me the chills.
Oh, Ben, you don't even know, but the empty throne
is the thing that's been introduced in one piece
and is, it's very mysterious.
No, I'm...
I mean, one of these days, I'll catch up.
And then the Lord will descend from heaven with a shout
and the beast with seven horns will do something scary.
You're finishing Dros Rosa.
You've got Zo next, then you've got Whole Cake Island,
and then you're on Wano now,
which is like maybe half or so over.
Ooh, ooh, a lot of good stuff.
Yeah, I got a lot of treats waiting for me.
Indeed you do.
Okay, next one we've got a voicemail from
Mr. Over the Waste T. Itzman is the name.
All right, go.
Hey, Dick.
Hey, Sean.
You know what makes me a fucking rage?
Calling into the wrong fucking podcast.
Spend all this time thinking up what you're gonna say,
and you try your best to make it interesting
to impart even a modicum of entertainment
to the good folks listening at home,
but then you accidentally call the wrong fucking voice line
and leave a message for the wrong fucking people,
and now you're just a fucking idiot
who can't type URLs into his browser properly.
If that ever happened to me,
I'd probably just fucking kill myself.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's my rage.
Well, I love you guys.
Hope.
Go fuck yourself.
Hopefully, I mean,
hopefully he doesn't even listen to this podcast,
so I'll never know.
He'll be in sweet ignorance.
That's the one.
Ignorance.
I hope, yeah.
Hopefully.
Stay away.
That's what we all want.
All right.
Next up, we've got, okay, pick a number.
Pick a number.
What a dead tent, yo, PCP.
Could I get you guys to all agree
and come to a consensus on picking a number
between one and 244?
Thank you.
Okay, let's pick a number.
What do you agree?
Give throughout 10.
10's good.
I could roll with 10.
A little basic.
I'm going to go with 100,
because that's what I'm always keeping it.
Damn.
I'm going to go with 144,
because it's 12 squared,
and I've always liked that number.
It is a good number.
I'm going to go with 88.
88.
Okay, then I'll change my number to 14.
Something about that number, it seems good.
I'm going to go with 144.
I'm going to 144.
You convinced me.
Where are we all supposed to collectively choose one?
I'm going to switch over to pi.
I think pi is a really good number.
Oh, you can't even say that's a four.
Going to some floats.
No more integers here.
That's cheating, but I'm for it.
It's going to make calculations hard.
He didn't say how long it was for.
No, no, it makes the calculations easy, Nate.
It's just the ratio of the diameter to the fucking radius.
Yeah, I mean, think about it this way.
If you chose 144, he has to hit three buttons,
but if you pick pi, you just have to hit one button.
Yeah, just find the easy pi button on your keyboard.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, God.
You know what?
Fine, pi.
Tom, are you in agreement, pi?
I mean, I think it'll ruin whatever bit he's going to go for,
but if we want to fucking throw a monkey wrench in there, I'm down.
Let's fucking do it.
All right.
He didn't say integers.
He did not say integers.
We've done everything he has.
All right.
Okay.
So, let us know.
Call in.
Let us know what's up if we fucked you over royally.
Wait, is there any follow-up to this?
No, that's all there is for now.
It's a mystery box.
Did he say there was going to be more?
I thought it was just pick a number.
He did not say there'd be no more.
I just wanted to do us a favor and call in.
Let us know.
I think this is it.
I think this was the point.
Just to pick a number.
I'm hoping it's four something.
I feel confident that it is not four anything.
And that the journey is a destination.
I have more faith in our viewers than that.
I would like to.
It would have been nice if he told us what it was for.
He didn't promise anything.
And frankly, I don't know.
Her ruin's the mistake.
I mean, I'm okay with that.
I'm just thinking if we say pie, then maybe he'll bake us a pie.
And it'll be really nice.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Maybe it's how many candles to put on my birthday cake.
And we gave him a real tricky answer there.
Strawberry and rhubarb, please.
Ooh, that's good.
Okay.
All right, enough of that.
On to the next question, voicemail.
We've got the professional Nate Triggerer.
Okay, let's get to it.
We'll see.
What's your name?
Nate.
King de Matz 3.
No.
Final Fantasy VII Remake.
A Gurren login sequel.
This last chapter, one piece was the best ever.
No, it's not.
You read one piece wrong, my friend.
You know, triggering Nate is a tough job,
but somebody's got to do it.
Yeah, that's true.
It's a living.
Just a literal brain holocaust for me.
I like that.
That's the beginning.
All right, there you go.
I'm slapping him in voice jail.
We can't allow this man to run ramp.
No, no, mercy.
Sanctuary.
Okay, we'll see.
No, I want him out there.
I'm going to get him some voicemail so he can get out.
All right.
I feel like we've made that joke before, but it's not old.
It's not old.
We need to have something between the voice
grail and the voice jail, like the PC purgatory.
That's good.
Voice a community service.
Did we decide that communist hell is below the
dungeons of the PCP jail or voice jail?
That seems good.
I don't think we described that yet, but I like it.
Can someone draw like a Dante's Inferno style?
Communist hell is under everything.
Can somebody?
Cosmology.
Can somebody build the PCP voice jail in the
PCP Minecraft server?
That'd be great.
Yeah.
Oh, that would be.
I actually, you know,
can we like quit like named NPCs in there or something?
Like literally next to Slime Corp.
Oh, we should.
Someone was building.
It was it was a juvenile detention center was being
built right next to Slime Corp HQ in the Minecraft server.
Okay.
And I keep working on it, lads.
Keep working on it.
That's got a lot.
We got a lot of Jews to lock up.
That's pretty good.
Okay.
I got to get in on this fucking server.
I'm so sad.
I missed the first one.
I really wanted to be there,
but I just wasn't around when it happened.
Too bad.
Yeah, there'll be plenty more,
plenty more to come.
Okay.
So a few people want to be in there.
You want to play with us?
That's patreon.com slash pcb minecraft.
$5 a month only.
Let's go.
Join your friends.
It'll be good.
Okay.
Next up.
Now here we go.
So this is a sequence of,
I think it's just three voicemails technically about an
issue that we were going to bring up.
We didn't yet.
Okay.
Let's just hear the first one.
It's a message from the past.
Okay.
Here we go.
Go.
This is a message from your past.
The Joker N-word countdown is at 24 hours,
four hours ago.
We've done nothing to stop him.
There's nothing we can do.
He's inevitable.
He's going to do it.
He's going to say the N-word.
We're so sorry.
If there's still a society after this is over,
we want you to know when we could.
There was nothing we could do to stop him.
Okay.
So there you go, lads.
I don't know.
If you weren't aware.
I don't know this meme.
Okay.
Well, Ben, let me tell you.
Me and Tom have been following this.
So from 10 days before the Joker movie came out,
a Twitter appeared at Joker and was called the Twitter N-word
countdown.
The Twitter, the Joker N-word countdown?
That's right.
The Joker N-word countdown or something approximately like that.
And it was saying just 10 days until I say it was the only thing posted.
Then nine days before the release,
nine days until I say it.
This started with zero followers.
By the time we got to the day,
it had over 130,000 followers on this Twitter account
posting basically just this.
Pretty cool.
And so it was eight days until I say it.
He's going to watch.
Yeah, you can look at it.
The whole society was crumbling.
Infrastructure is breaking down.
Moral panic was spiked to the heights.
And this is just the Joker at work.
This is just what he does.
And so this progressed until like a couple of days before.
I believe it was the day before he was going to say it.
He released a tweet with a video.
Let me see if I can get this real quick.
But it was a video that featured countless African American individuals.
And it was a video of him sewing image after image of them
giving the Joker their N-word passes.
This was like dozens, if not hundreds of people in this video
giving him countless N-word passes.
And so he just continued on his quest to say it.
To say it.
And so the day comes 24 hours until I say it.
10 hours until I say it.
Finally, there was one that was like 60 seconds until I say it.
And at last he released a video.
And it was the Joker.
Okay, let me just grab it real quick.
It's like right here.
And it's him, it's a video produced, the production value.
Okay, got it right here.
Look at this shit in the main chat.
Just take a look at this real quick.
The production value, like this guy hadn't made any videos.
He just made that one of all the N-word passes he'd been given by all those people.
And it was very rough.
It was incredible.
And this video is him sitting there saying,
you know, society isn't ready for what I'm about to do.
This video has over like 2 million plays.
2.7 million views at this point.
168,000 likes, like 4,000 responses, 50,000 retweets basically on the day.
And so he gets up to the end.
He says, you know, they tried to stop me, but this is my moment and I'm doing what I can do.
And then as he's about to say, he takes a deep breath.
The black man, the black man, a Batman wearing black guy,
bursts in and stops him and says the word instead,
stopping the Joker and his white privilege from running rampant
and destroying all hopes of him crumbling society.
Society was preserved.
And so, you know, the Joker accepts defeat that the black man stopped him.
Maybe next time he'll be able to say it.
And that's that.
But at the very end of the video, if you listen carefully,
he says, like, I was stopped again by the black man.
And then he says a word that's bleeped.
And then the black man says, don't say it, nigga.
And that's the end of the video.
Okay.
That's the end of the video.
So all right.
So this is his, this is the climax of the joke.
And okay.
So that's not the end of the story, though,
because there's a couple of things going on.
So just on this subject and tell him,
I'd love to hear your thoughts as well.
I'll just say that my analysis of this is, I loved this bit.
I thought it was hilarious.
I'm a well-known thinker that, you know, free speech guy,
like it's hilarious to act like just saying a word
is like such an amazing thing that like,
anyone's going to have a problem with just a word being said.
It's very silly.
We know it's offensive, blah, blah, blah, whatever.
So I was, I was looking forward to this as, you know,
just like a funny fuck you to everybody.
Now, technically, at the end of the video, this, you know,
he's a white guy who's playing the Joker here.
He does say it, but it's bleeped.
And to me, if the point of this whole thing
was to be like how silly it is that we're so worked up
about this word being so, like, just to say, not to call anyone,
not to spit it, but just to say, and he,
and he feels the need to bleep it in his video.
Doesn't that actually reinforce the narrative
that it shouldn't say the word?
And it kind of cut against the point.
But Nate, yeah.
Did you not see the tweet?
Oh, I did, Tom.
So the very next day, I do the very next day,
we see the guy say, fuck it, hashtag nigger on this account.
That's, that's what happened.
That's what was posted on his account.
And okay.
So, but, so everyone's like, oh my God, he said it.
He actually said it.
Now, I mean, it seems like the bleep,
like the fact that his was bleeped and the black man's wasn't,
like that seems like the point.
Well, I mean, but yeah, that is the point,
but isn't that by bleeping it, isn't that just saying,
like it literally is okay for simply a word to be said
by, you know, the demographic it's about,
or whatever, black people, but not anybody else,
you know, particularly white people.
Yeah, I mean, I feel like that's the,
that's the commentary or whatever, right?
But I mean, but he's, he is like whipping up hysteria.
Double standard or whatever.
I think the, no, the interesting thing to me, Nate,
like, okay, I don't know what, like,
because when the video dropped, I was like,
yeah, that was like a really well done video
and it's fucking funny.
Of course.
But there was a part of me that was like, man,
I kind of just wanted to watch the shit show
if he like just actually did it and to see what would happen.
Because that was really the most interesting part to me.
It's like, I was interested in the, the inevitable fallout.
I kind of think it would have been more interesting
if it had just been like a five second video
of him just saying the word and nothing else.
I'm looking at this, the Twitter right now,
and he's totally rebranded this Twitter
from what it was like two days ago.
Well, Tom, do you know why that is?
I don't, I guess I've missed part of the story.
Yeah, I'm getting to this.
Okay, so like I said, like the guy, so I feel,
and this guy had actually tweeted,
I'm going to get to that point, Tom,
because the big things have happened then,
like it lasts like day or something about this Twitter.
So like I said, this Twitter has like 130,000 followers,
like a lot of people have unsub
because the joke's over or whatever.
But like he actually, the guy who did it
has a separate Twitter account that I was,
it's like Connor or something, I'll link in the description.
So like we know who the guy is who did it.
He's like a reasonably small time YouTube comedian,
but he had this really funny idea for the skit.
And like after he posted the video,
he updated his bio to have the at to that guy.
So we 100% know like who the guy was,
looks just like him, you know, that's all there is to it.
Behind the scenes footage, et cetera.
Like on that guy's account, I started following,
because I was curious, you know,
what the man himself had to say about all this.
And he was saying things like,
like one thing he said was like,
maybe the worst thing about all of this is like, if I,
or he said like, maybe the real evil here
was getting so many people to wish that I'd said.
Right, yeah, that was going to bring up.
That's an interesting point to make.
So it sounds like with that point,
he's saying that like, no, no, no,
none of this was necessarily about like,
like defanging a word or pointing to the absurdity
of overvaluing a word just by itself,
not insulting people, but just saying a word.
It was actually like a troll, like here I am,
like, like the only reason someone could want me
to say the N word here is because they're racist.
It sounds to me like this guy didn't really have a clear
like theme or anything.
I think that's what I think.
I think the timeline of events here was that,
I think that's my perspective on the timeline of events
is that he started the account or repurposing.
It started with zero followers, by the way.
So he did not like, no, this was going to.
Yeah, because this account was made in 2013.
So like, he repurposed this account clearly
for this purpose when he had the idea for the joke.
So like, he starts and I'm sure he's not expecting it
to be calm as huge as it does.
And I'm assuming that it probably would have been
a very straightforward thing if it stayed small,
but when you have over 100,000 people waiting for you
to drop an n-bomb and like question if you're going
to hard art and shit, like it's that point you're like,
oh God, I have to do something like actually
worth the attention that I have now.
And I think this skit probably came from that.
I think maybe he overthought it.
I agree, Ben.
But like the change here is that because I think
he made the video probably because it's just like,
oh God, like there might be some actual ramifications
if I actually do it with this kind of spotlight on me.
So there's this whole skit.
Most cancel culture.
But then he did it anyway.
Right.
But that's the point because the account after the video
was very much like, okay, the bid is over.
Here's my actual account.
This is who I actually am.
This is the comedy I actually do.
And then he was making those comments
because I think there were a contingent of people
who were kind of bummed that it didn't actually happen.
Like the promise was not delivered in a direct way.
And so that tweet that you just mentioned, Nate,
about maybe the real evil was getting everyone to be excited,
that kind of feels like a justification made after the fact.
Like this is a way of spinning people's disappointment.
And then I feel like now, looking at the account now,
where it's unbranded and back to just being its own thing,
that he's just leaning into what everyone
really wanted the whole time.
Well, Tom, let me tell you why that's not the case.
It's because, at least as far as we know,
this could be an elaborate hoax.
He just dropped the hard R and bomb after,
like the day after, or like two days after.
It's because both his original account,
according to him on a video he posted on Instagram
or Facebook or something, both accounts were hacked.
Were hacked by, what was it?
The chuckling squad.
And if you look on his Twitter at The Joker,
it says right now, the pin tweet is a link to a Discord
and hashtag chuckling squad.
So unless this is some sort of particularly elaborate hoax.
Like it was hacked after the fact?
Yeah, because this had drawn so much attention,
and in the video, the guy bleeps out him saying the N-word,
allows the black guy to say it, blah, blah, blah.
It seems that he really decided,
or whatever, maybe never intended, to say it at all.
But now he just goes hashtag and says it on his account.
It really does look like he almost assuredly
was in fact hacked, and someone decided,
you know, I'm gonna correct this guy's mistake,
and they've gone in here and they've actually hashtag nigger,
and stuff like that.
That seems to be what's happened as far as I can tell.
Yeah, because I'm seeing the Discord link.
I've only seen the actual tweet, not the fuck it one.
I will try to find a link to the video,
because I had just seen it before,
and it's him on his other account.
He says, guys, look, all my accounts have been hacked.
Even this account, I think this video will be deleted quickly,
but luckily it was someone to capture it or something,
because all his accounts were hacked,
and so I don't have any control over my accounts now.
Again, we don't know 100% that that's true.
I believe that it is true.
It seems the most likely thing,
because I think if he was comfortable with saying the word,
he would have just done it.
Because let me just, my last point about the video
is I think the joke would have been perfect and flawless,
because the way he slips it in at the end and just bleeps it,
he had built it up, he undercuts the moment,
and then at the end, he slips in but bleeps it,
and then the black guy says, nigga, whatever.
I felt it would have been a perfect joke
if he just simply had not bleeped it at the end,
because what does that say?
It undercuts the hype, and it points to the absurdity
of getting so excited about this word
when he can just put it in at the end totally anti-climatically.
I wouldn't understand that, because if he just says it,
why would you have the black man character in there
and also say it?
Well, because the black man's point in the story,
the black man's point in the story
is to stop the Joker from saying it,
and so I felt he represented all the people who correctly or not
want to stop him from saying it.
All right, the thing with all this, I think,
is that the meme, the original joke,
I'm gonna say the n-word,
is not really about race.
It's the equivalent of you're at your friend's house,
and you say to them,
dude, what would you do if I stepped on all your video games
and broke them, and then your friend goes, I hate you?
And he's like, but what if I did?
It's just sort of like a, what if I did a really bad thing?
And it's just sort of the rush of imagining that.
And it's like, I'm gonna say the n-word.
I'm white, I'm gonna say the n-word.
Like that's why it's funny.
There's never really been, I mean,
among the people I've seen make that joke,
it's just sort of like kids who are like,
haha, I'm gonna say something bad.
It's hoping to sacred cow is what it's doing.
That seems to be the point of the joke.
Sacred cow, the n-word, precious.
And it's like this guy, I'm sure,
feels the same way about it,
which is why he had this whole like,
the black man stops him in the end.
And he's clearly an edgy comedian.
I've looked at his thing that I assume
that was what he was getting at.
If not that, I don't understand the joke.
Well, I don't know.
Whatever.
I mean, I don't understand the joke either way.
I mean, I don't think he had us like a vision for this
when it started.
This is what's, I mean, based on the conclusion,
I'm forced to agree that I think,
look, my reading of the situation
isn't the only valid one.
Maybe someone else understands this better.
I mean, I'd be curious to hear
what people have to say about it,
because this was a very interesting phenomenon I found.
If the point of this wasn't to basically make fun
of this word that I feel is given disproportionate power,
no one's being called anything.
He's just saying a word.
That's the point of this.
Surely, we shouldn't get too excited about that, right?
So if that wasn't the point, I don't get the point.
So yeah, that's where I feel.
I mean, I'm going to be, it's not optimistic.
I feel like the point was just to get the attention,
and he did it.
He did.
And you know what?
We should, I actually like the guy.
I think he did a good job overall.
The fact that he delivered with an impressively made video
at the end, even if it didn't exactly do the joke
the way I would have done it,
I still think his grounds for it's impressive,
it's worth celebrating,
he like almost got the joke perfectly in my mind.
So I don't know, I still really like the guy.
I respect what he did.
I mean, really, it's one of those like,
where the imagination is the entire thing.
Like the fact that there's a Twitter account
and he's counting down to saying the n-word,
that's the joke.
That's where you laugh.
That's the punchline in itself.
That's the fact that it exists.
He got so many n-word passes, guys.
Yeah, all the n-word passes.
That's really funny.
That's hilarious.
The culmination, I don't think it's even possible
to please everyone with that.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
You know what, when he first ended the thing,
he said, he changed his bio before it seemingly got hacked,
he like his bio became,
they're gonna hate you either way,
with a link to his normal friends.
So I mean, yeah, I mean, that's true.
But let's not play the joke.
I think he should have just committed to the bit
and just done it.
I think he should have just done it.
Like, I couldn't agree more.
I think it would have been a more interesting experiment,
if you want to call it that.
If he just fucking done it.
Like, just, like not.
And so, to those?
I get the temptation to subvert your audience's expectations,
but I don't really think, I don't know.
I mean, I haven't watched this video yet,
because it's two and a half minutes long,
and I have to check out the web.
But like, the way you describe it,
doesn't really sound like he subverted it
in a way that's that funny.
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
He's just sort of like, you know, he gets ready.
He's like, you know, faffing around,
like coughing, like getting his throes.
Clearing his throes.
Like, okay, you know, the obvious misdirect is to not do it,
after all that, like, silly build up.
And then he does not actually do it, really.
And I don't know.
He kinda does it.
He kinda does, but he censors it.
Which, I mean, the first time I watched it,
I wasn't even sure what was happening.
I think, like, the fact that he didn't say it,
was like, oh, well, the video's over.
Like, whatever happens after that,
I just wasn't really paying attention.
I don't know.
I just think it's very interesting to me.
And anyone who thinks that, like, oh, he changed his mind,
and he just tweeted it out, I don't think that's correct.
I believe that he was hacked.
This is what I think is extremely wrong.
Oh, with the hashtag?
With the hashtag.
Yeah, I mean, with the hashtag and the Discord server,
that does actualize it, and it seems legit to me.
That would just be, like, that would just completely undermine
whatever he was trying to do with the final video.
Exactly.
That would completely undermine it.
It would be really fucking dumb.
And that's one of the main reasons I think he was, in fact, hacked.
And by the way, they say that these chuckling squad guys
are the same guys who hacked Etika after he died,
and then also, like, Jack, when Jack's account,
like Twitter head guy, got his account hacked.
So, again, I don't know that for sure,
but it seems reasonable.
So, you know, that seems to be the best theory.
I see.
So, there you go.
Fascinating.
Oh, and you know, there was actually two more voicemails about this.
They're both brief.
Let me just play those quickly, because they are amusing.
Okay.
Sorry.
About the same thing?
It's about this issue.
We don't need to spend long on it, but they were funny,
so I just want to play them.
Okay.
And here, this is the unironic gang weed guy.
So, let's hear what he has to say.
Go.
Attention, all fellow epic gamers and gang weed members.
That's me.
It is I, once again, the unironic gang weed guy.
Back again with an announcement for you all.
Joker is now in theaters.
That being said, no chance.
Veronica's especially NPCs.
Blumfters, boomers, or sheeple are loud.
That means you, Nate.
Which one are you?
You should never be afraid of the outward.
Did you see that guy on Twitter who said he was going to say it?
But didn't.
What a shame.
In his place, I will say the n-word.
Oh, no.
Because he ran out of time.
That was a close one.
Wait, he ran out of just the time.
Uh, interestingly, I think we have another voicemail
on an ironic gang weed.
Do you have to follow up?
Let's hear what he has to say.
Go.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, you rascally wab at you.
Yeah, that one got me.
That one caught me off guard.
Better punchline than the actual punchline.
Yeah, kind of.
Okay, another quality voicemail here.
We've got Racky the Robot Guy.
Oh, wait, before we end this,
we have to, I have to say that we are suing the Joker,
because we were talking about this before,
that this is actually a copied bit
from the Procrastinators podcast.
What is this but racist forest gump repurposed?
We, exactly.
We have intellectual property to all, you know,
attempts to say the n-word.
All, all racism.
We expect the royalties.
Yeah, yeah.
All racism is property of the pieces here.
Racism is our intellectual property.
We are the source of racism.
That's another t-shirt in the making.
Nope.
Nobody else was doing anything with racism.
Nobody was being racist.
We alone, we alone were using it,
and now you want to swoop in and recuperate it,
and I, and I won't stand for it.
I don't think so, buddy.
I don't think, now when there's money on the line,
sweet dollory dudes.
All right.
That's sticky icky cashish.
Next we got Racky the robot guy.
Okay, let's hear what he has to say.
Go.
So, a while ago, I came in contact
with my childhood friend again.
After some chatting,
he reveals that he's gotten his first girlfriend,
which surprises me,
since he's the most virgin loser kind of guy I know.
But of course, I congratulate him.
However, after some time,
it comes to light that not only
is this an internet relationship,
but the chick lives in Michigan, U.S.,
while we live in Sweden.
Yep.
And he plans on moving to the U.S.
in a year or two to live with her.
How old?
I want to know what these people are.
Mind you, he's 16,
and longer communication is very role-playing
over discourse.
So, he plans on skipping out
on the last year of high school
and free college,
which we have here in Sweden.
Oh.
So, my question is,
how the fuck do I make him realize
how impossible this relationship is
without him, I don't know,
getting mad at me?
Off your good man.
You let him get mad at you.
That's how.
Okay, he will realize this is stupid.
Indeed.
But will you be in time?
I would hope if nothing else,
the system has enough checks and balances
in place to prevent this from happening,
but he will realize that,
and you should just tell him that so,
because when he eventually realizes that,
like he might be mad at you now,
but he will appreciate you more in the future
because you were right,
and you told him the truth.
This is what happened.
And you should play him this pod,
you should recommend him this episode
of the podcast so he can hear.
Yeah, we can break it down for him.
Let him hear this section.
This is the symptom of the false scarcity of pussy
that our generation is struggling with.
There is no scarcity.
There's millions of girls in every fucking town.
You can go meet them.
And like this is just,
this is a guy who's clearly,
like never had a girlfriend.
Like some girl online shows him some affection.
He's like, I'm all in, all my chips.
I'm going in on this relationship.
This is the one.
Guys, this is why every guy needs to develop
at least a fucking little bit
of the basic like social graces to get a girl,
so that they don't like sacrifice so much
for some pussy across the fucking planet
that like, it's a furry role play.
Like, oh my God, are you fucking kidding me?
All the red flags are there.
Is this the quality woman that you want to spend your life with?
Obviously you're probably not thinking about that level,
but it's just, this is,
the desperation is so obvious to everyone.
And it just comes from, as I always say,
the biggest problem in our world right now
is the weakness of men, the desperation of men,
and this false scarcity of pussy
that guides every false mentality.
Oh my God, don't be a fool.
Don't be a fucking fool.
Literally just go ask any girl like in your class right now,
like just do this.
Like, hey, I think you're cool.
You want to hang out sometime?
You literally do that.
And they will be gushing as a waterfall
before your sheer chatteliness,
because like no guys do that these days,
especially in fucking high school.
Like literally just buy, go to PCP,
Teespring buy, and I'm just being cool T-shirt
and live those words.
Live those words and just be cool.
Just be cool, couldn't agree more.
Unironically, good advice,
because even if you get shot down, like, it like-
You still got a T-shirt.
So that's a win-win right there.
That's very true.
That T-shirt will be there for you no matter what.
But also, it breaks like the barrier of like,
oh God, I can't do this.
It's too scary, you know, what you finally do,
and you realize that like you don't instantly
die on the spot if you get shot down.
Yeah, exactly.
It makes, it goes from something unfathomable
to something that you've already done
and is clearly doable.
Oh my God, I know it's hard.
It's literally hard, it'd be hard for me if I was single.
It would be hard to just approach a girl I liked
and like say she's cute and hang out with her.
It's always gonna be challenging.
It's hard for like every guy on the planet,
unless you're like just like some billionaire,
like a party you're hosting or some shit like that.
What do they call that?
Like situational lording, the club, whatever,
it doesn't matter.
Point is, yes, just let the guy listen to this.
And like he will think like, wow, you know, I really am.
This is kind of absurd.
This is kind of like, there's that cute girl in my class
who like I would actually love to like hang out with
and she doesn't exist across the fucking planet.
Maybe I could like talk to her once
and like just see how that goes.
Maybe she's a very role player, you don't know.
Exactly, and you could do it in person.
You could put your fur suits on,
you could rub each other's paw, what's the word?
Toe beans against each other.
Oh, it could be lewd as hell, my dude.
So go for it.
There's literally nowhere to go but up, unfortunately.
He's right.
As fortunate as to say.
And yeah, be mad at us.
Don't be mad at your friend for pointing you're here.
Yes, exactly.
Tell them that you left a funny goofy voicemail.
Friend, if you're listening, you know, it's cool, you know,
cool, you got the internet girlfriend, that's fine.
It's fine.
You're 16, it's good, you know, good, good, whatever.
It's cool, nothing matters.
Yep.
It's all gravy.
It's like the opposite what we've been saying.
Don't move to America, America fucking sucks, you don't,
don't come here for your own sake, don't fucking.
At least not until after you've done the whole free college and shit,
like that'll be a huge fucking leg up over everybody else.
Yeah, and like moving away from everything you've ever known,
like your family, etc.
Basically nothing by this.
Okay, if you can't shake the guy,
if you can't fucking shake the guy on this point,
then, and you will in time.
I mean, it's not your job to shake him.
No, no, it's not.
But like this guy rightly is just like, wow, this is retarded.
He's just being the reasonable friend who's like,
I'm 100% aware of how silly this is.
Like if nothing else, just tell him like, okay,
like what happens is right now,
this is an illusion of relationships.
It's a fugazi.
Tell him to make it real.
It's a spook.
Tell him to make it real by saying like, okay,
like initiate plans to meet up.
And when you see all the effort that's involved in actually like,
it doesn't have to be moved forever,
but just meet up one time,
like make plans to do that.
And when he sees how fucking impossible it will happen,
either one of two things will happen.
One, the more likely thing,
it will completely fall through and it won't happen.
And I mean, let's be real, this plan will fall through.
It's guaranteed.
Absolutely.
But if the miracle happens,
and he actually puts together the money
and gets over there and sees the girl,
either he'll get like amazing bomb furry sex,
extremely unlikely, not going to happen.
I guarantee it.
Or what will happen is to be like,
oh, this kind of sucks and is not worth all the effort I put in.
And then the problem will go away.
Boy, the perfect mental image I constructed in my head
isn't quite lashing up to reality.
Has he seen what she looks like in real life?
I'm very curious about that,
because that would be very interesting to know.
Or has he just seen her furry OC?
And you've done pictures with suit off and not with suit on.
This is very important.
You can hide a lot of those things.
Everyone looks good in their fur suit, dude.
Everyone looks good in their fur suit, but...
Sure.
Yeah, I mean, when you're me,
you know, looking at the world through furry eyes,
it's just everything's gravy.
But okay, anyway, there you go.
Okay, moving on to our next voice.
Guys, I've been waiting for this one.
This is my favorite voicemail of the bunch.
I am so excited to share it with you.
This comes from,
I hope someone who becomes a staple on this episode,
or on this podcast.
All right, all right, here we go.
I give you this, dude.
The one and only, the fall hype guy.
Go.
Bro, it's fall.
That means there's fairs and festivals and...
I'm about to watch figure eight derby racing,
and it's going to be intense.
I've been eating nothing but junk food all day long,
including no freaking ostrich burger, dude.
What's your favorite part of fall?
Incredible.
Oh, come on, that was good.
He's so hyped about fall.
Yeah, that's what I don't like.
It's infectious.
I hope it's ironic.
If it's ironic, I like it.
That was a budget munchie.
That was okay.
Oh, you guys, your standards are too fucking high.
Nate, your problem is that you hyped it up.
If you had just let it play,
we probably would have been much more invested.
Are you fucking fall, Stan?
I love fall, yeah.
You know what it reminds me of?
It reminds me of that very beginning
of Poo's Grand Adventure,
where they say,
on the last day of a golden summer,
a boy and a bear were hanging out
as some fucking adventure was about to dawn.
They say hanging out.
They say about to fucking stuck around.
They do say that.
I remember that.
That language, that flowery British language.
Ooh, it gets me every time.
Okay, well, I, for one, can't wait to fall hype guy.
I wouldn't mind fall, except that people go fucking weird for it.
I want to hear from this guy every three months.
I enjoy autumn quite a lot.
Because of the sort of gray.
Pumpkins.
Like the grayness of the outside,
but it's not cold enough to not take a walk.
So it's sort of a unique time.
The leaves are starting to fall.
They're picturesque in the eastern seaboard in America.
Oh, that's why they call it fall.
Because the leaves do it.
Probably.
Why do they call it winter?
Because that wind sure does turd.
Because it's epic wind, bro.
Or why do they call it summer?
What does that have to do with anything?
I want to get some of these nuts in my face.
That's what I'm talking about.
Anyway, call back in three months.
I can't wait to hear from winter hype guy,
and then spring hype guy, and then summer hype guy.
I'll be tired of the bit by then.
It'll be fresh.
It'll be mostly.
It'll be fresh again in however life.
We're all still alive at that point.
I'll say to that voice, I'll say hello, fresh.
Guys, no, climate change.
Seasons are fucking over.
We're all going to fucking die.
That's true.
All right.
We had a good run.
Here's a question.
If the seasons got locked,
which season would you want it to be forever?
I got to go with spring, I think.
I got to go with spring.
I mean, I like spring.
I like South Coruble bloom.
I like winter.
I think winter is aesthetic, but I'd get sick of it real fast.
Winter is fucking miserable.
Yeah, I got to go.
I like spring too.
Spring, maybe summer.
But summer's kind of fucking hot.
I want late spring.
It's all about spring.
If I had to, it's not my, yeah.
If you had to.
Gibber, are you a spring boy too, Gibber?
Imagine if it was winter forever.
Think of the practical implications of this question.
Well, I mean, there is one thing is that in spring,
there's a lot of pollen in the air, and I have hay fever.
So I sneeze way more than during winter, during spring.
Unironically, when I think about the seasons locking,
I unironically just want to center it around.
I've actually been studying this a little bit about,
did you guys know that the Sakura blossoms
in the land of the Surizing Sun, Nipon, they only bloom,
not even for like all of spring,
but literally for like, there's like a 10 day period.
And actually, the progression of the blooming
of the Sakura trees, it progresses,
and different areas have different days regularly
throughout the year.
So you can actually kind of follow the progression
of the Sakura blossoms from east to west, I think,
along Japan.
I've been looking into it for a potential trip in the spring.
So we'll see what happens with that.
Ooh, I love Japan, period.
Okay, but anyway.
Disgusting.
Next up, it is gross.
I apologize, everyone.
Next up, we've got IRL Riddle My Ass Batman story.
No joke.
So welcome back, Mr. Batman.
Do you know the black man of Joker fame?
I'd be curious.
Okay, let's go.
Go.
Hello, PCB.
Riddle My Ass Batman here.
First I have a question.
An IRL story, Rintangely.
Related to that question.
Question.
Are you doing it in October?
I've done it in the past and failed this year.
I made it two days before missing one.
Don't worry, I have a good reason.
Okay, story time.
I'm walking over the bridge.
On my way to work, I get off the bridge, talk to my buddy.
Not my buddy, it turns out.
Next thing I know, I feel a big wop in the back of my head.
Everything goes black.
The next part of the story, I don't really remember.
I have to piece together from what other people told me.
I wake up on the railroad tracks.
I have complete amnesia.
No wallet, no glasses, and phone broken.
Happened to stumble my way into a police station
via the train tracks.
After that, they ID me.
Talked to me on the hot team to the hospital.
No brain damage.
Talked to my family.
They tell me to bombard me with information.
Hopefully jogging my memory.
What does a little, and what jog memory?
Not in my family photos or anything like that.
What happened to jog memory is a little story called,
a little video called by Joseph Jostar,
called Entire Riddle My Ass Gavance Saga.
I said my memories come back to me
and I felt like I was taking a PCV.
Anyway, I started even told her as soon as I remember
how to jog again.
What happened to my next life?
Turned the next time to find out.
Same PCV time, same PCV channel.
Yeah, all right.
He said this was IRL.
He said no joke, but surely there must be joke.
I really like the idea that the story starts
when he goes on a bridge, talks to a friend,
turns out he's not his friend, then he gets knocked out.
Who is this mysterious character?
Yeah, I want to know about that guy.
Perhaps that was Riddle My Ass.
Maybe that was Joe, Joe, Joe, Jostar.
You know?
Maybe that was Joseph Jostar.
Maybe that was Black Man.
That could have been Black Man.
He sees Riddle My Ass Batman in Fringe of his Turf,
his copyright.
That would make sense.
I am not doing Inktober because I...
Well, I wouldn't have done it anyway,
because I don't like it.
I don't do traditional drawing very much,
so I know I would fail at it,
and I don't accept the legitimacy
of digital drawing for Inktober.
I think it's down when people are like,
oh, digital ink counts, I don't agree.
Stupid.
That's fair.
Fight me in the comments.
This is like Never Paint's time to shine, though,
because Never Paint always does
like IRL shit or whatever.
Go, Never Paint.
And I wouldn't do it anyway,
because I'm doing my fucking Phantom Horn comic,
and if I'm going to be drawn,
I want to be working on that.
Makes sense to me.
I'm doing Devtober, obviously,
so that's different.
Indeed.
Monthtober is the most viable.
It really is.
I feel like it's a new movement
that really needs to pick up some steam.
Nate, you doing Inktober?
I'm doing, no, just no, just absolutely not.
Are you doing like worktober?
I'm doing the same amount of worktober
I would do under the given month.
Nate's doing work supposedly,
but we don't see any results of it.
I'm making my weeagwas.
They're basically weekly at this point,
and that's great.
I'm chugging along, and I've had enough time
to work on other stuff,
so new videos of me, you'll see.
You know what?
By the time, I always say it by the time,
no, don't say it.
Don't say it.
Nate, a new video, we'll be out.
That's not even a weeagwa on my channel.
Don't say it.
Oh my gosh.
This is like my N-word.
This is my, you know, it's mine.
Don't say it, Nate.
Don't say it.
I'm saying it.
You'll be able to judge.
You'll be able to mock me mercilessly
wherever you please, if not.
I mean, again, it's lost its edge
when we can do it constantly.
He's going to say the C-word, content.
Yeah, there it is.
There it is.
We'll see.
Or the N-word, new content.
New, the N-C, yeah.
Well, you'll be the judge, folks.
Let me know.
Let me know if my thing is out when you hear this.
Okay, here we go.
Next up, we've only got a few left.
We've got Peter Griffin watches the PCP.
Oh man, what I've always been waiting for.
Okay, here we go.
Peter.
I'm just patron to the PCP.
Peter, did you ever have the last time you looked at the PCP?
Hey, Lois, I'm going to vape and smoke weed
while arguing about politics and my little pony.
It's Sans Peter Griffin.
That's how it happened.
That's the, that's Sans Peter Griffin's backstory.
That's his backstory.
Listen to the PCP.
He vape and smoked weed while doing something else
that I forget and then he turned on the PCP.
Vaping and MLP and politics.
The story started way with-
Arguable politics and MLP.
It was like, oh fuck, what's that movie?
They reviewed it on Red Letter Media about Dom Delouise
as the voice of the super skateboard, the intelligent skateboard.
Yeah, I forget, but yeah.
And just like this confluence of weird events
just happened to create this super,
it was like a lightning strike and all these like computer chips
and like some other, like you wished upon a star or something.
And the combination of these events just happened to create
Dom Delouise, the magic skateboard.
That it's the same with all these things coming together
to create Sans Peter Griffin.
That's, that's uh, that's a bit.
That story started with someone pledging to the PCP patron.
So like, I mean already-
Let that be an example for all of you right there.
So it was, it started at the happy end
and it was downhill from there.
It was a story of false and grace.
All right, next up we've got, oh, this is a good one.
The grammar fascist is calling in.
So truly an enemy to our friends and communists.
Tell, let's see what he has to say.
Yeah.
All right, I'm mad.
Anytime I try and tell someone they're a fucking dumbass
because they use the wrong there or they're on your,
and that doesn't make them a fucking dumbass, by the way.
They always try to tell me, uh,
you're just to be able to not see languages
whenever people make it out to be.
No, fuck off.
People act like there's no objective effect.
That's just wrong.
Everyone knows the whole helping your uncle Jack off a horse
and helping your uncle Jack off a horse thing by now.
It does actually do something other than just make the eyes
belonging to anyone with any common sense bleed.
Everyone knows this, but they always respond with a,
oh, that really makes a difference.
It's probably not gonna actually change the meaning
even though it could.
That's what I have to say.
And maybe you're right.
It usually won't.
But when you're proven you're so goddamn stupid
you can't figure out when you're even supposed
to use an apostrophe.
How can I trust you to know when your grammar mistake will
and won't actually matter?
The people who actually know the rules of grammar
will know when they can afford to post a typo
or not bother thinking about which word to use
because they actually understand the rules grammar works by.
And that's fine.
It's not annoying when that happens,
but the people who always make this argument
are the ones who can't even figure out which word
or common placement or colon placement is correct.
There's no fucking way for you to figure out
if your mistake will change the meaning or not
if you haven't bothered to learn the rules.
But no, they just always try and make these arguments
because they're so goddamn insecure
about the grammatical incompetence
that they feel when you do it so anyone who points it out.
It's real straight.
You make a good case, grammar fascist.
Yeah, fuck him.
Yeah, like, of course.
Yeah, of course there are grammar rules.
I mean, grammar is an authoritarian system, so.
It's true.
Who's to say?
I guess I'll be a grammar fascist too.
That's, I'll do it.
Yeah, I'll do it.
No, that's the one time that it's cool.
It's way cool.
I hope we get a call in from Bash the Grammar Fash next episode.
I hope that.
I look forward to that.
I hope, well, I guess they don't need grammar
when they're speaking.
No, not really.
Well, wait, in the spoken word, there are no rules
and everyone's just making it up
and it all, nothing matters and there's no God.
Well, I assume grammar is like, yeah, the commas and stuff
and those denote like pauses in speech or like.
Well, grammar is also like nouns and vowels and adjectives.
Okay, well, as long as he just speaks like an idiot,
then it would be fine.
Agreed.
All right, we compromise on that.
Don't learn your thays.
Learn your thays and theirs and stuff.
Like, I really don't know how people don't know them.
It's not even that difficult.
They just, I mean, I mean, it would be annoying, right?
Like, if you make a mistake, like that's,
if you make a mistake, it's a mistake and like, but yeah,
I would be annoyed too if you say like,
hey, use the wrong there.
I mean, you could be in, you could do it in an annoying way,
right?
And they would say like, dude, you're just being,
you're nitpicking, you're being pedantic.
Like, who cares?
Like, you know what I meant.
Like, and that would be fair.
But if they're like, no, there aren't any actual rules, man.
Like, then they're just wrong.
Well, yeah, yeah.
And both can be true at once.
You can both be an asshole and they're actually wrong.
So, sure.
Fair enough.
All right, let's move on.
Our last voicemail.
Our last voicemail, everybody.
This is from, okay, here we go.
This is from The Cuck of Monte Pisto.
Formerly, formerly, well-researched thesis
who has been locked away in the voice jail where they belong.
So, okay, let's.
What was their well-researched thesis again?
You want to remind me?
Wasn't that about things being human core or not?
And I think they said, like, the bathroom thing.
Oh, okay.
It was terrible.
Yep, yep.
I think that was them.
I could be wrong.
Let me know.
Okay, let's hear what they have to say from the jail.
Go.
So, I'm sitting here at a disgrace caller in the voice jail,
getting my daily lashes.
And I get to thinking,
how is an unfunny cuck such as myself
going to free himself from the voice jail?
And it hits me.
Yeah.
I'll suck mage's dick.
Wait, no, that won't work.
That's gay.
Yeah?
I'll suck mage's dick.
Wait, shit.
I'm pretty sure that got eaten out by piranhas.
Well, fuck.
There's no other choice left for me.
I have to use my last resort.
Go to patreon.com slash the pro-crasinators to support the show.
$1 gets you access to the Patreon Discord
and $5 gets you access to the bonus episode.
And a currently undetermined amount
gets you access to the Minecraft server.
I'm donating right now.
harass me in the Patreon Discord.
Oh.
You can recognize me as the cuck of Monty Pisto.
But I won't be patroning for long.
It's hard for voice jail convicts to find works these days.
And send in your voicemail, people.
If my shitty bits can get played on the show,
yours can.
Yours certainly can do better.
Listen to that shitty audio quality.
I'm calling for my phone.
This is like take 20.
Yeah.
Link to the speak pipe is in the description.
Oh, here come the guards now.
It worked.
I'm free.
Oh, no, wait.
What are they doing with those billy clubs?
Getting too uppity.
Getting too fucking uppity.
It's me.
I'm the jailer of the PC.
Whatever it is.
I'll leave him alone.
Oh, no, he's good.
Are we freeing him?
Did you notice?
Did you notice how he got a little uppity there?
He's like putting that vague thread of like,
oh, why am I in voice jail?
I can't earn money to give to the Patreon.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's worse than that.
He said he's not going to patron for long.
Because now it's even if the convicts can't,
convicts can't, and he's still a convict even to let him out.
So there's no hope.
There's no point letting him out.
Because if you let him out, he still doesn't have any money.
So what doesn't matter.
I mean, I think he's right.
If we can't squeeze his wallet, we'll squeeze his skull.
He's right where he needs to be, as far as I can say.
He's right where he needs to be.
This feels right.
You're right.
And thank him for doing the heavy lifting.
Now that we're at the end of this episode,
you heard it from the cuck of Monty Pisto.
Go harass him in the PCP Patreon Discord.
We'll give him an extra jello cup at his next weekly meal.
Yeah, that seems fair.
Yeah, so there you go.
Patreon.com slash theprocrastinators.
You heard it, $1 Discord, $5 bonus episodes.
New one is out.
That's 30 episodes now.
Incredible.
Speak pipe.
Link down below.
Leave us your voicemails.
We love them.
And at tbcrastinators on Twitter for updates.
There you go, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
Woo!
We'll see you next episode next week.
Have a good time.
Good job, everyone.
We made it.
Bye-bye.
Good bye.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, feet are saying.