Hi, Ben from the future here with a, I think this episode merits a bit of explanation. You see, you know, as every commenter has pointed out, the PCP has been a little bit, a little bit low energy lately, a little bit, a little bit low attendance lately.
You know, it's just been, just been some quiet, intimate, one on one, one on one on one kind of little conversations, just about whatever I want to talk about.
And that is obviously a huge, huge problem. So instead we decided, we decided to swing the pendulum hard, well I decided, this is me, it's my fault, blame me.
Swing the pendulum hard the other way, and say, no, fuck that, high energy, everybody, get in here, so I, you know, I had a couple of vodka gimlets, and I decided to put out a tweet saying, who wants to be on the next PCP episode?
And that's what this is. This is PCP episode 200 and whatever. Oops, all guests addition. Anyone who wanted to be on the podcast? Here they are. On the freaking podcast. I hope you enjoy the high energy that is about to ensue.
Power to the people, you're welcome. Oh, but anyway, before we get underway, I want you to know that this episode is actually seven different episodes because the guests were split into teams.
They were invited to separate themselves into six colored teams, red, blue, yellow, green, pink, purple, before the episode began.
I did not explain to them what the teams would be used for, but in the end, we split up the team, or the guests into groups, and then went group to group to group, having conversations, doing voicemails, doing a little chit chat, having a little sesh.
So we have the main episode that follows me, Tom, and Gibb going group to group to group talking to everyone, but we also have the separate editions. We have red edition, yellow edition, blue edition, etc.
That is just the groups chat alone, including the parts that me, Tom, and Gibb were in. So if you want to hear, we have a we have a little like a like light through a prism. This episode is split split into a rainbow, a rainbow of content for your enjoyment.
So we'll put this, we'll include a link to a playlist of all the different teams. There'll be link link in the description. So if you are interested to hear each individual team and what they talked about during this clusterfuck of an episode, there you go.
There'll be down there in the, in the, in the box. Just, just a heads up. Okay. Without further ado, let's, let's get this show pony on the road, pony. Baby.
One more time. Three, two, one, sing. Okay. And remember, do not leave the call at the end until we sync at the end again. Very important.
Welcome to the pro crass podcast. We're on, we're live, we're doing it. It's the, oh God, how did all these fucking people get in here?
Ben saying, and we've got, we got Tom Oliver, we got Gibb and take, and we have like 40 other people.
People are saying that was decided to remedy that by inviting everyone on.
Everyone said, oh, oh, where, oh, where's Jeff? And you know what, we've got, we've got better, we've got better options now.
All those people are in the past. This is the future. And the future belongs to the people.
As someone could say, we're better than they.
Ah, yes. The people's favorite.
So, um, all right. Topics, suggestions, everyone.
We're going to need some order in here.
Guys, we're really going to need some order in here. Everybody's going to need to quiet down.
Guys, we're flamboyant. Are you sure you go to voicemails?
Yeah.
How about voicemails? It just is the topic.
I have a question. You guys are all, you guys could all like give a voicemail live inside the call.
Yeah.
Too much pressure.
Can we go to voicemails?
We've got a lot of ladies.
This is a very good game.
We've got the voicemail team.
I got it.
I love the energy and I want to say this is exactly what the PCP has been missing lately.
I feel refreshed. I feel energized. I feel empowered. I feel emboldened.
Do we dare to go like down the list and like have everyone introduce themselves?
I think I want to do that. I think we can do it.
Let's start at the top.
Bring back the interview.
No, shut up.
Who fucking invited you?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Pap Jelly Beaner. Who the fuck are you?
Hold on.
Welcome to the Skauby Snacks Man.
Hey, Jelly Beaner. What's going on?
Pap Jelly Beaner.
A great quote from a great man in Talladega Nights. If you're not first, you're fucking last.
If you want great fucking shaggy impressions, go to fiverr.com.
That's the best thing I've ever heard in my entire life.
Hey, who's Pap Ben Sainte?
Bitch on Ben Sainte.
It is.
I'm excited to tell everyone.
Bitch on Ben Sainte.
Who's this Pap Kosol?
Kosol.
How do you say it?
No, no.
C-Tool.
You say it like C-Tool.
Oh my god.
She's a long time.
I don't even know what you mean, Quinn.
Why would you say C-Tool?
I don't care.
It's just funny.
She doesn't care.
I'm C-Tool.
She's too old.
But you might know me, but I'll ask the person who makes you want to die.
I don't know.
I'm too old.
I am too old.
No, no, no.
Can I get an U-Woo in chat, please?
That's the stuff.
Guys, what's your favorite anime?
Wait your fucking turn.
Tony M.
It's just Ben Sainte guy.
Who's FAP Tony M?
What are you doing?
That would be me.
I'm here because I sock Ben on Twitter.
Yeah.
How my life is gone.
Follow Ben on Twitter.
Follow my hot takes on Twitter for more of that.
No, don't do it.
Hap Chocomoto.
How are you?
You know, I'm doing good.
I'm that fucking duck Chocomoto.
I'm repping my purple bros.
That's it.
Hey-oh.
Purple bros.
We will talk about this later, but we did.
We are divided into teams.
We do have races, if you will.
Races, if you will.
We do have allegiances.
Yeah.
But we'll raise war.
Who's up next?
Hap Duncun.
Hi, I'm Duncun.
I'm also not a daddy anyway.
I am the most racist.
I run the purple team and we will destroy the other teams
because they're different colors.
Raise war.
Base war.
Nice chance to be a purple team.
Very coordinating.
Hap Eleazar slash FER.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm the editor of the PCP.
Ben, why do you do this to me?
How do you prepare for me to edit this episode?
My beauty is going to blow.
We have an editor?
We have a podcast?
Don't edit anything.
Just put all the audio files together.
And that's the episode.
Don't do anything.
Oh, yeah.
It's so fun.
Yeah.
Eleazar is so easy.
Like, what are you even talking about?
Yeah.
Like, what do you do?
What do you do?
I'm making a joke about not having an editor.
So why don't you make this episode sound like we don't?
Perfect.
Kajorah Bitterthorn.
It's just going to be why Kajorah Bitterthorn.
Tell me.
Hap Kajorah Bitterthorn.
Introduce yourself.
Explain yourself.
What's up, guys?
Kajorah Bitterthorn here.
Your local crypto aristocrat and waifu coin whale.
Hell yeah.
Vessel waifu coin.
I just look up.
He's also brown.
Same.
Yes.
No need, bro.
Who are you?
Yes.
I'm here to also wrap the purple team.
Procrastinator's Anonymous is better.
Procrastinator's Anonymous swiftly colonized the purple team,
leading to a huge power imbalance that will have repercussions throughout history.
Yeah.
Rito Torpedo also, Pap.
What's up?
Yes, yes.
I majored in offensive cooming and I have a minor in phrenology.
With a pedigree like that, you're doomed to be a barista, I think.
Bazinga.
No barista.
Yeah.
Pap Shondan.
How's it going?
Hey, guys.
I'm a big gamer, notorious gamer, big Yu-Gi-Oh head.
That's also what I'm known as.
I'm also a big proponent of the N word, because I am the king of the Nate heads.
Fuck them.
Fuck Nate heads.
Oh, no.
Amen to that.
The real N word.
That took a good twist.
Yeah.
We all got nervous, but humor is the relief of tension.
So you create that tension, then your relief, and everyone goes, ah, ha, ha, ha.
And we're in that way.
It's just like bad sex that could have been worse.
Pat Kodow.
Pat Zach Def, what's up?
Yeah, sup man.
This is going to be hell.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
He's so silly, so funny.
I wanted to die.
That concludes the anonymous proportion of the introductions.
Yeah.
See you next episode.
Yeah, that's it.
Boop Mozilla Fennekin, what are you doing here?
That's a good question.
How did I get in here?
It's all because I finally got out of voice jail.
Hooray.
Thank you.
I would like to thank the Academy.
Thanks.
And now I'm starting my own podcast.
I am the sole representative of the podcast of old fashioned piss shitting.
Thank you.
How did you get out of voice jail again?
You bailed me out.
Who the fuck?
I bailed myself out, actually.
On the stream?
Was that from the stream?
Yeah.
It's all thanks to Black Lives.
The stream that destroyed the channel, you know.
Yeah.
The stream that got it.
Hey, Bev, who are you again?
I'm here to rep the yellow team and the real purple team, the cop killers.
Yes.
Just going to say, it's almost just a school certainty.
Someone here has coronavirus and that's pretty funny.
Yeah.
Is it, is it, do you think so?
How likely do you think there's 50 people?
Or something like that, 40.
Oh, maybe in the server, not in the call.
Oh, it's a good one.
Fun fact.
If you cough into your microphone, you give people computer viruses instead.
Oh, no.
Gabe, why would you even make it when you have people to cough on their mic?
Like, yeah.
The podcast is very dangerous.
Please don't.
Everyone start coughing on their mic right now.
That would be so terrible.
This is the place.
Come now.
Okay.
Shut up, everyone.
Hey, Bobby.
What's up?
What's going on?
What's happening?
I'm just here to rep the pink team today.
I want to say fuck purple team.
None of you guys are funny.
Oh, you can suck my dick.
You're late to a death.
No, no.
Totally not something so beautiful like pink.
Listen, buddy, don't threaten to have me suck your dick.
You'll regret it.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
This check out really gay real fast.
Hey, what's a chilling chocolate?
I think I've seen, I think I know that guy.
What's up?
I fuck ass.
I shouldn't glass.
I fuck wrong.
Yeah.
I break off.
I'm just here.
To represent the yellow team, the purple team blew their load.
We're already past them.
And now all us yellows can just come together and recognizing purple is a horrible color.
It's for the children of the lie.
Yellows.
I'm all sick of you.
Yeah.
Oh, God, love this.
I preach.
Praise God.
Yep.
CJ, how are you today?
I loved you and GTA.
What?
Is it the fat guy?
No, no.
I didn't get the black guy.
I was thinking the fat guy I was thinking of was also black.
Oh, sorry.
Hard one.
You don't like big smoke.
It's the GTA 5 protagonist.
So like interesting caricature characters.
Um, so anyways, CJ, how you doing?
I'm doing good.
I'm happy to be here to represent the blue team.
Perpetual underdogs, the blue team.
We are the underdogs.
I'm pretty sure we actually have like the least team members.
No, it's green.
It's green.
Is there is?
Well, God knows guys.
Blue team is still better.
Green is a numerical minority, but they have an outsized cultural impact.
They own the entertainment industry.
So it's not a creative color.
Guilty as trash.
Uh, hey, Dan.
What's the big smoke doing?
Hello there.
I just wanted to say that can we please make the thumbnail for this episode
that one image of Homer in the bar with all the,
No, you can't.
No, we can't.
Homer in the bar with all the what?
All the people around and he's just so cramped and uncomfortable.
Post it.
Post it in general.
I don't know the senior talk.
I am in favor generally of, um, Simpsons posting.
Yeah.
Great idea.
But Eleazar, can you edit the faces of each Simpsons character to all of our faces?
Yeah.
I want exactly this many figures on the thumbnail.
I want each one to be discernible at a glance in the side.
Can you deep fake the entire episode to their faces?
I like the idea.
Jamele boss being our favorite.
Icon on the screen.
This is like cats where the whole thing is just introduction.
Come on.
I, all right.
All right.
Fan base.
Hey, who's that fan base?
What's up?
I made his video.
Okay.
I thought you were silent for a second.
You edit videos.
Who would do such a thing?
That's a bad reaction.
Fan base is lagging a little bit.
Maybe it's like far away from my microphone.
That might be it.
Oh, there you are.
I was just leaning back.
But I guess I can't do that.
Oh, maybe that's why you're quiet.
Okay.
It's like, it just takes so long for my voice to reach the microphone.
I'm speaking through a tin can to connect to do a string from like my neighbor's tree
house.
It's been a little loopy.
It's a sound wave.
It moves slower here in England.
I'm not sure if this person joined.
We have been saints now.
One of those fun Google.
Yeah.
No, the other one.
Wait, who is that?
I think they joined.
It's been saying, duh.
Who are you?
Wait, can we just all.
Wait, wait, wait.
This person's verified.
This person's blue.
So they should be.
No.
I don't think he's not recording.
Are you?
Are you sure?
He hasn't said anything at all.
Yeah.
By the way, I think.
Okay.
Yeah.
Wait, what?
Greg.
That's over.
Killed.
Well, I mean, okay.
I mean, whatever.
It's fine.
No, no.
It's been.
We can all be bent.
We could.
Yeah.
It's fine.
We're.
We're changing.
Okay.
Fat man falling.
How, how's it going?
Hey, I am doing good.
I just put out a video.
I'm only here for self promotion.
Go watch it.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm only here for self promotion.
Go watch it.
Hi.
I'm a degenerate.
Go punish me by disliking my video.
Wait, you don't know what your video is.
Tell us what your video is.
Post.
Yeah, what is the video?
It's a Ruby volume six review.
I complain about fake anime.
I have no personality of my own.
I want to watch it.
Ruby rose better than age bomber guys with you.
It is.
Yeah.
I think I can.
Your channel is also called fat man falling.
Okay.
All right.
Give it a fucking.
Give it a fucking down vote.
Give go report it.
I can't wait to learn that Ruby season six is bad.
I can't wait to find that out.
This mystery.
Fuck boy McSweet.
Tell me your life story right now.
My life story.
Okay.
So here we go.
I am the bastard spawn of sick Rick the creator of multiple me by
unless just.
Then I died.
And in that span of time, I created an album.
And now I'm just dead.
If only we could have had sick Rick in here instead of his
worthless fail son.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
That was that would be that would be legendary.
Who's playing that.
Based.
Who's this Gibbon take character.
I think we can skip that.
I don't think that's important.
Did she.
They're not recording.
She's not.
She's not recording.
She's not talking.
Yeah.
This is the worst thing that I'm going to fucking have.
I'm going to have her pay deducted.
I'm going to have.
Penalty, penalty, penalty.
It's like.
Given he takes us out of here more like how much of a cut of
how many PCP dollars do we get for this episode.
Haha.
You all this is slave labor.
This is fucking.
I'm crowdsourcing this to save on production costs.
You're all.
We'll get another pin.
You will getting paid.
Did anybody hear anything?
You're back.
What's up?
Go to.
Everyone in the call.
And you will see me drawing the Tezuka.
And if you are listening to this episode.
It's like, like the one person who didn't appear here.
And it's like listening to it like later on Friday.
I will have almost completed the Tezuka manga.
The Clarissa.
And it's real cool.
I'll be there.
And I just want to, I just want to like bring forth a topic of
discussion for this podcast after everyone has said who they
are.
Is a person and how big she is and how she gets stomp on you and
crush easily.
Yeah.
He's a kid.
The most can't wait.
If.
No.
If she went toe-to-toe against muscular.
Ask.
Here.
Here in the Chad.
How would she do.
She do hers.
What would happen.
Yes.
Let's go.
Missing.
All right.
Let's move on to do.
What's up.
Please.
Play this song.
Oh man.
He's really quiet.
You're very,
You're very quiet.
Can you get close to the.
Like one inch tall.
You know where it's quiet.
Your voice is a reflection of how tall you are.
Please suck on your mic.
Can you hear me now?
Hello?
Yes, much better.
All right, sorry about that.
No problem.
Hoodie, I'm a YouTuber, but fuck that.
More importantly, I write comics.
You can go on webtoons and shit.
You don't draw comics.
How do we find them?
What's your handle?
You can just look up Hoodie Song on webtoons.
You can find all right a Pokemon comic.
And I also did like a fantasy comic about it.
Is it a Nuzlocke comic?
It was loosely based on a Nuzlocke that I did, but it is like a narrative.
Okay.
Based.
Iluzon?
Iluzon.
Yeah, yeah.
What's up?
Hello, that's me.
I started 50 million things and I finished single one of them mostly.
And I am the best because I am in the red team.
Kill Communism, Communism Scrinch.
And I wow to give all the proceeds from these episodes to Eleazar to buy a new computer.
We're going to have to get that request read tomorrow.
Also, everybody check out, check out the prototype, which is the prototype of the game we are looking
for money for.
What's the game called?
Velvetist.
Like velvet.
What's the game of that?
V-E-L-V-E-D-I-S-T.
It's like GTA, but during Communism.
And then you go through the Velvet Revolution and into the 90s.
And it's a gangster mafia comedy.
Velvetist.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Velvetist.
I understand.
You know.
I don't know how to say this name.
Kerham.
I can talk to you.
I don't know how to say this name.
Kerham.
Kuram.
I can also...
Keram.
Kuram.
How did you come to be on the Procrastinator's podcast?
Sup sup.
I messaged Ben and now I'm here.
I
Princess beach
Who is right? Okay king protus. Well, I King Potus. What the fuck?
Hey guys, so happy to be on here. I'm really nervous
I'm a few voicemails, and I did the funny how you know mom mom on recording. No
No, no, don't turn off the internet
The long con on that bit
Perfect never never paint talk to me
It's anyone still listening to this
Hello, I'm never pained. I always draw. I made a dating sim about the PCP once that's right
And I made an animation a Reese release just yesterday animated showed
Never forest max dream go watch it on YouTube
I
Never paint
What huh where am I what who's what's going on just go to the next
Hey, it's it's nexus. What's hey who's hey it's nexus. Is that one guy?
That makes exactly
Yeah, that's a mate. Hey hey nexus remember when you drew that stuff for the Vapors book that's coming out
Yeah, that was pretty neat. Yeah, that was a pretty cool a cool time
Every single page, but yeah, you remember remember that all the other stuff you draw all the time
I
Can find my stuff
Tapas, you know the side tapas. Yeah, we're next next mania next mania. Yes base
I think people probably senior senior work posts. Yeah, I love nexus. Yeah
What's up
Hey, okay, you there tell us and tell us about yourself
You know, I I had a feeling this might happen
We're gonna sold you're on we're gonna
Hey, how did you come to be here now?
Well, I found it the good girls and
Yes, then I heard that the podcast was going on and I decided I would take part
Correct and what's what's your life story? I?
Grew up in a cult and
then I transitioned and
Nice really
R. C. K. Is basically the highlight of my wife. Oh
My god. Wow
I
Spend some time as a top killer
Yes
Let's let's just let's all just commiserate on our about our fck. No, we can't know we can't
Oh
Can I can I just can I can we just talk about
We have nine more people
Going five five and oh against munchie in the slime fast
Robo Robo worst PCP fan talk to me
What's up, and Mr. Robo, I'm 24 years old 23. I love to dance. I sell pottery into kids and rapes hit me up
No, no, you can't get me killers. You will never get me
You make munchies didn't you make munchies team that he lost five and oh, hey
Hey, hey in my defense in my defense munchie munchie was put in a bad position. You know, there were like killers
Hey, I can shit by my strategy at the best if I can prove it to you
I'm gonna defeat you with that team. We can renaissance fast with me. I'm gonna destroy you every time
It's perfect
We'll see about that sweet sweet
What up, it's it's me sweet mouse the wandering suzerain of social welfare aka malinax aka
Doppelkaiser Alexander the first of Russia
I've been described as combining a theoretical love of mankind with a practical contempt for men well-meaning and egotistical
I was so good at playing a part that Napoleon dubbed me the Talmer of the North and later
I
Like to make music
That's not me
Hey cool, hey cool and cool and good, but let's talk about this tarbuck transom fellow. What's what's that his deal?
Hey, I am fast-talking craftsman an indestructible super god tarbuck transom who you may better remember as the belt guy
Yes, I'm not to continue belt. Oh my god belt guy
Tarbuck wait
Tarbuck made me if at birth he was at Barone con
And that was when I met him and he made me he makes he made me this a cop killer
Oh belt out of these woven like fibers and it's like black and purple and green it looks sick
And a bracelet too. I have some deep lore about that belt and all the belt saga to reveal later in this episode
Next it is is the girl inside Ben St. What's who who the fuck is that?
I
I am the girl I am the repressed girl inside of Ben St. Who she has been repressing for her entire life and
Refuses to acknowledge me. I'm very sad. However, I do live rent-free inside. I do live rent-free inside of her head
So, I mean I have that going on for me. So pretty
I could see I could see how one could be base about that. All right. Well, that's very that's very uncomfortable for me
Hey, it's the teen CP also known I think as a podcast
Also known as
Eating something with spoons in that's in the voice jail, right?
The teen CP I haven't heard that name in years. Is this
But it's your screen cast I'm on it is I vowed I would never return podcast to the lowest
But I must I must continue for my fallen brethren munchy too old doesn't care anymore
And he Fred didn't didn't come early enough because his mom I guess his mom told him to like not I don't know
The brown on cast literally the worst thing I've ever heard of why would you put pro-crash pro and on with that?
Like 15 episodes that's like literally hours of content you could have spent doing really anything else
You could have spent it getting muscle. You could have spent a game
You
Can I stop and say something real quick? Yeah. Yeah, go for it. Well, I'll sorry. I'll sorry
I live in the same country as you if you keep interrupting the people with your music
I'm gonna go and kill you and if you kill the editor of the PCP you become the editor
Argentina screaming
These we have three people left
Ben said he likes people being based not playing base
Oh
We got we got this is beans who is who is this is beans?
Fight me. Yeah, I am the only person here who is unironically black
I
Know what's making money, it's great. What do you mean by unironically?
I was an ironic I was ironically black, but then you know
I
Mean I'm in way I'm in way over my death here. This is beans as bean boys. We're gonna stick together. You know what I mean?
We're done this podcast
Tom fucked it up he left the call. I love this episode
Right now, I don't know how to do
No
Continue I love you Tom. Toya. Hey, Toya
Hey, my name is Toya. I'm a voice actor. Yeah
Wanna fucking kill myself I entered this call an hour ago, and I am convinced that this is what hell is
Remember we decided teams for this. Yeah, me too
I think
I
Just made a tweet
Anyone want to be in this he's a pause for a second to give the actual backstory for how this happened, right?
I think I'm staying up really fucking late all week
In the morning Ben adds everyone in the procrastinators chat. This is the idea. I'm pitching if nobody says no, I'm doing it
No one responds because it's more in the morning. He's like I'm doing it
I
Different person okay drunk
It's completely unrelated to sober Ben and sober Ben cannot take responsibility for any of his actions. Thank you
It's not our fault
I don't I don't know if that's true, and I have no way to confirm
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do unless anyone begs me to stop and even then they really have to milk it
I'm really appealed to my kinder nature. I'm gonna put out an open call
Anyone who wants to be a guest in the PCP
Having an all-guest episode
Members are too busy with so many lofty pursuits
And you know what why should I deny them base base base for 25 a.m. Okay
This is
According here
This is not a troller meme
No, no, that can't be that does sound like something I would say and do
It's time to talk about how big Clarissa is and how much she can crush me. So, okay, I'll go first
I'm sweet mouse and I'm like very small so I could be extra crushed by Clarissa
You will try
If Melissa would be able to crash them I think that sounds like a good use of time
Here
Big tits are fucking disgusting small tits are way better
Oh
We can talk with we can talk about teams, you know, I'm actually reconsidering the whole team idea
I
Was playing what was your plan initially well my initial plan was I didn't have a plan and I was just gonna think of something to do
I was considering
separating you all into teams and then like in a in a twist like like turning around and turning you all against one another and like
Isolating you and like forcing you to like do some sort of like prisoners dilemma like everyone
Caps a secret vote on which of their teammates is getting like kicked from the call next
Except only for the purple team
Sounds like a great idea the rest of us will totally fall
And they want to do the podcast with us
Actually do a fucking podcast that is quality. Wow doing a podcast a very
Quality are literally like those are mutually exclusive terms
You never got to experience
I'm running in her
ASMR episode was a masterpiece
One person every two minutes until there is only like two people in the call
Give and take how's the how's the Tezuka contest how's your drawing going?
Watch the fuck
Subscribe to streams put bits in the jar, but it's getting it's a page
Out of 50 and so the I think by Wednesday, I should be done with a line art on Friday. I might be done with the whole thing
Do you actually like cut out all the panels you needed to to make it a coherent with the within the constraints?
It's coherent enough like like the the story is unfinished
Like the story that I'm set out to make it goes to page 50 where
Something bad happens and it could be continued, but it also could be like a bad ending
Yeah
Oh, no, how will she get out like in the real story there's
Explanations for that but for the Tezuka that's 50 page 50 and I'm like I'm cutting it off there
I'm gonna submit it if they say it's not a satisfying ending
I'm gonna nod my head and say Ohio because I must and that'll be that
Thank you. Thank you. I got a question. You might be spoilers. So like
Feel free to not answer but do we find out what's up with the hat?
Do we find out what's up with the hat?
No, the guy's hat I
Want to know what it's deal is
There's I mean
Initially like when I was sketching it out
I was like, it's just he's just a guy with a like he's he's the bandit king
So he's the king of the bandits so he's got a hat that looks kind of like a crown
But then I drew an eye on it and I'm like hmm
Laura potential so I won't answer the question
I got a question for Tom. Oh someone else is talking. What was that? Yeah, let the Australian speak
You make it real and physical and much so we can buy it and then
Ranch ranch ranch it would be right
If I could get like a like a toy story like Woody like doll of Clarissa. It'd be great
I
Know jelly asked earlier if there's a cool Clarissa porn right jelly is that what you asked? Yes, I want porn
There is
Encouraging some porn and you have
You were literally the first
Is Clarissa gonna is Clarissa gonna start an only fans like prompted no
She'll do it for free
Wasn't a slut she just like didn't understand sexual so she just talked about a different character. Oh, okay
Pump pump doesn't big big as big as the fan is is a fan favorite my fan. I mean me
Yeah, she's brand new and she's real big. She's nine feet tall and she's thick. That's all you really need
She's nine feet tall and she's nine feet thick
From a certain angle, yes
Hey, Tom, I really been waiting on a
On you know a new tablet review to come out when when's when he's like that Mike
Literally have a new drawing this way that I could talk about
Because I'm super fucking lazy. Oh god damn canvas 16 pro good buy it. There you go
In the description
Podcast I could if everyone's missing my patreon podcast
I'm telling you there's like 60 of them now. They come out every week not every month like these fucking lollygaggers over here
I only have so much to talk about. I'm not very interested. That's why you just
What was I'm addressing me no when is when is the been st. Livestreams gonna come back. I miss them
I
Yeah, I
I think they're probably gonna come back kind of soon cuz like I'm I finished the thing
Yeah, no, I
Wait, I finished slime and punishment and I'm gonna put out the sonichi lecture like pretty soon
Yeah, and after that. Oh god, there was like one other thing but like after that. I'm like
I have a little more
I'm like I'm like done and I'm like
Yeah, excuse me
Every now and then I just fucking finish season one of the Winnie the Pooh
I think I might I think I might I don't know
Yeah, they really are the best
You gotta make the you gotta make the Winnie the Pooh analysis so you two
Like you do the exact same thing you do you do the exact same thing you did before but then you say and that's why the left is right
My biases I feel I feel like the Winnie the Pooh videos were like overly there was like a they were like
Disproportionately liked like like a lot of people seem to really like them for some reason which is weird because they don't do very well
But like a lot of a lot of people are like they say like if asked they would like I would love you to please
Do do more of those. I don't know. I don't know why they seem to appeal
They didn't go viral
They're Winnie the Pooh who was craving Winnie the Pooh analysis. They're good. So I mean if you make a long enough one
Like anything can get big it just like I feel like it's it's not the sort of thing that would become viral
And and like and like skyrocket
It's the sort of thing that like over many years of consistent uploads suddenly everybody
Realizes it and then they go back and watch all of the things
Then make it make like a video at the end that is like a big
Yeah, just combine the videos or something
Yeah, put them all in one big video call it like the definitive Winnie the Pooh analysis and it'll get like four million views
Literally, yes
Like Winnie the Pooh was deeper than you thought
But it's not it's not though
It's how much
When they realize they'll be able to watch
You could see me lie about events that happened in between the lines. Come on. We need a poo and cap. Call the video
Call the video why eor betrays the depression community
Down the rabbit hole, but it's because it's rabbit
Going out instead of like down the honey pot we could we could we could call it like we could call it like like
We could call it like in rabbits back door because like as a reference
Should I do a Winnie the Pooh lecture, I don't know if I be qualified
Down rabbit hole
Down the rabbit hole call it stuck in the rabbit hole as a reference to that classic Winnie the Pooh episode
Oh, no step bro. I'm stuck in the rabbit hole
Tigger this is Kang this is rude. Feel old yet you you have to
So that I get too fat and stuck
That's okay. I see I see an opportunity. I'm taking it. We need a round table everyone all together
We need to shit on
Cassey and she'll for not being here. They said they were in a massive. They're you know, they're terrible people
Literally
Okay, like I'm okay. I'm all for shitting on someone. I have no idea who the identity of us. I'm all for shitting on michelle. Yeah
On three okay may also also wrote on twitter that you won't be in it
I mean, we should be glad that michelle isn't here, right who also said that they want to be on may
Is that what you said?
You should talk about uh slime and punishment releasing, uh, uh, how do you think it turned out? Uh, how was the release?
Oh, yeah, I've been hyping that up for for years. Um
Um
It was on
It was on on the slime during slime fest a debuted slime and punishment finale. It's done. It's out. It's three and a half minutes
Uh, it's got music. It's got music by six in it sounds amazing. It sounds really great for the tracks
Sixten who who tried to be here but couldn't a one minute silence for for six
But why don't you have slime and punishment on your website ben?
It it it is I I put it on it wasn't before but I I updated it
It's um, it's um, and I I think I I keep I watched it a bunch of times back
And I think that I'm really happy with some of the visual especially the part in the time void
I am really happy with how that looks and I feel like I
Kind of I in terms of like putting my vision of what it should be into
Into the video I I nailed it. It looks exactly how I wanted it to
No, can I can I can I drop some critique here some harsh real critique?
Oh, okay. No, no, you know, you know, uh, it was really cool
We had to wait a long time like almost a year for it to drop or something like that
It's not a year. No, no, well like eight months or something. Yeah, like nine months. I mean, yeah
Eight months of work, but it's okay. It is good
Uh, it's like genuinely like
Like it's like I after after ben said that like, oh, it's not as good as I thought it would be after eight months or something
Or not. It's not eight months worth of work. I thought it would be like bad, but no, it's like actually good
Yeah, this is what I said on the last episode is I know it's not eight months worth of work, but I still think it's good
Yeah
Months of time you have to like sleep and eat and live your life while also working on a thing
Yeah, it's like a week and a half, you know
I mean, it should have been a week. It should have been out sooner, but it wasn't so what are you gonna do?
It's fine. Well, but you took the time you needed and that's okay. Don't fucking condescend to me
Don't don't fucking talk down to me like I'm some kind of idiot who needs to be
Yeah, you're sucking his pee all right
I'm invalid I'm invalid
I mean truth be told truth be told, um, maybe maybe uh
I really like I really like the flip the flip was like literally all the aesthetics over actual substance
You know, I think it wasn't much as much as could have happened in a finale like this
So my final score is 10 out of 10. I appear upfront and do a funny jump and I was really glad
Okay, okay, okay
Tom Tom for real for real. Whatever you
Think like
Shut the fuck up god everyone everybody back to joining
Why is this 45 person
like people talking
Most people aren't talking I that's
I expected this to be a complete cluster fucking now because I understand anyone at all
I
Everyone
All right, all right, that's enough that's that's enough of that
That
There would be like this is why I thought there would be mini podcasts by team
Yeah, well, that's what I was gonna. That's what I wanted to bring up. I was
And with all the ideas shut up
What I was going to what I was going to do was we were gonna
I was gonna have an initial section that was everyone
And and and I assumed it would just be complete chaos
And then at some point I would we would split into teams and then I would you would keep recording
You like like keep recording yourself even when I when like us we are not in there
Or I mean
We could yes
We could
We could split it me like ben takes one and top takes a team and tom takes a team and give
Or we could just the pcp members could just go like in cycle one to the other and I was thinking maybe
It's on gib we can go
Okay, okay, so so do we want to split up into teams?
That's great
You been this podcast
I do think it's a little too late for that. No
No, it's gonna make it way more complicated. There is no need for it. No
If we just like the conversation it might be possible with uh, with you long interruptions of streaming in between, you know, I mean, I think
You know, you know what?
We're gonna have a vote. We're gonna have a fucking vote. Yeah, we're gonna do it. We're gonna vote
How are you gonna do that?
I
Okay, yeah, yes already has a majority
Uh, yeah, but okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, yeah. All right. Fine. Yeah, bobe bobe posted it in the general chair
Okay, fine. Just yeah, just react to vote
What are we voting? What is yes on whether
We don't have whether whether we split into teams whether we say no, okay
I'm I feel like that could maybe be interesting. So okay. Yeah, because we have lull michelle
We have we have teams she will she it's too late. She's not joining
I'm
Get out
Okay, so it looks like all right
We don't have to split up right now, but at some point we I don't know. Should we should we should we split now?
Okay
Keep recording keep recording yourselves. Um, we're gonna make different videos and you can choose your own
My team or how we I have an idea. I'm gonna make the team chat to the team voice chat, right?
I yeah, I'm going to make them available right now and we are gonna fucking go and and do that
Starting with red team
Welcome to the progress seniors and only monsters show about pcp
But then they all play at the same exact time
Yes
Pan slightly
Isn't it we are give him a second. We are we are I need I need to fuck around with the channel
I'm not going to cut anything
Okay, you know what that's fair
Hey, ben
Yeah, what's up?
Okay, so you can make the channels so that everyone can listen but only the colored team can speak
And that way
This is new age reparations
That might be the worst idea I've heard on this poll point
Ben, I know how discord works. I run a discord make me a model make that happen
Ben, I know how discord works. I know how children would all be the best discord moderator ever
All right girl girl inside ben saint lemal. All right. How do I how do I do that? I think I will do that actually
Yeah, just just make an admin role and then give it to me
We're instating trans fascism now, um, you're all my slave
Do you do you all do you all see do you all see the the color?
Yeah, I don't see the color ben wait you can't join them
Okay, you should you should be able to I can't join purple for some reason I can't join pink
Yeah
Yeah, let's just do the podcast here like that's a trick
We're just gonna we're just gonna split up keep recording yourselves, you know
Red team is the best but there's like only
Guess it's not that great then, huh?
Okay, so Ben Ben. Oh my god, what do we just split into teams and each team will have like a long time
I think we're are you doing the rotate thing or the uh, whatever I think actually
You're fantastic purple gone. I still can't get into pink. I think they're still working on pink. All right
This episode it's so fun
Right. Yes, hard
Massachusetts. All right, right cool red team
Uh, uh, I
What's what's going on? I gotta get I gotta get tom and uh
I gotta get tom and gibbon here
Hello, this has been a terrible idea frankly. Yeah awful. Yeah, it'd be the worst idea you've ever had
Yeah, well, you know terrible ideas actually. No, I know everybody is uh being ironic about this being the worst idea
But I think it's the best idea and because everybody is here and is having fun
I think it's actually the best idea and I you know
The the point of it, you know, it's
It's about
It's not about having fun. It's about making the commenters mad
It's about it's about all the angry comments that are going to be under it
Like wow, the pcp's really gone downhill. Like wow, they're doing this now like cringe, you know, like wow unsubscribing
Nate's not on the podcast. No, Nate. No, listen. See you next week. Uh, yeah, I did yeah
You fucking comment every fucking week for like four weeks now. I've seen that same comment and you fucking weirdo
Uh, uh, uh, what's your what's your what's what's what's his problem?
You know, like what's his deal liking Nate on ironically
Sure, I mean and that's just the start. That's just the start of this problem
The worst thing about those those comments are like the
the sort of smug
Satisfaction that the sort of like self-assuredness that they are like destroying our psyche and that they are like really fucking cutting deep
and it's like
No, it's no we're just doing the podcast and other people aren't showing up
It's as simple as that
It does seem like the pcp has both an incredibly dedicated audience
Like, you know, I don't mean this offensively
But like you guys do get relatively low numbers and still you have really high engagement on like your uh, patreon and whatnot and at the same time
it seems like
Your audience completely hates like half like each member each audience member probably has like three or four
You know members of the podcast that they just hate and it's like a really weird dynamic
That's quite that's what happens when you have a cult following that attracts autists that have hyper focus and
It's just it's just the way there's there's some weird intangible thing that these people
Really find themselves interested in and when it's not there the entire facade falls apart and they're like wow, this is terrible
I guess we set ourselves up. Yeah, you know
We definitely had like like great moments in the past
I'm sure people are just remembering those but like
I don't know. I don't necessarily think that the future is always worse
Like they they don't like the dynamic anymore
When there's less people some people do prefer it. So it's just it's a different show
Yeah, it's they they want it to be
Like the yellow episode every episode
And that's just like it's kind of in his in history now. You can't recreate that
I think yeah, I think there's a lot of people there was a lot of people to whom the yellow episode is the ideal pcp episode
If every episode was the yellow episode the yellow episode would not be special or interesting
It would just be worse than the noise. It's true. That's true. If every pcp episode was good. We wouldn't have hot dogs
I was just thinking about that
How much I want a hot dog
Last night. I was really hungry
I was curious how thick you guys's skin is because like
I do do you guys
I mean, oh like metaphorically you talk about how the yellow episode is the best episode to me that episode is like
No, literally how many inches how many how how hard would it be to skin you?
Yeah, I can't put them to me the the yellow episode is
It's almost hard to listen to sometimes because it's just arguing it is just no
I agree the yellow the yellow episode was not fun to record
It was like actually really tense and unpleasant. Yeah, I don't like it much
It really needs to be stated that like
I think it's obvious if like you kind of understand that episode but like it started in the beginning
Already kind of in an awkward situation because the argument had been going on before the episode started
And I think most of us thought it was just gibbs and gaffes and jokes
But it quickly became apparent. No, this is real rage and the longer it went on the more is just like
Oh god
This is really happening. Yeah
Yeah, yeah for sure for sure. It was not a meme. It was that was a real
I think people still think that it was like a meme and it was not a meme. No, no
It literally wanted to murder us for like a year after that and he probably still does I'd argue
I actually had had a similar experience, you know, uh when I staffed at
brony fair in in germany in berlin one year, you know, and
Uh, I I stayed at some people some people's house
Uh, some people's flat, you know, and I I like
And after the con I like was packed and everything and uh, you know, just chilling and I just asked the guy
Oh, so
What did you think of of the convention? You know, how did you like it?
and he just started going off and he he like started
Telling like one thing that was wrong after another and you know and in my mind. I was like, uh at the start
I was just
Thinking of what I would reply, you know, but after like the five minutes. I was like, okay
Maybe he's not stopping then 10 minutes. I'm like, okay. Maybe this is not worth it
And then, you know, when it started to go over 20 minutes
I was just resigned to just listening and
and he
he like
Yeah, he like
Complaints about a con for like 40 minutes. It was unbelievable
Yeah, yeah, that well that was my first experience of something that extreme. Well personally speaking. I think the podcast
I mean, listen, it's not perfect right now. I do think you guys on the upwards trend
I I think some of those past episodes aren't good to be frank. I don't hold the yellow episode in that high regard
I think the podcast as it is right now is a lot better than the audience seems to give a credit for
I think you guys have an audience that is full of whiny bitches to be honest
I I want to
As much as their favorite member is in it. So if you don't yeah the podcast is garbage, right?
If if the way if the podcast lately isn't to your taste
I'm not gonna say like I disagree like that's wrong
But but I definitely agree that they are a bunch of whiny bitches
Well, that's that's been the case since episode one. So I'm yeah
Yeah
Um, okay, we've been I think we're gonna do like a little five minute
John's we've been in five minutes. So we're gonna move on a blue team, but we will be back
No, I wanted to ask about freely printing. We will we will be we will come next time next time
I will I will be
Happy to chat about that. Okay. Here we go. Um, all right. Peace out
Oh god, this is awkward. I better I better I better
They'll
Oh, shit. Okay, they're here
They're here get your guns out get your strengths. What do you think?
I want to I want to I want to I want to talk on behalf of my team
We we learned what we learned as a team blue team blue team, baby. Here we go
Okay, we learned we learned that the pope in one timeline
Learned the beauty of Undertale and became game developer and made Dark Souls 4
Uh, thanks for listening to our thesis. Thanks. Thanks Matt. There's a lot of indie titles on steam
Who's to say that the pope isn't publishing right now?
God
I'm just trying to imagine
The pope that was like like the fucking map pack gave the pope a just a steam code not even a physical
Uh, okay, you can fight you for this out, man. You're you're good. Do you think the pope is like right?
Is do you think the pope is supporting yandere dev?
Absolutely
God has spoken to him and he says yandere yes
Actually, did you guys hear?
No, no
It's still upon him the cum chalice
Did you guys hear about uh, lovesick or the
They destroyed yandere dev's game by making the game better in like
I did
I don't know how long
Yeah, we should give that to better like they used the same
Fucking free ass free public assets and they just made the same game except better in two weeks
And then they're just like yeah, you're a fucking idiot
That sucks so bad. Oh my god
He threatened to kill himself over the fact that this game was made like please don't do it or I might hurt myself
Why don't we just do why don't we just make that game like over the course of this podcast, you know
We have done right now
like yandere dead
We should make a game jam podcast
and just
Yandere simulator
You know, we just it should be a trend just yandere devs like like speedrun just making the game
Yandere but it's but it's ben talking about communism to every single member of the
I don't understand how those things are related at all
I mean communism
You purchase the game on steam and it's just a lecture saying how you're bad
No, god, there's no ethical consumption under capitalism and it's no one's fault that they're complicit. Oh my god. Okay
Ben just goes up to people, you know capitalism kind of weird
You know, uh, uh, I just uh, I mean, uh, uh, I don't want to talk about this change the subject, please
I want I want to be I want to attempt to be like the straight man. Uh, not the not the straight man. That's like in jokes
Amen
Actually
Something meaningful and not like every other. Yeah pretty cringe
But you know, you know, if you are enough cringe surrounded by other people are cringe
might be a little bit base
That's what I learned from the pc
That's what I learned when I played undertale with the pope
Yeah, see it seems to be noted. So, uh, uh, well, what what do you guys think about like this?
Like having your fans get inside the thing you are making your
Your fans getting inside
I think that it's a great I think that it's a great source of free labor for me to extract surplus value from
So you're saying you're not having the mobile move
We are we are not capitalists. We are slave owners right now. We're we're we're straight up feudal monarchs
Anymore permanent podcasts us
Extract those tives, you know
Feels good. This is this is this is it. It's time for you all to pay the piper. We've entertained you for years and now
We call upon you
Jesus Christ
We know it was then it would like jesus on the beach now you have to carry us. There's only one set of footprints
But it's actually like 40 sets because there's like 50 people in here. So, you know
Ben points at the crowd now it's your turn
Yeah, I totally was not just away from my computer just now guys. I was I'm
Completely in on this conversation
That sounds like a great time for us to move on to yellow team, but we'll be back
I can't do this
We're just waiting for ben. Why is he taking so long? Why does he take even one side?
How is it that ben is late even when
Yeah, like on the thing
I'm a fucking idiot
It takes me so fucking long just to move craig from one room to another
Ben you can and you can just click on craig and drag him to a different
If you're on death, you really want to realize that craig is not a person. That's epic. Wait, really? Yeah
I think that breaks them. I think that breaks it. Uh, I oh if it breaks it, fuck you
Okay, I don't want to I don't want to risk it. I don't want to I know it breaks music bots
That's all I know or you stew. Okay better better not to better not to chance it then
Um, but so how how's everyone doing over here in the yellow room?
We're doing good. We were we were positive talking the pcp and shit talking the purple team, you know
Exciting stuff. We were trying to work our own identity. Let's let's shit talk the purple team. Yeah. Yeah
Before we shit on the purple team, I want to take an extra moment to shed on ellie is our specifically
Who was by far the most disruptive person in the general chat?
You're supposed to be the fucking editor. He went he leaned way too into the meme
He expected it to be chaos. We wanted to play into that and it didn't work and he was not charming and I fucking hate him
and I guarantee
He's he's not he's not gonna use the audacity audio from fucking anyone because someone's gonna fucking
There's no point in all of us recording. He's going to use craig because he's a lazy piece of shit
There's no he's gonna sing all these different
Podcast I don't think ellie is lazy. I think I'll use it. I mean, I I don't know. I guess I'm okay. No
Your rent is like completely leaped out
Because I was in charge. Yeah
I know you're listening ellie is our fuck you guys
I have the power to erase you from existence
I don't want ellie is our to erase this group for
The coolest stalin picture
The person next to stalin it's just like rubbed out, you know
Yeah
He has a full nine inches. He's the best guitar player on earth
Uh, uh, yeah, he probably probably the most I haven't seen his face
But like you can tell he's incredibly handsome like at least
I wish that apple was me
I'm speaking possibly, uh, give stupid idiot corner a funny jingle a good part of the podcast
That's too, uh, you know, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Given I want to say thank you on stream for the flourisheship for randomly drawing a hoop snake
And then drawing it again once you realize that you do it wrong
Oh, yeah, yeah
Thank you for drawing a zucchini punk. Oh
Oh, yeah, zucchini punk. Oh
Guys, I think it's important to go back to what's important in life though, and that's shitting on the purple team. Yeah
I don't know a hundred percent agreed
Is
We are we are the color of the sun we bask in light
Uh, every purple team is like that's just following the crowd pink is like, oh three people
I just want I'm not like the other girls
All right, my my experience with the other team is red red is pretty chill
Blue is kind of is kind of rambunctious yellow is like caddy and like mean
Good
Ben, you know, I'm I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna overcome the reputation by saying, you know
Slime and punishment of base a winning 5-0
Talking about rck and pcb is always good by the way. Um, I mean I appreciate that
You know, I don't ironically
I don't ironically been I've actually been rewatching, uh, the nuzlocs. I'm they're really good
I really hope you do one again someday every every once in a while
Someone someone like messages me on twitter or on or I get a message on a youtube videos the nuzloc videos
It's like yeah rewatching these again like, you know, I come back to these every once in a while and I'm like, ah
Man, I love I love I love I love that people do that. Yeah, okay
Speaking of teams having
This is a call out post to everyone. I don't have a middle of ground. I'm so sorry. No, this is much better. This is much better
Yeah, okay. This is this is a call
Oh my god
Say his thing
Okay, so yeah, so I realized something so we know that now
Diginee has changed her channel to diginee and digibro
So with what said I have realized that technically digibro aka may has been grandfathered in the procrastinator's podcast
So therefore I was wondering
Ben could you theoretically change your name to ben saint and the entirety of antifa and therefore make all of antifa
a member of the procrastinator
um
Mom could also add a zoomie or whatever and give him a handle of the characters
You've explained it so clearly that I you've answered your own question. Obviously. Yes, I can do that
That's that's well within every every uh member like all of all of the signed up members of antifa
All the members of the antifa organization are about to
I've seen I've seen like fake sign-up forms going around and I'm pretty sure it's like
It's like right wingers like sending them around to get people to sign up
I'd like to get their identity and like harass them or something to put them on
I know this one. There was there was this website that was like join antifa dot com and somebody just
Somebody just looked in the like in the like data of the website and it was Ben Shapiro's
Uh email
It was made by it was made by a left-wing person and it was just a joke. It was an easter egg
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It was it was funny. It does exist. It was really funny. Yeah
It was funny
uh
It was deliberately funny, but it's still funny. Yeah, okay
A sign what were you saying before I started to cut you off
Yeah, I feel like an idiot for speaking over death alchemist, but I'm I guess I'll say it anyway
I have the spotlight now. This is this is a call-out post because uh to anyone who listens to this bullshit
Right now. Oh, yeah
We we have we have we have teams. They have personalities. We need fan art. I want fan art
Of the teams. Yeah, you're listening right now. Make the fucking fan art or I will kill you. This is me being catty
Maybe a team or the catty team. So we need to all be cat
Maybe I maybe I can get maybe I can get married
Yeah, we need to like hire someone to draw like red team chan and like blue team
Yeah
Well-rounded rich characters
We need to be like the short spiky haired yellow haired girl with like the two little like spiky tooth
The that's like max from Beyblade. That's that's well, that was I won't talk about rad con
But that reminds me of something from rad con that is a still a secret. Hey, we got to get moving. We got to move
Wait, I have one final PSA. I have one last thing to say
Uh
PCP terrible for your health. You're the reason people are dying one hurry. Hunna speedrun
You should not be conditioning for less than three minutes
Your hair will get dry and you will be a bad person
So three minutes is the absolute absolute minimum for the speedrun and two keto diet is shit
I did it lost 15 pounds gained it all back. I did a real diet and I lost 50 pounds
Uh keto is bad
Um
Stupid
Uh now now 10 years of been trying to move craig
Oh
Why are tech god, they're right endless war is impossible to play text commands are so difficult
Okay, hello, we're we're here we're here green team. How's it how's it how's it hang it's going good
Energy is nice and calm. It's it's it's a good feeling
My regret is that my name starts with t and my team was green. So in both cases
I'm like three quarters of the way down the list
Uh
Oh, I thought you were gonna say it was like a pun like green tea. I thought that's where you're going with that
That would have been that would have been way more more coherent
They're thinking that we have a sense of humor
What do we think guys
Who's the worst team? Who's the worst team?
There are no worse team. We're all the same. We just split off from like a main team. We're the same team
That's that's too. That's a little too
That's a little too reasonable
This is the reasonable group. We figured it. We found them. This is the reasonable people the neutral party red was pretty reasonable
I'm forced to pick one. I'm going to pick purple just because of the the total number of people who are
shit posters without substance
That man has good content. I don't know fat man has pretty solid content. Yeah, but we're not counting good things
We're counting bad things
We're gonna be counting all day bad things
um
guys
You uh, you how about how about how about how I murdered munchie and slime fast pretty funny, right?
Pretty cool. Yeah, I lost all my slimes. I've been playing much, but uh, you know, that's
Uh, munchie lost all his too. So fuck him, you know, you know, he's that's that buster. He got busted
Bro, I didn't even get killed. I just it was just like nope level one again
Oh, you you fell victim to um, what do you call it a slime decay?
That must be it, right?
Just like I think it was after an update. I think it just happened right after an update
Oh, maybe that was during the dream arc when everything everyone was asleep and it was all a dream
Oh, okay. Yeah, that makes sense. Also, I'm a little concerned because I'm hearing thunder out my window
And if my power goes out, I will perish. No, same
I'm about I'm in middle sex county right now. So like, uh, it's not not it's not that bad
It's not that bad
What you need is an uninterruptible power supply. So it gives you like a five minute buffer for you to save and shut everything down
Uh, what is that? Is that like a generator or is that real? It's it's like a it's like a power strip
But like big kind of running and it's got a small battery in it
That battery backup power
Well, that battery continues or running after the power goes off up to a certain limit and then like
Shut down or yes, that's exactly that's that's good. That means you can save your work
That's always the worst thing. Yep
I haven't had a power outage in like
A number of years
I'm jelly. We have power out. Okay. So guys, should I talk about shit core right now?
Well, before you get into this, I want to
I want to fulfill the prophecy
Hey, Tom. Okay. Yo, what's up?
So you probably will only remember this about halfway through me explaining it, but okay. Um
Millions of years ago when the world was new and you made videos about my little pony
I hate you up
Uh to ask if you wanted a custom belt
Yeah
Literally in my field of vision right now
Right belt saga actually began with tom
I see
Yeah, everyone it seemed like when we got to brony con it seemed like everyone knew you and like you were the belka
And like I had never heard of you before and I was like, what is what is this? What is what was it?
Was it I think it was you found nate first or something and and natin happened to need a belt and then that was very
Amusing that you were a belt guy. Yeah, and then I
Spotted into something amazing like that. That's so fucking sick
Yeah, I and I saw you and I saw you making the belt live the belt has your belt skill improved
Substantially since that long distant past. Well when I set you that belt I had
Six patterns that I could weave and now I have 42 and all the rest of them are my own invention
That's pretty intense
Yeah, I think I like send you a high resolution photo of this belt
So you can do one of those memes on twitter where it's like 2013 versus 2020 and uh blow people's minds
Yeah, yeah, do you think you could like make a cape out of that?
Like a belt that just keeps on going
I could it could be done
It could be done. It would be a little unwieldy to wear because nylon is very heavy
Maybe a like a flower buds get or something. Hmm. I think you could make like a pleated kilt or something like that
That's a little more doable
But I mean to anybody who was there on the day, you know what the process looks like
That is and to get more width. I need more fingers
Which I uh, I'm currently at my at the limit of my finger subscription
This is as high as the uh as the subscription tier goes
And I hope I don't miss a payment. Otherwise, I'll just be like down half of my usable usable digits
Do we we gotta we gotta move on to purple team? Is there anything any any last minute last minute things?
Hey, what the fuck? I never got to talk about shit core. I didn't mean oh, you're right
Uh, you yeah, what's about what about shit core?
Okay, so do you do y'all know about shit core?
No, don't know. No. Okay. So shit core is a genre of music
Except it's not really a genre because you can play any genre you want. It's just about making the music bad
And so how I found out about this is from absolute trash media
Jesus, I found I found out about this from miss sarah louise
Uh, in other words blind sky watcher who is the musician who created a lot of the instrumentals for digi
nay digi nays
What's it called?
Go trial of the golden witch. Yes those albums. Yeah
and so
Okay
So there are a lot of albums on this label absolute trash media
Uh, in uh, in fact, you can just scroll for ages and never get to the bottom
Because more and more people just joining and create albums for this shit wait
And this is this third generation of this
Because the first generation you can't even write you you can't even reach that on the internet because that has been deleted
But the second generation vortex of crap dot bandcamp dot com
But there was a previous vortex of crap which contained like a hundred albums and that's just deleted
so
We got
Anyway
What's what's what's the what's the pitch like how does it sound like? Well, how would you describe it?
um
It sounds like a quality genre rather than just like blowing out your speakers with like
Times the amount of gain is actually kind of nice. It's weird. Okay, so you you can make that
um, that is actually
A lot of the albums are just like that
That ties the genre together than in a than like a sound is that kind of like the idea
How they would describe it on their discord channel it's just that they make music in order to make each other laugh
Okay, so it can make
Yeah
Okay, okay
Sorry, I'm sorry, but we've been here for too long. We gotta keep moving. We will be back
We will be back
Okay, we are going we're going to purple. We will be back in a little bit when we make our way around again
Oh multiple laps cool. We're making we're doing multiple laps. Yes, uh
Trying to keep the pace up. We'll be a group sinks in case we need to leave or at the end. We will probably all
um join up again
Uh, yes, uh, okay
Uh be be back be bex bebex soon
Shut up. I'm gonna shut up
One of the best is not a mess with a guest the the pcp the only three members
I'm like
Pre-edited
Crazy lightning hitting outside my house and I'm like yikes. I'm like I could be I could power at any minute honestly
I would be just to be smited
But if that if that happens top common give I have given you admin permission you have control of the voice of the
No
Be a pretty girl
What's up two things first, please make the episode less than three hours or I'm gonna have
I'm on your resume right now
Okay, that's fair
Why do you do this to me? Why I send you messages on this or about my concerns regarding anything this episode
You didn't answer none. I do answer none of them
Why do you do this to me? Yeah
Wait, you didn't you didn't DM me did you?
What are your concerns because they are never communicated to the rest of us. I know I
Don't know what what do you want from me, you know, we tell the film but all they hear is uh, hola, how are you?
Eleazar like I'm sorry. I'm sorry to call you. I'm sorry to call you in this
Eleazar
Eleazar you're you're lying because I'm looking and you didn't DM me
PC pc in the magic universe
Oh, who the fuck checks that
I see
I want the other podcast. Yeah, how's how are they going for you?
I don't know. Eleazar that last statement you put out seems to cover everything Ben's done so far
So
For the audience
To be a one episode thing I would have no problem on having lots of people and it being a clusterfuck you gave
Of course
You saw
Message
Are you've lost your melanin privileges hand them over?
Yeah, Eleazar you better vote for jellybiden
Yeah
Certain groups have certain auras
So we're gonna we're sort of thinking who's the best one and we're gonna ask everyone
Like who's who's the best
And shit talk and do bad things right now the funniest and the coolest
That is true
Beatable. We are the cute and the funniest
We're the biggest
Are we doing voicemails? Is that happening?
We're floundering
Ben load them up
Yeah, absolutely. Okay. No no problem. I got one for I got one hot and fresh out of the oven for you
No, this will be the first one, but
Okay
We are all gay
And I'm posting it in the in the purples in the purples chat
You can just scream it, you know
We are listening to it right now, I think a lot of people in this world are by and just don't know it
They are able to get by by being straight and they don't even consider the alternative
So
Just go out
eat a pussy
Being straight is a gateway sexuality to being by I never thought about it like that
You should wait wait what I mean. Yes, but why I think he's he's just right
What
Not not to be that guy, but I think conventional like sexuality is literally just a myth propped up by christian and
Yeah, he's clearly just on the recruit
We're all on the spectrum, right? We're all on the fucking kinsie scale
This is true
Hold on hold on hold on that is true
Sam, will you get a voicemail like this? You need to preface it by saying this is liberal propaganda for the all that
That would be fair. I can't do it
I
Had a very serious question about your slime and punishment
Yes, very good. Was there any uh inspiration drawn from the world plates and that um, what is that?
Yeah, no good quit. No, not really. It's actually based on um, because in episode 15 and 16 of sonichu
Magi-chan they go to the time point and magi-chan creates a ball and sonichu runs in the ball
And it rolls like a hamster wheel and that's what moves it forward and back up your time
Yeah, that's how they use the time orb to yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so the idea of it rolling
That the other day in preparation for slime punishment and 102 and I am mix. I'm on the edge of my fucking seat waiting for it
Can we get done a good job for what?
for the lecture
Oh, probably not more than a few weeks. I think awesome. Awesome. Yeah pretty pretty spaced
Can I just say you're an absolute chad for like low key dissing digi and they in the fucking
Message you sent them you are a chiro. You're a champion and I mean, I mean, I just don't understand
I don't understand people that just
A little bit of
More a little bit
Consistent
We got a we got a we got a we got to move on to pink team any last
Okay, can I just say one thing? We're sorry
Give you are cool and I love you and I like you but please for the next lecture explain what you're talking about
It's riska that that's that's the best thing around you don't need to know nothing except that riska is base
When will you be in the green ranger? When are you going to do a green ranger cosplay?
When I've always thought that if I ever got to like $2,000 on patreon
I would spend all the money on getting a complete accurate green ranger outfit. You know what to do everybody
patreon.com slash tomyoliver
Literally since 2012 that's always been like a
Is a goal
Our guests have left us
We're back in the
Okay, I'm getting I'm getting faster at this I'm getting faster at this whole
Hello, what's up?
We've you're you're the you're the last boys
Yeah
We have sampled we have sampled every team thus far and gotten a taste of their unique culture
Uh-huh, and we're gonna do the same to you whether you like it or not. What's what's going on?
What's going on over here in the in the pink team?
I'm talking
Sorry about stuff
Like half the people who are supposed to show up
So it's just been a real quiet quiet. Yeah, we thought we were like more than double our size
But we're just three lone souls
Three lone creatives. Yeah
That's uh, that's that's how it be. I I expected a lot of people
That like got verified wouldn't actually show up. That's just how these things go. Yeah, I mean we're lucky
Yeah, yeah
So what's what's the worst team?
purple
Okay, everyone has said purple
In this time we've decided to start beef with the pro and on cast so yeah
Good has been declared
Even even the even the humble green team the the green team is very like
It's pretty serious. It's pretty like it's not not overly concerned with uh with sentiment
It's just kind of like well here we are and we're gonna do or go through the craftsmen
They're craftsmen over there. What about the red team? Like is it awkward for just two people there?
They seem fine. Maybe when we get back there at all more than two people when we
No, that there was only two and then the three of us made five
I think yeah, I think it was just it was just the two of them. It's just two people
um
Even even the even the humble green team was like, eh, I guess purple team is probably the worst so
No, we hate the purple team with the with the passion. That's great. I love that
That's those are the two team personality traits hating the purple team and chilling our art
Yeah, yeah, shilling is good. I like already made a group
Really never we've shared our art shamelessly
I never paint. I I saw your film the other day. I liked it. It was very good. Thank you film
Wait, you really? Yeah, it's a short short anime. It's an animated short. It's like six minutes or something
It's it's two minutes. It was it was it felt like longer than two
Link in the description. Oh, yeah, put that in the description. You're on a speed more work. I'm gonna get to work
Um, yeah, no, that was that was very nice to work on. It's my first
Thingy that I did like everyone always talks about how animation is that big scary thing
That's so much work, but they never talk about that. It's also fun and rewarding and cool
But you like draw something and then it moves
It's like you're done, but the process leading up to being done is a painful nightmare
I think the love of the time it's it's because people have
Lofty ambitions of making an entire show or an entire like movie feature film like a gibby
And like making a an animated short is like relatively doable. You just need a couple months
Um, depending on the size and you can make a little thing and it'll it'll be great. It's fun
Only took like three weeks for this one. It was a school project
It's always nice when you can do school projects, but also do your own thing because the topics are loose. Oh, yeah, totally
Yeah, because I um, I am on like the school news
We're at where I'm at and I've been able to make a couple just really stupid projects and just have that
Also in the school news
Yeah, holy shit
I'm a real
Schools have news
Do you report on?
On campus this week
How many wedgies were there do you have murder mysteries at your school infinite wedgies?
What kind of school do you go to where there's murder mysteries?
Yeah, it's just that cool. You know, we kill people criminal justice school, you know, they gotta gotta keep them on their toes
The school newspaper has to murder people themselves
I get you gotta learn by doing
Yeah
Also, ben, I just want to say I am the sociopath who started the uh started the uh canonized ben as a saint petition
Oh
What's what's your name on twitter?
I think it's it's like will turn turn because that's my real name and then like some numbers
But squilliam fancy son. I think is the name. Yes squilliam fancy son. Okay
That that was like my that's like my artist's name that I chose a long time ago and I've regretted ever since
Yeah, seems seems good choice to me
Uh, uh, I should I should retweet that more often and be like, hey guys, we still and we've only we still have not gotten 100 signatures
What the fuck? Why are we slacking? Hope frances has not canonized you yet
Does he have the power to do that?
I mean, yes, I think so. I guess if anyone does it would probably be him
So, okay
And we should just get him we should just talk to him about undertale. He look we know he loves undertale
And that's another one. We should bond. We should just bond with him over that
Do you think we can get him in call right now? Does anyone need to have his discord?
I would say timezones, you know timezones. Oh, yeah
It many times on nine. I'm in the same time zone
Yeah, yeah, it's my neighbor. Are you in italy? No, I'm in germany
Okay
Yeah
Both uh, horde your roman empire. So it's fine
Uh, do you guys want to hear a voicemail?
Yeah
Let's let's do a voicemail while while we're here. Okay. I'm gonna post it. I'm gonna post it in the pink chat. This one is called
Want to do bitcoins?
Oh, no
Here we go. We're gonna we're gonna let's give that a listen on
Three two one play. Hey guys, it's me david here. I was watching my favorite youtube channel
Jake paul the other day and I realized, you know, jake paul is rich
And I I want to be rich
So I was looking into developing my own own bitcoin
And I asked my mommy about it and she told me I was too young to do that
So what I wanted to know is if you guys were interested
In DMing me to launch our bitcoin up off the ground
So we can become like jake paul one of the 1% and so ben can shed a tear because he's a socialist cry, baby
I
Could I just say I really feel the power trip for making shitty voicemails to listening to them? Yeah, right?
It's a whole different world over here
On this on this side of the equation
I think we had pc pennies and like as a potential concept
Yeah, but but nobody wanted to actually figure it out on the records and it's it's you know
It's a lot of work if somebody made real pc penny crypto
That would be the most amazing thing and I'm sure that it would go to the moon. It would put ripple xrp to shame
I will say
Because I never too young to bitcoin. They were talking about being too young
Bullshit, you can be six years old and make a coin and we're like go
There's like a whole video about like some really young kid or like did a startup to get like a coin thing going
He's going to conventions and stuff for crypto. This is real. You could do it
This guy's just using his mom as an excuse. You think real self starters don't listen to their parents
Fucking idiot have to be a true and cap and just sell your body for some bitcoin
I don't I don't even think this mom who doesn't think who thinks he's too young to make his own bitcoin is real
I think that's just like the personification of his internalized self-doubt or whatever
Agreed. Oh, I think you completely hard agree. There is no mom in quotes. You know what I'm saying
I
Okay, I think we got to move back to red. So we're gonna be we're gonna be
How often do you switch every I try to keep it to five minutes, but I usually go a little bit over
I've been going over a little bit. So five to ten minutes per per so we will be
How much longer is this going to go just wondering because I'm dying
Uh, I would say I'm gonna try and get it to be like maybe in probably less than another hour
Maybe down to half an hour one more rotation. If we do one more rotation, there'll be 30 minutes. I think we can do
Okay, let's let's let's try to do a reland after another rotation. Yeah, let's do another rotation
And maybe we'll do two more, but we'll see it. We'll see how long it takes. Okay. We are out
What what pink team out you guys doing another full round through all the parties? I think that's the plan
At least one more
Uh
We're really all right putting in the effort this week. What can I say? I wanted to ask a question real quick
I guess specifically towards gib, but have you considered doing like
Approaching like a publisher for your comics at all because I was we I was just talking uh with ilazon about
Uh, some comics he was reading some web comics and some that I were reading and it seemed like you could probably bring yours to something
Like I don't know like hive works or something
Hive works. Um, um, yeah
I've not thought of uh, I've not thought of anything like that. Um,
I don't know why I I guess it's it's obviously like a
possible
If it looks good enough. Okay. Okay. I applied to hive works one time
They they used to do like calls for submissions and I applied and during a call for submissions and I did not get accepted
Like very shortly after that they went like they changed their models
So they don't do calls for submissions. They just like anytime you can like email them and pitch them
Yeah, I think it's open all the time now. I I'm actually pretty good at their pitch right now that I'm trying to submit to them
I was I didn't realize you had submitted them. Did or did you say you actually did Ben? I did. Yeah, I did
And what probably would have been a like pitch look like
um
Well, they have like a an information like page that's like explains how to structure a pitch
You know, I had like like character like character art and like, um
Like a few a few pages of your of your it's just that's it just like a couple pages of your comics
so they can see what your art looks like and
Are you like text like one page or less like sort of text?
just explanation of what it is and like character uh, uh art
design whatever of an individual main characters
And that's it. Um, yeah
The one thing that sort of seemed weird to me about high works and this is I guess coming from a perspective of someone who doesn't
I guess the the amount of web comics I've read is fairly limited
I was talking to illison about this gaia web comic which I saw
Updated a page every couple of days. So we're talking like maybe two or three a week at most
How does yeah, how how do you even amass readers in such a way?
Like I don't how does how does someone decide to jump on a story that they know is going to be updated at such a slow pace
And it seems I mean it seems like that's like a pretty reasonable
That's like a pretty moderate pace for the for a web comic if you're uploading more than one page a week
You're like ahead of the pack
Yeah, I don't feel like that I don't like for a web comic. I don't feel like that's that slow
I think updates like the web comic format does work better for strips because you can jump in and jump out without having too much context
I think that's a why like four panel comics and stuff do so well. They're just so much more approachable
Strips are bad because
There's just too much of them and I'm going through the whole archive
But there's but like the biggest ones are those because like if you get a formula that works
Like they're so easily shareable. They're easily memeable
I saw um this this one that's like been recently getting big the the like great aliens that just say normal things but with like
Um, like a lot of words. I can't remember what it's called. That's not you on a web comic
It's just something that pops up on my facebook
Well, it is on the web. So I think it's on the web and it's a comic
I guess it's not a healthy comparison
But you think of like the stories that I guess most people would be used to is like manga and even beyond that
Obviously manga produces at a rate that no human should really strive for but even if you look at something like, you know, western
You know big two comics dc marvel. They're they're coming out like every month and to me that seems so
incredibly fast
compared to
the web comics
So I I guess to me it seems sort of like I don't understand how this works and yet it does seem to be working
And I I don't know just seems weird like imagine having to read one piece one page a week
And you get 50 pages a year. That's like that that is such a dwarf story at that point. You know what I mean
I mean, that's huge. That's kind of why I don't read a lot of story based web comics just because that drags so long
I'd rather just like read them in chunks of like a completed
Issue. Yeah
Imagine trying to read like scott pilgrim a page every week
It's kind of why stop. Oh god. That would suck. It would be terrible
But what you do is just have a larger number of them have them into ours as reader
And look look at it every day and every day you have different comics
That you read a page of work and like that's why they exist
It just like aggregates all the web comics because that's like the was the problem
Especially for me is like there'd be comics. I'd be reading like lc. Hooper and shit
I have to go back to the website
I'd always just forget about it
But then I'd have like a back luck to go through when I finally remembered six months from then
But it's not really good for audience retention
So I don't know it's not a great it's not a great format like story based stuff updating one page a week
It's just not ideal which is why nobody in like a professional capacity publishes that way
Yeah, just I guess it just only it seems like the only option
For someone who does not have the funding to gather a whole team
Like if you are just an artist maybe an artist and a writer you're not
You don't you just don't have the resources to have those six assistants that are necessary to be producing an issue
Right and you're also if you're starting out you don't this is probably not the way you're making money
So you also have to like work your day job and all that other shit
And so like it's just like a lot to ask of somebody in their free time to produce 24 pages in one month
I think what we're learning here is that comics is an inherently classic system that needs to be abolished at all costs
What else is new?
All you got to do is just be worse at art and you can make 50 pages in a month like me
That's how I made slime and punishment. You got to streamline some shit. You got to you got to make your choices. Everything's a compromise
Do you feel like slime and punishment is going going to affect the way you approach something like the vapors moving forward?
Are you going to simplify?
future
Maybe in places
Maybe in places. I think it was it slime and punishment was good practice for drawing efficiently and not like
Worrying about like small details where they aren't necessary
So yeah, I think in a way probably I will
be less inclined to like
Fucking spend an entire day like drawing and redrawing some like irrelevant thing
Which is something I was prone to do before which I'm sure I still will but maybe a little less. So that's cool
Hey, do you guys want to do do you guys want to hear a voicemail? Do you need to listen to a voicemail?
It's a goddamn voicemail. Yes. Um, okay. How about um, how about this one?
It is called metaphysics of frogs and I'm putting it in the reds only chat
All right. Okay. Uh, we're gonna listen to it on the count of three one two three play
Ben this one is for you buddy because something my brain just snapped
A few years ago. I was in a big uh, Jordan Peterson kick. Yeah, I grew out of it before becoming a far-right activist
Our fridge what really matters is that they get the the cookie omen to make a video
on the metaphysics of frogs because
He kind of sounds like kermit and cause pepper the frog and shit like that
So, um your character on the dnd is like a frog jesus in this interesting because frogs
They are amphibian. So they translate between the the water world and the earth world
and
this
mirrors the descent of the
Hero the hero's journey to the underworld to get the something that is most valid
Like in the tale of the princess and the frog when the frog descends to get the princess golden ball
um
It like in the bible when jesus he descends. Oh my god. How much longer is resurrected five second deeming humanity
That was very um Peterson core. Yeah of like loosely
The frog truly represents the mediation between the dragon of chaos and and the upper world of the of the goddess
Any frog start black and then turn green. So there's a clear
I mean, okay, well, I guess on the metaphysics of frogs. I agree
I agree with you about it. I'm with him and fuck Jordan Peterson. Yeah. Oh, no, no
Jordan Peterson is a funny meme man who eats nothing with beef. I hope I hope he's doing okay
He's he's going through a rough human level. I hope he's not literally dead. That is ideal. Oh, yeah
He seems like he's had like last I heard he had like brain damage
He was in russia recovering from like some medical bullshit. The winter soldier program
He was like they like induced a coma in it. Yeah, what there's so many based things about Peterson, you know
Like
He's like a cautionary tale of like what happens if like you blow up on the internet and are not ready for it
Like I just oh god. I don't I mean
I mean, he was ready for it and he was he he did he did pretty great
For
I'm like addicted to painkillers like that was like his wife got cancer
It was like the same time. So like he might have this might have been something that would have happened regardless
That's fair. Has anyone checked up on Nate to make sure he's not going down this path. Is he in russia right now?
We can we can only hope
Well, I hope for his sake that he's eating nothing but beef. That's the one thing I agree with
Okay, nothing to hurry. We are we are going to move on to blue. Wait, wait, what about what did you print last time?
What did I print?
Oh, okay, I've been 3d printing a bunch of stuff
Uh, I can't talk about some of it because it'd be spoiling other content. I'm working on but
I got some some some dnd minis. I printed some benches. I've been dialing in the settings on the anycubic i3 mega
I got it pretty nice now
I was having a lot of problems with bed adhesion and I realized it's because even though I had uh,
I had zhop enabled there was another setting that was overriding the zhop
So the nozzle kept clipping the supports and knocking it off the base and I thought it was
Problem with me leveling the bed, but it wasn't so I fixed that it's working good now
Uh, I just ordered replacement nozzles because the nozzle's like leaking shit. It's gross
It's probably all clogged up. So I'm gonna clean out the hot end and did you order different sizes?
Uh, yeah, I got 0.2 nozzle now. I'm gonna go even tinier details. It's gonna be sick
Also, I'm heavily considering getting an elegoomars pro. I really want to go resin. It's fucking cool
That's where yeah, none of those words were real
None of that was
Being encoded. Yeah
This is star trek technobabble from my
Just wait till he prints prints you an actual doll of of your character and you you'll start seeing it
Fucking cool. You can just do that
Okay, but we we must we must away. I think probably we're we're gonna make one more down
And then we will let you know we're gonna everyone will rejoin the general at the end
So I just wait wait for that. Okay. All right. He really is the best guy. I got no
You ruined it. You ruined it. What is Ben saying? I want Ben to say the counter
Understand what he's doing
Wait, yeah, we're we're not understanding what he's doing. I guess
If you are the best minor ever
No, thanks for watching Ben. Why are there?
What why are there two craigs? Yeah, what's up with that? Well, it's because I want to overlap them
I well, there's well, I mean lonely. There's there simply are two craigs
You can get craig and you can get craig too
And with them you you can you can be in two you can be in two rooms at one
How many audio files are we gonna have to stitch together to make this in any way too many? Oh
Maybe I mean, I don't know. I'll figure that out. I'll worry about that later. It's not important. It's totally irrelevant
Nothing could be less interesting to me
Then um any are any of the like conversations like
Any conversations we have that are like when you guys like when craig's not in here, uh, is that
included in
Probably maybe maybe
Oh
Unless like you really don't okay. I'm gonna say I'm gonna say assume. Yes
If like, okay, there's anything that you like must that you're like, I cannot have that out there publicly
I guess dm may and be like, please delete that part. I am sensitive to such things
That is cool
Stuff because I I don't know I feel like we we we we had a we had an interesting
Conversation, I mean, yeah, like, uh
um
go on
like, uh
What how do you guys feel about being?
We became friends. We are best friends now the blue team is now a band
Love Nakamas talking about Nakamas
These guys don't know shit about one piece, but I bring something to them that they don't need to know about one piece
But just a german open
Yeah, the german opening of one piece. I don't know if you guys heard about it
I
I don't know if you guys heard about germany, but it's this really
It's a really cool country
Whenever it's a young weave
And but there's a bunch of germans on this call actually
Oh, really?
Yeah
Jews
We might need to cut that we might need to cut that
But okay, so when you're young and we people tell you oh search the german naruto opening
So funny and you hear to it and you are like naruto blah blah blah sask the beautiful and it's so funny
So in one point I was like I'm watching one piece and I really like one piece
What about the german opening for one piece? Is there something out there?
And I searched it I found the the intro the first intro
It's like over over we are the the visuals of we are they don't say oh this is gonna be so bad
And I was surprised this it might be like top 10 one piece openings because it's a really
That sounds like actual pirate music
Okay, that's that's cool. That's cool and all
Uh, uh, and I'm a big one should watch this
Okay, good
Yeah, and riddle me this okay
Have have you guys considered?
Uh making commentary tracks for stuff someone I feel like someone brought that idea up
Wait, it was me
I think like a couple weeks ago
I might have like gone to the pcp chat and like said like hey guys idea
Movie commentary track or maybe or maybe we talk about that idea
I don't care what you do commentary tracks over just fuck
Ben didn't you record a commentary like video thing on uh for at radcon?
Oh, oh, was that the tarantino?
You know, I've never I've never actually watched the tarantino cast so it might be that and I just didn't even know
It's not in the podcast, but we did record the entirety of us watching that movie
Oh
But I don't know if we ever did anything with it. No, no, that was that was spiker that spiker
Video I think I don't know if that was turned into a video
I don't know what ended up happening to half the stuff we did at wreck
I don't know it sounds like
Uh
Okay, you know, you know what I actually really like I actually really like the idea of common like movie commentary tracks
I feel like that would be like pretty fun to do and not that hard
Yeah, I get favor spark to do it because like we watch all these bad movies all the time
In a call and we could just do reg and record. Yeah, because like
All the bad movies he records like half the time we'll like I'll get in a call and watch them together
I'm like, why aren't we like making this bonus content to make you even richer and he's just like
Profiting
At all and it's very strange to me coming from the pcp where everything we do is about making a buck and I'll like say
Look at all these great ideas
I have from the pcp you have a million subscribers
You could make like a hundred times the money and he's just like
I'm like, okay
Like we all get together and hang out like for new years and stuff
I'm like, why aren't we making content and crowdfunding this instead of like
Get here by ourselves. You have a million subscribers. He's like, hey, I'm like, okay
I'm leaving so much cash on the table
Well, that's what we also thought we were so so good such business people that we thought about another idea
Though if you're gonna include this in the in the main like everything we said in the main podcast
Well, that's fine
But you can chop everything up and like I said before but we we we brought up with with the guys
You can feel like your truth your own podcast and make like the blue path. Yeah branching branching paths
If you know if only fucking annotations were still a thing
Oh, yeah
This is like what they were for
For no reason. Yeah, I think we're having
Features this one like the bell and then you're like, okay
I'm so glad they took out annotations to make my subscriber feed not work and have to have like
Really like I'm so glad I get this trending tab, right guys, right?
It's more like the propaganda tag has nothing to do with trending. All right, that's hot
Okay, I think we're gonna soon. We're gonna move on to the to to yellow and then we will
The entire time here, that's crazy, bro. We but before we go. Love us. Should we do our own children?
Shut the fuck up
Let's do a voicemail. Shall we a voicemail? Yes. Oh, absolutely. Oh, yeah, absolutely. Okay
Uh, uh, I'm gonna post it in the blues only chat. This one is called. Um
A mango tree in dubai that has cancer and also aids
Mmm
We listen to that on three two one go
Damn this guy's a fucking menace
I was the only one that didn't hurt anything
You don't hear it. We're supposed to
He put in the blues only chat. Oh god. I'm so stupid
Wait, wait. Well, yeah, we're in blue. Oh, yeah, but I'll think people
Okay
Again, we'll start again. Uh, yeah, it's in the blues only chat
Play
In three two one wait, you tell him good
I'm gonna give you see it, right?
Okay, three two one go
Nice, we'll give him got the round
Yo, this mr. T
Ben, I ain't gonna bother all of y'all racist shit from a few weeks ago
But I pitted any food that run away from they simmer our master to join gay ass in
No, speak it out. He's
Then no, sir, please come home
No, I should talk. Oh, I thought he died come home
But until next time
Sayonara
Accent
You know what he found a new he found a new protege. Mr. T
So what does he need me for? Well, I hope him and mr. T are very happy together. He's just worried about you, Ben
I
I ran away for a reason. I didn't want to study the blade. I wanted to make a podcast
Okay
Did you guys watch the how is the show? I don't know the name in english
But the show with mr. T and the other get more dog and the guys
Yeah, a team a team
The a team, yeah
Then you love the a team was so fun
Like a friend of mine gave me a dvd with like a whole season of it on it and I got I got really into it for a little bit
Very briefly
Okay, that's it. We got to go. We got to move on yellow team. Hang around here. We're gonna join. We're gonna we're gonna go back to the general
Yeah
Later losers
Everybody wants to be a cat because the cat's
We've for concepts everyone in here has named themselves cat
So we became catty
I like I said that I said that could like completely off hand and I come back here and like it's like the entire culture the culture
But often evolved from it
The body you broke you broke the prime directive and this is what happens
So I like yeah cat girls now it's cat season
I like how you the yellow the yellow team's a team chat is like
As it has the least of any other it's just like gang gang gang epic
Everyone else
He said well, that's because we have that saying we have synergy
So we just talk in real life and we communicate telepathically
We really uh, we really uh, we really bonded in the time that you were gone
You use your you use your cat like anal like like scent glands to like
We we had a kind of a kind of a renaissance in the interim. Yeah, we're close now
We don't need you guys anymore. You can get out of here
We have a whole
Oh, yeah, we were going to
The non feline people here, I do want you to guys to
Say you you guys do agree that cat girls are better than dog girls, right?
No, we this is this is a this is not actually
No, I would I do I do agree with that
But it's I mean, I don't think dog girls are very appealing and that's why you never see him
Like when was the last time you saw a dog girl? I I saw
I saw no game no life once as a child and and that's that's formed my personality sense and always but especially in my
regard for dog girls, uh, and and Stephanie
Wait, actually, you know what my regard for lollies
You know what there's actually I just remembered
There's a twi an artist on twitter called they call him cake who draws the the biggest titties and
And his his characters his characters are dog girls. So actually I know I like dog girls better. I'm sorry. Yeah
Oh, no
The thing I associate with with with cat girls is like anime girls with cat ears, which is inherently lame
If you're gonna go with the cat
Yeah, I don't know about that given you do I think anime girls with cat ears are are are slightly better than like full furry
But I think for every I think honestly for dog girls. Uh, that's the case too, but you know, uh
Uh, uh furries are still good and uh are like more iconic at least, you know, like full anthro
Yeah
Like acceptable anthro aesthetic some of it is just like so jank and gross
Well, the problem is just furry artists are bad. Not that anthro is inherently bad. Uh, I think it's for me
I definitely
Disney aesthetics really animals with hints of human qualities rather than humans with hints of animal quality like if you go
Into the human
It starts becoming like really uncanny valley territory, but if it's just like a cartoon animal, that's a cool aesthetic that can be good
Uh, I think I think I think there's a broad base is what you're actually saying
Because for me, I love the disney aesthetic though. Though I probably wouldn't fuck it, you know
And I love the anthro and I love the I love the just like uh, what's it called?
Like, you know, kimono knee or whatever bullshit japanese. Oh, yeah, you know, I like I think all of them are good
And that's pretty indisputable. Uh, welcome to the furry cast guys. Um
Yeah, hey a pcp members. Are you team maw or team paul?
Oh
Uh
More's too like like too close
I guess paul because like
Because because like in real life you get a cat and you pick up the squishy paws like I enjoy that
Yeah, I guess i'm team paul
What do I need with a fucking animal's mouth? Nothing?
I don't understand the ramifications to this question because i'm sure it's heavy and scary
Maul and paul is mouth and paul
Yes
Oh my god, you know, you know, I makes perfect sense actually yeah people who are I love my ma
Who are in favor of ma are all childish and uh
Tit lovers too, you know, that's that's the people
Wait wait
The mommy milky's versus big boobies, right? That's team maw versus team paul
Yes, they precisely
Wait, but they're both big boobies
It's the it's a slight subtle difference preference thing and big boobies won by the way
Big boobies, I thought it was big boobies win. I agree. I agree big boobies pulled ahead
I think mommy milky's is I I've I explained this at some point before but you know big big boobies
Are are like, you know, the foundation upon which mommy milkers stand like no mommy milkers are not big boobies
Without being squares and rectangles
No, the the literal like genesis of that was like, um, what if ready fuckers cup killers, but big boobies mommy milkers like every every
We have a baby lovers and now big boobies mommy milkers
AU universe don't forget pissy baby fucker fappers. Yeah, that's that's the one pissy baby fucker
How could I forget?
You're right that boobies are the like foundation upon which milkers are built. That's like saying
Oh, I I prefer a wheel to a car because you can't have a car without
You know, you are absolutely right 100 agree
Someone was like, what's the more important invention? What's the more important invention the car or the wheel?
The milkers are yeah, but if you're choosing which is the more important invention is the milk
But which is better. It's the better one, you know the one that took the original and improved upon it
What's better the base of the mountain or the peak of the mountain?
This is this is you can't have one without the other. Yeah, but it is where you can it's still the peak like
If you put the peak on the ground and it doesn't have a foundation, it's not a peak. It's so there's nothing it's the ground
Uh, uh, but but it wouldn't be the peak then so it's definitely up high somehow. Yeah, that's why that's quite a question
Other than the base of the mountain. Hey guys, it could be like a
Yeah, yeah, we got listen. I could talk about this all day, but we gotta get going
Oh, oh, hold on hold on. Okay. All right. How long we how long were you hanging out with blue team?
This is discrimination. This is
Well, no, no, no before we go before we go I want to do a voicemail. Shall we? Oh, whoa
Yeah, yeah
Real quick. Um, my cat is literally right here on my lap. My cat just walked into the room. Well, ain't that
Ask the cat four or more. Um, okay, I can open a voicemail
Uh, this one is I'm gonna post it in the yellow chat. So to go look at the yellow chat. Uh, this one is called, uh
Failure is imminent
And we win listen to that. Oh god. Oh god. Um, three are we?
We all played at the same time. Yeah, you played at the same time three two one play
We have to kill god
He's a tyrant a self-righteous tyrant that blames all his mistakes on humans
But what if he's not real sir, then what are you yelling about?
But what if he is real then it's at the top of our drawer list to kill him. We have to do the chores
But how do you kill someone that's omnipotent?
But what if he's just shitposting and he can be killed then we have to do it sir
There's no way you can know that
Failure is imminent. But so is our counter strike. Well, I'd like this
Voicemail so it gets a little bit of credit, but it is bad and not funny. So no, this is
Extremely philosophical voicemail because it sets up a um, uh, what is it a pose mugging?
Uh, it's it's um, oh, what's this fucking name? Hang on
Yeah, pascals wait
Yeah, it sets up it sets up a pascals mugging where it's like we can kill god on the bet that he
Isn't god that he's just lying about being god, which is infinitely more probable than him being god
You know, I I do I do like that
That's a very good hypothesis
But I want to say that this this like performance wise it started out strong and it kind of peed it off a little bit
I I feel like it I feel like it started out at this at at a level and it it just kind of stayed there
Yeah, but it emotionally peed it out by not exceeding my expectations
Yeah, I would agree
And and I have the privilege of some experience with killing god with your lungs sound files
Um, and this isn't living up to the levy jevy ones
There's a little bit of of my mom's in other rooms so I can't scream too loud. There's a little bit
Yeah, I like their use of the hegelian dialectic. Um, I thought I thought that was really effective. I don't know
Um, it sounds like we've got a good writer who should have hired up
There's a you know, there's a lot
There's a lot to love here. There's a lot to love here. Okay. There's a lot to not life
Yeah, can I submit a last minute voicemail in yellow chat?
Uh, uh
Just an image here. Uh, sure a voicemail voicemail aka an image file
New piece of time image because it's pizza time. It's the joker and he's got pizza
Everyone listening go to the comment section. We're making yellow episode two. This is the yellow cast two
Uh, uh for yellow teams yellow cast two
So, uh, you can get all the juicy details of what happened while the pcp. We're slacking off talking to
Purple team. Okay. Okay. Hang on here. We will we will I will let you know
We're we will rejoin we will rejoin the uh, uh the general chat at the end for a wrap-up. So, uh, uh,
Stand stand stand by for that. Okay, sir. Yes, sir. Uh, jane. How you guys been?
Um, doing good. We've been bonding. I did it
I made it. Yeah
I made it back
Okay
What are what are we up to what are we what are we cracking open?
We were uh, well, I got uh burgen fels
Get it now. No, no, no
Is it here?
It's uh, yeah, it's it's beer. It's beer. Okay. Good
excellent
Anyone else drinking anyone else got a beverage?
God, I wish I was right now
I have three cans deep in diet coke
Nice jealous. I have I have a cup of um
water
That I have added a blue food coloring
citric acid
uh, a blueberry flavor extract
and and stevia
And I'm swelling it around
And it feels pretty good
Think until like stevia drops or like the powder
Oh
I have I have come full around. I was using the powder for a while
Now it's all about the drops. It's all about the flavor the flavor drops now
Do you are you you do you do keto keto? Have you checked out my protein?
Like they got some good deals on protein powders my I don't really do protein powder
They're they're not like
It's like not not so much for like working out or anything
It's just like a supplement when it needs supplementing so you're not getting protein
You know just like putting your diet as like because you know, maybe you're not getting enough
It's just you know a replacement or a supplement, you know
Well keto is about it's about fat. It's you want to go high fat like you want some protein, but not too much
God like I went to I went to fucking like school for keseology and like I've hated keto for the longest time
I still hate keto, but like I know it's usefulness and like interventions and how it can save lives
I mean
Like if you think back to
I'm not think back to because you're not a thousand you're not like you're not 10 000 years old, but
Before the invention of agriculture
You were in ketosis
99% of the time and you only had like little bits and bobs of sugar every once in a while
Yeah, that's the natural human state's what we're for
Thank yes one
Correct
Factually factually accurate, but bread is so nice. It goes crunch
It is really satisfying
And that's why it's the devil's invention
I wanted to be unsatisfied
Um throughout my life. I would um, I already am so I don't want to add to that being off not helping you
So why being off keto people say like oh, you know just eat moderately
It's like okay
Well being keto makes it easier for me to eat moderately because when I'm off keto
I I like have no impulse control and I will just eat me
I will eat an entire loaf of bread without even thinking about it
I do keto because I have no self control
Yeah, that actually makes sense if it's more sustainable sustainable for you than keto would be the thing to go with like eat what's sustainable
Yeah
I guess that makes sense. Yeah, do you like one piece?
Yeah, I do a podcast about it
I know I know I know
Yeah, but do you like it though?
Yes
It's it's my favorite thing
I think uh
Ahead of berserk in mangas
It's one of my favorite things too. Like I spent like many hours making this giant one piece video and then
in like
Fucking action giraffes in it. It's sick. It's awesome. Oh to shout it out. It's pretty neat. If you have time check it out video
Wait
I'm sorry, can you what do you mean oh to shout it out a video that you made this is what you're saying to me?
Yes, yes, I I'm saying this like okay
I'm saying it the the special intersection of
Oda shouting out a video that has action giraffe in it is is the best thing
What?
How did this happen? It's my favorite thing ever giraffe is not in the title
I can talk links about but that takes a lot of time
But like so I'll just tell you like, you know how Oda how Oda found it. So yeah, uh, japanese yahu
You know shared the video on like on a japanese news site after they'd been shared around on an amy news network and like um
Some other things that's the name of the video. How do I pass the vivre car?
I pass vivre car and I started the hashtag
It was cool and there's some ambiguity about who did all the work by spent many hours on it and like I didn't get paid for
It was a passion project, but it's a giant cosplay collaboration
Where I basically put a bunch of you know cosplayers from around the world and this giant pass the brush challenge
But like, you know, it's not like, you know next person next person because that'd be too fucking long
It's like a bunch of people on screen. It's a collage. It's basically a fucking video collage
and you know with
It's your own staff's twitter
What they what they do from my understanding is um
Oda sort of like has someone else this like team or two people or one person
Tweet on his behalf and they were like, this is pretty neat and like a lot
You know the japanese have a lot of nice things to say about it and that made me feel good
So now I edit stuff and now um
Nice
I was completely convinced that you were joking and there was no aspect of Oda shouting it out. That was true
But that that's that's great. It's like my yeah, like I asked, uh,
Mr. Best best guy like it's like, hey, could you just give me bare minimum action giraffe
Footage and he sent me like a like two minutes of just static action giraffe
So instead of taking a png I like like uh rotoscope like, you know
Action giraffe out of that video into my video and he plays kakku. I only like color like, you know changed it to make him more like kakku
But like uh, yeah, no, it's uh
It's action giraffe. We got anri okita, you know, very nice woman. Uh in the video. We got, uh
What's we got?
We got some italian hosts and we got a bunch of nice japanese
Footage and the japanese cosplays were fantastic. They all gave me their footage. Um
They all gave me their footage like in a nice folder for me where it wasn't like, you know
Later anything and they gave me 75 clips 76 clips of footage. It was easy. Everyone else was like, oh get to you later
I heated it. I heated it. I was angry all the time. That's why there's two versions
But the newest version has a nail in it. So that's kind of cool
Uh, that's uh, that's great. That's amazing. It's I was expecting it this to be like a viral video
But like it it's only got a few hundred views
So i'm really shocked that it would have made its way to oda himself
Well, no, there's a 20. No, there's uh, there's the one that's like, uh, they linked in the chat is like 20 is like, uh,
20 000 views
But like, oh, okay. That's not that's not that's not like that's the version that was shared and like the original plan was like
To like, you know, keep it unlisted because like, um, some other channel want to like post it but like it's like, you know
America's like it was Funimation's uh one piece like
PR department not PR but like marketing department or something like that
Where they're like, can we post this on the Funimation channel? It's like cool, but they didn't so I just said, all right, whatever
It got enough traction where it was like, I'll just post it on my channel and make it unlisted and like
It was unlisted so people were still getting to the video anyway from the news sites and like, uh
The you know and shit
He's really cool
But uh, yeah, no, uh oda saw action giraffe. I think that's fucking hilarious. That is that is that was funny
Um, shout that from the heavens, man. That's we know the purple story. Okay. Um, we um
All right, we can't we got we got to get moving but before we go
I am actually gonna take this chance to talk about
She's core once again
Okay
Get absolute trash media on the map
Absolute trash media. That's absolute trash media on bandcamp. Did I if you don't know where to start
You you'll just you'll just search for chicago house classics
That that that's a good part of that record label on bandcamp. That's absolute trash media
Sure, I have seen us before and I'm not sure if you recommended it to me or someone else did
But I have seen that I've seen this thing you're talking about. Okay
If you if you uh, don't want to check out chicago house classics check out whopper billionaires come album series
There is come one two three four five and seven
If you want to find uh come six that doesn't exist as an album because that was just actually sarah louise coming for real
And that's all I have to say about that
Um, good. I thought it was really good. Fuck fuck. Yeah, but you're doing great before we go. Let's let's do a voicemail
Shall we?
I've never done a voicemail before can we leave after that?
No, you got to stick around we are going to go through the last two teams
And then we will join up again at the group at the general chat for the end
But um, let's hear. Let's hear um, um, let's hear from uh
Liam cheesy and i'm posting this in the green the green only chat. You see it. You guys see it
Yeah, okay in the green only chat. Uh, we will play this on three two one go
You see I just got this wonderful wonderful grilled cheese sandwich
It was uh
What's the spicy the spicy cheese cheddar jack? I believe I could be wrong cheddar. I apologize if i'm not correct me
Do so someone
I believe it is cheddar jack and it was a really good
It was a really good grilled cheese sandwich
I bet
so
I'm going to assume you're an intelligent person whoever maybe you want to respond to this
And you don't see you're a real cheese sandwich normal cheese you do with a different cheese
What cheese is that because if it's normal cheese, which would be uh
What would you call normal cheese the normal cheese everyone thinks of why did I choose this boring basic bitch ass
clean looking yellow
Pepper jack is the superior
The thing is I actually did and I actually did curate the voicemails and I deleted a few and this one made it made the cut
Me I use clearly my group. Oh, we're actually talking about cheese earlier. So this works out very nicely. Good job
Yeah, let me tell you about the best cheese in the world
Pass this right now. Fuck all of the other cheeses
Best there botans ost best there botans ost
Best there botans ost if you think that sweden is obscure take a piece of swedain
Northern swedain, which is called best there bottom
That's where I live and that there we got the best there botans ost
And you know what motorel sticks everyone knows about motorel sticks, right? Yeah motorel sticks. Yeah
Yeah, take motorel sticks and take out motorel and put the best there botans ost in there
And there you have a button so stick
Yeah, yeah
Oh my god. Yeah, well shit the difference. What's the what's the what's described the taste?
Okay, so it's a strong cheese and it's not stringy. It's not a stringy cheese. It's a runny cheese
And if it's in a solid
State if it's in a solid state and it's not melt if it's not molten
Then it has a lot of holes and the holes are tighter and there are more of them
Okay, I can picture it. I can picture it in my mind
I would love to try it
All cheese is not good. I don't like any of it. I haven't good
I've never eaten a cheese that I felt that I would want more of this fucking christ. Really? This is the worst thing I've ever heard
And we'll give them this information
Okay, listen, I have to I have to go we have to go punish gib for this
So
We're taking away we're we're putting them behind bars. What are you gonna do? Okay? We're oh, we'll leave him here
Leave him here. No, leave him here. No, no, no, no. He's coming. Oh, no. No, she's coming with us. We're gonna fucking twirl
Corkscrew
We're going we're going to the purple team hang out
We will meet in the general chat in a minute and good. See you soon. Very fun. Okay. Bye
Welcome back. Damn. You guys just missed it
You guys just missed us talking about ben Shapiro's wife's drive-up
You know, you know
Oh, we were talking. Were we talking about that yesterday and I thought that that tweet was real, but it was fake. Yes
Yeah, it's so believable. It's something he would absolutely say
Yeah
The one that's like, um, I know
The jokes about me and my wife don't bother me. We know that there's more to a marriage than sexual satisfaction
Yeah, my wife don't bother me. Um, I know there's more to a relationship than uh sex
That's a lie. No, it's a lie. That's a lie. We need we need i'll be in here to get the impression just right
Yeah, it's funny because like if it's someone you thought would be having sex you'd be like, yeah, I know but it's Ben Shapiro
Exactly
Hey, you guys know Ben Shapiro's Jewish
I've heard that
I've heard that. Yeah, that's crazy
That's like the first thing I learned about him. Do you have the recent papers?
Lock it up. It's kind of weird Gib. We look at that. Yeah, why would you look that up?
That I just like I heard about him
You're looking at a list of as a he was a guy in a in a in a that's is in some video and he was like
Honing noobs and he had of one of the funny caps on owning well, so
The hat on so I guess that makes sense
the funny hat
Why why isn't it no bigger?
Yeah, I I always I always thought it was called a a yamaka, but like lately I hear I hear everyone call it a skull cap
I'm like do they change
Is just the Hebrew word
Oh, okay
Beanie but like it's
One that's like more form fitting to your head that's called a skull cap, isn't it? Yeah
I feel like I've heard people for yamakas as well
Yeah, I've heard I've heard people more often in recent years. I've heard people refer to a yamaka as a skull cap
And I thought it was weird. I thought
Why is it what is it? No, come on
Is it is it is it okay? Well, maybe is it maybe a thing that it's like cultural appropriation like to like to say it in their language
I'm thinking
Yeah
I mean, I don't I don't I don't I don't think it I don't think it would be weird either
I'm just speculating on what the motive could be for this change that I've perceived
SJWs
You're not allowed to say yamaka. In fact, all Jews are banned to the ghettos because having them live with us would be cultural
Appropriate
You're slipping you're slipping back
Disavow disavow disavow
I'm probably genetically Jewish myself anyway, who gives a fuck
Ben can be a bigot. He's not one of the goys. Hey, yeah, thank you very much. I love that
Yeah, you can get a voicemail
Oh
Here we go. Here we go. Yes
Okay, in in in the purple chat in the purple chat, we're gonna listen to uh sefirio
You crin you just smooth brained
Virgins who just left the chat somebody
Do you want to give a quick countdown ben? Yes. One two three
Shut up. It's it's in the it's in the purple chat there. Uh, three two one play
They're like two hours on a sunday afternoon
That is like so important that like being on the fucking podcast would have prevented that from doing
I know the answer. It's nothing. This is like a complete like this is like a total like false
Perception to be on the podcast is just to be present when the podcast is being recorded
I'm gonna say it. I'm gonna say it. Um being on the pcb is like such
It is like such an easy thing to do
I actually kind of feel like not doing it is like irresponsible
I challenge every pcb member that is not currently recording or has recorded in the last couple of weeks
To come debate this point come on to the podcast and explain why it's so hard to get onto the podcast
because if you don't
and uh
Checkmate
That's
Topic for topic next next topic episode. The topic is why we can't be on the podcast
And everyone's there
Everyone shows up back
This is a matter of great interest for everyone
Jesse everyone is here
Just like old times
Yeah
I hope it's transition and pre-transition eating and like
All of our pony sonas come in
All of the jennesy characters
Whoever the the the north cast should work on a uh a pcp fighting game next. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, just get on that. Yeah, just actually develop the rail rumble like
From that one manga where he's like all his spine's broken, but he'll use his muscles to stand that's
I think it might be I don't think it's was it. Oh god. I don't know
I've only seen a little bit of baki. So I don't know. Yeah, I'm pretty stupid
That sounds like something the way would happen in baki though. Yeah, it's yeah, it's that kind of show looking it up. I'm gonna find it
All right, any members. What would your ultimate attack be in in the pcp fighting game?
Yeah, what would your noble fantasy
My ultimate attack would probably be
I think it would oh, okay. I think it would probably be I summon endless war and he delivers a bone herding beam
Like mirrored like fox and falco
Yeah, I mean when she have like this mirror move sets
Your move says but mirror special special file moves. Yeah, I think I think so. Yeah, I think so
That makes that makes sense
Oh
It would be like peach and daisy pulling on veggies
Like he pulls up winning the poo characters out of a vvhs tape. So if it's piglet, he throws it at him
He gives him honey to recover health
Yeah, I was gonna ask are the cop killer and ben saint two separate characters?
Are the echo fighters or is one I think yeah, I think yeah ben saint is the c1 is the is the
Dimension 1218 one the cop killer is the one that exists in dimension c197
Duh, so so they would be they would have to be different characters because you know the echo fighters because yeah
They have different stats, but the same like moveset. I yeah
I think they'd be I think they'd just be echoes of each other
Munchy's neutral B is that he shoots you with a deagle
Okay, hey, okay, we we've been here in 10 minutes. We gotta move on to pink. We gotta move on to pink
Understood
When we're done, we will be we will all be we will all be meeting hey shut up
We will all be meeting again in the general chat. Just so wait for that. I'll let y'all know. Okay
What is the next video, Tom?
What
No, what's up
It
Hi, we've been bad now behind your back. Yeah, we've been talking about your back. That's that's what I like to hear
Actually, not not really y'all but mostly ben
We're back. What about we do that all the time? Oh, we've been talking behind your back. Yeah. I mean, that's what I expected
I would expect no better from the from the likes of you. Well, we just wanted to come clean with you
Yeah, and just tell you that like up that the rain fall down and coming cleans my favorite hillary duff song
I love that song my favorite hillary clinton song. It's my it's my favorite song to listen to the nightcore remix
I was just I was literally just gonna say that it's such a good nightcore song
It uh, I can't I can't believe you're unironically agreeing with me. But yes, it's true. I fucking love nightcore
There's a couple different versions of it
And the the good one is the one that has the art of the anime girl like skydiving out of a plane
That's the good one. The other ones are shit
I I definitely have had phases where I'm just like all I want to listen to is fucking fallout boy nightcore
Kesha nightcore
I'll just type it in youtube and just go down the rabbit hole
Like fallout boy normally not great. No
Trash
Yeah, fallout boy nightcore is completely different
I heard a snippet of like some pop song today and I like
I'd never heard it before and I heard like two seconds of it
But I was like, hey, that's like a catchy beat and it sounds like just like some piece of shit generic pop song
I should look this up and like look into more of this
Because I because I'm vibing with this right now
Uh, uh, this this is this is to my boring tastes
Uh dab
I thought you were gonna say that you were gonna nightcore it
No, no, I would never do that. I would never do that
I mean making nightcore it's not it's not just speed it up like a good nightcore mix is like mixed
Yeah, you have to make it. So yeah, so you just beat it up. It's gonna sound like shit
And I'm and I don't have the skills to do a good job with it. So why even bother?
I make a ton of nightcore edits of songs that I need to be faster. Yeah, I have tons there
Uh, do you listen to ag cook? You just put out like a new 49 song album. No, I don't know who that is
He's he's like the creator of pc music
Um
I'm not familiar with that
So he put out a 49 track album and like pretty much immediately after I nightcore like five of them and then put them all on youtube
Because I just needed them to be nightcore. Why would anyone do that to themselves a 49 track album? That's terrifying
I don't know. I think he had a bunch of stuff saved up because he released a 49 track one and then announced a 10 track one
Oh god, because yeah, I can I can barely put 10 songs together much less
Anywhere close to that the 49 track one is kind of like just a huge compilation of b-sides
But it's super good
I mean that is pretty cool. Yeah
Then we came to the conclusion that at the very least this whole podcast is an interesting social experiment
Yeah, yeah, that's my excuse too
Because we've just been hanging out here for like two hours now just getting to know each other at least three random people
At least drunk ben, you know drunk ben knew how to run a good social experiment
sober ben has no fucking clue what he's doing
So sober sober clue is floundering. Oh god. I'm floundering. Oh god go to voicemails. Oh fuck
That's why you're part of the social experiment
Yeah, I'm as much I'm as much as subject as anyone else because drunk ben initiated this whole thing and and
Sober ben is just like his victim. He just has to like live in this in he just has to lie in this shit
That's drunk ben made in the bed
So do you think this is going to do anything to like dissuade you from getting drunk ben out of the cage in the future?
Um, or is it gonna push him further?
No, this won't but other things probably will
Uh, uh, like how I fucking ruined my other roommate's day by waking him up at four in the morning yelling on my fucking computer
Oh, he was mad
And they made me made me upset
Okay, I gotta ask here
So you fell asleep like midway through that voice call and were like muttering no in your sleep
Were you being prevented by dream demons? I was muttering no
Yeah, and it was right as we're I mean it was where we were watching the every no and mlp video
But oh, but you are on the stream. So there's no way you could have heard it
What the fuck
Do you remember do you remember being in the call and like I mean, I do you know that you fell asleep and
Yes, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I remember that
Okay, a lot of people jumped in and talked around you which was funny
I mean, I probably couldn't hear anything because I wouldn't have had my headphones in if I fell asleep unless I fell asleep with them on
I don't which be
Seems unlikely seems unlikely, but I guess I guess you never know seems uncomfortable
Yeah, aren't you screaming in your heart and wake you up prove the headphone? Well, that's well, that's embarrassing
Terrible just just terrible
Uh, how would you do you guys want to listen another voicemail or you guys want to you know, what do you what do you want to talk about?
And here we got a couple more minutes
I wanted to tell a little story about
uh
Me and some friends met up over new years and some of them were also working on the dating sim
and on new new year's eve like after midnight
uh, we
I I basically we came to the conclusion that the release of a pcb dating sim would either mark
The beginning of the end of the pcb or revitalize the hype and i'm not sure what happened
I'm not sure which of these two things has happened. What what what made you think that one of those things would happen
I don't know because okay, it was around the time that um that we heard that mage left and
like a few weeks a few weeks later fucking, uh, bread happened
and
I don't know everything seems kind of
Uh, kind of climb climb mactical, you know, yeah, yeah
And with rad con, you know
Yeah
Of the other end rad con happened around that time. Yeah, that was three rad con and then there was rad con rad con was a high point for sure
I think on what's a high point, but then this came another dark age and it's it's yeah
I didn't see another one coming
Yeah, so
All of the all of the stuff with with brad and then how it came back and destroyed the videos
That's been a low point. I feel like we're getting back to things though. Like things are videos are being released
If it's another low point
It's it's climbing up
Yeah, the the second the second hack like felt worse than the first the second dark age felt worse than the first one
Oh, yeah, I think it's because it came. I mean the first one came unexpectedly
But it's like since you had already weathered one of them
It just felt sad
Yeah, it wasn't like
It wasn't there wasn't the sense of like, oh, how is what's gonna happen? Like how like what like what is our fate?
It was like we had survived the first one
But we hadn't had long enough of like a time to like feel good because the world had gone to shit
You also didn't have rad con to look forward to
Yeah, no and and then
Yeah, it's just sort of like we didn't get up to a high point before we were brought back down
It just kind of it just kind of felt like the first one had never actually ended. We were just like still in it
You know because it was like technically caused by the same problem or it was like an outgrowth of it
Do they ever specify like the reason why they terminated it?
Or why they like or why they
No, because I know it was related to the hack
But they never really said for what purpose we we assumed it was related to the hack
Because it was just the videos that came out after we got the channel back. I think it was it was um
It was for like illegal activity
Which i'm pretty sure means they thought they were branding banning like brad garling house
They're like ripples streaming or whatever. I think that's what they thought they were doing or what the algorithm thought it was doing
That's yeah, that's what I assumed. I just my that's my theory
I'm not entirely
What was weird to me was the part where you couldn't it was like the old content was fine
But then anything past a certain point got flagged that was fucked
Yeah, that's why it had to be hack related
The only exception was the the rad con stream the opening ceremony
That was the one thing that like escaped the the notice or whatever
Okay, anyway, uh, yeah, that was all shit. It was all terrible. We're talking about
voicemail
Yeah, let's let's do a voicemail and then let's jump back into okay. This is um
Okay, I won't do that one because that's just what we were already talking about. Let's do um, let's do uh
barefoot on the freeway
This isn't oh wait. No, I post shit. I posted in the wrong chat Lamal
Uh a bare barefoot on the freeway in in the pink chat
Okay
We gonna play this on three two one go
Okay, so I'm here with my brother. Um, and we're in California and the smoke is so thick currently that I can
I'm looking at the sun while I'm driving right now. Um, that's dumb
And it's it's fine. It looks like the moon. No, don't stare at the sun
But what I want to complain about is that there's no words at the end of the podcast
Uh, there's just the bum-ba-bum-ba-bum
What happened to this sucking and jerking? Please? Please help
Oh
In the sun my dick. I'm sucking myself. I'm jerking right. I didn't even notice that
Uh, I guess elias are stopped using that
um
I guess I guess the I mean maybe the idea was that the outro was like too long
So he just cut it down to only the music
No, no, no the the music um
Oh, is there not even a tune? There's an instrumental version. I yeah
Yeah, like I've I've in the past used
The uh, the one with vocals and then sometimes the one without vocals most of the time without without work focus, I think
Um, it's just because when you fade it out, you don't want to fade it out in the middle of a word. I guess
I mean if people miss the words
I just want to say I really like the voicemail because it was like an authentic conversation in a car
No, it wasn't any other guy. There's a special guest on the voicemail. Yeah
That guy's voice was scarily familiar to me and that worries me
Uh, dude, I don't know how much can you tell from the cell phone?
It's probably because you've talked on a phone before
But on the other hand, I'm kind of miss the high production voicemails
I missed them snakes. There's there's yeah. Oh man. I remember them snakes
There's one there is one in here that I got this week that was like
Someone just like says something stupid and then starts like playing a guitar or whatever starts like playing the piano
Uh, and I was like boy, that takes me back. That used to be a whole genre
Uh, they they've fallen they've fallen out of fashion, I guess but they could always be brought back
Uh
Was the do you remember the communist hell saga?
Yeah, a little bit. I don't know if it ever
Exactly ended
Yeah, I mean, I just can't I just went on and like cussed you guys out in spanish, but that was about it
Was that you was it or were you part of it? Yeah, I was communist shea gavara the ghost of shea gavara
Okay, I really killed it was the ghost of chairman mal. That's the one I remember is is the ghost of chairman mal
um
I don't
I don't did I I don't remember if the pcp communist hell arc ever concluded
Someone comment. I don't know how did that result?
I think it was it was like a weird thing where many people were like working on responding to another one another
Yeah, it was it was not a centralized effort
It was almost like a weird arg because then it overlapped where there was like the pc police
Trying to take you guys down. Yeah, I feel like that was happening like concurrently and it felt like related somehow
But it wasn't quite the same
There was a whole saga going on for sure
Multiple there are multiple multiple sagas. Um, okay. I think
We should break and I'll head back to the general chat. What are we? Oh, yeah
Sounds good. Yeah. Okay. We're headed back for for I'd I guess closing ceremonies or whatever. Okay. Fuck. Yeah
Last seconds of chill, okay
I
Told you it's not okay. You are a minor. I'll keep it down. I'll do it a little more quietly. Thanks. Thanks
Well, well, uh, we're all here now because uh
Today I learned the pcp fans are the worst
Um, they can't shut the fuck up and I became one of them. I am part of the problem now
I should be put down like a dog in it
Thanks so much. It was very peaceful. The yellow cast was great and peaceful. I think you just had a bad hashtag down
We became best friends
This is a new arc for the pcp fan
Shut up
Oh my god
This is the best in the list forever
100 episodes a week
Oh
Where are you
Are you real are you a real person? I don't think no nobody here's
I'm gonna crack this world time. I say is I pull my e-mask off
Why don't you pull your light
Between toxoplasmosis and killing two dogs. I think it's true the toxoplasmosis, but it's gonna suck
What toxophymosis? What?
It means he's afraid of Santa Claus
Can we cancel moses?
We should cancel moses
The red sea
When the actual the person other of that wasn't a pollion and everyone knows that
I'll be one better. Let's just give moses, uh the undertale copy, you know
You know, I think I'm starting to warm up to this moses guy. I think I like moses now. I think I have toxoplasmosis
Fuck you
When are you gonna put this in which place?
I envy green I envy green in their discipline their discipline to stay in their own chat until until ben and munchie
Or not ben and munchie
They're jerking off each other
Should we go back should we should we go back to yellow?
I'm sure this will cause no complications for editing. I'm sure it's fine
Get it down on here
Okay, now he's awesome with the
How are the 57 minutes?
All right, all right
So you know discipline is fake and bad and what you have to do is log your dicks
You just realize or your dyna or whatever genitals you have so you can jerk off and procrastinate jerk
I have undertale as gendaltaglia
I
Why don't you have your team name yellow's got cat? Why don't you have anything also chocomotus?
We are the best friends ever we are the best friends ever
Do really best friends if you don't have a tag in front of your name
They don't need a team name
Only best friends can see the dag so I can see your blue though
I'm so excited for for there to be a drawing of of of uh five different five different girls with uh
All with intense disassociative identities disorder. What the hell is going on in general?
Yeah, wait and no and like one of and like one of the girls is like a blue girl with like a red girl like trying and like
straining to get out of her
Oh
Steven universe versus one piece guys. Hey guys. What are you?
What jam are you? I'm a dime
Are we just I'm uh, I'm a god all of the kiln steven universe. We've got the red and blue fusion
We've got the yellow like catty cat girl like being peridot. I'm purple kunzai. No blue is from uh
Is it yellow? What the fuck are you talking about? Oh, you're right peridot screen. It's like she's like
But I guess uh, that was
I guess
But there is a green
Did the three face sometimes so like that's like us though
Uh, we are the cat team and we have here we go
He said he said
See told you should have defected to yellow
See told this is our culture not your costume
I know I saw
She told say nice
Don't forget you all are obligated to watch every second of every podcast is
Just watch every moment that doesn't have the actual
Is
I love that dead
I just just turn them up that'll help
I would I would say I would say I would say that I hope
You guys are cool, you guys are cool, you're all cats and I like
My my eyes have rolled back into my skull
Alliance
Blue team open to alliance we
Thank you for saying it out loud to everybody
I
Like a quick
Me over here man, that's a say your username I there are two jelly beaner
Okay, jelly beaner question. Do you do other voices as well?
I don't want to
No
So
I gotta I gotta I think that we've had we've had such a successful podcast this time
We've had so many so many people have been on this podcast
I
I've got I've got you know what I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it
Say I've I've got another voicemail and I'm gonna
I'm gonna put it in the general and I'm gonna and I'm gonna come down this one's called. Okay. PCP is home stuck. Here we go
Three two one
Hey
So you're like paint power cut for this or how's that gonna work?
I've explained multiple times that this is slave labor
So I expect room one
Okay, okay, uh, well, I one thing I can say for absolutely sure is that everybody picked purple team as their least favorite team
Yeah
It's a good thing that's the one that's a real podcast
I think that
Got one more I got one more voicemail from our boy
Here we go, okay three three two one go
No
Margarh here. This is an active call to action
Lost tape archive
lol pussies put your eating with spoons and
Die buster
Unite with me fellow voice jail members
We must storm the Bastille that is the voice jail
Just as the french revolutionaries in olden days
And we will
I've spent over a month in here and I can't take a day more
Set us free now
I
Well that
Was a was sure a journey. We had a we had we laughed we cried
We made we made new friends as well as enemies
Uh and all all secrets secrets were revealed
And and and lies were were uncovered and the truth made manifests before us whatever
Okay, hope you hope you like that
Uh, hope you enjoyed uh this special edition. I promise we will never never ever ever ever do this again
Never um lamal
But uh, but that's uh, that that's it. That's the episode and hey
remember
If you want to hear if you want to hear each team's individual journey
I will put a link in the description to the full playlist for that and probably an end card and end card
Uh link to that playlist right here. There you go. The content never ends
Never you're welcome
Uh, uh, thanks for watching. Uh, stay tuned for a problem a more normal episode
Next time on the pro crassonators podcast