Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Oh, we did it. Yeah, we did it. Welcome to episode whatever of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We got me, Ben Saint, you got Gibbontake, and we got Chrono, aka Gamers Tavern, back from the grave.
A man walks into a bar and says, hello, my name is Jose, and the bartender says, if you're Jose, where's hose B?
We are convened. We are convened once again for a great council. The great council has been called to stand in judgment over the masses. And our verdict is, fuck them.
Is you suck. So thanks for listening, audience.
Oh, fuck.
Me or?
No, no, I mean, yes, but not, no, I mean.
Yes, I mean, in general to all, I equally share my contempt among the masses.
Absolutely. Absolutely. I just realized, since we've got a guest, I have to download all of the voicemails.
Oh, my God, there's so many voicemails.
I'm sorry for ruining everything.
No, it's so bad. Oh, you, you, well, I mean, the voice, the voice mailers ruined everything, but you are like the, you are really just like salt in the wound right now.
Salt tastes pretty good.
Well, I better, I better start downloading. This will take me all episode just to get all these freaking voicemails ready.
It will take you all episode and it will completely cripple your ability to pay attention to the conversation, thus ruining the episode.
Absolutely. That's, that's what I hope for every time I get on here is something to please cripple my ability to pay attention to the conversation.
I guess I should have notified me in advance and did all of this in advance.
I should have done that, but I really wanted to sleep until 3pm.
Ben, just last minute thought, I just get gamers to heaven and so here is.
That's exactly what I did.
I had a dream.
Get ready for this. This is going to be a great story. This is the, this is the original, the original Ben St. Dream corner.
I had a dream that I went deaf and I was walking around.
What?
It was in my, what? I was at my, my old, old like college girlfriend's house for some reason and I was walking around and I went deaf and I was like, oh no, I can't hear.
Oh no, I can't hear.
Wait, it'll come back.
I remember what I was doing. I was, I was hosing off a dirty trampoline and suddenly I went deaf and I, in her, in her backyard and I was like,
That is pretty random.
And I was like, okay, okay, it'll come back. It'll come back and it wouldn't come back and I was, and I'm walking around the house just thinking it's going to come back any second now.
It's going to come back any second now.
It's like, you feel like you got water and you're, and you're like, I'm just, it's just a, it'll just, it'll just like clear up the water will come out of my ear and then I'll be able to hear again.
I mean, you ever have like, you ever have like, I don't know, like you stand up too fast and you get lightheaded and your hearing goes away for a second, but then it comes back.
Or something like that.
Yeah, it's like the blood's leaving your head too quickly if you move. Yeah, yeah, I know that.
Yeah, yeah, so I thought like, I'm, maybe I just like strained myself in some way and I'm momentarily deaf and my hearing will come back, but it wasn't coming back.
And I, and I would kind of like tap on my ear and I'd be like, I could kind of hear it and like, I would like yell and I can kind of hear it from inside my throat, but I'm like, I'm almost mostly deaf and it's like not coming back.
And then I woke up and I realized and I'm like, and I said something.
I'm like, huh?
And I could hear myself and I'm like, few.
I'm not deaf.
I only imagined the deafness.
But I realized that the reason why I was having that dream was because my, wait, hold on, my favorite YouTube video, 10 hours, gentle rain sounds on window, calm rain, black screen rain for sleep, comma study.
My rain sounds for sleeping video had ended.
And so I had gone from hearing a loud white noise to hearing nothing and it made me think I was deaf in the dream.
That's really cool that the outside, because I don't know how dreams work, but it's interesting to think an outside stimulus could influence what you start dreaming about.
Sure.
Because because in the dream, I was, I was hearing this white noise and then all of a sudden I was hearing nothing and I guess my brain interpreted that as like, I cannot hear anymore.
I cannot hear anything.
And you didn't, you didn't go from hearing white noise to hearing black noise.
What is, what does that mean?
I don't know.
I didn't, I didn't think that was true.
You ever hear of, you ever hear of a brown note?
The one that makes you shit?
No.
Yeah.
The magical, the magical frequency that makes you shit.
I've never listened to it, but I assume it sounds like a tuba.
It's great.
I recommend it.
My, you should put on my favorite YouTube video, 10 hours, gentle brown note for shitting.
You know.
You'll really, you'll really shit off more than you can poo.
That would be great to put on when you have constipation.
Yeah.
I was going to say constipation, brown note.
I'm going to try that.
I've been, that's been suffering from that.
And I've been, if it works, if it works, it would be really funny that I have to listen to that.
If it were, if it works, it would be really funny.
If it, I mean, if it were real, it would have all kinds of important medical applications.
There's all kinds of reasons.
You could like, you wouldn't have to go like not eat for, you know, 10, 24 hours before surgery.
They could just play you the brown note before they put you under and then you would shit it all out.
And you wouldn't have to worry about having food in your intestines.
I, I gotta know.
I mean, it'd be so.
I don't know if it works.
I could, I could Google does it work and then get an answer, but I'd rather just listen to it.
I believe it is, I believe it is apocryphal.
I believe it is a cryptid.
No, not a cryptid.
I don't know what the word is.
What do you do currency?
It's, it's a fiction.
It's, it's, it's pure fiction.
Like an arbor and legend.
Yeah.
Like, like the guy, like, like, number one in that, in that, that TV series where they would tell you fantasy stories.
And then tell you, and then tell you whether they were real.
And then at the end he goes, it's fiction.
We made it up.
Oh, yeah.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's a.
Urban legend is probably the word I was looking for a wives, a wives tale, a tall tale, a piece of a piece of modern mythology.
They should have a superhero whose power is that he can produce the legendary brown note.
His name could be brown note.
And he plays, and he makes everyone poop their pants in this audience.
And he plays the tuba.
He does it with it.
He has a giant tuba and he only through with the tuba can he produce it.
And if he gets, if the bad guy knocks the tuba out of his hands, he's like, no, I can't make him shit anymore.
How will I get out of this jam?
He's like pinned to the ground and he's like sees the tuba slide across the room.
He grasps for it.
He's grabbing, but he can't quite reach it.
And he gets it.
And everyone shits themselves.
This is, this is pretty relevant to my brand considering my logo is brown on brown.
Yeah.
Why'd you do that?
What were you thinking?
What are you, what are you crazy?
I always thought it was like Minecraft a little bit, a little bit of Minecraft or just some video game dirt.
I never really thought much.
Some video game dirt.
The logo represents the quality of the work.
To me, I always thought it means that it was like made of wood.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
It's a wooden sign.
It's like, it's like an old game, old timey video game, PC game tavern.
You go in there and they've got like a tavern one might say.
That's right.
Yeah, it's a gamer with gamers in it, placing Minecraft dirt and pooping and shitting.
Yeah, exactly.
When I think of a gamer's tavern, I think of D&D.
Like that's the kind of gamers I imagine in a tavern.
Yeah, most likely.
Different, different, different genre.
Yeah.
So, I don't know.
What's everyone, what's been going on?
Well, hi.
For everybody.
I have, I've been cooking.
I've been doing some cooking, learning to make new things.
No fucking way.
Pretty useful ice skill.
I'm in my new place and I've only got this one hot plate.
I have to figure out how to cook everything that I want to eat.
Wait, you don't have like a stove?
Nope.
Just a hot plate, just an electric hot plate you plug into the wall.
What?
You should buy one of those tiny ovens.
Did you say oven?
I think you said oven.
I didn't say oven.
But I'm shocked, I'm shocked because I saw your place and it's like a nice place
and I'm like flabbergasted that it doesn't have a stove.
Well, it has like a kitchen countertop area, but it's like almost entirely like the sink
and the drying area for the washing up.
This is like a tiny little bit.
There's a tiny little bit to the side where there's plugs.
You can plug in like a kettle or a coffee machine or a toaster.
This is insanity.
This is a European thing, I swear to God.
I just have space for the hot plate.
No, it's not a European thing.
It's not really meant to be a lived in apartment thing, I think.
Like the apartment upstairs has a whole oven and stove thing.
This is just sort of like a...
So it's supposed to all be one apartment, but it's been split and you didn't get the kitchen.
Yeah, but like I can do so much because I've learned.
I get it.
No, I get it.
Much that I already knew this, but I never really thought about it,
that all cooking requires is hot metal.
And if you can heat up metal and you have ingredients, you can make anything.
That's true.
I've talked about this.
When I lived in Poland after they fired me for being a terrible, terrible teacher,
and I had to downgrade from the company provided loft apartment overlooking the city
to the room downstairs, semi-shared with the 90-year-old woman
in a dark corridor with the bathroom where you had to pump your own hot water.
I also...
And the heating system that was just like a giant stone column
that would warm up during the day.
I had also had no stove and no oven and I had nothing but a hot plate.
And I would go down to the local Biedronka supermarket and I would buy sausages
and then I would fry a little sausage pieces on my tiny little hot plate.
I would cook eggs on it and things.
You know all the usual shit you do.
Sounds like the life.
It was, you know what?
Fifteen's laddies a day.
For 15's laddies a day, it was totally the life.
That's all I have to say about that.
I know a guy who...
So I've lived the hot plate life.
I've lived the hot plate life is what I'm saying.
You've lived the hot life.
I mean yes.
Also, also true.
What were you saying?
Krono, you were saying you knew a guy.
Was I saying?
No, that's what I wanted to say.
You lived the hot life.
No, you were saying you knew a guy.
Oh yeah, I know a guy who lived in Poland for a while.
Poland!
He has an oven in Poland.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm cruel.
I'm cruel by nature.
And I also, the same guy went to, he lived in Ukraine for a while as well.
Yeah.
And did he have, did he live the hot plate life?
Probably.
Funny thing about Poland, paper, okay, what's the word?
Toilet paper, brown.
Like a paper band.
If you've wiped clean?
I don't know.
I was thinking the same thing.
No, it's not dark enough.
It's not that shade of brown.
It's brown like a brown paper towel.
Like a beige.
It's brown like a brown paper bag, yeah.
You know, it's just not, it's just not, you know, it's a little rough.
It's just not right and it's just a little rough and it's just, I would say it's not optimal.
But you know, they're all communists over there.
They just don't have, they don't have the means.
They don't have the means for white paper towel, white toilet paper.
They can't afford it.
That's just what happens.
What a shit show.
What a filthy continent.
Yeah, I've been cooking and I made fucking puttanesca pasta sauce.
I made spaghetti bolognese.
I made chili con carne.
Puttanesca.
Puttanesca, yes.
Like the Kremlin.
No, it is Italian.
I'm sorry.
Communist.
I told you.
I told you they're all communists.
Well, America just wants to put it in his place.
Puttin it is, it's puttin it, it's puttin it.
Wait, is it like a fish, is it like a fish sauce?
It has anchovies in it.
So, yes.
Okay.
There's anchovies and olives and, you know, tomatoes.
Yeah, that's real, that was a really good one.
Savory.
I love that one.
That was like, excellent.
You know, I've been like, what's happening?
My dad saying, hey, how do you like cook this?
And he just tells me because he's a cook guy.
He's a chef man.
What's that?
What's happening, my dad?
Yeah, what's happening, my dad?
The only thing I say to him is like, hey, how do you cook like chili?
And he's like, okay, here's how I do it.
That's funny, but I can't talk because I got my parents on Discord so that they can actually
like contact me.
Well, my dad, as far as I know, my dad is not on it and my mom, I just, because they
were, because I saw them recently and they were like, Ben, you never answer your phone.
How do we fucking contact you?
And my dad was like, Ben, I want you to give me your, I want you to give me your roommates
like phone numbers so that I can call them if I can't contact you.
And I'm like, oh no.
Oh no, that means that like they're going to get mad at me if I don't answer my phone
for my dad because my dad will be bugging them and that'll suck.
So I was like, okay, here's what I'm going to do.
I don't look at my phone.
I use this app called Discord and I told my mom where to get it and she got it.
And now she occasionally sends me Discord messages like, Ben, you forgot to renew your
auto payments for your phone bill.
We want $30 a month for your phone bill.
I'm like, yes.
You're saying you made a horrible mistake.
I, you know what?
It's fine.
You should never mix places of work and home or whatever.
I feel like Discord is like, it's useful to have a WhatsApp for family and like normie culture.
So I can talk to people there and they don't need to see whatever weird profile picture I have.
And they don't need to know anything about what I'm doing on this side of the tracks.
It's not that bad.
It's not like she's in my servers or anything.
It's only a matter of time, Ben.
It's only a matter of time.
I usually contact my family on a Facebook Messenger.
I used to use Facebook.
My roommates all used to communicate through Facebook Messenger and it was a big, we had a big push to migrate to
Discord and I've been a lot happier since then because I would never look at Facebook Messenger ever.
Well, I only use Facebook Messenger for family now.
I don't use it for outside of family stuff.
Well, I mean, that's how I was.
We had like a phone chat.
Like we have like a group chat on the phone.
And it was like, on the one hand, like, yeah, it's nice to keep it separate.
But then on the other hand, it's like, because it is separate and it's in a place that I never look.
I never see it and it might as well not exist.
And I miss everything that goes on in it.
I mean, I get notifications.
But I literally do not even pick up my phone and look at it.
I do not even do that.
That's your problem.
I mean, it's awesome.
I know.
That's my problem.
Discord is the solution.
Honestly, I think I need a new phone.
I think the reason I stopped looking at it is because my phone is crappy and it's laggy and it's really old.
And planned obsolescence.
And I just, if I had one that like worked better, maybe I, maybe this wouldn't have been such a problem.
I can't even play Pokemon Go anymore because it's so fucking grindy.
It takes like 30 seconds to do anything.
Like grindy as in like a grind, you can hear the wheels grinding against each other in the machine.
No, grindy as in, no, grindy as in you got to catch 40 catapes to turn them into a butterfree.
Oh my God, you got to catch 300.
It's always been my bed.
You got to catch 300 sproinks to turn them into one grumpy.
I need that grumpy.
It sounds like an RPG to me.
I need my grumpy dudes.
That's what I mean.
You can't haven't played, haven't played Pokemon Go all pandemic.
And it's not even because of the pandemic.
It's because my phone sucks.
You better use some of that cryptocurrency savings to buy yourself a new phone.
I sold on my crypto.
Chrono, I sold it all right before it started going up again.
Oh, oh, oh, it's down.
It is down right now.
I was going to say you should buy some now.
Ah, fuck you.
It's not actually that far down.
It's still down to like the biggest peak.
Maybe a little bit lower.
Wait, this is, this is incredible.
Oh my God.
Actually, the Bitcoin went down a lot.
You should buy some right now.
Wow, just today.
Honestly, yeah, this might be a time to buy.
Just today in the course of like, in like a second.
Wow, it went down from like five.
It dropped like 10.
It dropped like 10% in like 10 minutes.
It was a huge drop.
I kind of bought a little bit too early.
I bought it when it was like 58,
but it dropped way lower than that.
You, you, you, you bought after it dipped somewhat,
but not all the way.
It kept going down.
I see, I see.
God, it went all the way down for a second there.
It was all the way down back to 50 or almost.
People are saying it's not done growing yet though,
but oh wow, that's.
I would say right now you better buy it before it goes back up.
Maybe.
It's going back up right now.
If you look at the hourly like time frame.
Yeah.
But if you look at the month time frame,
it's like, I don't know,
it does look like it's just going down right now.
Who knows?
I think it will go back up.
I mean, it's going up.
It's going up again, but it's not like,
it's creep, it's creeping up again
the way it was creeping up before.
It's going up and it's going down.
It'll take a while to.
I would imagine it's going to take a while
before it goes back up to where it was before again.
People were saying,
I was seeing some comments that were like,
can't wait to hear them like,
can't wait to hear them like cope with the fact
that like Bitcoin went up again.
I think they were talking about Dogecoin specifically
because that's that shut up.
Dogecoin.
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw that.
Does Tom still have Dogecoin?
I got Dogecoin.
I hope so.
I bought some one while ago.
I didn't get any of that, unfortunately.
I wanted, when it was first going up that first time
I wanted to buy it,
but Coinbase was just like,
your account's too new.
We just error message.
I would have had, I would have like,
I would have Dogecoin.
Oh wow, it's up to 30 cents.
I guess Coinbase has a policy against
socialists or something.
They, it was, it's literally just,
no, at the time they weren't blocking Dogecoin.
I actually think it was just that like,
my account was too new.
Like I made my Coinbase account,
and not my Coinbase,
I made my Robinhood account like,
right at that moment,
and it like didn't let me make purchases
for like another day,
but by then it was down to like three,
it went up to seven cents,
but by then it had dropped to like three cents.
If I had got, if dammit, it would have,
I would have, it would be 10 times
what I bought it at,
if I had managed to buy it then at that,
at that point.
I bought 20 pounds worth at some point,
which is 695 Dogecoin.
So I've got 160 pounds.
That's quite a lot extra.
That's pretty good.
It could go further.
I'm sure this is the riveting for the audience.
Well, you know,
they're gonna be like in the future,
and they're gonna say,
how have these fucking stupid idiots,
they thought something was the case
and they had a prediction
and it has been different in the future.
That's the, that's the entertainment for them
is to see how we are.
Here's what makes me angry.
It's that like when I,
when I look at this Dogecoin,
this huge Dogecoin spike,
I'm like, you know what,
I should have known that this would eventually happen.
And the reason why I should have known
that this would eventually happen
is because Elon, it's Elon Musk's pet project.
And I would have known
that he would just kept posting
like shitty boomer memes of like a smirking dog
and that like that is enough to make this happen.
Like, like as much as I hate it,
that it's true.
I know that it's true
that he can just keep mentioning Dogecoin
and this will occur.
So I should have known.
I should have known that this,
that this dumb shit would take place
because of course it would.
So it's really on me.
It's really on me for missing out.
That's how the stock market worked
before all the crypto stuff.
I guess so.
The news would make things go up and down.
Was it, was it this stupid?
Or was it?
I, well.
Has it gotten stupider?
I think.
Yeah, probably.
The veneer of the internet has like,
like given it a new coat of paint.
But I think it's basically the same shit.
It's just people.
People believe know what they're talking about.
You know,
you know what it is?
Change the way people think about stuff
and then everyone does that.
You know, people.
I think it.
Newspapers and publications or whatever.
I think it's that.
Just go on Twitter.
I, well, yeah, that's what I'm going to say.
I think it's that the,
the internet has made news cycles shorter
and because news cycles affect stock prices,
it has just made the cycles faster,
which has made it like more erratic.
Right.
Like these things happen.
These things happen faster now.
Are stocks faster or is it just cryptocurrency?
Well.
I think all stocks are going up and down.
I mean, GameStop was doing its thing.
I don't know.
I mean, this is probably not,
I mean, we live in extraordinary times.
So maybe it's not fair,
but on the other hand, you know,
crises of capitalism happen periodically.
So it's probably not fair to not consider this
to be a part of normal,
normal fiduciary operations.
Hmm.
You know, speaking of crisis of capitalism,
I've got a funny story, which is embarrassing.
So.
Nice.
As I said, cooking, right?
I'm cooking and I'm like, oh,
I should buy some potatoes.
I like those, but I know I don't have a potato peeler at home.
So I need to go buy one on the way back and.
Just eat the fucking, just eat the fucking skins.
Get rusted potatoes and eat the skin.
I mean, I like the skin sometimes,
but like if you want to make mashed potatoes,
I don't think you can have the skins on.
Maybe you can.
I don't know.
You can.
Well, it depends on, it depends on the type.
Yeah.
I don't know what the, I'm just thinking,
okay, I probably would need a potato peeler.
I, and today or the day I was doing that shop,
the, the UK COVID restrictions were slowly lifting.
And it was the day where now lots of shops can open
and you can go to a restaurant and, you know,
things are changing and now lockdown is being lifted slowly
and people are going out and about and be careful.
They go, okay, cool.
And shops that were on the high street that I hadn't seen open
were now open and there was a kitchen suppliers shop.
And I'm like, oh, but based, that's perfect.
I'm on the way home, kitchen suppliers,
I'll go in, I'll get a fucking potato peeler.
Everything's going correct today.
I go up to them.
I don't see a potato peeler in the store.
Lots of nice pots and pans and stuff.
I already got stuff from Amazon.
And I say to the lady, you got a potato peeler.
And she says, yeah, okay, we got one in the back.
She gets it and I hold it and I'm like, okay, I'll have that.
She says that'll be 17 pounds, please.
17 pounds for a potato peeler.
That's a lot of money for a potato peeler.
17 pounds, she says.
I did, but I was like, oh no, I've started this transaction.
And I'm like stupid.
No, it's time to haggle.
It's time to haggle.
And I just put no credit card.
I put no credit card on the thing and it went beef.
And then I was like, what the fuck did I just do?
No, you fell for the trap.
That's so expensive for a fucking potato peeler.
Made a horrible mistake.
It was like, it was just, it was better be a fucking,
made a fucking titanium potato peeler.
I haven't even used it yet, but like I brought it back.
Where did you walk home?
I was like, why?
Why am I so bad at normal conversing with people
who can't say, isn't that a bit much?
I don't know if I want this.
I could have said that and stopped.
Yeah.
But I fucking didn't.
I mean, I understand.
It's a high pressure situation.
You're right there.
You're staring down the barrel of the gun and you look weak.
Honestly, if you say, I don't want to pay $17 for a potato,
but you look weak, you look cowardly, you look indecisive.
You can't let your reputation take that.
I didn't need anything else at the time.
So I would have just left.
I'm like, I don't know why that has sway in my decision-making
that I would just leave without buying anything.
I have a roommate who once in complete earnestness told me,
yeah, I went shopping before, but I forgot to get,
I don't know, rice or something.
I forgot to get some essential ingredient that I needed
for the thing I wanted to make.
Guess I can't make the thing.
And I'm like, why don't you just go back and get the rice?
And he was like, well, then they'd see me.
They'd see that I went back and forgot something.
And like, I'm too ashamed.
I'm too embarrassed.
I can't let them know.
He'd never be able to live that down.
Yeah, I can't let them see.
I don't want to be seen losing twice in one store.
He forgot his rice.
Oh, little baby forgot his rice.
What a fucking dupe.
I understand that, but I've definitely gotten over that myself.
Yeah, I understand the feeling.
I understand the feeling, but I wouldn't actually let it stop me
from going back for the rice.
Yeah.
Where was this that they were charging you $17 for a potato,
pounds for a potato?
That's like $800.
No, it's a lot of money.
I was trying to rationalize it as I walked home,
like, well, I mean, if I...
No, it's a really nice potato peeler.
It's top of the line.
It'll probably, if I can make it last for like 17 years,
then it'll just be $1.
If I peel like 17 years worth of potatoes and it's still good,
then that'll be a good purchase, actually.
I was just trying to...
It was on the high street.
And I guess it was like a high class,
upper class, big boy kitchen place.
And they did look nice.
What is the high street?
I just didn't think...
Well, it's just a street in the middle of the...
It's just a name for, you know, generic.
Town has the main street where all the shopping happens.
That's called the high street.
Oh, I see.
Sure.
Okay. Got you.
Yeah.
So this is like banks and restaurants and shops, mostly.
Is it high street?
That was a high end thing.
I mean, I guess lesson learned, don't shop there anymore.
No, I will never go there.
I will see, every time I see those things,
they didn't have any fucking prices on the things.
And I know why.
If you had prices on those pots and pans,
I bet there'd be like 50 pounds for one of those casserole dishes,
like fucking...
Or about 100 pounds, probably.
Was it like...
Was part of the problem that there was like a very like...
Like a high end atmosphere in there,
which like sort of made you feel more pressure than you would
in like a CVS or whatever.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, it was a small place.
It wasn't like a bustling anything.
It was just one person at the cash register,
another guy in the back.
And I was just sort of like asking for a potato peeler
and they had one and that was it.
That was the one potato peeler they had.
They didn't have like a cheapo version.
I didn't ask.
I just bought it and I felt stupid.
Absolutely tragic.
That's my embarrassing...
My embarrassing capitalism story.
How dare money be exchanged.
We have to take them down.
We have to tear the whole damn system down.
That was the time I became a socialist.
That was like, this is so fucked.
They own these means of production and it's bullshit.
They extracted my surplus value.
I told them...
And it was so effortless for them.
They did it with ease.
I told a stereo...
They forced you to buy that potato peeler at gunpoint.
I told the stereos on Twitter.
Speaking of cooking, I was talking about how I have...
I have still not been able to find IMO or isomaltoligosaccharide.
I have not been able to find it in any reasonable quantities,
like from a vendor.
But I am trying a new ingredient called alulose
and I'm going to try and do a new...
I'm going to try the formula again with a replacement
and see if it works.
And a stereos was like, why do you...
I can't believe you work so hard.
What did he say?
He said, I can't believe someone who doesn't get high
would work this hard on gummies.
I saw that tweet.
And I said it and then I reflected on what I said
and I was like, this is absolutely true.
I'm not even joking.
I'm not even kidding.
I was sick and tired of them extracting my surplus value
through whole foods, through their keto gummies.
So I'm literally seizing the means of production
and I'm decommodifying it.
Well, that's not true.
I still have to buy the ingredients, but I won't let them take it.
Come and take it, as my hero Ted Cruz might say.
You're seizing the means of the slight profit that they would get.
Of this one thing that they sell to me.
And it made me think about gardening.
And I was like, I kind of see the appeal of having a garden
if it's making food that you actually use.
But only...
I don't know.
Vegetables are so cheap, though.
Vegetables are so cheap.
So I don't know if it's...
I think maybe people that have gardens, they get it
so that the vegetables are fresher.
It's not because, like, ah, now the greedy fat cat Jeff Bezos
who owns Whole Foods, he's not going to get my 79 cents
for this zucchini that I grew in my backyard.
Yeah, it's a lot of fresh.
Not tall enough.
I think it's mostly...
Sorry, we keep cutting each other off
because you've got a lag to me
and I keep thinking you're talking over me
and you think I'm talking over you.
The lag is kind of rough.
But go on, what were you going to say?
I just said free is cheaper than 79 cents, I guess.
It made me think about that.
And then I'm like, but vegetables aren't a huge drain.
And then I'm like...
But it's true, they're not expensive.
Yeah.
So, like, what things...
Like, to me, like, literally,
keto gummies are a thing that I would spend...
Like, you buy them at the fucking store,
like $5 for, like, a 1.5 ounce bag.
So, you know, it actually represents a significant savings
if I can just make them at home.
And I'm just thinking, like, I don't know,
probably I should do everything,
like, anything that I can possibly do,
like, that anything I can DIY
and not have to buy from, like, a commercial vendor is good.
This gummy talk takes me back
to the last couple of times I was on.
Really?
I haven't actually talked about it in a while
because I've had no IMO.
Yeah, but I think the last couple of times I was on,
you were doing gummy stuff almost on a weekly basis.
I was, for a while.
You were talking about it for a while.
I should have been on the bingo card.
Remember that bingo card you posted?
Yes, the bingo card that Vale made.
And then I asked him,
hey, like, you should tweet that so I can retweet it.
Like, so people will know that you made it.
And he was like, he was like,
he didn't want people to know, like, what his Twitter was.
So I was like, and he was just like,
no, you can just tweet it.
And I was like, okay, I guess I will.
And he didn't want to be associated with a PCP?
I don't think it was that.
I think it was, specifically,
he didn't want his Twitter account to be associated with it.
Because I guess he probably has, like,
maybe he's got, like, an account that he uses
for, I don't know, business, I have no fucking idea.
Something else, I think that was it.
I think I made a joke recently about how
all the recent stuff happening with the PCP
is kind of bad for the gamer's tavern brand at this point.
You think so?
We're poison on you.
No, it was just a joke.
It reminded me of what that person told you one time
that the PCP is ruining the gamer's tavern brand.
Yes, my friend thought that, you know,
ever since gamer's tavern went on the PCP,
he's, like, been more edgy.
And it's like you were a bad influence on him.
Yeah, well, now maybe it's going to become true.
What do you think?
Hey, let's...
The prophecy is going to be fulfilled.
Why don't you just go off?
Go off and just badmouth Trixie for a while.
I'll listen.
Talk about how...
Tell me about how good it is that she's gone
and how you never liked her in the first place.
Go.
You don't actually have to do that.
But I would enjoy it.
I'll just say that I have read everything that has happened.
And I have to say I'm firmly in the Ben St. Camp.
There's a small but vocal minority of people
who say that I am cringe.
But I say to you, viewers, that they are...
Some people are like, Ben, why are you so...
How come you're so mad about it?
You're a little too salty, Ben.
Don't you think you should just let it go?
And I'm like, I'm sorry.
I feel personally grieved and offended
and I'm upset about it.
But at the same time, probably...
Okay.
I think a lot of people assume that you don't feel personally attacked
or offended by what Trixie's done
and you are just doing it for fun and to bully her.
Which I guess it can come across like that.
I guess if you thought that, it would be like Ben...
Someone said, you know, I don't want to assume intent,
but it was on a couple episodes ago,
the one where Trixie had just left.
Someone said in a comment, like,
Gib and Tom, you should not be neutral.
And Tom made a comment that was like,
I don't want to just trash my former colleague just for clout.
And I don't want to assume that he was talking about me,
but it was a sentiment that other people echoed that was like,
yeah, that like, Ben, you're just dog piling on a victim
who can't defend themselves just for clout.
And like, I don't agree with that.
It's not true.
I have been feeling kind of weird about it in this one specific way,
where I'm like, you know, these things are happening.
And I feel like I don't particularly care one way or the other too much about like,
like, you know, but like the whole RV thing, it's funny.
Right.
And I can see that it's funny.
Visit isthereanrv.com, isthereanrv.com.
Yeah, that is pretty funny.
To see whether there is an RV yet.
It's like, I can see that it's kind of funny,
but I personally don't find like the intense, what do you call it,
anticipation for that whole thing to happen.
Like, if it happened, I feel like I'm too distant from Trixie in that whole crowd.
Well, they keep piping it.
Well, that's, it's not about them.
It's about like, I'm wondering whether that means that I wasn't very close to Trixie
in the first place and that this breakup doesn't affect me so much because I didn't.
Consider.
I mean, that's how like a close as much.
That's how I feel.
It's like, I mean, we barely even heard from her.
We barely even heard from her for like months and months and months.
Honestly, like, you know, she's, yeah, I said this before, she's got her new,
she's got her new posse who support, who unconditionally support whatever she does.
And like, I feel like there's no, there's no, there's no even interest in us anymore,
which is fine.
I mean, yeah.
I just feel weird because I, because I feel like.
But then people turn around are like, oh, why are you, Ben, why are you,
Ben, why are you trashing your friend, man?
This is your friend.
No, it's not.
Shut up.
You don't understand.
You do not understand.
You are projecting.
I don't know.
I feel like people are projecting on me a lot of the time when they say this stuff.
I mean, there has been like that whole parasocial relationship.
Like they've seen the PCP, they assume things.
But like, I think I feel weird because I feel like I should be like more close to Trixie
and therefore should feel more upset about what's happening with the whole like never
coming on the podcast again.
I know Trixie like doesn't.
She said like Tom and Gibb.
I don't mind you, but I hate Ben saying, and I was like, oh, well.
Well, there it is.
I don't think I saw that.
She said, she said.
In here, she said.
In here, she said like you guys contact, can contact me like about red.
About red stuff.
Yeah, specifically, I guess it's not put words in mouths, but I don't know.
I feel like if I don't know whether I feel bad that I am not angrier at her.
You know what I mean?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know what's going on.
People are very invested and I don't feel invested and I feel like I should be.
And I feel like that's an indication that it's bad.
I don't know.
I feel like you're saying two things at once.
It simultaneously sounds like you're saying you feel bad that you are not more sad that
she has left, but also that you are.
Feel bad that you are not more angry at her for her.
Well, I just I feel.
I feel kind of bad that I am not emotionally invested in whatever is going on to any any
any sort of extent that I feel like other people are and you seem to be.
I am I am I honestly I'm cool.
I'm cooling off.
I'm cooling off in it a little bit because like there's not there's nothing to I've
made I've made my jokes.
I've had my fun at their expense.
I've made my feelings on them clear and like there's really nothing more to be said about
it.
So I'm starting to cool off in a little bit like whatever.
Well, there's nothing more to say on it now until something else happens that is.
Yeah.
Well, sure.
I mean, they could they could turn around and do something that I found grievously offensive
again.
And then it would ignite my ire once more.
I mean, sure, that's possible.
I think it's only a matter of time.
I mean, I don't know.
Could be could be.
Well, I agree pretty much with with your take on everything, even though I don't personally
have anything against Trixie.
Yeah, she never did anything against me specifically.
Yeah.
Just the just the
just that she just that she would it was really mostly just about
the lecture, the not releasing the lecture.
I do it does offend me.
It does offend me and upsets me.
But the thing that made me really mad was just that she would let her she would let her
weird friends talk on our behalf about things that are not their business and are only our
business and then and then would defend that and then would get upset at me for objecting
to that.
Like, that's the thing that I'm like, this is unacceptable.
This is unacceptable.
I agree.
That's pretty weird.
Yeah.
OK, but like I said,
it's just there's only so much to even say about it.
And I'm not like you give them.
I'm not that I'm not that worried about it anymore.
I don't know.
Let the healing begin.
Maybe in a couple of years, she can come back on.
No.
No, thanks.
Maybe if she makes a full apology.
Maybe if she makes like a full and thorough apology to the point that I'm satisfied that
she has turned over a new leaf, but not under that's what it would take.
One of those apology videos I am.
I hear so much.
I would I would have I would I would take a lot of convincing.
I would take a lot of convincing to turn me around on her at this point.
But I guess I guess never say never.
That's I guess that's all I have to say about that.
Looking forward to that Alulose.
That's going to be pretty good.
I got to say I got to say, though, I tried.
I think even the company that inspired me to do this on the smart sweets like candy company,
I think they have also switched to Alulose, at least partially.
And I tried some of their.
I tried some of them again recently and they have a different consistency to them.
And honestly, it's not as good.
I feel like the texture is not as good.
And so I'm a little concerned that Alulose is not going.
I don't really understand.
That's that's what I want to know.
Can I fabricate it?
No, I don't know how it's made.
I know it is.
Okay, technically the FDA does not consider it to be a fiber per se,
but it is some sort of non digestible carbohydrate that comes from tapioca root.
And that's what IMO is.
And how how is it extracted from the root?
I have absolutely no idea.
I assume it involves some kind of like chemical reaction.
Does this thing cause autism?
That's just what you assume when you hear about a chemical.
Yeah, why not?
I don't know.
If it could be a solution.
It is the culprit of some sort of autism.
And honestly, I don't I literally don't even know what Alulose is.
I don't know where it comes from.
It comes from Alu plant.
It's, you know, I could, you know, I never did try corn fiber.
Corn fiber is also corn fiber is actually considered a fiber and it is similar in its derivation,
but it has a different like consistency.
I tried cooking gummies with corn fiber once or twice and they didn't come out well,
but maybe I just didn't try hard enough.
It's Oh, no, no, no, you know what the difference is is that IMO is naturally sweet.
Isomalt oligosaccharide syrup is like itself.
It is both a thickener and a sweetener, whereas corn fiber is like completely neutral.
So I would have to account for that.
Alulose is also sweetener.
IMO doesn't IMO doesn't sound too safe.
It's it's the worst.
There are there are some there.
I guess there's some very niche community of like culinary or like chemical YouTubers who had, you know,
they have maybe 10,000 subscribers.
There's like four channels like this.
They have 10,000 subscribers and there was a big blow up in their community,
which means that maybe they got like 2,000 views on a video explaining it when the FDA decided that
isomalt oligosaccharides, we will not we will not technically accept its categorization as a fiber.
You can no longer list it as tapioca fiber on your on your ingredient list.
You must now call it isomalt oligosaccharide use its full chemical name.
It was a big hullabaloo.
I don't think it was a PR thing so much as like people see chemical name on their product and they go,
I think I think it was that like people were talking about like, oh, isomalt oligosaccharides.
Is this a is this like a new like hot ingredient?
Is this like a new like a sugar alternative?
Is this going to be replacing sugar in a lot of new foods and think a lot of people were skeptical of it?
And then these people who were skeptical were vindicated by the FDA's decision to not technically categorize it as fiber.
And they were like, I called it.
I called it just like I called the election of 2020 and 2016.
I am a God.
They said I told you isomalt oligosaccharide is poison.
It will give you autism.
It's probably is it expensive sounds like it's pretty expensive.
Yeah, it's kind of expensive.
I mean, it's what was I paying?
I think I was paying like $11 for like a pound of it.
Wow, that's that's pretty pricey.
That's pretty right.
I'm pretty pricey, but not as pricey as buying the gummies from Whole Foods.
I'm looking on Wikipedia for the manufacturing of isomalt oligolarisaccharide.
And they say it's made from just starch from, you know, cereal wheat barley, starch, normal old starch that you can buy.
Starch is first converted by means of a simple enzymatic hydrolysis into high maltose syrup with di tri and oligolarisaccharides.
I don't know what that means.
Sounds right.
Glycocytolinkages, which are really digestible in the human intestine.
These things are further converted into digestion resistant glycosidic linkages.
Absolutely.
Creating something.
It's so difficult reading science Wikipedia.
Absolutely.
That is all makes perfect sense to me.
I can personally tell us that that is accurate.
They say they say simple enzymatic hydrolysis.
So all you need is to do simple high.
I'm going to click on the high.
Simple enzymatic hydrolysis.
That really that's all it takes.
Yeah.
Okay. Hydrolysis is any chemical reaction in which a molecule of water breaks one of.
Wait, does this just mean put it in water?
Does it just mean you dissolve?
Does it just mean you're dissolving it?
No, no, no, it's not.
It's not dissolving it because dissolving it is when.
The molecules of a substance are the molecule itself is not separated.
Like like the molecules are intact.
They just disperse through the water.
It's talking about the water itself is like reacting to break the molecule into two.
Sure.
Substances.
So it's not it's not just simple dissolution.
Sure, but it involves putting water next to it.
Didn't you major in physics or something?
In it's technically not just dissolving it in water, but in practice.
Yes, it's just putting it in water and dissolving it.
You just put it in water.
When I carbohydrate is broken into its component sugar molecules by hydrolysis.
This is recognized as saccharification.
So it turns it into a saccharide.
So saccharide from Smash Bros.
Smash Bros.
This is when this is like this is like this is the opposite of bimbofication is
saccharized saccharization.
It's when you turn sweet and nice.
I really feel like this means you could just buy like the sort of starch they use,
put it in water and then this third thing that I can't figure out if we can crack the code.
Can you link me this?
Can you link me this article?
It's just Wikipedia, but yeah.
So you're going to start cooking this stuff in your house like making drugs or something.
Like cooking in a bathtub and in a skill.
Yeah, you make a fucking ton of it.
You make an entire gummy.
You're going to become the Walter White of gummies.
This is this is what I that's literally what I wanted.
Like I would love to just have like buy like the basic like what's the word like elemental
materials like carbon nitrogen stuff and just like combine the molecules from like their
most base forms into like into, you know, benzene rings and chain the benzene rings together
to form complex carbohydrates and then, you know, and then fold them, fold the carbohydrate,
fold the benzene rings in the complex carbohydrates over a thousand times to harden them.
Yeah.
Have an entire laboratory in your house.
Oh, oh my God.
Yeah.
Gluc isomalto oligosaccharides are glucose oligomers with alpha D one six linkages including
isomaltos panos isomalto trios isomalto tetrose isomalto pentose.
Nigeros cojibeos and higher branched oligosaccharides.
This is this is a whole new world.
This is a whole world of saccharides.
Oh, so.
So is there any specific isomalto oligosaccharides that you were using or is it could you use
any one of them?
Is it just one thing?
Um, I mean, hold on.
I will, I have the packaging.
I have the packaging right here.
And I think it just says it doesn't specify.
Yeah.
The first ingredient is isomalto oligosaccharides parentheses vegetable source.
So you don't even have to specify.
You don't even have to specify whether you're using isomalto tetrose or nigeros or cojibeos
or any of the higher branched oligosaccharides.
They're all they all fall under the same the same banner according to the FDA.
I guess experimenting to find the perfect saccharide.
I literally I'll just have to find every vegetable and and, you know, hydrolysis it,
which just soak it in water and just see like what what fibrous fibrous powders float to the surface.
We could go even further back.
Like if they use the starch from from foods, how do you make starch?
Could you just could you just grow your own food, start to fire it and then
enzymatically hydrolysis it into a fucking oligosaccharides and then make that into gummies?
Could you do the entire thing?
Here's here's the important part.
Isomalto oligosaccharides are a normal part of the human diet and occur naturally in fermented foods such as sourdough,
breads and kimchi.
But it has been identified as a natural constituent of honey.
And although chemically related, it isn't.
OK, that's a different thing.
IMO is a sweet tasting high density syrup, which could be sprayed dried into powder form.
OK, the thing about it, the thing about this stuff, it sounds really bizarre,
but it's actually delicious.
Like you can just like this goo that you get this stuff that you fucking hydrolysis
out of, you know, complex carbohydrates.
It is it is just like a clear, like sweet syrup.
It kind of tastes like it kind of tastes like agave nectar.
It's delicious.
It's incredible.
I would live on it and nothing else if I could.
It's like.
I'm like, I'm like me with isomalto oligosaccharides is like fry in that episode with a slurm when the slurm queen squirts out
super slurm from her.
I just saw a clip of that the other day.
I also just saw a clip of that the other day.
They must have been going around.
It must have been a part of the YouTube algorithm.
Someone someone tweeted it with like an attached thing that's like, I don't know,
it was probably like, huh, this is like this is just like the Biden administration
and bombing the Middle East or something is like fry in super slurm.
It seems kind of random.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, considering like who I follow on Twitter, that's that's the kind of take I would expect to see.
But that's me though.
If I would, I would recommend you.
Okay.
You can.
There are vendors on there are vendors on Alibaba who will sell the stuff.
Like they won't sell you like a reasonable amount.
They will sell you like 10 pounds of it or even 100 pounds of it, which is what I would want.
They will only sell it to you in metric tons, which is bad.
But they will sell you like a sample bag of like one kilogram of it, which is not very much.
And it'll cost you like $50 because they have to ship it to you from from China.
But if you are curious, I would actually recommend buy like a sample bag of one kilogram of Isomolta
oligosaccharide syrup and you will get it in like a like zip tied like sealed like hermetically sealed plastic bag.
And you can just open it up and eat a spoonful of it and you will discover a whole new world of sweetness.
Well, I do have to caution from ordering stuff from China like in weird powdered form because sometimes they don't have very good regulations over there.
And that stuff can be contaminated with, you know, foreign substances.
No, no, no, they come with the entire thing is a foreign substance because it's from China.
That's true. That's true. That's a good point.
No, no, no, the whole the whole thing is a is a it comes with a certificate of purity that says like what percentage of the substance it is.
And it's usually like 99.99%.
You know, they sell to you they sell it's it's it's all very it's all very official.
It's all very I got mine.
I got mine from and you can look this up you can get this yourself you can buy one kilogram of of IMO syrup from tapioca source for $53 and 50 cents from a company called Focus Herb Corp.
Focus Herb innovation is our nature is their slogan.
That's a pretty good slogan.
Oh, you can buy they sell.
Wait a minute. Oh my God, they sell all kinds of great stuff.
They sell only anolic acid, muslinic acid, hydroxy hydroxy tyrosol and only European.
Well, you know, all kinds of all kinds of good stuff on offer here at Focus Herb.
A subsidiary of Shang Zifu Heng FH Biotechnology Corporation Limited.
They are they are related to the Umbrella Corporation.
Is that is that from Resident Evil?
Yes, the evil company from Resident Evil that spread the zombie virus.
I've never played a Resident Evil, but I still got the reference.
Do you remember there was an image going around of I don't know whether that was actually real.
Maybe it was of a Chinese bio lab that had a very similar logo to the Umbrella Corporation around the time COVID was happening.
Oh, yeah, I remember what you're talking about.
I was like, oh, no, I don't maybe maybe that sort of rings a bell.
Yeah, I remember this vaguely.
I don't know if it's real or not might have might have just been a joke.
No jokes, that kind of thing that I've heard of jokes.
I have no idea what you mean.
Okay, this is it seems too similar to be real, but I don't know.
I don't know if it's fake or real, but it's like it's pretty bad PR.
It's just got green arrows instead of red arrows.
Yeah, wait.
Oh, wow.
If this is real, it's not a very good idea to brand yourself in this way.
This seems this seems like too much of a coincidence.
I don't think I believe it.
No, I don't think I buy it.
But now that I'm thinking about it and looking, yeah, it seems to be debunked.
Oh, it's probably not real.
Well, that's good news for Shanghai, Rui-Lan, Bau-Hu-San, biotech limited.
Yeah, what if I Google that?
What do I actually see?
Maybe they're the ones that can fucking stuff speaking of locations in the world.
I've been playing a lot of geography quiz stuff.
I've been playing GeoGuessr today.
I got almost a perfect score.
I was looking around.
I'm really annoyed, but I guess it's understandable.
The GeoGuessr is now a subscription service.
You can play it for free, but only once per day.
That's the one.
It's with no R, or GeoGuessr, right?
Yeah, no U.
It says create account to play.
It says I have to create a game.
Wait, is this the thing that I was playing the other week?
No, it's different.
You mean the thing I linked where it was just the map of the world?
Yeah, what was that?
That was online.cetera.com
Cetera, okay.
So what's GeoGuessr?
GeoGuessr is like Google Maps, you go down into street view,
and you are tossed with trying to figure out where the fuck on Earth you are,
and you can zoom around, you can click around just like in Google Maps, Google Earth, whatever.
You move your little guy around the streets, you look at things, you zoom in,
you figure it out based on, you know, the location, the street signs, things like that.
And it's really fun because it's like detective work.
You have to look for clues, you know, you're plopped down some random place
that's in the Google Maps archive of photograph, you know, 360 camera stuff.
You could be fucking anywhere, and you have to figure it out, and it's, you know,
it's just so satisfying doing the detective work to like, okay,
cars are driving on this side of the road, so it can't be these countries, it could be these ones.
It looks like a hot climate, probably this sort of area, but I'm not sure.
The language, Spanish, that could be Spain, that could be South America, you know, like,
you got to look at things like that, and then you got to narrow it down, find landmarks.
It was extremely fun. I loved you, I guess. I'm really annoyed that I have to pay for it.
I'm probably just not going to play it that much.
Yeah, that sounds pretty interesting, you know.
Remember the sick acapella theme song to Carmen San Diego?
I remember the regular theme song, but not...
What?
What do you mean, what?
Chrono, you remember.
Are you talking about the regular theme song?
Yeah, the like, the acapella version, it's...
Was it played on the actual show?
Yeah, it was in the show, yeah, it was in the show.
Yeah, then I probably do know what you're talking about.
She puts the miss in misdemeanor when she stole the beans from Lima.
Yeah, I remember that.
How good is that?
From the Red Sea to Greenland, they'll be singing the blues.
Got tips.
Oh, colors.
She steals their soul in South Korea, makes Antarctica cry uncle.
Oh, no.
Somebody's got to find this girl and kill her.
They tried finding her.
The only person who could find Carmen San Diego is Waldo.
I was going to make that joke.
I remember I really liked where in time is Carmen San Diego.
And I literally, the reason I liked it is because it had crappy early 90s CG visual effects.
And I just thought those were so fucking cool.
When I was a little kid, the incredibly, the horribly, the horribly dated CG,
Megazord transformation from the Power Rangers movie, that was my shit.
That was the coolest thing I'd ever seen.
I remember that.
Yeah.
With the slime guy?
Ivan Ooze.
I remember that, that, that giant, like he becomes the size of a planet or something.
And he's like, I'm so evil.
And then he dies.
But that, yeah, there's nothing quite like seeing CG on TV for the first time or first few times.
Where it's like, no, early, early, like Power Rangers and shit like that.
But that's something that something zoomers will never get to experience.
I suppose.
They grew up, they grew up with CG.
Whatever.
They'll never experience everything that already happened.
They will never get, well, but they will never specifically get to see like bad,
like objectively bad CG and be like blown away by it like I want.
Yeah.
They really missed out.
They really did, for real.
Well, you know, millennials will never get to experience bagpuss for the first time and be scared shitless by a talking cat.
That's a real cat and it's talking, but it's not actually, it's a puppet.
She'll ransack Pakistan and run a scam in Scandinavia.
Then she'll stick them up down under and go pickpocket Perth.
Why is she such a bitch?
She's such a bitch.
She doesn't even do it.
She doesn't even do it for money.
She went all the way to Lima to steal some fucking beans.
She stole all the beans.
She stole all the beans from Lima, not because they were like worth money.
No, no.
It's like Lima's got some good beans.
It wasn't all the beans.
It was a misdemeanor.
It would have only been like a fucking handful of beans.
She just wanted to make the pun.
She had to do a misdemeanor.
Oh yeah, you're right.
It is.
She had to miss and misdemeanor when she stole the beans.
So she was like, she had to pay a fine.
She had to pay a fine.
She flew all around the fucking world.
Little annoying petty crimes that people can't catch her.
But it was just like that line from, it was just like that line from Final Fantasy Tactics.
If the penalty for a crime is a fine, then that law only exists for the lower class.
And she's like, you know what?
I'm well off enough.
I'll just steal all the beans from Lima.
I'll take the pun.
It's fine.
She's probably a billionaire.
I'll take the fine.
It's fine, she said.
That's not a very good rhyme.
It's not, no, it's a, it's, that's, it just sounds like something, sounds like a gamer's tavern joke.
I don't know.
Yeah, it does.
Isn't there like a rule that you can't, if there's a pun or a rhyme, it can't be exactly the same word.
But it's, the point is, the point isn't that it's a rhyme.
The point is that it's the same word that means two different things.
Does it, wait, say it again?
Yeah, that's, that's known as a pun in some circles.
Yeah, I'll take the fine.
It's fine.
Oh yeah, you're right.
Yeah, of course.
Of course I'm right.
It's just not a very good one.
It's, shout out.
It's fine.
It's fine, actually.
It's a perfectly fine and decent.
Perfectly fine and that it is like sand that is very not coarse.
It slips through my fingers easily.
But I really, I really like the, the writing and Final Fantasy tactics.
I think it's very good.
I, yeah, people say it's one of the best written RPGs.
I, I've said this before, but I, I'm one of the many, many people that got stuck in, in that, in the castle
against, um, will, will we graph?
We grow?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, I got stuck in that castle and I never finished the game.
And now I just don't have the patience.
I just don't have the patience for JRPGs anymore.
I'm just not interested in like a dialogue heavy fucking 60 hour game like that.
I'm just, I'm just not into it.
It's cause a lot of them are like you're, you're following a character as they grow in this harsh world
and the leveling up is sort of, it's, it's mirroring the story that's happening.
But you've, I've seen this story so many times.
It's not that exciting to see that he gets strong at the end and beats the bad guy.
And I also don't want to do all that grinding.
So like, I don't care.
Actually, yeah, yeah.
It's with a problem.
It's not actually the, I mean, I'm hesitant.
I don't read enough anymore, but it's the thing that I think would drag it down for me.
It's not the, it's not that it's heavy dialogue.
It's not that there's a lot of reading.
It's that the battles just take like an hour apiece.
And I'm just like, just give me, just put me in Noida and give me a wand that goes, that's all I want.
I don't have the patience to play RPGs anymore either.
But back when I did Final Fantasy Tactics was pretty good.
I, I mean, I loved that whole, the tactical RPG genre.
That was my favorite genre in like the PlayStation X era.
Whatever.
What if you just say PlayStation X?
I don't know.
I just remember reading, I remember reading a Game Informer and because there was a PlayStation 2, they would abbreviate PlayStation as PSX.
I don't know why they just, that's what they would do.
I played, last week I struggled to remember the name and then I remembered it was Front Mission.
Front Mission 3, I think was the one that I liked.
That one's on the PlayStation.
Yeah.
I remember there was another one called Vandal.
No, Vandal Hearts was like the more traditional fantasy one.
Vanguard Bandits was the one.
Okay.
Front Mission was the one where you were in mechs, but it was like a gritty, like futuristic sci-fi.
Vanguard Bandits, you were in mechs, but it was like fantasy anime mechs.
And they were like powered by like jewels.
And there was like this one like holy ancient mech that like the good, that like the good campaign was like based around like finding and like taking back your rightful throne as Prince of the Kingdom or whatever.
That game was like kind of bad.
And like, I think even when I bought it, like I went to this, like I went to fucking GameStop and looking for it.
And I asked someone like, hey, do you got Vanguard Bandits?
And the guy was like, oh yeah, we got that.
Yeah, I'm not that into that game.
I've heard of this game, but I've never played it.
Funny thing, okay, it plays like Final Fantasy Tactics.
You got mechs and like you got your characters in your mechs.
And like the characters have some abilities of their own, but mostly it's the mech that determines like what the character can do in battle.
And they, I don't know, they do like a tactical RPG thing and you can put different characters, different mechs and you upgrade them a little bit.
You can give them different gems that give them different powers.
There are like multiple story paths, like whether you want to become, you know, take your place as king of the kingdom or whether you want to like become an evil conqueror and like take over the empire.
Or there's like a third one where you become like a renegade and start your own, I don't know, anarcho-syndicalist commune or whatever.
But then the funny thing is whenever you do an attack in this tactical RPG, the game goes to like a fully, it's not very good, but it's like an animated like 3G, 3D polygonal cutscene basically where the two robots will like do the attacks on one another.
And it takes ages, but I was so into it.
That's a kid.
It looked so cool.
I think Front Mission also does that, doesn't it?
Does it?
I don't think it does it to the same extent.
I don't, I don't think so.
I think Front Mission 3, you would just see the little, you would just see your little pixel man like shoot the little little missiles or guns.
I'm pretty sure you can see it in 3D, but you can turn that animation off in the options.
Because I have actually played Front Mission 3.
I remember being frustrated because in Front Mission 3, you can eject your guy.
Like the cool part about Front Mission 3 is that you can, you can choose in a battle to not destroy, but merely disable like an enemy's mech.
And if that happens, you can eject your little person from your mech and have him go and run and jump into the enemy mech and take it over.
And like while he's out on the ground, he's really slow and he's really vulnerable and any mech that attacks him will just completely obliterate him.
Which is really, really cool.
You can steal enemy mechs like that.
And you can't do that in Vanguard Bandits.
There's no way to like eject your guy and steal an enemy's mech in that game.
But from what I remember, that feature in Front Mission 3 wasn't very useful because it was pretty difficult to do and enemy mechs weren't that good.
I, I don't, I was, I mean, I was a young teen at the time.
I think I just thought it was cool.
I think I thought it was cool and I wanted to do it.
There was a game for the Super Nintendo called Metal Warriors where you could do the same thing.
You can jump out of your mech and go into other mechs, but it wasn't a tactical RPG.
It was a, it was a side-scrolling action game.
Metal Warriors.
Yeah, I remember renting that one when I was a kid.
I don't think it's too good, but it was very interesting.
I remember this box art, but I don't think I ever, I think I probably saw this box art at Blockbuster.
The, the really good, the, the better mech game for the Super Nintendo is Cybernator.
It has a different name in, in, in Europe.
I forget what it was called in Europe, but in US it was Cybernator.
That one's pretty good.
I, you know what, I think I probably, I was never into like sci-fi and like mechs and stuff.
I think I might have seen both of these games and just been like, eh, eh, it's nerd shit.
Uh, uh, uh, Final Fantasy, uh, Swords and Sorcery please, for chads like me.
Actually, um, in my opinion, the, the most fun front mission game I ever played is, uh,
I think it's called Front Mission Gun Hazard, and it was for the Super Famicom.
Uh, but there is a translation patch you can download to play it.
It's a side-scrolling action RPG with mechs and, uh, you can buy parts and level up.
And, uh, it's pretty cool.
Front Mission Gun, Gun Hazard.
I have a review of it on my website.
Look at, okay, okay, okay.
I, this is such, um, this is so, uh, this is so like, wait, no it is, it's Squaresoft.
Oh, it's Squaresoft.
Yeah, it's made by Squaresoft.
Okay, this looks like, who's the Final Fantasy artist?
This looks like, this looks like someone trying to do, this is either him being really lazy
or it's someone doing like a bad impression of his art style.
Yeah, I don't remember the name of the artist, but I know who you're talking about.
The guy who did the art for Final Fantasy VI and V.
He does it for all of them, yeah.
And he did, and I think he did a bunch of the Metal Gear Solid, um, like, concept art
and he did a bunch of like, stuff for them to, Yoshitaka Amano.
Yoshitaka Amano.
Yeah, that's-
No, maybe he, maybe I'm thinking of someone else who did the Metal Gear stuff.
Um, yeah.
But this looks like, this box art, it's like, it looks like his style, but it looks bad.
So, I don't know what's going on there.
I've never seen the box art, but the game itself looks pretty cool.
It looks like Cybernator, but it has action RPG elements and it has a story.
And the story is pretty decent.
I like that, I like that.
Was it a side scroller?
Yeah, it's a side scroller, so you don't have to, you know, do the turn-based combat stuff.
I like the turn-based combat stuff when I was a kid.
I felt, I felt so fucking smart.
I felt so fucking smart beating games like that.
It's like, damn.
This is like a tactical, I'm making tactical choices and obliterating my foes.
Well, if you, uh, if you beat Final Fantasy Tactics as a kid, that was a pretty good accomplishment.
But I did-
That game is actually pretty complicated.
But you know that I didn't.
You know that I, that I, uh, got stuck in the WeeGraph's castle.
Oh yeah, I just, I just forgot about that.
I did, I did beat it as a kid and, um, it's pretty, uh, it's pretty impressive.
I was able to beat it at, at that age.
Um, I, I mean, I really like, I really like that it has permadeath.
I've always loved games with permadeath.
Always, always, always.
Does that mean you're like Fire Emblem?
I've never played Fire.
I probably would have loved Fire Emblem as a kid, but I never played-
You've never played Fire Emblem?
No, not a single one.
That's, uh, that's weird.
Is that weird?
I don't know whether you'd be into it today, though.
I would, it would be cool if you-
I don't, I don't think I would.
Yeah, those are good.
GBA, especially.
What I like about Fire Emblem is that it's probably one of the fastest-paced, uh, tactical RPGs you can play.
That's, I mean, that's good.
Oh yeah.
That's a-
It's, it's lightning quick.
It really does not feel like a turn-based RPG of any kind.
You, you have your guys, and the only thing you need to worry about, aside from positioning, positioning is the main thing.
It's positioning and, uh, the weapons they have.
And you can, sometimes you can buy new weapons.
A lot of the time you'll get weapons from killing enemies or getting chests.
And the whole game, at least Fire Emblem 7 and 8, um, they're very linear.
Um, 7's, uh, particularly.
So it's all, like, you, you can't, like, go back to an area to grind in 7.
So everything in the game is laid out in such a way that you can always do it, um, unless you really majorly fuck things up.
It does have permadeath.
I like that.
I like that it, I like that it, like, yeah, grinding and, like, playing the game in a boring way.
Like, isn't even an option.
Like, it's just, it's just like, you must progress.
I like that.
There is, there is one way, but it's extremely dangerous.
You can go into, like, in certain levels, there's like an arena, like a gladiatorial arena.
You, you send your little guy in there and you can wager if you will win the fight.
And, uh, the only thing you can do is just watch them wail on an enemy and then you can press a button to, to run away and lose the money.
But if they die in the arena, they die.
That's it.
And you don't get the money as well.
And so you can play a level, but you can, but you can, but you can save scum it, right?
No, no.
Fire Emblem has a unique thing where, um, every action you take is permanently saved for that playthrough of that level.
So if you fuck up and die, the only way to reset is to reset the entire level, which makes the stakes on the longer levels like raise and,
and when you get to the very end of the final levels of the thing, you're like, Holy shit.
This took so long to get here.
Don't fuck up.
Oh my God.
You know, it's very tense.
What console?
What console is this on?
It's on GBA.
I don't know how they did it, but like it was just sort of.
They have like, oh wow.
That's badass.
You could turn, you could turn the power off.
That's badass that they wouldn't even let you save scum it.
No, yeah.
So like if, if you're, if you're a little kid, you lose someone, you cry.
You click the little power button and you turn it back on and then you reload and it loads exactly at the moment that you turned it off.
So you see them die a second time.
And you cry again.
And then you realize, you realize that you have to restart level.
Fuck.
Fuck yes.
But you can restart the level and you do have to do everything all over again, but it's better than losing that Pegas this night.
I'll tell you that.
Yes.
Um, all right.
That's pretty cool.
You should play Fire Emblem 7 on emulator or something.
Oh, I mean, it's got, it's got cool characters in it, but that's mostly the fun gameplay.
The seventh one is the second GBA one, right?
Yeah.
The one with Ellen Woodland and Hector, the first English translated one.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking of.
What I should probably give a try is, um, Hades, which I bought at the same time.
I told you that people were telling me Hades was good, so I went and bought Hades, but then it recommended me Noida and then I also just also picked up Noida on a whim.
And then I ended up getting insanely addicted to Noida and I haven't even played Hades at all.
Um, I should give, I should give that one a shot.
The games that, that studio makes, they made like, what was it called, Bastion and some other ones?
Yeah, um, Transistor.
Transistor and yeah, so I think there's another one between.
Yeah, I've been hearing a lot about it.
I haven't played any, I haven't played any of their older games by the way.
Those, those all look cool and I can appreciate that they're beautiful, but there's something about that camera angle that really annoys me and I just don't want to play a game in that camera angle looking down.
You know what?
I feel the same way.
It just kind of inherently feels, I don't know, not as engaging as like a side scroller to me.
Yeah, the isometric, I know exactly what you mean.
And I, and I can't, I can't justify it.
Yeah.
There's no good reason.
There's no way I could say, oh, I don't know about those games because of something like that, but it is, I mean, I've told, talked before about how like, if a game is in 3D, I just like it more than if it was in 3D.
It's just some things that just resonate with me a lot.
I feel kind of the opposite.
When a game is in 2D, I tend to like it more than 3D, probably because I guess I grew up with 2D games.
I think I'm with you.
I think I'm a 2D guy.
If I had to pick.
If I had to pick one or the other.
I know it's not a fair way to judge things.
It's just a bias.
No, not at all.
It's completely unfair.
It's arbitrary.
It's, it's not fair, but it is fair.
But I can't help it.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's right.
Exactly.
Speaking of games, are you, Gib, are you caught up on Psycholonials?
Chapter 8.
Yes.
Shit's really, shit's really going places.
Shit's really getting, getting down to it now.
Only one more chapter left and.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I can't wait.
Can't fucking wait.
Yeah.
Spoiler alert.
Watch, I mean, yeah, read Psycholonials.
It's a technically a video game, but it's weird to say play it because there's not yet any
interactivity.
It's, it's, there's hints.
I mean, it's basically.
That's hints of future interactivity.
But.
I, I don't think there will actually be any.
I think it's, I think it's a red herring.
I don't know.
I feel like, I feel like the, the, the, the pull the rug on out from under the player sort
of moment would be get them thinking that they can't, they don't have a choice.
And then finally like do the same thing again and chapter nine, the last chapter.
And this time the choice actually does something and people like, wait, I didn't, I didn't know.
Oh, and then you see the consequences.
Maybe that would be a thing.
It would make, it would make for like a mechanical surprise.
It would be, it would be pulling the rug out from under you, but I feel like narratively,
I don't know.
I mean, it would depend on what he did with it.
It would feel, I would feel like it was a little cheap.
My inclination would be to think it's kind of cheap to like, oh, well, well, let's end
the story with like two endings and you get to choose which one and oh, you go and you
do one and, and it does one ending and you do another and it does another ending or something
like that.
I had like this idea that like, once you get the final chapter and have seen everything,
all the choices that were presented to you before, you could now see what would happen
if you had made different ones or, you know, see made different ones.
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
But yeah, it's getting really heated.
It's, it's getting very heated.
I really enjoyed, I really am enjoying the presentation of these things.
It's just, I agree.
It's just a really nice story and it's told in a way that's unique and cool.
I like Z.
It's very, it's very homestuck in some ways and it's very not homestuck in others and
I think it works pretty well for the story it's trying to tell.
And I like the objectively bad visual presentation of it.
I think it's good and makes it better.
Yeah.
I am.
Oh, I was a bit annoyed.
Did you see that the Sarah Zed video about homestuck that dropped on 413?
I, I heard about it.
People linked it.
I didn't watch it though, because it was really long and I was like,
what are they going to say?
Great pain or something?
I didn't, I didn't want to watch it at first because I was like,
Oh, what does she know about homestuck?
I was there, man.
I was there.
But no, it turns out she is like an old homestuck fan.
So I was like, okay, this is actually fine.
I'm fine.
And then, but I was a little annoyed because she talked about like,
you know, the Kickstarter, she talked about Hiveswap,
she talked about Homestuck 2.
She didn't even mention Psycholonials, which I mean,
I'm a little disappointed because I like Psycholonials and I would like to hear it mentioned,
but also because like, isn't that sort of relevant to like the state?
Because like, Homestuck 2 basically did a thing like,
like they're canceling their Patreon.
And it seems to be in a, in like a pretty like,
who knows what's going to happen with it.
So you would think the fact that like, oh,
Hussie then went and made this other unrelated thing.
I don't know, it just seems important and I don't know why it didn't get mentioned.
I was like, hmm, weird.
So that was unfortunate.
But other than that, it was like a pretty good,
it was a pretty good like rundown of like,
most of the video is actually devoted to like,
post Homestuck bullshit that happened,
like HiveSwap and the Kickstarter and stuff.
Maybe the first like quarter of it is talking about like,
the experience of like, what was going on when the comic was actually running,
but like, it's good, it's good.
Yeah.
Homestuck is how I feel during the pandemic.
You guys talked over each other.
Sorry about that.
No, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I just made a really stupid joke.
Something about the pandemic.
Hey, it's too soon.
You can't joke about that.
Just like 9-11.
It's too soon.
Yes.
And it always will be.
I was saying the Hussie's Instagram,
he's posted a new very unusual set of images.
Really?
Okay.
He's got like, he's got coloured hair and extremely pixelated faces on clothing
and he's got a basketball.
And it's, you know, it's so strange.
But you know, this is, this is, this is the whole thing.
This is the, the e-boy Hussie Instagram account,
which Psycholonials is absolutely like real and Hussie is doing it.
So obviously you saw that Hussie is in Psycholonials, right?
Yes, I saw him.
Did you?
He, he, he jumps in front of the, the, the horse.
Oh God.
What's the horses?
Dazed Hasselhoof.
Yes.
Hasselhoof.
Someone pointed out to me that like, I guess at some point you see,
like some of his makeup is scraped off and he is yellow.
Meaning that he.
I think that was the whole time.
His little character avatar, whenever it first showed up,
you could see that it had like the Hussie skin tone underneath.
This, this is, this is fascinating.
This is horrifying.
I mean, this, this suggests that this is canonically the same Hussie
that appeared in Homestuck.
To me, that's what that says.
This Hussie has got some hustle.
He sure does.
So the drip is unbelievable.
It's fucking sopping.
I, I like the clown.
I like the clown sonar better.
I don't know about this one.
I, in theory, I like the.
I'm just looking at his Instagram in general.
If you scroll down a bit, there's his clown sonar.
And then before that was some other cool, cool things.
This, this new outfit, I don't know.
It's a little upsetting, honestly.
It's that clown sonar.
But Sheezy's not here.
He, Sheezy, Sheezy is a big Psycholonials fan.
I turned, I turned Sheezy onto it and he loves it as, as he should.
I kept thinking about making my clown sonar, but I never did.
It's, I mean, yeah, it's, you read this and it's,
it's just the natural reaction.
It's like, I got to make a fucking, I got to make a jubilee.
I got to be a jubilee.
I got to make a clown sonar.
The, yeah, I don't know.
I'm just, I'm just pretty mystified and horrified to think that, I mean,
that means, that means that Psycholonials and Homestuck take place in the same
universe. That's the only thing that it can mean.
Well, I mean, it could, it could also mean that this universe right here,
that Zeezyn is one created in Homestuck as in like it creates universes.
And then Hussey just.
Sure.
Yeah, I guess, I guess the world of Homestuck is one in which that is one in
which there are infinite worlds, which are basically similar to our own or a
lot of them are.
So yeah, this could easily just be one of those.
I don't really take it as like a, oh, a cannon thing.
It was just like Hussey's putting himself in stuff.
But it is, but it is cannon, but that's what it means.
But it can, but it also makes no difference to anything.
So yeah, it does.
Okay.
I mean, yes, it doesn't make a difference to anything, but it never,
nevertheless, it's cannon.
It's fucking cannon.
That means everything.
The reason I don't really think of, the reason I don't really like to think of it
as like, oh, this means Homestuck.
Like, because Homestuck operates on different loads of physics that like
reality like can't have capture logs, whatever they were called.
Well, oh yeah.
No, I guess you're right.
So, so, so in, in Psycholonials, the whole is the fucking dreams real?
Is there actually like a clown god speaking to this character that's left up in the air?
Is it her going insane?
If like Homestuck rules apply, it could be real and it's more likely to be real.
And I don't, I think that the, the unsureness of the reader is important.
I, I agree.
I mean, I, I agree that if you think like, oh, this is in the same universe as Homestuck.
Therefore, I should be like thinking about the events through like a Homestuck lens.
Like what, what, what does the cannon of Homestuck say is possible in this world?
Then yeah, I agree.
You've, you've, you've read too far into it for sure.
Yeah.
I think it's more likely that Hussie depicting himself is just um,
because he does exist in our reality and where COVID happened.
So this is like that version of him, the real version.
And then the version that appeared in Homestuck is just him drawing himself into the comic that he wrote.
I, I, I think, I don't, I think the fact, the fact that it's yellow when every other,
every other person in Psycholonials is white.
I mean, he has to be, he's got to be the same.
He, he, he's true though.
Just look at them.
They all, they all white though.
They're all white.
I mean, well, they got the clown makeup on.
So I guess you can't tell for all of them.
No, but every other person, but, but even without the clown makeup, they all still have white faces.
Do they?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I can't tell.
All the, all the police did, Percy did, Zee and Abby do.
No, I'm pretty sure.
Well, let me, let me, I can go look.
If there, if anyone has had a non-white face, I mean, then I guess I would be wrong.
And maybe Hussie would just be yellow.
Oh no.
Yeah.
It's just like, like ff, ff, ff, ff, ff, ff, white.
Yeah, they're all, they're all ff, ff, ff, ff, ff, ff.
But Hussie's yellow.
I don't know.
I feel like it says something.
Like, no, I don't think it says something.
I think it says Hussie is letting us know that yes.
It does.
But it was, it's obviously him.
He didn't have to be yellow for it to obviously be him.
Cause it's, cause it's the same for, it's the same clown sonar that appeared in the trailer
and it's the same one that Hussie dressed up as on Instagram.
It was already obviously him.
It didn't, it didn't need that.
But he deliberately was like, well, I'll include this detail and make him the only yellow human.
I don't think that makes a difference.
They're all white.
So is this like an alt-right thing?
No, no.
Hussie's, he's good.
He's a good Bernie bro.
He's a good Bernie down the establishment.
Yeah.
Based.
I really do agree with that.
I really do admire Hussie's joie de vivre though.
I hope when I'm Hussie's age, I'm looking like a total freak.
Yeah, that's a good way to be.
Yeah.
He's tall though.
Being tall means you can pull things, pull looks off that other people can.
It's a shame.
It's a real shame.
Since we were on the subject of clowns, I'd like to present something.
Please.
It'd be good if Cheesy were here to see this.
I'm sure he will.
Did you hear that Cheesy killed the Pizza Party podcast?
I heard something about the Pizza Party podcast, but no specifics.
You heard it here first.
He did it.
He was our man on the inside.
He brought the whole system down and on itself.
I'm proud of him.
That's pretty cool.
Clown-Vis Presley.
I found this weird YouTube channel by accident, or mere happenstance, about a guy that dresses
up as a clown version of Elvis Presley.
Naturally.
He has a couple of music videos that are actually surprisingly good.
He does like a weird stream.
I don't know what the deal is with this guy, but I was very fascinated when I found this.
This?
I mean, is there like, is there lore?
Oh, God.
I'm sure there is, but I haven't dived in all the way yet.
Just look at the thumbnail to this video and tell me what you think is happening.
I haven't seen that thumbnail yet.
It looks like two fish eating an eel in between them.
Yeah, maybe something like that.
I thought it was two frogs shitting out their mouth into each other's mouth was where my
mind went.
Yeah, that's kind of what it looks like.
But no, they could be pulling a lady in the tramp with an eel.
I hope it's that.
I mean, it's too clear and perfect a tube to be like a thing of liquid happening.
I can see why you would see that.
I don't know why.
Episode 149.
What?
Yeah, he does like weird streams where he just talks to the audience and I guess tells
jokes or something.
I see there's like an alien puppet.
There's like an alien puppet in some of these, you know, just because.
It's very, very strange.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
This is a, this is a find.
This is a, this is a, I don't know.
I don't know what's going on.
I like it.
I was thinking we click a random one.
You should invite this guy.
I was thinking you should maybe invite this guy into PCP sometime.
I mean, I'm, I am interested in what he has to say.
What is he?
Okay.
You see he's talking about conspiracy theories.
Huh?
What?
I just clicked a random one.
He's talking about like this, this defies scientific understanding.
I don't, I don't know.
I didn't, I didn't listen for, for more context.
I don't know what his views are or anything.
I just know that he dresses up as a clown version of Elvis Presley for some reason.
He says clown this plays a new instrument, the marshmallow planted in soil from the
North Pole last week is revealed to be a full grown dancing snowman with basic skills.
That's the episode description.
Wow.
It sounds interesting to me.
Okay.
Scientology video?
Oh no.
It's got to be a joke.
I mean that, maybe that's Zinu, maybe the little puppet man with him is Zinu.
It looks like him.
I hope whoever this guy is, I hope he reaches a million subscribers someday.
He is only 5,000 for such, for such a, for such a winning, for such a winning concept.
Isn't it an undiscovered gem?
Oh, he's got a robot dog.
Oh, he's got a little robot dog.
This is very good.
This is a great character design.
It's fun.
You need to promote this guy.
This is what I wanted to see.
Clownvis covers insane clown posse, chicken hunting.
But I'm definitely going to check that out.
Perfect.
This reminds me of, well, it's not really the same, but okay.
Did you see that The Folding Ideas video about the Doug Walker Wall review that came out this week?
I saw a preview of that, but I haven't watched it.
I like that video.
I like that video a lot.
And the ending part when he talks about the, like, animated monsters,
Discount Gumshoe in my Discord showed me a little bit of, like, the videos that they come from, the Satellite City videos.
And that is a, I think that that is like a fascinating rabbit hole of, like, cringe.
The videos are very, like, the one I saw was, like, the guy who is on the phone in the Wall review.
It's him, like, yelling at another guy, like, pick my weeds, Slave.
Pick my weeds in my field.
Do it now.
I haven't killed you yet, so pick my weeds.
I have to pick the weeds.
And the 3D monsters are like, uh, hey, this guy's got to pick the weeds now.
I'm sure glad I don't have to pick the weeds.
And that's the video.
And that's the fucking video.
Wait, wait, that, of the person that made the original, that the ending cinematic 3D stuff, that's one of his videos?
Yes.
Yes, that's a video from Satellite City.
No, not from Clownvis.
Not Clownvis.
Um, and I don't know.
Like, I saw that video and knowing, because Dan mentions it in the Folding Ideas video, that, like, there's, like, pages and pages and pages of lore.
And I don't know, I just think it's really funny.
And apparently, okay, according to the channel description, the fena, this is the Satellite City guy, according to the fena channel description,
he has, like, the videos themselves are just, like, a side project.
They're, like, an experimental side project.
And his actual, his actual brain, ew, ew, it's face.
The actual project that he really wants to do, his masterpiece, is that he's writing a novel.
He's writing a novel called The August Few.
And the novel is the real story.
And these videos are just, I don't know, to gauge interest or something.
And I just hate them so much.
There's an animation test.
Hold on, I'll find it.
You know, these character designs, unlike Clownvis, these character designs are so overdone and terrible.
Like, any, I'm looking at one, and it's like, she's got it, I don't know what it's supposed to be.
I think it's a she, has, like, one wing on one side of her body, and then a missing leg, and then a weird eye.
Like, any moment where there could be symmetry, there is, like, make sure there's no symmetry.
Make sure there's as odd as, like, humanly possible.
Why do people do that? Why do people try to make every aspect of the character, like, different from every other aspect?
Just like, it's a hodgepodge.
Why? I don't get the appeal.
This video, this video that I just linked, this Lucy Lace Maker Oompa Pa animation test.
I hate it, because she's, like, dancing and singing, but she doesn't really move.
She just kind of, the rig just kind of stays in one place, and she just kind of, like, gyrates around and, like, swings her limbs around and makes faces at the camera.
And it's so awkward.
And the comments are all, like, the comments are all, like, oh my god, she thick, though.
Like, ooh, those hips.
And I'm, like, I hate, I fucking, I fucking hate what is going on here.
This reminds, and the fact that he is, the fact that his real project is that he's, ooh, he's writing like a, he's writing an epic fantasy novel about these characters.
It just reminds me of, do you remember that German guy Dave from the Brony days?
The furry guy, he did a bunch, he did a bunch, I've talked about him.
He did a bunch of, he did a bunch of art for Dr. Wolf, for no pay, of course, Lamau.
And then he, he was, his real project was that he was writing a novel.
He was a comic artist, but he was writing a novel.
And he would, he sent me, like, early drafts of the, of, like, chapters and was, like, here, what do you think about this?
And I was, like, I don't want to offend you.
I know English is not your native language, but the English in this chapter is very awkward to read.
And maybe you should be writing in German instead.
And he got, just got, like, really offended, like, no, there's no market, there's no market for fantasy literature in German, you idiot.
Like, that's, that's just, why don't you fucking give me good faith criticism instead of this bullshit?
It, it, it just reminds me of that.
And it makes me sick to my stomach.
The thought of a furry writing a novel just makes me ill.
I'm sorry. They just shouldn't do it. They just shouldn't do it.
I'm looking at.
Is that why you never criticize Trixie's music back when she was in the PCP?
I genuinely have no opinion about her music because I have no opinion about most music.
I know everybody, everybody says that the music is bad and everybody says that, like, her music has gotten worse.
I genuinely can't tell. I can't, I can't tell the difference.
So it's whatever.
I'm looking at this fucking video.
Imagine, but imagine what you were saying. These, these awkward, these awkward overdone character designs.
They're so hideous and overly detailed.
Imagine that person trying to write prose.
I haven't read any of it, but like, his priorities are like fucked.
His priorities are all wrong.
This person can't tell a good story. I'm convinced.
It's, it's like, um, like the character designs and this animation.
So much is happening and yet all of it is badly done.
Like, it's just a lot. It's just a lot of work.
It's just a lot.
And nothing is like, like, you know, it's like.
It's just a lot and I don't like any of it.
Like, like the people, people who like it, they're probably just like how it moves a lot and smoothly and doesn't stop moving.
And they just are amused by the motion because it's, it's just badly, it doesn't, it doesn't convey weight.
It doesn't, it's just not good animation.
The character designs are like overly like, like detailed with so many things,
but they're all like clashing, like extraneous details.
Whereas the focus supposed to be like all that sort of stuff.
Yeah, they do a lot of work. They don't work smart.
That's what the problem is.
I think that they, I think that the people that like this, they like what it looks like and they like that it moves a lot.
And that's like the extent of it.
It's not even like about like how it moves.
It's just that like, this is like a very, this is a very complicated.
This is a very detailed rendering of a creature with a certain aesthetic.
And I like the aesthetic and I like that it is moving around a lot and making faces at me.
And that makes me clap.
It's really a unsightly character design.
I mean, this one is, this one is pretty is ugly, I guess on purpose because it looks like a scary clown.
But then there's like the other ones are like dragons with like too many eyes and like and stuff.
And there's the one with the tits.
There's like the one with like the leathery neck and the tits.
That's and horns, I guess.
And I don't know.
I said this before, but it's just to reiterate, looking at these videos, I can see what this person's priorities are and they're bad.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
All right, this is funny.
I just saw that this is like behind the scenes of like the wall.
I always wondered how they made the iconic trial scene from Doug Walker's The Wall.
But that's not the funny part.
This is the funny part.
They put the footage of Doug in the green screen footage in the screens.
So I think you could get that.
He's pretty funny.
You could use his Doug Walker green screen footage if you wanted.
I just think, like anyway, my point in talking about this is just that this is exactly the kind of like,
this is exactly the kind of like lower train wreck that I think would be fascinating.
And I kind of would like a, I would like to hear like a deep dive, like discount gum.
She was talking about doing a lecture on it, actually.
And I thought that was like, this is this is perfect lecture material.
Like just don't, I don't want to watch this.
Just tell me like what's up with this and make me laugh.
As you explain it to me.
This, this is the kind of thing that is good for that.
So yeah, I want to lecture on clown vis Presley.
Yeah, that too.
Clown vis Presley is a is an enigma.
I wonder if he's read Cyclonials.
I wonder if he's a communist based.
You never know.
Oh, or almost two hours. Do you think maybe we should go to voicemails?
Yeah, I think so.
Two hours seems pretty good.
Okay, let's try.
I will try and you know, the voicemails were probably taken hour or more.
I will try to I will try to speed through them.
Okay, the first voicemail.
Oh God, first voicemail is called Grumple Stiltskin.
Here we go. Three, two, one, go.
Yeah, what's the point of it all anyway.
Great question. Thanks for the voicemail.
Next voicemail is called.
Yes, is called.
Unironic gang, gang weed guy.
I assume it's meant to say gang weed guy.
Everything if there's it's a long title.
Fuck it. Three, two, one, go.
Just like you said, $200 for red cotton.
I told you, I'm a man of my word.
So, where's the Virginia?
Jokerman, what did you do with all your money?
You see, I'm a guy of simple tastes.
I enjoy t-shirts, posters, streams, and the lectures.
You know the thing that they have in common?
They're part of Radcon.
You said you were a man of your word.
Oh, I am. I'm only burning my half.
All you care about is whether or not it was promised.
This show deserves a better class of content creator.
I'm gonna give it to them.
Tell your fans they work for me now.
This is my Radcon.
You were a freak.
Freak.
Well, why don't we cut you up into little pieces and feed you to the hellhounds?
And then we'll see how hungry a loyal jigger really is.
It's not about the lecture.
It's about sending a message.
Everything strands!
Okay.
You know, Radcon is a pretty good title.
It was kind of funny up until they sort of showed their handle at the end there.
Radcon is a good title because some people got conned out of Rand, if you think about it.
I don't really know what the message was, so I'm not gonna think about it anymore.
Next one is called The Monopoly Man.
Oh, wait. Next one's called The Monopoly Man, but last week...
Never mind. There was a voicemail I didn't understand last week.
And you know what? That's good.
It's good. I don't want to understand. Never mind.
Next one is called...
Someone tried to tell me, like, Ben, obviously it was meant to say this, and I was like, uh, okay, I guess.
Doesn't matter.
Next one is called The Monopoly Man, 3, 2, 1, go.
Ho, ho, ho, ho! This is The Monopoly Man, the president of the League of Natefuckers.
I'm here to announce that I have a plan for the well-being of Nate and all the Natefuckers.
I will let everyone fuck Nate from 9 to 5, one hour each, for 200 Dodgecoin.
This is my decision. Ho, ho, ho, ho!
200 Dodgecoin, as The Monopoly Man says, is like, that's like, um...
That's like, 60 dollars.
That's like, some money. Okay, next one is called...
Not as much as 200 actual dollars.
Next one is called Hi Ben, 3, 2, 1, go.
Hey, y'all, I just wanted to come in and say that this whole situation is fucking hilarious.
Thanks.
I haven't heard... I'm a little bit off.
I always listen to these on Mondays, so you guys have already recorded last week's episodes.
So maybe there was some Trixie Defender who came online last time.
A little bit.
Oh, no. Ben was being... Trixie did nothing wrong.
But like, let's be fucking honest.
Ben was right.
Everyone agrees that Ben was right, and this is fucking hilarious,
because anyone who pays attention to anything could have seen this coming a mile away,
when they uprooted his whole goddamn life to do something with Trixie,
and Trixie is never committed to anything in her fucking life.
Yes.
And it's very funny.
It's very funny, it's very sad, and it's just so goddamn funny.
All right, see you.
This guy's absolutely got the right attitude.
Hi Ben is a... Hi Ben for Voice Grail? Hi Ben for Voice Grail?
I don't know.
Your own personal collection, maybe.
Okay.
I was hoping to hear something from Doid Geysers.
Doid Geysers said that he is bowing out at the top.
Doid Geysers says that last week was his finale.
Yeah.
It's unfortunate.
It was a good way to end.
It was a good bit.
I think it had run its course though, and he went out on the high note with the song,
so let's hope he doesn't fuck that up with another voicemail.
Next one is called Fuck PCP Callers Addendum 321 Go.
Just listen to another cringus bingus voicemail.
Never mind.
I take it all back.
Callers are great.
Thank you.
True.
That's right.
It's all about perspective.
Next one is called Challenge 321 Go.
Name every former member of the PCP in the order in which they left the podcast.
What about that jazz guy?
People have left.
Majors definitely left.
Davoos definitely left.
When?
I can't remember.
Okay.
There was a time when they said, oh, by the way, I'm not coming back.
I don't want to come back.
Maj never even made a specific, like, I am leaving the PCP.
She never even did that.
Davoos did.
I would say.
Maj never wanted to make a thing of it, which was her reasoning, but I'm pretty sure she
does not want to come back.
There's no intention of her coming back.
She has said that here and there.
I guess it is.
Wait, has anyone else?
Who else has left?
I think maybe Jeff Mumkey, Davoo, Maj, who else?
Trixie, obviously, is the latest one.
Nate has not technically left.
Jesse has not technically left.
They can both appear at any time whenever they feel like it.
I think Jesse is pretty much officially.
I would say, no, I would say Jesse is officially.
Well, I mean, he came to red for anything.
Like if Davoo and Maj wanted to come back, that'd be fine.
Like there's no like contract here.
It's just how you defined, like, left.
I guess if Jesse hasn't been on the show for a very long time and it doesn't seem like
he wants to be on, then he's fine.
I would say that Jesse has left the show to basically the same extent that Maj has,
which is to say pretty much 100%.
Yeah.
He's basically left the internet except for his Patreon, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
I would say that he's basically left the internet except for his Patreon, I think.
And then he's basically left the internet except for his Patreon, I think.
100% he's basically left the internet except for his patron.
I think. Yeah.
Got to keep got to keep that shit exclusive.
Oh, and don't forget Munchie.
I think did you mention Munchie? Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Munchie.
He also has not like made a any like he's like mage.
He has basically said that he won't be back,
but he never made like an I'm leaving statement.
So he made an I'm leaving statement for for like the internet,
which I think just applies to everything.
Yeah. Okay.
My best guess for order would be Jeff,
monkey, DeVoo, Jesse, mage, Munchie, Trixie.
I think I think something like that.
Okay. Who's going to be next?
Who's who's leaving next?
My vote is I think it's going to be it's going to be me.
It's going to be me getting banned when Trixie comes back when it's when it's when Trixie,
Trixie, it's when Yig Studio fails and Trixie attempts to do like a redemption arc.
And everyone and every fucking sucker and mark immediately falls for it.
And then she and then I'm the bad guy because everyone wants to forgive her.
And then I say no, she can't come back.
And then there's a forced vote and everybody votes me out.
So Trixie comes back there.
I'm pretending to have a monkey pulled on you.
But worse.
That's pretty good fan fiction.
That's what's it's true.
It's true.
It's I've seen the future.
The next voicemail is called I don't like this.
It's called Noiter is bad.
And I'll upload it right there.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, the body of Isaac is a much better game than Noiter because it is top down and not as side
scroll because the top is always more powerful than the down and the side scroller means that
you are not equal footing with the game.
So you are actually more in control in Isaac, which makes it obviously objectively the better
game also.
It is the better game because it has items that are actually good and not just items that are
just bad like Noiter does.
Just bad.
Ignore all the items in Isaac that are bad, which you will always get on every floor because
that is that's just good game design for making it hard.
Noiter has bombs.
But at Noiter, when you get a shitty one, that is not a game design because
the game is bad.
You know, he wasn't getting me until he said that Isaac was bad and Noiter was
no, wait, he said Isaac was good and Noiter was bad.
When he said it in such clear terms, I agreed instantly.
Right.
I mean, that was, you said he wasn't getting you until he said that, but that was literally
like the opening statement of the voicemail.
No, no, no.
When he said the items is the, what I meant to say is that the whole thing with the top
down and side scrolling is dumb and stupid.
Just say it sucks.
That I agree that.
Yeah.
No, side scrolling is better.
Side scrolling is better than top down for sure.
We can all agree on that.
Yeah, I prefer side scrolling.
I just like doing things from the side.
Noida has, Noida's items are not very good, but Noida's has perks.
And I guess, you know what, Isaac's items are better than Noida's perks.
I'll give it that.
I'll give it that, but no more.
Okay.
Next one is called Penisus.
Penisus, it is there.
Upload.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ah, can't dance, ah, can't talk.
The only thing about me has been since big call.
Yeah.
Very good.
Thank you for the voicemail.
Next one is called Chad McChad.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, it's Chad McChad here.
And I just want to say, good coin.
More like shit coin.
Yeah.
That was all.
Drop 10% in 10 minutes, baby.
It's going through the floor.
Maybe it'll be back to 60,000 by next week.
Wait, it's kind of just hanging out.
Maybe my thing was like behind when you were talking about it before,
because it hadn't gone down as far and now it has.
I'm looking at it and it's been pretty stable since like an hour or two after
the big dip.
It's just kind of hanging out around 56.
Big dip.
Big di-ah.
Oh, my thing on TV has been Saints big cock.
That's going, Boy Scrail?
Boy Scrail?
No, no.
Personal collection.
Personal collection of Ben St.
All right.
Personal collection.
Who's personal collection?
My personal collection, which I never look at.
Next one is called What Is Happening?
3, 2, 1, go.
Okay, you're going to get me up to speed here.
Just listen to the episodes.
Okay, to be honest, I haven't watched a fucking episode of BZP in like two years.
See, this is the problem.
This is the problem.
Pretty much.
Are you even going to watch this one?
You fuck.
So I have no idea what's going on here with any of these things.
Jesus.
And I just noticed that Trixie is no longer here.
And then I saw that Nate's no longer here.
And I'm like, nice.
Like Ben and I like Ben and Gabe.
Damn, damn, damn.
So that's cool.
Hello, Tom.
Yeah.
Could you like compress the last two years into...
Dog, we've been doing that.
Into like a one thing.
So I can understand what is going on with this podcast at this point.
Okay.
Yeah, I will, I will.
Post.
He's obviously not going to listen to this episode.
So why bother?
Here's my soundbite version.
Post Redcon 4, Nate just basically falls off ever showing up.
Trixie also does that.
And, and that's, and that's it.
That's, that's like it.
Davoo was already gone.
They both just stopped falling off.
Trixie falls in with these Yeg people.
I hate them and I tell her so and she has a tantrum about it and is like,
I won't be on the PCP anymore because Ben doesn't like my friends.
And that's it.
That's what happened.
Actually, I just got a pretty good idea.
Yeah.
What if, wait, hear me out.
What if Riley replaced Trixie on the PCP?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, now we're talking.
Ooh, now we're talking.
Well, Riley on the PCP would be kind of funny, actually.
You could hash it out.
You could yell at each other.
Yeah, exactly.
No, I wouldn't, I don't want to do that.
It's, it's not cool.
It's just not cool, man.
It's like homework.
It's just not cool and I don't want to do it.
No, no.
They're dead to me.
No more.
Well, it was not an idea.
We're about a bird stork.
I don't know who these fucking people are.
Yes, I do.
I wish I didn't.
I'm going to pretend, I'm going to pretend that I don't know who these people are
because I would be a happier person if I didn't, though.
Who?
What?
What are you talking about?
Okay.
Next one is called, do you have anything more to add on
getting this idiot who doesn't watch the podcast up to speed?
No, that was pretty succinct.
It's more than he deserves, honestly.
Oh, this one is called obligatory Ben dick sucking bones.
Three, two.
Voice grail?
No.
Am I right?
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I've been a fan of yours for a long time,
but somehow I miss your preservation of the It's All So Ugly
original page, and I just stumbled upon it on stcomics.com.
And holy shit, even at the beginning, you were fucking funny.
That's not true.
This power of science comic is fucking hilarious.
Really?
Sophisticated entertainment.
And then you scroll down and you have this brilliant splash page of you begging for money.
I love it.
It's so funny.
I like that.
Why don't you do this more often, dude?
Holy shit.
Wow.
Thank you.
I hate all those old It's All So Ugly.
That one is like, I don't hate that one that much.
I think it's kind of dumb.
Some of the old It's All So Ugly comics are like really bad and embarrassing,
and I hate them, but they're there for posterity's sake.
The website, yeah, the website, if you've never seen it,
it's designed so that like the comic is at the top of the page.
And if you scroll down, you can see that it is me under the page holding it up
as I'm like kneeling on the ground holding it up to show it to you.
And I'm begging for money.
I thought it was a pretty funny design.
Glad you appreciated it.
I've seen your saintcomics.com website.
If you go to saintcomics.com, one of the like on the dropdown menu,
one of them is, I think it's labeled IASU.
It's also ugly.
This is short for that.
And it'll bring you to an archived version of the old website.
I should read your comics one day.
I mean, some of them are kind of good, maybe, if you're into that sort of thing.
Yeah, no, you absolutely should.
That goes for you, that goes for you too, listener.
Well, no one has no one has given no one has said anything, let alone anything positive
about it's also ugly, the brand in ages.
So I made my day.
Thank you.
Next voice.
Voice growl, right?
Voice growl.
Per personal collection.
I know what you're going to say.
It's your personal collection.
Next one is called based three, two, one, go.
LeMau.
Just.
No, it's fucking stupid.
You know, people say she's a pedophile, but I don't know, because I don't know if she
should be considered able to consent either.
So I think maybe her and a child should be considered on like similar footing intellectually.
LeMau.
Well, I did say that.
When did you say that?
Or was that on a PCP?
I didn't remember hearing that.
It was on a PCP.
It was a while ago.
I think it was like right after the breakup announcement or.
Was that talked about?
I think it was.
What?
I don't, I guess I just can't remember it being talked about on the show.
Yeah, we talked about it a little bit.
It was, yeah, it was after, I mean, it was after it was like a public.
Maybe it was, I think it was before the Ralph Braykin video.
Well, it would have been then before then, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't remember.
It was a while ago, but I thought it was pretty funny.
So I'm glad this guy thought so too.
Yeah, I think it was pretty good.
I really hate her.
I probably shouldn't.
Honestly, I probably should just like pity her and like not consider her like an entity with like
moral, what's the word, agency, like on a level that deserves hate, but I can't help myself.
She followed me on Twitter recently because I was, because I was making fun of Trixie.
And I said, oh, yuck.
Oh, gross.
Christ.
What do I do?
Who followed you on Twitter?
You mean Trixie?
No, May.
May did.
Oh.
You know who that is?
Do you know who that is?
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know.
I might, might soft, might soft block that.
Just might, might just wait, might just wait for a minute until she forgets that she did that.
And then just soft block that and just don't want, don't want those eyes on me.
Thank you very much.
Um, next voicemail is called Hamshank.
And here it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, fuckers.
It's, it's me.
I'm Hamshank.
Damn.
I'm like an evil Ben St. Guy.
What I'm like, I'm like a, I'm like a Ham guy, like a pig guy.
Isn't that just the regular one?
That's the regular Ben St. Guy.
You know, I'm gonna, I'm gonna kill Ben St.
Because I hate him.
I thought you were my guy.
That's my character.
And I'm gonna turn, I'm gonna turn him into fucking pork steaks.
I'm gonna fry him up on my grill.
I'm not, I'm not pork.
And also I wanna fuck Nate.
This guy is so on point.
He's got so much such strong theming.
Or whatever.
That's also my bit is that I wanna fuck Nate.
Also I'm one of those, I'm one of those Nate.
You're in good company friends.
That's me.
I'm Ham, I'm Hamshank.
Voice grill?
Hamshank.
That's a pretty good fit.
That's a respectable hustle with that bit.
Hey, thanks.
Nice to meet you, Hamshank.
I can't, I can't wait for the Hamshank arc to begin.
The saga.
That was, was extraordinary.
Okay.
Next one, I posted it.
It is called ice cream fiend, three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, I just wanted to know how you eat your ice cream.
Do you eat it right out of the box?
Do you, uh, do you microwave it first?
Do you pour milk in it?
Microwave it?
Let me know.
Pour milk in it?
Who the fuck eats it out of the box?
Do you mean just with a spoon?
Or do you mean you shove your face in there?
I would say, yeah.
Well, I mean, back when I used to eat ice cream normally,
I would just take a spoon to the tub,
eat a few bites out of the tub,
put it back in the freezer.
Now, the only ice cream I get is keto ice cream from Aldi,
and the way that I eat it,
because it's very hard when it's out of the freezer,
so I microwave it for about 30 seconds to soften it up,
then I scoop out exactly half of one tub,
and I put it in a bowl, and then I eat it out of the bowl.
Or if I'm feeling saucy, I take out half of the tub,
and I put it into a mason jar full of coffee and almond milk,
and then I, and then I stir it around in there,
and I make a, and I make a whatever the fuck it's called
when you put ice cream in coffee.
So those are the two ways that I consume my ice cream.
Thank you for asking and have a blessed day.
I just eat a scoops in a bowl,
and I sometimes put something crunchy in there,
like a Rice Krispy or like a chocolate flake or something,
something to give it a crunchlets.
Oh, wait, wait.
You like pour some Rice Krispies into your ice cream?
Not Rice Krispies, I'm trying to think of like,
there's things I've put in ice cream that were like, based.
Oh, no, like granola?
Like granola!
brownie bits it was brownie crumbs if there's like cake crumbs or brownie
crumbs from like a cake but then I put those in there do you do you do you
frequently just have like cake and or brownie crumbs like stashed no we're
not frequently not stashed I mean like if there's like a somebody's got a
birthday and there's a cake we put like the cake out on a plate and put like a
bowl over it and yeah and people can just take a slice when they feel like it
sure and similar with brownies like some sometimes my brother made brownies
just on a whim and then we would have brownies around and we could just have
them and I like putting ice cream on brownies so you would scoop yourself some
ice cream and they would go over to this like half-eaten tray of brownies and
just I don't know like crumble it with your hands like grab some with your
hands and just like crumbled up I would take a whole brownie it's not just the
crumbs I would take it's only a few times I put a brownie I just eat ice cream
so whatever okay putting putting a brownie on it it mean if you've got a
brownie sure that makes that makes perfect sense well I just I eat it out
of a cup and I shelled out you know just have an ice cool time I'm so I school
wait I want to go back I want to go back so you do not you're saying you do not
pour rice Krispies on your ice cream no but saying it makes me think maybe that
could work maybe I mean that's what you said maybe like you said you honey
and not Cheerios or something some cereal okay do you give it a crunch do
you actually do that though or is this just this is all hypothetical it's
hypothetical the rice Krispies it's funny it's a funny idea it's if I saw you
someone do that I would be like what the fuck are you doing hey it's ice cream
and cream is just milk that's different I you know I get I say that but at the
same I'm imagining it I'm like I guess it wouldn't be too bad I guess it'd be
alright don't you guys eat beans on toast I'm a beans on toast defender yeah I
think that's nice it's a nice little like a light tea time sort of thing yeah
yeah no it's alright it's alright it's a savory you know it's filling you know
it's a high in high in protein it's a healthy meal
Americans could learn anything or two oh wait weird you think it's do you not
like beans I think beans are cool I just don't know if I will put them on
toast they're cool they're fine I find on toast you know I get soft you spread
with a knife I put I put ice cream not on toast but on bread on like white
bread like crusty roll loaf stuff wait no it works no it's some it's some it
works that's I've never done that ice cream sandwich but literally this this
this voicemailer just asked us how do you eat your ice cream and you're like
oh you know I just eat it and then only as an afterthought you're like I do put
it on on bread I did that once or twice you're insane you're out of your
you're out of your mind because I was like you know what I need to I need to
innovate on this ice cream eating stuff because eating it with a spoon why who
cares you don't I'm putting it in some sliced bread but it was like nice like
tasty bread I don't think it would work on whole meal or anything it's sort of
the sweetness of like the the you know the processed loaf and you put the ice
cream in there and it's somehow it's good it's like chocolate spread like
Nutella you put that on a sandwich that works it's the same thing except it's
cold you know it's roll I don't know if I know that I mean I wouldn't put I
wouldn't put no no no I would I wouldn't do it but it's not because I think it
would taste bad I wouldn't do it because to eat a sandwich you have to bite it
with your teeth so you would have to bite the ice cream with your teeth and
that would hurt my teeth well you wouldn't put like so much ice cream it's
like the ratio of bread to ice cream is that there's enough bread to like soften
the blow of the cold so it's sort of like you've chomp in you chomp into it
and it's like right on the bottom and it's sort of like so sort of insulates
only as much so only as much ice cream as like you would put like peanut butter
on a peanut butter sandwich yeah maybe a little bit more but yeah something like
that it wasn't like seven scoops squished into I just I don't see I don't see what
the bread adds I don't see what the bread adds I would like right so I just eat
bread I like bread but not in this not what I'm in an ice cream mood I don't
know I'm challenging your perceptions of reality and you can't yeah and I'm yeah
I can't handle it stop challenging me stop fighting me on this maybe put some
pastrami in there and some cheese and have an ice cream cheese that sounds
really good without the ice cream without the ice cream that sounds great
no but bread is neutral those other things are like savory food that's why
it's like it's not depends on which bread you're talking about but I guess so
but like sometimes you get a white bread that's like kind of sweet or kind of you
know like not salty and it's just sort of delicious scrumptious you would say
putting ice cream on it turns it into a dessert thing rather than a I think a
lunch thing I think we're just I think we're just gonna have to agree to
disagree on this one I don't I don't think we're gonna see what about putting
I'm gonna leave the podcast I'm gonna leave the podcast I'm gonna leave the
podcast over this you just can't I just can't I just can't be party to this
anymore you're gonna make a website called is ice cream in a sandwich good is
the ice cream on a sandwich I that's a good one I okay we got to move on we
don't have much time we got to keep it under three hours the next the next one
is called sincerity bro time three two one go you know it does kind of suck to
see this podcast with such like a rich history and background rich like ice
cream a lot of lore behind it like pastrami fall to you know bullshit
fucking Kiwi Farms drama but that's what things have settled a little bit now
that you know there's been some finality to some long-standing issues and you
guys are doing okay and you have fun doing the show because I know yeah it's
fun it is you shouldn't fucking I mean you know I don't know how many fucking
like I don't know how many of those guys there are but it's just that one guy
whose name I s s s ch w videos he's just been doing that for like a year and
God bless him and hopefully there's good things yeah feature thanks for doing a
show thank you I mean I mean I thank you I appreciate it I disagree with the whole
like I don't see what is like watching us fall to Kiwi Farms drama like not
really it didn't have anything to do for I'm first of all I don't consider
Trixie leaving to be the fall I've said this before like it's just we just have
less members which like I don't know if you like those members yeah maybe it's
kind of a bummer that like Trixie was the one with the most subscribers they
associate that with it's a little leading the show and she wasn't on that
much and I especially recently recently recently but yeah recently I hate to
say it happened way before that I hate to say it it's a little unkind to the
viewers but like it's a bit when when people say like oh Trixie left shows
over it's a little bit of the like old oh the procrastinators podcast is Digi
Bro's anime podcast energy it's a little bit like that and it's like I don't I
don't know about that I just don't know about that but this I don't want to say
that this guy is not like that this guy is you're a nice guy glad you like the
podcast I'm still having fun yeah we're just gonna keep we're just gonna keep on
you know I mean it's it's so easy why wouldn't we it's such a surprise that so
many people have left it take it thank you thank you yes this is what I say
there's like there's so little there's so little involved in doing this there's
nothing you just show up for three hours on a Sunday and you and you just
fucking that's it I'm not having fun I'm just here for the paycheck that's
right that's right and we want and we aim to keep it that way you're not you're
actually not allowed to have fun when you're here you have to be working you
have to be picking up the slack for the rest of us but to move it along the next
voicemail is called what is it called it is called oh wait okay I had to skip
some here I just want to I got this this one guy left some voicemails and
apparently these voicemails were about being angry about not getting the
plebe and the weeb blu-rays a completely valid thing to be angry about in my
opinion but I guess but I guess this guy is in he's a Jesse patron and I guess
and I guess bring after bringing the issue up in that the Jesse patreon
server this guy was convinced through some by someone to withdraw that
statement and say no no I don't want you to play my voicemails where I'm mad I
know it's okay no no I'm not mad no it's fine it's really don't let them know
that I'm mad that I didn't get the thing I paid for so I just thought that was
funny but he wanted me not to play them so I won't play them Lamal you screened
this particular voicemail I didn't know I didn't listen to them but he just said
please don't play them and I was like fine next one so the next one is called
farms times three two one go is it not working do you guys hear I don't hear
anything I think you fucked up I think you fucked up oh well wait three more
seconds damn guy really fucked up farms times you beefed it next that one
should get voice grow voice grow voice grow no next voicemail is called
mom key three two one go it's me your mom you drill I love I would just like to
say that told you so what does that mean also I cheated on sheep it's true it's
true this is when you did a minute okay I guess this I guess this is a joke but
this reminds me some some people say and I don't know about this so I've seen some
people respond to the Trixie thing along with the doomsaing of oh no the
podcast isn't is ruined the podcast is over PCP is finally fallen to the sands
of time I've seen a few people say like Jesse knew this would happen Jesse called
it and I saw that and I don't know what that means I genuinely don't know why
you would think that unless maybe the only thing I can think of is like did
Jesse predict either that Trixie would leave one day I don't remember him
saying that did Jesse predict that the podcast would end one day well guess
what everything ends eventually so even if the podcast were destroyed and in
shambles and over wouldn't really be that much of a prediction so you know good
job I guess I think I saw them link to I'm not sure if this is a quote from
Jesse but they link to something where supposedly Jesse said that everyone in
the PCP will eventually turn against each other and hate each other that's
just how life goes of course obviously that's going to happen eventually on a
long enough time frame I think that's what they're referencing um well that's
not even true I mean it's I mean it's it's literally only like me and Trixie I
mean I think that's like that's that's by far the biggest beef that there is when
it when it comes to like beef between members that's the biggest one that I
can think of everyone else is like not not interested in being on a podcast
which is a different thing than hating each other but there was also the
the monkey thing before right okay but yeah yeah I guess yeah I mean I guess
that's true I guess that's true yeah if you want to count that one sure but still
still I mean was there infighting did it cause refs yes I mean I guess I mean we
had arguments way back in the day so like I whatever sure it was sure none of us
were like agreeing with literally everything else everyone else said
there was strong personality so like yeah I think prediction of that like you I don't know
whatever I mean I guess it's a little true but yeah whatever okay infamous uh yellow
argument right gotta say uh the the explaining yig studios video looking real
yellow looking real yellow yeah um the next oh wait I just why did I just upload
the same one twice sorry don't listen to that one the next one is called burp the
next one is called a janez oh there it is okay three two one go have you ever
talked to someone that happened to sound like a famous youtuber because one of
the people that I'm on a podcast with it's called the crash content podcast one
of them sounds a lot like most critical just wondering if you ever had that
experience there was um oh fuck I was listening to I was listening back to last
episode and one of the voicemailers sounded exactly like some youtuber but I don't
remember which one ah fuck um cgp gray was it no cgp white cgp no no those are the
only youtubers I couldn't think of even one other one no um wait wait wait wait um I think
uh oh give me a second ellie is our cut this awkward pause out uh a few moments later
damn okay maybe I'll what and back okay yeah I can't find it and I can't remember
what the I can't remember which voicemail it was and I can't remember which youtuber was
someone my point is someone sounded like something so great um excellent point thank you
thank you very much uh gib you know anyone it sounds like someone uh I know someone who
sounds like ben saint oh it's Nate best me too yeah it's Nate best man lamal uh next voicemail is
called uh let me get it it's called dolos three two one go um hi I've been watching the pcp anime
lately and I just wanted to say uh it's the best girl hands down no questions that's it just you
wait that's all I have to say just wait did did tom get uh misgendered oh my god I guess I guess he
did you know what I guess he did damn don't worry it's fine when a cis person gets uh misgendered
right and murdered uh okay next voicemail is called peace brokering idea three two one go
ben could paint his own scrolls if we called him ben paint uh you don't you don't paint a scroll
you you do you in a little japanese uh ink uh no that's that's what I'm saying you use ink
you don't use paint you use ink you use an ink brush yeah no actually uh you'd have to call me
ben calligraphy why didn't you call yourself ben paint why didn't I call myself ben what
ben paint because that's better than ben saint no it's shut up no it's not it's that's no mine's
better you know what and I don't even paint I don't even paint no you are terrible because of it
stop you must stop this um I don't even because you're you're a painter I'm not I'm not you fuck
die um it's shut up all right no never never never never if it was it would be bink it would be
bink saint like bink sake the song what why would it why would why would it be that I don't
because because ben ink is dumb but bink saint is different and funny oh my oh my god okay next
voicemail ben sink next moving on next voicemail it's called the end draws near three two one go
oh
Christ is this a is this a kuno ichi ninja summer okay it was a more that or you
I care a little just not as much as I care about the scroll you
do not return on ninja scroll it's a nice scroll I'm loving it have a no choice
so we do they are nothing better
that right we form a ryan see
enemy of a nipot terrible
it's kawasaki summer
kiyoto ninja in the returning misty tea fuck you
fuck are you
oh and ninja scroll but until next time sayonara the things the things I do for scrolls man
just the things I put up with but it's all worth it at the end of the day I see those scrolls on my
wall right next to right next to my uh full metal alchemist wall scroll the three of them all lined
up in a row and I'm just like this is what it's all about Japanese scroll you've also got this
he I don't think he has a scroll I don't think ninja mr. T has a scroll I think he's just a
long man he's probably got a may have an america clan I'm afraid I have to side with a mr. T on this
one uh I I just I I apologize for nothing and I regret nothing that's that's that's your default
state that's absolutely I've been I've been saying that more and more often lately uh next one is
called uh truest blue pill um uh oh okay yeah there is uh my computer froze for a second truest
blue pill three two one go hi hello pc people um I don't care about the topic I don't care about
b I don't care about anything I just wanted my nintendo 3ds and now I understand my fucking
freedom is like I understand now all I wanted was taiko no tatsujin for the 3ds that's all I wanted
nintendo just could have given it to me I don't know what this person's talking about I would have paid
them like $50 for it I would have paid them anything I would have paid them any fucking
price even my own like tatsu tatsu no give it to me to even like give me the chance to purchase
taiko no tatsujin for the 3ds I fucking hate them so I'm not like my 3ds and now I understand
the fucking freedom is like I understand everything now I can play any game any game I could possibly
imagine I can play rpg maker I could play ds I could play game why would you play rpg maker
I can make fucking anything and I've been just a coward I've been a coward to my business
would have played fucking system didn't work all right fuck that fuck that I love stealing I love
hurting I love I love the communism I love leftism I love everything I love the world okay bye
oh is this person talking about like using like a car no tatsujin is the rhythm game
by nanko no day taiko no glycogen as a keto as a keto boy I have I am against glycogen so no thank
you are they talking about a flash cart I yeah I think they're talking about a flash card which
yeah honestly that is pretty definitely the best way to enjoy the 3ds or ds or whatever
actually yeah super super cool super good that's how I played uh that's how I played heart gold
that was the game that I like when I when I got brunswick in that game I was playing heart gold
on a flash card um next voicemail is called stealing is cool stealing is cool shoplifts
folks don't get caught that's that's my shops are too heavy to lift next voicemail is called
frost drive three two one go so on a recent episode Tom mentioned the story of how Godzilla was
created to be a representation of nuclear warfare yeah and I'm guessing the Godzilla creators wanted
the message to be that nukes are bad but they did the exact opposite because Godzilla is the coolest
monster ever just like hell nukes are the coolest thing ever which is why they just made a new
type of nuclear bomb that can travel so fast that countries can't even detect it and respond in time
nice I love meaning the president in the white house will be killed and it's all destroyed
before they even know when nuke is coming and so how do you combat that you just make your country
automatically fire nuclear bombs to the other country in every country bombs every other country
and if you haven't heard of this guys I recommend looking it up because it's interesting
yet scary as fuck because this could be what ends life on earth if climate change doesn't you know
I know about I know about mutually assured destruction it's all inspired by Godzilla so
no thanks Godzilla no we got it backwards you're right you're right I fucking Einstein saw Godzilla
and he thought hmm oh right though god's nuke to make that real in in like other movies Godzilla
is like the kind of I mean he's he's just kind of like a dumb force of nature but he still is
like kind of a good guy who fights against some like even worse monsters I think which I mean
I guess you could argue that nukes could like if if aliens invaded and like we fought them off with
nukes I guess you could say that like we use them for good against a greater evil so maybe it's not
a complete metaphor failure I don't know the idea that you know I googled like a really quick
nuclear bomb fast nuclear bomb I can't find anything yet what does it seems like
my nukes are pretty cool I don't know I'm sure I'm sure there is a new a fast nuke that's undetectable
it sounds exactly like what we would do next voicemail not to get hung up is called a message
from your gaping ass three two one go hi Ben so I'm just driving around my car after a long day of
work and it's got me thinking is Trixie retarded um that's all I wanted to ask let me know and uh
love you I think I don't know what that uh like for talking literal medical I don't think so
I know I wouldn't say literally stick somewhere on the spectrum she's she's not I don't what you
can't just you can't just say that what you can't just say that you can't just self-diagnose that
huh everybody knows because she said so a doctor didn't say oh yeah okay whatever she's not well
whatever not neurotypical I mean what do you want she who says she's not neurotypical who said who's
to say I don't know because she does she act weird and dumb I mean so do I sometimes I mean not as
much obviously the title of this voicemail I'm surprised it wasn't just a giant fort
this this a message from your gaping ass has left voicemails before I I nominate him for voice
grail actually I'm a little bit disappointed this wasn't a no worthy one no no unlike all those
other ones that I nominated this episode that were absolutely grail worthy um I think she is
a fundamentally unintelligent person who is furthermore at the moment deeply entrenched
in delusional thoughts that are being enforced by others by her own choosing because she likes
those people because they reinforce her her thinking sure Ben do you think me saying that she
might be autistic um or like probably is is like uh uh what's the word absolving her of bad thing she
does no I don't I don't think no I don't I don't think that no I know I didn't I see why you would
think that I was assuming that that's not what I meant but I don't think it's it's no my problem
is a different thing which is like sure whatever yeah first of all we're all on the spectrum
but you can't just be like oh I'm autistic because I think I am like this is a you you can't you
can't just self-diagnose yourself you just you just can't do that um uh next voicemail what you do
with the diagnosis that you make but sure no it that you can't you can't you just you don't do it if
if you all right I know like literal technical like you can't say for sure until a doctor
does a test or whatever I mean but I mean like practically you can you can see when somebody
is a little neurodivergent in the way they approach things and I know me better than I know other people
I don't wait I mean I you don't I mean you seem pretty neurotypical I don't know I think I honestly
Trixie seems pretty neurotypical too they don't look they can judge their if if if if they can just
like kind of look at themselves and be like hmm I think I kind of act autistic then I can look
at them and be like hmm I think you kind of don't you where's the where's the fair enough I just I
don't know I don't I don't see a problem with it I just feel it's more accurate but what if um
if they like Sonic the Hedgehog then obviously they're autistic they don't nobody nobody likes
Sonic the Hedgehog um it's not no you're right no you're right I know you're right um I just okay
when you go to the doctor it's it's not like they take a brain scan and they look at your corpus
colosum and you're like ah the structure here is such like a test to determine like based on the way
you respond to the the questions when you go to the doctor yes yes yes and when you go to the doctor
they show you a picture of Sonic and they ask you do you like this then they show you with his shoes
off and they say do you still like it they show you they show you a train and then you're off the
deep end yeah they show you a train and then footless Sonic no okay I understand that qualitatively
all that a that a doctor does is basically just ask you like how do you feel what is your thought
process like how do you behave what things do you think and and what are you like and it's and it's
it's subjective in the same way that just like taking a fucking quiz online is but nevertheless
I like I would I would only trust an expert I would only trust an expert to make that judgment
I would never I would never trust a layman I would never trust a layman to make that judgment
about themselves including someone talking about their own themselves or anyone else is is is inherently
like biased like it's it's compromise yeah it totally is yeah it totally is totally the
this argument is called appeal to authority well it's a no appeal generally I feel like
there's there's nothing wrong with Ben's reasoning here when I don't think my reasoning is like out
of line either but you know it's just a difference it's a appeal to authority is only a fallacy
if there's not good reason yeah if it's not if a person's authority is not like directly relevant
to the question being asked um like sometimes doctors get things wrong you know yeah sometimes
they are more likely to be correct every every expert does something wrong at some point that
doesn't mean their expertise is therefore inherently bad because that would contradict the point of
expertise I I mean I I've said this before we're we're all on the spectrum I really think we are
all we are all to a certain degree autistic but like that doesn't really mean much no especially
not to this voicemail question who just basically just asking is Trixie dumb
um yeah well I guess you could say that we're all on the retardation spectrum to one degree or
another maybe I don't know that's a good point perhaps I don't know um okay I feel like we've
I feel like we've answered this one plenty um next voicemail is called uh
um wait next voicemail is called what I lost my place PCP protag three two one go hey so to
answer last week's question on who is the protagonist to the procrastinators it's really
more of an ensemble piece but I'd say who the main character is depends on what era the show
you're watching so I would say the original main character was Digi back when they were called that
because they were the one that everybody kind of knew and got into the show from them so they'd see
it through his eyes and then I don't think that's a good argument they left and the show kind of
went over to Nate uh because they were the one because he was the one steering the ship for
the longest time and now it's Ben Ben is the main character now that Nate is gone and Trixie is the
antagonist uh sorry give your side character get a subplot uh the end of the PCP Tom will be the
main character because everyone else has long been dead and he's just waiting out the heat
death of the universe because Tom will never die Tom is completely stable call me back Tom is a
completely stable element like lead he will never decay he will never change at all maybe it's true
that like when you when you assume when you assume the leader the role of leader of the PCP you
become volatile and eventually you explode and you have to you have to leave the podcast eventually
I thought I was a protagonist you are a you are a um you're like uh what's the word
you're an exchange student from an anime you're like you're like Griff what's oh the Griffin
in Milo Pony who had like the two episodes about her gilda no gilda you're like gilda you are like
a side character who I haven't seen the shows I don't know you are a side character who by by popular
requests keeps getting brought back for increasingly irrelevant diversions that's true yeah by popular
request next voicemail is called uh I wanted to say quick about the oh sure this the the side
character thing uh it sounds like it's a dig and I mean from their perspective I guess it would be
but like I've never been much for the the leader I've always been like a quip sort of person
even way back in the beginning I was always the one who like made the punchline while everyone
else like filled the air it would be like so I side character fits yeah it's yeah I don't know
whether I need a subplot like what would I do like I just take over the show like I'd be the one
saying welcome to the progress days it doesn't doesn't mean anything I'm too chill I think it I
think a side that would be just like you should be going at uh uh welcome to show when I first came
on I think uh in 2018 I think I think a side plot would be like it's not that you're hosting the
show it's that just like you're on the show and it's not like the main focus but you like
occasionally like make reference to some like weird side story that you've got going on in the
background you're like oh yeah uh you know these uh uh this week uh it's kind of kind of a rough
week I'm a little stressed out these guys these guys in black suits and sunglasses keep knocking
on my keep knocking on my door every hour of every day um just you know it's it's hard to sleep but
like you know I'm dealing with it you know and then like you're you're gone from the next week and
you're like oh yeah I spent the last couldn't be on last week because I was like duct taped in someone's
car trunk but like you know they let me out eventually and I'm back and like don't worry about it
that would be like a side arc I think well can't you have a multiple protagonists
yeah I suppose yeah I mean first this guy says it was an ensemble piece but then he goes on to be
well but in spite of that let me make arguments for who to pretend I guess it's a I guess it's a
reasonable I guess it's a reasonable way to category okay I don't I don't hate this uh uh
thinking too much it's fine voice grail voice grail I don't hate it voice grail sorry bits old bits old
next voicemail is called oh it's called a message from your gaping ass two uh I already posted it
okay three two one go hey it's me again uh just want to say like
is it wrong yes
um okay what wrong sure it's wrong definitely it is wrong probably deaf definitely wrong
uh next one is called l o b r rise up uh come on come on discord upload okay three two one go
you know I'm getting tired of the league of natebuckers so I'm starting a new
organization christ the legion of ben rapist oh god no come on because I'm coming for you
please come in hard gross it's even even more sinister because rape is explicit rather than
implied rather than the old one was merely implied yeah um the the um I how am I supposed to be
intimidated by this guy he doesn't even have a voice filter I don't I frankly I I don't think he
could do it I don't think he's man enough I don't think he's I don't think he's wait no I'm going to
say I don't think he's flanged enough but then no when you have a flange you don't rape you have
consensual sex when you are flanged and you have a non you have forced copulation when you're
unflanged because you're a loser so I do think this guy is unflanged but I don't think he will
rape me he he's got aspirations to be flanged yeah but he can't do it obviously nobody can only
only the only the greatest ape on the boreal range can claim that honor okay next voicemail
is called um the brony lecture is dead let's keep it that way three two one go
so Trixie is still going on about how she's willing to redo the brony lecture with you guys
I gotta ask what the fuck would even be the point anymore yep because even under the best
circumstances trying to recapture that energy would be kind of awkward and forced yeah but it's a
lecture about how you became friends and then half of the people who are at the lecture aren't on the
show and now you guys fucking hate each other and then Riley would be there and producing it
so it would just be objectively worse by every single metric imaginable I don't even want it
anymore frankly uh it's dead let's keep it that way this guy uh I still want sonichu 102 though Ben
I know I know the dimensional merge I I know that's true you're right about that um about the
brony lecture I totally agree I I would still I would like it if Trixie were to have a change of
heart and post the old lecture because it was an entertaining lecture she seems dead set on never
doing that um and if and if I mean I guess I can't force her so that that's just she has made up her
mind and I don't know what I can do about it the idea of re-filming it though is like I have no
interest in that at all I think for all the reasons you said it it's a terrible idea it wouldn't
even be good even if we did it which we shouldn't because it's stupid um and I I'd never really
considered the the the awkwardness of the recording I didn't mind in my brain had never even got to
the point imagine what it would be like if we actually did it imagine like reacting to that
and like pretending you didn't hear the first one yeah I agree that um that sounds like a horrible
idea it is so yeah no not interested in that under any circumstances um I would only care
about the first one but yeah that seems to be that seems to have been taken off the table
by Trixie so I mean it is what it is good voicemail and now you've been taken off the table too
I will take you out behind the shed and put you out of your misery sir
next voicemail is called Nate tells you what he really thinks okay come on discord discord is
being slow today okay three two one go who even are you you know you look like a real stupid
bitch fucker right now you stupid bitch fucker fuck you uh I believe it where is that from it sounds
uh sounds legit I think it I think it might be from his latest video I haven't watched it mean the
kingdom hearts hearts I have not watched that one um I haven't watched it yet but uh seems like it
might be good I think maybe it's pretty good it's like it's classic Nate talking about something
it's only part one apparently um okay well Nate I'm sorry you feel that way
next one is called yuck uh let me get it here there it is three two one go
hey studio a post more than RV
uh what was the first thing okay yeah it's a little hard to understand but I get it um you
know you know yick a postmodern rpg oh yeah I know that so the video well the joke is the
joke is yigg a postmodern rv oh I see yeah yeah I get it now very clever voice grail next one is called
the end of an age uh yeah end of an age three two one go
oh age of empires I get it see when you do age of empires and you finish it oh it's swelling
it's swelling this is too much I can't take it yeah I think he just literally like held a speaker
up to his phone microphone what yeah he said he said yep at the end okay well I well I agree
next one is called uh wait hold on next one is called
uh damn it hold on I lost my place again I'm so stupid here we go next one is called
congrats on the new place Gib first time caller please be gentle three two one go
congrats on the new place Gib um when I first moved the hardest parts were getting all the
furniture and like appliances sorted um so how about you do you have a fridge
do you have a but you got no stove you got no stove do you have a fridge
I I'm I'm like living it look at it look at this stoveless look at this stoveless
wonder stoveless wonder over here well I got so what was the hard what was what was the hardest
part of moving so what was what was the hardest part of moving I think is the question oh um
uh I mean I don't know it was most things are quite simple obviously uh the ground I got
everything I got everything uh packed and then parents helped me drive it all the way over there
it wasn't that long got it all out and uh then I had to like buy like a frying pan and a
and spatula and stuff for cooking on Amazon and that's it I mean it's not really been very
difficult to get settled in the only thing that sucks is that the illness that is
it's oh yeah that would be the hard part yeah I didn't expect it at first it was like oh this is
so cool I felt fine and then something something about the new location the water the you know maybe
I cooked something really bad for myself I'm not exactly sure what's different and I got sick
and I've been sick for a little quite a while now actually almost two weeks I'm fine some some of
the time I'm fine more than I used to be so it's looking up the um that reminds me um Munchie and
Cassie are moving in like because like with the end of the school at the end of the school year
oh did they yeah at the end of the school year they are moving to like a place and I told them I
would help them move so I guess I guess I'll be I'll be doing a terrible mistake Ben you should
never help anyone move I know I know but I helped I helped Cassie move into her dorm
like at the beginning of the year so I guess I guess this is just a theme now I guess I'm just
on the hook for all future moves didn't you watch the Seinfeld episode about helping people move
I feel like I think I have I think I have I don't mind by the way I don't actually mind at all it'll
probably be fun uh next next voicemail I guess is called exploring the great beyond lyrical
lithograph three wait no there it is three two one go if you have a fridge you'd know when you drop
it in the sea fridge it will go straight down down down onto the ocean floor no way you get it back
that fridge is made of lead so it's gone for good machines are meant to drown unless they're the
ones that have found a flying submarine
why are these why are these so
cinematic I agree that machines deserve to drown
the um the flying submarine by by the way um by the way um so this this caller
Ararare posted a compilation of all the uh what they call a clusterpunk cyborg and bear
compilation which I will post here they've collected all their all their musical voicemails
yeah I think I saw this before I retweeted it on the on the pcp twitter account but I will put the
link in the description link in the description to clusterpunk cyborg and bear if you want to if
you want to revisit all those magical moments uh uh uh how long how long is it it's it's about okay
it's been 20 minutes long 20 minutes collected um funny very short film very bizarre what a
what a bizarre uh what's the word what a bizarre um choice of medium I guess
voicemails for yeah for serious podcast voicemails bizarre medium for serial storytelling but
but here we are um next work for voicemail is it and it won't and it won't be the last
next voicemail is called um what is this it is called burn the world tree three two one go
hey guys when do you think yiggs gonna fucking die soon like it's gonna happen right this
shit is inevitable yes uh personally I give it 2023 like at the latest it's gonna be a thing
and it'll implode no no no 2024 tops um calling it out when it does happen Riley's
gonna try to steal the channel from Trixie I think that the rebrand was a way for him to then
be like oh well yiggs our thing now and Trixie's not a part of us anymore uh I'm a producer
or some stupid shit uh you try to similar thing with monkey jones he like wore the mask and
pretended to be him or something at least that's what I heard I heard about uh I think you talked
to monkey jones about it he said that he is down for an episode then I know that Tom and give don't
want to shit talk Trixie but monkey jones is definitely down to shit talk Trixie and I really
want to see it um uh make it happen uh I might do something I don't know I might do something um
but um okay I don't think yig I don't think yig by which I mean the collective entity that is the
four of them I don't think it will even survive the year um uh there's the the money's just not
there I kind of thought it's gonna last that long the money's just not there to sustain it um the um
I I don't okay I I thought like you that this is like a right that yiggs studio is like Riley's
scheme to rebrand the channel and call it like um hit a thing that he has partial ownership of
stealing the channel maybe but I think I have reconsidered and I think I was giving him too
much credit that he's some kind of like mastermind behind all this I believe Trixie when she says that
yiggs studio and like changing the channel was her idea maybe maybe she didn't think of the name
I don't know but I believe that like completely changing the channel and changing the branding
to something totally unrelated I believe that that was all her doing um because um from recent
comments on like streams and stuff from Riley suggests that Riley at least now he seems to be
or have been I think I think he probably said he wasn't against it before but I think he has seen
the consequences of it and is now saying that he was against the rebrand uh in the beginning to begin
with because it like has like killed the viewer base and uh and killed their ad revenue I think he
is against it and like he claims to be the one that is getting her to make anime content because
it's the only thing keeping the old subs around and he claims to be like uh you shouldn't you
shouldn't have changed the channel name you shouldn't have not parked your old twitter handle uh and
stuff like that so I don't think it's entirely like uh this is just Riley's scheme to steal the
channel I think there's I think it's more of a two-way street there um but yeah I feel like
regardless of of Riley and the gang I feel like Trixie would have done something like this anyway
due to associating the name Digi Bro with previous life and transitioning so get it rid of the old
name I feel like a rebrand was coming anyway you know that um old videos have started reappearing
though right uh few of them yeah yeah I've seen uh I've seen you mentioned that she has this really
this really annoys me because she in her in the announcement video she says I'm deleting
all but the video all but the videos that I feel like most encapsulate like my current mindset
or something actually uh I should correct you here because she said she's privating all of them
but you're right leading them she said she was she said she was privating them well she said
she was privating them permanently and she encouraged people to archive all of them and she
said that ones that she liked she would like re-dub and re and perhaps re-upload but she didn't do
that she has just started like un-privating them and I really think I really think this is a Riley
thing I really think Riley is like what you did killed the channel please unkill it by like
un-privating those videos even though you don't like them I did see a snippet of a stream where
Riley was talking about uh that the decision to private all the videos wasn't his decision
yeah yeah yeah that's what I mean he he he is now against it and well he should be because I mean
I think he's a little more pragmatic I don't think Trixie has like any clue she's like has like no
feat on on reality in terms of like what money is I think Riley at least understands that money
is required to continue this operation um so he's the more pragmatic one in this situation he's the
one that's like we gotta not kill the channel we gotta not do this I think he's yeah that sounds
pretty crazy I think he's panicking a little bit um uh anyway I guess that's all I have to say about
that um next voicemail is called Sakurakan ikimasu part one uh sorry let me get it here right there
we go three two one go I love sushi oh no is this gonna be all of them is he gonna do all of them
um I don't see a part two so maybe was it weekly okay every week please another roll honestly please
what's the next one is I love is I love Japan period is that is that number two I love sushi I
love Japan period I love Japan period well I'm looking forward to it I really am um next voicemail
is called uh the golden twitch okay um three two one go hi there uh this is uh
that this is uh this is welcome to welcome to void what is happening welcome to avoid tasers
the show where we smoke weed and try oh god and and try to avoid tasers
damn well they're not doing a very good job of it are they no they're they're not uh damn that
damn that sure would be fucked up if that shit was through maybe that's uh their next idea
oh my god okay you look like a pretty good uh video idea all right voicemailer you got me with
that one uh next voicemail is called uh free the pcp three two one go release the pcp
i'm sick of hearing every episode ending with oh no we're about to reach three hours and elia's are
says we can't go over that kill elia's are remove elia's are elia's are doesn't run the podcast
if elia's are doesn't have a computer that can edit basic video he shouldn't be the editor
you know what you're literally going to voicemail is just to your idiots be like
but i don't want to fuck me i don't give a fuck give me podcasts unconstrained by time release the
given cut um you make a good point i mean definitely definitely fuck elia's are um definitely hate that
guy um it's i mean it was confusing i was well i guess it's not that confusing but like doing the
the animated faces to our voice does it does break down after about three hours and like
after effects um but that doesn't mean you can't like do two passes and then stitch them together
in premiere i feel like it's possible to make a long video like that yeah yeah yeah it really
should be i mean we're we're already over the three hour mark now so i guess i guess we'll see
i guess we'll have to talk for so long it doesn't make any sense i mean a lot of it is the voicemails
a lot of it is the voicemails well we've been going for i mean we've been we've been on the
voicemails for about an hour now i don't know we just i just i just love your company i just love
you guys company and i love you the audience patreon.com slash ben saint if you love me
the piece the procrastinators oh yeah that's yeah yeah i guess it's been paint no no no it's
bink saint shout out all right next voicemail is called uh logical logon here we go three two one go
hey guys i just wanted to say that i really like the direction that the show has been going
lately so thank you give up the good work on that front but i have a question mostly directed
towards gib although the others are free to answer if they wish what is your opinion on the minecraft
of modding scene i know that on the pcp microsoft server you guys do like pixel mom or whatever but
i don't know a bunch of mods actually a lot of variance with other mods is if any so feel free
thank you well um good well in what do you think i'm not much of a like when i when i play minecraft
i like vanilla i occasionally i i add like a shader like i have been recently um for like
realistic shadows and and water effects because it just it's just really funny to see like minecraft
blocks rendered in realistic you know ish uh conditions like it's fucking real you can really
place the blocks um i've not really been much with mods ever mostly because i feel like i never
conquered vanilla minecraft i never beat the end the dragon on a single player playthrough
i never got that far play playing um playing uh minecraft on the pcp server i have i i kind of
initially didn't want to fuck with any of the mod stuff because i just thought it was like some weird
shit but i have i have sort of had to grapple with some of it and i have i have come to like um
what i have done i haven't really delved that deep into it but like there's um the magic stuff on
the pcp microsoft the magic stuff and the mana stuff it actually is pretty cool and i like what
i've seen of it um it's nice to i mean some of it is like like the fact that you can make these like
weird exotic metals and then craft the the tera shatterer out of them like it's hard to do but
it's a really useful item to have once you have it and i really appreciate it being there it just
makes mining so much so much less of a grind i don't know stuff like that is is pretty cool like
it's like an extra challenge in the game that gives you a a reward that like you know actually
affects your play experience positively it's pretty pretty cool pretty nice i like uh the pokemon mod
that you guys have going i i like it too although i will say it is very it's pretty rough it's pretty
rough in a lot of ways but it does like pretty well simulate like battling and catching pokemon
in minecraft so like it does exactly what it's supposed to do it's the pokemon mmo that nintendo
never released it it basically yes yeah it basically is which is i mean pretty red microsoft
server is the best place to fix i was gonna say i was gonna say i can cut this if you want me to
but i was gonna say that i really think we should i really think we should just cancel the pcp
minecraft separate server and just make membership like a a like pcp regular uh a pcp just regular
patreon reward at like the five dollar tier or something uh i kind of because like yeah there's
be against it i i really the more i think about it the more convinced i am that that's what we
should do because like makes uh makes sense there's definitely more people who would
the cross section of people who one listen to the pcp and two specifically want membership in
a minecraft server is like us is like small i feel like this there's more people who might be like
yeah i'd like to get the bonus episodes and oh i would also get the minecraft server that's cool
too as well as people i want to be in the minecraft server oh and i also get the bonus episodes
that's cool too um i feel like we wouldn't lose very much by it and it's probably just makes more
sense than having a separate patreon so i think i might just do that soon yeah okay uh so that's
just one more reason to become a patron a patreon.com slash the tpcrastinators the procrastinators
whatever whatever fucking url is tpcrastinators is the twitter yes just uh it just further sweet
ends the deal i'm going to be i'm going to be making that a pzp patron reward instead of a separate
patreon reward uh probably this week sometime it's it's a good idea i i i agree i don't think anyone
would mind cool yeah nobody would mine crap oh oh but they will though oh but oh but they will
um based okay next voicemail is called um uh based joker four three two one go when i tell people
that i just had a peanut they say hey that sounds delicious but when i tell people that i just had
a poop nut well suddenly they can't get out of the hot tub fast
that was a good one i think uh voice grail for this one voice grail voice grail for base joker
but i like yeah is he all fuck okay yeah yeah well it's too late last time but
oh boy good base fucking goodness gracious
base uh based joker should needs to battle riddle my ass batman
oh i don't know i don't know if riddle my ass batman has what it takes
you i don't i don't know if you can handle it
get out of the hot tub fast and that's good that's good there's layers to that there's layers
very well very well done uh you but you bitch um next voicemail is called uh listen to behind
the bastards ben three two one go hey ben uh since you know DMing you didn't really do much
i have come with voicemails because you are obligated to listen to me now price um
fucking go listen to behind the bastards you fuck what is it i don't know what i don't know what
you're talking about i guarantee you will fucking love it and it will make you stop being such a
dumbass left okay you all right okay yeah we'll see like we'll see you learn that goddamn this
like for one it's it's it's made by robert evans which i know you know you've retweeted these
stuff who the no i don't know who that is he's a fucking anarchist and he just goes deep just
does a deep dive into some of the worst people or worst things in history one of them fucking
Stalin and apparently this dude fucking Stalin at the end of like the so by the end of the
soviet union was just perpetually drunk like just continuously i've heard that i've heard Russian
drunk maybe all the time and he would like he would force his ministers to have gigantic night long
vendors every day where they would decide the future of the nature the the nation wild shit
bro fucking go listen to it you dumbass i don't know why you say this will make me less of a
dumb lefty i go to this i go to the behind the bastard's twitter account and like the banner
like it's red it's got like the fucking uh a soviet font and it's now been changed to behind the
police so this guy hates cops at least as much as i do so i don't know man i don't know if this is
gonna have that particular effect on me well um nobody's perfect not even joseph stalin
not even joseph stalin even even he succumbed to the drink uh if you can believe it um but i mean i
would listen i would listen to this okay i mean maybe i'll give maybe i'll give a listen i'll
leave the i'll leave the tab open here and maybe i'll get around to listening once or twice in a
blue moon i don't know we'll see i think that's unlikely it's it's it's unlikely it's an outside
chance but if people keep nagging me if people just keep nagging me then like anything is possible
um next voicemail is called corbin why three two one go why do you like jeremy corbin so much ben
he is a known anti-semite lol good one no he fucking isn't funny funny joke funny joke you
funny joke you limey you limey bitch funny joke you fucking you fucking turf islander you you
miserable fuck um uh corbin's pretty you know who loves corbin what what what what
what uh convince me what is what has done the most to convince me of corbin's goodness is
my favorite twitter account ze squirrel um i love them and they love corbin and that's good enough
from the robin well i'm convinced yes i think i've never actually seen robin hood but
yeah it's that she's got the disney squirrel as her uh logo wait you mean the the robin hood from
the disney uh robin hood yeah it's definitely a disney squirrel i thought i assumed it was from
bambi but it could be from robin hood i actually don't know but yes uh she's uh she's a genius
she's like my favorite fucking poster uh she like sends person she like sends emails to um
uh uh uh gnome chomsky and gnome chomsky just like writes back but but i mean apparently he
does that with like anyone apparently like almost anyone can just write him an email and he will
like write back like the same day um well if she's uh your favorite poster then you can put
her up on the wall i can put her i can hang her up on the wall right next to my samurai ninja scroll
and full metal alchemist wall scrolls that's right that's exactly right next voicemail is called um
it is called mister oh it's another one from mr sucking fuck three two one go oh god it's a minute
i don't know if i'm in for a full minute of this
i've looked everywhere for him
he has been a very very bad boy
yeah
and you know what must be done
oh tell me please
this person's
oh
well that was an adventure this is the prototypical pcp head typical back on their bullshit
this is what everyone is like this is what everyone sounds like but they all put voice filters on
sound normal yeah i like that i like i like to believe it um well thanks for the voicemail
uh next one is called explaining ben's bad politics uh there it is three two one go
ben's bad politics are how much he interrupts a gib i'm i'm sweet i the lag is bad the it actually
probably sounds worse on the podcast than it sounds to me when i'm talking because there's lag
and sometimes i start talking before i hear that gib has started talking this is a real thing that
happens it and i'm pretty sure it's happening with you and gamers tavern i'm pretty sure that's
why you and gamers haven't kept talking about it's also happening yeah it's it's an unfortunate
reality of discord calls from different continents yeah yes yes it's regrettable it's regrettable
but true okay next one is called uh do do or dodo one of the other um next three two one go
do not do the doughnut don't not a rod is one dimensional a woman is not
a what is one dimensional oh wait i'm listening to the
like do not do the doughnut don't not a road is one dimensional a woman is not
uh i don't know uh dick masters told me uh that uh women are one dimensional
true nice meme i couldn't guess what they were saying i think he said a rod is one dimensional
or i think he said a road maybe maybe it was a rod maybe i think it was road but
uh maybe not what difference does it make hey this guy this guy's on to something
uh next voicemail is called jebediah has made up his mind three two one go
okay 10 seconds in jebediah where are you
hello this is me
i just gotta say i don't think i like i want to fuck me anymore i think that's pretty
okay that's true that's true i think i think that's for the best all good things must come
hey what did he say at the end just say bye bye yeah jebediah thank thank you for sharing your
wisdom yeah that's good advice good wisdom your homegrown down to earth just i feel like jebediah
pricking sin is a himbo i don't know why really i i imagine him i imagine him has like a
as like a toll booth worker i imagine him as like a fat you know kind of just like slob he
probably he might sort of like a mr. plinkett type who kind of like maybe has like a a rascal scooter
to get around sits in a toll booth definitely a toll booth worker uh that's my take
uh next uh voicemail is called um receipts are important in any transaction verbal or
otherwise three two one go
uh
sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't get him.
The deal, the compact is broken.
The deal is off.
Alright, next voicemail is Friendly Reminder. 3, 2, 1, go.
Hmm.
I've been masquerading the castle in strife.
What?
You can't stop me.
I can't.
You can't stop him.
I can't stop him.
You can't stop him, Ben.
You can't stop the...
He's unstoppable.
He's got momentum.
He's got momentum now.
He can't be stopped.
He can only be diverted in his course, but he's definitely getting where he's going, one way or another.
Next voicemail, we're almost done.
Christ Almighty, we're almost done.
The next voicemail is called Cake.
No.
No, the next one is called...
No, I already played that one.
Never mind.
No, yes, the next one is called Cake.
Wait.
Come on, Discord.
Don't fuck with...
Don't fuck me on this one.
There it is.
Okay, Cake.
3, 2, 1, go.
This is everyone's favorite Natehead turned Saint Head Cake coming in with a request for Ben Saint.
Because you see, Ben, I actually purchased the Vapors 1 a few years later, purchased the Vapors 2.
And when I did this, I made a really grave, grave mistake in the sense that my Vapors 2 is signed by Ben Saint.
But my Vapors 1 isn't signed.
So now, every single time I look at my shelf, there's deep, immense, crippling pain.
A pain so strong, I cannot even begin to describe how painful this pain is in my right ankle.
It's preventing me from standing up and moving forward with my life unless I get this resolved.
So, Giga Head Galaxy Chat idea.
I send you my Vapors 1 copy.
Of course, I pay for shipping and everything.
And then you sign it and then send it back to me.
And then I'd be able to walk again.
And I'd also own the most Giga Chat item ever created in the history of the world.
If Vapors 1 copy is signed by both Ben and Munchy.
And you'd be an actual Saint since you had a performant miracle.
I think it's a pretty win-win scenario.
Also, Gib, any chance the old crew might be setting sail again?
I'd love to hear the tales of Wano from my favorite two boys.
Also, my house is actually on fire right now.
And because I can't hear of the tales of Wano, my left ankle is in immense pain.
So I can't stand up from that either.
Now, I'm just stuck in a burning building.
And I'd really like to kind of walk out of this building.
Like, this building is really on fire.
It's really hot in here, guys.
Reach over, grab your copies of the Vapors and throw them out the window.
And local authorities will arrive to pick...
A local telekin will scoop them up and send them to Ben's Saint.
Well, you gotta make sure to save those copies.
Do you want to answer about the Poty cast first?
Yeah, I keep forgetting to talk to Nate about it.
There's nothing holding it up except I'm not doing it lol.
I mean, it's both of you, right?
Well, yeah, he hasn't talked to me, I haven't talked to him,
but I feel like if I say, hey, Nate, let's do the Poty cast, he'll just say, yeah, okay.
So it's not really an issue.
Also, has cake left a voicemail before?
I can't remember if they have.
Possibly? I don't know, why?
Because I think that might be the cake that came to RFC KCON London
that I remember meeting them.
And they introduced themselves as a Nate head and everyone was like, oh my god, how embarrassing.
That's cringe.
But he was cool.
Cake, if you want, maybe you can DM me on Twitter or on Discord or whatever.
If you want to, I will do it.
If you want to pay for shipping, you can send me that copy of Vapors 1
as well as the difference between, oh god, I think a signed copy was $50?
So I guess, I'll look it up, I'll double check,
but I think it'd be whatever the difference between a signed and unsigned copy,
which would be something like 35 bucks or something.
Pay for shipping and pay that, send me that, I will sign your copy and send it back to you.
I have no qualms about it, sounds good, bro.
Was there something else that he asked about?
Oh, no, no, but there was, there's one thing, I don't know if I've mentioned this before,
but okay, about the Vapors 2, I went to the post office a while ago
and I found two copies that had been returned to sender
and these were both people whose copies had previously been returned to sender.
So this, for both of them, this was the second time I was getting them back in the mail.
Both of them, I contacted them and be like, did you change address?
And they were like, yes, here's my new address.
And I resent them with the new address.
So these people have chronic address impermanence issues.
But so now, I now have two copies sitting in my room.
I have contacted both of these people on, through Kickstarter
and asking them like, hey, it seems like it got, it returned again.
What's the deal? Where should I send it again?
But neither of them had gotten back to me.
So I don't know how else to contact these people,
but if you are listening and you never got,
you are one of these two people who never got their Vapors 2,
check your Kickstarter messages because I'm asking like,
just tell me where to send it, I will resend it.
No problem.
Do they happen to live in an RV by chance?
I don't think so.
They both had street addresses, technically.
Because you know RVs can move.
No, no, no, no, no, no, these are, maybe,
maybe these, they're just constantly on the move,
just living the nomad life. I don't know.
I don't know.
Okay, next one is the last voicemail.
It is called, Bleach Fan 17.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, okay, okay.
Endlessly adorned, knowing it will be cut off.
Endlessly polished, knowing they will be cut off.
They are terrifying, terrifying in their fall,
The hair flutters to the ground, a lifeless husk.
Hair and fingernails are beautiful ornaments.
So why do they seem so baleful when removed?
The answer is simple.
They are previews of what is to come, of death.
Jesus.
Bleach Volume 29, The Slashing Opera.
Well, at least it wasn't about foreskins.
He's right. God damn it, Bleach was right, all along.
Does that happen in Bleach?
Or is he just saying something and attributing it to Bleach?
I mean, there's a lot of Bleach.
I could, I could believe there's all kinds of
weird poetical shit in there somewhere.
I believe it.
I didn't watch Far Enough Into Bleach to know if this is something that happens later.
You both are saying, happens.
Nothing, nothing happens.
It's just like a thing that someone said.
I watched like one episode of Bleach ever.
So I don't know.
Someone probably says this in Bleach.
I'm sure of it.
Karen, I know everything about Bleach.
I watched a whole episode.
This is exactly what it's like.
I don't know.
It's pretty good though.
Makes you think.
Really makes you think.
Really makes you, I mean, no, that's, that's the, when you,
that's when you hear a brown note is what really makes you stink.
Yeah, exactly.
Bringing it all the way back to the beginning, baby.
Nice meme.
We, we did it.
We listened to all the voicemails.
Oh my God.
It's almost four hours.
Oh, oh my God.
That doesn't make any sense.
Sorry.
A minute ago I looked and it was only three hours.
Sorry, Elias.
Are we really fucked you?
But it was funny.
Sorry.
Not sorry.
Sorry to him, but also sorry to the fans, the audience.
Definitely, definitely sorry to the listeners to subject you to all this.
No, they like it.
They like large amounts of audio.
I hope so.
I mean, I would, if, I mean, I can't think of a podcast that I like,
that I wouldn't like more of.
I had a scene.
Yeah.
I have seen a couple people say like episodes are too long.
And if you think, if maybe if you like don't like the voicemails,
I could be, I could see being like, yeah, it's too long because there's too much voicemail
or something.
But like in the absence of like something about it that you don't like hearing,
I can't imagine being like, I wish this were the same, but less of it.
You know?
So I don't, I feel like that, that complaint needs qualification or I don't understand it.
Anyway, patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes of which there are what,
like 50 or more?
More than 50.
And, and also Minecraft server access because I am, we are merging, we are merging that into
one place, as I think we probably should have done a long time ago, but oh well.
And that's speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail if you want to send a voicemail, but hey,
we don't have to because we don't have to have like 50 voicemails in episode.
It's not a requirement.
Yeah.
If you really want to, you can send a voicemail.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no, I mean to them.
Oh my God.
I mean to them, like stop, stop speaking into the voicemail so that we don't have to listen
to them.
That's what I meant.
Oh, then I agree.
Then I agree.
I agree 100%.
Fuck these guys.
Fuck these mutants, these monsters, these fools.
Okay, I think we're done.
I think we got to, we got to wrap up.
Anything else before we leave?
YouTube.com slash gamers tavern show and gamers tavern show and follow me on Twitter at gamer
tavern.
Have you before we have you put out any videos lately?
What's what's the last video you put out?
The last one was from two weeks ago, I think.
What was that one?
Just a short like tips video hints and tips.
It's a gamer tips.
Yeah.
Very good.
Okay.
Well, glad to know.
Yes.
Check out gamers tavern for content and jokes and and gaps.
Okay, I guess that's it for this episode.
Sorry for everything.
Goodbye.
That's the end.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
Don't go deaf.
Bye.