Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best
guy ever and here is Hippocrit. And Munchy is here. Semperfied Delos to all our armed forces.
And just so everybody knows, this is the PCP. It's a show where a bunch of YouTube and other
place content creators, we just get together and we talk about stuff. There's your introduction
if you don't know what this is, that's what it is. Our topic today is The Military. What
an enigma. What can you even say about the military? Nothing. I've got the Urban Dictionary
open. Some of the definitions are lame. So I just went to the one that is like a bunch
of definitions. So here's like the third entry and there's like five of them on here. So
here we go. Military. A government department, it's got like that parentheses S, charged
with defense of national borders, two members of the military department forces in parentheses
for some reason, an armed government department employed to ensure security and home and abroad.
That's clearly a typo. Nobody gives a fuck about Urban Dictionary, I guess. An armed force
used to subdue or oppress groups which oppose governmental policy at home or abroad, and
a designation which bestows virtual sainthood in some cultures. Oh, I get it. That's like
the joke one. Okay, cool. So that's it. That's the military, the armed forces of nations.
I love war. I just want to say that. As a little boy you're told war is bad and you
don't want World War III. I guess I don't want World War III. But then you read about
all the fiction, all the stories, all the real life stories, all the cool things, all
the toys. Military war stuff is the coolest thing ever. War is a great time to rise through
the social ranks. You know this Alexander Hamilton, the play Hamilton, the musical that came out
not too long ago, that everyone tries to be like, oh, Hamilton's such a wonderful guy
and this is a perfect boy. But yeah, he pretty much wanted war so that tons of people would
die. War is not good so that he could rise through the ranks and grow. That was his
opportunity to do so. So he was kind of hoping for that shit nonetheless.
And Nate, you actually went to go see Hamilton, but then the entire cast wouldn't start the
show and they just berate you. And you're accomplice for not not respecting minority
rights and how you need to use your extreme executive power effectively.
That's right.
Like what the fuck?
I didn't appreciate that. That was very rude, but I will work on forgiving them in time.
As I strip away all their civil rights.
I want to clarify. Conflict is terrible. Conflict is like, oh, there's a group of people and
they're being bombed by this nasty guy and then there's other bombs going off and there's
drone strikes. That's boring. That's cowardly. It's terrible.
There's civilian deaths. Don't like civilian deaths. I do like battles with armies. Like
if we were to go to war with a country, let's just say, fuck you, we're going to war. Send
everyone, the robots, the nukes, the whole gang, the whole gang's here.
I love the idea and the romance of battles and war. But if we're talking about the military,
it's pretty fucked up.
That attitude is what started World War I. Everyone was real interested in like, man,
we've got all these militaries. We haven't used our weapons in a while. We've got all
these new ones like this mustard gas bombs and shit. Let's just have a big war. Then
they did and that was World War I and it was a little bit of that.
A little bit.
That's pretty much what started it.
We got to decide first of all, instead of just meandering around the idea of armies
and war and the military, what are we going to discuss about the military? Are we talking
about like in general or like current or American vs. UK military?
We can talk about like historical stuff, but I think more interest, you know, more like
relevant would be like modern military and like its place in the world and what we think
about and what it's doing, all that good stuff. Semper Fidel is to all our armed forces.
Exactly. But I have something far more important, military fashion. The Prussian slash early
empire had the best military fashion, Google search, Franco-Pussian war uniforms for some
fresh shit. You World War I Britain has some good shit too, but fucking debate me. All
fucking pickle helms, that shit were fucking sick. They were great.
I've always had a pension for SS officer uniforms. You know, I'm quite fond of them. I think
they're very attractive looking. The Nazis had impeccable fashion. There's no denying
it, at least for their officers, for their officers.
Barais have never been like cool until the military decided that they were the thing.
I agree. You think of a barais, you think of like a French guy with onions around his
neck and going home, I'm gay, a whole home. They're very afraid of vampires in France.
Yeah. Well, no, it's onions. It's werewolves with onions. Werewolves hate onions, right.
Vampires are like werewolves with onions. And mummies hate parsley. Just wave some parsley
in a mummy's face and you got that boy spooked. I'm pretty sure that's how that works.
Barais, like the British officers types, they're like, I'm in charge and I have a red
beret and I'm cool. And I'm like, yeah, you are. I believe you. You do need to have that
said. Yeah, I agree.
What about, okay, that's true and all, but what do we think about, you know, like, so
times have moved on and like if there were to be like a World War three, it would be
a big deal because the last like big old war, of course, is World War two. And that ended
with the advent of nuclear weapons. So like that's on the table now. And that's a big
deal. And I don't know how much we want to talk about like war, specifically versus
I think, I think if there is going to be a World War three, nobody is going to admit
that it is happening and that it's being called World War three because nobody wants
to live in a world where World War three is happening because so much time has passed
since the, you know, what it was called at the time of the Great War.
It would be really bad PR to have World War three.
It's not about PR, but I'm just thinking like general people, they're always like, oh,
World War three is just around the corner. It may already be happening.
Well, like the Cold War is kind of like the World War three, just in the sense that like
most of the world was divided up between like two sides. And I mean, at least America and
Russia or the USSR and like all its subsidiaries and shit. And then like, but of course, like
the whole, the whole thing there was like, we couldn't afford to escalate that to a bigger
war because if we did, and that's maybe why nuclear weapons are kind of good because they
force you to find other things or else everyone's dead, even though that threats on the table.
You know, if you don't find a way to, to avoid that outside of like, I mean, now that, you
know, nukes are on the table, like you're going to get a nuclear war and that's not so good.
It's not so spicy.
The next time a nuke is used, I think will be
to be a big deal. It's gonna be a big deal. And probably people will say, okay, now it's
happening like now World War three, because like you can't, you can't back down from like,
well, now we're going to try a certain this out peacefully because we knew you know what
the most likely thing for that is. I think that the most likely thing I think that probably
will happen at some point, but it's going to be like some sort of dirty nuclear bomb that
like a terrorist organization gets their hands on somehow, because like more and more countries
are getting their hands on nukes and shit. It's just, you know, the technology is known.
It's out there for like 60 years now. So I think that's going to happen. It's not going
to like destroy a country or anything. It's going to be very bad. And it's going to radiate
like a population somewhere. And it's going to be fucked up. London, I think it's almost
inevitable. Yeah, Olympics, baby. Here we go, drop the bomb.
Fun fact. Did you know that during the Korean War, a U.S. general wanted to just use a nuke
on China, not like on their capital, but just like to like stop their advance, like just
a tactical nuke just wait, wait, do you mean China or Vietnam or Korea? I mean, in the
Korean War, China helped North Korea. I was right. So they wanted to nuke China to stop
the North Korean advancement or something. Yes. Yeah. Okay. All right. I'm fine. Yeah.
Okay. I mean, you know, there's certainly a tactical advantage to using a fucking nuke,
but just think about how like how fast we would all be dead if that were to transpire.
Exactly. Exactly. So I think it's I think the moment that a single nuke is used, we are all
dead. And you might as well just say your yeah, it's it's it's it's kind of that's the nature
of deterrence. It's kind of it's so big a threat that it's kind of hard to wrap your head around
being scared about it. Like at any moment, a country could decide, you know what, we're
going to suddenly start using these. Fuck you. Boom. North Korea, dude, North fucking Korea.
Yeah. And it's like, oh, well, they have nukes and they could nuke us and we could be dead within
a day or two. And if we're not dead, the whole rest of our country will be in nuclear quarantine
and would be enough. All of infrastructure will fall apart and would be in the slums and it'll
be terrible. And you're like, you're thinking about how bad it could possibly be. And you're not
shying away from it, but it's just it's just too big to be like scary in a way that you can
understand. You can't feel that fear until it's like actually happening to you.
The people that are the most interesting to me in there are the South Korean people because like
right across that fucking Waller River, whatever it is, there is North Korea has nukes could easily
drop them on South Korea if they wanted to. And that's the big thing with why, okay, so North Korea
is possibly the most dangerous nation like in the world right now because they're so fucking crazy
and they worship, you know, like this one dude who runs the whole ship and can do whatever the
fuck he wants because he's like a god or something to the people. So like because of that, if we go
in and try to like take that guy out as a lot of people want to because he's just a toxic element
on the world stage, like the most likely thing that would happen is that we can't like instantly
take out all their defenses and they just dump everything they got on South Korea. They're holding
like at least all of Seoul like the capital which is right across the border. They're holding all the
population of Seoul is held captive to prevent like any action against North Korea period.
And like there's just and those people like I was listening to an NPR story I think about like
interviewing what South Koreans think of North Korea. Like they're hoping to get like a resolution
at some point. They want diplomatic talks. In fact, I think they just elected a president
who ran on a platform of like reform, reforming relations with North Korea. I mean who knows
that has any chance of working. I'm certainly no expert in the politics. But like they want that
to happen but like they are just like yeah like it's too big to think about for them. The fact
that every single day they could be wiped off the face of the earth at the whim of King John Moon.
Yeah, sure. This isn't the world politics, PCP. This is the military. It's related but yeah you're
right. I kind of wish it was. Let's talk about PCP. This is the fashion. This is fashion piece.
Yeah, yeah. Fashion Seoul. I guess. I guess. Dude. Dude. We're not in a fashion so cluster punk dude.
What is? Military fashion is so fucking cluster punk. What are you talking about? It's not cluster
punk at all. It's the most streamlined like disciplined organized possible fucking thing.
It could be. That's what we have to all achieve too. When the dark carnival starts. The jugglers
assemble their armed forces. Now that will be a cluster punk military. No, no. People will be too
scared to call it world war three so they'll just call it the dark carnival. They will be too horrified
to call it world war three. So yeah, we're in the midst of a dark carnival ladies and gentlemen.
All it would take is for Donald Trump to say I am now a juggler. I'm down with the clown.
And American brothers and sisters. And like everything will come true that was in Homestuck
just like we all thought. Just like we all knew. It will all come true. Guy Fieri will be there,
you know. Trump says I'm Dan and Clown ladies and gentlemen. He says as a nuke explodes behind him.
Like he puts on the shades like cool like walking away from explosions.
As he nukes his, cause he fucking nukes the White House, his own fucking house. He's just like
fuck this shit man. This is the carnival baby. And it gets replaced with a black and white house.
What a fucking North Korea just explodes itself. That point in life.
Well, you know, that sounds pretty cool. Unfortunately, like, you know, to the rest
of the world, excuse me, like the North Korean people are also like brainwashed people being
held hostage. You know, who knows, I don't know what they, if they actually like believe this
shit. I mean, I'm sure to some level they do cause the propaganda has been so intense.
I got an angle. I got an angle for this. For about the military. Your favorite historical army
thing. Like from age of empires or civilization. Fucking whatever you know. What is your favorite?
I like, I don't know. You go first, give, let me think while you say something.
Well, I played age of empires too a lot and, uh, fucking love that game. Learned so much more
about history from that game than I ever did in my books. That's what video games are. Video games
are teaching makers. They're like books only good. They're like books, but you don't have to open them.
You have to click on them though. Double click. But you have to install Linux and then boot your,
you know, Windows andulator. You have to fucking draw your own game. And then you have to draw every
frame. Yeah, exactly. Every frame literally a gimp painting is the way it's said.
Every frame of PNG.
But, uh, fucking, I loved, uh, in that the English longbowmen, mostly because I'm English and that's
like, oh yeah, I want to be an archer now. I want to be a longbowman. But because also that if you
get like 50 of them, uh, they can just completely decimate like anybody because they've got the
longest range. And it's so cool to see all those arrows flying. God, I love, I love arrows, dude.
Um, um, you would also nice. I fucking love knights and castles. Okay, but
Knights are you would love Sif five because they have longbowmen. England has longbowmen
a longbowman in that game, and he's fucking overpowered because he can see so fucking far.
He can see like millions of miles at a time. He is he's
Fucking literal, literally elves were based on Longbowmen. I'm making that up, but it makes sense to me.
I mean, J.R.R. Tolkien was English, so pretend you were wrong.
Proven confirmed.
But did you know, here's a stupid gay fact. Did you know that it was required by law that every male has to learn to be an archer in England?
And that was a law that was never stopped. It's still in effect. It's just nobody fucking gives a shit.
That's pretty sick.
That's awesome.
There's these weird old laws in America that you have to carry a gun on your way to church on Sunday in New England.
Because there were Indian raids going on, so they wanted all the men to be armed and shit.
But still, in some towns, you are by law ordered to carry a gun with you to church wherever the fuck you go.
I don't see why that's a law. You just do that normally.
Yeah, I hear you, dude. Jesus wants to see us pack any heat.
I still killed the Native Americans on my way to church still. No one stopped me yet.
You didn't get the memo.
You know, okay, my favorite military, I think, I mean, I'm quite fond of the Nazis.
I'm quite fond of the Nazis as well.
You know it, bro.
They were pretty cool, but I'm definitely going to give it up to the Persian slave hordes.
The Persian slave hordes are totally dope and they're full of magic.
I'm basically basing this just on 300, but they're fucking sick, bro.
And they hurl themselves endlessly and they just die in agony and pain.
They don't want to be there, but they're forced to be there by their god king.
That's the army for me. That's what I want to know.
Any army that uses elephants is so good.
So cool. So what elephants are the coolest?
Big guy with a big nose swinging out around.
You could pick up a club. You could whack him with a club.
Like, yeah, that's exactly what I want to see on the battlefield.
The most powerful nose in the Middle East.
All right, Munch, what do you like?
Oh, I don't know about that. Israel's got a powerful mouth.
Yeah, that's true. I could really sniff out a deal if you know what I'm saying.
There's a lot. There's quite a bit, so I'm just going to rattle off some.
My all-time favorite war of all time is World War I.
My favorite period of time is the 1800s through 1900s.
Everything before is gay, besides the ones that aren't,
and then also everything afterwards is gay, except it's not. It's even better.
So yeah, World War I, I like Venezuela.
I like the South American Wars of Independence. All of them pretty cool.
I like pretty much anything in Europe.
Anything there is good, besides when it involves anything in East Europe,
because each Europe is gay.
And everything in the ages is gay.
Yeah, that's pretty much it.
So which military force is your favorite, though?
Oh, wait. Oh, that. Oh, shit.
I don't know. They're all pretty bad. I hate them.
I'm like, okay, really?
What about the fucking World Warriors from Scotland?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. The Dragon Queen.
Oh, wait, fucking the Romans. The Romans, they're the coolest.
They made a fucking turtle's things with their fucking shields.
They made turtles on the battlefield.
Wait, you mean the, fuck, the phalanx?
Because that was a Greek thing first, wasn't it?
No, no, the Roman, well, maybe it was, but the Romans developed...
It was in 300, bro.
Yeah, okay.
Whatever.
But the Romans, they invented, like, mass producing by means of, like,
making the equipment exactly the same by using molds and stuff
and making everything to order exactly the same
so that their shields could very easily lock together
to make, like, big old, like, you couldn't fucking get them.
They're just impenetrable.
That's the coolest.
That's true. That's the phalanx, right?
I don't know whether it's called a phalanx,
but if you type in Roman turtle thing, you'll find some shit.
Also, asterix and obelisk is my dad.
I just want that to be known.
Okay, what was that one?
It's my favorite thing.
Hippo, red pillion whales.
It's just England, right?
Alright, whales is the little bump on the left side of the UK, England.
Great, like, yeah.
I know that at one point, I think it may have been a country with a king,
but I'm not actually sure that it ever was
and I'm not sure that it ever was not part of England,
but they just speak a different language and they have a flag
and we're like, fine, just have it.
It rains all the time over there.
We don't care.
I know that, I mean, Scotland has referendums on independence sometimes
that I think, yeah, that didn't pass last time.
Does whales ever have, like, referendums for independence?
Is that a thing they do?
Yeah, well, that's the thing, because I've heard once,
and I don't know whether it's true, but it was probably true,
because it was on television,
that whales is not technically its own nation,
but it's treated, it has a border and you need your passport
and it's basically a nation,
but they don't really care about seceding
because they have no real infrastructure,
like their biggest exports are like Tom Jones
and stuff like that.
What is Tom Jones?
What's your pussycat?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, I see.
That guy, oh my god, I'm clipping.
He's from Wales? Is that like an American?
No, no, there's a lot of Welsh singers
that are very, very good at singing.
For some reason, I think it might be the language.
They're just good at singers.
They're good at singers. They make good singers
and that's what they export. That's my point.
I'm clipping the mic and I've got to change the mic.
Well, let's, okay, let's talk about,
let's completely shift gears back to military stuff,
and let's talk about the current American military
and what we think about, because that's the thing
that we have the most, oh wait, I forgot, you're from England,
but nonetheless, you can talk about the British military
to care too, but like, I mean,
some of the guys that we were hoping to have on here
actually grew up near fucking military bases
and know a lot of people in the military.
Oh, did you? I didn't know that you were,
they're that near one. Okay, what do you think?
What do you think of our fine men and women in uniform?
Here is my opinion of people in the military.
Every single day, there is a helicopter
or a plane that runs over my head very fucking fast
and he always scares me because he just thinks
this is the day. This is the day where I get 9-11.
It's about to happen, but now it's finally transpired
and I am about to become the 9-11.
But it never happens and I'm getting increasingly upset.
Like, if you're gonna do that to me,
why not just fucking pull the trigger, you know?
You're upset that they're just delaying the inevitable.
Right, right. And soon those will be drones instead.
Oh no, 9-11 drones.
Yeah.
That will truly be 7-11.
I live next to like a huge military base
and there's like a town that's developed around the military base
and all of them are just rich assholes.
And so, I don't know, they're pretty gay.
Actually, no, I went to a bowling alley one day on the base
with a military friend and I like bowling.
So there, you know what, they're good.
I've changed my opinion. They're actually really nice people.
On the basis of they like bowling too.
Yeah.
I don't really know a lot of people in the military
but I have found everybody to be very, they're very professional,
they're very polite.
These guys seem like they know what's going on with the shit around them.
So, I don't know, I like them.
I guess I just, this isn't even really a criticism of the military
but I don't like people with guns near me at all.
I don't like when people could kill me if they want to
because I don't know these people
and I don't know if they're actually sane or crazy.
It always spooks me when I see like, when I'm in like the airport
or just like a, I don't know, like in Penn Station
a couple times I've seen like people with guns walk around
and like military people.
Yeah, it's a little spooky, it's a little spooky.
I just don't trust anyone in the world
including like the military or the politicians
or my friends or family.
I don't trust anyone. I'm on my own. I'm on my own.
And when there's people with guns, yeah, they scare me a little bit.
They scare me a little bit, including cops.
I don't think you hate freedom of speech.
I mean the Second Amendment.
Whatever, you hate guns?
Oh my fucking god.
Thank you for condensing my argument to the important part here.
Jesus Christ.
You know, I don't know how true this is
but I've always felt like, maybe it's just my own propaganda
on my side of the pond.
But the general feeling I get is that the American military is big
but it's not like tightly constructed.
Like they have bunches of soldiers and bunches of stuff
but there's a larger percentage of them that are just not that well-trained
and they fuck up and do bad stuff and kill one guy.
Now hang on, hang on a second there.
I don't know if that's at all true.
Huh?
Because like, I mean, how many military people do you and I really know?
I have no idea what's the process of military training
but I feel the need to feel better than you guys
because my military is smaller.
Oh, you would get to Paris and I see.
Yeah, yeah, it's smaller because obviously there's less people
but because of the smallness and the fact that we're an island
we have like a big old naval thing, we've always had that
and we've got a good air force
and we're like more tightly woven.
We're like a scare force.
Hey, I'm scared now.
Like, you know, put together very, very carefully and properly and trained
and like you gotta do it right otherwise you're gonna get slapped.
Do your bootlace.
What softener?
You can't drink the tea while you fly the plane.
I know nothing about fucking military, why am I here?
Well, here's why.
I want to join the military
and I want to drive a tank
and I want to shoot a head.
Consider this your official signing into the military.
I'm leaving the PCP, I'm joining the military.
That's what I'm gonna do.
They do bigger podcasts there.
They get more money per podcast.
They do podcasts while doing drone strikes.
That's what they're about.
It's an upgrade in a big way.
Those podcasts are way better because they have like live feeds
of the people they're bombing.
It's so cool.
It's part of the drone.
It's very engaging.
It's basically like soldiers react to carnage
that they're causing.
Let me say this.
I want to do that.
You should.
I think about, I have a lot of respect for military people
because I think that a lot of them do all their shit for the right reasons
and that they, I mean I'm too cowardly to want to do this shit
but they really are willing to put their lives on the line
and risk it for stuff.
I guess I didn't really say about the people who joined the military.
I think it's generally a silly idea
but I see why people do it.
It's like part, you want to be like a hero.
You want to be protecting people.
You do it for a good reason, hopefully.
You don't just want to shoot people.
You want to protect your country.
You feel proud and all that and this stuff.
But I feel like it's generally, it's pretty silly
because the government may have like a stupid idea
that they want to send you to the wrong place and kill the wrong people.
You have to trust your government really
or whoever's commanding you if you're in the military.
It's just like, I don't know.
I wouldn't join the military because I don't trust
really any government to put me in the place
that's going to do the best for the world at large.
I would care about my country more just in general
because that's where all my friends and family are
and where I am, I don't know.
It's a very big thing.
I say that not joining the military is like pirating video games.
It's like that.
Because you are reaping the benefit of like
labor that other people are doing, people in the military.
I mean obviously the degree is different.
You are profiting from like other people's work.
And yes of course we all pay taxes and shit
and if you're in the military you get paid
and good things come to you if you do so.
But you're taking an extreme risk doing that kind of shit.
You're putting yourself at the very least in harm's way
even if it's not extreme risk.
You could have like a desk job or whatever.
But you're part of this machine that's doing defense.
And you know what, I mean that's kind of silly.
I thought somebody would yell at me and I would concede
that it's not actually like pirating video games.
I was going to totally agree with you as a joke
because it sounds so funny.
Like a one-to-one correlation is exactly the same.
That's good.
But like, okay, I got a lot of respect for these people.
I always think about that scene.
I watch this movie all the fucking time.
A few good men with Tom Cruise and Jack Nicholson.
And that part at the end, like the most famous scene of the day,
you can't handle the truth where Jack Nixon's like,
son we have a country that has walls
and those walls need men to stand on them
and defend the nation for people who want to destroy it.
Who's going to do it, Lieutenant Weinberg?
You? You?
I forget the names of the other characters.
But yeah, like the point is like that guy gets it.
That guy realizes that like there, no matter what,
there's always going to be forces
that like want to take things that other people have.
And I'm not saying, like in their case,
they're talking about like Cuba.
And at the time like Cuba and America were very much not,
not liking each other so much.
You know, things are different now,
but there's always going to be something like that.
And I just really appreciate the people who do do that shit.
Yeah.
And like I've got a personal memory of this.
Like when I was a kid, I worked at Papa Gino's,
this pizza shop in Massachusetts.
Nothing beats it.
And like there was this, yeah, it's the best.
It's my favorite.
And there was this guy who worked there for a little while.
And he was a veteran,
but he was only a couple years older than me.
I was like 17 or something.
He was like 21, 22, like really young,
but he was an Iraqi fucking veteran already
and had like come back.
And like he told me the story one time
about how like, yeah, you know,
one time me and my buddies were like raiding this house
and you know, there was a fucking,
there was a perp there or whatever the word was.
Like there was a fucking guy there trying to kill me.
And so like I, you know, I,
something happened.
I like fell back.
I pop off a few rounds and I see this guy looking down to me
and I'm like, yeah, right.
I'm about to die for my country.
You know, I'm doing what I can.
I'm trying to just trying to, you know, be a good person.
And, but he didn't dial, he didn't get shot.
He survived that particular situation.
But now here he was just like barely scraping minimum wage
in this fucking pizza shop, despite being like that level
of willing to put himself in danger for like my sake
and everybody else.
And like the world just didn't give a shit about this guy.
And like, I get it, you know, capitalism,
you are the value that you can give to the world.
But like, God damn, I just felt like the world
wasn't respecting this guy enough and other people like him.
That's why I said it was silly because of the way veterans
are treated.
Not, not because I don't respect them because like,
they're like the jobs they do, they do very well
and they have to do very well.
Otherwise they're dead.
So it's like, it's very respectful and it's very like,
you know, that's why I said I like war.
Like it's very romantic.
It's very cool.
Young boys all over the world.
They just, they just dream of being a tough soldier
and defending their country and stuff.
When Gibb hears about a bunch of young boys in one place,
he knows that's the place he wants to be.
Yeah, school.
School, kindergarten, yes.
But like, yeah, it's like, they're just,
they come home and then they're fucked.
Like if they had, especially if they got a leg blown off
or whatever, they get a nice award, you know,
like a little dinner for you.
Fucking, it's just, it's just a really bad thing
to have to go through and then you're not even
in a position of power.
You're just, you're just a grunt.
You're just a throwaway object of a human being
to the government that you signed up to serve.
And it's just, that's why I think it's silly.
Like it's just, that's why we need robots to take over
the jobs of the military.
Not because, not because of like, you know,
well actually yes, because it's better.
Because, because robots, they can't feel
and they don't deserve rights.
And fuck them, I hate robots.
True, true.
We just need Mecca and then we can just fight
with our Mecca and not have foot soldiers.
Anything we can do to lower the total number
of people who die in war would be a good thing, I think.
Drones, dude, Obama tech.
That's true, only drones kill 90% not the targets, you know,
they just kill like other people.
Obama invented Obamacare and also Obama tech.
Obama's scare.
Obama's scare, there we go.
What is it with you, it's scary today.
I don't know, this is the Halloween episode.
I don't know.
That's what these drones are called.
He invented drones, he invented Obamacare.
That's what it's called.
Yes, that's right.
Okay, okay, okay, I have to interject here.
Just catch up just like a few sentences before I continue
what we were actually talking about.
Back up, I realized that my favorite military force
was actually the British.
And I like the ship of the lines,
I like how they go around and they fucking destroy people
and minorities, and I liked how they subgrade people.
And I wish that it lasted longer.
Oh, good things, all good things.
Pretty good.
What time period?
Yeah, what time period, like when they were the big empire.
Oh, time period, like late, like second half 1800s
until they got fucking their ass kicked.
After the Yanks broke away?
Like around the time when India was in full swing.
Oh, right, okay, sure, sure.
I really love the whole red coat sort of uniform.
Yeah.
The funny hat.
Yeah, man.
You know, George Washington wanted to be a red coat
his whole life and he never fucking made it.
Instead, he just became president to the United States.
Gay.
Yeah, that's the national anthem.
Yeah, it's a sick power metal album.
It was from George at least.
I like England, France, and Germany.
I like all the western Europeans besides Spain.
If you follow me on Twitter, you know my notorious eight for Spain.
If you listen to this in Spain, I fucking hate you.
Get fucked moved to Portugal or France.
I'm gonna blacklist all of you.
All of you are blacklisted from listening to this.
Hey, weren't you calling for Portugal to be absorbed by France
just so that the peninsula would look better?
Yeah, I did that before I was red-pilled on Spain.
Before I was fucking red-pilled on.
Yeah, Portugal should absorb Spain.
Yeah, the opposite.
Anyway, so I like all that culture.
Anyway, back to what we were fucking saying.
Right.
Why would I, like on military, like joining the military
and like, you know, people with vets and stuff.
Sure.
Why would I fight for beliefs and reasons I don't believe
or I think fully understand because the government's always like doing like
weird puppet shit and they're never gonna actually tell me
what I'm actually fighting for.
I don't have like a national identity or anything whatsoever.
And even if I did, I'd better things do than like die for a cause
that I don't have a stake in.
And like I respect, you know, veterans for doing this stuff.
But I do not, I do not feel like I am American.
And I know that's like not, I think that's like a problem probably.
But I don't feel like I'm an American.
You're fucking globalist?
Is that what you're telling me right now, Munchie?
I am literally a globalist.
Close Photoshop and end yourself right now.
I am literally Photoshop.
Yeah.
I like...
I understand the sentiment though.
That's kind of like a millennial sentiment to feel more like a,
like maybe a human or a world citizen as opposed to a national identity.
It's basically the internet, you know.
Yeah, that's right.
You're able for the first time to really talk to people from other countries, you know.
It's usually just the English speaking countries.
But sometimes there's, you know, other people from Europe who speak English
like Danes and stuff.
They say, hello, I'm from Daneland.
I say fuck off.
It's me.
You say fuck off.
Yeah, but like it used to be like that, like earlier, when it's like your nationality
in a YouTube comment section would mean something and people would laugh at you.
I mean, I guess they'd still do if you're on a video about like nations.
Sure.
But it matters so much less now because people have friends across countries so often.
So normal.
Where the military is concerned there, it kind of reminds me of Metal Gear Solid 4.
It's been like a bunch of years since Metal Gear Solid 2 happened and like the world has
changed such that like national identity has been like completely removed from like
militaries.
Militaries are now just like these hired groups that just, you know, they go wherever and
they just kill anyone and like ideology or like national borders no longer have anything
to do with like the wars that are fighting.
It's just like economics and, and I don't know, just petty squabbles or something.
I don't know.
I feel like the best way to solve most major conflicts is for like a, an actual good Google
translate to translate everything from every country so that everybody could talk to everybody.
There is some issues though, like cultural, like the fact that I'm just, I'm not gonna
say anime, but like-
AI that would figure out, like know the language and then know the thing and then maybe-
But, but I'm just saying some people, like just as one example, there's some, you know,
like Islamic people who want the whole world to live under Sharia law and that doesn't translate
very, like even if you understand what they want, that's not like helpful for when they,
you know, want to conquer your country.
Yeah, what I mean, what I mean is like you have like, you know, let's say video games,
like video games shipped to all sorts of countries.
If you have people from those games talking to each other from different countries and
they're just kids-
Will that solve all our problems?
Yeah, video games will save the world.
What I mean is like, you make friends as kids when you're naive and you don't know about
like world political stuff and Sharia law and like, oh well, I didn't know that, you know,
if you're like, if you're in the Middle East and you're a kid and you're online and you
hit, you know, your friends with all these American people and then your dad says, Americans
are fucking horrible and they suck.
Like some of those kids are going to be like, well, wait, I like these guys.
They're fun.
They're cool.
I don't, I don't know.
And then it's sort of, it's sort of makes the next generation a bit less prone to hating
people instantly.
I think that's definitely happening right now to some degree.
Definitely.
It's just, you know, the technology hasn't fully penetrated.
There's not enough Dota going on in like, I don't know, Iran right now.
We need to up our Dota levels a little bit so we can make this happen.
Dude, dude, okay.
E-sports will save the world.
E-sports will save us all.
Yes.
Okay.
Japan.
Oh my God.
Seoul.
Fucking Iran, bro.
Iran.
Dude.
Top E-sports exporter.
Exports, all of the E-sports, every single one is from Iran now in the future coming up
2020.
Are you, I was looking into this.
I had no idea.
I'm going to sound like a fucking idiot to people who like know politics well, but you
guys know that Iran like wasn't even like a very conservative place, you know, respectively
until like the current administration took over like 40 years ago and like the 70s or
something.
Like women didn't have to like wear veils and shit all the time, but now they do because
like there's like just the people in charge now change the country that way, which gives
me hope that it'll change, you know, to be more liberal in the future as well.
Yeah.
That'd be good.
I don't know anything about the Middle East other than that there's oil and also people.
I know a lot about medieval Middle East, but not about a current shit.
By the way, hippo.
Well, that's fine.
I just want to know if you also believe this because it could seem like I agree with you.
Do you also agree that like 90% of positive change in the world currently could just come
from us just like just waiting for people to die?
Just like waiting for that.
I've had that thought like it's I've had that thought, but I feel like the amount of time
it would need because like people are still being indoctrinated to the old world values
by you know, family members and stuff.
It's not like people are all, you know, growing up being better or different or not.
But very much less so, I think, than previous incarnations of the world.
Less so, yeah.
Munchie, where that's concerned, it is always necessary that older generations die for certain
ideas to catch on.
For example, like the like our parents are probably less comfortable with like the amount
of time we spend interfacing with computers and like this kind of stuff.
So like to them, it's like a little weird and especially like two or three generations
before them.
They find it very strange that all this interpersonal communications going on and you know, maybe
it's bad for humans in some way, but like it's just the way that that culture is going.
It's inevitable.
So like that transformation is happening and like we're the generation that's comfortable
with that.
However, as technology evolves, as we're getting older, we're getting into our 20s, 30s, 40s,
50s, etc.
Like things like like VR that like plug us into virtual worlds, like it is a distinct
possibility that guys like us will all, we're all already too old to like really understand
that shit from birth and like we will be the old conjures who are like, oh, I don't understand
this.
Like this is weird.
And so already like things are being developed that we are not prepared for and that we will
need to die in order for like the society as a whole to absorb it and like process it
and be able to, you know, use it as effectively as it can be.
So that's absolutely a pot like not every human is not able to just change everything
about what they believe.
Sometimes you just got to die for the culture to evolve.
That's just a technology, though.
Is there an example you can think of like an ideology like that?
Absolutely.
Religion is, I mean, is a huge one.
Yeah, that's exactly what I was about to say, Nate.
Most millennials aren't fucking religious.
None of my friends know even who a God is.
Yeah.
They haven't ever even seen one.
When I see a millennial talking about God, I execute that millennial because they're
corrupting.
You know, this is just what I do every day.
I take those motherfuckers out windmill style, you know, bro?
Swing my arm around very fast.
That's windmill style.
Very fast.
Very fucking fast.
Yeah.
You don't even know, dude.
Also, just like everyone in the government is soon, like they're all like 100 years old,
just like in a couple years they'll be dead and we'll be able to be free.
Our government is like the oldest it's ever been.
I mean, people live longer, but like the people in office, like, like, I was just listening
to this the other day.
I believe it's like Chuck Schumer, Nancy Pelosi, and like whoever else, like these are like
the leaders or like the Democrats and like the Senate and the House or something.
They are all like over 70 and that's like, that's really, really fucking old.
That's still like 10, 20 years.
Like I feel like...
That's like the danger that they'll just stay there for another 10 years.
Like these people are not going to understand new ideas.
But the thing is...
There's a reason why young people push out old people, you know?
I know, but like I feel like the old people will try to cultivate younger people to take
their place and that's been going on forever and it will continue to go on.
I'm not saying things can't change.
I'm saying it's not just going to be as simple as, oh, once they're dead, there's no one
who wants to take their place who is also evil.
You're right about that, but like a generation doesn't last that long at its longest.
You know, maybe like 20 years.
So like it's true.
People like Nancy Pelosi, let's say that they groom, you know, to be like the new leader
of the Democrats and the Senate, someone like her, yeah, a pizza gate.
They bring in people that are like her, but just because they're younger and the culture
itself is changing, it's inevitable that little change is creeping just as this process goes
along.
And some of them are major.
Like the whole gay marriage question flipped over the course of like one year from like
outlawed to completely legal in everywhere in the United States.
Like it's like, I mean, that, you know, was building up for a long time, but sometimes
things like that can happen that quickly.
And it's just, you know, really the people can force their representatives to do what
they want when they just like make their voice heard about what they really fucking want people
to do.
Okay.
But we're totally off topic here.
And I did want to bring up one issue directly about the military that we haven't talked about.
So I for one was doing a lot of praising of like the men and women in the uniform.
But I did want to bring this up because I feel like a lot of people talk about this
when they're talking about the military, especially on the left.
So like, okay, so the military's job basically is to kill people who are doing bad things.
So let's talk about people who joined the military so that they have an excuse to kill
people.
Say with like the police force or, you know, like I'm actually bringing up as like, do
you think it's maybe good that we have that as an outlet for people who just really want
to fucking kill people?
And like we have two choices.
We can like institutionalize them and keep them away from society in some way, or we
can put them to work killing the people we don't want around.
And I'm not saying wars are justified, just like, you know, we shouldn't just kill people
who are bad.
But if we can find like, I'm just going to say, if you're an ISIS, you should die.
So I'm totally cool with you people all being sacrificial land to make our murderer population
happier.
That's what I'm saying.
Find like the general difference between UK and US armies that I've seen from various
documentaries and various, I don't know, it may be propaganda, I may be talking out
of my butthole, but stop getting trying to give me to join the British military give
guide.
Damn it.
It's it's just there's this feeling of like, if they want to kill people, why not put
them in, you know, with a gun?
Which I don't I don't like as an idea because you shouldn't enjoy killing.
And if you do, you're more you're more likely to, you know, you're more likely to be fucked
up in the head and make a bad decision and get someone else killed or like, you know,
the military has to be a tightly run ship.
You need to be, you know, all properly coordinated and communicating and doing your job as you're
told because if you don't, you know, whoever makes the plan, if that plan doesn't go right
because some, you know, asshole on the field is just decided, no, wait, I can get him.
I can get him.
Yeah.
Should and guns.
And then the whole operation is fucked and, you know, it leads to other deaths or casualties
or or losing ground or losing position.
It's like, I feel like people who are fucked up in the head enough to want to kill a lot
of people should just become hunters and shoot deer or something.
Yeah.
It's not really a place because in the military, I obviously discipline is the most important
discipline.
Yeah.
That's the word I couldn't think of the fucking whole time.
Discipline, I feel is the most important.
You can't you can't go you can't go to war and be like a like a guy with a club.
You got a gun.
You got to aim right.
Well, let me, you know, I just think some people in their nature have a killer instinct
and I guess like, and that's a good, like me, you know, I just kill, I kill millennials.
That's my thing.
I'm the millennium killer.
That's, that's me.
I am the Zodiac killer also.
I don't even know what I'm saying that like it's good that there's a place for people
to go if they want to kill people.
I don't know.
I guess that's what I'm saying.
It's better than not having that.
I just, I don't think everyone with a killer instinct is an evil person necessarily.
There are good ways you can channel that.
I guess that's my point.
I don't, I don't even know.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing.
I don't think a good way to cause like you can give them like therapy that can make outlets
for them.
Maybe if they really like hitting things, they could be like a guy who, a junk guy.
He smashes junk, junk into cubes with his bare fists or maybe, maybe you could pick
up drumming and just go wham, wham, wham.
And he could be a better person through, you know, something other than getting a gun and
killing a human being.
Like I said, hunting, like, like that is a thing that people can do.
It's killing, but it's like regulated and shit.
Yeah.
I guess I hear what you're saying.
I guess I'm really just like approaching the idea of like, I feel like if we had a bunch
of hardcore lefties on the show, what they would bring up is like that they don't like
the military.
I hear this from people like Jimmy Dorr, they freak out about like people are in, people
are cops or in the military because they want to hurt and kill people and they like that
feeling of control that it gives them.
I don't know.
Like you think that's a serious thing?
You think that's like a big deal?
I think it's, I think it's, it's, it's a kind of an unavoidable problem because you're giving
people power and there's obviously going to be people that want to abuse it.
And you know, it's not much you can do about it, except like having stricter training and
making sure people who are prone to abusing power get weeded out early on or banned or
stuff.
I don't know.
I feel like if you give a police officer a gun way too early before you know whether
he's going to shoot some guy or if the same thing with the military, if you give a guy
a gun before you know that he's not going to just shoot some random kid because he's
brown, like I'm not, I'm not going to get into a race thing, but like, you know, some
guys just like killing and I think you should, you should do it properly.
Yeah.
I don't want to be, I don't, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not a gay, I'm not gay guys, I'm not
lefty.
Oh, no, I'm gay.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
It's fine.
No, I hear what you're saying.
Oh, hey, let's, let's just, it's, it's the thing I feel like, like, I don't, I don't
want to be.
You don't like, yeah, I think I understand what you're feeling.
I don't want to be a world peace faggot because I know it can't happen.
People like war, people like fighting.
I like, you know, the fact that war is cool is, is the reason it's going to continue.
You don't have been thinking about recently.
I've just been thinking about how I tend to spend a lot of the time in the theoretical
realm when I'm talking about my weird utilitarianism and shit.
I think I'm going to try to incorporate more of like present day realities into the things
that I'm thinking about.
I'm just going to try.
I don't know if it's going to work out, but that, that's kind of why I wanted to talk
mostly about like the, the military right now because like, I guess ideally a military
would be like Starfleet and like those people are like full-time employees shut up, shut
up, shut up.
I'm just, I'm, I'm just saying, I'm just saying.
You said immediately going back to Star Trek.
Well, just to make a goddamn point about what I'm not going to talk about as much.
Oh fuck this.
All right, let's.
No, I get it.
I get it.
Okay.
Yeah, you understand.
Like what I like about them is like their military like has another job that they do
the full like all the time they are explorers, but then like when there's a conflict, you
know, that's when like they're called in to, you know, defend and shit.
Okay.
Let's talk about one more.
Let's talk about one more question.
Wait, what are you saying?
Hold on, hold on.
I just realized.
The military should be a Star Trek.
It should be all like Star Wars, Battlefront 2.
No.
Every single like, like they're just a bunch of stormtroopers on each side and then once
they get enough points, the one who can turn into Darth Vader and then lose the push.
Yeah.
Dude, it's so true.
That is what it is currently.
Now, right now, after I said that, Obama was like, oh my God, we should get this guy on
the phone.
You're a soldier.
You kill like 15 people.
You turn into Barack Obama.
Yes.
That's right.
You can do the whole smash.
You should get Jedi floors.
You go down.
You use your fucking Nobel Peace Prize, Nobel Phantasm and just decimate everyone with
love gay beams.
All right.
Yeah.
That's what happens.
Okay.
Let's talk about one more question about this issue.
What do you got?
Here we go.
Topical alert.
Oh no.
We got the trans community ban from serving in the military.
Trump did it.
What do you think?
Verdict.
Well, from what I hear, the whole thing, from what I hear that the issue was that people,
trans people, they go into the military, some of them do, to get the free surgery to change
gender.
Otherwise it would cost a lot.
And I think that's the reason, but obviously people are taking it as like, Trump hates trans
people and he just for no reason decides to ban them from the military and they are
their soldiers too.
People may have constantly taken the worst possible reading of anything Trump does as
like what it must mean, but yeah.
So I guess if those things about people abusing the system are correct, then I feel like it's
probably like drastic to ban all trans people, I guess, if you're, if you have trans surgery.
Like if you're already post-op and you just want to serve, it's like, yeah.
Or you could ban like the usage of military funding for your surgery and stuff and it
could be very specific surgeries that you could have, like getting a new arm if you
lost it, like stuff like that, banning them, I don't know.
It's obviously, you know, a thing that's getting people riled up, but I don't see too much
of a problem with it, except for the fact that people are fucking pissed.
You know what's interesting about it to me?
I think it might actually be a distraction tactic because it's so random that Trump might
have just done it to make people forget all the other shit that's going on, like the Russian
investigation and shit.
He actually just did it because he thinks it would like make people talk about that
a lot and like he's willing to, you know, just whatever, take whatever heat comes from
that to just distract people from the other shit.
I don't know.
I'm not too, you know, Trump politic, literate, knowledgeable.
It's inevitable that comes up a little bit when we talk about this shit.
I think basically we're all going to agree, like banning them across the board, like what
is that?
Doesn't really seem like the right policy.
Like there's probably some awesome trans people who really want to be fucking warriors.
Chief Monk, this is Shovel Knight from Famous Video Shovel Knight.
Oh no.
My favorite military was Ruin.
Oh, fuck.
But like, yeah, the thing about the Trump thing is like it was a tweet that he sent
out that said that Trump was not allowed in the military.
Dude, the generals were like, whoa, whoa, you didn't talk to us about this first, dude.
You just tweeted it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not that, not that.
But like the idea is that he tweeted it, but his actual policy like in writing might
be different and might be actually less extreme than what he said, which is maybe the case
a lot of the time.
Nobody cares to look it up.
If that's true, though, he should just shut his fucking fat face and just like deliver
it properly the first time and avoid the shit, unless the whole point of it is to distract
and enrage people.
Like maybe that's actually what he's, I don't fucking know.
Anyway, I don't even want to talk about Trump.
He's a fucking bummer.
Well, I have an actual other military topic, like side to side.
Oh lord, okay.
It's just like the idea.
Jesus Christ.
How dare you bring that into this sacred podcast?
Okay, God.
It's the idea of the spending of the budget.
Oh yeah, okay.
Military budgets, I think we can all agree are fucking ridiculous because of the facts.
They eat up such a massive amount of the budget.
It's ridiculous.
It's really just because of the way budgets work.
One year they say, okay, well, we need some more fighter jets, so we've developed this
new fighter jet.
We're going to build 100 of them and it's going to cost this many billion and we build
them and then the next year, well, in order to have that amount of funding for this year,
we need to spend that many billion again, otherwise we won't get it the next year and
we need that funding because we're used to it now and we don't want to not have it.
So they just make more shit that's never going to get used because they don't need
that many extra jets.
There's so much waste.
So much fucking waste.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it.
I just hate the way I hate the way budgets work.
Why do they work like that?
Every single thing that's wrong is because budgets work on that basis that if you don't
spend it, you don't get as much next time.
Oh, I like this.
You're talking about all the right things now.
Yeah.
Yes.
These are these are solvable problems.
Theoretically, that's what I want to talk about.
I'm I put up a pie chart of American discretionary spending for the entire government in 2015.
$1.11 trillion, so $1.11 trillion.
The military budget, 54% of all spending was the military $598.5 billion.
That's too much money.
That's too it's it's I mean, it's more than half.
It's more than half.
Fucking food and agriculture is 1% of the budget, transportation, 2%.
Social security, unemployment and labor is 3%.
And people are screaming about how social security is like killing the American budget.
Meanwhile, fucking military, 54% of the entire fucking budget science, all science, 3%.
3% of the fucking budget.
What is this?
What is this bullshit?
All right.
You know, this is not good.
This is not good.
Guys, we got to fix this shit.
I got to look up the UK budget things for that because I don't I've never really looked
it up.
It's probably less than America's because we're crazy.
We're crazy.
Well, like a percentage wise, it probably it might it might be around the same.
I mean, America.
Okay.
To be fair, America has unique responsibilities because like we are strategically placed with
our military like throughout the world in a like stabilizing fashion like that that
is true.
So like it makes sense that we would put more into it.
But like Jesus Christ, $598 billion.
And like, you know how much it would take to like make like state college free?
It'd be like it's like a couple billion or something and like everyone could go to college
for free.
That's like not even 1% of the budget.
Oh, it's fucking nuts.
And like they argue endlessly that there's no way to take money away from this.
You could just look at this and you know that's not true.
You know it's not true.
I want to know your opinion.
Do you what is your opinion on the U.S. being like an intervention, like just fucking like
like going around the globe and just kind of like intervening and shit?
What do you think about that?
Well, I don't like that we're being a bunch of fucking globalists probably using Photoshop
to make all our goddamn logos and shit.
So I'm not I'm not a big fan of that American flag made in Adobe.
Thank you.
Disgusting.
Fuck yourself.
Wait, I think that was your name.
I can't say that I like it, but like I get it.
Like America's got its shit together when it comes to just like, I don't know, like
building its economy.
I mean, this is getting less true over time as we go, but like for a while there, like
after World War II, America just had its shit together better than anyone else in the world
by far.
Yeah.
It was great.
It was really, really good at the time.
So, you know, those those legacies continue, but like things like us jumping out of the
fucking climate, the Paris climate agreement are like kind of fucking with our position
there.
Trump get your shit together.
Okay.
In terms of like being interventionist, like the the the super lefty position is to say
like, no, just like leave everybody alone, dude.
Like what are you doing going into these countries and like, I don't like the fucking, I don't
know anything about like world events really, but like there was some genocides that like
didn't we invade Libya or something under Hillary Clinton?
And like, why did we do that?
I don't know.
Under under President Hillary Clinton.
Yeah.
During her day back in like 2008 or whatever, or I don't know, like 2007 or something.
Like, okay.
That's that's not good.
No, that was under fucking Bush or whatever.
Sometime recently we invaded Libya or something like lots of people died.
I don't know why we did it.
I have no fucking awareness of these things.
Okay.
But like Iraq, right?
Iraq's like the obvious one.
For literally no good reason in terms of like what we said we were doing it for, like there
was all this cover about like it's got something to do with weapons of mass destruction or
like Osama bin Laden's there.
Like it was, it was like two years after 9 11 and ultimately it was completely unrelated
and we were like fed all this bullshit and like, okay, I just recently looked into this
shit.
Fucking Dick Cheney, vice president under under fucking the, you know, George Bush W.
He was like, okay, this is going to again be super obvious to anyone who knows anything,
but I'm a baby boy.
I just learned that he worked for, I believe it was like he was like the CEO of Halliburton
or like a really high ranking guy at Halliburton, which is a defense contractor that was given
contracts to go fucking fight in the Iraq war.
Like, like, this is like the most obvious thing I've ever heard now that I'm aware
of the facts.
Like they just started a war so they could make money and then like take the oil and
shit.
They just obviously benefited the people who made the decision to engage so obviously,
I don't know how the fuck they got away with it or people didn't make this clear to me
sooner.
I blame everyone else for me not knowing this fact.
Um, uh, I, yeah, I might be, I don't know if 100% was Halliburton, but it was like something
like that.
Like that's fucked up, dude.
Like what the, okay, whatever, I'm not going to go into it anymore.
But that's not good.
Okay.
Things like that are not good.
The only time America should do any kind of interventions thing is like, if we're like
asked to give help to like a country that's, I don't know, like fighting against like an
internal terrorist organization or something like, okay, obviously that's like a thing
that makes sense.
If there's a civil war going on somewhere, like, like in fucking, uh, Syria right now,
like it's a mess and it's not clear which side is like better.
But like, I could see why we should like do something about that situation.
We shouldn't.
Okay.
Like I don't think it's America's responsibility to be world police or like manage the whole
fucking world.
But like, I mean, at the very least to be cynical about it, we could at least like protect
our investment in the world and like try to make sure the world around us doesn't fucking
fall apart and we can still continue to like do trade and, you know, be a healthy member
of the world economy and make sure that the people we trade with aren't like, first of
all, like are able to like actually have materials that we can trade with and get get us things
that we want and you know, utilize their population to make goods and services that we need.
But then also like we can, and then we can worry about like the humanitarian thing, like
okay, maybe we'll maybe let's trade with North Korea.
You know, maybe we shouldn't.
That guy like literally has gulags where he enslaves political opponents who like do
nothing against him.
Like that's not good.
Let's not do that.
We should try to do something about that guy.
Not as much as the fact that he's got nukes all this other shit.
I don't know.
You hear him saying like, if it's, if it's in our best interest, I mean, and it doesn't
hurt anyone.
I mean, yeah, sure, go for it.
If there's a civil war that you could help end in a productive way, then that sounds
good as long as it doesn't like, you know, cripple America because America is good.
America is valuable.
We shouldn't let this place just like crumble so that we can like help people who are not
as well off as America because America is one of the, America is like Apple or like Elon
Musk or one of these like tech giants that like because we're doing well, the whole
world is doing well or better.
And we can provide things to the entire world that improve life for everyone.
You know, fucking smartphones, just technology in general.
You know, there's things that we did bad as well, but, but rap music, exactly Afro American
culture that we is our number one export.
Got all of that.
The only thing export in fact, yeah, it's great.
That's just, yeah, like, I mean, that's why that's the thing with like countries like
Sweden that are literally cucking themselves out of their country just to like, they're
so sorry that they're white.
They're so sorry that they're fucking white and they just want to, they just want to give
up and hand their fucking country to like anyone who'll take it.
And right now that's a lot of middle eastern people and like, they're just making their
country shitty.
They're making it worse.
There's like rape gangs and I don't know, I don't know the full facts.
Okay.
I admit fully.
I don't know all the full facts, but like Sweden is like a number one place that
wants to cuck itself because it's, it's so liberal.
It feels bad about even doing well at all when there's people out there who are suffering
and they don't understand the way that like economics work, whereas like it's not like
if you're doing well, you're taking things from other people.
You're just, you're, you're making yourself better off and that, and then if you trade
with other people in a consensual way, you can help them too.
That's like the basis of economic growth, just in general and commerce.
They should just try selling IKEA furniture to the police.
Exactly.
That'll frustrate them.
You shouldn't, you shouldn't undermine, just to finish my point, you shouldn't undermine
your own ability to be productive or helpful.
And you know, maybe I'm exaggerating what that's like in Sweden, but you know, they've
got other issues.
Like they're, they're, they're a big welfare state that I hear, I don't know this for
sure.
I hear is crumbling there.
Um, like they're just taking out too much fun.
They can't afford it.
They're too socialist.
I don't know if that's true or not, but that's what I've been hearing and I'd be interested
to look into it more and hear what people have to say about it.
You can't take on everyone's burden all the time.
You got to look out for yourself.
Every man has a responsibility, every person has a responsibility to take care of their
own shit.
I agree.
And then once you've got that just in order, then you can worry about helping other people.
And America, you know, has had its shit together for a while.
You know, maybe it's getting a little shaky or whatever, but it'd be nice to help people
if we can do that without fucking ourselves.
It's just like in Minecraft, when, when you're building, when you're building, you know,
you go out into a server and you're like, well, these guys need help, but I need to
build my house first.
So I'm safe for the night.
So I'll do that first.
I'll, I'll, I'll worry about my shit and then I'll go help when I know that I have
a safe place.
Now I understand.
Now it makes sense.
I, I think I'm not totally, you know, uh, solidified in this, but I, I'm, I'm, I'm thinking
I'm toying with that.
Maybe we should, like, you know, I don't really like the intervention.
And I think that maybe sometimes it's better for the world if we just let them toil and
like not police and just let, you know, uh, the world change and like let people die and
like let, you know, because that is like, we always go to war.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, okay.
I'm just saying like that is exactly what Star Trek, this big Libcuck show, that is what
the prime directive is all about and they grapple with this issue all the time.
And it's about how like all the time when like the fucking, uh, you know, whatever the
westerners came to America, uh, and they fucking took it over, like they just fucked
those people over.
Like you can't just integrate yourself into a society that you are, or like the conquistadors
in South America.
Yeah.
They fucked that place up.
Uh, like you cannot just invade a place and expect them to like immediately accept
like the things you bring them.
You have to let people develop independently.
And if you, if you can get involved with them in like a small way, cause you know, we're
all on earth.
It's not like in Star Trek where you can just avoid a planet entirely.
You know, then you can, you know, slowly work to bring people, you know, into the fold where
you are.
But like, like even Star Trek, a big Libcuck show acknowledged like, yes, we absolutely
have to let some people die in order for this society to grow itself and us to not completely
fuck it up.
Yeah.
I really think the main thing that's, that's making like America and other western countries
great again in political stuff all over the world is that one, it's PR like he was showing
like, oh yes, we're such a great nation that will help other people because we're so powerful
and you shouldn't fuck with us cause we have the power to spend on, on helping other countries
fight their wars or whatever.
Uh huh.
Um, you know, there's that, there's the show of like, we're the best where you can do all
this cool shit.
But there's also like the idea that if you don't intervene in certain places, they may
be taken over by people who you really don't want to be in power.
Like let's just, you know, the general idea is like, oh, well, if we don't help the right
side of win this war that's going on over here, there may be another North Korea emerging
in the future and we don't want that.
We don't even want the possibility of that.
We want to make sure whoever wins the war is on our side and they like us.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
In, in the, in the beginning, in the beginning of North and South Korea, South Korea was
eating shit.
North Korea was doing pretty fine and not, you know, great.
Okay.
Uh, but like it, so, so that's how they got the head start and now they're fucking insane.
I mean, you know, they're always insane.
They're always calm.
But be a good one.
I mean, they were doing fine for themselves economically speaking somewhat at least.
Is it just because they had such ties with China?
Yeah, yeah.
They were just relying on that.
You're right.
Okay.
Uh, and, and so that's why I find like, like having just another North Korea seems pretty
far-fetched me because, okay, just take the obvious example, Middle East, some fucking,
you know, Syria, I guess, Syria just becomes a fucking super al-Qaeda.
They're, they're, the export is now 9-11 since their primary export.
Okay, right.
Uh, I don't, that, that government just will not last like, like, they just will not last
that long because it's built upon, you know, crazy shit that has no, like it has no grace
period of like being a good quote unquote country.
It just starts out shit and it will be continued to be shit, probably be, you know, probably
be on the map for like, you know, 10 years or something, but it will eventually crumble.
And I'm always thinking about things in like, like decades span.
You know, you're absolutely right about that.
It's just like, like North Korea really wasn't that big a deal at first after the Korean
War and it was just that like, you know, we just left it alone.
Like we knew they were doing crazy shit over there, but we just left them alone because
like, you know, the China's got their fucking back.
What are we going to do?
They got that shit covered.
So like it's just over time, they just got crazier and crazier and like we, we still didn't
address the problem.
And now we're at a point where they're like really close to having like the ability to
launch nukes against like the western coast of the fucking United States and they can
already do it to South Korea if they fucking want to.
Um, let alone Japan.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Japan too is within their range, I think.
So like that's, that's not good.
It's not fucking good.
Yeah.
Um, also like, yeah, like the whole rise of, of, you know, Nazi Germany, like they started
taking over a few places, but because they just had a huge war, everyone was like, ah,
we shouldn't really get involved.
Hitler was on the cover of Time Magazine or Hitler was man of the year twice, as I recall,
once because he was the best guy ever and they loved him and second because he was the
worst guy ever and he didn't like him anymore.
And they loved him as well.
Yeah.
They thought it was he, they really liked his SS uniforms.
They're really.
Before, you know, we end.
We're going to questions after this, so no worry, but yeah, yeah, go on.
We got, I looked up the, the, the whole British budget spending on stuff.
Oh good, good.
Remarkably different.
Uh, the, the total spending is like 762 billion.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, defense budget is only 44 billion.
Wow, okay.
So like, um, educate.
So like, we're like more than ten times more.
Yeah.
Education is like double.
But we're ten times more than fucking pussy.
You little bitch.
You don't even invest in fucking, see that's, yeah, okay, sorry, go on.
Yeah, even fucking keep Hong Kong, what the fuck asshole.
Yeah, I know dude, embarrassing.
The healthcare is like 138 billion, so I can see why people are like, you know, fuck
that shit.
Yeah.
Cause it's, it's generally okay, but it's, it's pretty fucking expensive and it doesn't
work very well for a lot of people.
Like I understand, like a lot of liberals just like, they look at this graph and they
think to themselves like, Jesus Christ, like my life is fucked right now.
Like imagine if I had had like a free college education instead of like having to, you know,
do whatever I had to do and not have the student debt.
Like wouldn't that be great?
And they're just looking at this budget.
They're like looking at all these billions of dollars just being thrown away and they're
like, I just want me a piece of that.
I want me a fucking piece of that so I can like square my life away.
You know, and maybe it's, maybe it's a reasonable request.
Like if I just hadn't had to take out these student loans, I wouldn't have gone under
financially, blah, blah, blah.
But you know, the only thing is I don't really have a lot of sympathy for people who feel
that, unless they really are in a bad way.
And I know I was totally privileged in my life, but I just like, just take responsibility
for your shit.
Take responsibility for your own life, you got to find your way out.
This is the situation you're in everybody.
So just don't cry about it.
Don't bitch and moan and feel free to campaign for what you think are like fair laws.
If you want to make college free for everybody, like, hey, go for it, campaign all you want,
no problem.
But like accept the reality of the life that you have and make the best of it, however
you can.
Be financially solving people.
Live in a tiny ass apartment like me so that you can pay off your student loans faster
and then you'll be financially free.
That's what I'm doing.
That's what everybody should do.
You know, just, just get your shit together.
That's what I'm saying.
Just from my privileged position of a guy who had really, you know, I don't know, middle
income parents.
I did just fine, grew up in a great place, had no major problems whatsoever.
That's me.
That's me saying all these things about how you need to get your fucking shit together,
you lazy sex shit.
That's me.
Pull yourself up by your bootstraps and then you set your boot on fire.
Speaking of that, welfare is like 113 billion for last year, by the way, this is all last
year, 2016.
How much is ours?
I don't know.
I closed it.
Let me pull it up again.
Yeah, go on.
113.
There's only three things on this.
There's pensions, there's healthcare and there's welfare and those are all over 100
billion.
And defense is like, it looks so small, it's like 44 billion.
It's like a libertarian government, like I can barely even see the suspense building.
I don't see, okay, there's no welfare, but it must be under social security, unemployment
and labor.
That's a total of 3% 29.1 billion and this is in 2015.
There you go.
What was it for?
It was like 170 some million for you guys?
113 billion.
That is a lot more than we spent.
So, 10 pounds, not dollars, so that's a lot more.
Yeah, it's a lot more and proportionally it's a lot more, yeah, just a lot more.
What do you know?
It's fucking more different than I would have expected.
Our fucking military is just so, needs so much, such a fucking money thing, takes up
so much fucking money, okay, whatever.
Well, let's move on.
Okay, guys, we all set.
Rolling for con crimes.
Yeah.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait.
I love the Ottomans' old big old hats.
Oh, they get their fucking sword.
Shwing!
And then they got their big old fucking hat.
And then they go that's what they say
Oh, and then they fucking kill those goddamn fucking
Austrians give give you need to see I just got a picture this hat
I'm trying to
I've got the picture at this fucking hat dude. You have to see this. No, you do have to see this
I know what they look at this
Yeah
I've ever seen that's not even a joke. It's ridiculous. Well, you know why they're so big why?
It's because that's where they keep their wives
That's how Islam you also that oh
By the way, also an actual thing fun fact back when World War one was like first starting
Like the like fashion-related the France like put on their fucking sick-ass like colorful uniforms
They're all like kind of hard-moving and also like colorful and then like they were just walking up to a fucking German
Like like before and then Germans could just easily spot them like on the fucking horizon
Just mow them down like one after another machine gun fire. So like they're uniform just made
Massacred all of them just fucking
obliterated
Is it is a time is an age gone by where where war was was like
Civilized and you're stood on one hill and with your flag and you saw the other guy and you went
And then you walked slowly towards them and since muskets such you had to get real close before you could fire
And then they just kept doing that and guns got better and then
Now everyone's hiding in bushes. You know when that changed that mostly changed during the American Revolution, baby
Thank You Native Americans for teaching us that shit. Oh, don't
What do you mean? No insane
That's when they they had to fucking fight with guerrilla tactics. That was like considered dishonorable at the time
So, you know like they didn't like it, but that's how we fucking what I well, okay?
I guess I didn't I didn't like that
They invented God damn it. We took we culturally appropriated it from the Native Americans
I would say the first modern war was like, okay
Either I would say like the seven years war. No, not this fucking seven years
I'm gonna say it was Sonichu versus the four cent garbage American Civil War the American Civil War
That shit's the first good one. Yeah, the first good one since a lot of people died also guns were big
Awesome, I don't know anything about Vietnam war because all the video games about it have Vietnam
Video are there a lot of video games about the Vietnam War? I mean there's a lot of comics and movies
I don't know. There's like battlefields Vietnam kill kill Chinaman the game
There's probably a couple in there. All right. That's it. All right, so we're done with military stuff
Let's we we agreed 10 out of 10 good
Semper fight Dallas to all our armed forces. That's right. Okay
Here's some questions. All right, here's some questions, okay
Here's here's our good buddy at Nat Blasphemous. This guy makes a bunch of art for us. He's a cool guy
Would you give up content creation at least publicly if you could live wherever you wanted and have all needs provided all
need you think about that
I'm imagining like
Like a really crystal clear like blue water beach log house with a pier
And a straw hat roof. I like that, but also I
Guess if all needs means this guy saying everything you want is all taken care of pretty much
Yeah, well a fucking course who wouldn't give up no no see see that that's where you're wrong the answers
No, of course. Yeah, because if you're not doing something you just shrivel up and don't my name exactly exactly right
That's what I want to do. You have to get you have to give up content at least publicly
Yeah, so like you could make it on your own if you wanted to I guess, but you just wouldn't release it
It'd be like your own. I just release it under a pseudo name. Yeah, it like that'd be I think I would not take this well, okay
I I would assume that the the gist of this question is like about if you would still like give up doing this kind of work
Or whatever if like, you know, you can do that sort of or you know releasing it to the public like I I
Mean no because there'd be no point to me doing the kind of work
I do on YouTube if people couldn't see it because the whole point of it
Yeah, people see it. I think I think what the general idea of the question is
Yeah, do you have a creative outlet that doesn't involve people watching it on YouTube? I think you're right on the Internet
I don't I would say I would say yes because I like sculpture
I like the idea of building sculptures if I had like plenty of money and no reason to
Worry about shit. I would just I would make Easter Island
I would buy an aisle I would be on an island and I would make sculptures and then when I'm dead people be like what the fuck happened here
He he also he says like all creative content whatsoever though, right?
He said content creation
Yes, but he said he said he said he said publicly so like you could do it on your own if like
I would
Statues I would I would build cool fucking statues over an island until I'm dead and then then people will find them
In my head the whole time
That wouldn't be public. That would be like invasion of private property. Yeah, let's let's just say nobody can find it for whatever
Okay, well, it's gay. No, I like making things and people to see yeah, I like
me I
Agree completely. Well, all my needs met includes a human being so like they're the you know company
Like I wouldn't want to live on my own forever. That's just generally shit
Okay, we're just talking about the content creation. You can just still be out and talk to people and whatnot
You know dumb question because it doesn't make any sense. It doesn't really make any sense. That's okay
That's like everything except the one thing that you also like
Like
I'd like everything and and that to mean everything not everything minus
Fuck you. I'm lost in the woods on this one. Okay. Let's go to another question here at read or Darrell asks
What are your thoughts on the announcement for the American live-action TV show adaptations for one piece cowboy bebop and
SAO is that TV show?
Oh
about
Cowboy bebop may actually be good because it's already pretty westernish
I mean, I could see that that making a neat transition one piece
Garbage instantly. I know it will be. Mm-hmm. I
Mean, I've seen cosplayers white people cannot look like those characters at all
I don't think anyone can in real life. They're too cartoony. I just don't want to see that
No, I've seen I've seen a pretty good. I've seen a pretty like a few pretty good-looking Japanese men being Sanji and
Yes, that's they pull that off. But like imagine imagine like someone trying to be Frankie just to picture it like no
No, it can't be done. It cannot be done
Okay, go get what were you saying give I
Was gonna say it's like the Super Mario Bros movie what Bowser's just a guy
Well, that was cool because it was so fucking weird, but I mean at the time I was very confused
But like that's what I'm imagining. You'll be like, oh, it's a guy
But he's got like tattoos of stars on his hands
I don't even it's legit like TV shows of cowboy bebop SAO and one piece
They're getting TV like I heard about the cowboy bebop movie like that was a thing a TV show. Is this real?
Where's he getting this news? I don't know. I'm just going to assume that it's correct
I did I did hear the one I did hear the one piece one. Yeah, that's the one I did here
I'm gonna enroll in a high school. I hope you want to join the football team with me
I would love nothing more than that
Jesus Christ
The only thing they'll make this good if we've got mum key D
Luffy on the team. Let's bring him in. I like the idea that it's not just a high school setting
But it's a high school setting where it's just like he is. He's just into football. Yeah
Oh kind of like those
Character that it's about remember one cuz remember that one like the sometimes Oda will do like a little side thing where he tells like a
Like a three-page story about like all universe straw hats
Remember the one where Luffy was like a super studious student and all he wanted was to like get into like the number one school in the country
And he was like that was his like pirate king thing like be the best student and get into this school like that's you know
You don't remember that one. I
Don't that's where shanks is like their teacher and you just told him to be degenerates and like not worry about it
Are you talking about like the little pages of like question answer things?
No, they weren't the SBS like so Oda's done a couple of these like
Stories where it's just like all the care all the straw hats are like different characters in like a different world like there's one where
They're all literal family members and like, you know Zoro's the dad
I'll have to link you. Yeah, they're great. They're really really good
Me Luffy. I'm not gonna. Oh, I bumped told you to some guy
Fucking way. God. This is a fucking nerd. Oh my god. That was another member of my fucking anime crew
We're gonna bond now in the kitchen. Oh
What a nightmare right? Okay, let's move on. This is this topic is killing munchie
I
Okay, here we go
Benjamin with at Benjamin Whistle asks what game have you played the most would you say it's your favorite?
Undertaker
I'm gonna Google search how many
Okay, I'm just gonna say the game. I've played the most without a doubt is
Decidia Final Fantasy the first one for PSP. I played that game every night for hours for years every day
And I it was the greatest. I am a real Final Fantasy fan guys. All right. I love Final Fantasy
It's my favorite and this was everything I ever wanted finally made real
Yeah
Damn, I hate that guy. I'm gonna beat him up. It sounds like a bitch
Yeah, that that game wouldn't isn't my favorite. No, but it is really really good and I loved it
I was doing coming out from ps4 soon. Yeah, Ramza fucking Ramza. Okay, but I'm fine now
Ramza one half
Hey, I played by far the most of Team Fortress 2
2,672 hours on record first played that in like
2012 I think early 2012. Okay. It's one of my favorite games. I mean not my favorite
But yeah, what like top five I would say I love team Fortress 2 too bad
It's game horrible now, and I would never fucking play it ever except for the time. They're like legacy servers. No
No, oh, it's just dead. It's just gone. Yeah, that sucks
Gibb is yours is it RuneScape the one you've played the most. I'm just guessing here. Is it RuneScape?
Um, I would say no because World of Warcraft
I would when I was into World of Warcraft. It was like all right. I've just woken up time to turn on computer
Warcraft I gotta play I gotta do it. Oh, I gotta get ready for school. I can I can get in 30 minutes of World of Warcraft
You know that was me the good thing was that I it didn't affect me too much
That's good like other aspects of my life. I was already a loser. Oh, it was all fine
It was all it was all meant to be
Probably one of the heights of my gaming career was one day
I was playing Mario Luigi Bowser inside story and mine like I was I was just I just stayed up all night just playing it and
And I like I wasn't even like at the final boss or any like it like you know story moment
I was just like the fucking like just the third level just midway through my mom knocks on the door like hey
It's it's time for school. You have to go I open the door and I'm fucking just like crying like mom
I want to keep playing Mario. Oh
No
Please I got my knees. Please. Let me play Mario. Please and she's not healthy
Christ what she do what you do sure I guess
So you just got to stay home and play Mario this day. Yeah. Yeah, just that day and then like the next day
I just didn't care. I just didn't care the next day. Yeah, all right
I just cared so much about playing just like I didn't even like beat the game
I just continued to play for like a couple hours and then I just shut it off like for just some reason
I just wanted to play very badly. The way what those were fake tears
I was legitimately crying for the like I just couldn't I couldn't play Mario for like six hours. What the fuck?
Sometimes I like that before uh-huh go ahead give I
Felt that though those feelings before it's like like I'm just really into something and I
Deliberate it on whether it was okay to bring my my GBA to school
Like if it was it really into playing fire emblem or something. I was like, uh, I've been playing it all night
I want to play more
Could I bring it to school? No, no, the bullies will take it
I never I never had bullies that would take things but I I always felt like if I had my
GBA I wouldn't be able to bring it out during class because the teacher would take it
I wouldn't be able to bring it out during you know in between times because the people would say what are you a gamer?
Kill me. Oh, no can't take that risk
So I never brought it to school, but there was one time when I saw a guy he brought it to his to school
I was like you motherfucker. You're so brave. How do you do that?
He's the real veteran here not the name of these fucking, you know boys and blue
Did you learn from that? Yeah, you're right. Did you learn for that? Did you bring it after that? No, no
I brought my game boy to school like for years every day
I was just so paranoid of like of of of turning on the game and sitting down and then having people come over and say
Oh, what game you playing and then I would shrivel up and be like, I don't know
That's what I would have said
Okay, here's a here's a good question. I'm at rum raisin seven asks. Um, why is munchies so bad at Kirby?
You know, that's a good question. It's a very good question
That's what that is that's a fake thing. It's a fake fucking made-up fact
Whether you can check with the government
Go check out the the Kirby race. Everybody's is great. Um, okay, here we go
Yeah, you that's true, you know, that's really it's funny that like it's just because you got more invested than me
Yeah, because you got more invested you got rocked harder
At Jip clip C asks why don't PCPs last for more than an hour now?
Actually, I know the reason I just want them to be longer. Well, we're already an hour and what like 20 minutes
Yeah, we're over an hour and a half now. So I don't know what fuck you dude. I think I think what it is is that
Sometimes
There's less people and if there's loads of people and it's a big topic. Yeah, everyone wants to get everything in but now
When the topic sucks
Sometimes it does and none of us have like enough to say each even if we all get a turn so
That's why
Pretty robust. It was with three people. It was still over an hour
There was gonna be way more people like and by way more I just mean like six or
Two more but they just didn't show up. So we were like we were we gonna flowers
I was at least I did had no idea working talking about this actually turned out pretty good
Yeah, the reason though the reason though that everyone's like, oh fucking. Why are they short now?
I've seen that multiple places because unlike the past two
I think but both times have just been like we've been in the middle talking and it's been like alright done BCPS over now
Bye, I don't I don't really think we need to go on that long
I mean we make a good product and we wrap it up. I'm pretty happy with how long they've been going up to now
Yeah, it's just both times
I've met a bit. I've made a big stick about Nate closing the PCP and so they probably like oh much. He's fucking right
We do you're right? I don't know. I'm pretty ill like this one is longer than I expected to be and I'm perfectly happy with that as well
Yeah, yeah, I'm having me. This is fine. Yeah, I'm sick of this shit. I'm pretty fucking fed up TBH
Okay, let's let's let's see. I got the answer another question. Um, oh
Okay, no this question fucking sucks
Okay, maybe you guys can tell me what this means at sys gum 69 our old friend
Can you talk about your head mates?
What does that mean the fuck is that I don't like like the people live with me in my head? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah, you know
You know what head mates are? I don't think so the term dude. I have so much like a topa. I have so many head mates
They're like topless, but inside of your physical brain. Is it like a split personality thing? Is that what it is?
It's it's okay. So here's what you do you pretend that you're insane. That's the first right pretend
That you're insane then when you when you're making your sick-ass fucking form posts that you just you know
You love to make every single day you laugh so hard making these posts that you just drop your fucking pretzels out on the ground
That those sick ass whores while you're making those
Just like in it. Just like enter colon
Barack Obama
Darth Sidious, you know the Martian from Looney Tunes any of those guys colon. Yeah, just have him say something retarded
Just say that okay, it'll make it better. That'll be your head mate
Just pretend that those fictional characters are inside of your brain
And then you say funny fucking quips that make everyone like you on your phone post guy online tumblr fucking
Yeah, yeah, all those or chan.org slash co all those nice places
Just get your fucking head mates to say some sick ass
Nihilistic wicked sense of humor shit and everyone will love you. That's what head mates are
Yeah, I I've done this a couple times
Like like quite that intense but like
You know every so often like I'm walking home from school and I'm like I
Feel like talking about something, but there's no one there
So I've just imagined what the possible counter arguments could be like a person doesn't agree with what I said
So I just argue with him and just talk in my head. They don't have different voices. They're just like saying different things like
Blah blah blah. I don't know about that and then you know, I just go go through the motions of this thinking about it
It's usually just to think it's just a way to think through just to imagine that there's another person that I am being also
Is that what it is or is it just I love I mean, I'm sure that's practically what it is or you know in a practical sense
Yeah, that's what it is. What people say is this is the fictional characters live inside their brain and then they talk to them
sometimes and and
I don't have characters and and and then sometimes in and on a blood moon one of those fictional characters will take over their physical form
Then like role play that character themselves these people are so special and impressive and amazing
I I wish I was as cool as them. They're so cool
Vampire Hunter D is now at the front. He's at the front now. I am him
I
Like the fact that vampire Hunter D has the has the feels the knees to explain that he is yes
This incredibly quiet reserved character who changed my entire way acted by never saying a fucking word announces himself in the room
I am
Everyone it's me. I'm real. I'm here. Yes. That's very in
That's the question the the question was
Can you talk about your head mates was the
Yeah, the rich personality of Darth Maul really takes up a large chunk of my head
Yeah, he's got a lot to say let me tell you
He's a fucking asshole
He's a fucking red-pilled Trump supporter piece. No. No, I go with him all the time about shillery
I should be fucking locked up and he just won't write fucking you won't take any of it
He's a big John Oliver fan
He always wants to switch the channel even when I'm trying to watch you know Sam hides world peace to get my red
pillow might my swastika's in
He's won't use won't fucking do it. I fucking hate you Darth Maul. I've got Odie from Garfield
Yeah, Odie and Darth Maul do not get to well together at all. They're like
They are exact Odie's the most migtail fucking
Oh
Cuz he's always making fun of Darth Maul's masculinity and it doesn't get pretty
The munchie actually has a lot of characters in this fucking head of course of course and I just Napoleon Bonaparte
Just had just hanging out. He's a military guy. I should have had him come to the front of consciousness for this debate
That would have been helpful
Unfortunately, all he does is play well in league and he doesn't have time to come to the front of my
So, you know, it's it's a real shame
Maybe yeah, we can one day we can do like a bonus episode. That's us with our head mates, you know
Just like being themselves that'd be nice. That'd be a nice episode
What what makes you guys have hold hippo? Oh good question
Give
I
Have hippo potter mess in my head. He's a big
Yeah
Is that like it's like like an off-brand hippo
I
Store hippo. Yes. He's a dime store. He's the he's like the bizarro world
More like more like scare store
What about you again, what do you got?
Tell me secrets
You look like you got a couple of you you hack-a-show characters
Just I don't know what you you hack-a-show. That's why you explain themselves. Oh
And we're still recording get the fuck out of here
Hey everyone Ben St here just wanted to pop in and give you all little context and what you're about to hear so
On the day of this PCP we had agreed that afterwards
We would all get together and hang out in the chat in the discord have a little group call have a good time
So I come in two hours after the PCP was meant to start and I see that
Everyone's in the call and I think ah
Surely the good times have already started surely my friends are just there waiting for me waiting for me to come and join
Them and have a real good time
so I get in the call and
Well
Yeah, and the rest is history. So I just wanted to give you that give you that context
So let's see how that plays out shall we?
Yeah
Okay, go on good what you say
You were you were telling us about your you-hack-a-show headbates you're telling us about yes, yes, but Yu-Gi-Oh headspace
I have in me
I have in my Yu-Gi-Oh headspace
The entire cost of Beyblade mushed into one character
right, yes, no one has the Beyblade
Yeah, the Beyblade. Oh
No, no, I have Uchiha Sasuke right and
um
Fucking
I think you got a headmate that's a an old world war two fighter pilot piloted by an anthropomorphic baguette
It's not even a fighter airplane not even like a royal like not even like a fighter ply just an airplane
An airplane
He doesn't like people flying inside him. He says you should fly on your own
Your own ways you should be like the bird and take wing. I'm not go don't go inside me. Don't go inside me
Uchiha Sasuke does not he's a real pigtail planes going their own way
You know, he doesn't need their these other guys. He's got his own life. He doesn't need you to make him a complete plane
Okay, there's one last question that we have to address. Wait, wait. I got it. I just I just have the thought
Yes, you know like like ghost pirate ships. What about ghost planes?
Okay, Emily ever the aeroplane robo. Yeah, she's not there
And then and then it's a plane going in a circle and it's like how the hell do you get in there?
What you're in there? It's like oh spooky
It's spooky. It's kind of like in um
Scooby-Doo. For some reason it reminds me of breath of the wild only breath of the wild isn't flying
Okay, if you combine a breath of the wild with the one before it in the sky
No
Yes, shadow the head that's what i'm trying to think of. Yes, what i'm trying to say is I like shadow the head
He just puts he just puts one foot in front of the other he's fucking there. Yeah, he's there instantly one step
He doesn't need to be quick
I guess is why we shouldn't let the women fly because Amelia our air are fucking died
Am I right bros boat? No, he nailed it dude. He nailed it. Okay. Here we go. Do we have any more questions?
There's one last question that we have to answer. Uh, okay. Here we go at
Muhammad H asks oh now that canada allows sex with animals
Is there any animal in particular that you want to fuck?
Sends the skeleton
Oh
It's the natural answer of under tail
This is kind of devolved into a bonus episode. I know it really dead. This is by oh shit
I forgot we've got we've got shirts everybody. I should have mentioned the beginning go buy our fucking shirts that were there
There's links. There's links in the description everywhere. There's bonus episodes become our patron a five dollar patron
You get more of this kind of nonsense. Like I can't believe we're still going with this
Everyone stand for the pledge. I pledge allegiance to sands. I love my sands
Please let me see your glorious face and I just want to be with you
Can't you just fucking understand you simple bitch
Special appearance by the under tail or five eight seven everybody
Uh, uh, yeah, go go be our patron five dollars for bonus episodes
Uh, you you get into our discord at any amount. We talk to people there to go do that shit buy our shirts
We got a bunch of merch up on the store now those remember those pcp
Patreon shirts you only get the good ones for one month and they're going away forever
Just like the old logo. So act now if you want that shit, uh, go get on the red bubble
And there's this other shit on the fucking print all over me pay-alm store
My favorite thing about the military is all the child slaves so I can ground into lube
I like that too. Uh, uh, follow our patreon at tpcrastinators and send us questions every week that we answer just like we did here
Using hashtag ask pcp and that is all the announcements. Go buy our shit everybody. Give us money so we can do more of this
I really like how our the announcements of patreon stuff was interjected
Occasionally by the undertaker. I think that should be a staple. It's appropriate of the patron plug is that the undertaker should be there
Sorry, I'm going on vacation
Oh, he's gone. Oh, he he evaporated he's gone
Well, maybe that tradition just ended find out next time everybody on the next episode
Thanks for listening to the Peruvian Crestinators podcast everybody. Wait, did we even answer that last question? We uh, uh, yes
Sam's the skeleton is the answer
Yes, Sam. Don't remember what it was. We're it. We're done. All right. Thanks for listening everybody. We'll see you next time. Bye. Bye
Goodbye. I'm back
That art ended very quickly
Right now, I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick I'm jerking
Myself, I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
You