Why dance around it? There are bad AVGN rip-offs.
Yeah, but then like they have like two minute intros and it's like he's a guy, and he plays a game.
And it's like just showing like their entire fucking collection of games and just literally like them bringing it up to the camera.
And then it'll just be like, Dragon's League is the game of the day.
You know exactly what I'm talking about!
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am Digibro. I'm going to be your host for today, and I have with me my co-hosts and friends.
Mr. Jesse Wood.
Roast beef and whiskey.
There you go. Roast beef and whiskey.
Uh, Hippocrit.
Siton.
Uh, the best guy ever, also known as Nate.
Or Guy.
And the DeVoo.
Aw yeah.
And today we're going to be talking about the subject of reviewer rules.
Now to explain what I mean by this.
We sure do.
We are the best.
To explain what I mean by reviewer rules, this is sort of a multi-part subject that we're going to go through one part and then the other.
We're going to be about rules that reviewers have for themselves or that people have for reviewers about how reviews are made.
Rule number one, don't be a reviewer. Do literally anything else creative.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good rule.
And the second half of this podcast we'll be talking about the rules which reviewers apply to shows.
Like what rules they have about what makes a show good and things like that.
And a lot of this is probably going to be us coming at these rules from a critical perspective of the rules themselves.
To start with DeVoo, I wanted you to talk about there's something that you called the reviewer rule that me and you get in our comments all the time and that we laugh about whenever we get it.
Do you remember this?
Is this like a definition that people post or something?
No.
DeVoo used to always complain because you have to be objective.
Sure.
It's the rule where they say, oh my god, this video is not objective and therefore it's bad or you're not being very objective.
You know it's funny about that.
It's a rule that carries over from back in the days of, well the current, it's the still living days of consumer reports.
They think you're supposed to be a consumer reports guy.
They think you're supposed to be an interviewer guy on the news media.
It's funny to me that people still make that kind of like demand.
They've sort of popularized like these objective reviews that are, you know, Steven Universe is a 10 minute long show.
It airs on Cartoon Network.
It was written by Rebecca Sugar and like, yeah, that's it.
Objective facts, yay.
And those are funny, but like it's because you don't want that.
You want their spin on it.
Well yeah, the perfect like criticism of the objective review was done by Jim Sterling.
His perfectly objective review of Final Fantasy XIII where it's just him describing the game.
And like making no value judgments at all.
And I think, yeah, there's a lot more people who understand that reviews aren't all about objectivity now.
But yeah, like DeVu said, people treat it like consumer reviews.
And like, yeah, and DeVu would always contact me and be like, oh, I broke the reviewer rule.
They're telling me I broke the reviewer rule.
Oh, you've come up with all sorts of rules.
Sometimes the rules get very specific.
Like your roller coaster video is bad because you talk about this aspect of the game first and the other aspect later.
You're supposed to do it in this specific way, didn't you know?
Didn't you get the memo?
And I'm like, no, I didn't.
Yeah, the thing about it, and DeVu, you had made this point to me very well,
where it's that these people who come to you with these rules, they don't know your goals.
They have their ideas of what you're supposed to be doing.
That's true.
That have nothing to do with what you think you're supposed to be doing.
People will come out and be like, oh, your reviews aren't very objective.
And I'm like, well, they're not supposed to be.
If you want objective reviews, go find another guy.
Like that's not what I'm doing here.
You're totally right.
That's interesting because I remember the first time.
I really think the first time I got into this at all was when my brother linked me.
Jesse's, what was it?
Crystal Empire review, like the Colt Corona one.
I think that was the first review I ever really saw that was way more than just talking about the thing.
And once I got into that, I got into all this other shit.
And it totally changed my perspective and made me look for a lot more out of reviews.
It was like, holy shit, they can do all this shit.
And I like to think that I try to incorporate.
But you didn't complain that it wasn't the kind of video you're used to.
I think a lot of these critical people think of themselves.
I didn't get it at first.
It took a little while.
This is a metaphor that Digi came up with in a vlog of his where these people like to think of themselves as they come into a sandwich place.
And they tell the cook, hey, the bread's a little bit burnt here and there.
The meat's a little bit dry here and there.
But really what they're doing is they're going into a sandwich place and saying, this pizza is very weird.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, and they don't get that they're doing that.
And they want reviews to be a very specific thing.
They have a very specific idea of what it's supposed to be in their head.
And yeah, they come in with their rules trying to apply them to your video.
And then, but here's the thing, is that a lot of them are reviewers.
And a lot of reviewers themselves follow these same rules and have these same ideas about what reviews are.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, when you watch people, like everyone seems to have their own ideas about like, this is how you're supposed to score a show.
And this is like, oh, you have to...
Nothing disgusts me more than like these arbitrary ass calcula...
Like, you know at Glass Reflections, this is the end of his and he's like, after doing the maths, I have calculated this is like a 2.5 episode.
It's like, shut up dude, just say it's pretty good.
Yeah, you know, and I used to have stuff like that when I was younger, like I was obsessed with scoring systems.
And I would try to come up with ones that were like, alright, well, you know, in my value system, story is worth this much and characters are worth this much and this is worth that much.
And I do all that, run all these calculations and stuff.
And then in the end, I realized that, A, I'm pretty clearly skewing my scores so that it will produce the result I already want, you know.
Like I watch a show and I'm like, that was like a 9 out of 10 and then I start doing math and I'm like, 8.7.
No, I've got to, well, I guess the characters were a little better than that.
That is a very telling exercise, yeah.
And those things, you can't just weigh each thing, like how the fuck do you separate characters from story?
Like how do you make those two different scores?
It doesn't make any sense, you know.
The story is the characters and vice versa, so it's really weird to try to do that kind of thing.
Do you think it'd be good to go around and talk about what we each sort of like to see in an ideal review?
Yeah, well first I want us to talk about stuff that we've seen other people do that they consider rules that we don't like.
Do you have any of those things where when other people say something in their review about like how they do it that you think, why are you doing it that way?
I think one thing that so many of them do, and it's not necessarily a bad thing, but I think it's a lot more interesting when they just leave it out, is the info dump at the beginning where they just talk about all the different things about the game setting it up.
Ben rails against the info dump, yeah.
It's just not interesting.
Even if I don't know about the game, I'd rather you just like, Davoo's videos are very good, they just get straight to the point and you talk about like a weird thing and I'm like, oh, that's cool.
I don't know anything about this game, but now I want to find out, you know.
I personally struggle with the info dump because I kind of enjoy hearing, if they can do it in a quick entertaining way, I kind of like it.
Matthew Matosis does it well, partly because his videos are long enough to warrant some establishment stuff.
If your video is five minutes long and you spend 30 seconds establishing the facts, wasting time.
It's a matter of like, what am I coming to you for?
Because again, like you said, the biggest problem is that people think of their stuff as consumer reviews, and it's all like they're trying to sell you something.
And so they feel like they have to tell you what the show is and then tell you whether it's good or not based on their ideas, you know, which of course a lot of them don't think of as their opinion.
They think of it as they have specific rules that we'll get into later in this podcast about what makes a show good, you know.
But like, that whole system is like, if I want the summary, I can go get that.
You know, like if I want to know what in general the anime is about, I can go read the chart and I'll already know.
So when they start off with like three minutes of literally describing the show, I'm like, okay, I want it.
I came to your video to hear your opinion of the show.
I already know what the show is about.
I have a thousand sources for that.
And what's strange is how confident a lot of these people are in the professionalism and informativeness of their content.
And I've just now realized maybe that's partly because the top dog video game YouTubers are first and foremost lets players who don't do a whole lot more than scream.
So they think, well, if I have any, if I even have a script, I'm miles above them.
And then of course the second tier is the normal boots hidden block people.
And those people just, a lot of them most of the time just play a game and make a bunch of jokes.
They're like, well, if I talk about anything of substance whatsoever, I'm brilliant.
And I talked to one reviewer who was like...
On an artistic level, it's true.
That's the thing, a lot of people don't really seem to set out to make something like Jesse did,
which is something that's like big and like entertaining in itself and tells its own story.
A lot of people are just like, I want to talk about the game.
I think people want to hear about it.
And it doesn't really matter how I do it.
And that's fine. You can do that.
But once I learned that there's all this other shit you can do when you're doing it,
it was like, Jesus Christ, everybody's playing checkers, but I've been playing chess for years.
I think there's a sort of mentality among a lot of reviewers where it's just like,
okay, I am a reviewer now and therefore my opinion on...
I have to give my opinion on everything in my purview.
I am now an anime reviewer, so I must review every anime.
And then it's just sort of they review whatever comes under their purview,
like a Glass Reflections type, where anything that's big and popular, he reviews it.
And he feels the need to apply the exact same formula to every review and review every show.
Well, I never got the idea that he would thought anything more of himself than just an informative anime guy.
So I think he's achieving his goals.
Let me double advocate here a little bit, did you?
What is this you speak of? Don't just talk about whatever comes into your purview.
Are you implying that there needs to be, or should be, ideally, some sort of relevance
or point to a video in its context of when it came out and the culture it's in?
Yeah, I think if you make a review, it should be...
I said this, I ranted about this in my Bloodborne Let's Play,
but in episode three, if anyone's curious, because I go on a huge rant and it's awesome,
but I was talking about how if your review of a show, like the end of it,
is that you say that there was nothing interesting about the show, then there's nothing interesting about your review.
I guess you could say why it's not interesting in a very entertaining way.
I don't think you can describe why you don't like something,
but that would make it interesting.
Sure, sure.
For instance, I've done this huge video series on the Asterisk War,
and while my conclusion is that the show is unbelievably boring,
the way that it's boring is interesting.
The way that they fuck up in everything, the way that everything's done.
But if you watch a show and you're like, eh, nothing about it really stood out to me,
then it's like, why did you have to tell us that?
We don't need to know that about the show.
But watch his Bloodborne video for much more and much louder version of this argument.
I just don't get why people feel...
I feel like people decide that I'm a reviewer now and therefore I have to give my opinion on absolutely everything
and apply the same system to everything.
The way I see it, every piece of art is different and deserves its own...
I guess now we can get into things we want to see from reviews, right?
Here's a big thing I want from reviews.
I want you to watch the show or play the game or whatever
and then talk about it in terms that make sense for that work.
Talk about it in a way that reflects what you're talking about.
Not necessarily that you have to go crazy like my Serial Experiments Lane videos
where it's like this huge experimental video style because it's the style of the anime,
but even if you have a lot to say about one show, write a two-hour video.
If you have a little to say about it, write a two-minute video.
If it's a show that's like a comedy and you don't know how to talk about it
in terms that you would talk about a drama, then don't talk about it in the terms you would as a drama.
Talk about it in new different ways and make each...
That's why all my videos have... there's no structure to them.
It's all like this one is this long because that's the kind of show it is.
Sometimes I talk about one aspect of a show because it's the only interesting thing.
And sometimes I talk about the whole show because all of it's interesting.
I think a big mistake that a lot of reviewers make especially at a young age like myself
is let's say they watch a movie and they think, wow, this is a 10 out of 10.
This is my new favorite movie and part of what I love about it is the character interaction.
And so then they chisel it down in stone.
To be a 10 out of 10, you must have great character interaction
because after all, how would that movie have achieved it?
But there could very well be a movie that comes out that is a 10 out of 10
just on its ideas, its philosophy, but it may not have very good character interaction.
So you give that other one a 10 if it excites you as much.
Like, Digi, you give a 10 out of 10 to Ghost in the Shell and Psycho Pass, both cyberpunk shows,
but one has better ideas and the other has a better story and characters.
And we'll get into that particular point later because that's what I want to talk about
with the rules reviewers have about shows.
But for now, I want to know more about your structural...
You know, one thing that I think is a mistake a lot of people make,
and I'm sure I have too, is, and it's related to what you were just saying before,
it's that thinking that everything they have to say because they made it a video
is inherently going to be interesting, is going to be something worth watching.
And that leads into my point.
When I watch a review, maybe I'm spoiled now because I've watched so many great
entertaining reviews as art pieces themselves,
I'm not really interested in just getting information.
I'm specifically looking for a great piece of art,
a big story told within the context of the review itself.
You know, I'm always searching for my next Anthony C's Cantralot wedding
because not only was that extremely well made in most ways,
Tom's voice sounds like shit just because the recording is bad,
but not only is it great, but it's got this incredible narrative that extends
even beyond it into these previous videos that all tie up in this one punch
that finally is delivered in that.
And also, I forget what I was going to say, whatever, it's really, really good.
And that's what I look for.
I want more of that.
That is the pinnacle of what, oh, I remember what I was going to say.
It teaches me something that I had no idea about.
It presents this argument that totally changes the way you could view this piece of work,
that, I mean, you could have possibly thought this before,
but it seems like something that he did research and he came up with justifications
that it could be true, and it was delivered in such an entertaining way
that doesn't seem just like a shitty conspiracy theory.
It feels like it could actually be something that was actually planned.
And it's just, it's a perfect storm of all the things that I want.
And I've yet to see a video since that day that really hit me as hard as that one.
And that video, like, has a narrative of the reviewer,
but there's also the reviewer can tell the narrative of the work.
I think YMS is the most acclaimed in this regard.
If he does one of his big YMS videos, often he talks more about the narrative of the movie's production
and release more than the narrative of the movie's plot.
Like in his, the one with Will Smith and his son, he goes on for like 15 minutes,
just talked about the context and where it came out.
So when you see a scene in that movie, you're not just thinking about the plot of the movie,
you're thinking more about why Will Smith and Imlight Shamblin put it there.
And that's a story that doesn't even exist in the movie.
It only exists in YMS's video.
And that's something that could only be introduced by a reviewer, which is pretty cool.
Yeah, I think-
Use the medium to its fullest.
Boyo?
That's right.
I think, like, for instance, Jesse Wood here is like kind of the master of having the narrative of the videos
is more interesting than the subject matter.
Because when Jesse reviews something, I'm not really, I don't care what Jesse's opinion of the thing is.
I care about how, or I guess I should put it, not that I don't care about his opinion of the thing.
Because Jesse always boils his opinion down to like, it was good.
I liked it.
Right.
And that's it.
And then it's everything else on top of it.
Yeah, the interesting thing about it isn't so much what I-
I tend to use the thing I'm reviewing as a gateway to analyze myself.
Yes, that's totally true.
And I love that because like, what I'm interested in is not what you're going to tell me about the show.
I'm interested in what you're going to tell me about yourself through the show.
Because like, what is a show but a tool with which we learn about ourselves?
Exactly.
Yeah, like, that's the main appeal.
Like, when I do my analysis videos, none of it is trying to get to the heart of what this show is and what it means.
And like, in terms of the creators, like, I do like using creative intent.
Like, I enjoy putting that in, like, I enjoy looking at it and putting it into my reviews.
But like, my goal is not to say how well did the guy who made this accomplish what he set out to do.
My goal is to say like, why do I react to this the way that I do?
Why does this make me feel the things I feel?
Why do people feel- why do other people feel the way they do about it, you know?
And like, because yeah, like you said, the point of art really, like the appeal of it is that it shows us something about ourselves.
Or it shows us something about the world.
But you say that because I'm just now realizing the problem with a lot of the reviewers that talk more about the objective stuff and the reason they're not as interesting is because they're not as egotistical.
They don't think that they should make the videos about themselves at all.
Yeah, not even egotistical, but like, self-aware.
I guess.
Like, introspective.
Well, I don't think I do that at all.
Like, in my videos, I just-
Um.
I don't think so.
I haven't tried.
If I have, I haven't planned it.
Uh-huh.
You do incorporate like your specific, I don't know, like your personality totally shines through in your reviews in a really great way.
I think with Hippocrite, I think it's built into the reviews because specifically of what games you talk about.
That's true.
Because you have exclusively covered like PS2 and PS1 games that are from like a very specific type of era and genre.
And I think that more than anything speaks, that gives it a narrative.
Because like, when I think of games Hippocrite likes, all I think is like, he's into PS2 platformers.
You know, like it's all like mascot platformers games like that.
And I think it inherently creates a narrative out of that.
Like, kind of like how, did any of you guys feel back in the day with Jon Tron, that whenever he talked about a modern game, it was really weird?
Because you were used to him just talking about like Super Nintendo and N64 games?
Yeah, that is weird.
Yeah, and so when he talked about like a new game, it was like, oh, Jon, I mean, I mean, logically you know he must play a new game.
Yeah, it doesn't feel as like Jon Tron when he did his like Final Fantasy XIII.
I like that.
I mean, it was great.
Sounds like a straight video.
Yeah, yeah.
It's always a little odd when he cut like a...
It's not what I expected.
Yeah.
Or that Valiant Hearts video.
That was the weirdest to me.
That was weird.
It was some random indie game thing that he bought and it's like, oh, you know, I'm used to you talking about like nostalgia and talking about classic games and talking, you know...
That was him like defying his own, like, what he had determined as the reviewer rules for himself.
That was him going, I mean, not that he had to.
I'm just saying...
I don't mind it, but I'm just saying that like, I just think that he had inadvertently created a narrative out of his videos where if you've seen the...
His Top 10 Super Nintendo games, for instance, where he goes on like this long, impassioned speech at the end about like, why these games were so special and why we feel nostalgia for them and stuff like that.
And then like, you look at all the rest of his videos and it's all these nostalgic games and like, it feels like that's what the point is in a way.
And then when he starts talking about like movies, then it's like, oh, I guess you also cover weird movies?
True.
Now that feels normal.
But when he initially saw that, it was definitely...it works for him, though.
That's why Jesse has multiple channels for multiple narratives.
Yeah, but I don't think that's ever really helped.
I think it always helps your...well, I guess it depends on what you're doing.
But in general, I think having him on one channel is helpful, you know?
I think it works out for Jesse because each channel has such a distinct personality where it's like, I mean, you can tell they're all him, but like...
My Japanese anime is one type of video and Endless Jazz is not that type of video necessarily.
And by the way, we're not just complimenting each other because we're friends.
We became friends because we like one other's videos.
So there's a reason why we're so biased, by the way.
I think all my channels are less connected by content or less distinctive by content in the yard by like, theme or attitude.
That's very true.
Shit, I forgot what I was gonna go on to.
We could let Gib give his thoughts because I don't think he really gave his about what he has for out of a...
And Jesse, both of you.
What are some things that you see either in other reviews that you don't like or that you wish more people would do in their reviews?
Is there some thing that you wish everyone would gravitate towards?
I hate scores, but we've already kind of talked about that.
Yeah, I don't know.
Most reviewers that are just sort of uninteresting to me, it's because...
I don't know.
Who are your favorites? Old John Tron?
Yeah, John Tron is pretty great.
AVGN is probably still my favorite.
Sure, sure.
He was great at creating a narrative out of the video just by where he was.
Davoo has often said that The Nerd's Basement is the greatest location in all of our viewers.
Well, except maybe Jesse's basement.
That's what I've said, Jesse's basement.
But The Nerd is a pretty second place.
Right, because with The Nerd, all he would do is show you two pictures of where he is,
and you immediately have this sense of, I'm in that room, I'm playing games with him.
He'll show you the old console, he'll show you the old TV he's playing it on,
he'll show you where he is, and you feel like you're in that room with him playing that game.
And I think a lot of people don't capture that because they try to do the same thing,
but they have normal looking rooms.
People are just, yeah, I'm in my room.
With The Nerd, you felt like you were in this place where time has not passed 1985 kind of thing.
He's playing on the old system, on the old TV.
In an old room.
And a lot of people, yeah, they kind of don't go all the way with that.
They'll just set up a set of Nerd stuff just barely in the frame of the camera.
I get pretty triggered every time I see a millennial standing in front of their Amiibo collection
and their Zelda poster.
It's just fucking in my life.
It's just not good cinematography when you can tell all their posters and figures begins and ends
within the frame of the camera.
Yeah, yeah.
I love, because Jesse will do these things with his set where he'll reorganize all of his posters
just for the sake of a video.
He built, I kind of copied this myself, but not nearly to the same extent,
where he sort of built each area of his room to be a different theme.
So like, there's a wrestling corner, there's like a pony corner,
there's a, you know, an Evangelion corner, and like, if he's talking about those,
like, go watch the Fuck Blue Ray video where it's like, he'd carefully put all the Eva figures on the desk
or the wonderful Waifus videos where it'll be like his Waifus corner.
The Waifus wall.
Yeah.
Very proud of it.
And like, and I like that because I like the idea that it's like,
it's not just that I wanted my collection in the background.
It's that there's a thematic relevance to my collection, you know.
Right.
And there's a video that I'm, we'll say, working on.
I've been trying not to talk about this video because I'm scared it won't get done if I do.
Sure.
But I started it off with like a collection shot, but I had the camera vertical,
like, because it's on my phone.
So I did like a vertical filming of just one shelf that has like all my DVDs on it
because I'm literally talking about my DVDs.
And then like, I walk into the frame and then I pan the camera and slowly until it takes up the whole frame.
So like, it's not me standing in front of my collection.
It's like, the collection is the subject of the video, you know.
Sure.
That's of course totally fine.
Quite proud of the way I did that, but I don't know if anyone will see it
and know exactly what I'm talking about anytime soon.
I do like all that like live action stuff.
But I also do like the some people who just don't go on camera at all, like Matthew Matosis.
Yeah, yeah.
Like there's something about the fact that he's just talking about the game
and there's like nothing really about him.
Occasionally there's like a tiny glimpse into his, his emotions.
You know, I'm with you because that reminds me of something I hate,
which is arbitrary shots of you.
Like if you don't need to be in the video, like I'm working on a video now that I already recorded a big live action thing.
So like to justify that big ending thing, I need to start it with a live action thing or it'll be weird.
So it may, you know, it's going to work.
But like when people just start, they're like, hey guys, today we're talking about the new Zelda game that just came out.
It's pretty good.
Me and my friends have played it.
And then they end it with like, okay, everybody, thanks for watching.
Hope you'll stay and subscribe.
I got more Zelda videos coming next week.
Fuck Zelda, man.
Fucking.
Yeah.
Actually, I've remembered what I hate the most.
Oh, good.
Attempts at comedy when you're not very funny.
Yeah.
Please stop it.
I mean, I don't hate them for trying, but man, do I hate it when I hear them.
I hate them specifically for trying.
Trying to force things that you're not good at in general is annoying to me.
Like people start doing reviews and they get off the mindset that like, okay, I need a live action segment and I need a joke here and I need this because everyone else does that.
And then they'll get on camera and it's like, you can tell that they know they don't have the camera presence or the charisma yet.
It's that kind of copying the formula of someone without having the baseline skills.
And I do accept that to get good at something, you should probably do it if you want to get good at it, but it's also annoying and you shouldn't fuck you and don't do it.
I think a lot of it's a sign of like a lack of confidence in your own skills because like, this is the fastest way to get me to close out of your anime review.
And a lot of anime reviews in particular are like this because like, basically, I think that a formula got sort of created in anime reviews like early on and then everyone copied it where they all wanted to have like a really, really well produced intro, which is completely useless.
No, it's usually more like an artsy looking like, you know, like very clean, like legitimately well produced, but I don't want to see that.
Like I don't need 30 seconds of intro. I just want to know what the point of your fucking video is.
And then they'll always start off, like they'll start talking about the show and then they'll say, this is the number one line that'll make me close your video.
Insert joke about this here.
That phrase.
Anyone who says insert joke here and I'm like, so in other words, you don't have a joke, but you think you need a joke because you're not confident in your own skills as a reviewer.
You think that people will only watch a video who has jokes, but you don't have jokes.
So instead, you tried to make a joke out of the fact that you don't have jokes.
That's something you've encountered multiple times.
Oh my God, all the time.
I've seen it. I've seen it all the time.
I don't watch anime reviews that much. I don't seek them out.
Yeah. Well, there was a time where someone on Twitter posted every anime reviewer they followed just randomly and I was like, I'm just going to look at all these guys.
And then I just kept all of them had the same, because a lot of them had literally taken template elements that somebody made and everyone had the same DMCA opening screen thing where it's like, this is fair use.
They had the exact same fair use screen on multiple channels.
Create your own review software 2016. Just bad opinions.
Yeah. And then everyone feels like they need to have jokes, but then all the jokes end up being about how they're not funny.
And I'm like, stop. Stop. Take that out. I know you're not funny.
I think this is good advice, not just for reviews, but for anything.
Accentuate your positives and hide your negatives as much as you possibly can.
Yeah. I've been thinking like in the recent scripts I've been writing that I instinctively write a lot of jokes where it's like scream really loud, but I'm not very good at that.
I need to start cutting that down because I've seen stuff like Jesse's content where he screams, it's like, whoa, that's cool. That's really funny. I want to do that.
But I tried and I can't do it.
That process, anytime you do anything that you're going to, because it's great to take inspiration from other video makers or anything from life, but always ask yourself, what is the me version of this going to sound like?
Because when it comes to recording, I do a couple takes and I hate it, so I usually end up cutting it anyway.
Sometimes they get through.
Video editing process. Record something. Hate the whole thing. Trash it all.
This is why we don't get new hypocrite videos, if anyone was wondering.
Speaking of you complaining about insert joke here, I know you also have a beef with pronunciation of a word. How do I pronounce the word?
I don't know how to pronounce the word.
Did you complain about mispronouncing words?
No, no, no. It's the joke.
Yeah, it's when they go like...
Studio Ghibli? Studio Ghibli? I don't fucking know. I'm a gook. Hilarious.
It's like, and I know why they do it. It's to deflect people complaining about their pronunciation.
Because you've gotten a lot of that in some of your videos. You get that every day.
Yeah, I'm always getting complaints.
Those are fine. You can do that. Just don't dwell on it and just fucking motor past it.
I did one of the monster musume that was pretty much that, but I legitimately did not know how to pronounce that word.
I didn't fucking dwell on it. I just moved along.
Did you eventually just dealt with it and decided to start pronouncing everything right? Because you hate those comments so much.
That's a good way to go.
Sometimes I pronounce it right.
I have been more and more like, now I've been trying to say niche instead of niche, because people complain every time I say niche.
That's just how I pronounce the word in my everyday life.
But yeah, with the Eva videos that I did, I kept saying Eva and Gelyon, because that's just how I say it, and people were complaining about it.
In one of the videos I go,
And no one complained.
Yeah, no one complained, but also nobody got that that's why I was saying it that way.
It was to show that I know how it's really pronounced.
It is usually funnier to just mispronounce it deliberately.
That's true.
Hey bonus round, rule for commenters.
If you think someone else has already wrote the comment, either look for the comment and thumb it up or leave. Please.
We can do a whole other podcast about rules for comment.
That's a teaser for the rules for commenters, which will be probably 7 hours of us just talking about how much we hate everyone.
Yeah.
I think we could get every reviewer ever on board for that podcast. Everyone will have it.
Let's get PewDiePie in here, guys.
Oh god. He's got his own forum for comments.
Well to be honest, these days everyone's got their own subreddit.
We've got our own subreddit, guys. You can go click on it.
Link in the description. Go talk about it.
Alright, here's one that's a little bit deeper that I want to talk about about reviewer rules.
So we were discussing the idea of bringing up this podcast.
It's kind of fucked up that I'm going to do this when he wanted to be here and I didn't let him come on.
But Jeff Do of Mother's Basement was talking about how...
You didn't let him come in and he wanted to.
He was like, oh, because I said we were going to do reviewer rules and he was like, oh man, I want to be a part of that.
But I think he was more under the impression we'd be talking about rules that we want to follow as opposed to where I was thinking this is going to be us complaining about other reviewer's rules.
But he was saying that to him it's important that you either...
There's a distinction between recommending things and judging them based on what the creator's intent was.
He was saying a review should be about figuring out how well they did the thing they set out to do.
And I feel the total opposite of that.
And I think it's just not a review. I think that's a critique.
That's an interesting conversation to have, I think, about something.
Yeah, well, because I think a critique of something is where you look at what they tried to do and you judge them on that.
And I think the most ideal way to critique something is if it's literally they're in the room with you.
I think I would want something critiqued before I release it.
Let's say someone writes a video and they send it to me and they say, like, what do you think?
Then that's when I'm going to try to figure out, like, all right, well, what are you trying to say?
And here's how well I think you accomplished that.
And then you can put it out.
And there's an extent to which you can do that in video form where if you know, especially if you know a lot about the creator,
you know a lot about the background of the thing, then you can say, well, here's what they seem to be trying to do.
And here's how well they did it.
You can never really know because you're not the one who made it.
So it's always going to be taken.
And people treat those kind of reviews like those are the objective ones.
People treat those like those are the best kind.
It's like, oh, I'm judging how well they did their job.
And it's like, yeah, but you don't really know what their job was.
You don't really know.
A lot of people fancy the interpretive ones.
This is what that person really means in their life as like the most intellectual highbrow ones,
Aaron's signal, I guess, is doing.
And then he critiqued himself for doing it.
And I'm like, what the heck are you talking about?
If you don't know what they're like, then don't.
Just talk about what seems obvious and ignore anything that doesn't seem obvious.
And like, I mean, there's an extent to which you can like talk about what you think a creator like.
I did that whole Hidey Echiano video where I had some information to go on.
Right. And constantly throughout it, I'm like, by the way, this is all speculation.
I don't know Hidey Echiano, but here's some interesting things that you might think about him through what he said.
Sure. Or he'd be like taking like Suda51's games.
Be like, oh, he's clearly like misogynistic.
He fucking hates women. He's all about male empowerment.
He likes to jack off all the time.
Well, you don't fucking know the guy.
I made a pretty long video on Alexey Pajanov, the guy who made Tetris.
And I don't think I said anything about like, he's the kind of guy who would make this kind of game.
I just went down the list of all the games he made and tried to make him seem like a cool, funny guy because he is.
So I just wanted it and I just let him let anyone watching it think about him the way they would think about a normal person.
I didn't inject any of my own interpretation.
All right. Well, here's where I'm going to take this a little bit farther and maybe maybe you guys will contest me on this.
But OK, here's I think also that reviewing like, especially with video games, I think that reviewing just the version that came out and that was packaged by the company.
Is less relevant than reviewing the version that people will actually play with all the mods on it and stuff like I agree.
I think like, for instance, to give an example, like Super Bunny Hot made a video about Fallout 4, right?
And he was talking about he was critiquing the game and everything and like going in depth about it.
And then he says, like, you know, this game will probably get a bunch of mods that will make it way more interesting and better and playable.
Right. And like one of the things he complained about was the dialogue options and how they don't tell you the correct dialogue.
Right. Well, then like a day later, a mod comes out that fixes that.
So anyone who had, like to me, I think the most helpful review of Fallout 4 would be a review that says, hey, if you're going to play this game, download these mods.
Here's my experience now that I've done that, you know, because that's going to be, I think ultimately for, for instance, with a game like Skyrim.
Or like everyone plays it with mods, like no one just plays vanilla Skyrim on PC like past the first couple months that it was out.
And unless they're like someone who's a purist who only wants to play the pure version.
But like, I feel like we need the reviewer who comes in and says, all right, here's the version that you guys are actually playing.
And here's why that version is relevant to like culture, you know.
Super Bunny Hop is good about that in that he's not ignorant of that at all.
He's very willing to talk about it. And you know, I do actually like your suggestion a lot that he should do another review of it when like all the mods are out.
I think that'd be a very useful exercise.
But you know, really, I don't think that it's useless to do an initial release, but I think his goal for that video, and as he stated, was to talk about the game as it was released.
And I think it's fine to do that, but I just want to see more of both. And he is good about it.
Like he did a, he did his Metal Gear Solid 5 review.
Yeah.
And Jesus Christ, some fucking loud ass motorcycle.
He did his Metal Gear Solid 5 review and then he came back like two weeks later and did a video just about achieving 100% in the game.
Right.
Because he kept going.
Which is very interesting.
Right. And that's something that not, not everyone's going to do, but a lot of people, that's their version of Metal Gear Solid 5.
And like he gave voice to those people.
Yeah.
I think, I think my biggest problem with video game reviews is that the format of them, and especially with professional ones, like if you work for a review website, then you're encouraged to play this game in like two days.
Right.
Yeah. You'll probably give it a 10 out of 10 because it looks really good on the surface.
And the play, the gameplay is super tight, but oh, they fucked up the entire story. Oh, it has no real ending. Oh, it fucks up everything about the lore.
Oh, it's not replayable.
Turns out it's not that good.
Yeah.
You're trying these games at like reviewer events where everything is, you know, set up to make you like the game.
Or if you're someone who has to play a game every week, you know, then like your experience with games is not really what normal people's experience with games is.
And so many people critique the reviewer events thing, but they don't realize that just being a reviewer, a professional IGN game spot reviewer already colors your perspective quite a bit.
The funny thing is, you know, you know who those reviews are for? They're for other professional reviewers.
That's who those are useful for.
Yeah, like, and, you know, I've praised before how I love that Yahtzee, like, admits all of this up front in his videos.
He'll be like, hey, I only have a week to play this game. I didn't get very far in it, and it's not my kind of game.
Where he often will give his Game of the Year awards based on which games actually got him to play it for more than a week after he was done reviewing it, which makes perfect sense.
He says, my attention span has degraded to almost nothing as a result of being a reviewer.
So anything that I keep wanting to play for more than a week must be the best.
And like, I think that's great because I don't think a lot of people watch Yahtzee for his actual, like, as a recommendation.
I don't think many people watch him that way. People watch him because he's funny, and, you know, I don't think there's a lot of gamers who have the same taste as Yahtzee.
Like, he's so particular. He likes this certain type of narrative-driven, like, anything that's like Half-Life.
Like, the closer it is to Half-Life, the more he likes it, you know?
Half-Life 1, specifically, I think.
Yeah, both of them. He loves Half-Life 2.
Isn't his favorite game Silent Hill 2? That's his number one, right?
Yeah, Silent Hill 2, Half-Life 1, or Prince of Persia, like, those are like...
Yeah, Prince of Persia 2.
No, the first one.
Oh, really? Oh, okay.
No, 2 is not nearly as good as 1.
Well, Spider-Man 2, that's what it was.
That's like one of his, like, joke favorite games ever.
What, Spider-Man 2?
No.
Yeah, he's like, that's a game that he considers one of his favorites because of the experience he had playing it.
Well, whatever.
He had a top five list, but he thought it was a joke.
Spider-Man 2 is pretty awesome.
Yeah.
Alright, enough about fucking Yahtzee's favorite games.
Like, the point is that, like, he addresses the way that he plays the games, and I think more people should do that,
and I think we need more reviews that address the way people actually interact with art.
Yes.
That aren't us trying to say, like, well, here's what the creator and Ten did, and here's how well they did that,
because that's, like, totally irrelevant to any person watching your review.
Right.
Like, I think what your review should, like, and I mean, I'm not saying that every review should be this,
do whatever you want, you know, like, do whatever you're passionate about,
but I want to see more that are about, like, the cultural context of it,
and the way that people feel about it.
Like, if your review of Fallout 4 doesn't address the way that most people played it,
and the way that most people feel about it,
then who is it for?
Because it may be for some, it may be for a niche, it may be for the way you experienced it,
and there may be some people who relate to that, or outsiders who think it's interesting.
Like, I think, like, the Jesse-style, Anthony C-style that's my ideal is a niche thing.
It's not like everyone's looking for, like, epic stories in their reviews.
But Lord knows I want more of it.
Yeah, I just want more reviews that are, like, to me, the interesting thing about art is
how it speaks to the human condition, how it speaks to you personally,
how it affects you, and how you interact with it.
I guess the question is, do we count reviews as art?
I mean, obviously we do, but do people give a shit?
I absolutely think, and I think it, I think this argument has always been happening for all time,
and that we are on the right side of history.
But like, there's a classic, there's a huge write-up by Oscar Wilde called,
which, you know, this is from, like, 1890 or something, called, like, on criticism as art.
Like, it's a huge fucking thing.
It's presented as a conversation between two guys, where basically one guy is just telling this other guy
in extremely long-winded form that reviews are art, you know,
and like, he makes all the same points anyone else has made.
So as far as I'm concerned, like, this is a non-issue that's been around since the 1800s.
I gotta read that shit. That sounds awesome.
I couldn't make it through it, because it's very flowery.
I obviously agree that a review can be art.
But I don't think that reviewers should just consider themselves artists as a matter of fact.
Sure, sure.
It's, I mean, for one reason or another, I don't feel as creatively fulfilled.
In general, I do have a severe lack of respect for criticism in general.
Yeah.
It's a weird thing. If I, like, draw a picture, even if it sucks, I'm like,
yeah, if I make a video, even if it's pretty good, I'm like,
alright, I'm not quite as into it.
It never gives me quite the same high.
In order for me to feel like a review has become, has value beyond being a critique,
is if it adds anything of its own that's creative or interesting beyond the deep portion of it.
I absolutely regard all of my videos as high art, so.
Well, so do we all.
Well, because I like, like, to me, I enjoy analysis videos almost more than I enjoy media.
You know, like, I spend most of my time watching YouTube analysis videos.
So, like, to me, some of those are some of my favorite things.
Some of those are more rewatchable, you know?
And like, if it was something like Sequelitis, you could make the case like,
yeah, well, it's also funny, and it's got obvious artistic elements.
But then with something like a YMS video, like the After Earth one that DeVu was talking about,
like, that's one of my favorite videos because of what he brought to it.
Like, even though it's just about the movie, it's just about the context,
but the way it's presented, it's basically a documentary.
And I think documentaries are art, you know?
Like, it's about taking the work that exists and then making something out of it.
And I think making art is generally that anyways.
You're taking something that's in your head and you're making something out of it.
You're taking the world around you and you're making something out of it.
I think that's fucking copyright infringement and everyone who does that needs to get shut the fuck down.
Yeah.
Well, before we move on from the list of things, rules for reviews,
I do have a big list that I jotted down.
Oh, cool.
Oh, let's hear it.
Of things that piss me off in reviews.
And there's quite a few of them.
I'll get through them all.
I preemptively apologize.
I'll elaborate on the ones that need elaborating.
And before anyone in the comments tries to catch me in some active hypocrisy or contradiction,
I will admit up front that in the past I have been guilty of some of these things
and arguably continue to be guilty of some of these things,
but there's still things that I fucking hate.
Art hypocrites are boring anyway.
So anyone in the comments section trying to scream,
gotcha, you can blow me, you can all go right to hell.
Okay.
Now that we've primed them for the list, let's hear it.
So the first thing I wrote is jump cuts.
I hate jump cuts.
They should never exist for any reason.
But Jethy, you've done jump cuts.
I've seen them in your videos.
Yes, you have.
Come on.
Well, I have a contingency for my use of jump cuts
because I only use them in Man Child Incorporated,
which is specifically designed to have no soul
and to be a satire of soulless channels,
even though I fail at that because I can't make videos with no soul.
Jethy, why didn't you film Horseshoe Finale in one take?
Why wasn't that a one take video?
Your editing was lazy and I think you should step up your game.
No.
What?
No, shut up.
One take, Jethy.
How would he do all the customizing?
First of all, motherfucker, I did film it all in one take.
Every fucking shot in that video is a fucking five minute rant,
at least, that I did in one fucking take.
The only reason I didn't just cut that all
is because I don't have the power to teleport around my fucking room.
All right, stop arguing with Nate's fake straw man
and get back to your points.
Anyways, jump cuts are obnoxious and alike.
If you jump it around the room, you're just fucking stupid.
If you have a script, you should fucking memorize your script
and put some goddamn effort into it.
I don't need you cutting every fucking sentence.
Alternatively, there's two easy solutions that get rid of jump cuts.
You do one of them a lot, which is just,
if you don't have to do jump cuts, just cut to not you.
Like, cut, if you can't memorize the whole script,
say the first paragraph on camera,
say the second paragraph on a microphone,
say the third paragraph on camera.
You can cut back and forth.
You can find creative ways to get around it
without fucking just jumping to yourself from yourself.
Method number two, be somewhere else.
I've done this where I've recorded each paragraph
with a different, like, instead of jump cutting,
I'm just not in the same place anymore.
It looks like I changed backgrounds
and now it's a new place and I'm saying the next paragraph.
I guess to be specific, I'm not talking about cuts in general.
I'm talking about specifically...
Well, I'm just saying that cuts are how you get around jump cuts.
If we take this long to talk about every point,
we're gonna be here all night.
I don't care how long we take.
My points are gold, baby.
It's gonna be as long as it needs to be, all right?
Okay.
I'm leading this discussion, god damn it.
That's true.
The next thing I wrote down is a big one for me,
a big pet peeve, unscripted, stammering, stuttering bullshit.
Jesse, why don't you want people to be real?
Why are you trying to put people in a box?
Just let them be real on camera, Jesse, huh?
If you can't be articulate, you don't deserve to be real.
If you're in front of a camera, like, fucking,
alpha, mega-sin, and every other word out of your mouth,
you can't even form a complete sense.
Yeah, exactly.
Again, play to your strengths.
Don't play to your weaknesses.
Don't be a YouTuber just because you think being a YouTuber is cool.
Do it because you actually are articulate,
and you couldn't do this.
Not to throw shade on any other YouTubers in particular,
but when I'm going down the list of things I hate,
it's gonna be kind of unavoidable.
Fuck that guy.
I think it's fine to give an example.
Then people can see what you're talking about.
Yeah, alpha, mega-sin is really bad at that.
His videos always lose me in the first minute.
I can't get through them,
because he just can't put a sentence together.
Yep, it's bizarre, and that's what people subscribe for.
He's inarticulate rambling, but whatever.
Let's move on.
The next thing is lack of self-awareness.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Now, I'm a firm believer of anything on this list
that I'm going to complain about,
you can get away with it if you're self-aware about how stupid it is,
which is something that I have utilized to great effect numerous times.
I do stupid shit in my videos,
but it's always with my tongue in my cheek,
and that's where your tongue should be.
You shouldn't...
Okay, I've explained that one enough.
Yeah.
The next one.
Tongue punching the brown eye.
The brown eye, not my ass cheek.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Dismissiveness of other viewpoints or opinions.
Ding, ding.
Sorry.
Oh, man, yeah.
That one, that will kill me.
You don't have to start every review with,
by the way, this is subjective and it's just my opinion.
I'm not saying you have to do that,
but don't do the opposite either.
Don't be like, if you like this, you're stupid.
That's gay.
You're gay to do that.
Yeah, that's pretty gay.
If you like saying, if you like this, you're stupid, then you're stupid.
Oh, and then when you're called out on it, don't own up to it.
Don't just say, oh, I'm just having fun.
Oh, yeah.
That's the part of reflection thing that happened.
Yeah.
Yeah, this kind of part of reflection has made this...
This is what I ran to him about in the Blood Board video
if you haven't watched it already,
but he just kind of took potshots at Kayon
and then was like, oh, but I'm sure people like it for a reason.
And I was like, dude, what the fuck, man?
You're clearly insulting the people who like this show
and then trying to play it off like they're not.
He was taking potshots at the people who like it for just being weirdos.
That's true.
He specifically insulted people who liked it, so that's not cool, bro.
Yeah, I mean, you're...
I think any self-importance of that kind is really annoying in a review
where it's like, I'm the arbiter of what taste is
and it's like, dude, you're just some guy who has an opinion.
Your opinion might be interesting
and a lot of people might feel the same way that you do,
but you are not the arbiter of taste.
I mean, this is what that anime snob's entire career is.
Which it goes back to lack of self-awareness.
You should have, as a critic, you should have the self-awareness
to know that your word is not fucking law.
And then act on that self-awareness by acting self-aware.
Don't just be self-aware or claim you are.
No one's gonna know if you are self-aware and just don't do anything with it.
Well, I think that's what Davoo is saying.
It's like that departed reflections guy was like kind of claiming that like,
hey, it's just a joke, bro.
I'm not taking my videos that seriously.
You need to modify your content to make the videos.
Right, right.
Alright, the next one is the big pet peeve of mine,
and even bigger than the last one that was big.
And that's the recap reviews.
And I'm talking specifically about the That Guy with the Glasses Doug Walker formula,
where you're fucking, instead of actually writing a think piece
or an editorial or a fucking opinion about something,
instead you go through the whole goddamn movie,
scene by scene, for 25 fucking minutes,
and just every scene you gotta make some glib comment about,
like, the way that the nostalgia critic does.
Every one copies it, and it's a horrible fucking format.
You know, the only thing...
Yeah, no, you're totally right.
And that was really bad when he would just play footage and do that.
I like that he now does like all live-action reenactments.
That in itself is kind of cool, but the formula is garbage.
Like, I understand that people want to copy him because he's popular,
and everybody starts out copying somebody, but...
Just remember, everyone's copying it because it's the easiest format.
If you're gonna copy someone's format, copy any other format.
That's a terrible way to critique something.
It's an okay format for movies, because John Tron did that with Birdemic.
He just went through it, and he made jokes.
But he's so funny, you know?
I know, he made up for it with the jokes.
I think, and we kind of discussed this last night when we were just talking,
but I think the only value for that is when it's something that no one's heard of,
then going through the whole...
If you're talking about some completely forgotten piece of 90s garbage
that no one remembers, and then you describe the whole thing...
Because that's kind of what YMS does, is that he'll take a shitty movie that no one watched,
and then he'll break it down every single scene.
By all means, go ahead and do it.
That was my first introduction to The Room, watching Nostalgia Critic's video on it,
and I loved that video because I had no idea what The Room was, and it was like,
holy shit, this is amazing.
I think when you start applying that formula to reviews of shit that people actually are watching,
then it's like, we all know what the movie was.
You're not pulling the veil over our eyes with the way you're describing it.
If Ben were here, he would be screaming about how much he hates it.
And railing against the heavens about this point.
Ben, I'm here for you, brother.
Just like me, do that format. Any actual content is incidental.
Any analytical point will just happen at some random point in the video
based on when it happens in the plot.
At the end, Doug Walker always does...
At the end, he'll be like, wait, I understand now.
It all makes sense to me, and then he'll play the sad music,
and be like, you know, at the end of the day,
maybe Mad Max isn't about angry men and lesbian women.
It's about being a family, or whatever, you know?
Yeah, some completely obvious conclusions.
And it doesn't even make...
It doesn't logically follow from what happens,
or it's so obvious that there was no need to do any of this.
So, fuck off, Doug.
Bonus rule, don't make your points more dramatic
and make it out to be more interesting than they are, unless that's the joke.
You have to justify it.
If you're going to play the sappy music, you better have a good fucking reason.
Something interesting.
Biggest critique I think we all have of Nerdwriter.
This is a good point.
Yes, overly sappy shit when it is not justified is a huge trigger.
Like the Planket Reviews of Star Wars,
he waited until, you know, two and a half hours
and then really lay down the big...
Yeah, and it was epic.
The payoff was fucking...
Oh, yeah, it's the best.
And I like to think I achieved something similar
in my Girl and Login video with its 40 minutes,
and then at the end, it all ramps up to it's like,
holy shit, guys, boom, you've listened to this shit.
Yeah, you know.
Alright, Jesse, continue your list.
Alright, the next one, I needed some clarification for it
because I'm a big doer of this.
That's a stupid way.
I'm Alpha Omega Cent right now.
I can't...
Continuity, specifically high stakes continuity.
Now, I'll explain what I mean by this.
I do continuity in all my videos.
Every fucking thing I put out
has some kind of connection in it,
because that's what I like, and it's fun and it's cool.
But the storylines or the stories that I'm telling
are all very low stakes.
They're just about me being an idiot and a crazy person
and living in my own madness here in a fucking basement.
What I hate is when people, again, no self-awareness,
they take it so seriously,
like you'll watch a Linkara video or a Nostalgia Critic video,
and some guy comes into the gun,
and he's like, we gotta save the world
by reviewing this fucking movie from 20 years ago.
It's the only way to stop the evil overlord,
and the evil overlord is just like him in a different hat.
Yeah, yeah.
If it's self-aware, it can be okay.
Yeah, there's sort of things that did start as a joke,
but they've kind of become the norm a lot.
Especially with the AVG in it.
They all do that sort of...
It started with the AVG as a joke.
There's no reason this should happen, and it does.
Now, we don't have to go too elaborate on stories,
because if you want a definitive, full, complete list
of everything to not do in a review story,
watch the Game Over Thinker episodes 43 through 100.
That will teach you everything to not do ever.
The Game Over Thinker is the perfect example of don't.
The thing is, I think that continuity can be great,
but each of your videos should be watchable
and comprehensible on its own.
If you're watching them all, unless it's the end...
With the Horseshoe Finale, for instance, that Jesse Wood did,
every video leading up to it made sense by itself,
and then Horseshoe Finale was just the ending of the story.
Horseshoe Finale might not make sense on its own,
but it's also not about anything else other than the story.
It's not an episode review that became a film.
It is a film about the story,
and it's made for the people who are following it.
I think with Game Over Thinker,
he'll put out a video that's called
Why Mario's Cool, and then you start it,
and there's 10 minutes of him fighting
three evil versions of himself in a CG background,
and you're like, what the fuck?
What does this have to do with Mario?
I'm all for continuity, I'm all for stories and skits,
but, guys, you are not saving the fucking Earth dimension
from a goddamn ninja by reviewing a fucking movie.
So while we're on MovieBob,
let's talk about something I've been guilty of,
is putting in something in your review
that makes sense as part of your opinion to you,
but you don't explain why it's relevant to your review,
and that's something that MovieBob does a lot.
Oh, like he sticks to his social justice agenda all the time.
That was actually the very next thing on my list.
Intrusive politics.
And that one means no explanation at all.
Your fucking opinions on politics do not belong in a review.
Well, okay, hold on.
Unless they do.
I think it does need clarification.
That's why I clarified intrusive politics.
Sometimes the politics are interesting,
and that's the point.
With MovieBob, with his really that good videos,
there's always a point in the video
where the politics are important,
where with the Spider-Man video,
he gets into this 9-11 part,
and it's like that was relevant to the story of the movie,
but then there's parts where he'll just be like,
you know, and if you're a Republican,
you're a fucking idiot moving on to the next point,
you know, and you're just like, what was that?
Like, why is that there?
Yeah, like his Independence Day review was like,
Independence Day came out in the 90s,
and now it's, you know, the 2010s,
and there's lots of things that have happened since then.
Bill Clinton has been great,
George Bush has been terrible,
and people have been racist against Obama.
That's all the American history that's happened between them.
That was the most violent rage quit I've ever had on a video, I think.
Yeah, it was pretty bad.
Alright, Jesse, next point.
Wait, I want to go back to your last point,
just real quick about the, about the stakes in videos,
because I want to bring up one of my favorite examples
of how to do it right ever,
which is, it was just Pinky Pride.
Yeah, it was in Pinky Pride,
and now it also includes the Crusaders of the Lost Mark episodes
of My Little Pony,
where the stakes are like,
incredibly low, right?
You don't need to do anything,
but it's like the tension in the thing is built up
in such a way that you really, really fucking care about it.
Everyone should learn from that example,
but okay, let's move on.
After intrusive politics,
it's intrusive skits.
Again, I'm all for skits.
I think they have a place, obviously,
but they shouldn't overtake the subject of the video.
I think the best guy who does skits,
besides me, of course,
on YouTube is Anthony Fantano.
Yeah.
All of his skits are like only a few sentences,
and they're just there, and they're funny, and...
But Anthony!
Yeah, exactly.
Review is, should be,
ten a thing,
and you even do everything.
Anthony, why you do this?
Shut up, Cal.
Anyways, back to the review.
Hello, everyone.
If you want to put skits in your videos,
why not?
Put skits in your videos,
watch Anthony, and take a note from him.
He's a good example.
They're like little golden nuggets,
because you never know if there's going to be one in a video.
Then when you see one, it's like,
yeah, actually, I kind of,
sometimes I'll get frustrated when there isn't enough,
like, Cal, and I'll just be like,
whatever, fuck this guy, I just want to see Cal.
But, yeah.
And I've taken a page out of the book.
Since I've started watching Anthony Fantano,
I've tried to make my skits more to the point.
Like, if you watch, like, my 2012 shit,
or my, you know, my old shit,
there's a lot of meandering bullshit.
Sure, sure.
Fantano highlights something really good
that reviewers can be, which is unpredictable.
Because I think some, that guy with the glasses type people,
they think, well, now that I have
a certain amount of narrative, I need to have
exactly three and a half minutes of skit
at the beginning of every video.
Whereas Anthony can be anything.
The universe of the needle drop
is like this unpredictable thing that's breaking.
Well, his April Fool's joke spawned this whole saga
about how Cal is dead and in hell
and made a contract with Satan.
And he incorporated that into his fucking, like,
pretty serious album reviews.
And it was great, everything about it ruled.
And it matches his editing style, where, you know,
the editing spazes out to cover up his mistakes.
Anthony, I made a deal with the daemon.
I got a burden, my doctor shows.
Everything about that was fantastic.
Got to pat the guy in the back.
Um, the next thing on the list
is derivativeness.
I'm not sure if derivativeness
is a word, but...
Don't be derivative.
Um, don't...
Nothing triggers me more
than when I find a new guy on YouTube
who is a blatant rip-off
in every way of someone else.
Yo, how about that demo-declone guy, right?
You know, I was about to bring him up.
I actually follow him on Twitter.
He actually seems pretty okay.
Yeah, we all left shitty comments
on this guy's video one time, because
he didn't do much, like, demo.
And demo is great. I didn't even hate that about it.
It was just, you know, it's like...
Well, that's the thing.
The thing about Departed Reflections is that, like,
he doesn't necessarily make bad videos,
with the exception of that K-On one.
But, like, the worst thing about it
is how he's cribbing demo
and not demo.
Because demo has an amazing voice
and a great microphone and a lot of charisma.
And this guy has none of those things.
He sounds like he's recording
like a muffled fucking, you know,
basically...
I have a pretty...
I only watched the 30 seconds of the K-On video,
but I have a very specific reason
as to why his demo impersonation
bothers me. It's because he's not doing it
for the same reasons as demo.
Demo does it. I don't know why, for sure,
but I infer demo does it
because it's an easy way for him
to sound charismatic
and fluent and read scripts well
because he probably tried reading everything like this
and it didn't come out well. He probably tried
reading everything like this.
I don't think demo writes any of his scripts.
Well, he tried to present himself
and that was the way that came out naturally to him
and helped him make his point.
I think the reason that demo sounds that way
is that only certain sentences are actually written
and he just kind of sits in front of a microphone
and then thinks of...
Because that's how I did my...
When I did a demo-style video, the one that's
Should You Watch Kaiba, there's no script for that.
I sat in front of a microphone
and played something in a really low voice
and it matched his flow.
And the flow of his
of his videos fluctuates based on
a point he wants to make. Let's just say
there's a show where a character gets killed
and it doesn't make any sense.
So he might say it like this.
So then she goes up into the cabin
and then she gets killed.
He might speed up all of a sudden
because that makes the point.
Whereas the first 30 seconds of the departed reflections
a guy, he goes,
he's been really busy at work
and school.
He has this big pause between work
and school. There's no reason
you could just say, I've been busy...Demo
if for whatever reason he was going to announce that
would have said, hi guys, I've been busy
with work and school.
Alright, you just reminded me of the biggest pet peeve I have
with all YouTube videos ever. It's when they start
their video and they're like, hi guys,
sorry I haven't made a video in a while.
Oh god, that's a really busy way.
That's really high on my list.
I don't even know yourself at that point.
I don't even know.
It's just, even if they just say, hey guys,
no, don't.
It's one part that...
I'm going to extend this a little farther.
I also hate it when people start off a review
by talking about how they found out about the
show or what their first impressions
of it were.
Unless that story is really interesting.
Unless it's really relevant.
I do think, and I've made a whole video about
why context matters.
With my lucky star video where I was saying
that a big part of the appeal of this show
for me is watching it with these people
at this time.
But you get so many people who start off their review
like, when this show first started,
I watched the first couple episodes and I thought
I'm not really sure if this is going to be
good or not. I'm not usually into
action shows.
But now that I watched the whole show,
I realized it actually exceeded
my expectations by quite a bit.
And I realized that maybe I should rethink
my, I got, shut up!
Just tell me how the show is!
Jesus Christ!
And if you want to see like,
basically the same list Jesse's
making that I would have is
my Attack on Titan review.
Which was an April Fool's review.
And it's just me doing all of
the worst parts of every anime
review.
I have listened to that one back many times.
It is perfect.
And it starts off with me just like, you know,
when I first saw
Attack on Titan, I thought
my first impressions of it were that at first
it seemed like
the first thing I thought is
going on and on like that.
Alright Jesse, you got another one?
Okay, one more thing to say about derivativeness.
Obviously
everyone is going to emulate the people
they like, especially when they start out.
But a good way to prevent
yourself from feeling derivative
is instead of stealing from one guy
just steal from multiple guys.
And that's how you create a stew
that eventually becomes you.
And I mean, I am all about
copying people.
I'm all about copying people once.
Like I love doing
like I'll find a new reviewer
and I immediately want to do something
in their style and I'll do like a
like I did Your Anime Sucks
which is a send up YMS.
Or you're probably the only guy I've seen
Digi that actually does that
and it's interesting that you're
so interested in just like trying
to do a copy of someone pretty much exactly
but you know, self-awareedly
and intentionally.
I like it because it's a good way to add
new things. Like I see someone
You learn something every time you do something like that.
I see someone with a different tool set from mine
and I'm like I want to learn how to use
those tools. So I try to make a video that's exactly
like them and then
from then on I know how to
like for instance, the asterisk war
sucks. Even though it has
sucks in the title is not supposed to be
in the style of YMS. But there's moments
in it that I use his techniques
where like in Your Anime Sucks
that was like entirely supposed to be this is YMS
but with anime where I went through everything
in order. I made jokes about it.
Does he gain his powers?
Like Mega Man style baby.
Yeah and with asterisk war there's certain
moments where I'll say like
and then she gets hit by lightning
we are three minutes into the episode
and this is all that has happened
and like that's a YMS gag
and I put that in my head
I'm just coming up at the top of my head
but uh
like that's a YMS gag
and I got that from him but like
it's something that can be applied forever
and even like he probably got that from
John Tron from Dai Katana review
where he goes like this is the first
three minutes of the game
it's turtles all the way down everybody's
copying everybody pretty much forever
yeah so uh
I think you should
look at other people and try to like figure out
what they're doing right and copy that
don't cuz it all comes down to
like the surface details
and that uh that what was the
film crit Hulk saying um the tangible
details where people look at it
and they go oh well demo
uses a low voice and it sounds
smooth and he stops his sentences
randomly so I'm gonna do that
demo's got the sexiest
sounding videos
on YouTube they're better than Markiplier
I don't know man I would suck that dudes dick
if he was here in front of me
I love you demo
multiple sources basically is what we're saying
as the song goes
I'm the macho dandy son
of Randy Savage, Captain Kirk
and Travis Touchdown
lots of learn from that folks
the next one I got my own lyrics wrong
yeah macho dandy bastard son
of Captain Kirk
um the next one
is a big do as I say
not as I do
um
alcohol
I'm sick of it
it's the laziest comedy crutch in the history of reviews
the whole oh I
can't even get through this without drinking
gotta knock back some of that
fucking Jim Bean
it's so fucking
laid out and redundant at this point
if you are
drinking alcohol in the video as a joke
fuck you go away and die
you're not the nerd you never will be and you damn sure ain't drowning in horseshoes
so don't even fucking bother
get outta here
I think there's a few ways to like
drinking is a very careful line and I think
if you're good enough to make it work
then you don't need us to tell you
but that's true of pretty much everything
I love doing like cause
I think you should do drinking
is part of your like character
is that you are an alcoholic
if you happen to be a guy
who drinks fine whatever
I'm not gonna tell a grown adult not to drink
but when it's used as like a crutch
for like the whole
I think it's a problem
the first time I watched um
drowning in horseshoes was the first time
I had been like impressed
by like somebody just drinking alcohol
cause like I'd seen the nerd do it
I mean he does it through that horse head too
like the AVGN
just takes a sip and that's just he cuts there
but like just he would like
open the beer
through the horse head
drink the entire thing and then throw it on the ground
and then there's a sound of glass
and the smashing it too is like man selling the joke is great
you gotta do something like that
it just goes to that level
if people do that then I'd be more interested
oh my god is that the origin of the fuck glass
all those broken beer bottles over the years
all the broken, all the continuity
all the shattering beer bottle sounds
that you hear in my videos are legitimate
I go I throw it over
I've always wondered that
but yeah like I think if you can make alcohol
a stunt it can work which Jesse always does
it's always like something impressive
it was invented by the nerd
it was perfected by drowning in horseshoes
and it was taken to a new galaxy
by Colt Corona so no one knows
and if you can make it a good joke
Nate did a great one at the beginning
of growing the gun part one
he opens three beers and does the father
the son and the holy ghost and the drinks
all three at once that was funny
but if it's just like I can't
take this I need to drink
like for me if I was gonna do
cause if I started doing live action segments
not even alcohol just specifically that joke
is the problem I can't take this
if I started doing live
action videos I would drink
in all of them because I love
having myself with a wine glass
because I've kind of become a whino for real
but like uh
I love that boxed wine have you polished that off yet
oh I did last night while we were
having our long ass conversation
congratulations oh this is my third box
it's been one this whole time
anyway um
I like how I complain about this
as I'm drinking whiskey
yeah
but you're not making a big fucking production of it
I think it's great
if the idea is like
I'm like
it's like two different ways some people are like
I have to drink because of this
movie whereas for me I think
it's more I have to this movie
because I drink
I think that's a better way to do it
I'm an alcoholic who's lost my mind
and is trapped in my room watching anime
that's funny you see that's a new
spin on the joke and that's way funnier
yeah definitely that's what I
that's what I want my persona to be
is I mean if you look at all my iconography
on my channel and everything there's always alcohol
so forget this
alcohol is not the problem drink if you want
just write better jokes
yeah okay what's next
the next one is
obnoxious overly long intros
we already did that we already went through that one
don't make a fucking long boring intro
to every video
but there's an addendum to that
specifically heavy metal intros
yeah
unless you're medox
and you're gonna play it through the whole video
everyone loves heavy metal
it's great and we all love it
but something about
putting heavy metal in the intro
as a part of your gimmick just seems so desperate
to me
I have never really watched much of Spoonie's content
I know a lot of you guys are fans but I went back
and watched the beginning of some of his Final Fantasy 8 ones
he's got this really shitty animation
and this like horrible
metal intro that goes on for like
a minute and it was like a nightmare
I could barely sit through it
but like that at the time I'm sure it was like awesome
this was like holy shit he's got an animated intro
this is fucking insane but like now
with the standards we have today it was not good
every metal intro
I don't think he has a metal intro
well it was rock and roll at the very least
every metal intro is always like just a chugging
like basic ass riff
like yeah
what I'm basing this off of is
one of the worst ones that I ever saw
was back in the
that guy with the glasses forum days
and there was this guy called the Hardcore Kid
and his
sounds amazing
he had this long intro
like the entire song
Kickstart My Heart by Motley Crue
and the intro had like explosions
and like he was like slow motion
dude what a badass
like him putting on the leather jacket
putting on the sunglasses
that's another one
did he evolve into Razor Fist later on
he might have lost some weight and became
Razor Fist
I'm just gonna go ahead and set down a fucking rule
when it comes to intro songs
if it's more than 5 seconds long
then here's the rule
it has to be an original song
made by a professional musician
not an original song that you made
or that some guy made
here's the best intros
that are more than 5 seconds long
John Tron's intro is incredible because it's iconic
and the intro is important to the videos
because he uses different versions of the opening
theme throughout the video
to create emotional moments
you'll hear the sad version with something sad happening
it's amazing right?
dude that's why I need to make a fucking intro song
so I can get that emotional pay off later
number 2 guy
we all need intros
the cinemasticist
he got Perturbator
the guy who does the music for the fucking
hotline miami games
and made him an intro
his videos are about
sleazy 80s action movies
and a guy whose entire career is making games
out of sleazy 80s action movies style
made him a soundtrack
the more I think about this rule
the more I fuck it
and number 3 guy
there's only one guy who's done the metal intro
justifiably
and that's Good Bad Flicks
because the band Psycho Stick made him an intro
and they actually know how to play that style
and here's a rule for intros that I have
especially if your song is loud
and energetic is how it then
fades out like in the middle of a verse
well that's unacceptable
that just completely throws me off
the song should be made for
the song should be
an intro song
it should not be a song that was written for any other purpose
it should just be an actual
intro song that's 20 seconds
like John Tron's song is an intro song
none of these rules should be
taken as set in stone no matter what
there's always exceptions to all of them
the cinematicist has always had great intros
the angry video game nerd
is so iconic and so perfect
it's the greatest intro of all time
even though he hates it
he hates it
which is sad
well I don't know if he hates it but he's gotten very sick of it
well of course
you're doing it for 10 years
whatever
guys if you disagree with any of our rules
prove us wrong
no you don't have to
prove us wrong because they're not set in stone
in any way
just go against the grain
alright Jesse you got any more?
oh I got tons more
oh my god how
we might have split this into two different podcasts
cause I also wanted to talk about
rules that reviewers have about shows
and the longer we go the more we run the risk of technical failures
so we should probably split that up
we're about halfway through my list
is anybody at risk of technical failure?
who knows anyone might lose power
their computer may lock up
I'm not worried about that Jesse continue to do that
alright the next thing on the list
is guys who only do negative reviews
and or shows
based around just cynicism
in general
that's why the mysterious Mr. Enter
is the greatest creator
on YouTube
actually I don't even know if he's
to be fair he does do videos
on good things as well
if the basis of your show
is I'm Mr. Angry Hate Guy
I hate everything and I
I hate everything guy
yeah I mean I actually
haven't watched any of his videos that weren't about the Daddy Derek shit
so I don't know
oh yeah see if I hate everything
don't have an avatar that looks completely hideous
and no one wants to have a look at it
don't have a disgusting repulsive avatar that's a good rule
yeah don't do that
even though he's doing well despite it
it's ironic the best I hate everything
video is the one video that's
I love everything and it's for Star Wars
where he's actually being positive
maybe that's a personal thing I don't know
I just much prefer positive videos
maybe it's a prodigal son sort of thing
where like you get used to him hating everything
and then he finally does a positive and it's like oh yes
I just think that negativity
as a gimmick is played out
I think you should
I think what it does
is like if you're someone like the angry video game nerd
it worked for him because
like it was all these weird games that no one's heard of
and it wasn't really him reviewing
like there was no sense that
you were watching his videos because you needed to hear his opinion
on this game it was about
the game you know
most part his anger was deserved
like it was an actual frustrating experience
right but I think guys like
JonTron and stuff like they do well with that
because JonTron mostly plays
shitty games or watches shitty movies
but it works out because of the fact that
it's about the thing
it's not about the review
it's not about his opinion of it
and if you're an opinion reviewer like I hate everything
then it's like we don't have any metric
for what you actually value
you know like if you only review
bad things
what I love about YMS about your movie sucks
is that he makes so many quickies
where like he reviews every movie
so like
if you were just watching your movie sucks reviews
those are funny and all but like
you really gain context when you see what movies he likes
when you see like
what he gives the 10 out of 10 to
and he makes those top 10 movies of
2014 like those are the
necessary antithesis
to the negative reviews to make you appreciate
what he values
otherwise those reviews would be nothing
he would say like this movie is shit and you'd be like
well I don't know what you like so I don't you know
and now that I do know what you like
then I can take it all with a grain of salt
a good review for negative reviews is
keep in mind just because you dislike something
doesn't necessarily it makes you mad
don't pretend to be mad in your video unless
you actually are mad as a result of the work
there are plenty of things that can be like a 1 out of 10
or a 3 out of 10 that you're just bored of
don't go oh it's terrible
just be like oh I hate it
I think it's pretty clear that the only times
that I've made negative reviews is when there's
like a strong emotion there
it's like this this
show made me really mad
and I have to talk about it
the entire asterisk and even then try to downplay
your anger unless you're funny and you're charismatic
like James Rolfe
you can do whatever be negative about shit
but you know just don't do it all the time
you gotta make it work
if you're mad through the whole video
then it loses impact
in your whole asterisk war series you scream just one time
just once
it's like when I reached the end of my rope
because most of the time I try to be like
sarcastic, snide like oh this is like this
but then there's those moments where it's like
well this is actually a real problem
so now we have to get serious
you know like or this is actually real frustration
so now we have to be frustrated
like understand the emotions of your script
don't flat line the emotion
because then it's just gonna get tiring
and it'd be fair Doug Walker does a
pretty decent job with that he usually creates
like a narrative out of his escalating anger
or conflicting emotions it's just that everyone
imitates him does it wrong which is another rule
try to out do your idols
try to do better than them
you won't succeed
but if you try to think of as your ultimate
pine in the sky dream is to be almost as good
as them you're always gonna be shit
so just make it your goal to be better
that's fair that's good advice
alright Jesse next one
next one adherence to formula
sure yeah
we were kind of talking about that
if you're doing reviews every couple of reviews
change it up don't just be doing
the same shit for fucking five years
yeah all my videos are different
I'm the greatest of all time
unless your formula is so loose
that it like
well in that case you're changing it up intrinsically anyways
like with someone like YMS all the videos
are like you know it's always 20 minute chunks
and we're going through the movie but like
he'll work the context in a different
ways you know it's never like
here's the part right talk about the history
and here's the part right talk about this it's like
it's all each video is its own
unique animal and you know if you have
like a formula that you stick
to real hard then okay
then people are gonna watch you for that
but if you ever change things
you run the risk of them like not giving a shit
about you and then just being like well fuck this
isn't what I signed up for I'm out you know you're not getting
them attached to you as much as
your content everybody go watch
my Super Mario
Brothers 3 review
Sim City review and my Hello Kitty review
totally different kinds of videos
and they're all great
well I just want to I just want to make it clear
that like even like even mother's basement
does like even though he'll do like
what's in an OP and every video is just about
an anime opening and it's 10 minutes long
but they're all very
different where he'll cover it like he did
the Dragon Ball Z opening and like most of them
will be like sometimes he'll say like welcome to the
NHK it's like an analysis of like every
image and what it means and how it's relevant
to the story but then he did like DBZ and
it's about the cultural context it's about
what the show did to anime openings
or the one punch man one which is like
literally a game theory video for the one
punch man OP and he's like calculating
how strong the punch is and stuff like
those are all changes to
the formula where it's not every single
video is the same thing even though they are all
about OP's and they're all about the same length
you know but I mean
obviously formulas will meet you with success
depending on what kind so there are
certain types of things where you can always be the same
you know the needle drop always has very similar
elements to every video zero punctuation
always has similar elements every video
these are not rules carefully selected
elements these are not rules that will
make you all these are not rules that will
make people successful video creating
you know what you know what this reminds me
of there's this book that me and Ben read
called how not to write a novel
and all it like no one no one in the world
agrees on how to write a good book but there are
tons of things people agree on to never ever
do if you want your book to sell book one
and like this is I think
I think the thing is like I think
when formula becomes dangerous is when
it's specific like if you do
your videos where you talk about
the story and then talk about the characters
and then talk about this
and you try to apply that to everything
you fail and I hate my anime
list reviews because they encourage that like the
format of the website is that you score
each element and then your overall score
is meant to be like the the the the
summation of those and and I've written
a lot of reviews in this style back in the day
so I know exactly where it's
it's failings are which is that
again you can't apply it to every
show you can sometimes
you can really talk about each
individual thing and and they're all pretty
separate but like if if
if talking about the aesthetics
of the show informs
talking about the characters of the show then
separating them into different sections won't make any
sense you know if part of
if part of my review of the visuals is that
this character looks this way and that informs
their personality in these ways and like I've
already broken formula and fuck it
you know so yeah
Jesse more points
the next point is posturing
and the worst defender
of this one I have to say is
razor fist
the main thing that drives
me crazy about his videos
is that he's never willing to be
the punchline he never laughs
at himself he always
has to be the cool guy making for a guy
that serious that's gonna cause problems
I mean laugh at yourself
again it goes back to like self-awareness
a lot of
most of my jokes most of my
videos are centered around me
being the punchline
you're you know I'm making
I'm making light of the fact that I'm a big
dumb idiot loser and
that's the that
to me is more funny
than trying
to seem like I'm the best guy ever
not not throwing shade
at Nate
but well Nate's videos do the same thing
it comes off as insecure to me
to try to posture
like you're the best guy
Nate's videos always the idea
of it is that it's all
fake posturing that like
at some point he pulls back the curtain
and it's actually some nerd
you know where like the idea
the girl in the gone video is like I used to be
this weak piece of shit and then I watched
the show and it made me the best guy ever
and like that's sort of the joke
I connect way more way easier
with people who
show that they can laugh at themselves
Nate are you still there you didn't have
any reaction to us talking about you
he's dead I killed him
oh no
you didn't have enough self-awareness
alright Jesse
next point
over reliance on memes
memes are a tool
they can be hilarious use them sparingly
alright do you mean
memes as in memes from other things
or like just you know
memes or is it okay to keep
your own meme like create your own meme
oh man creating your own memes is awesome everyone should
cause I love those
well if you watched all the nostalgia critic
you would understand how those can be abuse
okay well never mind don't do that either don't do anything
yeah uh yeah
don't use too many memes or too many references
yeah a well placed
reference can be the funniest fucking joke
ever but if your script has them
oh yeah I think
they're like a
like a very special silver bullet
like if you can put just the right
reference at the right moment it can blow
everything wider
a lot of things that people
I want you to talk about whenever you want to
talk you should
um what was I saying
something about references yeah
a lot of the time
I see people making references as
jokes in and of themselves
just like uh like I'm drawing attention
to the fact that I know about this thing
and that's the biggest one that comes to mind
is I Love Can Possible
yeah yeah you know
like it's just it's
meaningless but it does oh man
it does get the views it gets the kids all happy
they're like oh you know my thing
of all of these rules that we've been
like where Jesse was saying these won't necessarily
make you a famous youtuber they'll make you a good one
this is the number one rule to break
if you just want free hits
yeah make references to everything
load your video with memes
and all the fucking
put sans and papyrus in the thumbnail
of every fucking video
regardless of whether you're talking about it
just any good measure
anything that's popular or noteworthy
sans papyrus and shrek
throw it in there and then
and some illuminati triangles in there
the reason it works is because for some reason
people don't understand
internet is a place where everything you like
a thousand other people
like as well for some reason everyone
thinks that if you make a reference to something
and they get that reference it's like a special
connection like oh my god
you referenced a meme I've heard of and it's like
yeah everyone's heard of it
that's why I like to think and I take pride
in the fact that many of my references
are so obscure
that only three people will get them
yeah well the only thing about good references
is like a good reference
can make sense even if you have no idea
what it means or what it means in context
it just is a thing that you said
and it's cool
there's one other rule about doing references
that when I explain it
it seems so obvious but the nostalgia critic himself
continues to break it at least
a couple years ago back when I was still watching him
in general
don't set don't
this is what a lot of nostalgia critic does
he will show a clip and be like wow
that's just like such and such
and then show such and such
you're not even doing the structure
of referencing something correctly
if you explain it first
just throw that out there
while we're on the subject of references
this is just a flash forward
to what the future of this conversation will be
I'm in a nightmare it's still going
one of the rules that a lot of people apply
towards the things that they review
is that reference comedy
is somehow the lowest form of comedy
did anyone else get cut off
you said
what am I here
your hand if you would please
okay what I was going to say
is for some reason people think
that reference comedy is the lowest form
of comedy and they never explain
why it's just
something people seem to think right
and I think that like Lucky Star
proves that that's not true
and there's a great scene where
it's an initial D reference
suddenly the animation style
comes initial D and the characters start racing down the road
if you have no idea what it's referencing
it's still hilarious
because for some reason the animation style
completely changes
they went in on that joke so hard that you're going to appreciate
no matter what it's not like they just cut to an initial D clip
and it was like isn't it funny we're doing
something sort of similar to that right now
if you've never seen initial D you'll still be like
what the fuck is happening
the animation style is totally different
the music is totally different this is hilarious
but if you have seen initial D then you're like
oh multi trap drifting
holy shit
I think references
not only can they work on multiple levels
but also for the people who do get
the reference it can be fucking hilarious
people are always like
oh references the lowest form of comedy because it relies on
another work and not everyone gets it
and it's like yeah but if you do get it
guess what here's what's good comedy
if it makes you laugh
it's good comedy
if it doesn't
a reference has the ability to make people laugh
for like totally different reasons
so if you do it well that's pretty cool
the worst thing
about every review of comedy
is for some reason everyone thinks
that comedy has all these
really strict rules and every time someone
does a comedy review they're like
comedy is the hardest thing to get right
we all saw that king of the hill episode
where bobby goes to school to try to
learn how to do comedy by the book
and it doesn't work out folks
nobody laughs everyone thinks
every fucking video
where someone reviews a comedy they always have to have
this long speech about how comedy
is so different from drama and you have to judge it on
a different scale and this is the right kind of humor
this is the wrong if it makes you laugh
it's funny
and it's good comedy there's a million
ways that you can accomplish that
but trying to be like
oh well this kind of comedy
is never funny except
it is all the time references
are often funny
the easiest one to fuck up
but they are very often hilarious
family guys' references are funny
they animate ridiculous shit
the hardest I've laughed so far this year
was jesse's
in a analysis video
or review jesse did the video
about the christmas specials
and he has this long lead up
I won't even spoil the line
but it's too
you'll know it if you see it
what was this involving I don't remember the
alright fine he was telling this whole story
about Helga in the christmas special
of hey Arnold and the whole thing
is she's trying to get these shoes
and then like she has this whole moral
conundrum about whether she should give the shoes
to this other person or keep them for herself
and like jesse
frames this whole thing and then he says
she is truly drowning
in footwear and like
the way it all led up to it was so perfect
I was very proud of that one
a well constructed
bit in a well constructed video
and it's a reference and if people haven't been around
on your channel long enough to know what drowning
in footwear is then they won't get it
but like it's not intrusive
it's just something
that you'll get more if you know the reference
and it's fucking hilarious
and even if you don't get the reference
I added in that few seconds of like wind howling
and like the air enhancing
like that's not fucking funny
even if you don't get it then that's also part of the joke
that's how
that's what it means to be a comedy genius
people
you gotta bang on all cylinders
somebody mentioned kim possible
which made me add a new one right on the fly here
which is having editors
edit your own shit god damn it
have some pride in your fucking art
and edit your god damn
own videos
there is
except for me
that's the thing though
kim it's like
when we talk about i love kim possible a lot
you can't judge like her content
as if it's like her just making it
you can't say like wow kim makes great videos
you have to say like her videos on her channel
are clearly the work of a lot of people
putting in time to make a video
here's what it comes down to for me
I hate editing more than anything
in the god damn world
but the reason I do it is because
I have so much pride
and vision in my work
I can't do it
I can't trust it
there's been times I said devu edit a video for me
and he's like okay and I'm like no wait never mind
I'm doing it myself fuck it fuck it
and then the video never come out
I can't even finish it
it's just a matter of I don't think the rule should be
don't have editors it should be have editors
who you're working closely with
and who are communicating the same thing you are
and play what you try to do
I don't think I could possibly ever make a video
and have someone else edit it
somebody who wants and gags that come
from the editing process
that you think of during that
but at the same time sometimes you're
to me it's not a matter of
like I'm handing off my
my thing to someone else and they're doing something
it's more like I mean if you're a musician
and you're in a band and you don't play all the
instruments then that means
that every song is the collaborative effort
of you and three other people
and like with my videos
cause I hate editing
and I will just
not make the video as good as it should be
because I don't want to edit it
I just won't do it like if there's something
that I know that if I spent
40 hours on it it could be fine
but like there's no way I'm going to spend 40
hours on it then you know
I won't write my videos in a way that requires that
but I know that the DeVu
can take like he finds
the jokes that I don't even
take the time to look for you know
cause he'll see the show so many times
he'll edit the video in such a way where he'll make
the characters make certain facial expressions
when I say something that always is hilarious
and it's something I would never have looked out for
I would never have found so like
I think taking
editors is fine if they are
better than you and they
are like
they understand your vision
like just as well as you do
and can or if you just like
I like DeVu's videos that
he edits for me more than I like
videos that I edit for me so like
I would rather he edits them
I have an editor if it's clear that you're using it
to make your content better or bigger
or more voluminous like you know
I guess it's impossible it just feels lazy but
I think you guys are trying too hard to justify
using an editor you can use an editor for whatever
you want to be anytime
I mean it's just about what you want your
shit to be if you just want to have people
make your shit for you and you just want to produce
collaborative works that's fine I completely
understand Jesse not wanting other people to edit
his videos because the editing is often
hilarious and has great stuff in it but like
if you're like me and you
are just not good at editing
then maybe consider having someone
who is good you know doing it with
you know I mean I think most of us
agree that I'm one of the better editor amongst us
and even I'm willing to say
that I don't if I I don't think
it's necessary to I don't even think
I was gonna say like you do you don't
have to have the best video
it could possibly be all the time
like I don't yeah I definitely have been
moving away from putting too much effort in this
like especially on YouTube we're incentivized
to make fast content here we go
Jesse how about this how about this
for the rule earn your
editor how about that
sure or at least pay them
well you gotta pay your
if you're making money well yeah if you're making money
you should be paying them but what I mean by earn them is
I don't think KP does any work
on her videos I think the editors do all the work
that's true that's what I think
specifically watching a video going well at least
this is well animated what I what I hate
is like how I hate how
popular she personally
seems to be for her videos that clearly
aren't her she didn't do it she wrote
the script and read it fucking
not very well let's let's be honest
alright Jesse do your next point
let's move on fuck I had
something else to say but I can't even
someone's gotta edit this
we gotta cut cut that out I don't want to
nobody here listen to what I said
ignore that the next
one is things that everyone
has already fucking reviewed redundancy
don't write it
that's just don't do it
and the next like four points are
all actually redundant in themselves
I'm gonna go shit he's a hypocrite
yeah I'm
grouping these together blank is
overrated reviews
controversial opinion reviews
audience straw man
bullshit just in general
basing your review on other people's
opinions don't do it
it's not just an escape
you're a fucking review should be
your thoughts and no one else's
I actually had a video
that was gonna come out about this same subject
but I got to the editing process
and I didn't feel like doing it and I refuse
to hire either I realize
another another one that I want people to do
which is um
no shit I lost track of it oh yeah
don't do this thing where
you're afraid of having your opinion
polluted by watching other people's reviews
oh yeah watch everyone else's reviews
right because if you do like people always
say like oh well I I guess I get it
for like a guy like Yahtzee where
again like it's really about his like
very carefully curated
style of opinion then like
if if you're watching the video
because you want to hear that guy's
thoughts and like nothing but that
then I could see it but like
if it's if someone
puts out a review
five years late for a show
or even five months late for a show
five weeks if everyone else
has already reviewed it watch all of their reviews
and make sure that someone hasn't said what you're about to say
right or else you're just wasting everyone's
time especially your own like have something
new to say don't just say the same thing everybody else
and you know what it's I'm glad we brought this up because
this was a big reason why I was inspired
to make my Gernlogan video because
every single video I ever saw
has these disgusting little
like oh you know it's it's
it's good but like there's all this
there's all this obviously unnecessary shit
there's all these little like it's not that smart
and all the the ironic thing is
these people weren't that smart because they couldn't see the
incredibly obvious shit that all of us
did when we watched it and so
I this was this was an example of having
to do something like this show is is loved
but still vastly underrated
for what it actually accomplishes
which is bizarre to me and had to be corrected
so that's exactly why I started doing
my like with Eva and Gelyon
like I was so worried for a long time that
I was like everyone's already talked about Eva
and it's not going to be worth it unless I either
say absolutely everything or say
something new and then it was sort of like
gradually realizing
that there was a lot less Eva analysis
out there than I thought you know
and like trying to come at it from like somewhat new
angles or just sometimes it's just like
representing something that's not in that medium
like I'm willing to do a video on a
subject that I've read a lot of
reviews about but no one's made a video
out of it because I think that people
don't go back and don't read text
you know sure yeah like there's a few like
ghost lightning posts that I outright just want to
adapt into video because like
it'll exist in this medium now
I think that's a good idea they'll probably
get a lot more exposure that way anyway
alright so Jesse you finished off your list right
no oh jeez how many more
my list is eternal it's endless
like me
alright well let's do the next one
next one is
blatantly missing the point of what you're talking
about example
sure sure example is
Avon Gillian sucks because the characters are
unlikable fuck you
you dumb shit yeah I mean
I don't like reviews that are obviously wrong
not a fan like you could say
the characters are unlikable dot dot dot I know
that's the the intention but I don't like
it then that's fine
well I have a problem in general of people saying
this character is bad
so the show is bad
well that's going to get us into part two
of this podcast so
part two people having
my list god damn it
no your list is going to apply to this as well
I think okay part two of this podcast
people's rules
about shows
like that one that like
here's here's the one that bothers me the most
and this is what made me want to do this
podcast in the first place
my trigger is when someone
says that the pacing
is bad and then
doesn't explain why
that is my number one trigger now
in an analytical video
is because people have
taken for granted that
a piece of work is supposed to
be certain things that it's
supposed to be paced a certain
way that it's supposed to present its
narrative in a certain way the characters
supposed to be a certain way and the only times people
break from their their pre-interpreted
formula of what it's supposed to be
is when it's obviously
not supposed to be that right sure because
everyone loves art house movies and stuff
where like you look at it and you go oh
well they obviously paste it differently because
it's it's sending a message but then
when that's not obvious people are
like it's just badly paced you know
yeah and that drives me insane
because it's like you're so close to getting it
and not like you clearly understand
that every work is trying
to do something different and that you should judge
them on their own merits but then you're trying
to put all of them into a box at the same
time and it's like certain things are just
the exception because you can tell its art
you know like oh well obviously
Ava's trying to do something different
because it's Ava whereas like
if some you know late night
TV at a bay that's like really weird
and no one gets why
and they're just like yeah it's just
I should just I should rephrase
the wording of this rule
instead of missing the point of what you're talking
about the rule should be
saying anything negative
about Evangelion ever for any reason
or disagreeing with me
about anything
you know that's an important point
to remember when interpreting
the intentionality of a work is that
most almost any every single
detail was intentional whether or not
the intention was smart oh god
there you go there's another huge one
this is another one that like immediately
pisses me off is when reviewers
think that they are smarter
than the creator
that's what I was trying to say
what said stupidly
the worst game designer
is categorically a more
fulfilling artist than the best reviewer
that's my emotional opinion
that's how I feel
I think that a lot of bad
art gets made in full
self-awareness
I think that a lot of stuff
there are some cases where obviously
the person just doesn't know what the fuck they're doing
like if you look at like Birdemic or The Room
where like the creators really thought they were
making like a masterpiece and really came out
and said that and then people were like
you're insane like this is no
this is not good you know right that's a different story
there's obviously a reason why he picked
the individual gifts for the birds
like he's like well this one is pointing in this direction
which will make more sense than that direction
yeah but I mean I'm talking about like in the broad
sense you can tell the guy
doesn't appreciate what's bad
about his movie until people told him
you know but I think that a lot
of creators make stuff
like especially professionals like if we're talking about
like an anime show gets made right and like
the plot is full of plot holes
the guys who wrote it probably
know that like they are professional
writers who are in the industry
they're not trying to write a 10 out of 10
every time they're trying to write something
and like you know okay like I have
this video series on the Astroscore right and there's
a bunch of parts in there where I talk about how
like I like my problems with A1 Studio
but my problem is never that
I think they're ignorant of these issues
I think they know exactly
what they're making and they just
they have to because it's
it's just their job you know like
they're doing it and if you look at
like if you listen to a lot of interviews
with like Japanese creatives and stuff
they very often make it clear
that like everything was intentional
like the style of story
like Japan is very like demographically
driven and very like
genre driven where like
if they're making a show about beautiful girls
it's a beautiful girls show
you know like they'll call it that
like that's the concept they went at it with was
oh we wanted to make a beautiful girls show
so we came up with a story and here's what it is
you know and like everything else
is kind of incidental to the fact that it's a beautiful girls show
you can make a great
show on that basis like
something like Girl in the Gone they went at it like
a sex show or
or Ereka 7 which was we wanted to make a video game
that had an anime tie in
and here's what we made you know
wait did they do that
yeah a lot of anime
is based on it being a franchise
where like they
like with Ereka 7 it was like
we want to make a video game and an anime
with this robot designer so let's come up with them
you know I didn't actually play the first
video game of that I didn't know it was like
I thought it was just a derivative work afterward
no but it's the thing is that like
it's different teams working on each right
and like the people who made the game
didn't make an amazing
game that will remember for all time
but the people who made the anime did you know
but like it just happens that
like I think everyone knew what they were doing
everyone works on these things just like well
maybe it'll be good and then they make something
and sometimes it just happens to come out really amazing
and they're like sweet and we actually did it
and here's how you put it in one of your old videos
one of the best points in your really old
videos was nothing is made
thoughtlessly it's just that some things
are made with stupid thoughts
but it wasn't like they didn't even think
I mean every single problem
in My Little Pony for instance
has been acknowledged by the writers they
they're completely aware they're like
yeah we had to do that because Hasbro
mandated it or yeah we had to do that
because we didn't have time
to fix it you know like
like the episode 15 of season 1
of Feeling Pinky Keen
the one where she's got the powers
like the writer of that
like he had written
the episode no it wasn't that episode
it was one that's in season 3
or an even better example magical mystery cure
where Emmy Larson came out and admitted that
everything I said was correct
right yeah you wanted to be two episodes
you just couldn't fit in it
he specifically said drowning in horseshoes
the greatest reviewer in history
but I'm not just talking about like studio mandates
there was one where it was the guy who wrote
this one episode that was
something from season 3 but it was a really shitty episode
where the ending was like really confusing
and backwards and I asked the writer
on Twitter like what was up with the
ending and he said like it was just a mix-up
in the scripting and we couldn't fix it in time
I wonder if you could
evaluate all the reviewers and get
like a robot to calculate which
reviewers most often neglect
the context of the fact that the writers are human
oh here we go
mysterious Mr. Enter that's my biggest problem
and then test to see
if those reviewers who are more
likely to do it don't make any art
of their own outside of these youtube videos
like if they're not the kind of kids who made
you know drawings that much
I wonder if that's what they are
about the few mysterious Mr. Enter videos that I've seen
is that he will
he really focuses on the writer and he'll be like
Megan McCarthy
how could you make this shitty episode
and I'm like I am absolutely
sure that she knows all the problems with it
she wrote it no one is
more intimately familiar with their flaws
than the creator and we all
I think we can all attest to this right every flaw
in all of our videos we know what it is
like I know many problems
that people don't interpret as problems we do
see them as problems
every video I've ever made there's a take to heart
we know better than you what the
fuck is wrong with her every single time
I flub a word in my script I find
it because I edit the video
so like you know I record this long script
and I edit it together and then I hear
where like I skipped a word at one part
and I'm like oh fuck and then every time I watch the video
all I can think about is that
sometimes we just don't get
around to fixing the problems and I think a lot
of like really professional
stuff it comes from that place
like with anime especially because it's all churned out
on like a schedule you can't just go back and fix it
you have investors there's people
a time slot picked out you know
if you get to episode 12 and you're
writing and you don't have time to fix the
slot hole then it's just fuck it we're shipping it
like we can't not you know it's
it's too far along and I think
so few people appreciate that and they act
like oh this writer is such
an idiot how could you do this thing it's like
I assure you they're aware of it
that's true that's true you shouldn't assume
those things but you should still of course
incorporate those into your thoughts
on the overall show
he's felt bad about a lot
of his old reviews and is like taking them down
I think because it's good he should take down
his whole channel fuck him
I think as I've said
oh shit
I lost my train of thought because you brought up
Mr. Enter and I forgot what I was going to say
this is what Mr. Enter does to the community
well speaking of Mr. Enter
the next item on my list happens to be
overly complex
scoring systems
get the fuck out of here with your
well it gets a 3 out of 5
sound design and a 2 out of 5
for voice acting a 4 out of
5 for graphics
I don't know what piece of media
has those criteria
yeah
fuck that just talk about the thing
and uh
here's what bothers me about rating systems
is that they should always be fluid
and therefore they should never be in a video
like if I watch a show
that's a 10 out of 10
and then a month later I watch a show
that I consider to be much better
and that's now my 10 out of 10
the old score is completely irrelevant
I'll put it this way
if I
if I have sex with a hot girl
and I'm bragging all my friends about it
which happens often
as these guys get a test too
oh yeah
but if I had sex
well that's what I'm about to do
if I have sex with a hot girl
and I'm bragging about it
like a douchebag as I am
I don't go
5 out of 10 but her butt
wasn't 6 out of 10
and then
I give her one numerical value
and only one for the whole package
because people are not a bunch of separate
compartmentalized things
people are wonderful beautiful creatures
even when they're like a 6 out of 10
you gotta
but her pussy game man
10 out of 10 on that shit
here's what I think that
every scoring system falls apart when you try to do it that way
cause at some point
on my anime
list one of the scores that
it's like sound, video, character story
and then enjoyment
and enjoyment
is such a weird thing
because like overall
the music but overall enjoyment was pretty shit
but here's the thing
to me enjoyment really means context
and like here's the thing
if I watch a show like let's say Lucky Star again
and the context is super important to why I like the show
and then another show
that I still think is amazing but there's like
no context into why
what if I watch a show with all my best friends
and I give it a 10 out of 10
versus someone else who watched a show like alone
and they had just been shot and they're currently bleeding out
like okay my German was a 0
didn't like the show
I think that's another one of those cases
of like being so close to getting it
but not quite where it's like
you get that there's an ephemeral
factor to why you like stuff
and you try to then define that
and it's like those scores
mean nothing
like the context
should not have a score
it should just be a part of why you like the thing
you know like the context is inseparable
from the work but like
I don't think like if I
if I watched like Kaiba
and it didn't have any special
additional context score
so that's just a 0
and then Lucky Star it's a 10
against the other like am I supposed to go
story 9 characters 9
art 9 sound 9
context 0 and then take the
average of that and it completely
fucks up the score it's like no
it's indefinable
getting towards something about
just the general consumption of media
and sorting your feelings on it
that has been like one of the best things
that you've indirectly taught me is
do not hold on to your opinions
don't hold them as precious
don't flip at the drop of a hat
because it's way way more
oh man that's also another
once someone especially
an amateur reviewer give something a 10
they feel an obligation
I used to feel an obligation
to make sure that I always
continue to like it and if there was any doubt
I would start rationalizing to myself
no it has to still be a 10
it has to be nothing is worse to me
than when someone has
a narrative opinion
that has clearly
been like too long
in the works like when you like you said
like they have their favorite anime
that they watched like five years ago
and they continue to compare everything to that
even though if they watched it again
then they have to select I've seen it
where people like rewatch something
and immediately realize they don't love it as much
as they did before but
because they gave it a 10 once
they don't want to admit they were wrong before
and so they keep talking about it
as much now but I mean it's still the greatest thing
well I think part of it
is feeling like they don't want to be wrong
but I think more importantly it's the feeling of
they have an obligation to be loyal
they don't want to abandon it
for example you did a full playthrough
with your brother on Sonic Adventure 2 battle
and it was your favorite game as a kid
a lot of people remember that game very fondly
even though it's objectively shit
you have no
you have no trouble
reconciling the fact that you think it's a terrible
game now but you thought it was an amazing game
then and you can simultaneously appreciate
your nostalgia for it while also hating it
you don't have to
continue to say it's good in order to
enjoy your nostalgia for it
and it's so much more satisfying
to just let your favorite stuff change
constantly like moviebob's favorite game is still
Super Mario Brothers 3 and I'm like are you fucking
kidding that's...
I don't care that you have your favorite game
forever the idea that your favorite
to change constantly is way more
interesting I think it's both possible
and probable to actually have a
favorite forever if it's just something that's
so special to you
and that's why letting you
like I think that did you if you were
to rewatch any show you gave a 10 and you didn't like
it as much you would have no trouble
no hesitation giving it an 8 or a 7
and you would totally take things
off your favorites list rearrange it which is
why the fact that Kaon has been
at your top for like 5 years is so
impressive it has not been up there for 5 years
but it's faltered here in your
it's been a little while it's been for 3 or 4 years
it wasn't even when I first watched it I didn't even consider
my favorite show of that year
well however many years
it's very impressive that it actually
has managed to regain that position
yeah it's a yeah
and like yeah I change stuff
up so much but yeah like I think that it's possible
to have a favorite because of the context
around it and like that that it's been
with you for so long that that's why it's your favorite
but again it has to be
genuine like my friend
Ghost Lightning his favorite anime has been
Super Dimensional Fortress Macross for like
27 years or something like that
but he rewatches it all the time
and like reaffirms his feelings
and finds new reasons that it's his favorite
and like recontextualizes it
and like has all these different reasons
whereas everything else in his favorites list
changes all the time you know it'll be like
oh I just watched Utena and now that's
my number 2 because I can't believe it's real
you know you have to ask yourself a question though
is it possible that that show
he could learn something about it
or that something else would like beat it out
considering all the investment he's now
put into loving that show
that's the thing I think that's valid though
like I don't think it's that he's blind
like he's very openly admitting
like I don't expect anyone else to feel this way
but here's why I feel this way
it's not like you're not allowed to do that
like there's so much to why he likes it
that he can go on and on and on all day
like I've listened to him talk for hours about
this is a more recently
exacerbated problem when
fan communities show up on Tumblr
oh god let's not even get into fan communities
that's a whole other
well the point is it makes people even more invested
and it means that like people have to keep
it's that much harder to get out of it
like Undertale is a single player game
with a few different story paths
and once you're done you could probably put it down for a year
and come back to it but because
so many people just draw comics and no one cares
but then they draw stands crying and people care
and now they have to care about Undertale forever
like mage says currently it's her favorite game ever
would it be without Tumblr? no definitely not
what would be my favorite game though
it's a matter of you get trapped
you get trapped in the idea that you're a fan
of this thing and that's like
I think the problem is just people
taking things as their identity
like identifying themselves as a fan
I think that's how so many of those
nostalgia things stick around for so long
is like that uh
cause my ex-girlfriend was pretty bad about this
like everything she liked as a kid was still
perfect to her because she liked it
as a kid but then I would like literally
watch her like re-watch something with her
and like see the realization
that I don't care about this anymore
but then she couldn't like admit it to herself
because she'd identified it
you know that was rough for me when I re-watched Poo's Grand Adventure recently
that's a movie that had a lot of
meaning to me and kinda shitty
kinda not that good
people just don't get it which is why they
when you stopped being interested in my little pony
that much people were like
you are betraying your identity
you are betraying the thing
you are betraying our entire religion
if you no longer like
this my little pony show that much
it's not a matter of fear
everything we knew about you must have been a lie as well
you must be losing your grip on your sanity
they couldn't understand that you just move on
to a different show
I've had so many people think that I became
a depressed and different person
just because I don't watch the same cartoons anymore
alright Jesse what else is on your list
let's see
the next one is flash
over substance
John Tron
what have you become
these days he's the prime example of that
I'm gonna say
it's not just flash over substance
because I think John Tron was always mostly like
flashy jokes
but do it right
if you're gonna have
take into consideration
what your production values mean
like I've been saying this a lot
how John Tron his set
does not look like a house anyone would live in
and therefore you do not have
it's like a creepy dark brick
fucking fortress
it's literally a set
when you watch John Tron's videos before
the idea was he's in his apartment
playing video games
when you look at him on the set you just think
why the fuck are you playing video games on a set
why are you doing that
completely undoing all the
comfiness of his old stuff
he's got this slave extra he hires
and he's got people coming in
through the door and dressing these fancy costumes
it's like what the
I actually like the Ethan Klein Kool-Aid thing
that was a good joke that was funny it was simple
it hit the point that was everything that was good about John Tron
he'll do these
he'll use these HD cameras
and have them
do these slow pans across
pans are not funny
wide angle shots are not funny
the close up shaky cam zoom in
on the face that's funny
that's good stuff
nothing will ever be funnier than
oh my god
and the camera just zooming in on him
making this facial expression
the face is funny the camera
mimics the joke
having a slow panning shot of you
in a weird set in HD
it's like this is what
I would expect from a product shoot
a fucking comedy video
here's basically how it works
the more details your joke has
the more every single detail has to be perfect
if your joke is bare bones
but if you're going to be complex
you have to be an absolute master
in every single medium
John got to this place
by doing the opposite of what he's doing now
and now he's trying to apply that same formula
and it's not working at all
it's totally wrong
if you're going to up your production
he can't be doing what he's doing now
if he's going to have all these high productions
he needs to do like, I don't know
something else
you can't just have a set
because it looks expensive
have a set because the joke involves a set
I get so mad when I think
about how much money he's wasting on this
only to make much worse content
it furiates me
it really hit me when
he had a small
horse pony on the set
and the joke was
I have a horse
and it's doing things to my set
it would have been a hundred times funnier
if he had one of his buddies in a shitty horse costume
that would have been so much better
not cost a thousand dollars for a day
and the whole video wasn't about horses at all
it was just he had the opportunity to buy a horse
I could never do this
how much funnier would it have been
if the joke had been
it was a guy and a horse
and he was dressed as a horse
it's now and then it's a guy in a horse costume
that would have been much fun
it's like some letterman shit
they bring out celebrities
and do retarded dances
it feels alien
do you think it's possible that
beatum has deliberately avoided buying good audio equipment
to create a narrative that he's some random asshole
throwing together something in a movie
in this case no
I think he's just cheap
he clearly doesn't prioritize you
I don't think that's the only reason
that he's considered getting good audio
he's like well if I keep it shitty
then I continue to look like a total jerk face head
and you know like
I don't think he really concerns himself
with his own YouTube narrative
there's three more things
there's only three more things on the list
this one is reviewing
people
don't do it
aren't we doing that right now
I mean like specifically
guys like Sargon of Akkad
really does is like pick out people
and that leads me to the next one
this is the main part of it
that annoys me
response videos
that pause to make a glib comment
about every fucking line
oh shit
Sargon of Akkad
even Thunderfoot kind of does it
he's better than most
amazing atheist, Shuwon head
all of those fucking people, TLDR
it is the laziest
whole way you can possibly do it
sometimes it's funny, I admit it, I've watched a lot
sometimes they're funny, especially like when I agree with them
and I'm like hey yeah fuck those guys
they're completely wrong, I don't give a shit about their opinion
like it feels good
but it's intellectually bankrupt
to act like the other person is just
you're just mischaracterizing everything they're doing
you're acting like your opinion is the only one that has
any value and the other people are obviously
objectively wrong
it's smug and like self-satisfied
and all these people are like shooting
over 100,000 subscribers because people
eat it the fuck up
it's like the way that children communicate
like you take everything a person says
you interrupt them and go child issues
second piece of shit
if you're gonna do it, one format that's especially bad
is anytime you're
talking it's represented by a still image
of your OC
everyone does that
one like 11 year old kid
made that for my roller coaster
tycoon 3 video
I commented so politely that he
deleted the video, deleted all of his videos
that were liked and apologized
and I'm like good on you
great example, I hate everything
we were talking about that the other day
if you do the still image
of your OC
YouTube is a fucking visual medium
you lazy goddamn hacks
everything is especially funny
because he's talking about Derek saying
I'm actually a decent person and I don't hate everything
and I love my work
even if you're on screen
and I also want to say
I hate any
dehumanizing arguments
even if someone says
something that you completely disagree with
they probably have a reason
and a background
and a reason that led them to that
and I understand being angry at people for being wrong
and spreading misinformation
but we're trying to
the way forward is conversation
insulting people
making them look like idiots
is not going to bring us closer to
like, YMS's response to Daddy Derek
was perfect because he was explaining
to him, here's the things you said
that are wrong, he has this very calm
demeanor like, I'm trying to explain it to you
he didn't just assume that everything was
obviously wrong, he didn't even need to explain it
he took the time and thought it out, it was good
he clearly came from the perspective
but YMS obviously thought Daddy Derek
just is ignorant
he didn't come at it like, this guy is an
evil monster who's trying to fuck us
out of our money, it's more like
Daddy Derek, you are ignorant
you don't understand what you're doing to us
having seen a cool cat save the kids
it's very understandable
so I think a great example of this
that happened to us just yesterday is
the gaming badger who was
railing on DeVoo and Jesse Wood
just because they said things that he doesn't agree with
and therefore he presents them
like they are fucking idiots
and we talk about it
we're all proud that Jesse blocked him on Twitter
and it's like, dude
you haven't, you have dehumanized
your opponent
have fun being proud of the fact that you're an annoying moron
and somebody hates you enough to block you
have fun, go ahead and frame it
on your fucking wall
I want you to fucking frame it so that you can look at it
every day and it can fucking remind you
what a stupid piece of shit you are
you dumb motherfucker
the day that Endless just
blocked you for you
was the most important day of your life
and for me, it was Tuesday
motherfucker
wait, who are you talking about?
it's a gaming badger
let's move on real quick
I don't hate everybody
who does that, I just think their videos
are vapid
they're playing the game man, they're hustling
so do what you gotta do
great minds discuss ideas
average minds discuss events
small minds discuss people
like Ellen Roosevelt or something
I think it was Ellen DeGeneres actually
in her leading role as Dory
alright, Jesse
and the final
the final thing on my list
the number one worst thing
that a reviewer can do
listening to jerks on the internet
tell you how to make your videos
oh, shit
oh, it's a mom shall be
and that's an excuse
you all failed
I think Jesse would self-aware
kind of joke right there
that's why he gets all the subs
that's why he gets the big ones
although
word of advice, take everything we've said
in this video very seriously
and please consider it, because I don't want to have to watch
more shitty reviews
I bet there are people who already sucked
if they tried to follow this advice
for some reason it'll get even worse
if they aren't true to their crappy selves
I'm not saying
let this inform your overall idea
of what a review is
it's all part of the artistic process
you put out the ideas that you think might work
you see how they do, and then you adjust
and you find out what works
and better yet, just rip off all of us
because we're all great
and that's the only reason
like DeVu said earlier
the reason that the five of us are friends
is that we all love one another's videos
the reason this friendship happened
is because each of us were very big fans
of what the others were doing
and so we all sort of became
this group
and the reason that
it's just that we all have the same ethos
and we all sort of understand reviews in a similar way
and we've even kind of tried to introduce
other people that weren't
that and just put them in here
and it just doesn't work out, they just leave
because I think you really need
if you want to impress
us specifically
please follow the rules we've talked about
and maybe you'll become our best friend
in the world
you could be in the procrastinators next time
that's your incentive to make videos that I want to watch
that's going to decentivize them
don't want to be with these fucking assholes
the egos are getting
ridiculous right now
I think this is our longest video
beating out episode one now
maybe only by a little bit
we pretty much covered what I wanted to say about
reviewers having rules
I guess my rule is
don't
just don't apply the same logic to everything
everything is made
for its own unique purpose
and you should be looking for
what is interesting and unique about that work
if you can watch a show
and be like well the pacing sucked
it's like by what metric
what are you comparing it to
what's the grounds here
I don't like it when people have a very specific
this is what a show should be
it's so narrow minded
and puts everything in such of a same formula
and box that it really
disturbs me
you need to talk about why what it attempted to do
either succeeded or failed
and it's one thing to say in pacing
or in passing rather
the pacing bothered me
but if you're writing a reviewer analysis
you have to justify that
you have to justify that belief
because that's the point of a reviewer analysis
is not to state your opinions
because I don't give a fuck about your opinions
it's to justify your opinions
that's the purpose
yeah
to just want to say
if you haven't
if you've always wanted to
do reviews and stuff
don't let us like all these rules
intimidate you into not trying
you're allowed to make a lot of mistakes
and make a load of shitty videos
the only way to make good videos is to make a lot of shitty videos
eventually if you keep trying to improve you way
I think
for the number one thing is
just don't send them to me
make all those shitty videos
just don't make me watch them until you're confident
sure
I mean I know it's obvious
but you know do the videos you want to do
like if you want to have an ultimate example
the new storyteller makes videos for himself
and him alone and he clearly really likes
doing it is that that sonic guy
no he's a guy who does that
Thomas the Tank engine
that guy
yes
what was his name said again
the new storyteller
well over 10,000
Thomas the Tank engine
he's the most prolific person ever
he makes like three a day
and they're long
they reach like two hours
so do what you want
because I think a lot of people just really like making boring videos
and if you just want to come to peace
to terms with that
oh I have no qualms with anybody
who does something just because they want to
like just because it seems like
I have problems with people who want to be famous
or they want to be in the reviewer circles
or they want to be just like their idols
and then they completely misinterpret it
well because you see for me the number
one of my biggest incentives for being on this
for what I'm talking about here is there's this guy who does
really basic videos
very basic videos that tell me nothing
but then he also feels bad because he can't come up with ideas
and he doesn't understand
and he's not
he's like unsatisfied with his videos
but he's not trying to pursue
something interesting
what do you do with people like that dude?
you tell him just like keep trying
there was a great Ernest Hemingway
that I just saw on Twitter today
which was
if you think you want to be a
it was anyone who wants to be a writer
but doesn't write doesn't
sure
if you think you want to be a writer
if you don't like writing don't try to write
and that's exactly what happened to me
we were discussing this last night
that I didn't you know for a long time
I thought I was going to be a filmmaker
I thought I was going to be a novelist
and I really for like years put myself in that mindset
that that's what I was going to do
and then I just didn't write
and at some point I woke up to the fact that
if I'm not writing like everyone who is a good writer
who writes professionally
all they like to do is write
Stephen King pumps out a book every year
literally all he likes doing
if it doesn't come
like if it's not something that you
innately want to do
then maybe it's not for you
like if it's something you have to force yourself
and you don't even enjoy it
and you just feel like you have to because it's obligated
you know
because this shit is hard fucking work
this takes a long ass time to make something
like all of my videos are completely out of like
I can't live with myself not sharing these opinions
you know
especially Jesse is the most like
I can't do anything but make videos
and therefore that's what I'm going to do
guy you know
yeah like if your only way to make
like let's say by default you make your videos
shittily like they don't have good production values
but if
by making the videos well produced
and following these rules that we've outlined
makes it completely not fun for you
like obviously making the videos good
takes a lot of work and it gets really tedious
but if the work
really drains your
enjoyment of it
then just make shitty videos
because then those videos would have more soul
and soul counts for something
make shitty videos and don't complain that you're not popular
and don't send them to people
don't complain that we're making fun of you
the number one golden rule everybody
the only one that is really important
the only audience that
matters is you yourself
fuck everyone else
the audience is always wrong
everyone can go fucking take a long walk
off a short pier
anyone who tells you what to do
or fucking fuck them all
fuck them the golden rule
as always
doctor horseshoes golden rule
fuck them
alright that's it everybody
see you next time on the procrastinator's podcast
hopefully you gained some insight
into this or just enjoyed the catharsis
of listening to us beat up on
people
just some real shit
as soon as you said your big point
it was your skype
I just laid down the most inspirational shit
and no one will ever hear it
but it'll be in the recording though
rest easy
my friend
you're gonna get the recording it's gonna be like
remember
alright let's all stop our recording
alright everybody say goodbye
goodbye
bye B
I'm just making fun of myself at this point
frankly