Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
guy ever. Today we're joined by Goblins 1 through 4 and I'm here to slay them all. Goblin
1, aka Ben Goblin. What do goblins sound like in goblin slayer? I haven't uh, I don't partake
I don't partake of the eastern of the eastern scrolls. Yeah, no one knows. Hippo goblin. Ben,
that SFX that just came out of your mouth is like point for point like exactly the same
as the goblin like noise in the Jimmy Neutron video game that I reviewed. Exactly that.
Little Aurora goblin. I am the purple one. And Tom Gobliver. My parents fucked up my name
really bad. Doesn't work at all. Nate, I'm here, I'm gonna collapse a cave on you all,
you're all dead. I am the goblin slayer, that's what I do. Nate. There it is. Nate. Here we
are. Nate. Yeah. Nate. What? Chicken butt. Do you remember as kids on our dad's computer running
Windows 3.11 for work groups? Do you remember a game called Dark Castle?
Not just from that. It was a black and white game. It was like a side scrolling kind of like
puzzle adventure and it was like you go into a dark castle right and it's like you know screen
after screen of like things to do in this dark castle and you know it was way too hard for a
kid like I could I could not figure it out but you know you you would go into a new room and
sometimes there'd be like bats and you could like you could pick up rocks and you could throw them
the control it was it was like tank controls to the to the nth degree it was like first person
this is no no no no it was like it was like a you were a little man in sort of a side scroll
I don't know kind of every screen had its own perspective but anyway I just bring it up because
I remember there was one screen where there were these little like goblins running around
and they would and you would have to throw rocks at them to knock them out and they would make a
sound like I recognize that sound not because of the Jimmy Neutron thing although it's similar
it's because AVGN reviewed Dark Castle and he and he got it right that's right he did he did
and it was an incredible blast from the past because yeah yeah yeah I mentioned guys I've
actually been getting into AVGN recently but specifically I watched one of his game reviews
but the rest of it was just all his like monster madness movie compilation reviews those have been
great those are pretty good times and whatnot yeah those are so good I should get back to
a fucking like he like knows about movies you guys he like knows about like makes them and
everything it's fucking crazy childhood is thinking AVGN is funny adulthood is realizing
that it's all about Bored James no it's terrible no it's the truth Bored James is very funny
I'm looking at his review of Dark Castle right now and this looks vaguely familiar
that's the best I got it's the best I got it's like he's taking you back to your past
hey speaking of getting taken back to the past it's almost to play to play shitty games that
suck ass yeah yeah yeah yeah uh uh my mom came to visit uh as made famous by the last episode of
Shackles for heckles yeah I hate you how how do you how did that how did that go like okay so so I
could not I could not fucking believe you pulled that shit Ben and team was kind of great Shackles
for heckles so always tune in you never know what's gonna happen it was it was well it was it was
munchy and hippo and I jumped in a little late um for for TF2 yeah and I came in to chastise Ben
for being late releasing the pcp episode and uh and I had his mother our mother on deck to yell at
him for being late that's fucking incredible like it was great I like I couldn't I I did not expect
to actually be her so like I was expecting you to have like Michelle do a voice or something
or something like but no I was like oh my god
hippo hippo when like did you accidentally invite Byte instead of Ben to TF2 that time
oh no I was doing it as a meme for like five minutes oh like we need Byte on the team like
he's in an integral part oh yeah he's he's a machine he's just one of the people who was on
my friends list I was just like you have Byte on your team friends list uh yeah from like
way a long time ago huh hey well so the reason I bring up my mom is because there's a topic uh
that I want to bring up related to that uh if you guys just seize the day on that um uh here it is
it's uh uh it's it's how desperately I want to make my parents proud of me is is the topic
I guess I guess making your parents proud or making proud of your boy I'll make you proud
of your boy that's what I feel like all the time and I know Munchie and I I think talked about this
on an episode previously but just having her around was so nice and so great and I so desperately
want to make my parents proud of me uh this is such a major motivation in my life alien concept
you're talking about to me right now that I can't even relate at all well that's interesting too
all right I have I have thoughts maybe because my parents literally dab on your parents and
no like that probably I just I just I have like I guess I have a similar related motivation I just
want to stick it to my parents okay that's okay I feel like those are two sides of the same coins
it really is it's just like it comes from a position of lover brutal hatred uh which is where
I'm coming from I have a lot of gratitude but again what were you saying well I was saying like
I have like I I know the feeling but I also like I have had the bad experience of that where like
trying to make my parents proud was like like a thing that fucked me up in school because I tried
really hard but I was really depressed and they didn't understand because I never talked about it
and it was and it was because I was trying so hard to make them happy and then they said
but we want you to be happy and I was like oh okay you know like I was I was severely fucked up in
the head and that like has ruined my my whole childhood and like I never really talked about it
like that so like and now having gone through that I I don't necessarily want to make them unhappy
I don't hate you know but like I'm I'm more like for me and then I guess yeah that's very
understandable um I mean that's what parents want right they want their kid to be happy well they
want them to be happy but I mean I talk about this and I think about this a lot it's like like I
want to do the things I want to do in life but I want to like make them feel not worried and
like content I just got I don't know what what changed at some point I just became so focused on
like wanting my parents to be happy with what I'm doing and you know what I say that but then like
I call them fairly rarely they're just like it's like a daemon in my mind you know my my desire
to make my parents proud I mean is that like a societal thing like you said I wouldn't be
fucking sick if I just fit in I you know I was probably one of the guys yeah um I'm pretty I feel
like I don't know it sort of feels like a sycophane task you know you're like like I don't know like
you're never gonna be perfect right I always never maximize this I always felt like I always felt
like attempts to do good attempts to do good and make the parents proud we're not generally met with
like any greater enthusiasm I don't know than than any other time I always felt like well I always felt
like trying hard to do that was sort of pointless well I think the maximum way like based on everything
that mom and dad always said grown up I think the maximum way to make my parents happy and proud
would be to be incredibly successful at something that I love doing yeah and being financially
secure so that they don't have to worry and you know like all the it's never going to be perfect
of course so that's why I think it's a large part of why I'm so economically well I mean you've you
I mean I mean you've you've done all that so so you're fine but I'm not I'm not I don't know
like I think about this a lot too our whole generation has such low standards for quote
unquote making it yeah mine are much higher than I think a lot of other people and so I just think
like like I mean for example like dad's career as a psychologist and stuff is like way beyond
anything like like what youtuber I wonder what tier of youtuber do you have to be at to be like at
the level of like earning as stable and good a living as like a professional psychologist
I would estimate it's massive I would estimate maybe maybe if you're in the 10 tens of millions
yeah exactly yeah exactly um and like as a as a programmer right now I do like so much
better financially doing that than youtube and I know I'm still a small youtuber but
it's like uh I don't know like I really want to do all those things that I love doing but I'm very
concerned about doing it in a sustainable way so that nobody they don't have to worry about me
and I don't know sounds like it's holding you back you material success always just seemed like a
rigged a rigged game to me you know but it's there I mean obviously there's a lower threshold
you have to be no one who wins it no one who wins that game says yeah I made it and now I'm happy
well some people do it's what it's a security blanket sort of thing I think yeah it's like a
safety net more than anything else well I mean obviously having enough that you're not in financial
peril is good but I mean like like having a million in the bank so that you can just go try to be a
huge I mean our dad is not I mean our dad is not rich right like our dad like we're not we're not
rich per se but like I think I think I think I've heard that like something like 50 or $60,000 a year
is like the cutoff point where like happiness does not increase beyond that I believe that was 70,000
and that that is the peak and after that it goes down if you if you go up I'm pretty sure our dad
makes more than that maybe not by that much yeah yeah yeah he makes more than that and like you know
I mean I'm not criticizing the guy for making money but yeah I don't but I think that in in
his case it's he's it holds true that more money does not increase happiness you know okay Ben
you're totally right but all of us here today are significantly below that threshold wait even so
just saying that there's even even not wait no wait not you with your real ass job I am actually
above that threshold at this point yeah obviously obviously uh well I mean it's it's a it's a thing
of like living well within your means like like as long as you're happy with less then you don't
need as much money and I agree that like it seems like people of our generation have lower standards
for what would be considered good enough my standards are too low I'll just I'll just come right
out my standards are too low I'm glad that you admit it yeah but like yeah but like it's it's not just
because like oh our generation is lazy it's also like like things are more expensive and jobs are
harder to find and like that it's not exactly the same criticism isn't about laziness so that the
generation is bad it's that like for whatever reason like their standards were just made to be lower
that like because everyone wants to be like a starving youtube artist or something and obviously
not everybody but like in in my circles like guys like like really Ben is the worst of the worst
absolutely you know you know I'm just I'm just it's a rigged game material success is a rigged
game I'm convinced I don't disagree I mean if you're shooting for like your money and possessions
aren't gonna make you happy when you're about and I and I know and I know that my I know that my
standards are too low and as a result I am I mean you know I'm motivated I don't know I'm not
unmotivated but I am I am I'm I've kind of I've sort of let myself be content with enough to get
buy on but not enough to like be secure exactly Ben's an economical chameleon able to adapt to
whatever situation he siphides himself in pretty much damn um humans can adapt to anything do you
feel this whole thing about want to make your parents proud I mean obviously to some degree
but I'm just curious what you think oh yeah like I've been I used to have like this terrible
terrible issue of um feeling like I've disappointed my parents because I feel like a lot of sort of
you're just a lowly artist after all so that's a that's a blow to the old parent ego I'm sure
kind of like that was a joke and you guys did not rebut it so I'm uh no I mean I mean we're all
creative people yeah you guys all know no this is terrible so we're all like yeah no no no that's
true okay I just feel like my parents invested a lot of hope in me and I kind of disappointed them
at least that's how I felt I don't feel like that anymore but it took me a lot but yeah yeah I mean
it's excuse me I mean every parent has no idea what a child is until it's already grown up and
then well I have a sister especially if you're the older one and I have an older sister yeah maybe
your older sister really fucked up I don't know if this is true or not and they were hoping that you
would be the one to save the day which is what I am for our parents for sure she's doing quite quite
well actually but but she has like I don't want to get into it because it's personal for her so but
like yeah I should have I should have killed you in the cradle when I had the chance to like now
motherfucker oh no all right all right I want to go around the room okay how many of you your parents
were like how many of these child fulfill my fantasies because I failed no well our parents
were definitely not like not like they were very encouraging yeah about what we wanted a lot of
my pressure I feel I was self-inflicted yeah with myself did did you have any of that kid no because
like if I like I used to think like oh shit I got it I got to do all the the stuff I got to be the
perfect boy because I like my parents and I want to make them I don't want to make them unhappy
but like if I thought about like their decision to bring me into the world it wasn't so that I could
become you know the prime minister or whatever it was just so that they could have like a nice family
and then as long as I'm a nice son that's all it really matters yeah I just treat them right and
that's it I what about you Tom yeah my parents like they don't my parents don't really even have
dreams that they even want to pass on to me uh my dad's a writer though that sounds like he writes
the only reason he even started writing is because I told him to so I'm gonna take credit for that
but uh no like my parents they're just like they have a very specific vision of what they want me
to be like they just like please please son get get a real salary job and stop like hobbling around
and and just like being a piece of shit and I'm just like no I like I love being in the gutter
it's so comfortable the slime I just like it gives me solace at night I have another I have one more
thing about why it's a rig game not just material success but pleasing your parents specifically
as a rig game because as the old saying goes parents will never get it right I suppose yeah
I mean how how many parents like really know their kids like you know what I think about Ben
all that all that all that all that parents know like all that most parents like they have some idea
of what their kid does like like our parents don't understand don't really understand what we do
right they and and I think that's probably true for most people like they'll know they'll know
their kids job title they might know what the one or two things that they will have loose associations
that they make oh my son's a lawyer oh my son's a dentist or whatever but they don't know right like
all they want well they wouldn't know like if I was like I'm a programmer they also don't understand
what that consists of yeah well exactly yeah so they can so they can say oh my son's oh my son's
a programmer oh my son's a programmer and that's fine you know that probably is pleading but it's
just aesthetic like like for them on the parent side it's just an aesthetic thing and say oh my
son's a programmer oh my son's an artist yeah it doesn't always the real they don't they don't
experience the reality of it and I feel like it's a fool's game not always though like I have a friend
and her mom is very very involved in her activities and stuff and she always knows what's up so well
that's not that's not me well I think it's not so much like literal like they don't get it it's that
like for them being a parent is an entirely different lifestyle that they've known so
everything they're doing is like they're full of stress they're like oh shit this is my life is
completely different now I've got to try and adapt to it like by the time they're grandparents then
they get you like grandparents and and and grandchildren like well my grandma so can't
wrap her head around the concept of the computer I mean it's it's not it's not like the the the
literal like what the kids are doing but the fact that like what you know how to raise a kid
like like the fact that it's new and it's different and it's challenging and it's all this stuff and
it's like a grandparent would would get it a bit better because they're not they're not in that like
you know they've done it already they can see it happening again they're like ah yeah I got this
I think the difference there is that like a parent a parent has the job of making their
kid as good as they can be a grandparent has almost zero responsibility so they can just
chill and like connect with the kid it's it's why it's why grandparents and uncles and aunts are
like more fun a lot of the time absolutely they don't have to be the disciplinarian or anything
but I was gonna say about uh to to Ben's point I kind of do agree with the whole um parents will
never get it never get a thing to a to a pretty large that's not even just that's not even just
like an edgy teen thing I just think like parent unless you're unless you're one of those kids
who has who's like super close oh best friends with my mom who but I but I make I'm making a
jerking off gesture right now good um yeah I was listening to Joe Rogan's podcast he had Billy
Corrigan on who is the main guy from uh Smashing Pumpkins and like Smashing Pumpkins is like a
huge world-renowned band super famous whatever point is um uh like Billy Corrigan was talking
about how like he had I believe he said it was his grandpa and like in his family they got that he
was like a big deal but his grandpa even when he was like a platinum selling like huge deal
didn't give a shit until like until until like was he on Oprah or something no no no none of that
stuff made any difference to this guy but it was when he found out how much money that his son was
making that's when he was well now I get it now I understand people care about this and that's
why I'm saying Ben the parents won't care they'll never understand exactly what you do as nobody
can really understand what's going on in your job pretty much unless they're in the same exact field
but they'll understand if you have that dollars in the bank my dude that's what they'll understand
the universe that's how my parents work because they wanted to take it from me as soon as they
thought I was making money they immediately started charging me to stay in their house despite despite
my charging you rent what villains am I right I don't mind paying rent now guys now I don't mind
paying rent the thing was that it was as soon as they found out that I had money it's like oh we can't
let you keep this now we will we'll take it more like the fact that you can't pay me no no no no
you gotta you gotta understand the full context the full context was I was working a job yes
then I got uh laid off then I got on patreon and then they were like oh uh now that you're making
money online we need to charge you rent but if you go get a real job again you can stay for free
that is a little bit uh a little bit iffy my dude fuck your dreams go be a slave was was pretty
much the message I got from that point okay guys guys guys so uh um earlier I did sort of protest
against uh Ben's argument but like I do agree with him to to an extent like a big extent the the
one I mentioned was mostly an exception because from my experience is Ben is quite right at least
in my experience like I think the people that are close with their parents are kind of creepy
personally yeah yeah I love our parents my whole family has no idea what I'm doing online sorry I
was just saying that like I love my mom I love having her around but like I love to see her once
it's not even that I don't like to see her it's that we don't have a ton in common actually yeah
so yeah I know we've got like our whole lives I mean so that's fair we can talk about any of
that shit but uh it's like I think all the time about just like working and editing and being online
and doing this stuff and you know my job and stuff and uh I think she wants to hear about that so you
know yeah it's different I think there should always be like a healthy awkwardness when it comes
to parent child yeah because like with your siblings like you are the same like you know
you get it you you know you're basically the same age you you would understand each other a little
um you should always know your siblings better than your parents like if your parent comes in
and watches sees you watching a youtube video that's kind of weird like you should be a little
like ASMR slime uh goop extravaganza you know it should be it should be awkward because if it's
not awkward then either your parent is too as I hastily put my dick away yeah like you are doing
like you were doing like the too much of a normie thing my sister just don't understand me like at
all like the difference between me and my sister is she's significantly older than you right like
six six years I think but she's so she's such a normie like like like a month ago or so that
should be a buzz sound of mage going she's such a normie I want that your sister sounds like exactly
the kind of person who would get hello fresh like that coward monkey white picket fence 2.5 kids
ass motherfucker there was a great voicemail about hello fresh I can't wait to get to she does have a
house and she does have a challenge she's gonna maybe get a second one my sister turned into a
normie and it's been this slow decline that's just depressing me to no end let me let me tell you
let me tell you a quick story about my sister I just kind of made me sad like a month ago or so
she was like hey I was talking to my boss about you and like I have nothing to say about you
because I don't know what you're doing could you like send me some of your drawing so I could show
it to her I was like okay that was weird but you know why why are you talking to your boss with me
about me yeah but yeah I sent a few pictures a few drawings to her and she was like oh all of them
except for this one are ugly
she's been like this for like forever like the last time I showed her a drawing was back in
my pony days and I showed her a drawing of a pony and she was like is is that a flower and I'm like
never showing you anything ever again and then I made the mistake of showing her stuff we need to
get a picture of mage's sister put it on that meme of the guy and just be like have the have your
drawing like is this a flower oh yeah oh yeah yeah that's a we need clearly no observational skills
whatsoever hey I've got I've got uh an extension of this topic slightly which is ties into a couple
things that just happened to me earlier today uh which was so so um another way I want to make
my parents proud and to like be a real man this is definitely more of a socially influenced thing
is I want to be able to like fix things and repair things and you know be a man and that in that
kind of way and I'll uh so so I was using Michelle's uh electric skateboard and stuff
and you're using it a ton and having a great time but a week ago it broke and it wasn't
fucking working and it was expensive so I was I was very upset and I thought that I had broken a
thing through excessive use this is very sad to me but like a man I took it apart I found the
problem it was that one of the rubber bands had worn one of the rubber like treads had worn out
from excessive use excessive hardcore grinding and rail riding uh naturally ordered the part
got here yesterday replaced it myself was out there killing it and having a great time and
being a hero and I love fixing things also side note I fell for the first time off the skateboard
and got a big old fucking raspberry on my fucking arm and I was posted for you now in chat so you
can all enjoy I don't think I want to see my wound I'm not sure they used raspberry I don't think
that is what it's right right raspberries are like raspberry is what will ferrell said in uh
anchorman when uh jack black fell off his motorcycle and had a bunch of scars and you know you blow
raspberry you don't get a raspberry from you mean an indian burn he said raspberry and anchorman
god damn it he's he's he's he's he's not even human well the point is I love fixing things and
repairing things uh and it was great yeah and I'm better than all of you because I did when you feel
good about fixing shit it's like yeah yeah it was broken that's right that's why you wear longer
that protectionate uh well I actually you could have stuffed this as a matter of fact mage I actually
was wearing my hoodie I got this through the sleeve of my hoodie so if I wasn't wearing it
I could only imagine how fucked up either yeah pretty rough I actually I hit a patch of wet grass
on a black top and just went whoa plop sick it was pretty dope I was actually I'm now I've
gotten my first fall and I feel good about it it's out of the way um I'm gonna be shredding your
neighborhood soon listener so keep an eye out for me spot me in your hometown I'm doing a cross
country tour I'm gonna fall on your lawn and sue you uh okay that's all I had to say do you guys
enjoy building things Tom you build computers I think you can relate to this it's fucking it's
it's a good feeling I've been like building more computers than ever because like we're returning
digi house into a cyberpunk 2077 technocratic future state uh dope there are computers everywhere
it's insane ordering parts all the time building things fixing things getting pissed off and things
this is all part of going full games uh a part of it yeah some of it just like I I just had a
bunch of shit lying around and I was like oh yeah I don't know what I'm gonna do this I guess I'm
gonna sell it did you just like no just bring it over here I'm like okay so now there's like a
computer in every room in the house for no reason and uh yeah and and I'm building one for May that
I had just hitting around I'm gonna upgrade that make that cool because like they broke their laptop
like three times in a row and it was funny okay the screen just falls out now and it's it's insane
yeah so I'm just I've just become the IT for I am game that's my job description it's real
oh good and that's what I do and uh yeah fantastic uh I can I can do other pools I can dovetail
into a new topic from here is that okay yeah go for it go in terms of technology and just in general
we have been having so much technical difficulties with trying to get I am games to work because
every time we switch it to a different game we got to change the entire setup get to unplug
everything and plug everything back in and then there's always something that breaks or doesn't
work and even in like my personal work doing like working on the game and and trying to just like
make computer shit work like digis uh motherboard didn't work for some reason so we had to send
that back and then like for some reason like my stream capture software on my big 12 core processor
can't record more than 20 fps unless I disable windows arrow I'm like there's a bunch of bullshit
that just constantly happens and I don't like like someone I ordered a new cpu for maze computer
I have to send that back because even though it's like the right kind it just doesn't fit in the
slot even though there's no reason it shouldn't be so I just want to get like a t-shirt that just says
it should be working but it's not because that's my entire life these are the kind of things that
make me want to kill myself and not put up with life anymore maybe you should maybe the t-shirt
should have a computer with a little speech bubble that says I'm supposed to be working right now
oh my god I am games oh and on the back there's a big I am games x pcp thing or something it's
like crossover damn that's good I could make that immediately we did I did just make a brand
new shirt for iam games yesterday and it was great the pcp will take a cool 98% of the profits from
that well I'm in both ventures so I double dip on the price that's true damn just saw this elbow
it looks it looks painful uh yeah it hurts a lot right now as a matter of fact you can see the skin
just scraped right off like with its ice cream scoop describe it with a tiny ice cream scoop just
I feel your description is worse than the image itself stop that's that's true the image it does
just look like a raspberry yeah yeah it's even got kind of like bumps on it the way I read well
Farrell is such a wordsmith I guess so yeah he's created a new phrase that did not exist before
I'm angry with him because I swear like blowing a raspberry it's like it's like yeah like it does
not leave a mark it's just like yeah mage you're you're absolutely right that this is a new
this is a new neologism playful with language and uh yeah raspberries can be many things sometimes
creativity try it out sometime yeah maybe send that to your sister when she went to ask what you do
stop drawing flowers mage get get more creative speaking of physical maladies
yeah um so I'm dying last week I was talking about how I could feel a cough coming on yeah it did
it did yeah we're all well aware at this point my throat hurt pretty bad for a while but that
went away and I thought I was over it but then I've just been I've just had like a I've had a
what what a what a doctor might describe as a productive cough uh forever since then is this
is a keto induced illness or no no absolutely no this happened this happened after I went to
I am games I'm pretty sure that I am games made me sick uh it had to be okay so it's a video game
we are just in yeah video game made me sick and now I'm like well now I'll like start breathing
and my breath will be all like oh yeah it'll all be all crunchy in my lungs because it's
mega man 11 literally gives you cancer conferred do you guys feel uh when you feel like that
afraid to go to sleep because you're afraid that you'll die in your sleep and your body just won't
be able to breathe yes but I'm all the time well I'm not about this not about a cough but about
things like a fever or something yeah like an asthma okay I've always suspected I have asthma
it's not for me it's not even when I go to sleep it's just all day every day even right now like
what if I just die I'm afraid this the switch is just gonna get flipped uh you know oh yeah I
I used to be really paranoid I think I'm a little less so nowadays but yeah yeah there was a time
when I was like what if I just die what if I just drop dead for no reason what if my heart just stops
you one could fixate their whole life on that but yeah I sort of get what you're saying but
like I don't fear death because like shit found like when you're gonna be dead you're not gonna
care that you're dead yeah I mean yeah when I'm dead I won't care but the me that is alive now
cares that I will be dead then and it's a separate for the living for sure if you're not gonna notice
that you're dead but no but but I notice now right now I'm afraid of it I understand the feeling
of I get what you're saying but I don't agree of feeling because like it isn't a rational thing
my room has as like a lot of dust in it and it has had a lot of dust ever since uh we like
refurbished the room underneath it and like the floor was all torn up and put back down
I need to re-go over it because there's dust there's like bits in the wall they're sort of
cracking and I know that every time I go to bed I think this is there's there's just dust in the
air there's dust all over the place and sometimes when I go to bed I'm like I'm breathing it in
I can feel it going down my throat and I'm like all right I know in the morning I'm gonna be
you know smokers cough like here yeah I'll be fine later but like it's happened too many times
and I haven't done anything about it and it's sort of like I feel like this room that I'm in
has given me like an eternal cold that is not debilitating but like it's just like
I'm sort of stuffed up at all times with like dryness but like it's never really it can't
like I don't remember what it feels like to not be stuffed up and it's the sort of it's the sort
of thing where it happens for so long that I'm not even really sure whether it's happening or not
maybe I'm just like losing my sense of smell normally and this is why we need transhumanism
I'm so I mean that's true we need uh uh okay so first of all somebody please draw a picture of
Gibb uh eyes wide open bloodshot staring up the clouds of dust hanging over him as he tries to
sleep it's not a lot of dust but like over the course of like months and months like I haven't
I haven't even put a put a I don't know a water in here I don't know what you're supposed to do
about dust like a lack of dust you just put dust in there you got a dust yeah I gotta remove the dust
do I mean okay the right thing to do is to like to rip down the walls and then re-plaster them
because the plus I was gonna say if it like if more is coming from the walls uh I don't know
what's to be done about that I gotta move maybe go to different room I guess I mean yeah it's it's
not like every night is terrible but like occasionally it'll be like oh yeah fuck I think it's like
it it it it adds to a cold like it's cold like I might have a cold now but like it's made it so
that the line has the the line has blurred between having a cold and not having a cold
like I sort of like suddenly I'm like I'm sneezing I'm like oh wait am I sneezing or do
I have a cough or no and actually I'm fine like I sometimes I just don't know and I think I'm dead
I think no one should live in that kind of in between world the twilight it's kind of weird
it's kind of weird to be constantly not sure and kind of definitely sure that I am sick I just
remembered something that that kind of relates to this topic of of death and sleep and stuff
so back in my so back in my Lithuanian home and in this room that I usually stay in the layout
has changed over years every now and then and like there used to be like the where the bed is now
it used to be on the opposite side and there's a shelf like where it used to be okay there used
to be a shelf on the side where the bed is right now and the thing is back when the bed was on the
other side one night the shelf just kind of fell and it like it was the big crash in the middle of
the night as well and it it spooked me really really bad and that was back when I was living there
but now whenever I go over during the summer I have to sleep under the same shelf that fell at night
oh no that's a real uh what's that sword the edipus
damocles? sort of damocles? thankfully the shelf has been removed this year so I actually
managed to sleep peacefully oh man that's nice I mean who the fuck would want to sleep under that
I'd be freaking out the whole time oh I thought you said like you you had to as in like I just
want to feel that rush like at any moment all night while I'm sleeping I can't I can't sleep without
that adrenaline I have the same paranoia whenever I have to sleep but whenever I sleep on a bunk
bed I'm always like if I'm on the bottom bunk like the top one's gonna follow me I'm fucking dead
to be to be quite fair like I'm not that scared of dying myself I just feel like it would be an
inconvenience because I want stuff like I want to do some stuff in my life and I haven't done it yet
I was like well I don't want to understand that's where a lot of the fear for me comes from is just
that like I if there's so much not on the table yet there's so much I still have to do I just I
just be annoyed if if there's some sort of afterlife I just be annoyed just like well I wanted to
do this thing and now I can gosh you know it's it's weird before like bucket lists and stuff because
I I never felt like I remember like as a young child like oh shit a bucket list is things you
have to do before you die and like every cartoon has that episode where the character thinks they're
gonna die and they do everything on their bucket list and I'm like I should write my own and then
I it it's just never actually appealed to me to have a list of things I need to do because I don't
I don't know I just don't care I guess there's some things I I guess I take things as they come
that's fair now that I've like been to Hawaii like I feel like that would be something that I would
have put on except I've already done it but like I'm sure like it's made me think about like other
things I'd like to do because travel munchies right guys travel is so great yeah it's so worth
doing to go to amazing places and I hate travel well fair you do it more than most of us I think but
probably more sick I do it pretty well she does it like once like twice a year she goes from one
place to another that's not an obligation though I guess I don't like I don't like traveling from
country to country I guess through the yeah you think you think it's hard going from country to
country over there in Europe it's just it's way easier like getting out of America is so much
harder although once Britain's out of the EU that might be yeah I'm thinking of doing like an EU
like a mega a trip just so I can see all of it before I'm locked out and forever that's a great
idea you really should do that I yeah I like that a lot I don't care how much hard it is I just don't
like the traveling aspect it was like so many people so many stupid inconveniences and waiting
in line waiting in lines with a lot of people I hate it I hate public places I like hang on hang on
I want to answer this question again if you had to go one place in the EU what's your number one
place you want to go I had to go one place um I would like to go Auschwitz please one ticket to
Auschwitz I mean I I'd visit I'd visit yeah but I want to go to Hamburg because I haven't been
I'd go there and press F
I was laughing at the meme would you say I'd go to Hamburg um because I've never really been to
Germany properly like I'd stayed there a little bit um for an animation thing but like um it's a
country that is cool and it's also not incredibly hot so that I won't die maybe it's a true Brit
you should go to I forget the town where the European Union is based in Germany but you should
consider blowing it up like uh you know like who's that who's that guy guy fox guy fuck pull a guy
fox on the EU and be a be a real best guy ever for no best guy forks damn it that's guy best guy
forks ever yeah that's it hey but what you need to do is you just you need to go to all the places
you want to go in the EU we need to make a vlog series about it called eulogy because it's dying
not bad not pretty good
make it happen now I hear that cat me yeah no that's not mine it's my cat my my cats oh my god
Luna get out of here oh no now you're having the same problems I used to I can't if I stand up I have
to take my headphones off and I can't hear anything um hey now you know my pain now you know my pain
I feel like I've talked a lot this episode I don't want to dominate but I do have a very funny
short story that I thought I'd bring up the thing is I don't know if I've told it before
have I told a story about me my dad and a roller coaster game in the past have I told the story
roller coaster not that I remember okay forgive me if I've told it before but I'm gonna tell it again
I was I was thinking about this I was telling this to Michelle and I just realized what a great
story this is um so okay so one day me and my this is the story of one of the worst things I've ever
done in my life uh is is what it is this is I think about this memory haunted by the ghosts of
what I did in this story to my dad and and so this is what it is this is what it is so I was around
I was probably around between 12 and 15 probably something around there and me and my dad it was
just totally normal we were at like some kind of store like a what's called like building 19 or
something or like oh dude I love building 19 yeah I think it was a store like that kind of just
suffer a little save a lot yeah yeah they're cool and um uh like as we're we just went to buy some
stuff my daddy cabling or tubes or something or whatever and uh and we're leaving and as we're
leaving I spy on the side of the of like the aisle there's like a game there and it's a roller coaster
game for the pc and it's not roller coaster tycoon it's something like like roller coaster builder
simulator 2000 or something some like nondescript totally unaffiliate with any big thing roller
coaster building game it's like an engineering sort of thing and I see this game and for some
unexplained reason I'm filled with lust for this game just immoral passionate massive lust to play
this roller coaster game he's a young man he's gotta have it sometimes yeah and so I say dad
you need to buy me this game and he's like he's like well uh oh okay um by the way this game is
like it was like 10 to 15 dollars I'm gonna say 15 or something and I'm like I don't have any money
on me and I'm just like I didn't have much at the time anyway dad buy me this game he's like oh uh and
my dad never buys me stuff um or not it's not that he's mean he's just you know like why would he uh
but but in this one situation I'm like dad buy me this game I need it I need this game that's pretty
frugal yeah yeah yeah and my dad he's just like he's just baffled understandably he's like Nate why
do you want this you really like this is the thing you want so bad and I'm just saying yes
yes I want it so bad uh I'm going to play it forever I say to my dad meanwhile in my mind
I know I don't even want this game that bad I don't even really give a shit why just why this game
I don't know I'm being so too faced in what I'm saying to my dad I'm manipulating him intentionally
pretending I have these strong emotions because I just kind of want to play this game a little bit
who wins in this situation what was that saying our lord and master who wins in this scenario
no one wins because oh I beg and plead convince him to buy this game and he really thinks he's
doing something real nice for me and he's it was it was a touching moment for him for me it was a
purely evil moment and so we get home we install the game on the computer I play it one time for
like an hour and I was super bored and don't give a shit and I never play it again I I just manipulated
my dad into spending $15 he didn't need to spend uh and it was the most evil I've felt about pretty
much anything in my life years later this was like a year ago or something I remember that this
happened and I just I throw myself at my dad's feet he didn't know any of this he just thought he
done something nice for me but I'm just like dad I need to confess something to you I I did a bad
thing and I tell him this whole story and he's just like oh I don't care it's fine yeah yeah nobody
gives it and so just I believe it was just yesterday I tell this whole story to my mom who's visiting
and she just looks at me you know Michelle's there and she just my mom looks at me just like
god you're boring
so my question for the group is do you like rollercoasters
wait what no nothing I do you like
oh yeah yeah so that we get the expert divu on on the show we do yeah yeah it would have been good
to have him here uh yeah I just I just get consumed by these tiny immoral things I've done in the
past this is what I'm talking about this is what I'm talking about you think you think you do a
thing you're you think your parents will feel such in such a way and they just don't like I've
there's been so like so many times like I thought parents would be mad and they didn't give a
shit so many times I thought they'd be pleased and they didn't give a shit in fact almost all
the time they just didn't give a shit I'm seeing up I'm starting to see a pattern here well they
sure they've they've they've given up they've let the the ship sail up to be fair though to be
fair though I didn't really think that my dad would care that much I just thought that this is
just something that really bothers me that I did and so I had to it's a good example of like
doing doing anything for your parents say doing anything to make them proud it's like it's a
fool's game you it's sysaphy and task you will never get that boulder up the hill in fact factoring
no seriously I factoring anyone else's feelings into any of your decisions at any time is a
fool's errand and is a mistake and will result in greater suffering for the world yeah it's going
too far no it's not no it's not you need to it's like you need to just eliminate you have to put
yourself first in any and all things you know it doesn't make any sense it does not make any sense
to do otherwise I think I know why that is for anyone it's it's because they made you and then
they were tasked with like making sure you didn't die for like 10 years oh and and then they had to
like deal with you being a teenager and all right well it's 18 20 whatever yeah once you hit 10
you they give you they give you a pokemon and they shove you out the first door like they do all
that stuff and then by the time you're an adult they're like just I'm done with you yeah they're
you're boring to me it's time to cash the chips in at that point it's time for you to go away and
then uh like put me in a home come back uh uh yeah I mean that's fair enough it's fair enough
you know the bend your point there reminds me uh I didn't really understand uh well what you're
saying reminds me of objectivism as explained by rucka rucka Ali in the podcast I did with him
about objectivism which I'm sure one could learn more about but it was I didn't fully agree with
him on this or that like that I subscribe to this belief but it was that like there's kind of an
inherent almost spiritual value in like pursuing one's own goals as opposed to like worrying about
society so maybe you uh you're a little bit of an objectivist in that in that way I mean I think so
yeah I don't know I sure as soon as everyone else is an object I really feel I really feel like when
you put like you can like you can factor others desires into your decisions as data points
for you to make an informed decision but when you put other people's needs above your own I just
it never a little cook it never works yeah it just doesn't like it just doesn't work I just
find that even if the goal is to like oh well we'll get this person what they want I just don't
ever feel like they actually are happy to receive the thing that you think they want it's like people
don't know what they want well it would be more like I think what you're gonna say is like you would
do things to make people happy so that they would then do things for you it's like or just that it
makes you happy that they're happy like but yeah like it would all come down to like yeah self-serving
things but like yeah if you don't feel like your parents give a shit then that isn't going to make
you happy it's kind of like that expression happy wife happy life which is just like yeah like if
you're married you know make your wife happy it'll make your life easy because you know you want to
just like yeah I reckon the only way I have the only way I interface with the universe at all
is my own level of happiness and I'm just aware that if I make the world around me happy and
better it'll be better for me too so that's yeah yeah yeah obviously I mean that's what I mean
like yeah yeah I think we agree on this pretty much yeah like like take take take take those things
into account but you always gotta put yourself first I totally agree okay all right then then
there's no need to argue any further uh well all right I feel like I got like three topics in this
time so who else who's that something to break I have something to talk about okay uh it's the
fact that I'm dead like hypocrites dead and he's been killed and he's never making a video game
reviews on the ground what uh canonically what's hypocrite doing right now what's the hippo he's mad
that I quit the show and he's writing his own reviews but they will never be published because
I deactivated no I banned him from using the computer yes he has to he has to ask me to use
the computer and I was like no how are you such a monster that you just made yourself the villain
of this tale I'm definitely the Maddox in in the in the breakup of me oh yeah well yeah I mean
let's talk about it so so it specifically what you've decided to do as I understand it um is like
the the game reviews specifically you don't feel are working out the way you wanted them to so you
want to direct your energies elsewhere right it yeah I mean I I framed it like that because it was on
that channel but like what what it really is is like the idea of like making a career on youtube
yeah has always been the thing that is it's you know the most stressful and the most difficult
thing and youtube used to be about just having fun and putting stuff on the internet to make people
laugh once money came into it money sort of you know owns your mind and then everything that isn't
making money is like oh that's a waste of time I didn't make money off of that when before it wouldn't
have mattered so much so like I've what I've done is that it's not just I'm not I'm stopping game
reviews is that I'm stopping youtube being my career as an end goal like if like if I ever make youtube
videos again they would not be for the purposes of building uh you know any sort of youtube presence
up and if it does happen it happens accidentally what about uh you talked about still doing I
think animations would those be posted to youtube in some capacity uh yeah because it's just an easy
way to put things on on the internet like youtube is a very handy platform but like as a career
opportunity like that's gone like I'm never gonna think of it as a career thing ever again
because it's just not worth it even if it gets better it's never gonna be perfect
oh and never gonna be good enough I think you know this is this is very interesting to have somebody
one of us uh adopt this opinion because the thing is I think it's a completely reasonable
and just grounded thing to recognize if you're just not obtaining the success or wealth or whatever
like at a certain point you gotta be like like I mean look at me I've decided I decided a long
time ago that I wasn't doing well enough on youtube to just do it so I like hopefully one day I'll be
able to uh and I'm working towards it but like yeah uh I want the fans of wanting I like I don't
actually want to have youtube as my career but I like uploading stuff on youtube and if it makes me
a little bit of money for like once every five months I don't mind yeah it's fine that's like I
think it's it's really just like I used to enjoy the video game review things because I watched AVGN
and I just wanted to do that and then I learned over time that youtube can be a career and like
jontron was making money and I was hearing about that on game grumps and I was learning about how
let's plays make so much money and then once that's in your brain every time a new fad comes in or
like a new billionaire youtuber or like a vine star like makes so much money you're thinking
oh if only I was doing that which is kind of easy like you know I just I just need to be doing that
and I can get so much money and it sort of muddies your intentions like the only reason I got on the
platform was not to make money it was to make stuff that I liked and the the two of them became
intertwined and like video game reviews became synonymous with money and because they weren't
making money they became depressing I know what you mean that's that is how it works do you know
for sure it's it's a shitty fucking feeling like there's like there's like a an area where like okay
if you're not making enough money to even have it be like anything then you probably like work a job
or like you do whatever else you need to make money and then you do the youtube like as for fun
and that has however successful it is and I feel a lot of people can do really well like in that
space then there there's the tier of like struggling to make it where you like try to make it a thing
that's kind of where I'm at where I'm like trying to get ahead trying to you know push ahead and
make enough money so it can be your thing but there's going to be tension there and temptation
about like selling out to make more money so you're making it and then there's that and then
eventually you can get past that like wave crest or whatever and you're in the land of you just
make enough money up top where you kind of have another freedom that you obtain and you can kind
of do whatever you want but even when you're there you have the constant fear that you'll lose right
there's no security on youtube like it can be gone at any moment like and then the people can turn
on you the algorithm can change you can't build up a safety net on youtube it's like every day
you're one bad word away from being dead I mean it's getting more like that all the time and I
feel like like this three tier it's kind of like a not really a class system because it's not like a
hierarchy it's just like I feel like like somebody who comes to mind is like mr meddaker is a guy who
like has a full-time job is a popular youtuber or you know internet aristocrat as it used to be known
like he isn't that first camp um in that he doesn't depend on it to like make a living and stuff at
least I don't think so he's like uh he's like uh deleted his accounts and like slashed and burned
and like yeah because they get too big before he wants that freedom so like that you can feel
about him however you want but like it's interesting to note how because he's never depended on it
you can you there's a sense of authenticity about his work I mean he just doesn't give a
shit about whatever his whole his whole his whole platform is like to point out how absurd
this entire like thing is yeah but and then like uh I mean that's absolutely true and then you when
you move up then there's other people and like it's sort of like you can feel the authenticity
kind of dissipate as it be like when when money comes into it and like you've know like hey man
I've got like a wife and kids I'm a youtuber I have to feed them I'll do whatever it takes
to get enough money to like feed my family this month or whatever you get guys like
not to shit on the guy or I mean he didn't do very good things but like Monday and Matt for example
is exactly the first person I thought of oh yeah he kind of like he's a full-time youtuber he got
some success he has a wife and a kid and he got into this thing and I mean whatever his whole
thing about claiming people's videos or whatever it doesn't matter the point is he like you could
feel kind of him tailoring himself and designing himself to be able to survive on YouTube and
don't get wrong I'm like this too with like we are going shit so I'm definitely in this camp as well
to a degree um and then like I don't know guys like James Rolf just like they've made and they're
in the clear basically yeah I mean what seems at least the thing is like you have to get to the
point where your brand self-perpetuates it's it's up you're no longer dependent on YouTube's mechanisms
like when you're in that like second rung you have to play the game because you have to build up
momentum you no longer have to I mean if I I'll bring I'll leave an example and I don't mean to
shit on the guy uh but Psy Psy is like that like he succeeded by the YouTube algorithm but it didn't
he he didn't have like a like a dedicated audience that was like I'm sure he'd agree with that
willing to I mean to a certain extent he did but like not to the extent that you would think like
like you know a lot of his videos went really viral and stuff and probably made a decent amount
of ad rev but then like when he tried to transition into other things like it just didn't carry over
for whatever for whatever reason yeah because it was all it was he succeeded on the algorithm
right it was the force the other that's true for him it was like if YouTube if YouTube just
dissipated then then it all it all went up in smoke and it's such like a uh it's like it's such a
double-edged sword succeeding on the algorithm because you don't even really have any control over
it you can't yeah because you because nobody knows what it actually is like we can make assumptions
but like if you get into the algorithm you don't really you can't pinpoint how you got there and
you can't continue that wave it just kind of starts and stops and then you're just like okay
uh shit you just have to trial and error it yeah I mean that's true and I guys like Matt Pat
early pioneers and stuff and I can't remember who made this but like somebody made a video recently
about how like uh yeah like like PewDiePie would never have gotten to the places out if you started
today just like making the content he does yeah right in a wave basically it's really fucking
emplemin I think that's exactly right it was emplemin and by the way not and I think I need to
finish that was that was pretty interesting uh none of this to say that I'm at all happy that
like hypocrite videos have like gone away obviously I think I'm probably one of the biggest fans of
the hypocrite stuff but uh yeah yeah I mean you know like I'm also a big believer in facing reality
and making important decisions that are tough when you feel that way and like I sure hope that
things change and you come back and make more great videos but yeah I mean I I hope I feel like
the the like sincere drive to make a game review again that's funny like like it was it was just
inspired by stuff I was looking at that I you know I admired AVGN it's like it was really funny
game review stuff and so I just wanted to create based on that and yeah like the money forces it
to become like a repetitive cycle it's true and it's true I feel like if I if I have enough time
away I might feel a hankering for like actually doing it again but for the foreseeable future I
probably won't like it's yeah yeah it this reminds me it's just sort of gone this reminds me of
something really interesting I've been watching for the last couple days like I don't know if
anybody here knows Gary Vee Gary Vanderchuck sounds familiar he's like he's like a guy on YouTube he's
like a YouTube personality but he also runs like a 150 million dollar business called Vayner
Media's like a consulting business stuff he's like a business guy he's an entrepreneur and that's
like yeah about entrepreneurship and stuff and like it just like it reminds me that like you
have to love the game to be able to do this because like he just started a new series on his YouTube
channel called Trash Talk and what he does is that he has he's got like millions of followers
stuff he makes a fuck ton of money his company makes 150 million dollars but he loves the game
of just like making money so much that he just goes out to yard sales and flips things on the
weekends and I was documenting it so he's like you can watch his Twitter just like yeah just picks
up a 50 cent sold over 10 bucks fuck yeah and he's like super stoked about it because he's trying
to like teach people how to like make extra money and like you can do it on no budget but like he's
jones to go out and make ten dollars and like he loves business as a thing that much that even
though he has no reason to do this it's just the act of it and I feel like that's a thing with YouTube
is that like you have to love just like the act of being a YouTuber like if you have like if you're
using YouTube as like a means to have different end you're gonna sputter out eventually or it's
going to become mature so yeah like like you can love making YouTube videos but hate being a YouTuber
and hit a wall eventually yeah because so many things just have like a finite shelf life you know
you have an idea you make the idea but then like there's this if you've built up any traction
by getting that idea done there's this unspoken like obligation that it has to perpetuate into
infinity and then that's where the problems start yeah also like the the platform itself shifts as
you grow older like the the thing that you want it to be as as like it's changed and is no longer
what it used to be anymore like literally like I used to be like also like I was inspired by
like the nostalgic critic and that guy with the glasses and all those like funny silly stupid
review shows and I wanted to be on the big collective the the big like every so often
like movies they would make where they flew everyone out to one place and they did stupid
video game movie cliche trash and I just wanted you want to be on channel awesome I wanted yeah I
wanted that um like like a lot of people did I mean I was a little I was a little boy and it was
just like really cool to see a crossover of of things like I didn't really care about all of them
but it was just it was just cool I just I want to be in a community I want to be part of a thing yeah
and so when I was a little kid I really wanted to be a reviewer for Game and Former magazine
I wanted to write I wanted to write for EGM really bad I loved that magazine a lot yeah
and and and it's just like you grow up and you realize that those reviews are generally bad
and it would be really stupid to have gone to that thing like I was too young to go to one of those
yeah um but like if I like if I had the clout now at age 25 would I go like would I be like I
probably wouldn't like even disregarding like scandals and stuff that has happened well I mean
those things kind of seem to me like like rad con but less cool and also more polished I guess
it's just like your your tastes change so like if you desire to be a thing
are based on like a childish impulse and you start that as your youtube channel and you get
into that and then you grow older and you don't want to do it anymore but now that you're you're
stuck in a cycle where people expected of you and it's all I've I've thought once in a while about
like will I still care to review like anime and video games when I'm like 40 I mean I don't know
I have no idea probably but who could say who could say you got to think about what were you
going to go from there folks we have a like the main thing is like like like think of what you're
doing and if the money was gone would you continue it assuming that you could get the money in some
other way right right because like to take money out of the equation would you still be doing this
thing see that's exactly why I think about like uh like your like the animation you did for endless
war for the end of season one uh was just done out of love and was so great and everybody loved
it for that you know little community that is the rowdy fuckers cop killers yeah and uh it was
truly legendary piece and it came out of nowhere and I didn't expect anything like that to happen
and it was like one day you were just like hey so I made this thing and I watched it and it was
like the coolest thing ever it was unironically my favorite piece of media definitely from the last
several years uh yeah and it was absolutely incredible so like I hope to see more stuff like
that from you I mean not it doesn't have to be that maybe something that actually makes any money as
opposed to literally zero oh yeah by the way everyone go to Gibbon Fortress 2 and watch that
a million times yeah please do we got to link that to Gibbon Fortress 2 for sure you can you can also
see it on twitch.tv slash rowdy frickers cop killers I gotta say the way that it that that happened
during a stream in rowdy fuckers like that was the most that was absolutely incredible no nobody
even I barely saw it coming god it was so great guys way to go I think you didn't even tell me
you were making it until like that day yeah I was I was just like oh I had the perfect idea and I
made it as fast as I possibly could yeah it was great the chat went nuts the chat went nuts don't
you love people with big projects like that it's my favorite it's my favorite it's it's pretty cool
but like what I love the most is when I go completely insane fast editing recording like every time I
have like a funny stupid give and take vlog idea that is just one stupid joke and I was like oh I
gotta make this I make it in like 10 minutes yeah yeah yeah the best idea is that you just bang out
they always like those those moments of inspiration like when a dwarf in dwarf fortress gets a oh god
what do they call it a fey mood pickaxe yeah yeah a fey mood or a weird mood or whatever it is like
I'm surprised you knew that mate I actually been watching no no I've been watching a person
played dwarf fortress with my boyfriend it's like fun stories yeah that's dope that's awesome like
that's where my like my my Ridley video and the subsequent okay like the Ridley one I was just
possessed with a ravenous inferno of inspiration to make a celebratory video about uh like the
inclusion of Ridley into smash bros at long last and luckily for me it's also like the most literally
the most popular game series except maybe for pokemon uh so people were interested and I like Ridley
because he's purple how basic of you who could have care so so so gib like what's your new focus
where what are you what are you working on primarily now well I'm I'm working right now I'm finishing
my comic bail jpe yes uh so definitely before the end of the year maybe even at the end of
october I don't know but I'm working hard on that oh shit and then I have like a lot of ideas for like
like I've had this idea generally for like doing music review not music videos um to
license music that will get copyright struck and like like a demonetize like uh in my head I'm
listening to it and it's like this is a perfect song I don't care if I don't get money I'm just
going to call it you know unmonetizable music video that's how I feel about my and then do that do a
bunch of those and just be like I don't know guys dance into it so is there well yeah I mean cool
dude I I want to see him also I also have like plans to make like adventure time but with my
characters instead because I love adventure time just make adventure time but with me and hippo
you fame oh actually I want to ask you about this you famously rewatched all the adventure time
recently famously you're renowned for this don't don't talk about the finale because I'm on season
10 and I'm almost at the finale okay I won't talk about anything specific but I love the whole
show it's perfect you said Gibb that there was one bad episode uh to for to your estimation
and I want to ask I forget what that was and I maybe that I assume that it was correct one
ends it was season four episode three or four the spiders having marital problems that sounds
like a stuck in a web and they don't really do I remember that episode now I actually did see
that one okay but I wanted to bring up the worst episode I saw that made me quit the show was when
they brought back party god who was like in love with an island or something oh that was so weak
did you what did you think of that episode game I was really curious um the episode itself is fine
it's just where the party god is the guy that they use party god it has no relevance to anything
else party god is like hawn's mole man you don't want to know like what's going on with him behind
the scenes not to mention there's there's vast different continuities for the origin of hawn's
mole man that all conflict with each other and that's exactly how I like it thank you very much
I I like I rewatched the simpsons like a year a few years ago like the whole thing well there's
like there's like a thousand seasons well I watched like the first like 12 seasons or something like
it was a big marathon yeah um okay but like I didn't even realize that his his joke is that he dies
every time like he dies over and over more less yeah he's coming back I terrible things happen so
I may have mentioned that I watched this uh the simpsons simpsons tuber on youtube called the
real gyms who does uh he does a bunch of different simpsons related content but in
particular he does simpsons histories where he goes into like the whole timeline of like a character
and simpsons miss you you know them I love them I've seen a few I love the I love the real gyms
he did a simpsons histories about hawn's mole man oh good and uh there's cannot be like 35 or
something right well it depends because yeah the one in that in that like AA meeting he says like
I'm 35 years old uh but then in in a in a later episode he was actually like like 50 years ago
he was mayor of Springfield yeah because like he's in old homes for old folks homes sometimes and
it's it's yeah it conflicts and like I don't know it was interesting because like apparently his
early appearances he's like he's usually driving and he's usually interacting with patty and selma
and these are like the two things that are consistent in his like the first couple seasons
that he starts appearing fascinating fascinating yeah because he can't see he's like he's like yes
the old man because his glasses are so but he was probably introduced as a joke of like he's the old
man driving who like I don't know they'd fuck with or something well also in in an old tracy
omen short there is an old man in a movie theater who is questionably hawn's mole man he sort of
bears a slight resemblance to hawn's mole man okay it's probably based on him I bet there's
literally like a hawn's mole man episode uh because it's gone there is not that's so weird
there is not there is not a hawn's mole man spotlight episode did you say your sister's
husband's name is is hawn's no no I said I said it's so weird that his name is hawn's why why is
that weird I don't know it's just I never realized he had a name and now his name is hawn's isn't that
like some miscellaneous european name it's it's I think it's German oh yeah right hawn's well all
right he's probably actually a nazi I bet there's an episode about that uh because you know Germans
they're all bad um yeah he doesn't he doesn't he doesn't die in us with Abe Simpson he doesn't
die in a star as burns the one with the man getting hit by football that's good he should be the
star he should be celebrating it's gonna he's gonna go hit by football yeah a fate worse than death
uh hey we're winding down what do you say we get to the voicemails let's let's go yeah yeah yeah
let's do it up all right oh wait wait I got one more I got one more thing to talk about I got one more
life update oh whoa hey we were gonna get pumpkins later me and michelle what do you know hello what
happened to your voice I suddenly had a house and money for a second there was crazy how many
you think it's a fool's game Tom it's a fool's game what what's that Ben I said having a house
and money is a fool's game oh yeah uh hey how many pumpkins you think are going to be carved this
halloween to look like pump would you say all of them prop hopefully all of them and you have to buy
a funny jack o lantern face too so yeah you know nobody it's like hiding your power level but with
jack o lantern carving pumpkin so good I did carve a couple years ago I did carve some
problem sleuth pumpkins don't I'll do something I kind of want to carve a pumpkin someday saw my
bucket list uh fuck them oh it was uh I hate that shit it's dumb it's gay I love it it's it's like
it's like um it's like building something but you're destroying something instead when mom was
driving out here you know it's almost halloween and stuff she she stopped at like a halloween
pumpkin display thing and like they had the most she took pictures that she showed me the most
insane pictures of carved pumpkins I'm gonna see if I can get one for her to put on screen here
but it was like there was one for example that was uh it was like a tiger but the thing is they had
like shaved parts oh I hate that so like there were various lane it wasn't just like cutouts it was
yeah fucking you know what I mean like it was glowing at various degrees at various points like
based on how thick or thin the skin was yeah yeah there were other ones I I I hate those so much
why why are they try hard the no well in one way yes they are try hard but like it sort of
goes against the whole idea of it being a fucking carved fruit like like no it doesn't it's fine
I don't know they're still carving the fruit it's it's technically impressive I just don't
like it makes for a good image on your Instagram but doesn't make for a good fucking pumpkin you
want something to scare the kids outside well sure I don't like I don't like halloween but I guess
I guess carving pumpkins is the only is kind of an okay part of it because it's kind of creative
and it's kind of cool and it's not the not the getting sweets part I like that's a good part
that's not keto I never actually that's not keto halloween is not keto that's not keto at all
at all arguably the least keto holiday I get the children chocolate dipped potatoes
I kind of thought halloween had become an international thing during halloween
you know they run movies and there's like oh you know they sell candy and stuff like that but I
don't think anyone actually goes trick-or-treating or whatnot so it's sort of like an acknowledged
holiday but no one really you know does that thing people in the UK do celebrate it yeah but
obviously not as much as America we do I like I never really got into the whole trick-or-treating
that much I did it a couple times with my my brothers and we would just go around the neighborhood
but when I got into a teenager phase like other teenage teenagers and stuff they would go like
you know let's go around and and egg people's houses and do stuff that's on the simpsons and
like yeah that's yeah and then and then they were the young adults and let's like let's go get drunk
and do the same thing we did and I'm like I don't want to dress up anymore it's stupid I think like
I love the halloween version of halloween I went trick-or-treating twice but they weren't
too successful over times like the first time one of my friends was in the UK or in or in Latvia
or Lithuania oh I know I know you're Lithuanian I just fucked up it's okay it's okay in the first
time my friend's bag of candy was stolen by like teenage boys and I ran after them but I couldn't
keep up damn that sucks yeah and the the second time a lot of people just didn't open their doors
because they were rude wait was this in the UK no Lithuania yeah I you gotta go to like a good
neighborhood like there's the neighborhoods where like families live with lots of little kids
generally in America yeah well pretty good you know that was my neighborhood and you know my
neighborhood so yeah bombed out uh I just this whole conversation just tells me thinking about
how great America is for creating halloween and I'm picturing you know that picture of uh okay so
there's a picture of a fat wojak face fat feels guy face wearing an american flag and crying
shirt that says you will always be a mera fat but there's a variant of that that's which is coming
to mind which is it's super buff super swole a smug ass wojak uh wearing american flag boxers I think
and there's a noose around his neck but he's he's breaking the noose and it says you will always be
a mera fat um so it says the same thing but uh he's winning anyway his name is wojak yeah he's
he's made by this polish guy named wojak you're talking about feels guy yeah yeah I I did not
realize wojak is not realize he had a name I feel bad even calling him wojak it like that is
kind of one of his you guys are experiencing what made just I I only know him as feels guy
well okay that's perfectly acceptable but is that why they called bojack crossman bojack well maybe
he has a lot of feels a lot yeah maybe do that I wouldn't be shocked uh but do you have a life
update or should we go to the questions uh my life update is just yeah since I've been sick I may
have mentioned this before but it's getting sick I broke keto so that I could chug cough syrup and
get and get high on that lean um is that break keto cough syrup it's the sugar in it there's sugar
in it I mean I could have I was just like I'm gonna be eating cough drops and drinking cough syrup
so I'm just like can I get the bear cough syrup please yeah so I just uh so I just I haven't been
I was ready to chastise you hardcore but that barely counts in my in my well no no no it's because
like I was drinking the cough syrup but I have also just been eating carbs normally because I was
like I fuck it oh too bad okay guys yeah but I'll get back I'll get back on it I gained I gained a
couple pounds in water weight and I'm very I'm very you know it's very very distressing so you know
distressing um I since we were talking about Halloween I actually looked up of maybe buying
like candy corn online and like the thing is yeah the thing is I love candy corn nobody likes
candy corn I am candy corn is good advocate I hear people like the either love it or hate it
there's no in between I haven't heard a person say I was like oh they're kind of okay you might
like them but I don't or something like that I haven't I like them people that say that they're
people that say that they're bad and compare them to the sweethearts are criminals what is that a
real thing there's like a people are like oh candy corns grows oh it's just some chalky shit like
sweethearts oh my god sweethearts are literally in sweethearts aren't even food yeah they're disgusting
they taste like medicines yeah but yeah but like candy corn looks like soft cough syrup is literally
tastier than it is sweethearts and also it gets you high as well the good news mage is that people
have been harassing us for some people were telling us that we should send you candy corn I was like
she's a big girl she can get her own damn candy corn but at least the bullying will end now if you
seal this deal hopefully I get to decide if I want to because it's expensive and there's a lot and
what if I don't like it I don't want to just throw away like 15 quid worth of candy cord which is like
300 15 quid like it's it's it's costly to get it he it's to get it shipped here at least on amazon
from what I've looked it's 15 quid that's like four thousand dollars
he's just in line with a couple people maybe I'm a couple people I don't have friends Nate
what about a gay boyfriend uh I don't know you got your topa you've got your head mates you know
you've got a whole squad why don't you send your cat out to get some for ya that is important
send your send your cat out to get some have she's got a polar way the only thing my cat brings back
is rats wait what would you say geb I'm looking at amazon.com for candy corn little bag of candy
corn it's like six pounds it's half off that's good that's good oh right now wait put it on your
amazon wishlist all right I want to have like an amazon affiliate link in the description so you
can buy candy corn from the UK there's speaking of candy corn candy corn right now is teaching me
self-control because six quid for 300 grams that is madness it's a bit it's a bit shit but yeah
did you and me put out a whole big thing of candy corn and it's just sitting there and
I don't know if I said it on the pzp but Ben Ben inspired me to go keto so now I've been keto for
a week and I can't have it and it's very difficult but I'm learning to like consciously control
because like when I go out and buy food from like the store I have to like consciously make the
decision but with candy corn I could just grab it without thinking and I haven't fucked up yet
but it's there constantly tempting me I don't understand like a lot of people do this and I
don't get it people that like have like candy bowls out and I don't understand how people don't just
eat at all my work my workplace has a candy bowl with like just tons of fun-sized candies I'm
I'm eating that shit every day yeah it's not like when I'm around it's pointless yeah I don't
have no semblance of portion control like whatever the package is is a portion to me
yeah yeah yeah I know people that leave food I might have I think I got mad about this on the last
one people that leave food unfinished I don't understand people that leave that is more than
don't fit people that like will leave like a quarter of a sandwich unfinished and like put it in the
fridge for later that is a constant thing that happens in this house and I don't get it there's
happy and food everywhere I don't I don't get people that like don't finish their food when
you're full you stop yeah that's so rare no you stuff your face until it's done if you put a
personal pan pizza in front of me I will eat it and be satisfied if you put an extra large pizza
in front of me I will eat it and be sick but also satisfied I'll be full and I was like but I'm not
gonna not finish this pizza right there is there is some there is some hefty psychology um which is
what I'm gonna call it that uh seeing a plate uh like cleaned or food is like yeah incredibly
satisfying to some people and others not but like if you give like children like a big old
bucket of spaghetti they will eat as much as the of that as they possibly can but if you give them
like a small plate they will eat it and they will be just well they'll be happier I think you don't
feel like they got shortchanged right exactly it's all about the packaging like if the if the
large pizza came in two pizza boxes and you ate a whole box you'd probably be all right
yeah maybe I mean I love saving food for later and I yay I get to enjoy the rest of my food later
I'm happy about I mean I have leftovers I love I love having leftovers but I never but I rarely
do because I'm just so compelled there won't be any leftover if you're once you're done with that
yeah yeah I used to when I was a kid psychologically to just torture myself like whenever I didn't
finish my food I think I think about like but there's people out there who are hungry how can I
waste this food and it's like I did this when I was a little kid and I always finished my food
because of it because I felt guilty about wasting food I just get a job starving children this ain't
my problem and then I go about my day throwing my pizza in the trash all nine tenths of it
like I got I got so upset when I went to college and I had a friend like and for the friend like
the mom would pack her a lunch and she would like usually not eat it and just throw it away not even
touching it was like but why just take it home just poor plan just take it home the weird thing that's
me is like like there are like stores that will throw out their extra food at the end of the day
and not yeah it's like they can't resell it and then apparently like you know people like people
who need food will come and like take it and like there are stores now that will like dump bleach on
their leftovers so no one could eat it okay why why there is a reason to do that sort of thing
and it's that okay the market demand that they're satisfying is hunger they want to keep hunger there
so they can sell you food and if they just give away food then there goes their market so that's
some fucked up capitalism doesn't work shit right there kind of yes kind of I uh I um you know one
thing yes I've been off keto so I've finally been able to eat some of those pastries that my
housemate brings home from his uh job at the pastry shop uh not not too great I feel like I'm
gonna talk to you about this last week like that I had like I had a pastry and like they're never
as good yeah they're just not as good decreased or something right or they're just like they're fine
but they're like why was like why was I craving these so bad like they're just whatever they're
just food do you think you're gonna have to like ease your way back in to keto again or do you
think like you're just gonna be able to flip the switch instantly and just get back I think it'll
be a I think it'll be a little bit of a challenge now that I'm out of it to shift gears back in but
you know I did it once I can do it again it's entering so far it's been surprisingly not as
hard as I expected yeah it wasn't as hard as I thought like you can eat you can eat to satisfaction
you can eat like you can eat a whole bunch of shit you can eat like a lot and like be full on
keto and it's fine I want to see uh I want to see a superpowered keto individual fight the vegan
superpowers and uh somebody on twitter the ultimate fight it was a while ago someone tweeted
I'm sorry I can't remember who it was because it was a while ago but someone made tweeted at me with
like a write-up for like a keto superhero it was a guy he would no it was like a guy he was like
he had two forms he had his his he was normal he was a really buff guy but he was just a normal
buff guy with no superpowers his superpowered form was that he would become really fat
but he would be keto but what in his super fat form he was fueled by his fat and therefore had
super keto powers okay it makes sense isn't that like it's an actual character in my hero academia
like he his fat gives him powers I forget his name I think I think you're thinking of choji
from Naruto no there is a guy in my hero academia but yeah there is a superhero and like as he uses
his power he gets skinnier because his fat gives him his powers yeah that happened didn't that happen
to choji didn't choji literally like burn off his fat long yep in his first and only good fight
in the series fucking keto um all right let's go to the voice shall we go to shall we go to
voice yeah let's do it let's do it yep all right here we go um we got we got on deck okay we're
checking in with uh wolf spar wolf spar wolf spar wolf spar what one is this one is this one spar
okay I mean how is a Halloween themed perhaps it's been a transformation let's let's find out uh
what do you got for us buddy all right as of this recording it is october 14th and as you
no doubt remember I said earlier that october 15th is the official end date for the bounty
and I'm pleased to announce that it was a huge failure yeah no time stamps in the document
and uh the chances of the conspiracy ever being proven are between slim and none but hey there's
good news sorry about that you see after last week when I got my legs broken by those guys I got
by wolves but I managed to befriend them and now I live in a wolf den and I have a wolf family I
even got asked a wolf yeah the thing I was wearing this fursuit the whole time and asked for what
will happen to me well I was able to pay off the wolf mafia for protection so I don't think I have
to worry about the starfleet guys anymore so yeah I think I'm just gonna let the bounty die uh to
heck with this to heck with you guys uh I have a better family now uh wolf family I have my very
own tree in the yard I marked it it's mine now no one else can go here so you stay the heck away
from it uh goodbye you know congratulations once you know you know you know you know wolf spar yeah
the newly dubbed wolf spar you can't always get what you want but if you try sometimes you just
might find you get what you need like a wolf family yeah this is guy saying lyrics yeah yeah yeah
I'm a musical I'm a music man an end to this thing I don't even know kind of what the point
of all this was no I don't know where this was going um but I'm glad like a huge ass from the
beginning so this was just him like finding a way to come out as a furry I didn't explain why he had
that fursuit from the beginning I feel like the point of this was that his his bounty idea completely
failed and he needed to narrow but he needed to narratively justify it with the humorous conclusion
so he let us on a wild goose chase culminating in a wolf in a wolf in a wolf happy ending also
he's like we were we all were richer for it I wasn't aware of this link to a document that he like
wanted updated with timestamps anyway so like maybe if he'd given us that information uh we could
have helped him out maybe if only if only we had uh helped him out with that he would be he would still
be among humans true his own kind well he's fucked now but that's just a sale he's a total
romulus remiskay right now that's that's true uh so okay so here's one here's one from food boy
there's another message from him gross what we're past that but let's see what he's got
hey hear that sweet sizzling sound yeah of course you don't because you're weak weak of body from
a shit you're consuming and weak of mind there's not a single one of you managed to present a
non-retarded opinion food so lonely a venerated mealmaker to set the record and all of you faggots
straight the soulless process of assembling a hello fresh kid does not teach you and cannot be
considered cooking yeah understand what you're doing following orders like a fucking Nazi
switching out ingredients and methods of preparation and seeing what works it's a creative process as
opposed to the mindless adherence to dogma this mind washing service demands I agree I agree at least
you're eating real food when you're done good thing no one in the pcp proselytizes for going that
step wait fucking kill me all right um all right disagreed uh on all counts uh no he's on point he's
on point I'm I mean I'm not saying you can't you couldn't learn anything by cooking a hello fresh
meal I'm not saying it has no value the hell is hello fresh is it like hello kitty but different
we talked about last week if the service munchie has they deliver specifically the
ingredients you need to cook like one meal like oh terrible it's you know hello fresh is childish
hello fresh embarrassing is like a tutorial like you go online you're trying to learn like programming
or art or something and you follow the tutorial perfectly it's like oh I made this this little
baby thing but like it's not you would never like make a tutorial and be like oh I did it for real
like no that is like I guess that is like getting getting a lego kit building the lego kit and then
never ever experimenting with that lego yeah yeah a fair enough fair enough you people were
defending fluttershy when she was taking baby steps but it's not okay to get hello fucking fresh
fuck you all it is it is baby steps and uh and and it's it's training wheels and and if you just
really need to cook a nice meal right and you don't know what the fuck you're doing then yeah
you could maybe get some of this right the baby steps is you go to youtube or you go to google
you type in how to to cook x and then you find the ingredients list you go to the supermarket
you find what you can okay you're gonna save so much money in the long run if you just go buy
fucking groceries yeah you'll save money but what if I just want to save time by having them give me
literally everything I need and I can just cook that I think in the long run buying in bulk will
save you both but I don't want to think about it I just want other people to do the thinking for me
it's like not thinking about it it will result in you in the lifelong dependence of you right
subscribe if you don't want to think about it then why you want to learn how to cook like you're
clearly not interested in it okay you know what the longer the longer you the longer you go without
thinking about it the longer you are you're siphoning money off to these fucking millennials running this
bullshit millennial company you're not wrong as much as much as it sucks to burn a meal or to not
know what you're doing that those are like important formative steps to being a chef is to like okay
so if I if I put garlic in with the oil uh too early then it gets black before I put the other
stuff in so I got you know it's just like things you you learn that apply to loads of different
types of cooking and different meals that's true like you need to learn basics through trial and
error or like you know like you can use youtube tutorials and I guess hello fresh is fine once
or twice but you should never have it as like the be all and all I don't I don't think it's I don't
think it's worthless but I don't think it's worth much is I guess that's fair enough I kind of want
to try it though just for a time I don't know maybe I won't end up doing it by the way this talk of
millennial bullshit just reminded me of uh uh yesterday hello fresh is quintessential millennial
bullshit what characterizes to me what characterizes millennial bullshit is a desire to like fake
creativity and individuality and hello fresh embodies this idea that you have a shortcut
that you have this like shortcut that you can pay for to like fake a to like fake a creative skill
I guess that's true I guess that's kind of it's it's it's like buying a ready meal but you know it
it's it's it's the selling beads on Etsy of cooking it's I did speaking of ready meals like like
we had like a person knock on our door which is weird how did he get in because we have like the
um we live in a flat and you know like the it was like not the outside it was the inside door so
that was weird and he was like so he knocked on a door and he was offering like some sort of service
of gusto I think.co.uk and it's it's like you order a meal specifically like a meal on their
site and they make it for you and then they deliver it which is kind of like takeout but you know
their meals are like not like pizzas and burgers they're actually kind of cool yeah I was like oh
that's kind of neat I might I might try that and that sounds like the sort of uh thing they have in
old people's homes that they deliver it does but I like those I like those a lot I yeah I'm not
saying that that is like is a bad thing it's like yeah you know fair enough by the way you you want
to order a roast dinner it's a way it's a way it's a way to try out all these new different recipes
of foods and stuff speaking of this millennial bullshit though that I was mentioning uh when me
and my mom went out to this place Finley Market you know whatever it's a nice place around in
Cincinnati highly recommended uh but like have you guys been aware I don't know how many of you
guys live in cities but like there's been these these things I've seen around of just like people
using these scooters they're just using scooters and then you'll just see them on the side of the
road this is like in the like not the inner city but like in the city there's like urban centers
you'll see like there's just like green scooters three hours ago did I well I figured it out I
figured out what the issue was and I rode them and it was dope it's all right here's what it is
there's these two services called like a bird and lime and what they are are
they just leave scooters around the city and you can use the apps to GPS locate where they are
you go to them you scan them in your phone and then they activate they're all they're all electric
and then you can just scoot around on them like like an electric skateboard only you know a scooter
I've seen I've seen like I've seen like in Boston there's like bike racks with like bikes that I
similar to that yeah there's like and you like you can like rent a bike and like ride it between
like bike locations there's a bike rack like that around UC in Cincinnati as well it's just like
that it's called like blue something I want to the ones in UC are red everything in the city is
red because that's like the color but like the the thing about these is that you literally leave
them on the side of the road you just leave them there and you you say that you're done riding
after like 10 minutes right in the middle of the road well what stops someone from just taking
absolutely nothing except the fact that they're probably GPS tracked or something well I don't
know I'm probably also the the fact that they're electric and they won't like maybe the brakes are
on by default and you you can't like ride it around without yeah being activated but couldn't
you just like pick it up and toss it in your truck or something you you definitely could do that I
don't know exactly what stops them but it's gotta be something they must have a business model here
that if they're GPS track that they are yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe easy easy crime easy crime catch
it's pretty cool though and we rode them and they were fun and I liked it though I missed my skateboard
was it uh expensive uh no it was like it was like I don't know five bucks for me and my mom
both took a ride for like I don't know 20 minutes or something uh that's pretty good you know maybe
it was less I didn't actually check how much it costs now I think about it but it said like a minute
or like a dollar for like an hour or something I don't know I could be wrong but it was it was
cool I liked it I've never I've never seen scooters like that it was but it was I don't think we
have them around this is kind of like app-based activation city living things just such millennial
bullshit and I'll just have none of it thank you very much but that doesn't sound bad though
millennial bullshit is characterized by being bad I don't agree with that uh what's it called
what's called birds one's called mime they're two absolute the exact same thing
they're called scootaloons that's true all right let's move along we've got another
that would be a good epony for this blue bikes the thing is called blue bikes
metroboston's bike share program all right well it's uh it was the thing we've got around here
yeah all right here here's another one this one this one's called the dreamy or the dreamer army
anthem and I believe it's by center point let's it's it's 10 seconds long let's see what this is about
wait how long are you saying 10 seconds yeah
fucking it shit okay that that's all it is I think what this is is I think these are the
people that are very much hashtag let mage dream and this is their anthem I didn't think that's
a classic beat sequence is that the the segment intro I think yeah that's the intro oh guys you
know what this is actually a great idea um it'd been proposed that we should do this at some point
maybe this should be like a separate show or I guess it could be an episode but literally like
the dream cast and the here's what it here's the conceit of the show oh my god you play dream cast games
in uh like let's play format while discussing your dreams that's the that's the format oh wouldn't that
be sick isn't that dope I mean we have a dream yeah yeah I think that's not people suggest that that's
yeah we could do that for for heckles for shekels we should do that cast one of those heckles for
shekels dream cast um it's a good idea it's for for dreams and if you feel if you viewer if you
feel strongly uh that people should be allowed to dream or if you feel the opposite way that
dreams should be banished and abolished and punishable by death uh you got to get in the uh
procrastinators bonus lounge and to argue your point you got to get in there and be a soldier
yeah true for whatever side you uh you want yeah yeah yeah we need to there's the there's a civil
war there's a civil war breaking out the dreamers versus the memers and it's dreamers will dominate
dreams will be crushed uh memers for life your dreams are my memes uh right okay so there you go
you've got an anthem now fantastic congratulations um here's here's one here's a here's a here's a
thank you here's a cute little message from uh Nate Senpai please fuck me um all right okay
let's let's hear it let's hear your pitch this question goes out to Nate I was just wondering
if he could shove his big black juicy uh yeah all right that's not that um what do you think
what do you think Nate what's your uh you know what's your face will take it's quite a pitch
that's quite a pitch um I'm leaning a hard yes I'm gonna get back to you a little bit later on
that you have a special someone already well you know the space I'm a public figure age I have to
be used by my beloved public in all facets in all capacities uh here's another one from our old friend
sheet public use public Nate's public use now that's right I am the town bicycle public don't
what do you got for us buddy hey guys first of all thanks for the advice ban but I decided
I'm not gonna fast anymore this is the faster guy I am on an eight hour fast right now but it's only
because my mom's doing busy fucking her new boyfriend anyway you guys were talking about
your and if you didn't hear it from my accent already I'm from the Netherlands and there's
this something we do here in the Netherlands we speak Dutch so I was wondering how are you
guys with foreign languages do you speak any do you want to learn any is Esperanto cool or is the
meme it's a meme questions sorry about that okay bye yes I do speak a foreign language
Esperanto is a meme but as a memer I'm all about it I'd like Esperanto to replace all the languages
I think why not why not have a language that people already speak be the language that takes
over the world it's an ideal what is what is this what is Esperanto oh uh give Esperanto is a
it's not fictional but like it's a it's a one-man made a team made up a language that was supposed
to be like easy to use easy to learn it's like similar you know how it's around Star Wars there's
like basic where everybody in the fucking universe knows basic so they can communicate with each other
that's what Esperanto is but here in Star Trek Star Wars and Star Trek both have this I believe
yeah I think so and it's called basic in both I call common well I'm everything
that's indeed it's called out wait wait hold on Star Wars and Star Wars both have a common language
called basic I know it's called basic and Star Wars I don't know what's called the Star Trek
it is called galactic basic standard according to the wookiepedia let me see basic
language
it's brought up Klingon top 10 Star Trek languages to answer the question maybe Star Trek doesn't
have basic maybe yeah maybe it's just uh my my favorite foreign language wait it's not favorite
I'm not good at anything I can speak English but only bail federation standard there's a federation
standard language uh so there you go I studied Spanish I studied Spanish in high school and
through a bunch of college so for like six years or something I took Spanish class I was supposed
to be really good at it I did really well in Spanish class when I graduated college never used
it it's completely decayed I don't use it at all it was totally a waste of my time same with me in
German and then when I went to Poland I learned a couple of phrases because I wasn't interested
in learning another language for a country that I was probably never going to go back to right I
I learned a bit of German I know a bit of Russian by like cultural osmosis yeah yeah the
unfortunate thing about languages nowadays is that in order to learn a language you need to
really really really want to like I have like oh yeah wouldn't it be cool to have like no a language
but the only reason the only reason I would need to learn a language or like would would want to
learn a language is to impress other people with how many languages I learned this is and not because
I really want to go places and use it yeah I know because I don't need to everyone speaks English
well I mean I have a strong desire uh uh
my inichi nihongo de hanashitai no no no uh benkyoshitai every day I want to learn Japanese
because there's actually a real tangible benefit uh because not everything gets translated fast
you're a weeb enough for me I'm big enough into the weeb shit that learning Japanese would be
actually useful to me and so why don't you and did you gonna make your Japanese video series I mean
I've still got I'd love to do it now once we move and we're closer we should talk about that more
but like I think I'm learning Japanese I think I'm like I have an app I've been bad the last I
know a couple of weeks I want to be practicing Japanese every day on my little app what's called
it's called uh Memrise Memrise it's pretty good um we're like more like meme rise hey you're not
wrong it's accurate team memer for the win another point for us come on dreamers pick up a pace I
would like I would like to accidentally learn a language like Bart did in that episode of
Simpsons where we learned French just by being in France like that's how the most efficient and
best yeah it just clicked one day it just clicked and suddenly he could speak perfect French I always
do that like if I if I go to like Swahili or something I like I stay around there and I like
suddenly I'm speaking with everyone and I'm like you know I become a pirate 13 Swahili country uh
Swahili language I can't remember I don't think there's a place called the Swahili cut wait maybe
there is you know that episode of Simpsons where Bart learns French I always thought that you know
like he's talking like trying to get that Constable or whatever the the French police to like help him
with his whatever it is and uh like the Constable like gives him a big pink candy I always thought
that candy like somehow let him speak French suddenly like it was like a I really thought that
for a long time because it's like as soon as it gives him this very strange looking candy
he can suddenly speak French and I stand by it actually I still think that's what happened
now I want to go and re-watch that you see I would prefer to learn I prefer to learn a language
like in Dexter's laboratory when he has to study French for a French test and he only
learns omelette du fromage and all the girls are instantly wet for him and yeah yeah that's
that's the way to be yeah that's accurate but like it's it's it is like a better use of your
time to go to a country and just be an idiot for a while um living living among like real people
not in a tourist trap um and then you'll you know you go to the market and you say uh you know you
have the pocketbook of like basic phrases but then you'll learn more as people speak to you yeah
you gotta be like you gotta be like Jeff Ferrell the soccer guy you gotta go to Mexico City you
gotta go to all right Cuba and Canada you gotta go to the city center juggle your soccer ball
get called a gringo get them to take pictures of you uh decide no no teach teach random strangers
English even though they didn't ask you to come home come home and try to and decide that maybe
I'll become a Spanish teacher even though I barely learned any Spanish and my Spanish sucks damn
yeah that's a bold plan that's that's how that's how to live anyone could pull it off it's our boy
Greg um with Jeff Jeff right um yeah whatever it doesn't matter okay let's move on next call from
mr bones rattling them up lads let's see what we got I'd like to express my sincere appreciation
for munchie j trump and the way that he criticizes the other members of the pcp in a kind of playful
ribbing manner you know like the way he takes digs uh the kind of miniature cultur personality
surrounding Nate so I'd like to invite the rest of you to take a moment and give a small piece of
critique about another one of your fellow pcp members uh also mitian is gay fuck you
well fair enough uh I mean I do like that about munchie like when he sees something
that nobody's talking about and he will just say it because it's like it's funny to draw attention
yeah no it's good it's good uh a lot of the times people can be too worried about offending their
friends or something and I want to rock the boat yeah the thing the thing is with munchie that he
has that that that boyish charm that makes it like water for ducks back and we know we don't get angry
at him that's true even though we all agree he he he takes he can take the core gesture of the pcp
there's no he can he can take refuge in audacity you know what I'm saying you know what I mean by
that I know yeah he can compress those waveforms and it sounds fine no that's not because the court
jester uh traditionally could say things to the king that like if like a serious lawyer brought it
up he'd probably get fucking executed but the gesture can be like he's like he's he's like the pcp
the the contingent of like serious lawyers well you know discussion about as as clowns go he's more
like the evil kefka like whispering in our ear with his fork tongue just like telling us sweet
nothing's in like gradually turning us into who is that king in lord of the rings kefka kefka
didn't whisper in anyone's ear except when he was fucking sling their throat here who is who is the
guy in um in yeah worm tongue and lord of the rings yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
true i'm confusing him with worm tail from her that's a named character i think if we're talking
about gentle ribbing uh i'd like to say munchie sucks and i think we all agree and that's you know
frankly all there is to be more specific you have to be specific otherwise it's just a gentle
let's let's see if we can think of some some some actual minor gentle ribbing criticisms um
i'll i mean i'll i'll come out sure you're pretty like munchie you're not afraid to stir the munchie
has i mean munchie has uh where's fuck where's fucking investigators yeah fair okay okay i know
i mean i will say that i know he has released some pages i don't know how many there's someone
his tumbler but he has not made it public at all and i interpret this gesture to mean that he
is not actually ready to have people see it probably because if he was he would say he would
announce it he's been very secretive about it they're up on his tumbler and i feel like he put
some out just sort of to like be like yeah yeah i put something out like i'm getting something done
but it's not ready and he like it needs to get ready it's still not ready fuck you
uh good i don't know what i should say but you know i'm guilty too i'm guilty of the same thing
with vapers three yeah where the fuck is vapers three it's coming a bunch of stuff but i mean i
mean that's fair you know i've been where i've been working on the max reviving tbap i've got a
while i was working on ten paces and draw for a while you have a whole list you have a whole
list of shit i i bang out a new page of vapers three whatever i get like a free day yeah yeah
i still like seeing vapers the the vapers on on my shelf next to like home stuck and problem
sleuth it's fun man when vapers three is done i'm so i'm so excited for the second kickstart i think
the second kickstarter will do even better than the first one probably because i'm gonna have bundles
i'm gonna offer bundles because i know a lot of people people sometimes ask me like hey where can i
buy the vapers out none of the kick starters over and i tell them hold on i'm not just selling it
like on a one-for-one basis i don't want to just like sell like sell just whenever just whenever
anyone happens to email me no they'll be like available for the second kickstarter and i feel
like there's a lot of people that miss the first kickstarter and will want to get in on the second
one along with all the third people that did get in on the first one that are gonna want to buy
volume two uh i'm really excited and uh i want to finish vapers three before before i run that
campaign though yeah anyway good that's that's uh that's sorry to derail about that yeah whatever
no past all right mr. bones there you go we discussed things nobody else nobody nobody else
you fucking cow i have i have a i have a gentle ribbing of of of nate uh you suck no uh you have
um a tendency yeah i mean i've told you this like in private so it's not even really a big deal but
you have a tendency to bring in like topics that are not real they're just like here's
something that happened today lol and then and you hope that that will like blossom into a big
discussion i mean it didn't happen this time so my because i thought it was really good give me
give me do you have do you have an example um the last time the skateboarding one is what we talked
about nate nate just brought up the fact that he was on a skateboard and he liked it and that was
topic that he brought forward cool that's yeah i mean i use you change it around for this one i will
agree there okay well that's but i have to rip someone i have to rip it somewhere i'm a little
fraught no that's fair that's fair it's true i guess we all gotta we all gotta make sure we
bring something actually good and not just more shit thing more more more ribs um tom someone killed
me someone killed me well hang on okay i got one for tom you can't do it i'm too powerful i don't
understand where your career is going tom and it confuses me and i i feel that what this really
indicates is is a lack of like uh communicating to your audience where you're like like are you
working on getting a game done right now or are you let me let me let me let me simultaneously
bolster that statement as well as pose a follow-up question um so you were talking before about
a game demo i don't know anything about the game you're making yeah i mean wait i i have
a sort of a sense that it is it's a side scrolling action platformer right correct i know that i i
think i know that much about it i've been i've released it of a devlog every day this month
there's 13 of them out yes the fact that we don't know that is a problem was it on maybe is it on
polystation uh it should be they're on youtube and they've been tweeting about them on twitter every
day and oh you know it starts with like they all so okay i guess this is on me then shit i have
seen those pcp uh like um feed for content like did you upload them all at once um first 13 i they
were originally private because i was doing them for patrons but i was like fuck that uh people
should see these okay so that was kind of a cared yeah so but for the last like five days they've
been up to public every day and there's another one coming out today those all appeared at once
and i was like well i don't really want to watch all of them i'd rather just see the finished product
or like see like here's my promo trailer like here's my game okay that's all fair here's here's
a thing give an elevator pitch for this game it's a side scholar in the style of a classic
sega game with more forgiving controls and expanded mechanics make it more appealing to
modern gaming tastes okay i mean maybe this is all way premature like like maybe you're
playing to get it out in like three years or something and i don't know i'd like that's
he said you said you were gonna put a demo out in like the next couple weeks right yeah i'm trying
to get some sort of like demo slash vertical slice in people's hands by november 8th because that's
when i'm gonna be an old man and i want to have something i'm semi-proud okay well i i guess my
question is so is this the main thrust of what you're working on um for right now but like okay the
whole idea is that like i want to have like kind of like the the assuming characters like a multimedia
project there's going to be like animations and motion comics and games and stuff but like the
game is just something like tangible and like meaty okay that i can get done and like have a
forearm 30 so that's what i want to work on right now you know that right there is interesting i feel
like this this concept of a multifaceted multimedia like character it like it confuses me like what
that's going to and i just think that as like a viewer i just like i'm left with nothing i can
grab onto except the game like the game obviously is the thing that you're talking about so maybe
i'm just talking out of my ass here i don't know what platform what platform what platform are you
building the game in uh it's uh construct three it's like a it's like a visual programming
sort of thing right now you'll be able to play it on your pc gaming system band that's yeah it'll it'll
be a very i don't know i knew it was going to be a pc game i mean like what engine like game
game maker yeah it's it's something like game maker essentially is what it is okay my playful rib
is i have no idea what the hell you're ever doing tom and now you're explaining it to me which is good
but now i'm wondering if maybe that's my fault maybe i just haven't been paying attention well
the audience could only blame itself so much for not right i did be in you know i did see uh i did
i did see you were uh the slime i did see you modeling that slime which was very pertinent to
my entry that is like i have a death animation for an hour it blows up into like a pile of slime
and it looks cool cool all right well okay well i will definitely go check this out now that i
understand more uh well this is good feedback i will try and be more blatantly obnoxious about
developments so people can actually see it i think what would be helpful for me like if i like if you
made a video that's like i'm making a game it's whatever azumi fucks everyone that's the name
guys come into your computer right now you like jack and your dick you like furries i'm your man i'm
tom oliver i am a furry uh you know something you want him to make a billy maze commercial
that would work i mean it would it would be pretty fun uh yeah well whatever okay i get the point
we're not we're not trying to fucking break the man's spine here more more more more more
more ribs i have a rib for all of us because i'm trying to think of one thing in particular
okay that that bugs me but we all do this we when it comes to the pcp we all suck at making
decisions we all sit here and discuss it for 10 hours and all the good things that have happened
to pcp lately it's just one of us just doing it and letting it be real like what uh the voicemails
i just did it and that happened and then that just happened like these were things no censor that
censor that that can't be on the episode put a beep over that no one can know no one can know
what is it okay uh it it matters to me it when when will they know uh soon okay i promise i promise
i guess i'd assume this would already been talked about on an episode because again this
just reinforces my point that it takes too long for the shit to happen okay no you tom you're total
i agree with you on a lot of this but the thing is uh like like that thing happened and i'm like
let's run with this and then people are like um actually i don't think that's where i think we
should like gib was doing this i don't actually think this is perfect like we want to change
something and you know what i actually agree on some of those points but that's where we hit
snacks you know with those sorts of uh the pcp is not a perfect production and it needs to just
be flawed and bullshit so it can actually get things done i you know i know it feels like
everything moves at a glacial pace but like i understand why like like when i when we get
into a meeting and we're talking like it's not like it's nonsense like that it makes sense why
there's like disagreements and we can't move forward yeah and those have to be resolved in some way
which they almost always can be if we meet and like people show up to the means which none of you
did except for munchy yesterday so you know well i was like was there a thing was there a thing to
be discussed at yesterday's meeting was there like a specific i mean there was at least one there was
actually this exact topic that we're censoring right now was the one i wanted to discuss with
everybody i am usually not abreast of what is going on that is why i usually just i just i just
just don't worry about meetings when i happen to be when i happen to be at my computer since we
can't actually talk about this since it's centered i'm going to dovetail this off into another targeted
rib digi i know you're not here but you can't fucking complain about things changing in the pcp
and being mad about it when you don't show up if you don't show up that is there yeah you can't
that's not yeah the thing is with digi he thinks the meetings are pointless for some reason uh but
then he doesn't they are the only thing that gets things moving and done basically uh well at least
like the bigger issues not not like like i'm just going to make the voicemails was great uh yeah i i
think well of course he would think that they're pointless because he doesn't come to them and
then there's things just happen without him thinking about him so to him it just seems like
things just happen on their own right but that but he expresses great disdain in these changes
and like says like in this upset that they're happening like well if you want to
make them not happen be there when the changes are happening i mean i just for example digi
i'm not trying to show you too hard but if you ever came in into the pcp discord like added everyone
and said hey guys like what are the relevant topics like i'm there all the time and i'm there to explain
everything that's going on digi you don't even need to do that you can just go up one flight of
stairs and be like hey tom what's going on that's that's true but i mean i don't know like i kind of
i kind of feel for digi only because like like because the pcb is set up to be like that you
don't have to worry about it unless you want to pretty much yeah like you know yeah i mean i'm fine
with him not participating as long as he doesn't then complain and bitch and moan which he has does
sometimes once in a while i don't know yeah i don't blame him that much it's not that big a deal
but i that's fair that's fair criticism of the guy um well the thing okay so gib uh i would have
criticized probably up to this point the fact that like i don't know exactly what your goals are
like i'm not sure you like you seem to have a feat in multiple worlds and you seem indecisive
but then you've just made a huge decisive step which i think is very good for you to do in in some
direction that you're confident so like that criticism is kind of curtailed by you doing yes
and taking those actions so dodged yeah so that's real i mean again i'm not happy at all that like
the hypocrite reviews won't be coming or at least not nearly as regularly if ever uh but like you
know facing reality making big decisions hard choices about how to handle your life mate here's
a fucking rib you're terrible at ribbing you're such a little skating yeah yeah yeah yeah these
are these are pussy that's you're you're right you can feel like you're reading you're reading some
little you're reading some little pussy some little pussy piglet pork ribs you gotta get the big
ass beef ribs you know i'm saying the table and it just there's there's no they are absolutely
both right now so you know well at least he's giving some uh let's give major rib all of us guys
how about a mage i don't understand uh how you make any money if you make any and this worries me
and i'm confused by it that's what i have to say to you friend what's your business model
i i do come i do i do come you know commissions that's what it is i yeah i didn't really post them
but yeah are those things that like can't be posted because they're like you know they're
four people so like they use them for projects and then they're up doing stuff some of them yeah
sometimes i just i'm just lazy mage is a prolific porn artist with commissions she just doesn't
want to ruin her innocent image on the piece she never talks about it her dark her her after dark
pain yeah uh shit what was i gonna say oh it's like um we like with some of the people that i work
with like who've made like music for me or something like i'll want to keep the thing a secret but
then like once the project that it's for comes out then like like then they're like allowed to like
retweet it or like make it public that they like did this work or something so like i don't know maybe
i don't know you know my criticisms i guess aren't even really that relevant you're just
kind of in a totally different world than me that i couldn't really follow even if i wanted to i mean
i could i guess but it would be who you talking to right now talking to mage i'm talking to mage
like the world of commissions is one i don't understand or you know yeah it's it's like uh i
don't i mean when you do a commission mage i'm curious do you post it on your like social media
and stuff do you post it like hey guys look what i did or do you just give it to the buyer and like
don't give it to the buyer and then i'm too lazy to post it most of the time well there you go dog
what's your future business plan how do you grow from here and get more money and you know build
that 401k i like doing commissions and i'm not short of them right now it's like i'm currently
i hate doing commission i like i'm i'm so envious of you for being able to do commissions i could
make so much more money if i just didn't hate doing other people's dirty work ha yeah yeah i used to
not like them back in the pony days because all of all i i had to do is draw ponies can you draw
my lc fucking twilight sparkle i mean like i like drawing ponies but it got really boring because
i had to draw like basically the same things in a way but now i get i'm getting varied requests
and i quite like that perfect perfect scam you just make a show accurate template
and then you just swap out assets on like the whoever's on top you swap out to be their oc and
the one on the bottom you swap out to be the main six of their choice makes sense and then you can
have uh yeah yeah you can have uh yeah yeah infinite infinite commissions available in a moment's
notice your character here whoa uh whoa that's a funny joke that should have been a real character
i get it i get it why is why are we not actually doing this makes so much money who says we're
oh we could we could have made money i don't know if we still we'd probably make something still
i mean furries are still evergreen right furries will never stop be cash cows yeah yeah yeah like
the the pony thing may be on the on the decline but furries are forever i mean the pony fans have
to go somewhere and where else what's more adjacent to pony than furry the only place for them to go
is patreon.com slash tbbvap that's the best bitch about ponies they all get they all get a migrate
from derpy borough to fur affinity probably true um all right that was a good healthy round of ribbing
going around um all right let's let's move on next up uh we got we got i think there's four more of
these um bongo fag let's see whoa play one for me champ i asked you pcp how can i go to a school
literally called friend school and at the same time feel like i have no friends because like i
talked to people at my school and even follow a couple of them on fucking instagram but they all
feel like ghosts they all feel unreal and transparent and i've considered the possibility
that perhaps i'm just too intelligent for all of them i'm just too woke for all the normies yeah
yeah yeah i was like i was saying gay ass podcast every week right this is what did it but i've also
thought that perhaps they're all intelligent too intelligent for me oh no that i'm just no that
can't be it he's breaking the condition please send help uh i i would say that like it sometimes it is
that you are like you know more intelligent in that you have deeper interests in stranger things
and that they can't understand you like stranger things so much more than everybody else it's just
a real yeah no oh yeah i hate that thing lol um um i i mean i don't believe i i know this guy was
memeing to a certain extent but i'm just gonna take his yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna engage with
his question yeah i'm gonna engage with his question on on literal terms um i don't really
believe in intelligence as like a metric like some people are just more or less like it's not that's
simple uh people just have people are on different wavelengths people's people's you know thoughts
occupy different uh different like different vectors right people think along different
vectors and trajectories and sometimes they either they either do or don't match up uh so i don't
really think yeah yeah i don't think that's such a thing as like being too smart or too dumb yeah
for for to engage with someone it's just do your thought patterns like are they are they compatible
with each other i basically agree with that um do they map to one another yeah oh yeah like i
this reminds me of like the comic the xkcd of all the people in the train all having the same
thought of uh all these people are just sheep only i am like the true deep one uh but i know i know
that you're kind of joking they're they're all just unthinking you know like what i would say is
that like they're all just i think most people come across just inherently as more like like if you
don't know someone and then they just say a sentence you could like be like wow this is what this person
thinks and nothing else how embarrassing that's simple meanwhile yeah you know like they probably
have a lot more going on they have they have their own internal life that is not being shown to you
just like you have that's not being shown yeah and also also there's always there's always the
possibility that one of them who is engaging in normie topics or whatever um is doing so because
they have nerdy topics but the normie ones are the only way they can make friends so like yeah if you
just say out loud like i love anime like a couple people like oh the guy loves anime i love anime
would perk up at that or something you know but not that that's necessarily the best way to do it
but the point oh it is the best way to do it because it's very funny walk into walk in a class this is
what these are for walk in a class wearing one of those big t-shirts that have all the um all the
shit what's it called the the like orgasming girl faces on it you know just like all over
hey go from hentai hey go what are those called you know a ha ha hey go a hego faces i've been
saying can you hear me or what sorry maybe it was low jeez i said it like three times i had going
this whole time okay so walk in a walk in a class uh no we'd be wearing a hoodie all right be wearing
a hoodie and then this is like that scene in american history x where the guy walks into the
the courtyard he takes off his shirt and there's a big nazi sign on it you'll be doing similarly
only you take off your hoodie and you've got this shirt covered in a hego faces and everyone will
be like it's it's putting up a flag dude you're making friends instantly by making this alternatively
you could buy a pcp shirt on red bubble and get the same effect this is okay unironically this is
kind of why i wore so many anime shirts uh like my whole life because i'm i'm putting up flags to see
who wants to talk to me about anime guys please someone do it yeah this is like a real psychological
thing like this is what people do they look for like i have like a waking up podcast shirt like
why do i wear that uh one because i like sam harris and i'm happy to like you know supply
with money and shit for his shirt but also because like i would sure like it if other people who like
the same thing i like come up to me and talk to me about it uh you know that's why everybody needs to
go to i am games and i am games t-shirt we have we have multiple designs now if you if you want to
rep your doomer pride get a doomer t-shirt we also have a new shirt based on an old digi video
of a pixelated ken of uh of uh of mountain dew ice also i am a fucking alicorn princess you know
that is we should put that on that on there for posterity's sake you should yeah yeah yeah
no this new shirt's great because it's just a pixelated can of of uh mountain dew ice and
then under just says it's a sprite because you know it's a sprite is like my favorite videos
did you made well we have a shirt for it now and it's a sprite of a can so it's a double meaning
it's i haven't seen it i haven't seen it's a sprite google did you know is that like the pipe
watch that video it's like a minute long it's great i highly recommend it's a good video it's
like 24 seconds i watched it again a few days ago it's i really love that video i got it i gotta
get that boy 24 seconds of ad revenue but just to the guy's point like obviously we're i'm not
saying wear on an anime shirt like so you can talk to other anime fans like solve your problems
but like you you probably got to break through some people's barriers to like actually get to
know who they really are like so i don't know work on just like talking to people and not being
weird and creepy and join join a fucking club or something be a social extracurricular activities
are a good way he's right yes because like when you're in school everyone's like in zombie mode
you gotta like get there yeah you're gonna have you're gonna have you're gonna have superficial
interactions and like following following people on instagram is another superficial
interaction you've got to engage with people on a deeper level and an extracurricular activity
is probably a good way to get something like that good idea it's a damn good idea yeah all right
well there you go uh moving on guys guys what do you do when you leave school there are no extracurricular
activities they're recorded that's what i want to know www.meetup.com there's um i got that app but
none of it's tender tender um i actually i was looking into this when i moved to Cincinnati a
little while ago and like i joined excuse me i still get messages even though i want them to all go
away there's just like it's like meetup.com and then you can just like people have clubs around
they put them up there you just like go and you know there's people doing fun things you can go
hang out with them and i would love to go to a game dip. I uh unironically enjoyed a bunch of like uh
like Ohio free thinkers which is like the atheist group because i really i really like the fucking
uh what is it called uh it's not the wake of the podcast there's there's this podcast out of Austin
with Matt Dillahunty that i can't remember the name of that i've always wanted to be on oh the
atheist experience and i wanted to be in a group like that of just super intellectual gods who know
that god is just a fucking joke but you are you're in the pcp uh what you're right sometimes i need
a bit more sick all right post christianity podcast exactly okay we got we got another one here from
puny philosophy i don't know what that means i think there's that indian for vagina uh whatever
no that's yoni okay i believe hey guys i see you're looking for the multiculturalism well here i am
all the way from india yeah i hope it was all that you hoped for but uh get to my point uh can you
guys please get digi to never talk about nihilism or subjectivity ever again yeah yes it's all an
interesting position every dumb philosophy undergrad has to be weaned off of this everything is subjective
nonsense this is really good also read a fucking book digi
he should probably read a book you know what i mean indian comrades what a great what a great rib
from from uh yeah that was a fully fully bone fully boned rib on that one uh yeah so the thing
about digi's nihilism thing is that he's not incorrect but like you can go a lot further like
like i feel that i have gone a few steps further i recognize that there truly is no subjective
reality but we can if you want we just make some assumptions and i'll listen what sorry what if you
want peak nihilism you go to the amazing atheist youtube channel that's the biggest nihilist of
all times am i am i right is this is this money did digi like go to like one semester of college
take like i think it took like one philosophy class and like dropped out before it was finished i mean
i or something like that i think there was something along those lines i don't know i'm not trying to
rag i mean i actually i remember his mom was doing photography uh i remember his mom was doing
photography yeah he went like with his mom that photography is not philosophy give well they sound
yeah they're so similar are you sure they're not the same uh anyway okay good good good good philosophy
is just photography but for the mind you take pictures of that's my subjective opinion yeah and
you can't disprove it um so you know there there it is okay all right next mail uh here we go this
way we've got uh three more you know if did you know if did you would show up to episodes more often
we wouldn't trash myself from these vicious riddles um we've got one this is from a discount
lacroix shoe is the name of this individual let's yeah oh it's this sound gum shoe oh yeah you're
right here you go right like oh oh you hear that you fucking boomer i do it's sparkling water
it's carbonated sparkling water okay i'm gonna drink it okay um carbonated water carbonic acid
i love cockroach water i don't know why this is so funny but it is boomers are weak i love making
boomers feel uncomfortable you're the song choice is doing that you'll be so weak
fucking sucrose on the synapses what's it feel like boomers
wait it was like he was like the final boss the final boss of the podcast was discount
gum shoe drinking lacroix and challenging us to stop him and we can't we can't do a damn thing
megalovania the background i like that but there was there wasn't enough slurping yeah
it wasn't enough loud gulping and slurping noises we had we hadn't started the battle yet that was
just the uh the pre the pre pre battled calm before the storm yeah i think he's right uh well
that was powerful um moving on uh quick hard uh left turn to starving and tired uh with this next
message do it piano man
okay i just want to say i am very disappointed that the podcast was late this week oh yeah i'm
sitting here on a god damn friday waiting waiting for the good news to come to me and my brothers
you fool but lo and behold it is not here my friends for we have to wait wait until our
seven shitty overlords decide to get off their ass press a fucking button
watch the there was a shekels for heckles going on just you just want just tide yourself over with
the shekels for heckles that was happening as you made this all right but that was some hardcore
ribbing to ben for sure yeah well deserved all right yeah that sigh at the beginning was truly
earth shattering um the weight of his mistake was instantly known to bet he the sin i'm really
feeling the sins crawling on my back right now speaking of which um our last voicemail is from
better ben better ben impossible let's see uh end us on a strong note
bad things are about this is known
fucking okay so my rabbit died and that really sucked it made me really depressed
then the same fucking day i got stood up on a date and then the hypocrite channel the hypocrite
channel is gone yeah that's sad but not that sad because reviews are fucking gay
reviews are so gay and stupid and no one should do that
fucking end uh look yeah they're bad they're so bad and they're so terrible sounds like he's not
that sad about it actually yeah about that i agree i guess he's comforting himself with this thought
bad things happen yeah but some of those bad things weren't that bad and yeah i think it's
i think it's just sour grapes talking i think now now that he can't have it he has to say
ugh reviews are stupid anyway hypocrite was dumb didn't even want it
maybe this guy's just also named ben but he thinks he's better yeah that's my guess that's my guess
well he's wrong he's wrong of course well i need some proof before uh extraordinary claims require
extraordinary evidence as they say that's true that's true yeah exactly yeah well uh i guess that's
it if you want to hit a real high note in your life you've got to hit up patreon.com
slash the procrastinators the euphoria you will experience as you click that pledge button and
you pledge at least five dollars a month to get those sweet 18 bonus episodes will be
unsurmountable it'll be unsurpassed in your life that's like fifth that's like 30 hours the next
time then is late with an episode you'll have 18 on deck ready to fill your need that's true he's
right he's right they're all high quality uh that's a lie but nonetheless you should buy
our money some at least some of them are high quality that's true that's fair that's a fair
decision there are some there are some there are some definite winners i say this most of them are
like there's a few strange ones you're gonna want to go straight to the asmr ones start there there's
a couple of weird there's a couple of weird experiments that maybe didn't quite work asmr was
that were maybe not that were maybe not quote unquote consumer friendly
maybe may not worth the money you spent on
fucking owned fucking destroyed uh and you might as well still follow us at tpcrasnirs on twitter
though uh we're not doing questions guys we're just doing voicemail i should have said this before
the voicemail is probably um but yeah that's fine it's fine to end on that we said we said we said
we said it last we did we did uh i mean maybe if somebody you know one episode maybe somebody
missed it but oh fair enough if you got if you got a question send it fucking ask us on the speak
pipe we all know the voicemails are better guys it's way better uh million times better and cooler
and doper and that's it so why even bother uh so we'll okay we're trying this out if there's
some giant outcry we'll think about it but you know this is what we're doing we're gonna see how it
goes and go fuck yourself if you don't like it um oh no now what do we do we can't end the episode
like this um yes we can um goodbye