Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
This is number 202, don't check that dial, you're in the right place, I promise you.
I'm the best guy ever, and we've got Tom Oliver.
I am ready for another action-packed episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Same.
We've got Gibbontake.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
He's Ben Saint.
Take a look at my brother.
He's the only one I got, unfortunately.
All right.
Let me, let me quickly.
I don't have to spend too long on it.
Guys, I've developed a new skill.
I can read the minds of presidential candidates.
This is Bernie Sanders at this very moment.
The blacks.
What did the blacks betray?
Why?
I give the blacks everything.
And they just, they give me shit every day.
He fought their rights.
Why can't they vote for me?
He got arrested protecting their fucking right to be in our society.
Like the damn white savior that he is, god damn it.
And frankly, we're all sick of it, us in the black community.
It's okay.
It's not just yet.
South Carolina.
South Carolina is a freakish, little mutant state.
Black people in South Carolina are not like other black people.
They're South Carolinians, i.e. they're freaks.
They're monsters.
Listen, funny thing, funny thing about the South, this is a factoid that I learned.
People in South Carolina overwhelmingly voted for Joe Biden.
Even ones that reported agreeing with Sanders on like every issue.
It's got to be optic stuff.
Yeah, ones that said they were for Medicare for all voted Biden.
Ones that describe themselves as very liberal voted Biden and so on and so forth.
It's just like a cultural, like social pressure expectation thing.
They all just like Joe Biden and you're expected to like Joe Biden if you're a South Carolinian.
Got to be the O.Q., the Obama question.
It's got to be a factor here.
Maybe.
Partially.
Maybe South Carolinians don't look up who does what.
Funny thing, there was this guy, this House Majority Whip James Clyburn is like a very
I learned what a whip is from House of Cards.
I know what that is.
I actually don't know what a whip is.
Tell me what a whip is.
What they do is they get their party to vote for the things they collectively decide they want.
That's what a whip does.
They literally call the vote.
They want to get the representatives of the party.
If the leader says we're doing this thing and the whip will get all of the other people
to do it.
That's the idea.
Yeah.
To literally whip them into line.
As in he convinces other people to vote.
I mean, yes, correct.
But isn't that what all representatives do?
No, no, no.
They're arguing their case.
It's in what do you call it, inside thing.
It's not like whipping the voters into shape.
It's whipping the other representatives of that party.
Right.
I know.
But I thought that's what representatives do.
They go to Congress.
They make speeches.
They talk about stuff.
They make proposals and then they vote on them.
I kind of thought...
Yeah, and then the whip just changes their vote.
Just destroys them.
Inside our politics stuff.
We probably would want purely the will of the people from whatever area they're from
to pressure people.
This is like an internal congressional pressure system.
The idea that a local community votes in a representative says,
I'm going to do this for the local community.
He goes up and he's part of a party and then a guy from the top says,
change what you say.
Change what you're doing because the leader of the party says, fuck you.
I've got a whip here and I'm going to fucking whip you.
That's the reality.
But I was elected and my local constituents, they won't mean it.
They won't mean it.
No, no, no.
Whopam.
The upshot it.
I stayed up last night watching the results.
The upshot is this.
Bad result for Bernie yesterday, but they are...
Is he surging ahead overall?
He did surge ahead with Nevada.
South Carolina has almost...
I think Bernie is still ahead in delegates, but not by very much.
South Carolina is the most populous state that has voted so far.
They have the most representatives that voted so far,
and they also happen to be the worst state.
By the time people hear this, Super Tuesday will be over,
which will basically determine the whole rest of this fucking shebang.
Why is that the case?
Because this happens to be one day called Super Tuesday
where I think 13 different states vote,
including really big ones like California and Texas.
I think Texas.
So you get so much momentum if you win at all from that thing.
A big part of the delegate count is decided on Super Tuesday for some reason.
Is it like once the results come in, everyone who hasn't voted yet
in their states will be like, oh, I can see who's going to win,
so I'm just going to vote like that?
Yes, that is the effect of reality.
Basically, yeah.
Isn't that stupid?
It shouldn't work that way basically.
But wait a minute, isn't that stupid?
Yes.
I think the moral of the story is that the more you dig into this process,
the more you realize that 99% of it is asinine and moronic,
and it doesn't serve any purpose.
There's been two caucuses so far.
At the Iowa caucus, sometimes they had to flip coins
to determine who got a delegate.
In Nevada, sometimes they pulled cards out of a deck.
Such fucking cringe.
Yeah.
You got to decide the shit somehow.
I like the theming.
I like the theming that in the Vegas state,
they flip cards to determine who gets the fucking delegate.
That's some like homestuck level, like a modus,
fetch modus level.
I say we upgrade that.
We have it so that the candidates have to personally speed run.
What's that sonic level that looks like Las Vegas,
like the gaming zone or whatever?
They should be decided based on that scale.
I think they should add a clause that says
that any candidate who successfully back hovers
and clips through the walls of the White House
into the Oval Office.
Whoever can do it with the least amount of A presses.
Through the wall.
I could see Bernie doing that.
I haven't seen the inside of the White House,
but I now definitely think there is an endless staircase
up to the Oval Office.
You need a certain amount of political stars to gain access,
or you could do the backers long trial.
You have to get 120 delegates.
It's like how many...
No, that's what they're going to do if they force a brokered convention.
It's like what's the fewest number of delegates
you can get and still cheat your way through the walls
into the Oval Office.
That's been the race.
They coveted zero delegate winner, which I'm looking forward to.
The fabled. Nobody thought they could do it
until they unlocked New Tech.
It was called Super Delegates.
Before I explain how Super Delegates work,
I'm going to have to explain. Parallel universes.
It turns out they can actually...
We don't accept Super Delegates.
There are no tool-assisted runs in this competition.
Right. Very much.
This is just a hypothetical run.
You could potentially get it,
but if you're playing on the real hardware, it's more difficult.
That's true, but you've got to use the Japanese copy
of the electoral voting system.
You've got to long jump from Japan to get into the White House.
It saves you a couple of frames here and there
when you long jump.
Buildup speed. Ah ha, funny. Ah ha, hee hee.
I would care a lot more about politics
if they were all true gamers and they play video games all the time.
There's an account on Twitter called GamerPrez.
Have you seen this guy? Yeah, I'm aware of him.
Let me...
Is it Andrew Dang?
No, it's Ace Watkins, GamerPrez 2020.
GamerPrez is pretty great.
Does he stream?
No, he's just... Not that I know of.
No, he does.
Yeah, he twitched out TV slash...
Oh, no, he was streaming from PAX this weekend.
Well, he needs to clip into the White House.
I mean, obviously, this is his turf.
Society is like a big game of Smash Bros.
Yes, we're all playing the same game,
but many are forced to play with a sideways joycon.
We need policies that let all Americans play
with the GameCube controls.
They can hit beefy Joker combos to the best of their ability.
You know, when you put it like that, I understand.
At last, I see.
That's a good one.
This is, by the way,
speaking of broker conventions,
whipping delegates into producing the results desired and whatnot.
Wait, wait, I just want to say...
The reason I brought up the House majority whip James Clyburn
is that he endorsed Biden, and I guess it made a huge difference.
But what I'm confused about
is how are the people of South Carolina
so clued in that they know who their state's
House majority whip representative in Congress...
I don't know who my local representative is.
I don't.
I think they probably just...
But not clued in an ignorant enough
to not know that the Medicare for all guy is Bernie Sanders.
I think, Ben, that's a very revealing question.
I think what it says is that, I mean, fair...
Whether it speaks well to human society or not,
I think people identify themselves with a guy
that clearly they like, like this representative
from their area and whatnot,
and they think, I'm going to trust this guy
rather than independently investigating which candidates
may or may not represent their interests best.
No, it's not. He's from Delaware.
He's just very popular in the South.
Well, okay.
What I'm saying is that this Clyburn guy,
he's not like a big... He's a representative.
And I'm saying, I don't know my representative.
I feel like most Americans probably don't know
who they represent.
To me, if my local representative was like,
hey, guys, actually Warren is going to be really great.
I don't fucking care what you think. Who are you?
I mean, I heard that...
But apparently these people are clued in enough
to know who their local state rep is,
but not clued in on the race enough to be like,
boy, I'm very liberal. I'm for Medicare for all.
I think the system needs reform from the ground up
and not just moderate change.
But my neighbor said Biden's a nice guy,
so I'm going to vote for him.
But what this may speak to,
it's the fact that most voters are, in fact,
like older adults who know those sorts of things more,
as opposed to our generation.
I don't know. That's my best guess.
I'm just saying, but then they should know who Bernie is.
They should know that Bernie's...
They should know the policy difference.
I mean, Bernie does better with younger voters than older, so...
It could be like there's like a local news
that sort of shits on Bernie or something,
and they're like, ah, yeah, fuck him.
Fuck that guy. He's got white hair.
He does. My... Unlike Biden.
God, let me just... Let me complain.
The thing I hate most about Biden is his haircut,
and I don't like how he keeps it long in the back.
Like a mullet?
It's like a little long, I don't know.
Every time I see him from behind, I'm like,
dude, just trim me off the fucking back of your head, dude.
Why do you keep it long back there? It's fucked up.
It's fucked up, man.
It's unfortunate.
The thing that keeps me going, though,
demographically, not similar at all to the United States,
the Democrats in South Carolina are basically Republicans,
because there's just...
In some parts of the country, I think black people just are Democrats,
even if they're conservative, right?
Because I think it's just like...
I've heard something like that.
It's just like societally expected.
Like, if you're black, you should be a Democrat.
That's just what people think.
But like, South Carolina is a very conservative state.
So they're basically just Republicans that call themselves Democrats
because that's what you're expected to do.
So, I don't know. It's a highly unrepresentative state.
It's the worst state in the Union.
We should crack it off into the sea.
Let's vote. What's the worst state?
I mean, you know, this might have been a setback for you
for South Carolina. I would go with...
Florida might be the worst. Florida...
I think Florida and South Carolina are...
Florida's cool.
I mean, the whole South is pretty bad.
And Florida men. Countless Florida men doing all kinds of kooky stuff.
That's true.
I'm a fan of those.
Florida's very entertaining.
If nothing else.
If any state was going to succeed
and become an anarcho-capitalist godland,
it would be Florida in my guess.
So I have hope for them.
A guy on Twitter the other day...
A guy on Twitter the other day was sincerely arguing at me
that we should have no minimum wage
because, sure, workers might not be able to buy that 70-inch TV they wanted,
but collectively, employers would hire more people.
So even though individuals would be getting paid less,
on the whole, the total working class would be more employed
and be getting more money.
And no.
Oh, God.
It's a complicated fucking... I don't know.
That's not...
That's the worst fucking idea I've ever...
Yeah, no minimum...
Yeah, just let them pay fucking workers like fucking 50 cents an hour
if they want.
Like, sure, okay.
I mean, great idea.
1,000 guys at, like, 0.1 PC pennies.
Just employ the entire population of the United States at 0.1 cents an hour.
I mean, they can dig and do that, but the only problem is,
let's say you do employ the entire working class at, like, 50 cents an hour.
They can't buy any of the product those companies need to stay in business,
so they'll inevitably have to adjust prices anyway.
The thing that a business will do, they will always do that.
They will always hire the fewest number of people at the lowest wage possible.
Sure.
The argument that, like, if you lower the minimum wage,
businesses will hire more people is total bunk,
because there's no incentive for them to hire more people than they need.
Well, there's a little incentive.
Just because wages are lower.
They still want to hire the least number of people,
no matter what the wage is.
If you have more workers, like, if you can...
It depends on, like, what your business is and what it needs,
because, like, for example, if you can hire two workers and double your production,
and now it costs the same as it was to hire one worker before,
then, theoretically, you could do that,
because it could be a bigger benefit to you to double your production speed
than to just reduce your overall labor costs.
There could be benefits down the pipeline of your particular business.
Well, I mean, yeah, sure.
I guess so.
But, like...
Okay, I'm losing...
It's a very complicated question.
There's a lot of factors, but, like, on the whole,
a minimum wage seems like a safe thing to have.
A business might be able to...
Yeah, okay, I guess it's true.
I don't think it makes any sense.
I don't think lowering the minimum wage is so...
I think that a business that cannot pay a living wage should just die.
I think that's how we should do it.
I guess we have to die, because we can't afford to pay Eleazar a living wage.
We don't hire him full-time.
He's not working 40 hours a week for us.
Ben, would you say that's true of any business, regardless of size?
Yes.
Because you know that I was...
You know, I happened to hear your boy, Vouch, the other day,
who was doing a debate where he argued because that his channel was so small,
he was exempted.
You just said it matters regardless of size, Ben.
Wait, weren't you?
Yeah, I watched it.
Yeah, okay.
But I mean, Vouch himself said he felt that his business was exempted
because he was so small, it didn't make sense economically, for a small-sized business.
Do you disagree with that?
Exempt from what?
From paying the people who work for him a living wage.
I think morally, it just shouldn't be the case that you can get away with not paying people a living wage,
whatever a living wage happens to be.
I agree.
I mean, is it also true that Bernie Sanders himself couldn't pay his wages,
his workers $15 an hour because their organization couldn't afford it?
That is true.
Didn't that also happen?
That did happen.
Well, obviously scale matters.
I mean, that would probably be...
I don't know.
Where are you getting that information?
I don't know how much Bernie...
I don't remember.
I don't know how much Bernie pays his employees, do you?
It was like a year or so.
It was a while ago, they were talking about how we couldn't afford to pay $15 to whoever was working for him.
If he can't, then I'm sure nobody else on the campaign show can.
You hear, like, Khloé Bouchard is apparently fucking withheld benefits
and withheld payments from her employers and stuff.
Well, the point here is just to say, these things seem like Amazon can't afford,
so they did.
Fantastic.
Like a mom-and-pop shop that's trying to get off the ground doesn't seem appropriate
to hold the exact same standard for them as a giant corporation.
Well, this...
These things should probably vary.
This brings up...
I was watching a video.
And let the workers decide if they want to work at those places or not.
There was an interesting point someone was saying that the minimum wage actually helps,
like, fuck up the way business is done because, like, if you have a minimum wage,
like, big corporate interests, like big corporations like Amazon, like Apple and stuff,
you can afford to pay higher minimum wage while you're driving smaller businesses out
of the equation.
So you basically, like, consolidate corporate and business interests like a hand of smaller
and fewer, fewer companies.
Which kind of makes sense.
Yes, sure.
But here's the thing.
Here's the thing with the minimum wage.
Like, we're talking about $15 an hour, but $15 an hour is not, like, a mathematically
arrived at number.
It's like a slogan that sounds good because it's better than the deal that everybody
has now.
Like, living wage is different from state to state.
And, yeah.
The whole thing is that there is so much inflated costs and all of the things we buy already
because corporations are trying to ring every dime they can out of their customers.
Like, even if you can't have a living wage in terms of, like, paying $15 an hour, like,
just ethically speaking, like, if you're working full time, you should be able to at least,
like, afford a minimum standard of, like, supporting yourself, you know?
Because, like, a lot of the common defense I hear of against, like, the minimum wage
and stuff is that, like, oh, a lot of these jobs weren't designed to live off of.
And it's like, that could be true.
But that doesn't change the fact that, like, the reality is there are people who have to
take these jobs and need to live off of them.
And so, like, there is a problem here and it needs to be addressed.
It's the same thing with Medicare for All.
You know, like, a lot of the argument is that it's so fucking expensive.
How are we going to pay for it?
It doesn't make any sense.
It's like, yeah, it's expensive and that is a problem.
But that doesn't change the fact that, like, when the coronavirus comes around and we all
have to take, like, a month off of work and quarantine, everyone's going to go, like,
$40,000 a debt in medical bills.
So, like, there are problems that need to be solved, regardless of these issues.
And the discussion needs to be had at some point.
We can't just keep kicking the can down the road.
Uh, yeah, that all sounds pretty reasonable.
Um, workers of the world tonight.
I don't know what else to say about that.
A minimum wage is good.
Raising the minimum wage, I don't know.
I think it's good.
Like, you could say that, like, oh, it might kill smaller businesses and only the juggernauts
will survive.
I mean, maybe.
But do you think Amazon wants to be forced to pay all its workers $15 an hour?
No.
At the end of the day, no.
That costs them a lot of money and that's good.
Well, I guess it comes down to, like, how does the equation play out long term for Jeff
Bezos, right?
Like, he pays his employees $15 an hour and that's bad.
But, like, maybe 10 years from now, uh, all of the local competition for Amazon is destroyed.
And so everyone has to buy from Amazon now and now he's making more money that easily
pays for the $15 and then some.
So, like.
I mean, I, I, I don't, I don't think that's, that doesn't seem very likely.
That doesn't seem very likely that demand, that demanding Amazon pay more would through
some, like, weird, I mean, through, through some kind of like accidental math calculus
actually ends up making the money.
It just seems really unlikely and like an outside scenario.
I mean, I don't know.
I'm just saying it's possible.
I just, I'm not an economist.
I'm no fucking expert.
Isn't there a phenomenon that is already happening like with Walmart and like squeezing out businesses
where they plop down and they can afford to undercut businesses there because they have
so much funding from their, you know, international business that like they're able to sell things
cheaper.
So people just go there and it squeezes out.
I think the whole like big shops destroying small businesses is just a thing that is naturally
always going to happen.
Yeah.
And the workers being paid fairly is not the tipping point.
It's, it just slowly always happens.
It depends.
Like it matters which tool you use to solve a given problem too.
So like, is the solution to all of these concerns make a nationwide like set limit for minimum
for any given job, or is it to like for Amazon, for the people who specifically work at Amazon
to like, if they want to unionize, that seems like the right kind of move.
And if they want to fire everybody, I mean, fair enough, but like it's for the workers,
I would argue, to negotiate these issues with their specific employers because not every
employer is in fact the same.
And there's always going to be differences between these things that have to be worked out
based on the specific circumstances of that employment.
Sure.
That'd be my guess.
Well, it is, I mean, it is for, I mean, under capitalism, right?
We can accept capitalism for now, for the sake of this discussion.
It is the responsibility of an employer or a union on behalf of the employers to negotiate
these things.
Things like Medicare for all $15 minimum wage and gives those, that party more bargaining
power and just like a better place coming into the negotiations.
I don't know.
If you're living-
I think there's just a good faith argument to be had that does that specifically, does
that solve all the problems we want and not generate more than it fixes?
There's an argument to be had.
I come down, I come down on the side that like, okay, we've got this gig, we've got the gig
economy, we've got high employment, but high underemployment, lots of people working, having
to work multiple jobs, lots of people like being underemployed working jobs that don't
pay enough to live on.
That seems to be a situation in which the employers have all the power, right?
They've got all the workers they want, but they have them at like, they have them working
for no benefits at really low wages.
That seems like a situation in which the employers are the ones with all the advantages and so
it would seem like a good idea to pass reforms that, you know, balance the scales.
For situations like that, sure.
I'm definitely sympathetic to causes like that.
Yeah.
That's my opinion.
I didn't think this would go on for this long, but anyway, hope Bernie wins on Super Tuesday,
guys.
Well, everyone will know what's happened by the time they're listening to this.
Yeah.
I'll be curious to see what people think.
No, this is going to be great.
This is going to be great because this episode is going to go up on next Friday, right?
So that's like when Radcon starts.
So we can go directly into Ben either celebrating or raging about this very topic mere hours
after this airs.
Yeah.
Let's address that.
By the time, when you're here in this, we're half an hour in, give or take.
Like two hours after this goes live, we check in at 4 p.m. into the Radcon for Paradise House
and we'll be kicking off the festivities, probably with a live stream as fast as possible on that
day.
That's the plan for me anyway.
We'll see.
We'll see what's going on there.
So, hey, Tom, our flight is on Friday morning.
I believe so.
I think you told me, Ben, that you were getting in around the same time as me, which I thought
was around noon, but correct me if I'm wrong.
On Friday, though, right?
On Friday, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
On the sixth.
I gotta get, I'm nervous.
You gotta get your shit together is what you gotta do, Ben.
I do have to get my shit together.
All right, Ben, poster update, status.
What's the deal?
How are we doing?
Wasn't yesterday the deadline for people to get their pictures in?
Okay.
That's true, Ben.
But as you and I discussed, there's tons you could have done before having every single
person in.
And by the way, there are three outliers.
It's literally too late if you're hearing this and you didn't already respond, but I
tried so many ways to reach those last few people.
I'm sorry, but fuck you if you just didn't.
What else can I say?
Yeah.
We'll do our best.
We'll put like a blank, empty thing with like your initials or something on there.
I don't know.
You'll get your fucking credit.
Fuck you.
I'm surprised there's only three.
I figured there would be more.
They trickled in.
Oh, and you know what?
Good news.
One of the three is Riddle My Ass Batman.
So let's just slap Batman in there with a confused look on his face.
Yeah.
Okay.
That one's covered.
But the other two.
Wait, he'd be the Riddler, right?
Yes.
Well, he is in fact Batman.
Wait.
No, he's Riddle My Ass Batman.
No, he's Riddle My Ass Batman is the Riddler.
No, Batman is one of his characters.
He's one of his characters.
Yeah, he talks to Batman.
He's kind of a fusion.
He's both Batman and the Riddler.
No, no, no.
He's the Riddler and he says Riddle My Ass Batman.
He is the Riddler.
You're right.
But he also speaks as Batman.
Well, he's not the same guy when he does that.
Yeah, but he's just playing a character.
He's two characters.
That's true.
I think the true core of Riddle My Ass Batman is the ass, I think.
I'll just draw him as a weird composite of the two.
It's fine.
Sounds good.
And the other two, I mean, I'll reach out to him one last time, but they're fucked.
But you, Ben, here's Inside Baseball.
We did the math.
You have until the end of March 4th to get that done.
That's when Munchie needs it to print it.
If not, we will lose several hundred dollars in printing costs, which we'd like to avoid
if possible.
Yes.
I know about that.
I know that.
I'm actually going to start it today after this very recording.
Sounds good.
I'm very excited.
Oh, and you know what I discovered?
I've long regretted.
I was looking at the Shovel Knight Kickstarter, for example, and I was like, oh, they've got
like a cool banner behind their thing at the top.
How do we do that?
Because I didn't think it was possible.
Turns out, once you have a successful Kickstarter, you can go in and edit like the image behind
the top of your Kickstarter page.
I never did it for Radcon 3, but for Radcon 4, I want to put that poster art once it's
there behind it in big, glorious, you know, artistry, so everybody can see.
So there's further motivation to not fuck it up.
I didn't realize our Kickstarter became an art piece once it was successful.
Only after it succeeds, but yeah, I guess so.
That's pretty silly.
I got to tell you.
This very day, I finally sat down and I have been building an outline of my Nate's Mysterious
Unnamed Lecture that I'll be doing, but I have a basic framework for it.
I've been going over the details.
I think it's going to be meaty.
I think it's going to be juicy.
I can see where meme potential lies, and a lot of those things just emerge as they come
up naturally, so I can't predict everything, but a lot of epic memory and I can't wait
to point out all the little minutiae that I care about that nobody else does about this
particular thing.
Oh, it's going to be good.
It's going to be like a live, you know what?
I was going to say some of this spoily, but I just won't say it after all.
It's going to be good.
It's going to be fun, and I can't wait.
Yes.
God, Radcon 4 is so close.
It's so nerve-wracking.
I always get that sort of, that anxiety about that.
I get those coronavirus shakes.
It's weird whenever I fly, you know what I'm saying?
Ben, I'm going to bring masks for us when we have to go to Logan, so we don't die.
Not a bad idea.
It has been a case of coronavirus in Boston.
I saw that article a month ago, and I was like, Ben, what did you do?
The odds were extremely likely it came through Logan Airport, wouldn't you say?
Oh, I mean, it's almost probably, like 100%, absolutely.
So the whole place is infected?
Yeah.
Maybe.
Could be around there.
I can't wait for Radcon 5 coronavirus as we infect all of you.
Yeah, that'll be fun.
Radcon 5.
It'll be like the eclipse.
There'll be no Radcon 5.
We'll all be dead.
Maybe one of us will die in the eclipse or not.
I'm already thinking of Radcon 5, and like the artistry we use for it, we call it Radcon
5 the eclipse.
And it's five of us have been infected with the coronavirus, like the five godhand from
Berserk and one of us guts, me, I'll say, is still alive, while the five of you attempt
to murder me with your deadly disease.
Excellent theming, Nate.
Well done.
I'm jotting this down.
All right, I'm ready.
A famous rape that goes down in the annals of history.
The annals of history.
The annals of history, yeah, yeah.
Excellent.
On brand.
It's perfect.
Oh, that'll be the OVA, the rape scene that will go on Pornhub for that one.
I was just thinking earlier today, I was musing to myself and put it in the chat, that I was
just looking at the numbers, and obviously we couldn't have really predicted things 100%
the way they came out.
But now that we know how much interest that there is in a radcon, I was just thinking
of old plans.
I was thinking of a radcon five.
With 20,000 to 30,000 dollars, that's got to be in the realm of actually being able
to make an actual rad convention possible, as in renting out a location.
With 30,000 dollars, that has to be enough to rent a place for a few days, maybe two
maybe three years.
30,000 dollars, that's almost enough to pay off my student loans.
Yeah, wouldn't that be nice.
We just got to do a couple more dates.
Oh, the pain.
The 30,000 is going somewhat to plane tickets and accommodation for us as well.
Well, that's definitely true.
We wouldn't have an entire 30, I mean I don't expect, well maybe actually, I guess if there
was like radcon ticket, like you buy a ticket and then you can come to the thing, what the
hell would we do?
I have no idea.
I mean just stand there on the flip side.
Well, I mean obviously lots of plans would be there.
The number one thing would be live lectures.
I mean I feel like the lectures could just be at least experimented upon.
Live lectures in front of a crowd.
In front of an actual crowd.
We could do, I mean we could do people like the Game Grumps or like Chappo Trapp House
or whatever.
They do like a, or I think the Dick Show does this or whatever, they do live episodes, right?
Remember when we did the horse cast live at BronyCon and stuff?
It was good.
It's basically like a PCP live.
It'd be the same.
It's exactly, and it's just we just fucking chat on stage in front of a crowd.
See I think like with that stuff, some lectures, like I don't know, we could do, we've all
got shows.
Like we could do a fucking can tent episode live, a pod D cast live.
Like there's definitely stuff we could fill the roster out with.
Absolutely.
So I mean, I think it's totally doable.
It's just a matter of organization, a little bit of funding.
We have the, I mean we have the, how much would renting like a theater cost?
It depends on the venue, right?
Maybe a couple thousand.
I bet we could get a decent place with an audience for like a couple thousand, or even
we could rent like the stage at like a bar or something and just like fill up the bar
with people.
That's true.
I mean, I think realistically, based on our Radcon 3 or Radcon 4 earnings, like if we
just got a humble $20,000, I think that would be more than enough to cover like all of our
flights out and like renting a reasonably small space for like a day or two to do stuff
within.
That's my initial guess.
That seems fair.
Yeah.
The problem is...
And we could sell tickets, Ben.
Think of the profits.
Well, I mean, the only problem is I think our audience is small enough, but I don't know
if we have...
Like they fund it, but there wouldn't be tons of outside people maybe would buy tickets
after or something.
Yeah, like our audience is dispersed enough that I don't think we could go to like New
York and there's like a, there's like a sizable contingent of PCP fans specifically in New
York, for example, who would...
Well, the solution to that problem is we all need to blow up and then act like I don't
know nobody, but we don't do that.
We actually do act like we know each other, so we all get more famous and then we sell
this thing and we get everybody who even likes us a little bit to come to our rare public
appearances.
I mean...
This is my thought.
Yeah.
Sounds pretty cool.
It's just...
Yeah.
Let me just go do that.
Let me just go do...
Be famous.
Selling tickets in a specific area seems like it would be tough.
I mean, certainly possible.
Let's go to the moon.
Let's go to the moon for Radcon 5.
I mean, we know.
I mean, one of the things...
How much is a fucking rocket?
Let me just pay one of the sets to stand out on the street and be and give out flyers like,
hey, you guys want to see a comedy show later tonight?
It's gonna be really funny.
I mean, I think there's tons of stuff we could do with it, but one of the things that got
me thinking was just, excuse me, the reality that like, whether we intended it or not,
many people or at least several people are straight up flying out to come just to hang
out at the one appearance that we're doing at fucking Radcon.
Do we have an idea?
Oh, and by the way, we decided on a location to meet up.
If you haven't seen any updates, we're gonna meet at the Poseidon statue in Virginia Beach.
So if you're hearing this on the 14th, that's where it will be.
There will be updates out there, but in the link in the show notes, we'll put like the
actual Google coordinates so you know exactly how to get there.
So there you go.
Update.
I would suggest if you are maybe not in the, if you're coming out to the meetup, but you're
not like a big backer in the, you know, the PTA server, I would say maybe just join the
regular PCP server, we'll probably be updating people there like where the meetup is and
what's going on.
Right.
For sure.
If you want to like follow along, like make sure you're abreast of like where we're moving
to.
Oh, and just for the times and whatnot, right.
So Poseidon statue link below to exactly where it is.
It's well known.
It's famous in Virginia Beach.
That's on.
And it's at 2pm on March 14th.
That's where we will be on that day.
Poseidon.
Okay.
Sick.
Mm-hmm.
That's the real shit.
I don't know what we'll do, but it's on the beach, we're gonna go hang out and we'll
figure something out.
We'll probably stalk around on the beach, maybe go get food, maybe move to a bar or something.
Yep.
I don't know.
Just hanging out with the, with my boys.
Just fucking around.
Just fucking.
We're just gonna be.
Straight fuck on the beach.
Yeah.
Let's all bring our, our signs and say hashtag just fucking.
Just fucking.
That's a new T-shirt.
I'm just fucking.
Not bad.
Okay.
This could be good.
Sick.
Buy a PCP T-shirt and.
Please, God.
And so we know who you are when you get there.
Oh, that, that would be true.
Where your, where your market distinction.
I saw some of our backers wearing like I am game.
Distinction.
I saw some of our backers wearing like I am games T-shirts.
I don't know if you got fucking the famous Gibbs shirts.
The, the BROP.
No.
I don't know.
Some BGE shirts.
I'm just being cool.
Wear a Ben Saint shirt.
Wear a Ben Saint heart shirt.
Wear a, wear a Yang shirt.
Wear one of my Yang shirts or my Lisa 2020 shirts or my Feel the Burn shirts.
I've got to put out a call to anybody who's there.
Any of the Nate heads.
We have to band together and defeat the Ben's once and for all.
Ben heads?
I guess they're Ben heads.
Uh, yeah.
Saint heads.
God heads.
We'll go over cop killer stuff.
If you choose to be a Ben head as well, that's fine, but we need to do glorious battle and
settle this once and for all.
I will kill all my supporters.
Will Ben's cowardly tactics defeat the god like Adonises that are the Nate heads?
There's only one way to find out.
We'll settle it.
We're on the beach.
We'll, we'll settle it and smash.
That sounds good.
So any of you guys been doing any, I mean, I was saying before, oh, I don't think I finished
my point.
Oh no.
I'm excited I am specifically for my lecture because I've been going over the details and
getting it all ready.
I'm nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
I need to, um, not only do I need to finish my, um, the art work, I need to, I need to
reread all of, um, the JDRs comics.
I need to make notes.
I need to, um, I'm kind of fucked up about that.
I can't, like I can't bring my computer, like I can't bring my tablet or anything.
So I'm going to be, I guess I just have to save a bunch of like important info to my
phone and bring that with me or put it in a Google drive account or something.
I'm going to be really limited in this stuff I can do at Radcon.
Like I'll barely be able to draw.
Maybe we should, I mean, about some of these things.
I mean, like I was thinking that like it'd be cool to have, I mean, not like a PowerPoint
thing, but I was thinking if I could have like visual aids with me, that might be cool.
So like, should I like maybe print things out ahead of time?
I don't know.
But maybe, maybe some discussion could be had about like, is there any kind of projector
technology we could use or I don't want to over complicate things.
Well, I mean, you've done lectures before.
I'm nervous because I haven't, and I have no idea how it would come together.
But like, surely all you need is notes and maybe to have thought about how you would
structure it before you start speaking.
You know, when I, like my final fantasy one, I was a little scared for because I hadn't
been prepared as much for that.
Like the Kingdom Hearts one, I literally did no prep work and it was not an issue at all.
I just knew everything and it was great and that's probably why it was good.
But like for the one I'm doing now, I also know very well.
But like I was nervous this morning, but then I sat down for like half an hour and busted
out an outline.
And now that I just have that much, I feel way more confident.
And I'm like, okay, now I know what I'm doing.
That's all it took, just a few minutes.
I think, I think that'll be like, I should remember that like, it's actually really helpful
having you guys there, having the little crowd there to like ask questions and stuff.
It helps it all flow smoothly, helps you not forget anything, helps you like go off on
funny tangents and stuff makes it entertaining.
So it's probably, if I had to go up there and just kind of give and just give it like
off the cuff, it would probably come out like, okay, decent.
I do, I do want, no, I want like a set of notes in front of me that I can flip through
and be like, oh yes.
The underrated aspect of the lectures is how much the audience, us specifically, who know
each other so well and are pretty funny, contribute to it and enhance the experience.
We also generally know these things.
It's true.
So that's why you're Tom, Dick and Harry, pretender.
I know you people trying to do your lectures.
The problem is that your audience is full of shitters.
You got to get some red-pilled migtails in that audience, you know, some real elites
to bring the real shit.
When is the fucking RFCK lecture going to come out?
I don't know.
Like a month and a half ago.
That was supposed to be out before the goddamn radcon starts.
You've got four fucking days or five days.
I hoped it would.
I didn't know.
I guess Ethan was working on the stealing your dads and I don't know if he's started
working on the RFCK lecture yet.
I want it so bad.
Don't even bother with over-editing it.
The whole point of a lecture is it's just, it's just simple and the commentary kind of
stuff.
You know what I'm going to do?
Visual aids.
Like in the Tales of Guts 12 lecture, I threw up images of like the characters I was talking
about.
And I do think that is helpful.
Yeah.
I mean, I just regretted not doing that.
But like, that's all in post.
That's all in post.
I wish in Sanichu lecture if I had, like when I talk about the chaotic combo, like I showed
like what they look like on the screen.
It would make it funnier.
A little goes a long way and I regret not doing that for mine.
And actually, some people like, especially for the Kingdom Hearts one, one dude like
remade and re-edited it with visual aids to help.
And we and I talked about like how I felt about him uploading it.
We came to an agreement.
Like this, for the next one I do, I will be adding visual aids, 100%.
No doubt about it.
It's going to make it better.
Always got to add those visual aids.
I'm glad, I'm glad somebody made, I'm glad somebody made for you a Kingdom Hearts lecture
1.5.
That's pretty great.
Indeed.
That's true.
Other thing, I was thinking I've got to do my lecture, you know, writing.
But instead today, I did some of my lyrics for the diss track.
Right.
That's what I made.
Oh, God, I have to do those, you know.
That is unironically the thing I'm most afraid of.
Once some people start busting out their lyrics, I was thinking of mine a little bit today
as well.
Like, there's not too much any of us individually has to do to get that ready.
But so I think it would be like less of each.
Really the thing I was figuring out is like, how does this fit into bars?
I don't have like a natural wrapping understanding.
So I was like tapping my foot or like slapping my knee and be like, okay, so this is the
first beat.
And then I say like this.
And then it's like, that's how many beats, how many bars is that?
Oh, God, it's three.
It's not enough.
I need to add another line.
So I was like figuring that out in the Google Doc by like having a line of lyrics and then
a line underneath like one, two, three, four to find out where the beat lands on like what
syllable and that helps me realize like, because like I've had problems before when
I've tried to rap for anything.
It's like I write lyrics and I don't know how many syllables in a lyric and goes into
one bar or like four beats.
It was like, yo, it's diamond tiara and she's here to say I love being rich if you're not
you're gay or something like that.
What a legendary line.
Yeah, I'm studying my career with that one.
But yeah, the lyrics.
Oh, remember how Ben drew the gangster give and take pony for that legendary moment?
Wait, did I do a rap?
Yeah, I bet you that.
Remember drawing gangster give?
What the fuck?
Did I ever sing a rap at anyone?
That's impossible.
It can't be happened.
Once upon a time, I did draw gangster give and take.
It's true.
I think I still have that.
He's a blast of history.
God damn.
Speaking of music briefly, did any of you see the track, the song I posted on Twitter
that I was very embarrassed and scared about posting because I didn't feel like it was good enough
and then people said it's fine?
I have not seen it.
I'll get a link.
It'll be in the show notes.
How are we?
How are you feeling about it?
I feel like it was pretty good.
I wanted to make music for years and years.
I've made a few acoustic things before on a band camp and I've never been comfortable putting lyrics to them
or thinking about song structure.
All I know is guitar really well, so I just stick to that and I don't bother with anything else,
which means that if I ever try to play with other instruments, it's like I can't record them.
But now that I have an iPad and I've got garage band, it's a lot easier to just make a little beat that I can play along to.
So I made a song and I was like, this is it.
This is the time where I finally made an entire song that has more than just guitar in it.
Now all I need to add is lyrics and I couldn't think of any, so I mumbled a bunch
and I thought it was disgusting and disgraceful and the worst thing you could ever make
and I was going to kill myself and so I posted it.
You know what?
I didn't even know this for the longest time.
Apparently everybody knows this, but I'm a big fan of Elton John.
I think he's fucking sick and I love all his shit, but I just found out when there was talk about his documentary,
the movie based on it wasn't a real documentary, that he just doesn't write any of his own lyrics
and he just has a guy he's worked with forever.
I've always attributed everything good about Elton John's music, specifically to Elton John,
even though that's incredibly naive.
People work with tons of studio musicians and other collaborators, etc.
But I was always like, oh, kooky, wacko lyrics for what the fuck is leave on even about.
I don't know.
But some dude just writes all the lyrics because Elton John just hates doing it
and I'm just like, God, I need more people in my life who I can offload the things I don't specifically like doing to
and everybody should.
It's highly efficient.
It's a very effective method to surround yourself by people who can do things.
David Bowie was all about finding people who can do the things he can't
and working with them to make so many great songs and albums,
but it was always his thing because he was always organizing it.
But how much of anything is like a David Bowie?
It really just depends on who's doing the instrument part.
It's not like to take away anything from what he's done because they wouldn't have done it if he didn't ask them to.
By the way, that reminds me.
Michelle was watching some of Jojo Part 2.
He's the hussy for his own now.
He's the executive producer.
He's got the creative control.
He's the one making the final calls.
In a word, producer is the right word, I suppose.
But that reminds me.
Michelle was watching Jojo Part 2 and it reminded me that one of the plot points of Jojo Part 2
is there's the redstone of Aja, or Asia is it sometimes translated wrongly.
Everything in Jojo is a musical reference.
That one, the redstone of Aja, is a reference to the album Aja by Steely Dan.
That got me listening to Steely Dan music or something.
One of the YouTube recommended was just a documentary on the making of Aja featuring Steely Dan.
Steely Dan is actually a weird band that emerged out of this weird New York bubble
that these two guys, whose name I totally forget, merged into some other band.
All these things start weirdly.
They merged into this other band. They completely took it over from the inside.
As they evolved as a band, they just dropped many of the original members
and moved on to continually evolve the band.
They stopped touring for 20 years or something because they hated it.
They just wanted to make music.
They got to this album, Aja, and it was entirely made with just these two guys who produced it.
Every other person on the album was a set musician.
Some of them were part of the old band or whatever, but just totally unrelated.
It's just these two guys who just sat down.
They were English majors from Bard University or something.
They were big intellectual boys.
They just banished many of their bandmates and just chose exactly the people they needed
to get the exact bits and pieces of songs they wanted from these different musicians
with different talents.
On some of the albums, there's none of them even except the lead vocals
from the one lead vocal guy or something.
It was just fascinating and just such a radically different one.
When I make YouTube videos, I feel like such a weird urge to have everything be me.
I need everything I upload to be 100% Nate or it feels wrong somehow.
I'm currently getting over that working with an editor as I've done a couple of times in the past.
It's always felt weird, but I'm improving on it.
That's just obviously the right way to expand yourself and grow outward as an edit boy
or a fucking creator of any kind.
It was a very interesting watch and I'm learning a lot from these professional people out there.
Also, it was fascinating just to see how an album is made in the fucking back room or whatever.
So, a shout out to you, Davoo. Steely Dan. Pretty cool. Pretty cool band.
Last night, I recorded my end of the month Patreon Q&A podcast thing.
I had to go on a long tangent because Bevan asked about Slime and Punishment
and about what Christine Weston Chandler, creator of Sonichu,
the electric hedgehog Pokemon, had said.
So, I read out all of the things she had messaged me about like,
hey, this is what happens in your story and it was exhausting.
It was exhausting and frustrating and I got kind of fed up reading it.
It's all secrets, but I talked about it there.
Ben's hiding canon true Sonichu lore behind his paywall for people to go and discover.
How calculating.
I bring up Slime and Punishment because I've got a couple of people who are contributing to the finale.
Sixthin's going to make some music, I think.
Smyrg is going to make some cool visual things.
Shaddock, you know Shaddock? I don't know if he's a guy.
Names familiar.
Homestuck. He did some Homestuck animation.
He did arm retrieval animated way back.
Yeah, that's right.
Way back, I'd say, reminiscing on the good old days.
Wait, did he actually contribute to real Homestuck as well?
No, he does a lot of Homestuck fan stuff.
But he's really good, as I recall.
Yes.
Also contributing some things.
And now he's a big endless warhead.
Yeah, nice.
I'm going to be, I don't know, hopefully after Radcon, I'll be able to, I'll have all that and I'll be able to put it together.
I've been putting together shots, I've been compositing shots, I've been making some nice, some really nice little images.
Just putting it in Vegas and making things move around.
How does this look? How does that look?
Very, very excited to be working on that.
Kind of mad, kind of frustrated that Radcon has to be now when I would like to be finishing Slime and Punishment.
But it's okay.
Fair, fair.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'll do it.
I feel a little bit the same about the Lord of Ghost comic, because the day is leading up to it.
I'm like, I've got things I need to figure out and sort out and make and it's anxious, anxiousifying.
I can't really spend so many hours drawing, so I've just sort of stopped production on chapter four and I'll pick it up later.
Yep, I feel, yeah, I've got it, right now I've got to drop everything and make notes for my lectures and I guess write this fucking rap verse.
And I have to pack?
Hey, should I bring the Oculus Rift?
Oh God, I want to use it, but can we?
Will we have the opportunity or like the equipment necessary?
I mean, it needs to plug into a computer, right?
Yes.
I don't think any, maybe Digi will have a computer.
Did you guys see my legendary fucking absolutely slaying at, like whatever it is, like Beat Saber that I posted on Twitter?
I saw, yeah, no.
That fucking crab song, I want to, like that was on easy mode, I want to do it on fucking extreme and kick the shit out of that song.
I was fucking sick.
I haven't used the Oculus in a pretty long time.
I kind of, Econ was telling me I should get Beat Saber.
It does look like maybe it's fun.
Yes, it's fucking, I mean, I had a great time.
If you play songs you actually like, then it's fine.
Setting up, setting up, especially because my room is small, like setting up to use the Oculus is like an involved process every single time.
For Radcon, I'm willing to commit to it, like if we have the ability.
Oh no, I'm talking about just that in my house.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, I mean, if anyone thinks we can use the Oculus, I'll bring it.
Okay, let's just go for it.
I don't know if we can, like I'm bringing my laptop, but that's that kind of problem with Oculus.
If Digi is planning on bringing his like actual PC, then probably we could use it and I would bring it.
I mean, his PC will be like an hour away.
So even if he doesn't initially.
But I mean, he's gonna be driving his car.
It's like 20 minutes away, basically.
Yeah, I'm just saying like if he doesn't initially, we can say like, hey, we're gonna do a thing, bring your computer and he'll be like, okay.
I would love to.
I would love to stream some of that shit.
That would be fantastic.
And we could probably set up a green screen and I don't know, do all kinds of crazy stuff.
Digi's got at least his little green screen we could use, I'm sure.
Potential, good potential there.
Would love to do it.
Heck, heck yeah.
You'll find out in an hour and change probably when our live stream starts if we actually follow through with any of these plans at all.
We're gonna have 100% green screen us out of Radcon completely.
That's right.
When you're hearing this, we will be at, we will be in Virginia for Radcon.
Not me.
Oh my God, we've been recording roughly two hours.
So like, yeah, oh no, wait, we've been recording one hour.
So in one hour, give or take, if you started this the moment it released, that's when we'll be there.
I'm just, I'm keeping an eye on the clock.
This is amusing for me.
I'll be like, in the middle of the Pacific Atlantic ocean.
And I'll be, you know, I was thinking, if I can't think of anything, I have like, for the lecture, I have like 14 hours or whatever in the air that I could type away.
So I got time to make stuff.
That's true.
It'll, it'll be possible for me.
I wouldn't have, I wouldn't be able to like, look at anything on the internet because fucking airplanes suck.
The Wi-Fi sucks.
It does.
Even when they have Wi-Fi, even when it's free, it sucks.
And you guys know me, I've been very concerned about managing our time to make sure we get everything done.
I'm pretty happy with like, how much stuff is set up for each day.
It's given us plenty of room.
And like, let's not forget that like, the raw creative energy when you're at Radcon is really, is really kicked up a serious fun memory.
So good ideas may just fall out of the sky.
When I think now about like, what am I even going to do at Radcon?
It's like, I didn't have a plan last time.
We just get there and we figure it out and we're all having a good time and it just, it takes care of itself.
I mean, I was like hype for Radcon, but then I started watching some Radcon 3 content.
Some of like the behind the scenes stuff because I never really looked through all that until it was linked in the Radcon 4 discord a few days ago.
And I was like, oh, I'll take a gander at this.
And I got super fucking hype.
It all came rushing back and my dick was rock hard and I was ready.
I was like, fucking, I gotta go.
I gotta go right now.
Right now.
Here's a little, I mean, I don't know if people heard about this, but here's one of the things that you missed out.
Although you can still technically buy it on Gumroad if you want to play $11.11.
There's a link somewhere, I think, to the behind the scenes footage.
There's like one of the videos, someone just posted as like, this was fucking hype.
Like in the PJ thing was when Ben and I just busted out like the Judas song from Jesus Christ Superstar.
And then like the camera pans up and Digi from the window up above starts singing out as well.
And we all just fucking joined in.
That was, I mean, that was just a little thing, not planned, but I mean, great backer footage for just backer people.
That was right when we picked up Ben and we had to record the episode in like five minutes.
And so you guys spent 10 minutes singing Jesus Christ Superstar and we were late.
But it didn't matter because the internet was dead.
So we had to be like hours late anyway.
It took us like hours to get it working anyway, right?
I relived the whole week in these playlists and it was glorious.
Oh, that's a good shit.
I can't wait for the internet to fuck up again.
It's gonna be a good time.
I'm gonna bring my shitty camcorder because it's just easy to open and record.
Yeah, someone needs to.
So we can have more Dansoft toilet seat as a misadventures about that.
I gotta find my fucking GoPro.
Just imagine the horror if we get to this place and there's all soft toilet seats again.
Oh, no, it can't be.
We didn't ask the question.
That would have been a deal breaker.
Red soft garlic seats.
Oh, God, they'll team up.
They'll do a DBZ fusion.
It reminds me, I'm wondering, because I don't remember I checked this, how many bathrooms there are at this place.
Because it's not like a huge house like last time.
I hope there's at least three, but I guess we'll find out.
There's always the ocean if you need to go pissed.
So that's always there.
Group piss round two in the ocean, what?
Unironically, I mean, people suggested that and I think it's a fantastic idea.
What if we do it during sunset?
Oh, I was wondering, okay, with the group piss in the snow.
Why not?
Don't be a square?
Yeah.
Are you some sort of bitch?
What the fuck?
Because I wasn't getting piss coming from everyone else coalescing around us.
That's gross.
Oh, you're standing far enough apart.
It's fine.
Oh, my God.
We're literally going to be coming off the Radcon for gang bang.
So if you're going to get fucking uptight about this, I mean rethink your priorities, buddy.
Delicious.
No, no, I mean, some people suggested that.
I mean, I think there's, imagine it's sunset.
We're all glowing, the six of us, the gods of the beach.
I bought a little elastic, like black lace sort of like a mini skirt, like Tutu, I think.
Oh, gross.
To wear over whatever bathing suit I ended up getting.
Me and Munchie and some people, after the Bernie rally yesterday, we went to the garment
district to buy bathing suits.
And it turns out they don't carry them this time of year.
So I still have to find one.
Makes sense.
I'm going on Amazon.
Yeah, I ordered mine last night.
I'm really terrified.
Are you ordering it like to go to your house or are you ordering it to go to the Radcon?
I have Amazon Prime, so it'll get here like tomorrow.
Shit.
I ordered mine weeks ago.
It was wise.
That was wise.
I'm not worried.
I'll have plenty of stuff.
If I need to, I'll just go out in the town and find something.
If it does have some things in mind.
I'll just get a different size and I'll ship it to Digi's house instead and it'll be there
ready for my shame.
See, that's the thing.
I'm okay looking and completely terribly embarrassing, but I don't like having pee from other men
around me.
I don't like other men's pee, you know what I'm saying?
You ever get that feeling when you don't like other men's pee?
I can't relate, frankly.
I cannot relate to that.
I guess I'm in the minority here.
That's fine.
Indeed.
You know that image of the small white lady with all the black guys behind her in the
couch?
It's Gib in front, but all of us are peeing.
We are peeing facing the other direction.
Yeah.
There we go.
Beautiful.
That's the situation.
One thing I can't wait to do is play video games all day.
Yeah.
Did I already mention this before that Jade Moreau and I think a bunch of other people
were telling me that's...
I think a lot of people's favorite PCP video ever is the monkey game?
Ape Escape.
The Super Bowl.
No, the five hour full let's play of Ape Escape.
Right.
What video game consoles are we going to have there?
We know that.
We were talking about that.
We're obviously going to have a ton of switches.
I'm going to bring my switch.
I mean, if somebody else is bringing theirs, that's fine, but we got to have Smash.
You got to have Ultimate available.
Oh, god.
I don't...
It's a fucking bad video game.
I don't want to play them.
You don't want to play 1v1 against Monty again?
I'm going to have my PS3 with Scott Pilgrim versus The World The Game, the exclusive
game that you can't buy anymore.
That's so weird.
Was that because of copyright shit?
Yeah, because it was Universal or whatever.
It was famous for ruining video games.
They had their claws in Spyro and Crash.
For the PlayStation 2, they said, uh, Naughty Dog, Insomniac, sorry, fuck you, we're going
to get some real cheap pieces of shit to make the next bunch of games, which is why those
franchises fell into disrepair.
I had no idea.
Fascinating.
Universal Studios Productions, Crash Bandicoot 3, and then Crash Bandicoot 4 was okay.
If those guys ever get into Smash, I will definitely work that piece of lore into the
Crash-confirmed or Spyro-confirmed video.
Yeah, Universal is Universal-e terrible.
Universal bad.
Right.
Thanks for watching this Hippocrite review of Crash.
That was my big comeback.
Don and Don.
I don't know whether I should bring Hippo himself.
Do it.
Of course you should bring Hippo.
Of course you should bring him.
I don't know because he's dealing with something in the old endless mud.
Well, okay.
I mean, if he's busy, fair enough.
I certainly want to bring action to Giraffe.
He's ready to travel.
He's ready to go.
Hippo could do like another animal cast together.
Remember that?
They should.
Of course.
Radcon 2 is such a long time ago.
Radcon 1, I don't even remember.
Radcon 2 three years ago, Radcon 1 about three and a half years ago.
Three years ago and a few months.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
We really cranked him out back then.
We sure did.
Wasn't Radcon 1 basically just like an accident?
Like we didn't mean to do it.
It just kind of turned out that way.
No, no, no.
We decided to meet up.
Because we knew that we didn't want to go to Bronycon anymore.
So we just decided to meet up.
Like go to Digi's house.
Was Radcon 1 like right when me and Davoo moved into Digi's house?
I believe it was.
That was like the impetus for it.
Right.
I wasn't at Radcon 1.
You weren't?
I was not at Radcon 1.
What?
God, I don't remember that at all.
Okay.
It was a long time ago.
I know.
It was not a full cast.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Radcon 2 introduced Tom, Jeff and Munchy.
And Munchy.
Munchy wasn't there.
Yeah.
And that was the second one was the year we did the lectures.
So what even happened in the first one?
Nothing.
You weren't there either, Gid?
I'm pretty sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
You were there.
Well, Ben's lecture was from Radcon 1.
That's probably the biggest thing.
Other than that, I don't remember anything.
That was the only lecture at the time, right?
Nobody else.
Because like Digi had said like Ben, please do a lecture.
And you were like, it will do.
Yeah.
Strange.
It was a good idea.
It worked out.
And then Radcon 2.
What's the views that sit in that?
Is it 1.1 million yet?
1.2?
How many views?
Yeah.
I'm just curious.
It's just over a million.
Okay.
Well, hey, nonetheless, don't let your memes be dreams, kids.
Definitely not.
Bad views.
Although, although if you count the ones on the 360 degree classroom, that's another
100K.
There you go.
Yeah.
Hey, by the way, what was the meme I said before?
Was it hashtag just fucking?
Was that the one?
Yeah.
Just fucking.
Okay.
Don't want to let that one slip away.
Hey, should I bring all my like Copic markers and stuff?
Should I bring like art supplies?
That depends on what you and the draw boys want to do, which I am not a member of.
That's cabal.
So I have no, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm bringing my iPad, obviously.
I mean, yeah, I could bring, I have so many fucking Copics that I never use.
I like having them.
Bring them, dude.
Additionally enough, maybe, maybe we could do something with, I don't know.
I'll toss them in my duffel.
I need a bag.
I do not have a bag.
I need to like borrow or steal a duffel bag from someone.
Lol.
I'm looking at the first video in the Radcon 2016 playlist, the arrival of Ben St.
Top comment.
This is like watching the Avengers.
The Avengers assemble.
It's exactly like that.
Well, it's like watching like the Avengers of like, you know, like baby Avengers or
like baby.
Like muppet babies.
Yeah, like muppet babies.
Yeah.
It's like the Muppet baby version.
Like it's them, but they're babies at the time.
And they got, I'm looking at the playlist.
It's like, we've got the, the PCP live 360 camera.
We've got Japanese.
Right.
We've got Japanese niggers, a bunch of vlogs.
Disavow.
A few Digi spin the crunchy roulette with people.
And then the, the 20 man Royal Rumble.
And yeah, the lecture body cast.
That's it.
Oh, and a bunch of Let's Plays.
That was, yeah.
Humble beginnings.
I mean, nothing we do now is so much more complicated.
We just do more and we like try to generate more footage, like cause it's a Kickstarter
and stuff now.
Yeah.
So it's just like amped up, but it's pretty much the same shit.
Oh, very exciting.
Very high.
My favorite comment is still, imagine paying these guys $34,000 to go on.
I can't.
Thanks buddy.
I can't believe it.
Everyone in real life I talked to about Radcon is thoroughly confused.
Yeah.
It's very funny.
Everyone, everybody, everybody trying to be a badass until they say that you earned $34,000
and then they start sucking your dick.
Wait, you made how much money?
On a, on a what?
On a what exactly?
I was talking to, I was, I was talking to our mom, Ben, about what a disappointment
you are to the family.
Yeah.
And after we exhausted that topic over a few hours.
Funny, I was doing the same thing about you.
Fascinate.
She's playing both sides against them.
She's a, she's a warren.
A tactician.
She's pulling a warren.
Damn, damn mom.
Really living up to the Karen ideal.
I know.
She's like, like, like she's not really repping her people very well.
She's.
No.
The Native Americans that is.
She's letting them down.
What was I saying?
Oh, right.
I was just, I was talking to him.
I was just like, hey mom, you know that Radcon thing we do?
And she's like, oh yeah, that's a few of your friends are playing little games together.
Yeah.
I talked to mom and dad reason and I told them like, yeah, that Radcon thing raised like
$34,000.
Yeah.
Dad just, dad was just like, mm, very good.
Very good.
Yeah.
God damn it, dad.
Be impressed.
You piece of shit.
He was impressed and I was fine with it.
I was like, yes.
It is very good.
I don't know.
I agree.
I would talk to first.
I mean, one of us talked to him first because maybe they had already heard because like,
when I talked to mom, I just said like, hey mom, guess, guess how much we made.
And I was like considering the fact that we got like $9,000 last time, guess how much.
And she was like, mm, $12,000.
And I was like $34,000 and she did her typical get out.
Get out.
Yeah.
It's a classic mom.
Oh, we need, we need, we need a mom get out t-shirt now.
Get out of here.
Remember Grace's brief cameo?
We could get, we get more family cameos.
The fam cam.
Meos.
Oh yeah.
Good.
You're a dog and I'm sick of it.
What a strange, what a strange legacy.
Yeah.
That's true.
Hey.
Yeah.
I've, right.
Here's, here's a small like thing.
I've been going back to, to listen to destiny lectures.
Notable ones.
Obviously the John Trum one, which was where I first heard of it.
You mean the streams?
The streams.
Sorry.
Loll lectures.
He gives lectures every day.
Big, big, big academic.
That guy.
Yeah.
The first time I saw destiny, he was like a fucking stupid, annoying piece of shit.
And I don't like him.
But going back with my knowledge of like, huh, you know, some ideas are okay.
Some ideas that are previously thought.
Another good t-shirt.
Yeah, some ideas are okay.
Yeah.
Oh man.
I kind of want to make that one for real.
Holy shit.
So I go back and I'm like, maybe I had the wrong idea about destiny because I listened
to this John Trum thing.
And I was like, okay, John Trum is saying white nationalist talking points.
I don't think he's an actual racist, but he is saying those things that is very silly.
Don't listen to Sargon, John.
You're not, don't do it.
Stop doing it.
Are you tacitly implying that just Sargon just is a white Nash?
It means is that we try to sneak in there?
Because I think you'll have a difficult time actually making that point.
He's a little bit of a white.
I saw another stream with destiny and Sargon and there's talking points there that like
lead in a racist direction.
Sargon denies it, of course, because it's like.
No, I'm not letting you get away with this.
You say one, like you make one point that has anything to do and you're just like, oh,
they're like on the pipeline now.
You just imply a little point.
And you just imply a little bit that maybe we should keep America white and suddenly
everyone's calling you a white nationalist.
Now, see, you're twisting that the way you want to.
I'm not saying that any different way.
Like the pipeline isn't necessarily you are like rotten to the core and you're like an
evil person.
White nationalist is not a thing that is, you know, it's not like a slur in the same
way.
It's just a way of thinking, a framework of thinking.
Like to say that Sargon might be a white nationalist is not to say, don't trust anything
he says.
Everything he says is stupid.
That is not what I'm saying.
And it's not what a lot of people are saying.
But the thing that I came across, came away with with listening to these destiny lectures
and, you know, there's one with Lauren Southern and he went on the kill stream and stuff.
And I get the sense that, I mean, I think he said at one point that he doesn't do the
arguing to make people understand.
He just likes the arguing.
The people on the left really are annoyed that he takes the leftist points, but he doesn't
present it in a way that the right can reasonably like understand without getting really annoyed
because he is annoying.
He has an annoying personality and is an abrasive guy.
So like he does all these things and he's not trying to be smarter than everyone else.
But he is sort of an edgy lolster and he likes it when they get triggered and upset about
talking points and he likes calling them an idiot in, you know, calling them idiots for
the viewpoints they have.
And they get really riled up because it's a natural reaction to being called an idiot.
But it's, I think, it's like as well as the Digi lecture, Digi stream, what Digi was on.
Like I could see where Digi was coming from, but the reason that there was a big divide
in like understanding between Destiny and why Destiny thought Digi was a complete idiot
was because Digi was using words wrong.
As he is known to do, he has like an idea of what a word means.
Destiny is like, what do you mean?
I don't understand.
Please explain.
I'll reframe your argument and you'll tell me if it's right.
And Digi is like, you're reframing my argument.
There's lots of, it's a little infuriating when somebody doesn't listen to Destiny,
but I can see why they don't because Destiny is hard to listen to if you're predisposed
to dislike the things he says or the positions he holds.
So it's like, it's very entertaining when you agree with him, but when you don't, it's
so aggravating.
I mean, it's kind of encapsulated in that meme of like, oh no, the worst guy you know
just made a really good point, which I'm not saying anyone always makes a really good point.
But it's real hard to just be like, can't, ooh, Destiny, you really have a concrete reason
for why like 100% of children should be aborted.
I can't refute it, but I just hate you.
So I disagree.
I lost a lot of respect in particular for Mr. Medeker and Dick Masterson hearing them
debate Destiny and just hearing their complete self-assurance that they are correct and that
this guy they're talking to can't possibly be making any good points, even though he is
the big, big Destiny on them.
The thing that really rolls me up is like, a lot of time where, you know, Destiny will
start making a rebuttal to their statement and they will cut him off and saying, you're
just a piece of shit, like some sort of, like they get riled up by the way he starts his,
like he brings up a hypothetical and they're like, yeah, but what about like an exception
to that hypothetical and they don't accept the hypothetical scenario in order to start
the discussion about it.
So he just gets cut off over and over again.
And they think that because he's trying so desperately to push forward this hypothetical
so that they could start that he's being hysterical and he's, you know, he's a crazy
leftist and he doesn't listen.
And it's so obvious that they aren't listening to him.
And it's just, there's so many points like that.
It's like, you know, Destiny isn't definitely not like everyone's cup of tea to listen to,
but I definitely feel like there's worth, it's worth like trying to listen to him unemotionally
to see what he's actually saying.
I fell down the Destiny hole.
I listened to a bunch, for a while I was listening to all his shit.
Lately, lately he's been really annoying.
Hearing him make like a totally like non-emotional argument for various like progressive things
that I had never really heard anyone make like an intellectual appeal to before in such like a
straightforward way was really good.
He does it for like immigration.
He does it for like trans identities.
He does it for, you know, stuff.
He has an approach that I think a lot of people on the right don't expect some fucking SJW to use.
It's great.
I love it.
I love him, even though he's a big fucking asshole and I hate him.
The debate he had with Sargon, they went over a lot of topics, but what I really came away with
is not that Sargon is like, you know, obviously nobody thinks of themselves as evil or racist.
And there are moments where Sargon is getting to a point where he's like almost agreeing with Destiny.
Like the Destiny's talking point, Sargon is like, oh, that's a reasonable, like I can see you have a reasonable opinion there.
You're just contradicting the other statements you're making, which are, you know, things that you say in your videos,
but the things you're saying here when under scrutiny, they seem more reasonable.
And Destiny's trying so hard to get him to understand that he has contradicted himself and this thing that he actually believes is more reasonable
than the talking points he makes in his videos that are more right-leaning sounding.
And it's like, please, please listen.
Please listen, Sargon.
You're not as bad as you make yourself out to be.
You kind of make yourself out to be worse than you are because you're kind of stupid and you don't listen.
And it's like, I feel like that's such a common thing.
Like nobody, like Dick Masterson isn't a fucking criminal or an evil person.
Neither is Sargon, neither is Jontro, neither is anyone who's ever been considered on the far right.
The people who attack people on the right for their opinions that they have,
unless they're out and out racists who are like saying it or like, you know, heavily, heavily, heavily implied racists,
if they're just a pundit, they're usually normal people who have like white people who feel like their whiteness is being attacked
and they didn't do anything and this isn't fair.
And so they just gravitate towards these talking points.
They're not bad people, but it's just, it's so difficult to watch a Destiny stream and see them kind of be
okay, but still double down on the thing that is like leading down, not exactly leading down always,
but like tends towards a path of getting rid of brown people sometimes.
They double down on the bad part, yeah.
Because like, I don't know, like with Jontro in particular, you could see it.
It's like, this is just a thing he's assumed, he's just uncritically assumed.
And like, he can't really articulate why he thinks it, but he doesn't like Ed question.
Like nobody likes being called a racist.
So he just kind of doubles down on it, yeah.
It's nobody likes being called a racist or implied that they could be a racist or have like, you know, male privilege, white privilege or any of that stuff.
And so they get very defensive and it's not the worst thing in the world.
It's not the worst thing in the world to be like having, like you can change.
It's just, I don't know.
People on that mindset, it would be so easy to just be like, oh, did I say something that was kind of racist?
Whoops, I guess I didn't think about it and realize that it's kind of a racist thing to say.
Thanks for pointing out to me the logical conclusions of this belief that I held so I can reevaluate it.
The issue with this is just that I feel like you guys are going to call something like, you know what, I think we should have less immigration.
Is that racist? I mean, you probably would say it is, but it's not.
No, that's not in and of itself.
Oh, there you go. Why do you straw man me like that, Nate?
No, but like I could see why people...
You know that you'd say that.
You're wrong. You're literally wrong.
Why is Sargon racist then? Why is Sargon racist?
He's not racist.
Is it because he like notices that like with Middle Eastern immigration, like rape rates have gone up, is that why he's racist?
The thing with those conversations is that they haven't, like the data proof...
He doesn't back up his statements with facts.
That's, yeah.
It's the thing that doesn't...
I mean, that's not even my position, but that's where I understand his position to be.
Exactly, like when it comes down to facts, like it's not that I have a latent racism and so I want to get rid of immigrants.
I would like it if they didn't commit crimes, but it turns out that generally it's not actually as bad as, you know, certain media outlets make you believe it is.
And if you see...
You know, the whole thing like Jon Trum thinking that rich blacks commit more crime than poor whites.
That was some data that he got from somewhere and he believed it because he didn't...
Because he was already thinking social justice and the left hate me because I'm worried about immigration.
It's okay to be worried about immigration.
You know, it's not like immigration is perfect.
It's definitely a lot of problems with it, but like the issue is always about nuance and a lot of the time the nuance lies...
You know, it's very obvious when somebody has not delved into the nuance to come away with like a real opinion on the matter.
They just have heard a thing and they believe that and so they will go along with their life believing these things without really delving into it.
And I can't say that I'm like a...
I know about immigration in America any more than, you know, just a few videos I've seen, but like it's interesting in these debates and scenarios where destiny is so into the facts and the logic.
And you know, it just makes me think like, damn, maybe I don't fucking know anything.
Maybe I should really think before I speak.
You know, not to discredit destiny or anybody else, he could be 100% right.
The reason I get suspicious of people who, I mean to you, like destiny, oh he's so obviously right.
There are such strong incentives to find the data point that works for you and then cease your investigation at that point.
I feel like that operates in a lot of these circles and then they're just, you know, you find the convenient answer that justifies your belief and then you just...
I mean, you could say that about anyone.
Absolutely true.
You could point to any person arguing anything and saying like, oh, they're only using the evidence that agrees with them.
That is exactly why Ben, I feel so uncomfortable making any real world points ever and I'm only comfortable debating like philosophical things I think are kind of correct or stuff like that.
Well, sure, but at the end of the day, you're going to argue about facts.
You have to fall back on data and then it's become like, okay, who's got the better and more compelling data?
Perfectly reasonable, perfectly reasonable when that is the debate.
To say Saragon is the worst guy ever just because he's kind of stupid and like it's not fair on him.
At the same time, it's fine to make fun of people.
So like there's many ways to do this.
It's not like destiny is right and everyone who he debates it is always like guaranteed destroyed.
Like I don't agree that like Digi didn't have a point when he debated him.
It was just that his point was a different type of thing.
Like he was talking about arguments as in the way human beings talk to one another and destiny was talking about debate as a form of like official recognized.
This is how we come to consensus because conclusions are through debate and Digi was like, I mean, if you really listen to that, you can see Digi's point.
And you can see Dick Masterson point that Digi was trying to explain.
But you can also see the destiny is like arguing something else and he just doesn't care.
That's my recollection.
The thing that Digi was going for was like so unimportant to him that it just became a big like shouting match.
I watched them. I saw the I saw destiny call into Vosh right to talk about I won't go into the whole like background of it.
But they were they got into an argument and Vosh was like, dude, destiny.
I thought you were supposed to be an SJW and destiny was like, dude, I'm the only SJW left because all you people all you lefties abandoned intersectionality for class consciousness.
And it's like, damn, what what a thing to say. What a debate to be having.
And I'm like, you know, even though I'm a more Vosh guy than a destiny guy now, I generally agree with Vosh more.
But like, this is good. This is good that like these two guys, these are both one way.
They're both probably left of center kind of and they're having a debate and the argument comes down to, you know, intersectionality versus class consciousness,
which is the right approach, which is the right approach to righting the wrongs of the world and making things better.
And I just reflected on someone a right leaning person would be in here trying to argue that no,
both of these things are bad and making the world better in any way is wrong and foolish.
And I thought, boy, I sure do hate the other side of the aisle with all my heart.
The end. That's all I have to say.
And that is why you will fail to convert them, Ben.
They'll never be converted because they're bad on the inside.
See, this is the difference between them and me.
I'm trying so hard to be like the bridge builder.
I want that more than anything.
One method is more effective than the other.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, Ben just enjoys sitting in his toolbox.
They had a whole life.
They have their whole life to figure out what was right and good and decide on it and they failed.
And so now it's time to employ the guillotines.
Their number is up.
You know, they did not pass the test.
We've decided to make a better society.
Well, they should.
I mean, you know, good ideas.
I think I do think good ideas should win.
Yeah, that's true.
Okay.
Hot take, I know.
Indeed.
All right.
Nate, how many voicemails do we have?
Because we're at an hour and a half right now and far be it from us to deny anyone listening to this as soon as it comes out.
The live stream that's coming up in a in a mere half an hour their time.
Well, okay, that's only when we can get in.
It's going to take some amount of minutes, even if we rush to set up like streaming equipment.
So I wouldn't say it's going to start exactly then.
Mathematically, I think it can't be done.
I mean, few of us could just like make sure that we start streaming as soon as the episode is like out for the amount of time that the length of the episode is.
We probably shouldn't start immediately.
Because like most people aren't going to click play and play it all the way through the moment it comes out.
Well, I mean, I didn't even know until now if anyone was even interested in starting like immediately or not.
I mean, it's on the schedule.
I'm definitely going to be tweeting a storm with pictures of like us fucking around.
Indeed.
Well, of course, of course.
The content will flow like wine.
It'll be great.
Although Gib will not be there until later that night.
And Munchy not till the next morning due to their schedule and whatnot.
But no matter.
No matter.
The answer to your question, Tom, is that there are exactly three voicemails.
Oh, we're good.
We're voicemails.
So we'll not do much to delay things.
We can keep talking forever.
Or I mean, I have them right here.
I'm ready to get to them.
I don't know.
Let's do it.
Do we have anything else to go over?
I feel like it's a clean time to transition.
So let's just do it.
All right.
So here we go.
First voicemail.
This one is from, let me see.
Oh, and of course, speak pipe link down below.
Leave your voicemails.
Although I guess it's fair to say the next PCP you see will be a live stream.
So we probably won't be doing voicemails for that one.
That's true.
Maybe we'll do some sort of live, you know, ask PCP thing on Twitter that we're scrolling
and reading questions.
We'll take Superchats.
I don't know.
Superchats are probably the right way to do it.
Yeah.
Maybe one of us can watch this.
So I mean, if you do this next time there's a recorded PCP, we'll probably do it for that.
And so, okay, now you're aware.
But the link to the speak pipe, speak pipe is down below.
Use it at your leisure.
All right.
The first voicemail here is from, I'll die, petitions to give the PCP more money.
I'm excited to hear this one.
Let's see what he has to say.
Okay, go.
Listen, guys, I'm going through a crisis.
Vic and Hope is the only thing that keeps me sane.
So I was ecstatic to see that we finally got a new episode after like months on like Sonic
the Hedgehog around when the movie came out.
And in that episode, Vic was saying that there has been a lot of content.
It's just that he wants to edit footage of like they've tripped to Japan over it.
So that way, you know, we can like see what's going on when they're talking about it, which
sounds really cool.
And I'd love it.
But the problem is just that he's busy and he doesn't have the time to do that.
So like, here's the new strategy that he's going to Rack Han For, but he's just going
to be the cameraman.
That's no good.
He needs to edit.
He needs to make a new Kickstarter to hire another cameraman to take Vic's job.
He'll still get paid as the cameraman.
It's just that he'll edit his show while this other fucking piece of shit does his job
for him.
So I don't have to go insane not listening to Vic and Hope.
Thank you.
I think we'll all be happy with the solution.
Make sense.
If the money comes, we can make it happen.
This seems like less of us getting money and more of this camera guy getting money and
I'm suddenly less interested.
I thought the idea was that we do the Kickstarter and we then exempt Victor from the need to
do that.
And like, obviously we got to make his payback ourselves and then we give some lesser amount
of money to whoever's doing the job in his place, I guess.
Too complicated.
Just go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
That's the only place to send your money in a reliable and trustworthy way.
Alright, enough of that bullshit.
Vic and Hope, that's not even PCP affiliated technically.
Well maybe it is.
I guess technically it is.
Second cousin to PCP.
Remember the fucking Tony Hawk endless Jess Vic blue glow.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
There you go.
So Vic's officially, yeah.
First extended universe content man, aside from being the brother of the Digi.
Indeed.
Okay, here's a voicemail that's simply called, they killed me because I knew too much.
Okay, go.
PCP, I need you guys to wish me luck.
The coronavirus has entered my state.
Before I die, I just need to tell you guys, I have information that will indict Hillary
Well, the coronavirus killed his microphone.
Microphone started coughing and I couldn't record anymore.
Or the odds you think.
It's a really funny like instant death.
He didn't even sound bad.
It was like a Sopranos ending moment there.
His whole state just like dissolved.
It was like, he just got fucking Avenger Infinity Ward.
What are the odds that Hillary Clinton personally, that was yes, that was infinity war.
What are the odds that they arranged the coronavirus, the Clintons to Epstein, the decrepit old men
that are currently on top of the ticket to make room for a virile young up and coming
Sprout like Hillary.
A hundred percent?
Two hundred percent?
So like Hillary paid China to develop the coronavirus and spread it around the world
just so that everyone else except her will be killed.
This is my, yes.
Correct.
She killed off her competition because you know she's starting a podcast.
Hillary Clinton is starting.
She calls it an audio program and she says that her inspirations include Howard Stern.
So she's going to run a Howard Stern style audio program.
Oh my God, imagine Hillary working the sound board the way I do.
Fart with reverb.
26 will commence again.
All the highlights, all the highlights.
Very excited for that.
Hillary will be tuning in.
She's going to need promotion and I think the PCP is the place to get it.
We should have coronavirus on the PCP and ask it.
Corona Chan.
Why?
Give us a call.
Corona Chan's definitely going to come to Raycon 4.
I can't wait.
I'm very excited for that.
It's going to be a blast, a vomit and shit out of every orifice.
Looking forward to that.
All right, we've got one more.
All right, so there's an image that goes along with this one.
So check the description.
I'm posting it in the thing down there.
Behold this image.
And while you're looking at that, listen to this PCP voicemail from our friendly editor,
Eleazar.
And let's hear what he has to say and go.
Hey, Eleazar here.
So the other day I was walking, wasting my PCP money on beaches and beaches.
And suddenly I found this.
And at first I was very confused.
Like PCP, what, what.
Then I read the text at the bottom.
And I was really happy because if you translate it from Virgin Spanish to chat English,
it says, integral attention to children and adolescent with disability.
I didn't know PCP HQ was real.
Anyways, congratulations, guys.
In Argentina for presents.
Like really great, really great.
Thank you.
So yeah, bye bye.
Thanks Eleazar.
Lovely to hear from you, my boy.
We're cultivating our low IQ demographic.
This is the main, we think we have most potential in the low IQ circles.
We are a big, big fan base in South Carolina.
Everybody there disagrees with our policies, hates us personally, but votes for us anyway.
They just, they just, because you know, we're just, it's just the thing.
They vote for us to be podcast of the year.
Yeah.
They're going to vote for us to defeat Hillary Clinton in the podcast elections.
The podcast.
The podcast, got to think of a word.
PC, I don't, I can't think of it.
Proletariat.
PCPOTUS.
Yeah.
PC, put them up.
PC, put them up and you raise your dukes and punch and there you go.
That's what's going to be.
That sucks.
This sucks.
Delete the next one.
That was just shit, dude.
Hashtag just fucking everybody.
Let's skip back to that, because that was the last voicemail.
Some ideas were okay.
Thank you, Eleazar.
Some ideas are okay.
Some ideas were okay.
Like leaving a voicemail with an image attached.
Thanks, Eleazar, for that.
Hey, hey, if you want to get your fucking voicemail played when we come back with a recorded episode
episode that'll be edited and whatnot, click the speak pipe, speak pipe link down below.
I'm expecting an influx of rad con shit when you hear this and all kinds of good stuff
is happening.
So I guess that'll be that.
End of episode, scene, curtain falls, transition.
Clear your schedule for the rest of the day because it's time for live content from rad
con 4 all night long.
I am pretty stoked.
You'll see us in the flesh very soon everybody.
All our goddamn Twitter's, there's gonna be updates going on all of those.
Follow Twitter, follow on Instagram, follow on Byte, follow on TikTok, follow on LinkedIn,
get followed everywhere.
We should make an epic TikTok at radcon that's the girl going, one of our anime girl OCs
from the OVA that's going like, are you masturbating to porn?
Oh no, are you masturbating alone?
And then you turn the camera around and it's like, no, I'm with my boys.
We should do that.
That's a good TikTok.
All right, radcon starting immediately.
Thanks for everybody who donated.
So we don't.
Who's their shirt making it happen?
And it's gonna be a great time.
For the fucking, if you're the goddamn PTA, be active in that Discord because who knows
when you'll be called upon to perform services to tell us what to do or vote on things.
It could be any time.
We make no promises for when things will happen.
We'll just probably throw fucking vote tallies, fucking, what are those voting websites again?
The Lincoln, whatever, you know what I'm talking about, voting for things and straw
polls.
That's what I'm thinking about.
Any time who knows what's going to happen or voting or all the super chats, all kinds
of things are happening.
Fuck you.
But if you want to hear, hey, if you missed the, if you missed the boat on the PCP radcon
behind the scenes, radcon for behind the scenes stuff, not all is lost because me, Gib and
Tom did a bonus episode that just came out a few days ago that covers a bunch of the
behind the scenes stuff that you might not even hear anywhere else in our planning and
the trials and tribulations of getting it stoked.
Hey, I'm on it too.
I have more content.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I'm on it too.
With this cameo.
That's true.
I'm a big, I have a big, yeah, yeah.
It's, I'm the, you know, my time on the episode is low, but I would say I'm the emotional
core of the bonus episode.
It's like the Jesus, you know?
It's like Jesus.
He doesn't show up often in your life, but when he does, notable.
It's a big impact.
Notable.
All right.
That being said, go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators, pledge five dollars to
get 35 total bonus episodes, including that one.
Monsters twos in there.
Fuck in monsters.
One.
Wait, no, that was a normal episode.
It's a bunch of ASMR, just a legendary batch of episodes there and $1 and you're in the
main discord, which I would recommend you be because this is going to be an active fucking
week of PCP stuff going on and you're going to want to be there for now is the time.
If you feel guilty that you miss the Kickstarter, you're like, God, I really wish I could have
contributed somehow to this epic level production.
Get in the patron, just do it.
Every dollar helps.
That's right.
And I guess that's it.
We'll see you in paradise at radcon4 and follow the Twitter at TPCrastinators.
That'll definitely be the central hub for like news and updates and like if things happen,
like we have to move the venue of the, like of the meetup because it's like raining out
or something.
Follow that.
Important stuff's all going to be there.
All right.
There you go.
We'll see you soon, everybody.
Fuck yeah.
Here we go.
See you in like a few minutes when we're streaming live, everybody.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
All right.
Resync.
I'm going to count of three.
Here we go.
Count of three.
One, two, three.
Sink.
One more time.
One, two, three.
Sink.
All right.
Done.
Heck yeah, dudes.
Oh God.
I got a fucking pack and shit.
I am skewed.
I don't want to fly.
I hate flying.
Okay.
We can fucking die together when the pilot catches coronavirus and I'm going to give myself
the coronavirus and then I'm going to go to fucking Milwaukee for the national convention
and then if they don't give Bernie the num, I'm going to detonate myself and splatter
my guts inside the state house and give it to all of them.
That's what's up.
That's what's happening.
Ellie is arped.
Don't fucking let the viewers know that I said that I'm going to do political violence.
I'm still recording.
Lamal.