This one goes out to my mortal deity, Sans the Skeleton, my favorite ghetto spiritualist and sewer priest, Endless Jess, and my dad. Please forgive me, sensei.
Just sitting here on my bed, cleaning out my botflies, and making them dead. It doesn't matter though, they'll be back on the attack in like three fucking seconds.
Cause I have botflies over my house, and in my bed, and in my head, and in my brain, and my pants are fiddle with them. I really like Ulysses as Grant.
Killed the blacks and the gays, not cause they're bad, and they're okay. I just want to make everyone skeletons like my god Sans. That's my mission, you see.
Haha, alright, bitch. Gonna spread over to my Mexicans house, friend's house, and stuff burritos down my lemon pipe. Real spicy too. Gonna torture my dick daily and nightly. Whoops, oh fuck.
Disneyland police guard people are here, and they found my bathroom rap studio. Oh god, when I get nervous, I shit them on soon. Relicosa tattoo is my favorite video game.
I have a tattoo of Sans the Skeleton on my actual literal butthole. Like, directly on it, bruh.
She's like, oh fuck, they're trying to forcibly rape me, am I rape me? I mean, I mean, we're dude, they're sorry, man.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the Procrastinator's podcast.
It's back, and it's lit, and it's undog shit fire on your doorstep, here we are, I am the best guy ever, that's who I am, and I'm joined by Hippo crit.
Hello.
And Endless Jess.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
And Digi bro, I'm still gay and still dead and then saint I'm these farce from the mic and
Today we have a
Unbelievable honour to have this special guest with us
Florian Hymsel co-creator of binding of Isaac what's up, dude, oh hey guys. Oh man. What a surprise
you must be a big what are you doing here how did you get here on to our
channel oh no I was the last in introduction oh no that's cuz you're
the most important of course so so we noticed recently that you commented on
the binding of Isaac video from rad con two that was put up and you were just
like hey guys check out my game looking pretty good on this channel and then we
just started talking and now you're here and it's a it's fucking rad dude it's
great yeah um if I may I just like to ask sir Hemsel how how how did you find
the PCP how did you get them how did how did this come to pass I've been
watching for a while it's quite my favorite podcast actually
oh why that was my first question too well he doesn't have to answer that if
he doesn't want to actually yes it's which one of us did you find first and
that's probably did you bro actually cuz I watch the sword art sucks and then I
watched some more but then I forgot about did she and then later I discovered
chess and I I watched all of that and it was brilliant yes your secrets are not
safe they're all exposed and I found all of the rest and and so I was I was it's
it's well I think I was surprised just because I mean you know I I'm familiar
with your work and you've you've been involved in like you know the fucking
highly successful binding of Isaac so to me I mean you're like a you're like a
you're like a seasoned industry industry fucking professional guy and so like for
you to be watching our our our rinky-dink little shit you know us all like us all
struggling barely barely known artists over here you know we're fine the thought
of anyone watching my channel of anyone being a fan of me is this the
it's my worst nightmare really one of the one day I'm gonna go back in time and
I'm gonna erase my channel from the picture like Marty McFly that's my goal
as a youtuber that we all look forward to that day but so our topic in general is
gonna be indie games but really it's just an excuse to talk about Florian and
his work and I'm really curious about his experience in the industry because
he's very much an indie guy and he's made a bunch of cool shit over the years I
don't know about you guys but as soon as I heard he was gonna be on I I move
my ass straight on over to comics games dot com and checked out all the shit he's
made over the years and I was pretty great embedded right on the website is
Binding of Isaac and you can just fucking play for free fuck paying for it right
but the demo version right yeah that's probably one of the reasons I got so
successful is because there's a free demo that everyone can play on the
internet on the new grounds I didn't play the demo on new grounds before I
ever yeah I played the demo on new grounds I honestly didn't like the demo
because it was pretty limited but then like when I saw the real game and I saw
all the shit that's like in it I all the literal shit that's it you know I was
I was really big into into roguelikes at the time and like I was playing I was
deep deep in the well of dungeon crawl stone soup at that time of my life was
that before you played Isaac I thought it was afterward oh no I definitely was I
was I was playing stone before I found Isaac but yeah and I saw Isaac and so I
had to fucking jump on it yes and well let's just go and by the way I should
I should just say that I have definitely played probably hundreds of hours of
Isaac I feel safe and saying that about myself too were you saying give I was
just gonna say like I think everyone here has played Binding of Isaac at least
the first one I never really got into it so I won't really have like you know
questions about it but I do understand it's pretty great like I've seen people
have a lot of fun with it and I do like roguelikes in general it's just like one
of the biggest things about it is that I like watching people play it wanted
playing it myself almost because I can see them get trolled by my game and it's
glorious yeah dude I was watching on I was watching on your channel which
game squid on YouTube and I was watching a game you were doing with some guy I
don't know a friend of yours who was in a couple of the videos and he did this
this amazing run as it wasn't like it was a new character I had never seen
before because I haven't kept up with every single update but it's like the
last one you unlock it's like this weird devil angel baby thing and like just get
all the fucking power-ups he got I mean it was such an unbelievable beast just
demolishing that game completely it's so satisfying I had played a bunch of
rounds just to get myself back into it so I'd remember what playing the fucking
game was like and I fucked up real bad but it's so glorious to watch people get
those like runaway successful runs and he got all the way to like this new area
called the void that I'd never seen before and beat this guy I don't know
some big white motherfucker who was like the new final double triple boss
oh it's so great I love that kind of shit that's funny why is it such a great
game yeah I I'd never heard of the void either I was playing it back in back in
back in the rat like the early wrath of the lamb yeah that's the very newest DLC
they made for after birth rebirth after birth plus it is called and it has that
stuff in it so that's right yeah so I let me let me let me complain let me
complain about the new about the remakes about about rebirth oh and this was a
big reason we wanted Ben here so we could complain about the new one that
flooring is not involved with just talk about how much he loves the original well
too well I do I want to hear about it I do fucking love the original I mean I
mean game I have played a little bit of rebirth and like gameplay wise it seems
pretty much the same which is fine you know there's a lot more shit in there
which is always cool but like all right there's a bunch of things that really
pissed me off which is the the pixel aesthetic I don't get I don't get why
it was done I really liked you know Edmunds original like hand-drawn wobbly
thing I thought it fit the game the tone of the game way better and the the
fucking cutscenes look like ass in the new look like ass they look like they
look like ass and not even in a way they make sense like not only do they look
worse than the original cutscenes in the original version they also they look
worse in a way that fits the new visual style even less yeah it's it's it's
really dumb they feel a very outsourced to me like they feel separate from the
rest of the game almost because they're that I don't know they're just
unpleasant in their difference in aesthetics from every other thing about
Isaac I mean I got I got really close to getting Platinum God once and then my
save got erased or I sweet I got a new computer yeah yeah and so then I got the
game again in wrath of the lamb and got really close to getting Platinum God
again but then my save got erased again and so by that time I was like you know
what I think I think I'm done with Isaac and so no don't be done with Isaac
rebirth rebirth was out right after that and I didn't I didn't pick up rebirth
because at the time I was like yeah I tried to get back into rebirth as well
when it came out just because you know all the new content but I also just felt
I had I had reached the depths of what I was getting out of Isaac in terms of
you know I was so frustrated getting screwed out of Platinum God twice but
again I want to reiterate though I love this game and played it for literally
hundreds if not thousands of hours for an entire year to a very important
question for Florian do you still make money off of rebirth somehow did you get
did I cut off a little bit did get off sorry oh yeah we talk about money too
much that would just just wouldn't be good I think so oh that's half of my
questions I what about just in general okay do you have any is that what you
wanted to ask oh no no I mean I'm not curious about that at all I'm just
wondering if you saw like penny one from after birth at all since you were such a
major component of making the damn thing is that is that something you're
okay to talk about just a little bit I get a little money don't worry about me
great okay that was another one thing I wanted to know I mean I mean it just
stands to reason because like you fucking don't built the original thing it
would be pretty fucked up if you were just like well I don't that's that's why
I wanted to know that's exactly why I wanted to know because it would be fucked
up if he was cut off so I had to know if he was you know I don't be possible to
just cut me off right there but yeah well I'm imagining I'm imagining like
some like you know fucking Gabe Newell comes in and like you know big in a big
yeah in a big like shoulder padded suit smoking a cigar and says we're buying you
out Florian we brought a dump truck of money to the front of your house and
we're gonna fucking cave your house and it's gonna be a night it's gonna be a
truly ironic death it's just like when my friend sold for a million for a
billion dollars to two billion dollars I was a billion yeah Jesus because it's
like it's like a minecraft is like a platform in itself that people use for
all kinds of bullshit I've just heard enough industry horror stories that I
wanted to be sure that we're not a you know like that that talk well I guess
the fact that you're so willing to talk about Isaac would would suggest that you
have an amicable relationship with the game still yeah oh yes my greatest
pride or maybe that's great that's I'm so glad that that's that that's the case
the only thing that bothers me is that they made the pics lodges like Ben said
but I still don't I don't get it I don't get why that decision was was it to make
it look like I'm shitting myself was it to make it look more like a video game
Isaac character in real life yeah he really is he lives in the basement it's
a nightmare down there it's full of piss and molded mildew and it's a nightmare
for everyone he's he's he's like Isaac is in many ways the true story of my
actual life have you been inspired by Isaac in such a way I like to think Isaac
was inspired by Jesse's real life oh no what if we had like a PCP version of Isaac
like a mod with all the guys of us oh you know I played I played an
undertale mod of Isaac once yeah I played a homestuck mod once and it was
neat oh it's totally doable it's totally doable anyways somebody get on that
somebody out there who knows shit Florian you get on it
my precious time
we're taking it all we're taking it all baby so anyways Edmund just wanted that
rebirth look different and he didn't want them to trace his art in any way and
he wanted it to be his own art style so he passed them into making this this
pixel art style so he had to actually convince them to do it this way well
they gave him a bunch of what I call it like different choices it's like when
someone when you pick out colors for your home it's like it was like that I
suppose so man that okay but he but he just wanted it to look different yes very
different I can sort of understand that I suppose yeah I guess it makes but
reverse is still pretty good it plays well enough unless you record it in
which case it lacks for me it was great I don't know that it's it's really good
for it felt it felt it felt like the old game but expanded which is pretty good
yeah can't it's hard to argue about the the cool new content and that's that's
all very enjoyable I want to ask about like the the initial development of
Isaac because I heard it took like two months like you just hashed that thing
out real quick yeah but about three months it was insane there was so much
development and creativity going on and then we released a completely broken
game and then only years later it's it's it's only only only very broken still
but not not unplayably broken so at last perfect that's man that's awesome I
was wondering I really wanted to talk about since I'm a programmer myself
definitely not on the level of complexity and stuff you do but all I was
just wondering what a nightmare it was to program all the little things in there
like one thing that I was thinking about was must have been tricky to get the you
know those how bombs when they explode next to a rock they make a little
platform appear you know in that hole yeah was with things like that a
nightmare to make or are you just able to do this kind of stuff easily well back
then it was certainly very hard for me I think I've learned a lot over the the
time now but still haven't released any game were you were you a rookie
developer at the time well not not exactly I started hobby programming when
I was 12 because because I was a nerd and and such so get out of here we don't
abide those kind of folks around here oh god I made like 20 different small
flash games over the years before Isaac and then I've hardly made any sins
because I finally fulfilled my dream of being able to do nothing all day and not
that's the dream by the way we all speak everyone in this everyone in the
PCP we all need to figure out like how to find something we could do with
residual pay that's what we're that's the golden goose we're all missing out on
clearly is residuals hey I was since we were bringing up your your old games I
wanted to mention a few that I enjoyed from your from your page I played I
don't know if this was the C word but on your page is just cunt which you also
made with Edmond that exists loved that game it was art was beautiful and it was
simple and fun I have not played it go to comics games calm it's great hang on
hang on did you make oh god I'm gonna be so embarrassed if this is wrong but did
you make triachnid I did actually yes I fucking loved triachnid like at least
at least five times back there's a game called cunt how can I play it go to
comics magical games comics with a K dash games dot com it's you know what I
heard is when you play the game of cunts you win or you die this is very
correct yes there was another game that I really this is the one I played the
most out of all the ones on your page now that I play every single one but but
seed where you play as a dude wearing a cowboy hat riding a sperm through like
downtown Manhattan as like the army comes out and tries to kill you and
there's this awesome mechanic in there where when you you control yourself with
your I think with oh no you just continually move forward and then use
the arrow keys to like rotate yourself but there's this great thing you can do
with you the tail of the sperm which is when they're shooting missiles at you
which happens constantly if you whip the tail around really fast you can
deflect the missiles away I just thought that was the tightest fucking shit and
that guy that seemed like it was to be really hard to do there must have been
like some state you enter when you move like at a certain speed or you rotate at
a certain speed that like it triggers that effect to happen on missiles when
they hit man that was awesome it was super cool oh man I like that game I
love doing that game there was an animation called sperm rider where it
was this very sperm and was that in like like a pencil yes it was just like
the game because then I went and contact the artist and I did I convinced him to
make a game or did he convince me but I defy message him first it was so cool
because he made all this pencil drawn art for it and then he could just ride
around on your sperm you know why you're a hero to me for you sweet you're a
hero to me Florian because you've done what I'm increasingly getting into doing
and it's that you you have like a vision for a project and you make it and you
outsource whatever you need to outsource that you don't personally have the
skills to do and it's specifically art for this stuff and you just you don't
let those things get in your way right like a lot of people might give up like
when I made games back in the day it was always a big fucking headache to to
worry about art and I had my sister do it for some she was garbage at the time
so it's terrible and a bell bell bell really has an unbelievable fucking
background I don't know what I tried to play the cut I tried to play the game of
cunts I didn't die he died did a bug crawl up your dick and made you explode I
didn't I don't know what was happening I was it's a beautiful game though everyone
go check it out it looks it looks I highly I highly fucking recommend
triac that I didn't play that one I'm going to it's so it's so great I take it
that that because you know Edmund McMillan is rather well known for the
sort of scatological humor of games like Isaac and in all his other games but I
take it that you also have a similar sense of humor even without him around
I made about three games that are that have sperm as a main character
that's more than your average person I'd say yeah
most people round out around one yeah you're ahead of the bell curve there and I
think only one of them I did with Edmund but it might be two I might I might not
remember that right that's great that's awesome it's just it helps me to
understand why you're a fan of the PCP because this is exactly the kind of thing
I'd expect our fans to be making yeah this is a podcast primarily about me
shitting myself hey but I was curious about one while my court of clowns talks
amongst themselves if I'm not totally fucked up in my timeline you're getting
together with Edmund would have been oh wait you know you know I was gonna I was
going to say getting together for Binding of Isaac would have happened
after the runaway success of Super Meat Boy which I mean he was already getting
fairly well known but that was like his big breakout success and I was going to
ask like how did you guys meet but then I realized you had already done games
before that point so my whole question is retarded so never mind yeah that's right
little known fact I've actually been doing stuff with Edmund for a long time
in fact he got me into game development at one point because oh my god I mean not
precisely to game development but he was a mentor for me because I never knew
that you could make money off games I was just a little boy playing around with
little yeah little yeah he was the best kind of mentor that's that teaches you
how to make money oh yeah right such a good man dude he was your column he was
the commoner to your Simone what a beautiful thing he told me I could go
and get a sponsorship for my game and then I I think I got 500 bucks for for
making a little game that was basically a remake of Pac-Man and it was amazing I
assume that's that's Pac over here that's the one I think that's the first
one I properly released it plays horribly but I did the art in it at least so
it's all me oh that's beautiful what a wonderful story so I'm so happy to hear
that your relationship with Edmund is still positive I just I didn't know and
that's great we started doing podcasts on my channel as well oh really I had no
idea I have to go listen to those he keeps telling me he'll be around but then
he keeps getting busy the last excuse he was he was that he got sick from his
baby so
he's a little baby man speaking speaking of your of your YouTube channel
well I guess I watched I watched it and I saw it and I was just just like I was
surprised to hear that you were listening to the PCP being being a
successful dude as you are I was surprised that you had fucking ventured into
the cesspool of humanity that is fucking YouTube YouTube video content oh yeah
what brought that about what what urged that that move yes that's right not only
am I an inspiration to you but also the other way around because I really want
to make video games no videos YouTube videos yes and first I started out I
just wanted to do lazy let's plays like not online or whoever they just upload
daily and it's just them playing but now I now that I've seen what you guys do
it's more interesting to to attempt to do it that way though I obviously don't
have as much time so well I mean I do have time I just have to work on games
beautiful that's beautiful to hear my friend sweet so very gratified are you
we could do that also terrifying yes but I want to let's just jump into the
other major thing here so you've got a new game that's percolating that's
work that's that's being cooked as as we speak and it's called poor mouse and
everyone should go check out the trailer for it on on his GameSquid YouTube
channel so I think I had everybody here watch the trailer but would you
describe to us what the the main thrust of that game is gonna be oh yes so you
are a mouse and it's very dangerous even though you can fly with your ears
because a magical mouse you still have to do that's the tagline right there very
dangerous even though you can fly so I wanted to make it so it's basically like
Super Mario meets Dark Souls but I'm sure I'll completely fail and it'll just
turn out to be the next no man's guy I mean Super Mario meets Dark Souls is
about as marketable a premise as you can fucking even even think of so it sounds
like a strong start there it's true especially with a cute animal in the
mix it's perfect never hurts this debatable because the mainstream games
they're not really about Dark Souls or platforming so it's not mainstream
marketability but I suppose indie marketability should be pretty good you
know you know what your problem is with that game you need a couple more white
guys that's what you need that couple couple of white guys that's what's
missing from that you just need it I don't see a white beefcake space marine
anyway yeah I can't relate it to be Dark Souls like enough for a body
video to make a Dark Souls like video on it and then you'll have an instant I
wish that guy still exists huh yeah god got tired of that guy a year or ten ago
I still make content it's fairly entertaining he only existed on like on
Dark Souls Eve night is about to be made that's that's when the blood moon is
full that is true but it's because they've been making Dark Souls 3 DLC so he so
it is still dark I guess I forgot because I haven't played anything since
Dark Souls 2 anyway wasn't it wasn't it though I got this is my this is my
Dark Souls 2 this is my Dark Souls 2 story when I got to the Queen and I tried
to shoot her with an arrow and there was an invisible wall and I was like this is
this is no Dark Souls Dark Souls 1 Dark Souls 1 let me shoot Gwen Gwendolyn fuck
this game when I hear you fool Gwendolyn yes yes yeah well it also let me shoot
Gwendolyn but whatever that's true you know about this bug where you could shoot
minus from the DLC from I do I did that I fucking did that shit I killed him what
what the fuck what you can shoot manners from outside the boss arena if
you aim it right no shit yeah it's a very it's a very pussy way to win
sucks thanks to I know thanks to Matthew Matosis that you can shoot the
man-eaters in in or one of the man-eaters in Demon's Souls but I never
played Demon's Souls so what a ton of arrows stand where he can't reach you
shoot at him for hours and hours now he's dead
who was that sexy boy who said that I just watched that recently just just
earlier today I walked into the living room and Davoo was playing Demon's Souls
and I started saying Demon's Souls yeah and he joined in and it was a fun
family time from from soft boys everything good I did I did seven years
ago just like Florian with binding of Isaac brothers has been brothers
I'll be I'll be someone again I'll show you please please do I mean hey I was
curious so you're working on multiplayer for for poor mouse that seems like a god
damn nightmare it is it is pretty much terrible before I started making poor
mouse I was going to make a multiplayer game but then it was completely fucked
up because I couldn't get a single thing right so and then I worked on poor
mouse but now after many years of learning about unity and multiplayer I
think I finally have a chance of making it work this time hey a quick question
what was that cancelled game about oh yes for the secret it's about gladiators
firm and that's all I'll tell you sperm gladiators I assume oh no not dig
fighting how how long how long has poor mouse been in development now I think
more than two years already and I was supposed to make it come out on early
anxious but then I delayed because I was going to make multiplayer instead which
would take me forever and it means I can't release the game until it's at
least a lot better than it needs to have a really good multiplayer mode so that
people can instantly get into the multiplayer mode and not just be in the
early axis and then lose interest because multiplayer requires a fan base to
to be active around the clock oh and you were telling me just the other day how
much you love the arena in Dark Souls 3 and the kind of instant multiplayer you
can do is that what you're looking for to get if possible for poor mouse yeah I
really do play Dark Souls a lot now this DLC with the the arena it's amazing and
I want to make it so that there's a bandit's mode in poor mouse where you can
kill other mice and then they drop their seeds and you can use the seeds as a
weapon but but also you need to you need to collect seeds and whoever gets 50
seeds first wins it would be awesome yes so like okay so so gameplay in poor
mouse it's like so it's like platforming but with like gliding and
there's combat and and what's like okay so it's a competitive multiplayer scene
where you where you like compete for seeds like you run around you get you
steal each other's seeds what have you I'm trying I'm trying to I'm trying to pay
myself you know can you can you relate in terms that we understand say it's the
Dark Souls of X and then we'll understand what that means oh boy I already did
that he did in fact the Dark Souls of Mario oh shit you're right so how much
of that two-year development time is just because you moved to 3d because it
looks like this is a fully 3d game well it was always going to be 3d
but I hack now I mean I mean moving 3d I didn't I didn't mean I got it that game
I bet you in general actually it took me forever to learn that oh my god it is
so hard but then again I I'm probably just really bad because I was just a
young boy of 21 years when I made Isaac and I only knew how to program in flash
and nothing else and so that's why the performance of Isaac is so poor because
it's made in flash so moving away from that alone was hard but then yeah moving
into 3d is difficult all the more because you would not believe how hard it
is to make this 3d rotate rotations work they have a whole new type of rotation
called quaternions and they all they're pretty much not even understandable
hang on what's what's the name of the rotations quaternions quaternions yes
there's also I'm a math I'm a math guy I thought I thought I might be able to
flex my math nuts a little bit but I guess not you might have heard of rotate
you along the fourth dimensional axis or something that's what it sounds like
yes I think somewhat there's a different one is called Euler angles and that's
just three axis and it it's just three different numbers and that's
understandable but then it gets translated into quaternions and that's
how the computer understands it oh my god so it's a lot more complex that way you
know I've actually done a little bit of developing in unity myself before I
started YouTube with Ben I was working on a 2d platformer in yeah with my
buddy in in unity and I we we definitely stopped short of anything and it wasn't
3d but I'm a real I'm a real boy too it's got some levels it's got some
levels yeah what what what do you what do you hello did someone just leave the
call monkey joint but he's muted monkey oh right he's free gonna start
recording himself you can jump in if you want monkey I don't give a fuck about
anything I made a game once I made a video game on RPG maker for steam oh boy
you go you're you play as a guy me and I go there's a tree and you go up to the
tree and you click on the tree and the tree says it's a tree or some shit I
don't know that's as far as I got what I did it I made it what does it say I did
have trees say just something I don't remember but you could read a tree you
could read signs oh I know what it says it says it says I wish I was a flutter
shy oh I got him the ponies in bring in that's bring a pony game of course I
should have known yeah that's why it was never completed because I didn't know
make it a pony game yeah you would have gotten all the fan funding do you miss
that how how big of a brony are you Florian we're all fucking deep oh no
that's the most important question of all how many stocky markers of the main six
do you own none but I don't believe in such childish material goods but oh yeah
I mean either me neither that's that's what I was gonna say to it's much more
mature to play games to make games where you're a penis trying to fuck a giant
cunt floating in space you know but it is the finest higher level of maturity here
but anyways it's good that you brought up the ponies because I was wondering did
you notice all the the pony references in Isaac of course I know that there's
the spacebar item right the unicorn horn it turns you invincible I'm sorry it's
been a while since I played yes and oh me I did that you absolute bastard that
unicorn horn has saved me many a run oh it's pretty bad though it's like a
good starting item I like I like it cuz it lets you get it lets you get over like
you know spike doors and stuff the problem yeah that's it's got some
utilities but the problem with that thing is anytime you're using it a boss
like you can deal damage by running into things with it but you never can I
could never properly time when it ends so I'd usually just be mashing up against
a boss when my invincibility ran out and that would take damage and I blame you
for all of those thank you for try hunt that boss get hit dude wouldn't like a
pony ducky marker or be like sideways dude well sure how would you hug a
sideways the body the body pillow you know it you don't be appropriate you
know how ponies have legs if you had legs off the side oh you know what they
should do you know those big pillows that kind of have the parts that extend
around that you can kind of put your arms on when you're leaning back on it
there should be a pony one like that with the legs you know with the legs you
know that's an add-on that's an add-on for the pillow you got to buy that
separately
naive boy you didn't think of where to put the pussy hey Florian what do you
think about the best game ever undertale oh boy I was gonna say your
very first podcast was about the best game ever now we're talking about it
again the binding of Isaac perfect oh yeah you know wait wait yeah didn't I'm
didn't I bring up binding of Isaac you said it was your favorite game of all
time and then your mind in the very same podcast it's amazing what an arc
you have gone through and then you just went and went to suck underdale's cock
again just like everyone I remember in the best game ever podcast I brought up
Isaac as one of the games I've gotten the most fucking enjoyment out of just
the amount of fucking you know time I spent on it and you know loved a lot
and stuff I can think of at least five or six games which Ben has referred to
as his favorite game of all time there's many different ways it's like it's the
the best game ever conundrum is is is like a jewel that you should you twist
hither and thither and and the light and the light reflects into your eyes from
all of the different ways and angles what anyway how do you like undertale
for Intel with the greatest game us with the tail of undertail I'm just here to
talk about under oh boy undertail have I got a tail for you yeah a very short
tail in fact because I watched video game donkeys video about underdale and I
decided I'd never have to play it that's a shame because it's a good game
and it's pretty short but whatever do whatever the fuck you want I mean we
on undertale I haven't I haven't seen donkeys video on it but like undertale
is the worst fucking game to let's play of all time except for that one time the
flow he calls you out that's great everything else about undertale is just
makes for a miserable let's playing experience oh my god so emotionally
incidentally speaking of let's plays I think I think we owe it to Florian to at
some point do a better binding of Isaac let's play I was not happy with my
performance I spent I spent like 20 minutes in the fucking game room trying
to fucker trying to fuck around with you just trying to optimize that's how you
win everyone yeah I'm fucking love that shit I love I love nitpicking and
fucking you just just fucking around with the odds and just spending spending
five spending an hour to save five minutes and trying to eat out every
every possible advantage I can it's it's actually fun for me to do things like
fuck around with the game room in the heart now's an appropriate time to tell
you did you that you are as big sack as shit for not appreciating the the the
hard work that the optimization that you have to put in if you want return on
your investment of your runs and Isaac you have to do the grinding you're a
hack fraud how about how about I mean like sometimes you can get a run where
yeah you just get lucky and you get good stuff so you don't have to grind you
make your own you find yourself in a run you find yourself in a run where you
need that level of luck in order every time you just grab that run and go to a
good run what are you talking about you grinding since you can find an Isaac you
just fucking go around and found a way you can play the arcade that's all yeah
you you if you know how to play smart and like conserve your resources and like
you know when when is it best to use your keys and bombs and stuff and like you
know how what do you have to do like it are you looking for a really well what
are you what are you yeah what do you got to do to make a devil room happen you
know like these are the kind of things that you got to keep in mind you can't
anything but you can maximize your odds of getting a good run it's not it's not
all luck because to a certain extent you can control the odds if you know you're
doing well I'm just I'm just I'm not saying it's all luck I'm saying that if
you can have runs where you just get lucky from the outset and then you do
better throughout the game then when you have a run that's like shit at the
outset and then you have to grind for 15 minutes scrap that run and go keep keep
killing yourself you find a good grinding can make the difference and in any
case as I said fucking eating eating out a barely eating out of victory from the
jaws of defeat is just fucking way more fun than yeah that's right yeah you if
you give up on a run that doesn't look great and that's perfectly acceptable
but it is always a good idea to put in the extra time and effort to you know
whatever ways appropriate if you get fucked of course you can abandon a run
like I probably should have abandoned that run early on when I got and I think
I got P and I got some other thing that was ranged down and it was just just a
fucking bullshit set up from the get yeah yeah polyphemus one of the best
items but I think I actually know that in my my latest well yeah that's right
I got P and polyphemus and it was just a terrible combination yeah polyphemus
didn't get didn't used to give you a short speed but down but now it does but
have you played to the eternal edition I don't think any of us have how
recent was that one or two years I never remember but you definitely had it on in
in that video but you'd have to enable the hard mode for it to work because then
you open yourself up for a whole new world of bullshit there's all kinds of
champions that just do in same things they wouldn't imagine and that was the
best part about it you gotta try it yeah I was that eternal mode cuz like I
booted up steam cuz I wanted cuz I was I was like let's make it let's make a
binding of Isaac play let's do this podcast to binding of Isaac and I
signed into my steam on digits computer only to find oh shit I don't even have
it on fucking steam I don't wear the piracy I guess I must
are you a goddamn pirate you know what but you know what I made up for it because
I bought the game just to record that fucking podcast I paid my dues that's a
good pirate yeah private here I redeemed I redeemed myself hey I was
curious about something so one of the coolest things about Isaac is the
ridiculous complexity of the different item variations that stack and cause all
kinds of crazy effects and I always imagined getting those to work
properly and never completely fuck the game was one of the most challenging
things to do is that accurate yes it is because I completely failed at that for
example you get Ipacac and you get my reflection then oh yeah it kills if you
would expect that it would home back in on you and it would be annoying but you
would not believe the level of how annoying it is because for some reason
the bullets glitched up really high so you couldn't see them and then it would
hit you out of nowhere how much how much okay here's a question I just thought
up but I'm kind of interested in the answer to how much of like item
interaction is like is is just emergent versus how much like code like how much
it has to be specifically coded about item interactions like like like how much
of that code is like is there like just for the interaction part versus how much
is just like the item has its own behavior and the two just kind of the
two just kind of modify the the tier the tiers or the game separately you know
what I'm saying well ideally would have it so that most of the things would only
be their own self-contained thing and then they would automatically stack with
everything but of course I did it completely wrong because I had no idea
how big this game was going to turn out so when when I had when Edmund told me
there's an item that gives you double damage I just just said if item then
double damage but then they're never more more items so it got more more
confusing and I never really had it set up so it would work so I had to redo all
of that so it could have multiple items that give you more damage without it
being weird you need some sort of complex formula for calculating damage now
probably or something's indeed well well there was I know there's like the
in-game menu that kind of shows your stats it's like like like there's like a
bar that fills up on the pause menu but like I don't know on most of my good
runs I would find that like I maxed out the bar I would max out like at the
damage bar and then you know the bar would the bar continued infinitely but
like you couldn't really see it or you know like like like the bar itself would
only show you so much and then there would be tons of shit going on behind
the scenes that was not like you know visibly tracking on that stats screen
or that's how it always felt to me yeah the bar isn't very accurate and it was
added after the fact so it's more of a I guess it it kind of determines how much
damage one single tier does but it's still there's still things that that
that make it more complex like when you get the lump of coal that makes the
tears grow steadily larger yeah that for example doesn't even show up in that
stat I always had there was something I was always clear on do your tears
automatically turned red when you got past a certain damage threshold or was
that like an item visual an item specific visual thing I always felt like
when my tears got strong enough even if there was no item that was specifically
made the tears red they would turn red anyway was I just fucking crazy I had it
that way but they removed it in in reburse because apparently that wasn't
the intended way of Edmund so I guess I just made that randomly and Edmund that
son of a fucking bitch you know let's just talk some shit about that guy that
piece of that shit don't you just hate him tell us how you want him to die tell
us all the dirt tell us the deeds hey Edmund I'm sure you're listening right
now the worst man who ever lived your words not mine he said the worst man of
all time do you think you listen to this actually well he said I should send it
to him so probably more like more like Deadmond because you're gonna kill him
is what you said now hey Edmund hey Edmund leave us a comment patreon.com
slash patreon.com slash Ben St yeah I did it yes please I don't even have a
patron you could just buy Isaac can I get money from that yeah yeah do that and
you'll get a cool you can confirm that that you make money every time we buy
Isaac yeah but I don't say how much so I was gonna ask you know obviously your
your friends Edmund who's a sort of a superstar of the of the indie gaming
world do you have any indie gaming friends or anything who you you want to
promote like who you think deserve more attention that's a great question there's
this there's this kid Phil Fish have been hearing a lot about recently you know
really was in the news again I probably I don't know oh god well I guess there's
that one guy who made Orbox C which he could buy on Steam he's a really good
friend and it's a good game and no one has bought it and it's a tragedy what's
the game I never heard of it Orbox C it used to be a flash game but then he made
a lot of levels and put it on steam and it's pretty good it's possibly some
links in the description to or or boxy yes ORBO X space C right let's all buy
it right now let's play oh god I just logged in the steam I got all these
gifts people gave me games what's happening oh it's like Christmas of
morning you're funny caught up to you are you on are you on are you on steam
Florian oh yeah and by the way like are you on steam and do you do you play a
lot of games in your spare time or is all your time spent doing the dev side of
things oh I'm I've been a procrastinator far beyond for you guys all day all of
yesterday's sick bro it is sick bro don't fucking patronize me but do be a
much do you and I is me at patreon.com
god damn this guy is savage so good so good at what I'm just turning it back
every time rubs hands so what are what are some of your favorite games as of
late any recommendations you have for us oh yes there's certainly one that I've
been playing and hating and I just can't stop myself from playing and
hating it it's called enter the gungeon it's the worst game and definitely the
worst game and you can't stop playing it it's it's I saw you had a video called
like how to improve into the gungeon that sounds fascinating oh I got a lot
of hate for that one now gun guns kind of similar to Isaac isn't it's like another
oh it's very similar only that it's not bugged but also it's too hard I cannot
believe that there would be a game that's too hard but it is I always assumed
that the harder the better but enter the gun to improve me wrong it's too hard so
like how does it feel knowing that you basically caused this this huge boom in
roguelite games because I want to say Isaac seems like the flashpoint of this
for sure literally flash oh yeah well my question my follow-up question to that
would be do you agree with that like I mean yes I have created roguelike it
is true yes I mean I I know it was I know it was a thing before like roguelike
elements were already creeping into like other genres and like genre mixing
before Isaac but it has only grown it has only grown since that's why that's
why I said roguelite like this genre of things that take roguelike elements and
then you know apply some other game style to it like in the in the wake of Isaac
there's definitely been like an explosion of these you know we've got like risk of
rain and FTL and dance dance Crypt of the Necro dancer and all that how do you
how do you feel about all those games you fan of the the roguelite genre well
I do love roguelike very much but the problem is that they're all filthy
pixel art I just wait for the day when someone will make a beautiful 3d roguelike
game that doesn't play like ass because I've only played once that that play like
ass or they pixel art but it's not been one that didn't apply to these did you
ever play dungeon crawlstone suit I did not but I'm sure that looks and plays
like ass it's not it's too basic it's basically like ass it is far it's not
asking me but it basically might as well yeah great yeah um what was that one
uh there was one 3d I love asking what are you talking about it's pure ask you
ask is pure it's just funny because it sounds like ass don't you understand
it plays like ass key sure I got you very very mature very mature oh yes if
only I could poop and piss on everything yeah that you'd be like Jesse yeah my
hero me pooping and peeing on everything and everybody every day and on
everything pooping and peeing on everything here I go one two three and
up oh yes p-style too perfect yeah you know his p-style I know all your
secrets do you know but chugger too I couldn't actually I I got like one
minute into that and I couldn't give it all try you really should you gotta
follow and you've got to follow through to the end on but sugar yeah it's all
about and please leave a comment because I want to coming of age tail much like
the binding of Isaac it is but chugger has probably the most the most
shockingly deep narrative of any retarded ass song you'll ever hear oh sweet
it's great it's by it by the way let's let's plug your channel your YouTube
channel is game squid right oh yeah you gotta check it out it's just like these
guys but with developer content oh man freeing which is far more valuable and
good so go check that out it's like it's like it's like what we do but from
someone who knows what the fuck they're talking about yeah yeah yep that's right
it's actually I'm curious have you done anything to promote your channel because
it is shockingly low view counts considering well actually it turned out
but when I started it was just bullshit it was just let's place and they weren't
even good and then my partner left and I got someone else it didn't start out
very well and whenever I made when I made Isaac a first day I never made I
never promoted myself in fact I didn't even do interviews because I was so shy
in basement dwelling so now that I want to be famous I I have all these hurdles
and then they can only get my my fame drip thread from me by Edmund I am
delighted to be a part of that process whatever whatever small amount yeah
thanks oh yeah does Edmund help promote you oh yeah occasionally he definitely
promoted the eternal update for a little bit and people played it and then
they decided it was bullshit and then they discovered that it was meant to be
bullshit oh good so you're basically still like that came out after after birth
right like you're still developing elements of the original Isaac even
while the new versions out yeah I I think I how when did I start on that was
that before we burst came out before after birth came out anyways I I did I
decided to delay it's a three births could have its day or after birth but
it no one really cared about eternal addition but that was fine because it
was just a minor thing I just yeah I mean I guess it's a little bit confusing
some things I mean I didn't even know I played after birth but I wasn't really
aware of what was going on with the parallel development despite being a
pretty big fan at the time it came out so I guess it just got lost in the shuffle
a little bit unfortunately oh yes all the bad reviews even though it was all
free so it was a lot of free content at least yeah what like what what changes
were there in eternal addition because like apparently I bought eternal
addition without even noticing I was just I just want original Isaac and
that's why you get it for free if you have wrath of the lamb because yeah that
way you can uninstall it if you want but you can also just play it for free and
it's great so basically it has these new eternal champions which are just white
champions and they have in the same patterns and they do bullet hell things
and there was a bunch of little fixes and they really troll you hard at times
like that you know that boss that splits into little pieces the fistula no
that the mini boss actually so he he has a power where he recombines if two pieces
of the same size hit each other so you could you could get that on an early
level and you'd have to fight him for for half an hour before he stops doing
that does he regain a little bit of health when a when that happens or
something oh yes but it gets less the longer you fight him so it's not completely
insane it's almost like you thought about how to implement this pretty cool
pretty cool yeah maybe we'll have to I I definitely want to see Ben try to play
this so we should definitely play all the time kind of let's play a great oh
okay yeah so to do that you have to do it on hard mode to get these bullshit
champions oh yeah all right that's what we'll do then you should do an Isaac
race I you know I think it's just too hard for most of us I think we can get
well we can we can just fucking play Isaac in parallel and it'd be like you
know who who wins yeah basically like that and you just edit it together I
mean Ben Ben Jesse and Nate are all pretty hardcore Isaac players so that's
that's three right there and I am good at being shit at video games using
playing Isaac right now you guys didn't even know it that's how good I am I'm
the sneakiest at video games well Jesse your IRL life doesn't count get out of
that basement go live your life go be a real boy mom's coming for you I'm just
thinking about the fact that Jesse is literally in a shit filled basement like
it destroyed well I don't know I guess it's all cleaned up now right or how how
wrecked is the basement currently Jesse well I'm in it so pretty bad so it's
more filthy than it was before I came home yes oh the antagonist is mom just
like in real life that's yeah yeah HIPPO are you also firing up Isaac is this
way everybody's going quiet is everyone just playing Isaac playing or boxy
because it's on a mini clip I tried to play Isaac I turned on Isaac just now
but then I realized I still have the undertale mod installed so it was like
I was playing the wrong game no give me out of here
game sense could actually get bought flies in his lemon pipe oh my god
fantastic gotta get munchy on this let's play was it monthly was it munchy that
tweeted about that didn't someone tweet about that recently that that that
binding of Isaac is bought flies in your lemon pipe yeah yeah you okay sick well
classic I sure do take a crap how about you so why don't you tell us your
future plans I'm very interested to know what your you know five ten year plan is
as a game developer where do you see yourself going or maybe as a youtuber
maybe you I mean maybe long-term you'd like to get away from game dev I mean I
hope not but perhaps it feels that if I had access to YouTube and if I had been
shy I probably could have had a pretty good YouTube career but now I'll just
have to start now it's not too late I think it's still big I think it's still
big in your that's why I was astounded that you would you know condescend to
speak to us lowly plebs from your pedestal of a real game dev who's made
one of my favorite games of my life and you know just yeah all that shit it's
the first time we've had someone who's a fan of the show who like does work that
we respect I got to say I like I like where this is going I like where this is
going good mom kiss not listening anyway well like you know I mean the PCP is
just a bunch of youtubers and we've had other youtuber well yeah I'm special
go yeah sure yeah I always forget that with the furtive the furtive Ben
Saint so easily forgotten I guess I guess what I'm trying to say is that like I
hate that guy we have on youtubers who we like but I think that everyone in the
PCP thinks that we're better youtubers than everybody anyways so it's like you
know we have on people who we like their work but you know I it's not like I
think any of them are better than me at this job but then you are someone who's
made something that none of us even could make and all of us are fans of and
think is great and so it's it was that I think that's why it was so shocking to
us to find out that you were not just watching the video of binding of Isaac
but actually a huge fan of the channel and we were just like how could it be
possible that someone who's done it a real thing it's very it's very
gratifying that someone who's not some kind of fucked up wasteoid dwee
bazoid waste of space asshole like the rest of our fans like the rest of our
fans like the rest of you fans listening at home would be watching our shit
thank you with you little pissant YouTube channels oh we inspired you oh
it didn't inspire you enough obviously cuz you stink you all stink we didn't
inspire you enough because you still haven't put that bullet in that chamber
yet we're waiting for it I'll get to that already buddy incidentally if if
there are any people who have who have made real things that any of us have
heard of that watch the show let us know it really boosts our egos strongly yeah
yeah oh but I'm not that great I'm just one of those annoying commenters you
don't like um baby you know what guys have we learned something here have we
learned that commenters actually can be decent people all right fair enough this
has flown in the face of everything I've ever known yeah it was it was it well
the funny thing about it is that like that that Isaac let's play because the
audio recording was so bad and it was like we recorded it at it was it was like
six in the morning after we just done like eight hours of other let's plays
that are all for Jesse's channel and we were like we didn't want to go to bed we
still wanted to record and Ben's like let's do Isaac I can play that you know
I've played a million hours of it I can play it sort of on autopilot Ben wasn't
as tired as me and Jesse were but we're like like you know that there's not a
whole lot of conversation it's sort of bad audio and so I considered like not
even releasing it it was like you know will anyone actually be entertained by
this but I'm now I'm glad I did because now we found out that the guy who
programmed the damn game is a fan of the show and I was like you know this just
goes to show everyone put out every stupid shit video that you make don't
don't throw anything away release it all you never know when you'll meet the guy
who made binding of Isaac by way of your your crappy shit videos there's no
escape for me relatable relatable that's why you said I'm sticking to it from now
on no one can stop me release it I've started a terrible downgrade of PCP
content everything will be terrible thing possible I don't know don't worry
we fit on a downward spiral quite sometimes ready for more content than
there are even hours in the goddamn day and all sweet we'll just turn on we'll
just turn on a camera in the corner somewhere and just leave it going it'll
just be going and going I've already made my declaration that I don't make good
videos anymore and I'm sticking to it it's bad videos from here on out it's the
only kind you're gonna see for me it's the only kind I want to make the only
kind videos are the worst ones what about horse shoe finale part 3 where's
that coming out it'll come in the fucking toilet and I'll wash it down into the
sewer and no I'll make it I'll make it but no one'll ever see it I'll spend a
year making it just so that I can upload a video of me deleting the file that'll
be my ultimate that'll be like my gg Allen committing suicide on stage but he
never got to do it cuz he died in his own shit first but if he did that would
be my analogy for that had he like promised he was gonna do that and then
did yeah he didn't make it he said he didn't make it to the promise day cuz he
he like shot heroin up his butt pipe or something and died first heroin in my
butt pipe
I'm with you I died in my own shit at
me
Florian I have to ask what is your favorite and least favorite PCP meme
that's a good question oh god not the main solution outside perspective usually
ignore the memes altogether I was very shocked when I talked to Nate's that he
was just talking purely in memes was all just cack and lol and everything
he knows that I'm secretly the best me did you thoughts on the undertayler any
uh you know upvoted down what the official PCP mascot how fucking hype
were you to see him get his at the hands of everyone at the hit the people's
champion brunswick yeah I'm a swine I think I must have missed that one
he's not a real PCP fan get him out of here it was all he infiltrated us to
chill his game that no one's ever heard of the binding of Isaac on our little
7000 he knows he knows the market there he was that patreon.com
ben saint money he fucking does doesn't he all I need all these idiots who give
Chessie money so you can insult them I need all of them now don't insult my
idiots you son of a bitch that's my job oh fuck good I'm glad I think we I think
we all understand each other a lot better now that's that's true that's true
it feels good something valuable lesson here today well I'm if you want to get
rich get on the PCP because we're all rich that's right that's the true lesson
here we're all rich rich boys patreon.com slash we're not really rich give us
money it was all joke yeah it's always a dangerous joke that patreon.com slash I
don't have health insurance anymore help me please that's a good picture it's
100% true you think I fuck around with this shit insurance I don't think I've
ever had that once you got it once you got it you're suddenly scared of
everything when it's gone insurances for the birds it's for a little pussy baby
girl the birds well I wish I was a bird insurance insurance is like the PCP of
adults no one needs it and it shouldn't exist hey one I've got a real question
that I was wondering about Florian what would you say were your game like
inspirations when you were making you know all the stuff you did what are some
classics that you loved as a young lad yeah yeah your art what what the classics
that inspire your your your dev shit yeah yeah oh man I I don't even remember
if I had any kind of inspirations at the time of making Isaac we just kind of
trolling around on new grounds and just seeing what people were making and you
know well I was but I never really got into flash games even though I made them
myself I never really I can't point out one good flash game that I really like
except I can't point out one good flash game that is hilarious um well like what
I mean what would you say are some of your favorite games well I actually made
a top 10 list that you should watch about my favorite games but I am a PC
master master race master and so my my my original games not like they're not
Mario or anything like that's their mind sweeper I play mind sweeper and I'm
really good at it yeah yeah I love fucking mind sweeper yeah man so it's
soft that like like my current computer I guess I have a pirate in windows so it
didn't come with mind sweeper oh no makes me mad but I but luckily it's it's a
browser game now you can easily just type mind sweeper into Google and it's
fucking there but I've spent spent many an hour I think I've won maybe two or
three times those were the most glorious moments of my life I have never
won a sweeper and I just don't see it ever happen in for me it really boils
down to luck at the end because like I have difficulties where you play yeah
yeah I have only on like super like I set the difficulty like so if you can't
even lose no you got to set it to you gotta you know you play hard mode with
99 mines and you fucking flag them all and if you but when you get down to the
very end there's always gonna be a point where like there's just no way to know
like there's always one moment where you just can't know and you have to guess
are you casual mind sweepers I got a 25% win rate on expert it's very doable
even though sometimes it's fucked and you have to guess but it's very doable
25% of the time I love your inspiration is fucking mind sweeper how do you feel
about how do you feel about space pinball you big fan of space
can I get any love for jazz ball I fucking love jazz ball how about that
how about that a screensaver mice amaze that you'd like the mouse just goes
through and finds the cheese was that a big gaming inspiration I see monkeys
saying jazz ball is the shit you know I think monkeys mentioned jazz ball before
yeah mom that is you it's it's really cool look it up I got a game for you it's
called dark souls what about what about what about the quest for donut or
something there's a game oh yeah the best game of all time
yeah just Jesse funnily enough while maybe has not developed any indie games
has like three about him yeah about that and there should be more and there I
don't want there to ever be a to be a lull in the in the people making games
about me meme more sense hey you know what speaking of which games here yeah
just do it bro just just download make game dot exe and run that shit I got I
click team micro media fusion something or other too I'm gonna make a game
right now I'm just gonna open it up all right that's that's great oh no we're
gonna have a world I've earned in a game relevant to that I was I was tweeted
out a little while ago you know ask us questions and stuff and monkey jones
asked a question for you Florian a procrastinators how much do I got to pay
that guy for a monkey flash game so what what are your rates so what could we
you can't afford me I'm can't afford you seemly expensive he's got the monkey
money dude he's a youtuber he's making all whatever whatever monkey offers you
I'll double it to not make a game about him oh my god the bidding war that'll
never end that's fantastic incidentally episode 42 of the procrastinators
podcast is being published right this second oh my god and you're all
missing you Florian you're missing out on your favorite cast cuz you're too busy
being on your favorite part because I was afraid I would just stop playing
Dark Souls and fapping just like I would normally when I play when I listen to
you guys lucky to have the same time that's hard mode I usually just use
the controller to jack so I can use both my hands on the buttons but you do
do one hand each oh like like you wrap the cord around your dick and you like
yeah yeah it's easy it's the only kind that gets me off anymore yeah only to
Dark Souls yeah oh yeah there's undead naked women perfect especially when
it when they turn into beef after you've been hollowed yeah I'm just I'm
just gonna say the what is it the fuck what's that what's that roast beef
covered beast from Bloodborne that's just got the floppy vagina on its back
oh yeah I'm talking about the blood starved beast the blood starved beast is hot
as a beef beef the roast beef beef the DLC roasted beef oh no school you blood
born for not coming out on PC yeah yeah they really fucked you over with that
one it's awful just like the biggest meme in the world Ben yeah it's cuz Sony
published or help them make it or something? I don't know.
Okay, let's transition. We got some questions here that we can take a look at over on the
Twitter. Here's an important one from at Cygriz after the D. They want to know, why does Digi
shit naked? First of all, I didn't even know that was true. And second of all, please explain
Digi. Why you shit naked?
Well, I can think of a few good reasons. One, it feels good. Two, it feels good.
I mean, really, there's only the one reason.
The full aesthetic package is delivered. Make sense to me. Here's one that's stupid, but
I'm going to ask it anyway by at Yath and Cool. What do you think Western animation can learn
from anime and vice versa? Nothing. Run. Flee. Do not take anything from anime. It's
trash, my dude. Tentacle porn. Shouldn't these questions be for our guests? Oh, yes. Yes,
they should. Maybe you should have specified. We have a guest this week. Oh, God, it's true.
Nobody knows. Actually, I heard that Monkey leaked the secret info in the discord, in the
fan discord. Yeah. So if you were in the PCP fan discord, someone on Snapchat told me that
Monkey leaked it in the fan discord. So if you want to be on the ball with hot gauze.
That fan discord is going to be the death of us. The idea that there's some fucking
hive of filth and villainy where fans of us talk about us amongst themselves. Who knows
what they're saying? Who knows what sick things they're saying? I don't know what the fuck
they're saying, but I'm glad that they're saying it, whatever it is. Well, actually,
some people did actually ask specific questions. Well, I mean, Monkey was one, but here's a
real one actually for Florian by at steel viper 77 asks, Florian, what was your favorite
project to work on with Ed other than the binding of Isaac? I like coil. It's the sea
world, of course. Rainbow fills. Amazing. And everything just stays in the back. It turns
black and it's all just filthy fluids everywhere. What is what is coil? I'm not familiar with
that one. I don't know if I can go look it up. Are you gonna make him fucking explain the
whole game? Just fucking go to his website. Fine. Fine. Never mind. Part two in the sperm
trilogy. Can I just say that the that I think just as much just as much as Isaac, I think
your contribution to gaming history of having made the game called cunt is absolutely invaluable.
It's the it's it's something that I cherish the game called cunt. So I was curious. So
I mean, it's also known as the seaward. So was that so that could be released on various
platforms or just so we could be advertised? Or, you know, what was the thought process
there? Well, I suppose that was just the name that it would have on the on the platforms.
But then when you click on it, it would say cunt. So make sense. I guess it's mild censorship.
Sure. Time to fuck or whatever that Ed did, which is just called time fuck in the actual
game. It's just to get around the loopholes there. You know, hard to run advertising,
I imagine on a game called cunt. Well, that's right. Free flash games need all the advertisement.
Break in taboos is well, I know. I mean, maybe the advertising that would have been on like
new grounds or whatever, they might might might not be able to run ads next to a game called
cunt. Oh, yes. And meanwhile, they have that game where where you're the big daddy and you
chainsaw children. Yes. Yeah, I know, right? It's very amusing to me constantly the exceptions
of violence and the rejection of anything sexual or that other game that they have very other
animation, which is a clown who plays propeller with his dick and it plays some goofy music to it.
Yeah, meat spent. Excellent. Oh, no. I don't make it worse than of it.
Um, these questions are all garbage. And nobody's asking anything good. Do you guys watch Always
Sonia Philadelphia? Yes. T vice writer. Now shut the hell up and never comment again.
Yeah. Yeah. This is what I want to hear. This is what I want out of this guy says this guy says
Hey, what did you guys think about Final Fantasy 15? Fuck you. That's what I think about it.
You ass hole. I can't shit on my buddy at rabbits foot 99 with their incredibly cute duck icon asking
does dieting matter too much or is it all about exercising? Dieting super important. It's more
important than exercising. Do that if you want to be healthy. So there you go. There's a real question
for you. Great. Thanks. Oh, okay. Let's just do one more because these are all garbage. I got a
question. I got a question. Oh, okay. What is your favorite videos from all of us? Oh, put them on
the spot. Put them on the spot. It's definitely gonna be horseshoe finale. I've just watched that
again recently and it's just always so weird. So it's amazing. I have to fucking ask, does that
mean that you have watched the horseshoe saga that led up to it? No, not all of it, but I have
a red track. Well, I suppose actually, I guess so, but I've watched the finale first. And now
it's also tragic in its beauty because now it means that all of you guys have stopped making
pony reviews. And now who will explain my little pony to me? Who will do it? There's no one left.
There's a lot of costs now. There's none. There's only a pale limitation. You know, after horseshoe
finale, they stopped trying. That's when the show went downhill because they knew. The inspired
art had surpassed the original creation. So it was time to shut down shop. That was always the case.
There was that one cartoon Max Gilardi did and that was amazing. The Dotmove series, yeah.
That's the one. There was the friendship is Witchcraft, which was better than the original
show by Miles. There was this one channel called I love Kim Possible a lot and you'd think that it
was a Kim Possible channel, but it was actually a my little pony channel and it was the most
hard hitting in-depth fucking out of control underground. No holds barred. No fucking mainstream
bullshit. It was real analysis for real fucking bronies. Let me tell you. If you wanted to know
what the fuck was up. That was your hub. That was your hub, not the hub. One of the, you know,
probably the chief influence on drowning in horseshoes was the legendary I love Kim Possible
a lot. Any fucking ways. I think Hippo was asking for your favorite video by each of us.
And don't be afraid to hurt our feelings if you don't know any of us.
Yeah, I'm not gonna be upset if you don't know which one of mine you like.
I know about you. I'm just curious.
I've seen-
Just what Hippo wants to know is what's your favorite video of his? Just answer that question.
There's a fish at the door. There's a fish at the door. It's amazing.
Oh, fantastic. I'm glad you know about fish.
That water. I've seen that a while ago before I even saw the rest of his channel. So yeah,
that was cool. Great. By the way, is that on the Gibbentech channel or is that on Hippocrates?
A quick question about that, about the lore of fish at the door. Did that man go on? Was that a
business that he started selling water to these fish? Do they pay? Is this a, you know, like a-
Yeah, he's started a bar. He made, you know, he made the best of a bad situation. All these
immigrants coming over. Immigrants. From the ocean. Right. He got like all this tap water. He's like,
I can supply these fish what they want. I know. I agree with you and it'd be if Hippo was like,
yeah, it's all a metaphor for immigration. I have a very right-wing policy about these things.
Well, actually, that's a very left-wing policy about accepting them. This is actually a pro-Trump
propaganda piece. Finally, I was waiting for an excuse to talk about Donald Trump, the best guy
who's also I hate him, but I can't decide today. Every day is different. Every day. I've trolled
so much about Donald Trump. I don't even know where I stand anymore. I've trolled myself into a
quarter with Donald Trump. Help!
Nate, what was the last question you wanted to read?
Okay. Yeah, here's one. Oh, fuck, I lost it. What's your favorite bird? What's your favorite bird?
My, uh, my, at Simon. At Simon asked, what's your favorite type of bird?
Oh, that is hard. It's both of such majestic creatures. And they're also beautiful.
Ravens and crows are cool as shit. They're cool as shit. And they could be your friends.
Yes. Every possible topic has a Jesse meme. It's true. I got an actual answer.
The wood duck. The wood duck. Why, man? Why? If you get made of wood. Google, Google wood duck,
and you will see the majesty that is the wood duck. And it's beautiful plumage.
Oh, it's got nice stripes all over it. It's all colorful and iridescent and shit.
I love it. Pretty good. That's a good ass duck. That's pretty good, right? Yeah, for sure.
Loving that wood duck. Living a wood duck life. My favorite kind of bird is a Pidgeotto.
Oh, no, no. My favorite bird type Pokemon is missing. No, because it's the only bird type Pokemon.
Yeah, that's true. Oh, I see. It's glitch type bird type. You got outclassed, motherfucker. God damn.
Well, well, you know, Pidgeotto's been a, you know, even though I'm sick of seeing his ass,
he's been a very helpful companion in many a Pokemon game over the years. I can't say there's
any other bird I've spent more time with. My favorite bird is Big Bird. Yeah.
Because he's the fucking biggest. Nobody's as big as Big Bird. God damn it. I'll fight a nigger.
I'll fight anyone who says he's bigger than Big Bird. I like Dynablade from Kirby Superstar.
He's strong. He's a good mom. He loves his family. You know, got strong Christian values. You know,
there's a lot to love about the man woman. No, the best bird from Kirby is definitely Heavy Lobster.
I do like Heavy Lobster. Heavy Lobster is a good bird. What I'm trying to say is I love
Meta Knight's Revenge. It's the greatest Kirby game of all time and Dynablade helps you and that's
nice and Kirby is an evil man. But I love that game. 10 out of 10. Meta Knight's Revenge. There
you go. Best Kirby game. Dynablade just is fucking Songbird from Infinite before it was cool.
Yeah. Only you never fight Songbird. So whatever. I think my favorite bird will be a Cassivore
because it's so deadly and beautiful. Ooh, I'm gonna Google that. It's pretty much an emo with a
spike at its foot, I think. Unless I misremember the name. Oh, it's all blue. I think so, yeah.
That's a good bird. How do you spell that? I can't do it. That bird is like half Buffalo.
Link me your search result, dude. I'm too lazy to Google it myself. I couldn't find it. I am
leaned back in my chair and I cannot be asked to lean forward. Ben, please. If you'll, if you'll
please post the link. God's sake. I don't know how to spell this thing. Yes, right away. Right away, sir.
Okay, there we go. All right. Now, that looks like that's a dinosaur is what that is. That's just
a straight dinosaur. Yep. Dinosaur bird. Goddamn. I'd like to fuck that board. It is beefy.
It looks delicious. It's glorious. It does look delicious. Got a lot of meat on them,
non bones or hollow bones. Oh, oh. Oh, no. What's that other super delicious bird? Chicken.
They're also delicious. Yeah, yeah. No, no, there's another bird. The most delicious bird.
No, it's green and it's weird. I like green food. Green eggs and ham. Everyone type in green bird
on Google. We'll find it. Green. Oh, we'll find Kawabiba. Oh, it's Polly. You know what? My favorite
green bird. Cacopos. The cacopo is the most delicious bird. Is that a cacophony in its
unevolved form? It's a caca. I just think it's Pokemons. It's all Pokemons. I'm sorry. I totally
cut you off, Hippo. But I was just talking about the penguin being my favorite because he's got
green, green screen skin. He does. Oh, the penguin. Your penguin, right? The Hippo penguin.
How could I forget? The soon to be a real character penguin boy. When are we seeing more of that
young man? The reference literally no one will get penguin boy. I get this. When's he coming back,
Gib? When's he coming back? Well, I mean, there's a club penguin news. Oh, yes. Oh, that's exciting.
Oh, my God. He needs to avenge his people who are all being fucking executed at the end of
March. Oh, my God. That's very exciting. That's very exciting. Okay, we're done. We're out of
steam, right? We're done here. Oh, no. Wait, I'm trying to take a picture of the game that I'm
developing right now. I'm trying to take a screenshot. It's better be the best damn game I
ever seen or I swear to God, I want my money back. Yeah, print screen, print screen. Well,
I'll do it after the podcast. I'll show you. No, I do it now. I want to see it. All right.
Oh, shit. I got to open up Photoshop. Just fucking screencap. Why? Just the screen cap
software doesn't do it. I'm going to teach you something incredibly valuable right now.
Press the print screen button on your keyboard. Let me teach everyone the most important thing
you'll ever learn about your computer if you use Windows. Go into your start menu and in the search
bar type snip and snipping tool will pop up, which instantly is a thing that lets you capture an
area of your screen. It automatically converts it into an image that you can just control v-paste
anywhere and use that for the rest of your life because it's the most valuable thing in the world.
Okay, so use that. Yeah, print screen will do. Yeah, do it or do it. I have it already.
It's Super Mario Hippo. Number one hippo in gaming. You made all this art during this podcast
and made a fully functional game with nothing in it. I love it. I love it. That's an incredible
amount that you've done in this short span of time since announcing that you were going to do it.
Oh my God, Gippo. You know, you need to get later in this game. You need to upgrade your
propeller hat so you can just fly all the time. That's exactly what I was thinking. Yeah, he's
basically Rayman. I can't wait for that. Okay, so good that everyone was cutting off Hippo so he
could have had time to make all this perfect. That is great. He's utilized his disability for
good at long last. It's wonderful. My crippling disability. Oh no. Okay, well that's it. By the
way, I just wanted to let you know that right before we did this podcast, my heads had broken
the most ridiculous way and I'm not sure if you've been able to hear it, but something on the inside
of my head that's broken off and now it sounds like a rattle whenever I shake my head. Listen to this.
I hear a little bit. It's driving me insane. A little crunchy sound. I hope it wasn't too noisy.
I can hear it until now. But now I'm going to go back and listen for it. It's like an Easter egg.
Now you can listen to this podcast at home, viewers, and the second viewing will be more
rich for the experience. Replay value. That's what it's all about. Yeah, replay value. Well, you
know, like, what's it called? Fucking Discord has really good, like, it only picks up audio if it's
above a certain level, but Audacity doesn't have that. So there's a good chance our audience will
hear a lot more than we did. Quite possible. But I can't be that bad. Well, I tried to hold
still for you. We appreciate it. We appreciate it. Well, that was another episode of the Pro
Crastinators. We sure are a good bunch of friends or something. We sure are a bunch of guys. We
did talk to another guy. We, um, yeah. Oh, boy. Yeah. Cute a song. Now. Yeah. Everybody say goodbye.
Yeah.
I'm not working. I'm doing nothing. My dick. I'm jerking myself. I'm sucking. I am an asshole.
I am stupid. I've got a deadline. Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
What they came for instead, I'm tweeting. That's why there's no
heat and holes in the ceiling. Yeah, it's quite the burden. It's a hard knock life being a genius.