Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the main dude, the guy who's the number one cool guy, that's me, best guy ever.
And who we got here today with us?
We have Hippocrit.
I'm the number two guy.
You're poop.
We've got Tom Oliver.
I was going to say number two guy, too.
Oh no.
You guys are both poop.
You have to fucking kill each other then to see who wins.
Actually, you already team up to kill me in the brawl.
Find out.
This episode.
Yeah, the brawl.
Go to the Redcon 2 Royal Rumble to find out who is poop.
You did fucking wreck my shit.
You know, I don't mean to.
Oh, you just spoiled it.
You idiot.
They may not have seen it.
They've all seen it.
They've all fucking seen it.
You know, there is a slight similarity between the ultimate victor and poop.
I do see some visual similarities.
But in any case, let's move on to today's topic.
So this is from a while ago.
It looks like during Redcon, people weren't asking us as many questions.
So come on, guys.
Keep asking questions.
But in any case, this is a topic I thought was cool.
And it is by, right here.
Yeah, okay.
Here we go.
Vitalis the Kid asks, Topic for PCP, what did you guys aspire to around the age of eight
to 14?
Oh, there was an age bracket.
This is like writer, game developer, or Spider-Man.
Well, he said that, but I don't care about that at all.
So just ignore it.
I just like to read the whole thing for fun.
So Gib, what do you think?
Well, I have a long list of things I wanted to be because I changed my mind basically
every time I find something cool.
Makes sense.
The very earliest thing that I wanted to be was, you ever seen Hercules?
Sure.
The Disney one?
Yeah.
You know, the big ice elemental, I wanted to be that because I really like him.
His legs came off every time he walked, but he would still grow him back because he's
so cool.
He's so cool.
He's really tenacious, willing to fucking break his legs.
He's like, ice cool, you would say?
Yeah.
Hey, did you know, Gib, you played Kingdom Hearts 1, right?
Yep.
And you play the 1.5, right?
Yeah.
Did you know that if you go back to the Colosseum at the end of the game, after you've beaten
like, I think like mostly everything else, that guy's a boss and you can fight that guy?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
And it's super fun.
It's super fun.
Oh, you can find Sephiroth 2 and he's like the hardest boss in the game.
He's gay.
I don't care about Sephiroth.
You gay.
I just care about the Isolamentals.
I love elementals in games.
They're my favorite trope.
They are?
Pretty great.
Oh, and just speaking of Kingdom Hearts, everyone, my Kingdom Hearts lecture is definitely going
to be out by the time this is out.
So make sure you go to the Radcon 2 playlist and watch all our shit.
There's a big Kingdom Hearts 2 lecture, so go learn yourself some knowledge.
Should I keep going with my list until I'm done and then we'll do the rest?
I think so.
I think so, if you don't mind.
Okay.
It's not too long.
The next thing I wanted to be was a wizard at Hogwarts, because I read the books and
I wasn't yet off age and I was like, well, maybe my parents are just really good at hiding
secrets about this or maybe they're muggles.
It could be.
Like Hermione.
Hermione's parents were muggles.
Yeah.
They didn't know shit.
Dude, I remember when I turned, I think like 10 or 11, I was just like waiting for that
letter to arrive.
I was like, I know what's going to happen to me.
I'm the special boy.
I'm the chosen one.
It's going to be me.
Didn't happen to Ben.
Fuck him.
Yeah.
Fuck Ben.
I'm the, I'm the Lily shit.
What was her name?
He's the Petunia.
Lily Potter.
Yeah.
No.
She had a different name originally before she, I'm trying to describe how I'm the cool
younger one with all the abilities and the prettiness and the cool sister.
And then Ben is Petunia, Vernon's wife, the horrible aunt, you know, that Harry grew up
with.
I don't know.
I don't know the last name.
Okay.
Whatever.
Lily.
Billy.
That works.
Lily.
Billy.
Yeah.
So after I turned whatever it was the age, I was like, oh, it doesn't exist.
Fuck that shit.
Yeah.
And then I wanted to be a drummer because my dad was a drummer and occasionally he
played at our school for various things and he's real cool and I was really proud of him.
And I wanted to be a drummer, but I didn't really express deep interest.
I was just thinking about it as, you know, a dumb kid.
You don't realize as a kid, you got to do things, you just think about stuff.
Then I would, I think it was like 13, 14 where I started reading Mango and I read like
volume three of Dragon Ball and I wanted to be Goku and I wanted to be a martial artist
and the way I thought about it was I would just train like Goku.
I don't need to sign up for like a training lessons or anything like that.
I would just, you know, get asked for Christmas some weights that I could wrap around my feet
and I'd put them on and if I keep them on for like a month and I take them off, I should
be able to jump real high and that was my...
Just like the turtle shells.
Yeah.
That's just exactly the same reasoning.
I thought it would work.
It didn't work.
That's too bad.
I was pretty sad.
I guess...
But after that...
Oh, sorry.
Go ahead.
Well, I was just going to say, now seems like an appropriate time to say that that was
also my goal and I also bought a bunch of training weights and wore them throughout like most
of high school, little like two to five pounders on my wrists and ankles the whole time and
yeah, I just...
Actually they were kind of cheap and they would spring holes and just leak sand everywhere
sometimes so I would just leave trails of sand behind me wherever I walked and they'd
be like, whoa, there goes that swole kid.
Leave sand everywhere.
Fuck yeah.
One thing that was cool about those weights is that, I mean, they wouldn't let you jump
high but after you took them off, you felt like your knees could go to the ceiling.
You know, you could do like the, like, whoa, I am really, really strong now.
That's true.
Just for like five minutes.
It's cool.
It's kind of like that thing where, you know, if you stand inside a doorway and you try
to lift your arms up and then you just do that for like a minute and then you step out,
your arms just go up by themselves.
It's like...
Oh yeah.
I love doing that.
So I saw the manga was in the school library which is where I found it but nearby was the
how to draw manga and after learning that manga was a thing that you could do as a job,
I wanted to be a manga boy.
So I tried, this is the one thing that I actually tried doing.
I still have my original manga that I drew and I think I mentioned it on Twitter what
it was a combination of.
I made it like a strange Photoshop of everything that was in it and I actually, I kind of want
to redraw it at some point and put it out there.
It was never finished.
Was this an original story?
It was an original story but it was very derivative of a lot of different things which is, I guess,
the perfect recipe for a great, perfect manga that I would have made.
You should redraw it though.
That sounds cool.
I'd like to just see the original stuff.
I don't think I ever saw it.
The thing about the manga was I could not be bothered to start from the beginning.
Every time I thought of like a cool story or something I would just imagine how it would
get to the climax and then I would draw the climax.
I would write about the climax because that's the cool part and the setting up is like,
yeah, it happened, I guess.
That's hilarious.
So yeah, it's just a climax to a story that nobody is ever going to know about.
Then there was a time where my dad, being a drummer, being a rocker guy, he introduced
me to Led Zeppelin by playing the Royal Albert Hall 1969 DVD special thing where he would
show like John Bonham playing the drums real fast for freezes and it's like an amazing
thing and all the Jimmy Page stuff, it's just so mesmerizing.
I just wanted to be a guitarist after that and so I would play guitar from, I think,
age 17 till now.
That made a big impact on you, it seems.
I never really got good enough or confident enough to like write songs or talk to other
people who played music but I can play guitar so I guess that was one thing.
It's funny, my buddy is definitely worse at guitar than you and he is a very shy guy
but he knows a bunch of people and he just did a show is what I'm trying to say.
He was on, he just went to some like open mic thing, him and his buddies and they performed
a little bit and it was original songs actually and it sounds like it went pretty cool.
So you should do that too, it's cool.
I wish I could, I don't think I'd ever really get a band unless I just went out and did
stuff by myself.
You should play with your dad sometime.
I'm sure you'd be happy to do that.
I would want to, I don't know, it's hard to do stuff, you know.
I do know that.
Yeah, I think we are all aware of that for you.
I hate stuff.
I mean this is skipping ahead to the end of my list but I don't really know really what
I want to do at the moment but I'll continue your list for now.
After being a guitarist, I was still kind of wanted to be a guitarist but then obviously
YouTube was the thing and I learned that you could make money off it and my favorite guy
was AVGN so I was thinking, oh maybe I could one day make a video game review show and talk
about PS2 games because that's a thing that nobody does and I eventually have done that.
In between I did My Little Pony as a practice run which was pretty good and then sort of
in between all that, in between the pony stage and before the real video game stuff, I had
to go to university because my parents were getting mad at me for not choosing something
to do for my life so I decided, I like drawing and I like the idea of making a Hayao Miyazaki
movie and just drawing it and making the coolest world ever because I love all the Hayao Miyazaki
movies, the spirit and the way the Laputa Castle in the sky is probably my favorite
just because of the environment.
I just love the idea of just building a world and then being able to look at it and then
it being animated and that's like, oh yeah I could be an animator, obviously I'm not
that good and I probably never will be because I'm not Japanese so I did that for three years
and now I'm done with that and I don't really know whether I want to do animation and now
I don't know what I'm just doing YouTube because I do YouTube.
You kind of got a bunch of possibilities in front of you.
I've got a bunch of possibilities, I don't know what I want, which one I want to be when
I grow up and I'm already grown up just too late.
That's cool, yeah, that's pretty thoroughly answers the question, except Gib, you fucked
up because you specifically said 8 to 14, you wasted all of our time, thanks for ruining
this entire cast, Vitalis the Kid I'm sure is furious that you went outside of his predefined
age range, fuck you, Vitalis.
We're all still 14 at heart, so.
That's true.
Everything up to the manga stuff was 14, 8 to 14 I think.
Well that's cool.
Yeah, I was interested.
Okay, well hey Tom, why don't you tell us about your dreams as a child?
I think the first thing I was legitimately interested in being, I guess I have some
fictitional things too like Gib was saying, I definitely wanted to be a Power Ranger back
in the day because my name was Tom and then the green guy was Tom and that was the coolest
thing ever and I was like we could hang out and be Power Ranger bros and I definitely
had dreams and shit all the time of being a Power Ranger, it was the coolest thing ever.
You're still latching on to that to this day.
To this day, honestly, I still want to spend like $500 some day and get one of those really
good replica helmets of the green ranger and just wear it all the time in public, I don't
even care.
I still want to go to a con wearing one of those and then get the green ranger t-shirt
and just be a street version of a Power Ranger and just walk around like a boss, that's my
dream.
It's going to have attainable dreams.
Give me money, I need $500 for that.
I also like, but in terms of like serious things I guess, the first thing I wanted to
be as a little kid was the guys who drove the big fucking construction trucks.
I had this weird fucking obsession with those back in the day.
I guess it's not super weird.
I've given a lot of little kids like trucks and shit but I was like, that was my super
first like massive obsession as a little kid.
I had tons of like remote control trucks, like dumb trucks and like the front loaders and
the back hose, like all them.
I remember my parents got me like one of those, you kind of like sat down and you could like
dig up shit with it and put it in the backyard and I would do that for hours, like every
day just like in my head and be like, yeah, I'm fucking doing all this cool shit.
So we would see little Tom Oliver in his little drivable car thing, driving around his
own backyard digging holes with his child construction equipment.
Is that correct?
Awesome.
Some of them didn't move.
This one kind of just sat there and you could like dig shit but I had like a remote controlled
like bulldozer.
I remember it blew my mind because it was like super huge.
It had to be like at least $100.
It was so like dumb and I was like, this is the coolest thing and you like dig shit with
it and I had like an army of these things and that was like my thing forever and like
I had all these videos about like trucks and shit and I was like, it was autistic levels
of just like this is my jam.
For a long time, like through like, hmm, I guess once I started going into like elementary
school and started like actually learning actual things that kind of changed.
The next big thing I wanted to be was a scientist was my next thing.
I was super into science all throughout elementary school, specifically astronomy.
Astronomy blew my fucking mind.
Space was the coolest thing.
A child with his eyes on the stars.
It was, I guess so, but that was just like, ah, it was, I don't know, it just fascinated
me.
I liked learning about the solar system and like black holes and supernovas and all
that stuff.
And I guess like, I think Ben might have been in that, into that too.
Like, you know, he works at AstroCamp after doing physics stuff and he's kind of into
it now.
I wonder if he was into as a kid too.
I just wonder because he's not here, but sorry, go on.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know, I was, I'd always look forward to science class as a kid and like
I guess also this time my dad like is like, dude, you should watch Star Trek and I got
into Star Trek, like the classic and so like space and then lost in space and so space
was a big deal as a little kid, big into like the sci-fi and then like science class always
talked about that a lot.
I remember one time I think it was in third, no, fourth grade, something like that.
We did, we did a project where you had to like create your own planet in the solar system
and like trying to explain like why no one had ever detected it until now.
I love it.
I came up with this planet that like its orbit instead of going like horizontally was like
vertically and it was like orbiting in such a way that our orbit never like crossed paths
with it and that was kind of the whole thing.
I had like this whole explanation for the project, it was pretty cool.
That is cool.
And I was totally obsessed with science and astronomy and shit up until I think middle
school when math started showing up in science, I was like, I'll fuck this and that killed
that dream right quick because math and me do not get along at all.
So that wasn't really working.
After that, there was a huge period of time where I didn't give a shit about the future
and just played video games.
So good, it did nothing.
Just played a lot of PlayStation 2.
Then at some point I was like, I think I got into new grounds and I was like, oh, you can
make video games.
I want to do that because we had this class in school where it was like multimedia design
and then you there's like this is flash, this is what they make all that shit.
And I was like, oh, so I started doing little animations and stuff and flash.
And I was like, all right, I want to go.
Was this in high school or was this in middle school?
This was still in middle school.
I think it was like eighth grade or something.
OK, all right.
So I think I'm already past the 14th.
So maybe this is the end of my journey.
But yeah, animators slash video game guy was the last big thing until like it became
comics and then writing stories and YouTube and all that jazz.
So well, you can keep going and like tell us when that happened because I'm still
curious if it goes past 14, it doesn't matter.
It kind of it kind of it started with with programming and making video games because
that was the big thing I was into is like, oh, I could make these things.
That'd be really cool.
And I had a friend in high school who already knew how to program.
He was making games for like the TI 83 calculators that everyone had to have.
Oh, yeah, yeah, awesome.
So like he knew all that shit is like you can put like a custom OS on this and then
you can load all these games.
You can play all these games.
So like we'd look like we're doing work, but we were just playing like Phoenix, which
is like this like schmuck game and they had like a Mario clone for it and like a
doom clone.
So you're just playing all these games on your calculator and the teachers are too
dumb to realize doom clone on the calculator.
Yeah, it was pretty cool.
That's awesome.
Those TI 83 inspired a world of hackers and late gamer MLG before the iPhone.
There was the TI 83, the original fucking gaming and disguise machine.
So OK, but seriously, I'm really wondering was it even possible to play
doom reasonably well on that thing?
How could it be?
It's no controller.
Well, well, they had they had a d-pad on it, which you can move around with.
And then you could use like the second button, which is like the function,
like a second one on the other side.
And there's another button under that they kind of was generally used for controls.
And they had an engine called the Raycaster engine that did pseudo 3D
like Wolfenstein 3D and doom did, but they somehow made it work on the calculator.
And so like they had 3D FPS games on there.
They worked reasonably well, which is really fucking crazy.
Our TI 83 calculators like standard issue for a lot of American schools.
So I've heard a lot of people talk about them, but I've never seen one.
It's like that just now.
Yeah, they're kind of like you're expected to buy one.
And I remember like parents got really pissed because like a hundred something
dollars and it's just like, I don't want to spend that much on my little kid.
But they're like, you have to.
We have to learn how to use grass.
I mean, I had to buy a calculator too, but they just called it like a scientific
calculator and it had like all the buttons, but it didn't have a screen like that.
Yeah. So the difference is that the the the step
above scientific calculator is a TI 83.
They're called graphing calculators and they have the dot matrix screen is
essentially for being able to plot graphs like you put in data points
and the screen lets you plot the the data and like map like the trends and stuff.
Because there was a lot of like, I don't fuck.
I didn't I never did any of this shit because fuck math.
But that was the reason that the graphing calculator did someone order pizza by pizza.
I mean, killing your orphans and also eating your babies.
How do I know just in time?
Hey, hey, you're just in luck.
All right, hang on.
Tom was finishing his explanation of scientific and graphing calculators.
Yes, super, super fucking interesting.
I wanted to be a scientific calculator when I grew up.
No, that's the reason they were made.
But then people like hacked them and you could put like custom software on there
because they ran programs and so people like, well, programs, let's make games.
So they had like a custom OS you could put in there called Mirage OS.
It was a launcher for launching games and then you could play like Mario
and Doom and bunch of other like shooter games and stuff like that.
And somehow it proliferated all throughout our school and everybody had those.
So my friend could code for this because it was all in basic and he knew basic and shit.
So I wanted to do that, too.
It was my friend, Stefano.
He'd actually he went after high school.
He moved to California and started making like iPhone games and stuff.
So he actually sounds like he was above the curve here.
He he was he could do like super like photo realistic art and drawing
and was super smart and was super rich.
He was like one of those guys like crit hit on life and I hate him.
Right. But he was a cool guy.
So he could do all that shit and I wanted to do that.
So I bought a book on doing programming and it was the fucking hardest
shit in the world. I couldn't understand it.
And I realized that like the thing I liked about games wasn't the gameplay.
It was like the storytelling.
And so that's where like, oh, I want to do comics and stuff came from.
And that is him lasted all the way through a couple of years ago when I realized
I just want to write and now I'm going to be an author and a YouTuber guy.
Word. And that's the story.
OK, cool. Good.
It's a sink.
You got the full picture. Yes.
Thank you, Munchie. All right, Munchie.
Well, Mr. Wise Guy, why don't you tell us?
Why don't you tell us about your dream so we can laugh and shit on them?
No.
That's right.
Tell us. Tell all much.
Reveal yourself. He's still like is in this age.
Well, Munchie is 16, so he's just barely outside the range of this thing.
Before I go into mine real quick, Tom, have you ever heard of Temple OS?
I have not heard of Temple OS.
It's it's an OS based deeply in the Bible and it's and and it's it's based
on two principles.
God is good.
And number two, I can code better than the CIA.
Wait, what what hardware does this OS run on?
The Bible. Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't understand.
It's like a computer.
It's a computer operating system.
OK, so this is a computer that runs.
What was it, Mirage OS?
He said Temple, a temple, a temple, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Temple OS.
Right.
Is there anything particularly special about this?
It can run fast and it's Christian.
OK, that's good. It's approved.
It's code here. OK, Munchie.
OK, well, I wanted I wanted to be
I wanted to be, you know, one of those video game.
You want to be a video game or OK.
Then like and I wanted to be that like up until like I was 10.
And then I like saw code and I was like, oh, never mind.
I make them. Yeah.
Yeah. More specifically, I wanted to like like draw the like.
Take that dick out of your mouth when you speak, Munchie.
All right. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Got caught.
Damn it.
I was just sucking off my best friend for San Francisco.
Yeah, because because that's gay.
That's right. Yeah.
Well, you know, I got stay true to life.
I wanted to draw the like like the
sprite sheets for video games.
And now I was like, no, that's gay.
And then I was like, I want to draw like shit, like not like that,
but like still like that.
And then I was like, and here I am.
I've I've drawn both of those.
Sprite sheet art.
I mean, when I was working on Bell with my with my buddy Rich,
I did a bunch of sprite sheet stuff, and it was a big fucking pain.
And it really sucked.
And what I am I I used to take the sprite sheets from Fire Emblem.
The the portraits and the animations and just alter the colors
so they'd be different guys.
You're a D.A. color.
Fag.
Well, I didn't do it for like any reason other than I liked the idea of like,
oh, yeah, if I take the light blue in this guy's hair and change it to light green
and then take the light, the dark blue in this guy's hair and change it to dark green,
he'll have dark hair.
He'll be my original character.
Oh, I see what you say.
That's I was doing it just for myself.
And I was I was just fill bucket in paint like click, click.
Yeah, it's different now.
Hey, we didn't make some great comics with Kirby Super Star ultra characters.
Oh, I want to see those.
Was was that big bird a character?
I forget his name.
Well, you know.
Well, I'm a street.
No, no, this is a big bird and Kirby Super Stars.
Oh, oh, Dynablade.
That's the one fucking cock.
Yeah, it's Dynablade.
The little babies.
Yeah, I want to see it.
A Sesame Street Kirby crossover.
Oh, that'd be cool.
Kirby would suck up his big old going ads.
Kirby would eat all of Oscar the Grouch is trash.
Yeah.
And then Oscar the Grouch would be revealed to be a no-legged man.
Hey, so Kirby eats a lot of stuff.
Does he care about what he's consuming?
Like, does he taste it or does it just get absorbed?
Like, does he only explained in the anime?
Oh, really?
This is please.
There's like a like a black hole in his belly.
And that's that you're exactly right.
Yeah, well, whenever he eats something,
it's transported to a endless and infinite space dimension.
Does Meta Knight have one of these in this space dimension?
So he can never be full.
That's kind of tragic.
That's tragic.
Does Meta Knight also have that
because he's the same kind of being as Kirby, right?
Meta Knight is like a grown up Kirby.
So I guess they like lose that.
OK. Also, yeah, and then they they get on their mask
and then they're like, I got to fucking stop, dude,
like nightmares and shit through the play.
Hey, Kirby is male, right?
Or is it not specified?
No, it's male.
OK, they refer to him as a boy in like every game.
I was just thinking about it because, you know,
like Kirby's got this endless void to be filled
and Meta Knight's got this big rod to insert into things.
So I'm just wondering, you know,
if there's something going on here. OK, all right.
Well, well, well, if you think that stops people,
then you've got another thing to comment more
on what I wanted to be because that's what the podcast is about.
Yes. I also, like for a while, I thought that
I wanted to do claymation.
Oh, I had a phase.
I had I tried to arrange my Super Mario plushies together
and like like cut over and over again.
So I would have the perfect Super Mario plushie YouTube video.
Actually, if you go to the very beginning of my give and take channel,
you'll see like a few animation tests of like stop frame
where I turned my desk into a studio, put a blanket over the screen
and I would take pictures without knowing what I was doing.
That's cool. I did that, too.
There was like this guy on YouTube back in like the mid 2000s
who did a lot of like really crazy claymations
to like pendulum songs and stuff.
I watched that as like, this is the coolest shit ever.
I want to do it.
So me and my friend are going to start, but he never did.
I did a couple of experiments.
I'm just like, it's too hard to quit.
They are really hard.
I think I did a little at some point.
I don't know. This was like a recent thing.
I did one in college to take an animation class.
So I did do a couple stop motion animations in college
and they're actually kind of not shit.
That's cool.
All right, much. What else you got for us?
I also have. Well, the comment on that real quick.
I eventually got my friend on and I need two people to help me move around.
Munchie, I appreciate that you're trying to be interesting,
but making up things about how you have friends is just we're getting away from real life.
So just keep it real.
How like people die when they're shot with a video game gun.
Yeah, right, right. In real life.
Yeah. Well, I guess what I'm going to pull up my rocket launcher.
OK, I'm with you.
Why do you pull out your diesel?
No, I wanted to say that, but then I was like, nah.
Anyway, we were doing a skit where Peach was talking to Bowser,
and then I just say like in a gravelly voice as Bowser, I want to have sex, bro.
And he was like, he shut off the camera, looked me dead in the eyes
and screamed, why would you say that?
Why do you think idiot? All right.
Anyway,
other than that, I was really interested for some reason in the idea
that I could possibly do like be like of like a voice actor,
but not really like like like I didn't like actually like believe
I liked my voice whatsoever.
I just wanted to like be the Lion King.
Are you Mufasa or like the movie like a DVD copy of the movie?
You want to be that a VHS copy. OK, right. OK.
How'd that work out?
Pretty good. I'm halfway there.
I have a murdering part. How was your role?
You're halfway there.
Not bad.
You sound more like the bird.
Two K and Sam, my favorite guy.
I don't think anyone remembers that bird's name.
Oh, you ruined it.
I was trying to think of I was trying to think of what type of bird he is,
but I forgot because Tom's really into the extended Lion King universe.
So he knows all this shit.
That's my secret, Tism. I don't tell anybody about.
So what what type of bird is Zazu?
He's like a he looks like a two.
He looks kind of like a Toucan, but like smaller and weirder.
He's probably some crazy African species of bird that we don't
understand. Tiki Toko.
Yeah, I don't know.
African words, something.
Tell us in the comments what species.
Is a fruit loop.
He's a fruit loop.
Who's a fucking fruit?
In England, we call it toucans.
Really?
Yeah, we don't we don't pronounce it a toucan.
That's interesting.
Hey, why is re-tard England?
So like puns regarding two cans would be like two can play at that game,
not two cans of pecan's or whatever.
I see.
Interesting that in that particular example, he used can for both of those words.
Well, toucan fucking.
You know, I feel nobody, everybody hates a.
Agreed.
OK, I also figured when I would grow up,
I would just be rich not for doing anything.
But I just figured at one point people would recognize that they needed to give
me money. Well, that kind of they would proceed to give me money.
A kind of lifestyle is reinforced in our modern television programming
with expectations of wealth and riches and fame.
How's that working out?
Well, I started out my my journey in order to acquire money by selling
not drawing not like actual drawings I tried to do,
but I just like wrote down on like line paper smiley faces
and I charged them for six dollars a pop.
Dude, that's like paper.
That's like what Fantana was doing, selling his his.
What was it like images of Hillary during the campaign when he's,
you know, trying to be with her?
Please buy my art for thirty five dollars.
I'm a starving artist trying to survive.
And and and that that gumption,
that that that real that real fire in me transformed into nothing.
And now I don't care.
Good. And the world was better off.
Oh, there there was also a brief moment of time
where I wanted to make specifically apple and orange juice.
And I felt very passionate about this.
I like that.
Did you ever want to dabble in making apple butter?
You know what? No, I haven't.
But I don't know what apple butter is.
But I think you and me should team up, become the Hennessey brothers
and make apple butter.
That's been a dream of mine for a long time.
I did a real night.
Your real dream is to be brothers with someone other than Ben.
That's true. That's what I wanted most of all growing up.
One day I'll achieve that. I'm just looking for replacements.
Yeah, you're you're forever on the scale.
You have a very high expectation of your future brother.
Yes, I need you make sure you get the perfect one
because your first one was such a disaster.
That's right. You need to prepare yourself.
That's exactly right.
OK, so you got any other dreams when you think you do, you know,
any of that shit?
There is there is a brief moment of time
where I wanted to be a superhero farmer and kill the KKK.
Now, hang on.
Does that mean that you were going to be a farmer
and your crops were superheroes or you were both a superhero and a farmer?
Both a superhero and a farmer.
OK, I see, I see.
Like Superman.
Yes, exactly.
I'm not familiar with this character.
Fucking plagiarism.
Oh, yeah, he's from a farm.
I remember now.
He grew up in Kansas.
But does he does he like do shit?
Well, he's probably knows how to plant a tomato.
Oh, I don't believe this for a fucking second.
Put it in the ground, cover it up with the earth, done.
Put up with a water on it.
Hey, if there's farmers, if there's farmers on other planets,
instead of calling it Earth, do they call it like alien?
Is that we don't call?
Well, I mean, we call this planet Earth.
So if we call another planet Mars, they would call it Mars.
Oh, I think it's like two definitions for Earth.
Earth isn't soil and Earth isn't the planet.
I think we just called the planet Earth
because we didn't know it was a planet back in the day.
So maybe every alien planet is actually called
their equivalent for dirt, because back in the day,
they didn't know there was a planet either.
Here's a here's a thing, though.
Nobody fucking speaks alien because nobody exists.
Oh, that's not true.
Well, I mean, we don't know.
But I bet aliens be real if we aren't.
Yeah, I believe that there are probably some forms of life
out in the universe elsewhere as if there's big old aliens.
You know, I agree.
That's why you should get the news that there aren't aliens.
There's only Jewish people out there.
And the cause that's the difference is only.
You like because what's the deal with alien food?
Yes, they brought their alien humor to us on this planet
that we just can't understand.
But it fascinates us like Seinfeld, their leader.
The show is the leader of the people in it.
Oh, the show. Yeah, that's a shame.
I don't get on the mothership.
That's why I felt impressed.
That's a good one.
Right, Nate, you're fucking gay.
Shans, I can't think of what to say when I was growing up.
Shans, he was defeated in the in the wrestle rumble,
but he'll never be truly dead.
The under the spirit of the Undertale fandom will always endure.
There's no getting rid of it.
Fortunately.
OK, when I want to be a kid, you know,
you guys remembered a lot more details than I can.
So I can really only remember a couple of things I actually wanted to be.
Like when I was a kid, when I was in elementary school,
I found out about Dragon Ball, the show, actually,
not the manga like Gib did.
This is Dragon Ball Z.
And so like I just got really into being fit and buff
because I wanted to be like a super cool guy like Goku and beat up bad guys
and have all the ladies like me and stuff.
So so yeah, I started working out like an elementary school.
And I mean, I totally fell off the wagon for like years in between
and started seriously again, like way later in college.
But Goku was always my hero.
And I wanted to be Goku, like DBZ Goku specifically.
And like the only other profession I can remember
or really, I guess that Goku isn't a profession.
So the only profession I can really remember
wanting to be when I was that young was I really wanted to be a doctor.
And I believe that is mostly due to the fact that when I was a kid,
I saw Osamu Tezuka's Blackjack.
I saw like the OVA from the 90s.
And I thought Blackjack was the coolest guy and the doctors were fucking sick,
which they are.
But I just I really wanted to be just like Blackjack.
So I so eventually that just manifested in me going to
the school I went to for their biology program.
And I had the intention of eventually like going into med school afterward.
But when I got there, I realized like, oh, my God, this is going to take so fucking long.
There's no way I'm doing this shit.
So when I was in college, so you could because you had such reverence
for breast examinations. What a babe. Am I right?
She's pressure is kind of a babe.
Like she's got a weird mom babe body.
Yeah, I don't I was like, she's the hottest girl.
She's the hottest girl on Star Trek, for sure.
There's no girl hotter than Beverly Crusher.
I'm talking about fucking Stambame.
I don't know what the fuck that means.
We're talking about a second size.
No, shut up.
This is my this is my time.
This is my story.
I space road.
Yeah, I space.
Yeah, that.
All right, whatever.
Well, it doesn't it doesn't matter.
But when I was in college, like I decided not to be a doctor and I did like game design
and then later computer science and then just like
now I'm program and do YouTube stuff.
But that was that was way later.
But another thing I was really into when I was a kid.
This isn't really about like a career, but there was a character
who I emulated even more strongly than Blackjack or Goku or anyone.
This had like a huge impact on me in the way that I
carried myself until like college from from like middle school.
That was when I saw the movie Vampire Hunter D. Bloodlust.
Dude, I that was like my favorite movie ever.
It's it's fantastic.
It's the best animation version of like Yoshi Taka Amino's Hunter D.
You have the will of the D or is that just pretend?
He's well, yeah, I mean, say, yeah.
He's he's just like so that whole movie is.
And even like there was a I hadn't seen at the time,
but there was like a first Vampire Hunter D movie that had been made
as well as like the light novels or maybe they're just normal novels
with great art from Amino in them.
But like I hadn't read any of those hadn't seen the first movie,
but I had only seen this one and just like consistently.
And did you always tell us about this because he's read some of the books
like D is fond over by every character.
There is a scene in in one of the books that digits has told me about
where D walks into a room and it is described that all the women
instantly fall in love with them.
But he is so beautiful that also the men also instantly fall in love with D.
So it's where it wants the D comes from.
Is this where I mean, I I think so.
I think so. Clearly, it has to be the case.
Yeah, the Vampire Hunter D was a big inspiration for Ren Descartes,
who made famous the D meme.
But of course, it all comes from from Vampire Hunter D.
But all that matters is that he was super beautiful.
I wanted to be cool like him.
He had these awesome gothic clothes that I thought were super rad.
And like I was a little kid when I saw this movie.
We went to this thing in Massachusetts,
this big Renaissance fair called King Richard's Fair, which is pretty cool.
Have you been there, Tom? I have been there.
Oh, cool. It's it's a fun place.
And when I was there,
I happened to see a giant floppy leather hat just like D's.
And it was like a hundred dollars.
And I spent like my life savings of a hundred dollars
on this giant retarded floppy leather hat that I still have to this day
because it looks like D's. It's back in my parents' house.
Well, I can't wait to see it in best anime ever.
Vampire Hunter D.
Oh, I definitely will wear that exact thing.
Oh, my God, yes.
That I have to do that.
What?
If it's back at your parents' house,
Ben has already taken it for his own.
Oh, my God, he's wearing my hat and my shoes now.
Fuck you, Ben.
Give me my goddamn shoes back, you bitch.
And last thing about about D was that D is like a real
the whole movie is D kind of by himself doing shit.
And then he runs into people and he deals with it.
But like he spends most of his time alone and like his hand talks to him.
So like the movie is filled with like he's got a parasite in his left hand.
That's like his best friend and helper guy.
And it talks to him.
It's this weird face thing.
Yeah.
And it's kind of exactly like, you know,
the monk from New Yasha, who has like a wind tunnel in his hand.
It's just like Marocco.
Right. It's just like that.
Only this one's alive and talks to him.
It's it's way cooler actually than Marocco.
It is way cooler.
This guy is like personality and sass.
And he's like, oh, D, you fucking idiot.
I hate you, you little bitch.
But I'm going to help you because I actually like you so complex.
He's a very complex character.
But so like the whole movie, D barely speaks at all.
He's so soft spoken, but he's so powerful and he gets so much shit done
and everyone loves him.
This made a big impression on me as a kid.
And I I stopped talking in class
because I wanted to be just like D and just became a silent guy for like several years.
It lasted a while, actually, until like the start of maybe college.
I was all of high school and middle school.
I really tried to be reserved so people would think that I'm super cool,
but it did not work out.
The world does not work like an anime, unfortunately.
That's when I learned that lesson well years later.
But that's it.
I have a question. Sure.
If you don't have the story, I'm pretty much done.
Yeah. OK.
When did you become a gay faggot idiot?
I guess when I saw this movie.
That's when it happened.
We can isolate the incident right there.
But I watch that movie again.
That light novel Nate officially was gay.
I was just I was just one of these guys
charmed by D's beauty and wanted to be just like him.
But I went a step further and so like in high school,
I was this kid walking around with I had super long hair, by the way,
was down to my waist.
So that was another thing inspired by I've got some pictures,
but it's fucking weird.
I was this kid who wore like death note shirts.
I wore I wore Kingdom Hearts arm bands,
a heartless and a nobody civil on my wrist.
Yeah, dude. Yeah.
I and I wore like weights as well on my wrist in addition
and on my ankles, because I also wanted to still be Goku.
So I was like training this whole time.
I'm wearing all this shit. Oh, my God.
I was a God. I was a God.
I was a fucking king of that school.
As you can imagine, my mom would not let me be
because I wanted to do that.
My mom's like, you're not going out in public with that shit.
That's with this fucking death note shirt.
No, I don't think so, Buster.
If I saw you walking down the schools, the halls of my school,
I would have been scared from my point of view.
I thought you were going to say you'd beat the shit out of me.
But hey, you don't want to mess with a dude with a death note shirt,
dude, who knows what the fuck he's going to do?
All right, well, that's that's about it for me.
Yeah, did we miss anything?
I mean, if we don't have anything else,
we can just kind of jump into questions right away
and just start doing other questions from Twitter.
I mean, that seems like a fair idea.
OK, wait, go on, before you do that,
I forgot to mention that at one point I wanted to die.
You wanted to die.
Well, that persists to this day.
So that would be past it.
Anyway, I wanted to be in 1880s, like Pilgrim farmer.
OK, did you?
I just thought that would pay itself.
That would pay for itself.
Well, yeah, being a farmer is kind of cool if you can sustain yourself.
You know, I do worry a little bit about if society collapses,
that I personally will definitely not be able to survive.
I don't have the skills to do so, you know, that's a bit of a worry to me.
So I will long for that.
Sorry, I imagine myself going up to gang members
and and smart talking them when they pull a gun on me.
But like, yeah, whatever, bro, you're going to shoot me.
I don't even believe in bullets, dude.
Just try it. Just try.
I just have fantasies of that because, like, if I die, then that's what I want.
But if I don't, then I'm the coolest guy in the world.
So you want to die.
But if you live, it'd be cool.
So yeah, OK.
So I just need to find some black people, I guess.
Oh, no.
Oh, believe me, I can arrange that.
I believe Trump is going to ship them all out to England soon.
So don't worry.
Yeah, there will be plenty.
Cool. Nice. OK.
Frosch is not going to allow that.
OK, let's go to the questions here.
Let's go to the polls.
OK, here's one that I thought was.
Yeah, let's go to the polls.
Pokemon. I've been with her.
I don't. Is this question
retired or not? You guys left to tell me by at Josh rushing.
If you could be an anime protagonist or antagonist,
which genre would you want your anime to be?
Josh, you blew it, buddy.
I would want it to be a romantic comedy.
And I would want to be.
The janitor,
who peeps on all the girls and doesn't get anything
and also gets beat up by somebody.
I would want to be in one like Undertale and or.
She's not an anime.
That's all right.
That's a good point, though.
That's not an anime, you idiot.
Oh, I wanted to be.
I wanted to be one, though, so I'm going to be a sort of better.
OK, I'll make an exception.
You get to be Undertale, my friend.
Sick, bro.
Tom, this is the origin story of the Undertale.
He wanted to be an anime,
but he chose Undertale, which really fucked it up.
But it somehow worked out he got immeasurable powers.
OK, Tom, what about you?
Well, I mean, I think like the natural first inclination to say
you want to be in an harem anime.
But that's what I was thinking.
That's what I was thinking.
Anime never get laid.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's why you need to watch the best
harem anime of all time.
Anime, anime, anime, anime.
You got your fucking hand on your dick the whole time.
High school DxD is an anime where the guy,
I mean, I didn't finish it.
The guy has not fucked anyone yet.
I'm just saying.
What? Say that again?
DxD sounds a little gay.
I'm just saying.
No, that's true.
It does sound gay.
And now you say it like that.
But it's about this dude who's just got such lust for the puss.
And he's just all about it.
And the girls all get naked and they rub up on him all the time.
And I haven't seen him have sex yet,
but I think he's working towards it.
I think there's real progression.
That's why I just want to be in Vampire Hunter D. Clearly.
We've already established the best that he's like fucking
long-lived, super badass.
Everybody wants to fuck him.
Yes, that's true.
And his hand is always there for him in more ways than one.
You know what pisses me off, though,
when there's a harem anime and the main guy just
does not fuck all the sluts?
Right.
Like Tenchi, like Tenchi Muiya.
What a fucking cuck bitch.
I hate that guy.
Agreed.
Fucking.
That's why you can't be a harem anime.
Because for some reason, like you just,
if you're the protag of a harem anime,
you hate sex and you hate women.
That's true.
Which is something that I believe strongly.
So I would resonate deeply with all the harem protagonists.
OK, let's move on.
Actually, I changed my mind.
I changed my mind.
I want to be a fucking, I want to be a porco rosso.
I want to be the pig and be his.
A pilot boy.
Because I like flying planes and I like snorting.
And also the girl's cute.
I think he gets with the girl.
I forget.
Doesn't he get like character, like beast, like beauty
and the beast rules or something at the end?
Yeah.
I think he does.
I can't remember.
But yeah, he's cool.
He has a sad moment with the flying boys.
He's a good boy, porco boy.
Oh, I was going to say, I'd want to be in a sci-fi thing
because I love sci-fi.
And that's it.
What?
Stimple Bible.
Yeah, yeah, that.
And also a witch.
OK, bye.
Anui on me again.
Hello there, Anui.
What procrastinator is the best dancer?
I got to go with Robo Gupta on that one.
He's a well-known, you know, professional
dancer.
I mean, he has shoes specifically made for tactical dancing.
That's exactly right.
How could you beat that?
I mean, maybe if I were to steal those shoes,
I might be able to beat them out.
But.
Well, see, here's what you have to understand.
He himself is already a professional great dancer,
but those shoes make him 12 times better at dancing
than the average robot.
OK.
Well, no one could compete with that.
Yeah.
Let's see here.
Um, some of these are just very vague.
Guys, that's specific questions.
If you ask, like, what's your favorite movies?
That's real vague.
Actually, you know what?
To be fair, those are better questions
for, like, a topic of an entire discussion for this part.
Favorites are not my favorite.
I hate having favorites.
My least favorite thing is to have a favorite of anything.
It's dumb and gay and stupid and list-enabling.
I hate lists.
Fuck you, Digi.
I feel the same way your life.
And I laugh at you.
Lol.
You're sick, Vern.
I do have one favorite, and that's
my favorite method of murder, is what's challenge pissing.
What's that?
You try and piss six feet straight up in the air
and not get wet.
Through what means is execution caused,
or is murdered, exercised in this method.
Well, if you get pee in yourself, then you die.
You have to kill yourself.
OK, all right.
That makes sense.
I wouldn't want to be tainted like that.
That's like, imagine pee roulette.
Oh, no.
Like, you got, like, six guys, each of which
has a drink of various.
May or may not have to pee.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, here's one.
By Elton or aticekiller159, who's got that really cool
escavelier Pokemon icon that I love.
When eating cereals, do you pour the milk first
or the cereal first?
Cereal first.
Always cereal first.
Does anyone do milk?
You have to be a fucking animal.
If you do milk first, you're a common, you need to be shot.
I suspect this.
If you do milk first, it's objectively worse,
because you don't know how much cereal meat.
Like, you might put, like, too much cereal in,
or not enough cereal.
But the point is, you don't know how much cereal you want to eat.
If you put in the milk first, the cereal
floats on top of the milk.
Like, every what I mean is what I mean is,
everyone has a preferred amount of milk-soakage-image,
right?
Like, everybody likes maybe a bit more milk left over,
maybe no milk left over, like me.
And the amount of cereal you're willing to eat
depends on how much milk you like
and how much the milk you need to put in.
True.
So if you put the milk in first, you
don't know how much you're going to have to eat.
And if you have to eat too much, then it's too much.
And you know, this guy at your very best bud,
Declan Khan, immediately replied to that,
what kind of a savage pours the milk first,
the very image has physically shaken me.
He's literally shaking, you guys.
But I was going to say, you know, we all kind of
do have experience with this horrible phenomenon.
Because once you're eating your cereal,
after you've eaten all the cereal, all that's left is milk,
if you want to pour yourself a second bowl,
you have no choice but to do it.
And so we all know what a horrible experience it is.
That milk goes everywhere.
It's a nightmare.
Nobody does that.
I don't know.
But if I have extra milk and I need more cereal,
I will usually always put in more cereal
and then add more milk to balance it out again.
So, well, yeah, but you still have to add cereal on top of it.
I don't actually have the splashing program.
I guess everyone else is just really vigorous with this cereal.
I just pour it in like a normal person.
I put more effort into pouring my cereal than I do
into being a decent human being, which is zero.
OK, here we go.
Here's maybe this will be our last question.
I don't know.
We'll see.
And this one is just a light topic
by Mr. Upload X XG Upload.
Oh, TP Crasnators.
What do you think of the current political climate?
I've got I've got a few choice words for you, my friend.
Pokemon, go to the polls.
It's up to you, my friend.
You decide.
I think Trump's going to be an all right president.
He'll probably not live up to everything that he said he would.
But, you know, that's just politics for you.
You're not in America.
I think that I'm going to think he's going to be, you know,
he's going to be a bit funny, but silly, but a crazy guy.
But, you know, nothing's right.
You are. You are so brits, blaming to me right now.
This is very offensive.
It's going to be pretty fucking shit and normal and normally shit
and shittily normal for everyone.
And it's the world's going to just slowly.
No, no, what are you doing?
You're scaring away our intense SJW audience
who think that Trump is going to be a nightmare.
I really hope Trump is actually going to blow everyone up
because I don't want to die.
Sam, sick, bro, sick.
I think the current political climate can be summed up in one way.
And that is shit is fucked up, but also not that bad.
It's pretty good. All right, sick.
I mean, you are a staunch SJW cuck.
So I know that's true.
The most blue-pilled person on the first of the earth,
the most blue-pilled person on the face of the earth
in the most red-pilled podcast on the face of the earth,
the procrastinator podcast.
It's a match made in heaven.
I got a fucking clear pill, dude.
Whoa, that's just iron-pilled, actually.
Go on. Make sure you research all the,
you make sure you research all the pills that you know.
Because you put the image in the chat, but I was on mobile
and I clicked it and I couldn't fucking see it
because it didn't show it.
Let's try to remember to post this intense pill image
somewhere in the comments or something.
I'll remember.
Okay.
God, we are floundering hardcore.
I think we're all done.
Anyone got anything else?
I could, let me grab one more question.
How about, God, these are all just so vague.
When I was a little kid, I really liked the idea of being God.
Interesting. Interesting.
You know, and I did it.
Hey, you know, I'm God.
The guys who made Death Note are making a new manga.
Oh, guys, it's called...
Life Note.
Nah, I forget the name of it.
I'm gonna look it up while I'm talking about it.
But they, oh, the premise behind it is that
it's kind of the opposite of Death Note
in that like a bunch of angels
that are invisible to most people.
Life Note.
They come down and they visit fucking,
just like how the Shinigami joined up
with an individual person.
Like the angels come down and they join another person.
But now they're all in, it's a competition
between, I don't know, there's like 30 of them
who have done this now,
and they all have to kill each other.
Cause whoever is the winner at the end
gets to become God, which is pretty fucking sick.
Oh, it's called Platinum End.
It's not Life Note, it's called Platinum End.
It's called Platinum End.
Is it the Japanese boat that you wanna be?
What Kim?
Is it like the whole, like the angels come down
and they're all in Japan?
Cause Japan is the only place that has God?
Well, you know, it's the only non-godless place left
in this corrupt world of ours.
I don't know, the only characters we've seen
have been like Japanese high schoolers and shit,
but I only read like 10 chapters, so.
Oh wait, no, there was like a serial killer.
There was a serial killer who got one,
who was a cute girl, who was, dude,
that was pretty sick.
Speaking of serial killers,
don't you hate it when people say
they put the milk in first?
Yeah, I feel like becoming a serial killer
against everyone who does that.
Yeah, dude.
Speaking of serial killers, hey guys, it's me, Munchie.
Hey, Munchie's on serial, dude.
I got you.
By the way, I wanna stop this meme.
We should bring Serial Experiments Lainan on this,
in her opinion, you know.
She's the expert, she's the expert.
That's like my most popular tweets
from last year. It's got like a thousand retweets
or something.
It's the best thing I ever did.
You'll never top it.
I wanted to stop this meme,
that of people not pouring a lot of milk
into their cereal, slurping up the milk
after you eat the cereal is the best part of cereal.
I pour a lot of milk myself.
I'm a milk boy, I admit it.
I admit it, I'm a milk boy.
Good dude, you're gonna drink that fucking milk, bro, yeah.
Okay, all right, we're done, that's it.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
No, you weren't gonna get a new question?
I thought I did, oh fuck, no, I forgot.
No, you didn't, you did. Right, one more, one more.
Let's see here, how about...
Dike.
God, these questions are all shit.
You guys need to step up your fucking game here.
These questions are gay, and...
Oh, okay, here it was.
I remember seeing this one before.
I thought it was a good meme.
Okay, so bye, at John Attenbury.
Clothes at the soup store.
Procrastiners, if you could inhabit the body
of another PCP member for a week,
who would you choose?
And my answer is obviously Mage,
so I could masturbate and then just sleep
for the rest of the time.
That would be all I do.
And I probably experienced female sex for a while,
you know, I'm into that, I definitely wanna do that.
Also, I could do that as much as...
I would be Mage so I could masturbate all day
and then sleep.
Well, you know what, you know what,
if you go into Mage, then I could become you,
and then I would also be Mage.
And then Munchie could be me,
and then he could also be Mage through that.
It would all work.
Let's all be one guy.
At the same time.
No, and then Mage becomes Davoo,
and then we're finally collective.
Oh, no.
That's how it happened.
That's the origin story right there.
I feel like there are a couple answers to this.
I would want to either A, B, Davoo,
so I can understand what the fuck is going up in there.
Yeah.
Going on.
Number two, I would wanna be...
No, that's it.
I just wanna be Davoo.
Yeah.
Well, I would say...
He's a mysterious man.
I would say...
I would wanna be Davoo,
been real quick because I wanted to ruin his career,
and then I would jump out.
It's a good idea.
Just delete his comics.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I would probably pick either Mage
for the reason you said,
just because it'd be interesting to be a girl,
and I don't know what that's like.
Or I'd be Digi,
so I could PayPal all of his money to me,
and then when I go back, I'll be rich.
You know...
I don't know.
I don't like any of you.
I don't wanna be anyone.
I don't blame you.
That would be a really good answer to give.
The most interesting person to be is me.
Not me, me, but as in me.
I would probably enjoy becoming Colt Corona
for a little while,
just so I could feel what it's like
to be a good person once again.
If we're opening up shit like that,
then I would definitely wanna be the Undertaler of 5.8.
What do you mean shit like what?
Well, you know, characters.
What do you mean characters?
What are you talking about?
Oh, this is awkward.
This is awkward.
I understand.
Nate, Colt Corona.
Colt Corona's gay.
Oh, no!
I thought he was a good person.
It's ruins it.
Oh, well, there we go.
Forget that plan.
Also, I like how you try to apply the Undertaler
of 5.8.7. It isn't real.
I would never apply that.
He's me.
I can feel him growing.
He's with it all of us, really.
Every Undertale fan.
He's a collective tumor.
Every Undertale fan has a little piece
of the Undertaler 5.8.
In fact, there are 587 pieces of the Undertaler
scattered throughout the cosmos.
We have to reunite them like the Dragon Balls
to make the ultimate man.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
A goal that hopefully will never be around.
That's what happened after he was defeated
in the Royal Rumble.
He was shattered and scattered throughout the cosmos.
All of his atoms broke off into different arches.
He only has 587 atoms, yes.
He's very, very small.
He's very, very, very non-dense.
What's the, what is it, a dense?
I don't know.
Non-dense.
Non-dense?
No.
Vacuous?
I don't know if there's even a word for that.
Light?
Gay.
Okay, whatever.
Sea-worthy.
Boyant, yeah, buoyant.
Things that aren't dense are buoyant, so there you go.
Okay, enough questions here.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
We're done.
All right, thanks for this, everybody.
Hey, make sure you go to fucking at TP Crasnators.
Yeah, first go to those polls.
Then head over to Twitter and tweet us questions
and topics and shit at TP Crasnators,
and we'll fucking do them just like we did today.
And we need more, so send them in, you little bitches.
Okay, thanks for listening, everybody.
Let's say goodbye.
Bye.
Yeah.