Hello everyone, welcome to The Prolapsinators. I'm your host, Benjamin Saint of theprolapsinators.com
slash email. Who else is here? Question? Really fast. This is boring. Let's skip introduction
and get right to the meat of it, shall we? They call me Nate, and they call me Rosebud,
speaking of prolapsinators for a reason. If you know what I'm saying, ladies and gentlemen.
You know guys, I think that we aren't giving ourselves enough credit. I think that we need
to, when people ask us what we do, we don't have to shy away from it. We can say that
we are professional lapsers. I mean, we prolapse. We shouldn't be so coy about it anymore. I
think it's bad for the perception of us in the greater world. We let things... We lapse
in a lack of judgment. We lapse in a lack of skill, you know? We just lapse and we lapse
and it just keeps... I'm gonna lap at your fucking blood if you come at me with that
big old knife. Oh, you stabbed me before I could do it. Man, I should make threats I
can't keep. We professionally blundered over and over into this situation we find ourselves
in today. I would like to demonstrate something for you. Please. Because I am home alone. There
is absolutely no one in my apartment right now. My family is gone and they have left
to go see Michelle's girlfriend, Michelle's mother in Hawaii. Oh, wait. How much of that
is accurate? Did they go to Hawaii? Yeah, they went to Hawaii. So you're home alone, huh?
I've been home alone for the past week. So what are you wearing? I'm wearing briefs and
that's it. Yeah. All right, that's all. That did it for me. We can go to Hawaii. Munchy,
munchy. Yes. Why wouldn't you go to Hawaii with the rest of them? I pine for Hawaii. I've been
wearing my Waikiki pink and white wristband to remind me of those Halcyon days, long past,
and to look forward to my next trip. You can't live in the past, Nate. You've got to throw that
shit aside. That's fair. That's fair. Well, well, Nate, there's a very good reason for that.
Because they did in fact offer me to go. They were like, you know, we're going to Hawaii. This
was like many months ago. You want to come along, right? I was like, you know, Hawaii's sure cool,
but and then I take off my heart-shaped necklace trinket and I open it up the inside and I see
a picture of the URL to apsadventures.com. I say, there's someone else I would like to see more.
And so that's that's why I'm that's why I'm going to London in July instead of going to Hawaii.
Oh, okay. So is this like, I got it. I got it. Yes. So they they offered to pay what they would
have paid for Hawaii trip. Oh, that's very nice, which it was accounted to like to like one fourth
of the cost because going to London is really expensive. I would I would I would love to go. I
would love to go to London. But like you said, it's really expensive. And I just don't think I can
justify the cost. Okay, okay. Well, that's fine. There's okay, there's really fucked up. I don't
want to talk about this on the show. So is this is the hotel thing? Yes, it is the hotel thing.
It doesn't it doesn't change the fact that it's still like prohibitive. I want to hear it,
what's the deal? Okay, so this is just crazy. So I calculate the plane ticket. And it's like,
it's like over like $1,000, like it's really expensive. And so I just I just say out loud
a mile, I'm like, man, this this thing is fucking expensive. This sucks. And she's like, well,
let me let me let me let me try and like, let me see if I can find a good price. I'm like,
okay, mom. Yeah, okay, all right. And then she does it and she finds a plane ticket that has a
bundled hotel room inside. So you buy, you know, it's a plane ticket and combination hotel room. So
you get a room in a place in London. It is less with the hotel room. That's what how is that possible?
I have no clue. So just to reiterate viewers, the plane ticket is more than if I got a plane ticket
and a hotel room for the entire stay. There's got to be a racket here. Something's going on behind
the scenes. Back alley corruption hotel deal. I have no clue. But so obviously, I just did that,
obviously, because like, right, why not? And so I just have a hotel room that will be mine in London
that I we can just retreat to when we want to. Are you staying with Gib? Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
And you've got a fucking hotel. Yeah, shit. It's gonna be it's gonna be great. It's gonna be like
Munchy can come see all of the stuff and then he can go back to the hotel at his leisure
when he's sick of my of me and my family. Oh, that's great. I'll never get sick. But I'm getting
jealous. I'm getting jealous. I've never been to England. And I can't wait. You're a good example
Munchy. You're setting a good example. I'm gonna be I'm gonna be way more patriotic than you are. Give
the entire time. It's gonna be super obnoxious. Gonna be I'm gonna be the the stereotypical American
tourist and it's gonna be incredible and just fawning over everything. It will be. I
expect and hope and pray that you are as loud as possible and scream constantly in the streets
drawing everyone's attention. Have you uh have you talked to Mage? Are you gonna see Mage?
Fucking we could easily see Mage, I think. Are you sure she won't be back in her homeland?
She might she might actually be back in the old Lithuania at the time because she does that for
summer. Oh, she does that for summer. She's going back to that desolate wasteland. Well, you should
ask her. You should ask her when she's going back. Yeah, definitely lock that down because that's
once in a lifetime opportunity right there. But wait a minute. All that to say is I'm alone right
now and I've I've I've obviously been I've experienced a lot of time away from my parents
living in Boston. But I've always had like another like human being like around you know. So it's
never been like I've been like like on my own. And it's really cool. Obviously, this isn't the
first time I've ever been like alone for like a day or anything like that. But you know, yeah,
there's seriously no one here like not a joke. It wasn't like a lie. It wasn't like a surprise.
They were going to come back, which is what I initially thought. Like, you know, there's no
way I'm gonna be actually alone in the house. But I am and I have to feed the dogs and I have to
clean up everything. And you know what, I love it. I love this is so I am so I don't I don't know
what to make of the fact that you find being alone in your house to be like a novel experience.
It's it's not a big deal, man. It's okay. Well, hold on. Let me clarify. Again, I've been alone in
my house before, but not like multiple consecutive days in a row. I mean, this is probably the first
time, at least that I can recall, I've been alone for maybe like three, four days. But this has been
like for the entire past week, and then like a little bit more, you know, that's very cool. That
reminds me of Ben. Remember how our dad, our dad got into a thing when he started sailing,
which he's been doing for a long time now, when he would go away for like a full week,
and he would go sailing with his buddy and they'd sail around like Martha's Vineyard and you know,
like the the Cape of Massachusetts and whatnot. Like my our mom was still there. But like our
house was a totally different thing without dad around. It was like fucking stay up late,
play video games and shit, go have pizza pies for breakfast. Holy shit. Yeah, you know, yeah.
And he was thoroughly lashed when he came back and found. Yeah, I mean, you got to pay the piper
at some point. But okay, but here's the thing. Here's the great tease of it all was that because
here's because he was sailing. Everything was totally dependent on the weather staying good
and making for good sailing conditions. That cruel moment. Again, I love my dad, but that cruel
moment when the when the weather is turning south and you the phone rings and here's dad,
son, I'm coming home, as he would say. And you know, I'll never remember his his deep baritone.
I'll never forget rather lost at sea one day. We'll find him again. Perhaps he should have
come home that one time. What a pathetic fallacy that is for the weather to to to to to punctuate
the dad. You know, you know, dads, they go out for they go out for a pack of sailboats and they
never come home. Except when you don't want them to, except when it starts to rain and then they're
like, ah, fuck it. Yeah. Dad always have another sexy sleepover with your friends trying to max
out your DDR and guitar hero scores. And in Walt is your father to call you gay and smack your ass
and do everything that you were praying he wouldn't in public. Honestly, I don't think a single one of
those like extended sailing trips lasted as long as it was scheduled to like every every single one
ended at least a little early. I mean, I can't even blame him. But it seemed like it was weather
every single time. But yeah, I mean, you know, he didn't get to do his like he was his goal was to
sail out to X point and then make it back. And he not once I believe did he do it. But I mean,
you know, you want to just do to the weather and stuff. But anyway, that was that was a liberating
time in life. Just this is when the when when parents are away. The kids will play. Oh, that's
that's correct. That's correct. The way the way my life has worked proceeding. Yes, I hope you're
I hope you're having a like teen boner comedy style, like invite the whole neighborhood over for a
big rager and you surely have it all cleaned up by the time your parents get home. But then uh oh,
we're coming home early because the big the big deal fell through and we're coming home and we're
really poor now and we're really fucking mad. Anything, even our own blood, for example. All
right, love you. See you soon, son. The way my life has worked. This isn't like a new found sense of
like responsibility or like independence in a way since I more or less live a like a life away
from my parents in a way where I'm always upstairs and if I'm not upstairs, then I leave the house
that I'm not there and they don't really have really any influence over me directly. However,
it is nice to have to do like a menial labor for once because I don't interact with anything
outside my room. And so I don't clean it because I don't interact with it literally at all. If I
cook something, then I clean up the kitchen. But other than that, I don't do anything. Uh and so
it's it's it's sort of I don't know the word's not refreshing. It's not like I'm like super psyched
about invigorating. Yeah, I would say so. It's like I'm taking care of my space, you know, I'm
taking care. I'm a real human. This is my house currently in a way that I interact with it more
than I have previously. And I have to feed all the animals to clean up after all the animals and
take them on walks and stuff. And you know, and now you'll learn to hate them as I do. Oh no,
I already hate them been good. There's not a I like my dogs out, you know, on the street to the
moon if I had my way. You know, living on my own as I have for the past many years now, it uh I
think that what you're describing is something I'm a big fan of. And it's it's like when you're
when you're a millennial youth, you're growing up in your room and like, you know, generally
everything's taken care of for you. You know, you got your occasional chores you got to do. But I
mean, at least my experience is like, my dad took care of all like the big work and he would have
us help sometimes. And whenever we did it, like I resented it like I didn't want to do it. It sucked.
Hey, let's time to time to mulch the fucking yard again. Yeah, we gotta have new mulch because
that old mulch just isn't cutting it. You know, gotta gotta gotta gotta gotta hold the ladder
while I cut down a branch of a tree that I think is that I think is kind of ugly.
It's the dynamics that are interesting about that because I think once you like if parents go away
suddenly you have to fend for yourself and like everything like you're saying, it's a total
different way to look at the world. It's not that like all the clockwork machinery is just keeping
things going, which are your parents and society and whatnot. When it's up to you, suddenly you're
a man in a jungle, and you've got to intimately become acquainted with that jungle and know how
to get food and what to do. Yeah, and it gives you kind of a native of it. Elevate it reduces you
from a higher level like intellectual electronically based consciousness down to an
earthy like Native American style in tune with nature, groundedness, you know. In the suburban
household. That's correct, but there's definitely a pleasure in that. Using it as a part of it.
It's responsibility. You feel it feels more fun to clean up the mess that you made rather than the
mess that you know would be cleaned up anyway. Because there's a story behind this mess. You
can relive all this. It's not abstract like the reason to mulch those trees was completely
abstract. Completely I have no idea. Completely mystifying, completely resented having to do,
man. Yeah. Let me just go off on a rant about this. I would always be like, I'm like, I can't
fucking believe I hate having to mulch these trees every fucking year with this giant pile of mulch.
You got to put mulch around every tree. And then it's like, and I'm like, I'm grumbling about it.
And dad's like, hey, hey, you got a fucking, you know, you, hey, he's like, no, you don't want to
smile, please. Smile, smile about this, please. Yeah, I know you don't want to do it, but you're
going to see, you know, you're like, once it's done, you're going to appreciate, you know, the job
well done. And I'm like, of course I'm not going to. I don't understand how I don't understand,
I don't understand how you don't understand how I don't see the same value in fresh mulch.
You know, I love dear old dad, but I got to say, I think it was a, it was a,
not to criticize his parenting, but I think it was a tactical error to not, to not be, quote,
a good enough father to like, to just, to simply explain to us why this activity was important
to him, which I mean, you know, maybe he tried and just like got frustrated and gave up, but I
still don't understand. Yeah, there was like a, there was sort of a thing where like, he really
seemed not to grasp that we did not see the value in this, in this activity. Like if I, if I was,
when you, when like, my son turns like 18 or whatever, like I understand and I kind of enjoy,
like, you know, when I do the PCP pay every month or whatever, you know, generally try to get it
out on time, but like, there's a certain pleasure I take in it, but I could absolutely see, let alone,
like my children, when they turn 18, like dealing with their taxes, but like any of you trying to
like, you know, go over the facts and figures, you know, some of you can enjoy it. We have talked
about it on occasion, but like, I totally get how it's uninteresting busy work for a lot of people,
but I, I obtain some joy from doing it. So, you know, it seemed, it strikes me as something similar.
You got to, you got to touch like the foundational idea behind the activity itself. You can't just
say, throw these numbers together in this way or throw this fucking ground up wood under these
trees because there's some nebulous benefit to be obtained. You have to understand the motivation
behind it. I don't know. I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. Well, after you applied the mulch bin, did you pound
the pavement? Oh, I pounded that pavement. Oh, I was out there. Oh, I was walking the streets.
Okay. You may have pounded the pavement, but did you control your anger? Hardly. You mean my rage?
Oh, your rage. Yeah. Sorry. Did I control my rage? Occasionally.
Yeah. I threw a little bit. There were, there were, there were successes and failures in
the battering. Did you guys ever get into, okay, you guys, you, you whiteies have lived a life
completely alien to me in like a completely, completely free of all your post scarcity star
track in the future. Yeah. We've been living up in the Holy Land of Marizioa in our fucking
sap bubbles, breathing our pure holy air. Munchy doesn't get this reference, but these people
will. No, I have no idea. Yeah, I'm not white. I didn't watch the room then. Sorry. Okay. Anyway,
so, so you guys, how do we see that episode of Doug? Real quick. That just reminds me. Doug.
Sorry. That just reminds the real, I saw someone shitting on anime and being like,
look at all these white people. Like, why aren't we, why are we paying more attention to the black
characters in anime? And I'm like, these are like from Japan, dude. I don't know what's going on here.
Okay, anyway. That's the thing about it can't stand about anime. It's just too many white people.
Too many white folks in there. Yeah, that's fair. That's fair. Okay, anyway, so I assume you guys
have lived like a, like a, like a stereotypical, like 90s household experience. I imagine you
guys are just melting in the middle, but there are three mountains. You ever want to say it by the bell?
Yeah. That was me. Okay. That was us. I literally believe that. Did you guys start getting like
fights with your parents? Like altercations that like you scream at them? You mean physically?
Not physically, but just as in like, you got really mad at them and said like, I don't know,
like, I'm going to my room because I fucking hate you. Rarely, but sometimes. Yeah, I did a bunch.
I think Ben more than the rest of us, but I'm a bit more of a mediator. So
I found, I found a lot of dad's mannerisms to be completely infuriating. And yeah,
I flew off the handle a couple of times. One time once or twice, I like kicked a hole in the wall
and my punishment was that I had to like do all the labor and stuff associated with repairing
a hole in the wall, which was quite intense and definitely taught me a lesson about not doing
that. That seems like the perfect punishment for some of like. It was. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You ever
try to fucking plaster a hole in the wall? It's, it's an all day, it's an all day process. And
that's if you do it right the first time. Indeed, which I think you did not if I remember correctly.
No. Yeah. But the reason I ask is I've always had a pretty like independent
and like attitude for my mom, but like in a way that like not like as in like,
I'm not going to do what you say mom, but as in like basically since I've been like 10,
she hasn't really like told me to like, let me rephrase that. I don't have to fight with my mom
because she'll always like, she asks very little and like, you know, she's my mom. I'll just fucking
do it. You know, not really a big deal. I don't really mind. I've never had like a single like
fight. I've never screamed at my mom or like ever done anything to the effect of like, you know,
when I was like a real little kid, like sub 10, then I like pouted and stuff. Sure. But I've never
had the experience of like, I fucking hate my mom go like, you know, stomp up to my room and slam
the door. Well, you know, I think that that speaks to a lot. I think both your personality and your
mom's personality are probably an important factor in that. Like, I think Ben and I were a bit,
we were a bit of lay about children. We wanted just to hang out, watch TV and play video games.
I mean, if I, yes, please indeed, if I was growing up, I mean, I think about this. If I have like
lazy children, like I'm going to want to motivate them to do things and you know, get engaged and
I don't know, go socialize and whatnot, because it's good for them, whether they know it or not.
So like, you kind of got to be more on their ass. But then again, I mean, if you're just like,
I don't know if you can like make a person. I mean, I don't know if it'll be successful.
You can't really make someone do stuff that they don't want to do, at least not like consistently.
You know what I mean? Like, I do for them to like consist. If you want your kid to be such in such a
way, they're not going to, unless it's what they want. Like you can incentivize them as much as
you want, but you can't enforce that kind of thing forever. Well, tell me what you think about
this, because I've meditated on this issue about when it comes to rearing children and whatnot,
but it's like waterfall. Yes, indeed, indeed. Like, I don't think that a lot of the seeds that
specifically dad, like all the fucking lawn work and like the little tasks and I don't know,
like becoming Eagle Scout was very much like guided by my dad and he did a lot of the work
for me, basically, at least on my Eagle project at the end. And not even that, but like all the
tasks he had me do, all the chores and all the stuff we had to do over the years, which is,
again, I'm not complaining, totally fair. I feel like I was very much a lazy layabout kind of guy.
The chore, it was fair that we had to do stuff. I just couldn't stand his attitude. Well, the
attitude of like, we should want to do these things. I mean, I get that. I understand where it
comes from, because to him, these are things that have to be done. And like, you live here too.
Why don't you have the same, you know, get up and go attitude about accomplishing these tasks that I
do? That's disgusting. Like, it's not that I think it was wrong to ask us to do stuff. It's that he
was like annoyed and like angered sometimes by the fact that we didn't just want to fucking mulch
the trees on our own. I don't care if the trees get mulched. Well, okay, I mean, I understand your
point. But so that's the reason why I can I can discuss that. But like, but my point before I was
just making was just like, these fucking trees have dreams have nightmares or a mulching trees pound
in those weird pound in that pavement stakes and the weird stakes into like below the trees,
fertilizer stakes. You know, I've never even touched fertilizer in my life. But I can't imagine
you know, have you touched have you not touched poop, munchie? You know, and you have well, okay,
I mean, it's just like a disconnect like our dad, our dad really likes like grass, trees. Yeah,
you know, that's all the human core. You're in an urban jungle out there. So you would know about
this thing. You know, he loves all that he loves all that shit. I don't give a shit about it. Obviously,
our priorities there are different, you know, it's I guess it's unavoidable.
Nate, on one of the most recent rfck is that the last one, but the one before that I think
Ben describes how there were like contracts for chores in the house. And things like did the place
so hard. Like another another piece of the Nate jigsaw. Because you know, the point I was gonna
make about that was that I feel that when I was young, like until the time I was like
2021, up until that point, all the chores that my dad had me do enough stuff, I felt like it was
planting seeds. But it was when I finally moved out on my own. And like I was responsible for myself.
I kind of feel like all that like teaching from my dad blossomed. And it all like that's when it was
like, like I was prepared to like, you know, take out the trash, do the dishes, do my chores, pay my
taxes, be on top of my financial game, you know, make sure I was at work on time every day. And
like, I feel like I just kind of rapidly became an adult. And all the lessons that my dad had
been indirectly teaching by making me do these things and my mom too, but most of my dad,
like I felt like it paid off. And like I became that person, like as an adult only. And you know,
that that's I kind of think that's what happened to me. You know, in a weird way, I almost think the
opposite achieved the same result for me, where I would never like like doing the things that I
had to do, you know, when I did have to do chores. I did I did not have the, you know, the the immense
hatred that that Ben might have felt. But you know, what do you mean me? Why are you singling me out?
Well, neither of us liked mulching the trees. I mean, I guess you're more vociferous and you're
hatred, but hey, I'm just responding to you. Yeah, yeah. I think I kind of look back at all
these chores with a fairly rosy lens, because I like I think about them as like, helping me become
a more disciplined person. So even though I hated them at the time, I look back. I just remember
how annoyed I was by the attitude behind it all that fucking. It's like a such a boomer attitude,
honestly. I agree with you, Ben. But anyway, I I I always didn't want to do it. And so now that
I'm on my own, I don't think like it's not like as in like, I'm so unprepared for what life entails,
because like, it's not like, you know, this is not this is not rocket science here. You know,
I know it's really not that hard. It's really not. And so instead of it just being like,
what I think you might feel where it's like, you know, you just feel like you have experience doing
them and they sort of just turn into, you know, busy work that it's not really an issue. To me,
it's just like, well, how do I minimize suffering? Well, and then I think of ways to like, like,
what's the word like, I consolidate power and I make things more efficient for myself. And so for
instance, you know, I have like scheduled times to do things and I have specific ways I can do it
to maximize efficiency. And I just I just completely like locked down all the chores I have to do,
so that I can spend the least amount of time on them as possible. So my dislike for doing them,
it's not like I got mind break dosioned into liking doing dishes and stuff like that. But like,
I understand they have to be done. So I might as well do them for as little time as possible.
I mean, that's that's good as well. So I mean, are you basically saying that like your the approach
that like you were raised with was like, you were just given the freedom by your mom and your
instincts to just, you know, want to, you know, get things done so you can just be happy and,
you know, not worried about stuff. That's kind of what motivates you to do your shit. Yeah. Yeah.
Oftentimes, parenting can be like, you know, you can have like a desire and it won't have the
same way that you would want it to. It's sort of weird that stuff like this can be like, you can't
like both like, okay, your dad obviously instilled in you this sort of belief, probably intentionally
to give you this outcome. My mom didn't and yet I still got that sort of lesson probably not in
the same way or the exact specifics. It's hard to know how much of that was just you. And I mean,
again, it might have been nothing. It might have just been in me all along that just came out when
I got older or something. What do you mean by in you? You mean like, like, I mean, like, I notice
now that I approach like tasks and accomplishing things like very similar to how my dad did.
And like, we never we did talk about doing things that way. But I don't feel like that's
anything I learned from him. I feel like it's a kind of an innate way of approaching issues.
I feel I feel like a lot of the time it's it's not down to like a literal lesson, but you just you
just can't help but copy the adults in around you in your life. Yeah, that's why I do things.
Okay, I think it's probably a combination, but like you are his son. There's probably some sort
of like some what similar brain chemicals in there. And you know, he's your fucking dad,
you are random a lot. Obviously, some of that, you know, I would never say that like my dad's
teachings are obviously always going to be effective case in point, Ben. But you know,
I'm I'm much more like mom. I think so. Yeah, much more relaxed about life. You know what,
I'm happy with that. Well, that's good. I remember on one of the draw casts for monsters.
Unfortunately for you, Ben, a mom's penchant for shit. Wait, what's that thing when women
marry up? Mom's pension for hypergamy won't save you, Ben. You're in the rut. You got no way to go.
Well, I don't know. What the fuck does that mean? I mean, I was making a joke because mom isn't
actually hypergamous, but I don't know. Well, then marry Alexa. What a bizarre thing to say.
I mean, it is in fact simply inaccurate, but I thought it'd be funny. Anyway,
I mean, also, our dad is dead. I said the dad was dead before. Why aren't you on my ass about that
too, Ben? Okay, Nate, you're very consistent. I'll send you. Was that like an insult against mom or
something? What me? No, no, like saying, okay, you never mind. I just I just it's like such a like
esoteric joke to make. You know, I think so. Well, what a classic Nate's dad thing to say.
Oh, oh, God. Oh, and like Ben's like his mom's that that tendency would save me. I don't know,
but it won't save you because you're a man, not a woman. Okay. Yeah, that was that idea. Nate's
more like his dad. Ben's more like his mom. You guys are gonna have to pop out a baby real soon.
Oh, oh, Ben already had kiddie stone. He already went into labor once. We got ectobiology as hard
at work as we speak. Yeah, finally, you know, finally. What are we talking about? I would imagine
that I'm very uncomfortable. I imagine a baby between Nate and Ben would be like a lump of
coal or possibly some sort of like raw material that would be like use just fuel fuel and then
burn up. What the fuck? In what way would that be the result of our well, I mean, there's human
offspring. Well, okay, like it's like you didn't yank, right? If you didn't yank headed, baby,
probably just be some sort of like inert mass. Yeah, yeah, yeah, just some sort of like like
being that was not made to be sentient in any way. I mean, look at it me and Ben, I suppose,
as our mother and father's children, I guess they just either go one way or the other. I don't know.
Yeah. I feel like grace is more like you, Ben, and more like mom. But again, I don't know. Yeah.
Yeah. Not 100% if you had children. There would be basically your mother and father,
but as children. Yeah. I think we've got two moms and one dad out of this particular relationship.
You and me, Nate, we'll just have two babies and like one of them will have like a beard and be dad
and the other will be mom. It'll be like, you're gonna let a beard be dead. You know, in Lady in
the Tramp at the end when they have like a litter and like all the girl puppies look exactly like
Lady and all the boy puppies look exactly like Tramp. They're not a mix of the two.
No, no, no, no. Everything in its right place. Yeah, yeah. Separate but equal. That's my policy.
We keep the genes separate even when we interbreed. We just make sure the ones that aren't entirely
one or the other. We just we just dump them off a little bit. Really speaks to the myth of race
mixing, you know. But now I'm thinking of like your children being just tiny versions of you,
like a tiny Nate, like heat miser and snow miser. They're little puppets during the scene.
Real quick, am I remembering correctly? Did they ectobiologize at the end, like in the Homestuck
epilogue, just like a million combinations? Not in the epilogue. I meant the Snapchat thing. No,
no, no, not the epilogue. Like I remember seeing pictures of just like a million mixed up genes.
They use that to make the human race. Right. Based off of four template humans. Did they
use all eight or did they use just the four original ones? Probably all eight, right? I don't
know. Man, that's so fucking weird and kind of gross in a weird way. They're all like related.
They're all clones anyway. It's a fucking no, dude. I will say, by the way, just before we
transition off the being alone thing, I will say the worst thing about being alone is the fact that
my kitchen is still fucked. I think I talked about this on the PCP, but for like like a month, if not
more at this point, my action. No, yeah, more than like two months probably in what way? My
kitchen. Okay. Well, like, okay, there was something wrong with the dishwasher. I don't even fucking
know what, but we were having a perfectly fun functioning kitchen. They some repairman came
over to fix the dishwasher. And then there was sort of there's mold behind the dishwasher.
And so like smash fucking cut two weeks later, the entire kitchen ripped out cabinets,
dishwasher sink and fridge and like Island is gone. And there's an alien like quarantine ET
like like like hospital blinds around my kitchen. What does that have to do with being alone,
though? Wouldn't it be that way anyway? No, that's what I'm saying is that even though I'm alone,
I wanted I would like to like have cooked for myself. But now I like I have to like just order
out no matter what I would really just love during at this point to be home alone, you know,
I have to worry about anything. I can just go on downstairs and I have anyone, you know,
mess with me or try and talk to me or fuck with me and cook. But no, I'm robbed of that.
I've been I've been cooking. Actually, I know that cauliflower, that cauliflower pizza,
it sounds delicious. There was that. I made that maybe a week ago. And then I've been,
I went on sort of a spree, like I bought a bunch of like bulk shit from like Costco and I ordered
some stuff on Amazon that I couldn't find, just a bunch of like general like keto safe
ingredients. And I want to try the keto coffee, the bang keto coffee. No, no, no, not that,
unfortunately. I got I got a pound of raw cocoa butter, which is just like blocks of stuff.
Sick. I ordered a giant bag of like of desiccated coconut power desiccated coconut desiccated
unholy coconut. Imagine if you will a dark coconut. All right, here's what you have to do.
Here's the picture I want next week. PCP show notes. I want you sprawled out, you know,
on your bed. Just watch YouTube. Watch watching an Arlo video on your YouTube. You're drinking
bang. You're drinking bang keto coffee. Did I mention cooking Arlo's pizza recipe? Did I mention
that last episode? You're watching Arlo. You're kicking back a keto coffee and you're eating a
cauliflower banana pudding pizza. And that's your keto. It's your keto day. I'll mix it with
like sugar free banana like yeah, yeah, something. Okay. Yeah, I think I mentioned this last week,
but in case I didn't. Yeah, Arlo like was tweeting about like making low carb pizza. And I used
his recipe for a pizza crust and it was great. And I'm gonna do it again. The Arlo. I got I got
the bunch of coconut. Arlo would be great if he was a cooking show. If he had if he had like holds
a spoon and he goes through the little chef hat. Yeah, good. There's still time Arlo. We've got
notes to save you from your he's got nowhere to go but up. He's got room to expand. That's true.
Anyway, so this very morning. Okay, see, I realized something. I've realized that even
though I'm still doing keto, I haven't really been losing any more weight. I've only lost like
maybe three or four more pounds and maybe five pounds. Do you want to lose more? Are you are
you still I could I could use I could lose a little more, not too much more, but just a little
bit more. But I haven't lost any. So I decided that maybe I should actually start counting
my calories again. So I'm gonna do that. So this morning I woke up and I'm kind of hungry,
but I don't want to eat. I want to go back to the one meal a day thing because I was working out
pretty good. So instead of eating, I satisfied my lust for food by cooking food and not eating it.
So I made a so I made a I made fat bombs, which are basically just like fudge balls
that you put in the fridge. And I made a coconut flour.
Well, the recipe was for cupcakes, but I just cooked it into a whole cake.
I had to substitute heavy cream for coconut cream. That's unfortunate, but I had no choice.
I'll fix that. Do you plan to eat these later or this for fun? I will. I will. Yeah, I'll eat these.
Yeah, this is keto shit. This is keto shit, man. Now I'm set. You've heard of Kino shit time for the
keto shit. So so I've been, I don't know, I've been cooking more. I've been experimenting in the
kitchen and it's pretty it's pretty fun, I guess. It's because it's because the results are useful.
You see, I was very gratified, extremely gratified to buy all this shit. I spent like like more than
100 like 120 bucks buying these like big bags of shit. But I did it with like, this is going to
save me in the long run so much. If it's like if I'm buying like five pounds, I bought five
pounds of shredded mozzarella and I'm like, yeah, it's really expensive, but I'm going to eat it all
and it's going to save me in the long term because it's cheaper to buy in bulk. And I rub my hands
together and I was like, Oh God, I can't afford not to buy it. All the savings. I'm playing the long
game and it feels good. Well, that's good. We have been ordering far more groceries and eating
out far less than we used to. It's fairly rare. So I'm very happy about that. I don't know. We're
just getting groceries instead of eating out. So just a life upgrade, just a life upgrade.
Similar, similar. I started a, I signed up on Jewel.com to get my Jewel pods directly delivered,
which is actually much cheaper. Well, that's good. Significantly cheaper than buying them at the
fucking convenience store. And the best thing about it is that I can actually buy the good flavors.
So I got creme brulee. I got mango. I got cool cucumber. You know, I got everything a boy could
want. Well, that's great. But I'm a happy camper. I have not been cooking much. And I got to say,
if only I had the wisdom to get blue apron when I had the chance or whatever the fuck it was.
I could have been a God by now, Ben. You've divided your meat. Because I'm too dumb to look
blue apron. That's pussy shit. Hello, fresh is the fucking
blue apron is like the lift of fucking of cooking delivery.
I don't understand. What do you need it for? You just, okay, I'll tell you, I'll tell you exactly
why something in my head. And it's the same thing. You don't have to pay for it. I'm because I am not
a cook and I don't think about cooking. I need someone to force cooking on me on a day to day
basis that I will transition into a little baby. How about the fact that you don't have food?
It's called baby steps. What? I'm sorry, say again. I said, how I said, how about the fact that you
don't have food to force you to cook? Well, but we do. We've got some ingredients. We got some,
we got eggs, we got bread, we got exactly, exactly. So cook something with them. Yeah.
What do you mean? Yeah, I could do that, I guess. Yes, you could. Exactly. What about the thing
that you said you really liked that I could, like the eggs with the bacon and eggs combined?
I want that. It's so easy. You just fry bacon, you put eggs on top. I don't have that kind of
English bacon. I don't know where to get it. I assume the grocery store, but I don't know.
You just use the regular old American kind. I think it's just thick cut, isn't it?
Could I just, could one use normal American bacon in the same way and just cook the
grease into it and just keep it in there? Yeah. Okay, okay. I gotta give that a try.
Nate. That's keto, right? More fat, the healthier you are, as I understand it.
Keto gives you kidney stones, as well as energy drinks. Well, I'm down for some of those.
Okay, all right. Ben has gotten a kidney stone, right? Since this started?
But my whole thing is that everyone's like, oh, it's because of keto. Oh, it's because of energy
drinks. And nobody fucking knows. It could have been nothing. It's one data point that I'm taking
go to, but okay. It is one data point. Actually, there's a couple, but yeah. A couple contradictory
ones. If you're anything like me, Nate, you will go to your kitchen and think, okay, I got some
ingredients. I guess I could make something. I'm just going to make an egg. I'm just going to crack an
egg and that's it. There's no food here. It's all this worthless ingredients. What's a man to do?
Ingredients, ingredients everywhere and not a meal to eat. Having all of your ingredients just in
one place and having a specific recipe like mandated on to you means that you will want to make that
and it will be so often of a completely higher level than you would initially want to do. You
could make anything. You could make anything. Okay. I got the, I know the, here's the issue, Ben.
What's more fun? Tell me what's more fun, Ben, starting with a blank C plus plus file and saying,
I'm going to make a game and it could be anything or like firing up Minecraft and being like, let's
tool around here and like, you know, build a fortress. It's that disparity in my mind. I want,
but which one gives you the greater sense of life accomplishment? Well, I totally agree
that it's, but I got, I got other things to give me. As always, I work up to that. Ben, your
version, your version of these on such a visual level makes me so mad and I'm going to kill you.
I am. I really am just averse on a visceral. I really just see it as spending money on something.
You know, Ben, you are a cooking elitist is what you are, Ben. I'm a baby. I need baby steps.
I'm cooking elitist because I advocate that you should do it. That's correct, Ben. That's right.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Hello, fresh and stuff like this is always a stepping stone. As I've mentioned,
I don't get it anymore. I don't have a use for me. Well, you've evolved parts. Part of that.
But it's like, yeah, it's a stepping stone in, in, you pick, yeah, you get the stepping stone,
but meanwhile you're surrounded by like other perfectly good stones. No, you're not. It serves a
purpose. We've explained it to a thousand times. Google anything. Google. It has. Listen,
how would he know? How would he know any name of any food you can think of followed by recipe?
Hit enter. Done. You don't need blue apron. It's a matter of convenience. It's so convenient. Have
you ever heard of paying money to save time? That's what this is doing. Then you might as well just
fucking go out to a restaurant. You seriously might as well just do it the same shit. You can learn
the skill to apply later in the ways that you're advocating. It's just a stepping stone so that
you can learn how to cook better and then you won't have to rely on it anymore. This is such like
a weird, like false trichotomy. No. Okay. Yeah. You, you could cook to learn the skill, but you could
cook for free. So you're paying money to learn, you're paying. Listen, listen, shut up. You're
paying more money to learn a skill that you could learn for free. What's the fucking, like, I don't
get it. It's easier and I really think I really think what the money, the money that you are paying
is specifically so you don't have to do any thought work about what to buy, what recipes to
make. It's so easy though. And look, I know you might think that's dumb and like a waste of money
and I'm sure to many people it is, but you know, it's a convenience. That's all, that's all.
I see some value in that. I just, I just, you might as well listen. And you know what, maybe a
recipe comes up. No, no, no, here's the thing. Here's the thing. Here's the thing. Okay. Listen,
I got, not Blue Apron, I got, I was treated to the ingredients in a, what's the Hello Fresh,
in a Hello Fresh package. And like, I don't know about you, Nate, Munchy, but I don't think that
I'm ever going to cook, I don't think that I'm ever again in my life going to have the cause to
cook Frisco burgers with mango chutney ever again in my life. So I don't know if I did, I don't know
that I did learn about you. I don't think I, it's a game. Listen, it's, it's not that it wasn't cool,
it tasted good, but I'm never going to make it again. But you learn about that. Okay, okay, listen.
I learned to do a thing I'm never going to do again. Okay, okay, hold on, wait, okay. If you,
if you look up the ingredient, if you look up how to make something that you actually will make in
the future, then you've learned something. There's so much different that the experience is actually
making it. But you might as well just go to a restaurant for it. That's, that's the level that
you're dealing with. First of all, just having the experience to make a fancy thing if you want to
is inherently valuable. Also, I understand there are some Hello Freshers that are above like, you
know, I'm not going to do this every day. But there are vast swaths of like, okay, if I simplify
this even just a small bit, then I could easily see doing this often. For instance, there's a,
there's a lot of recipes that I would love to do. How fucking hard is it to learn to cook a hamburger?
You got to fucking subscribe to some mail-in order service for like $40 a month to learn that
shit? Are you kidding me? This is literally bullying. This is not bullying. It's retardation.
I feel bully. Ben, this is, it's, it's, how fucking, why do you need Hello Fresh to teach you how to
cook a fucking hamburger? I'm literally mad. I'm literally shaking right now. Yeah, that's hard.
We all need to claim the victim high ground, the climb as high as possible, like less than
mine. I got it. No one else can have it. Ben, you're right. It's more cost effective to not do it.
That's why the end goal is to not do it. This, it should be like a month, maybe two months at most.
And it's not that, like you're over, you're over, you're over, you're over stating how expensive
it is. It's not like it's a fucking like a king's ransom. How much is two months of Hello Fresh?
I don't fucking remember. I'll check. Throw me at a number. Probably like, if I recall correctly,
it was like $40 a thing. $40 wasted. $40 wasted. That's all I'm saying. You, okay. I'm serious.
I'm serious. But you get ingredients. Yeah, you get the ingredients. It's not wasted because I ate
everything. Okay. And we didn't have to buy groceries. Okay. Just, okay. I'm sorry. Just mostly
wasted. Well, okay. All right. I could have bought that mango for like 75 cents at the grocery store.
They probably charged me like 250 of each one. That's all I'm saying. That's all I'm saying. I'm
gonna go sign up for Hello Fresh right now. I fucking can't. I can't fucking abide it. It's,
it's, it's unholy. It's unholy. Look, we got my Hello Fresh experience was, was completely valuable
and it changed my life forever. And now I cook regularly. I'm, I'm, I'm willing to drop it.
Let me just say one final question. What is, what is hard and what is averse to you about
just Googling a recipe and then buying there's nothing adversity whatsoever.
That's the alternative. I have the answer. You've got to see what you've got to step into what my
life is like. I'm sitting here in my piss and my shit. And I just don't know what the fuck I'm
doing here. And I need someone to spoon feed me baby recipes. I don't understand what it is. I don't,
I don't even know, Ben. I'm terrified. I'm terrified at the very idea of thinking about
what food to make. This rocks me to my core and that's where I'm coming from. Wait, Ben,
any old fucking thing, there's, there's more to it. There's more to it than just it having a recipe
for you. It is completely coddling. Hello Fresh and everything is baby-fying cooking for you
as baby steps. And here I sit a baby in my piss and shit. Listen, wait, no, no, wait, no, let me
finish. Let me finish. It babies you. It gives you recipe with extremely clear like picture book
X like pop up book baby shit recipe steps. It sends you all of the ingredients and like that's
twofold at what it says with the green so you don't have to go to the grocery store. Also,
it sends you the ingredients as like a ticking like clock timer, like a bomb that will go off
if you don't want to waste the food. Like it's here. You have to cook. You cannot avoid this.
You can't just have like stuff, you know, random shit in your fridge and like, oh, you know,
I'll cook it. Like, you know, one of these days, I'll Google how to do a recipe, you know, I'll
just do it sometime, you know, in the future at some point. I'm saying, I'm saying do it now.
I, but if you have Hello Fresh, then you're forced to do it. It's literally not like it's not an
option to not do it unless you just hold hostage by your own volition. And it's great. It's what
I want. Listen, I got this bag. I got like a four pound bag of coconut flour. And I'm like,
what the fuck do I do with this? So I go on the internet and I Google keto coconut flour recipes.
I find this recipe, I find this recipe for coconut flour cupcakes. And the ingredients are like,
it's like mix this shit, microwave this shit, mix it in, put it in a pan and wait an hour.
Okay. And that's it. I know I'm not cooking is not difficult. People are scared by cooking more
so than they should be. But okay, before I started Hello Fresh, I had basically not cooked
whatsoever in my entire life. I did not know how to cook a steak. Last time I tried to cook a steak
before Hello Fresh, I literally like like burnt my hand like sticking the steak into boiling oil.
I was that level of incompetent. I did not know how to do anything. Hello Fresh saved my marriage,
satisfied my wife. It fucked her for me. I didn't have to do anything. It was super convenient.
It was just what I needed. I got to apologize. I realized that I'm arguing from a position
of privilege. And I, you know, I'm privileged to be competent at things and I can't sometimes I
have trouble empathizing with those that aren't. I appreciate you acknowledging that. So I'm gonna
check my privilege right at the door. Enjoy some nice keto fat bombs later on in the day
and just feel sorry for the lot of you. That's my plan. That's my new plan for this Easter Sunday.
It's not for everyone. I wouldn't even, I don't even know if I would say that like,
I recommend it as like a blanket thing. All I'm saying is if you're intimidated by cooking
and you are able to pay for it comfortably, because it's not that much, then you can do it for like
a couple weeks, think, okay, this isn't that bad. And then stop. It's not like I'm advocating to do
it forever or even for a long time. You can do it if you think any of this sounds valuable to you.
You could eat, you could do it online. It's not, not valuable. I'm just saying it's reasonable.
And I'm just saying you could do that or you could do literally the same thing for free. Okay.
It's not, why do you think it's the same thing? That's all I'm saying. Let's, let's move on. We
have to move on. Listen, that's all I'm saying. We've got to move on. That's all I'm saying. Okay,
here we are ready for this talking prompt. Okay, here it is. Okay. Two diametrically
opposed quotes. Okay, here we go. Reggie fees him a from Nintendo quote, the game is fun.
The game is a battle. If it's not fun, why bother? Okay, that's Reggie. Other man, Neil
drunk, asked for context, or are you deliberately leaving out content? Well, it was, I don't know,
who's talking about his conceit of making video games. That was the idea. Oh, the making of the
game is a battle or rather like, why? I think he was talking about Nintendo games in general. And
he's just like, you know, if the game's not fun, why bother? Was the, was the, see, okay. All right.
Now, juxtapose that with Neil Druckman of Naughty Dog. I don't know if he's CEO or whatever. Here's
the, here's the quote. It's, we don't use the word fun. That's the full quote. And specifically,
that was in reference to the development of last of us two. They don't use the word fun. First of
all, who the fuck would say that when you're developing a video game? That's just the most
pretentious shit what the problem is there at all. Yeah. I mean, I mean, I think it's weird that
Naughty Dog would say that, but I don't think last of us and stuff. I mean, last of us is a
shooter. That's fun. It's just, I don't know. The word cucked really comes to mind when I think
about this. What do you, what are you talking about? Imagine making video games and not having
your primary goal being it being fun. That is so hard. You fucking fool. Survival horror games.
They're not fun. They're stressful. Sion Hill 2 is super fun. And well,
well, dot, dot, dot. I mean, it is fun. Horror games are not meant to, I can't even,
I fully agree. I fully expect you to be like, well, obviously you're right, Ben, but what I
meant was dot, dot, dot. Like games don't have to be fun. Games are an art form. Games can evoke
any, any emotion you want. They can have any message. We don't have the expectation that movies be like
fun. They can experience the full range of human emotion and we'll still have enjoyed
experience. Okay. All right. You know what? You know what? I realize all of a sudden this is
dumb because everything here hinges on the definition of the word fun. And it wasn't an enjoyable
experience. Like you like, I found Silent Hill 2, for example, a notable, very much liked horror
game, a very enjoyable experience. Like, I don't know. Like does, does unraveling the, the narrative
pathos of the tragedy of, I forget the name of the character, James is like psyche and all the
horrors. Like is that fun? I mean, I found it very enjoyable to play through. So I could call that
fun. You know, I guess I'm sure people would say the same about like Last of Us and Last of Us 2
when it comes out. Maybe Naughty Dog is taking a page out of Garfield Itz's book and they don't
talk about fun. They talk about entergagement. Do you guys know about Garfield Itz? Oh, of course.
Of course. I'm not sure. I'm not sure if I'm following. Did I talk about, okay, well, there is an app
and I think it is currently only available in Saudi Arabia. But it is, well, no, no, I think, I think
it was in one of the countries below Saudi Arabia that I could be wrong. We continue. All countries
are below Saudi Arabia, but go on. But it is Garfield Itz and Garfield Itz is an app that lets
you order a Garfield shaped pizza, comma, a lasagna, comma, or a Garfield themed coffee.
And then while you wait, you can play Garfield themed mobile games and read Garfield comic
strips and watch the old Garfield cartoon show. And there is fucking videos of Jim Davis, the man
himself on the website talking about the core concept behind Garfield Itz, which is a concept
called entergagement, a combination of entertainment and engagement. That's fascinating. Garfield Itz
is entergaging fact. I mean, that's that's kind of an interesting idea to like keep people on
this app that's or for ordering food and then it also has games embedded in it.
Interesting. Yes. Good. Capitalist nightmare. Absolutely.
If you'd please direct yourself to the Garfield Itz website, which will you'll start scrolling
and you'll start thinking, haha, this is really funny. And then the God awful music will start
playing and you'll just like scramble to the volume mixer and fucking have a herney in the meantime.
Garfield Itz's catchphrase slogan is love me, feed me, don't leave me. It's the neat. It's the
neediest app of all time made by a disgusting man who photoshopped his own mouth to be tiny and dull
like because maybe that's cool. It's Saudi Arabia or something. I don't fucking get it.
The head manager is this is a guy who like just like he talks about how much he loves Garfield
and he has a small mouth because he purposely tries to Photoshop his mouth and all the in all
the Instagram if you go if you go to like his uh personal Instagram all the pictures of his face
his lips are like shrunk to make him look more attractive question mark. Huh. Yeah. Okay. Well,
that's cool. It's what it's allies with this man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Well, the guy had
like the idea for the app and then he went to Jim, I think. Okay. And Jim was like entertainment.
Like, is entertainment not in and of itself? If you are entertained, are you not also engaged?
I mean, you'd think so. But I mean, maybe I would keep you that way. Like, I would think so.
Like, I mean, this app almost holds you hostage. It's like the it's like the message. It's like the
rallying cry for to use this app is like, come be ensnared in our corporate web, like have your
focus have your focus diverted to our IP. Well, you know, man, that's interesting because I that's
kind of how I think about like MMOs in general, which is why I've never really gotten into one.
So people, you know, depending on the quality of it, people are willing to sign up for that
shit. Well, yeah, yeah, but they don't say it like that. Well, yeah, I mean, yeah. Okay, fair enough.
They don't talk about like, like the hot this hot new MMO is going to enter gauge the shit out of you.
Well, you know, I might be tempted. They might say, you know, I'm going to be immersed and,
you know, I'm going to get my Pete Garfield shape lasagna delivered to me or immersed. I don't know.
You know, it's the talk about like immersion, talking about like, you know, adventure or
whatever, like those words are like, they're trying to sell like how fun, how much fun you'll
have, how cool it'll be, a word like enter gaugement, which is like, prominently featured on the
Garfield eats advertisement. Yeah, no, it's like, it's like naked business naked business talk,
like right out front. Guys, can you can you even like it's palpable. It's inside base. It's inside
baseball brought outside into the day. The markup they can charge on a pizza that they fuck up the
dough on and make slightly like like implied Garfield ears by just like not creating the dough
correctly and like, like making a little bit misshapen. The markup is like $4. It's I'll pay,
I'll pay, I'll pay extra to be enter gauge. I'll pay extra to have my pizza suck shit, please.
Yes. I mean, I think about like, what makes me like, please misshape my pizza. I'll give you
anything. I'll fucking order it from any app. I'll pay any amount. Please make my pizza not a
circle. It's like think about Garfield for one extra second of my life while I cut off his fucking
ears to devour. I should mention that's like the delivery of the like, like the Garfield eats
delivery service, like they all get delivered on like eco friendly green like scooters. Oh, yeah,
like they have like a fleet of Garfield eats scooters that is like going around fucking
Dubai or whatever. You know, when I was in Japan, pizza was kind of a luxury item there. And like,
I don't everything's really condensed. So like there's this tiny little pizza shops,
but you see outside of them, like in Tokyo, you'll see like a fleet of little buggies
that are like that's how they deliver pizzas in Tokyo. I mean, that's just that's just that just
seems efficient. Also, the pizzas are tiny, but that's that's Japan. They're like that in Italy,
too. Italy, pizzas are like a like a personal thing. They're not for it. But it's Italy. What
are they doing? They every pizza should be twice the size through the through the sheer. What's
that like the the geographic boost, like the stat boost to be a whole team, a whole team
advantage like stab stab stab type, you know, advantage. They just don't see differently.
It's it's a change in perspective. I guess it's not it's not communal engagement. Italians hate
the family. They're trying to actively destroy it. Yeah, you know what they say about Italy,
when you're here, you're not family. Hey, but on this game subject, though, like, okay, I'm thinking
about a game that I love right now, Sekiro. And I'm like, why do I play Sekiro? What am I getting
out of it? Specifically with Sekiro, it's like two main things. One is like the sheer joy of
exploring the environment, because it's totally sick. And the other thing is like, like, obtaining
mechanical competence and overcoming obstacles, especially in flashy and impressive ways. So,
so, you know, that that's pretty sick. But like with an MMO, like, I guess you definitely get
both of those things as well. But there's also like, I don't know, when people talk about like
VR and like wanting to immerse themselves, I get like almost scared of the idea of getting immersed
in like a VR world. I want a clear, defined line between me and the virtual world. Have you well,
have you have you used a Oculus Rift or something? Have you used a VR headset? Only like once at
Bronycon for like, oh, yeah, yeah, that that was rainbow dash flying around or something. That was
my first time using one, too. Well, you know, I have I have an Oculus Rift. Yeah. And, you know,
it's not it's it's not like you don't know there's a screen. Well, sure. Sure. So I don't know. Well,
I'm more questioning the the motivation doesn't concern me. What do you mean? Well, like, like,
I mean, with this with this quote here from our boy, Druckman, you know, like, we don't use the
word, but like, yeah, it's interesting to think about which game he's talking about. Well, he's
not talking about like, you know, some like you could imagine VR or whatever being used for like
just to create like an environment you can like explore and walk around or something like it's
just cool in some way. Like that may or may not be defined as fun. But he's talking about Last of
Us 2 specifically. And like, I don't know, like that game I would imagine is fun. And like, isn't
it fun to like get a sick headshot when you're down your last minute and you know, you got to make
the primary goal. So they thus they don't talk about the word fun.
I mean, I guess that's not their primary ethos when developing the game.
You know, honestly, I think probably their their ethos of it was probably like, you know, immersion,
engagement. Yeah, maybe. Intergagement in a way. Intergagement, you know, building tension.
Which, you know, might have the side effect of fun. Well, at what point does it become like a
primary focus? And what point is it just a side effect? I mean, they're making the game. They
know what it's going to evoke in people. They do testing and whatnot. Do they though? I mean,
I mean, they made Last of Us 1. Death of the Author, baby. You know, it kind of doesn't matter
what their ethos is. If like the end product comes out as something people want to experience.
I mean, whatever they call that fun or not. You know, honestly, this is a semantic argument. I
could, you know, I could rail and whine and bitch and virgin rage about his usage of the word fun
in this particular way. But ultimately, I mean, I would argue that I think you're trying to make
the game a little bit fun, dude. So that seems a little strange to me. But you know what? Who gives
a fuck? Oh, it's part of the problem. Okay, it's part of the problem to you that it's like,
like, you're trying to make the game fun. Like, like, are you like, like, obviously, that must
be something that means to be sub numbered in your calculation. So are you trying to say that you're
not making it fun to appease other people? Is that what you're suspecting that he's trying to be like
hoity toity and not like like be like games are an art and we're not about fun here. We're about
telling a story. Yeah, is that where the end comes from? Yeah, my my my gaydar flares when I hear,
you know, things of that nature. So yeah, so yeah, I have multiple gaydar various strikes. I mean,
you know, it is for a company like Naughty Dog to say that I mean, they made like Jack and Daxter,
right? But times have changed, you know, I guess times have changed. But still,
yeah, still that that's not the company I would think of to say something. I would mean, I would
think of like, you know, maybe someone like Jonathan Blow might say something like that.
Yeah, yeah. But I mean, like, what are the guy who made papers, please? When I played,
what are those Nathan Drake? What are those games, you know, explore uncharted when I played the
uncharted to only and like the whole time, those are definitely meant to be fun. Oh,
yeah, that's true. But like, when I was playing that, I felt like this is this is kind of weird,
like this game is a little bit too close to like a Hollywood movie that's not that great. And like
also like the controls like aren't super fun. So like, I feel like the the goal of that game was
just totally not what someone like me, like sure, it looked beautiful. And like, I don't know, I'd
rather just like watch a movie than play that particular game. I have never I have, I have
never played an uncharted. Yeah, I listen to like reviews of the whole, God, was it was it super
bunny hop or someone? Yeah, someone did like a big like a big like series of reviews about the
whole series. My impression is that playing one of those is basically just like a a like watching
an Indiana Jones movie, but like, you're hitting the buttons to make it happen. Yeah, yeah. And
which is very weird. And yeah, it does kind of seem like the antithesis of what I want in a game,
because I'm all I'm all about fucking, you know, action and like I'm all about like
platforming and like twitchy reflexes and enter the gungeon and down well and stuff that that's
my jam. I'm I like my I like my games, gamey. Same please. But I but I mean, I just suppose
that the sort of I don't think I don't think it's invalid, like I don't think that game. It's not
invalid, but I guess it makes me feel that like the the category of what makes for like triple
a great top of the line game like that. That's really widened. And maybe games like Final Fantasy
Seven are like responsible for you know, I mean, it was it was a big one along those lines. Although
the game that game was gamey as fuck. But it'd be it'd be foolish to not address the FMB creep.
Which game? Final Fantasy Seven, Final Fantasy Seven. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. That was a big
was a big boost and all that shit. And look where it's landed screenix now in the shitter,
I would say in many ways, in many ways. I don't know games are complicated. It's weird.
Video game consoles are weird. Like I have to like consoles are weird and I don't like like
they're a computer. But PS5 was just announced. Yeah, they're a very limited streamlined computer.
PS5 was just an I think like documents are released. Who fucking cares at the PlayStation
PlayStation sucks, dude. It's all about the GameCube. PS4 is doing I think it's leading. I think
it's like winning the console war currently. The console war is like you like okay, you pop out
two you'd pop out three babies, you put them in a pig pen and you was like come back three years
later like oh, who won? Oh, I guess this baby won but he's still corpse. You know, it doesn't
matter. They're all dumb and I hate them. Consoles are like 600 bucks now, right? Well,
600, but they're expensive. Yeah, like consoles being as expensive as they are,
I kind of don't understand why we aren't just why we aren't just playing on PC. Yeah, I think
I think things are moving more and more that way. But I don't know. There's a lot of console
loyalists out there. Something like the switch like the switch brings something to the table.
And I know I don't have a switch, but I know everybody loves this. I have a switch and it
almost turned me away because it was extremely is way more expensive than I wanted to pay for
something. Yeah, because for the amount that I that I knew I would use it and continue to use it
now. But ultimately, I think it was worth it. But like a play station where it's like the reason
like the switch is because I can play it, you know, outside the house or anywhere like tucked away
and warm and cuddly. Exactly. I'm all about getting up and like turn on my TV to play a video game.
No one's got time for that shit. And that would be the most uncomfortable experience of my life.
I would hate doing that. I would never want to pay $400 to like turn on my TV. That's a nightmare
I can't abide by. I've just got a super powerful, you know, video game machine,
aka my computer that I just played Sekiro on brand new game. It runs like a dream and is fantastic.
And my computer is great. So it's not a problem. But sitting above it, I've got my ps4, my ps3,
my switches to the left. I mean, I got them because like, I don't know, had to play Bloodborne.
So had to buy a ps4. But for how long? For how long is the question? I'm surprised we're still
doing the console model. Honestly, it's weird. Yeah, I don't get it. I don't get why we have an
all transition. I mean, the weird thing that's happening now is like, have you heard about
like the Epic Store is rising as a real arrival to steam? I have heard of it. And I don't know
what it is. It's basically, you can just think of it like steam only, like they are much stauncher
gatekeepers of what content gets onto their shit. Because they kind of they make more of a pomp and
circumstance about which games get on there. They're like, wait, what are they? Are they selling
PC games? Like, are they basically just steam? Yeah, yeah, that's right. That's right. Okay. Okay,
Nate, why do people hate steam? I mean, I can tell you why I personally hate steam. And it's
because it is so I don't know how to use it. And it's so fucking hard every time. It's like weird
to like find games. And I don't know, maybe I'm not a PC genius. If I don't understand, if you know
what you're looking for, it's not hard to find a game. You know, that's probably true. I have been
plagued by confusion and issues with using steam for years. Maybe I know, I know, I know, I know
that I know that steam has a lot of like shit on it. But like, you don't have to buy. Yeah, you
don't have to wait. Okay, hold on. Okay, Nate, that's so contrary to my steam experience. Here's
I just did this to test to make sure I click on the steam app. It opens up. And I and I it's
literally one click away from being in a game not as into type over the games list. I mean,
you just have a list of all the games I own immediately upon pressing start. I might just
be an idiot. All right, let's do a challenge. Wait, wait, wait. Okay. Yeah, I don't I actually I
don't get what you don't understand about using steam. I do it does annoy me that all my steam
games have to open steam and like games won't run if I'm not online because that's annoying for
sure. Yeah, that is horrible. And I hate it. But like, what do you mean? That's stupid. Okay, it
shouldn't be the case mandatory, but it doesn't bother me at all. I mean, it does bother me. Okay,
but I've just learned to live with it at this point. I mean, I guess that's okay. Let's do a test.
Name a game on steam. What's a game on steam? I probably don't have to. Oh, are you talking about
buying games? Hattiful boy. Oh, okay, wait, okay. I'm gonna go try to buy this right now. I'm not
going to. I'm gonna see if I can do it. All right. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, you know what?
Nate, stop, stop. Of course you don't do that yet. The search bar issues with like the library.
Look, I know I had like my parental thing was like locked on for some reason. I couldn't get to my
Okay, here's what we're gonna do. Okay, okay. Okay, I'm gonna close steam. You close steam too.
I'm gonna time us and we're gonna see how long it takes me. This is so this is so fucking dumb.
You just you just type the name and you find what's the problem? We're gonna see. We're gonna see.
We're gonna see right now. What's the name of the game again, Ben? Hattiful boyfriend. Okay.
Hattiful boyfriend. All right. All right. Start the timer now. I'm starting up steam right now.
Here I go. Yep. It was closed. It's updating. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Updating for available updates.
All right. Gonna do this for 45 minutes. That's fine. All right. So we'll just we'll wait. We'll
see what's passed. No, I can still wait. 14 seconds in. 15 seconds in. I got it.
I'm searching the store. Okay. I'm there. It's still updating for me. Hattiful. I see it right
there. Okay. I'm at the page. I see there's a there's a bird. That's the bird. Okay. And I'm
still updating on add to cart. And where do I purchase for myself? I'm clicking on it.
And okay, I'm at the place where I can now buy it. Okay. So that's it. That was that was 30 seconds.
So what was the problem? Okay. The problem may have been some reason I have had like my parental
like limit on on steam for like years. And I don't know why and I did fix this the other day.
But it's just given me a real sour taste in my mind. I can only imagine. But you know what?
You're free now. I guess I'm free now. I suppose that's true. But I just feel I don't I don't
trust this. Like the birds and hatch a full boyfriend. This feels like a false sense of
security. This this bird's cold gaze looking at me. I feel like at any moment, it's real. It'll
betray me. He means every word. I feel like I've been here before. But I guess we'll see. I guess
we'll see. You felt this way before. So. Okay. Well, the point is steam. You know, a lot of
I don't I don't understand this. I know that a lot of like, particularly,
uh, well, I guess I'll just say, you know, like left wing ish, like free anti free speech kind
of people are like one, they don't like the Twitter allows a lot of hateful rhetoric on Twitter.
And then similarly, I think that same crowd also doesn't like that steam lets like unsavory content
on it. Like that's what like, like, like school shooter simulator and, you know, stuff like that
or, you know, like all the sex dojin stuff. Yeah, I from what I understand, those people
don't love that steam lets a lot of, you know, that kind of things on air. I don't care. Let
everything on. I don't give a shit. Okay. I know some people make an argument that like the crap
covers up the good stuff, whatever, don't care. Anyway, so Epic store exists. And some people
are making the jump because steam was the only party in town for a while. Wait, hold on. I want
to touch on that. Sure. For the crap to cover up the good stuff, you'd have to be on steam,
like, which I guess that's how some people use it. Actually, you know what, I have done that
because there were like, like, at some point, I would occasionally just jump on steam and look
at what's on sale. Yeah, that's the issue. I guess they're talking about just scroll through the
really cheap stuff. And yeah, there is a lot of like, really bad, like completely amateur hack
shit that I don't know why it's on there doesn't bother me at all. Actually, that's how I found
that's how I found Lisa the painful. Oh, there you go. I was just going through like cheap
shit on sale on steam. I mean, and I found and I found Lisa on sale for like $2.99,
and I thought the trailer was cool. And it was fucking great. Yeah.
Like does not impact me whatsoever, even one bit. It just means there's more options on the
platform. It does not obstruct any of the views. If you know, possibly like all it takes is like
like we just did with our wonderful exercise just now, if you know the game you're looking for,
it couldn't be easier to find you simply search for the game. And it's either there or it's not
if it's like not on steam or whatever. So yeah, so I mean, there's nothing to cut through there.
It's cool that people who don't like it have an option now, but I just never understood why people
don't like it. Hi, Tom Oliver here, world renowned video game creator and editor of this
Procrastinator's podcast. And there's really only so long I can sit here listening to these
fucking idiots talking about video games out of their asses. So I'm here to set the fucking record
straight and save this episode from heaps of criticism in the comments. First of all, the
console market exists primarily for two reasons in this day and age. One is cost and two is barrier
of entry. Even if consoles cost $600 now Ben, which they don't their 300 bucks across the board
are probably going to drop in price within the next year or so as the next generation of consoles
are announced. The reason that this market exists and this cost is important is because PCs to play
games at the same level of consoles are more expensive to build a PC right now in the mid range
that can adequately play games is about $500 to $600 for decent components. And that's not
including a Windows license, a display and then decent peripherals like a mouse, a keyboard,
and a gamepad. Put that all together, you're in the $800 plus range to get set up on PC,
as opposed to a $300 box that plugs into your TV you already have. So it's much cheaper for the
average person to just buy a PlayStation and not think about it for five to 10 years, as opposed
to building a PC and then having to upgrade the components constantly every couple years to be
able to play at decent settings. The second reason for consoles kind of builds off of that.
No pun intended. Building. To get a PC at a respectable price, you have to build it because
you're going to pay extra to have another vendor build it for you, whether it's a big company like
HP or Dell or a smaller vendor like CyberPower or iBuyPower or what have you. So if you want to
build a PC that takes much more skill than just again going to Best Buy, paying a single price,
getting a console, putting it on your desk and forgetting about it for the next 10 years. So
for these two reasons, consoles are around to stay because they're easier to get into and for
most people they cost less. Now for the Epic Games Store, this is really less of a problem with
consumers and more of developers versus consumers because consumers like Steam. Steam's been around
for like 10 fucking years now. Everybody has a huge library on Steam. The platform from a consumer
standpoint is very mature. It has all the features you'd want, wish list, shopping carts, user reviews,
a big community feature. Steam is established and people like Steam and users. However, because
they allow everything on the platform for the most part with very little curation, new developers
coming in who want to kind of like have their shit be noticed is very difficult because
dozens and dozens of games release on Steam every day. So unless you've built up a huge
presence on social media outside of Steam, you're not going to have a lot of people finding your
game. The onus really falls upon the developer to build up hype for themselves. The value of
publishing on Steam is not as big as it once was because everybody can just fucking do it.
You know, before in the beginning, if you were on Steam, you were on the big platform that not
everybody could get into. And so the clout of just being on Steam was a reason to be there in and of
itself. Nowadays, since everybody and can just asset flip on Steam, it doesn't mean shit, which
means you the developer have to work harder to get noticed outside of that platform to build an
audience before you even launch. So you're going to have any success on Steam anyways, because the
majority of your games sales happened within the first three days of release. So if you're releasing
with 50 60 100 other games at the same time, and you haven't built any presence outside of Steam's
launch, you're fucked. This is why Epic Games is targeting developers making all these deals to
bring in big high end games to be exclusive on this epic game store for six months to a year,
because that's going to bring in consumers, people who end up buying games. And it's also
attractive for smaller developers, maybe not one man studios, but smaller dev teams to go
onto the store that has less noise and a better chance of their game being seen by the public.
Now, Epic and steam aren't the only names in the game. You also have origin, you have you play,
and you have Gog. Gog is really good because they don't have any DRM or anything. But another
interesting player for small indie guys is Discord. Discord is trying to build their own
publishing service. And they're integrating it with Discord communities, which lots of small
development teams already have. So there's tons of players in this game right now. And it's going
to be really interesting to see over the next couple years how everything pans out. Epic does seem
set up to be the big new player that's going to be able to actually give steam a run for its money
and might actually end up being the de facto players because 10 cent who own so much of Epic
has so much cash to throw around, they can keep just getting all these exclusives. So the next
like 12 to 24 months is really going to be interesting because Epic has the exclusives,
but has none of the features that people from a consumer standpoint really enjoy about steam.
But at the end of the day, people are impatient and want to play their games. And when Borderlands
3 drops, you bet your ass is going to be a huge spike in Epic Games installs that day.
That's all I have to say. Get back to the podcast, patreon.com,
such as Polystation 2. If you want more commentary about games, that's actually informed.
Well now, now the world that we're arriving in is a world where like instead of having a bunch
of consoles, what we might find in the years to come is a series of icons of different online
game stores on your desktop. That's less bad. I mean, it's just probably annoying that I have
to deal with that. It is the biggest issue. You just kind of know which platform it is. I mean,
as long as it doesn't cost me anymore, I don't care. Like for my own convenience, I would sure
like if everything was in one place. But again, if I consider myself a relatively educated consumer
here, I will know what games I want to play and I will go find them. But you know, I find myself
at times, like your lease experience there, there's times when you're just looking for a game and
you know, you'd want the quality curated so as you don't waste your time. And at those times,
I have been frustrated by the like swaths of totally amateur like crappy visual novel shits for
99 cents. But like it's weird to think that like deals. It's weird to think that the solution to
this problem is ban more things from Steam or you know, don't let them hold on. Hold on. It's not
we're not talking about banning. It's a question of curation. I mean, of like quality of like,
like they're a company. And like to you might argue that like their, you know, values or their,
you know, their quality standards are reflected in the products that they're willing to, you know,
host on through their platform. I mean, sure, sure. That's true. But like, let's just accept
the reality that there are games who that are there on Steam now that as this progresses may
not be there anymore. And I mean, I would argue that's a bad thing. I'd want them to be available.
I don't know if they'll get promoted. Nate, I mean, they're not, they're a publisher. They're
not obligated to publish everything. Like every publisher has to choose like, what do we want?
Like what's good enough? What do we want our brand to be associated with? Well, I mean,
that's choose what to publish and whatnot. That's certainly true. I just simply want the
availability of every game somewhere. And I mean, again, like for me, it's just the most
convenient thing. Well, yeah, but not through, I mean, you're arguing that a privately owned
company should be obligated to publish everything? Well, first of all, I never said that. I did not
take that position. That's what you just said. I mean, no, that's not true. Maybe you're trying
to follow my logic through to what you think is the conclusion. I mean, look, they're a private
company. I can't force them to do anything. That's the end of the story. But you didn't
talk about what you wanted me to do. You want them to publish everything. Here's what I want.
I want someone I don't care who to make every game available in one place for my personal
convenience. That's what I want. But I'm aware that that will not happen. So there's no even
point telling me it's dumb. I get it. That's the end. That's the end. Every every game includes
some shit that some kids shout out in their fucking beginner programming. Yeah, so just have
those be, you know, on the platform. So I have to search them out if I want to get them. But you
know, why do you why do those have to be on a platform? Those things can be like those things
can be available for my convenience is why that's why for my simplicity. That's the only reason.
Well, but as long as the game plays, that's all I get like whatever. It's just a portal.
That sort of flies in the face of like what it is to be a publisher.
But okay, well, why is it that I mean steam themselves took the look there. I know that
that's changing recently seems to be mostly due to market out like, you know, consumer outcry or
whatever. But like remember when steam took the position that like, we're just going to allow
everything that doesn't like break the law or whatever. Like they already did this. I'm just
saying that I liked that. I thought that was good. So you know, I know that I really like I
don't understand. Okay, I love I like the fact I literally enjoy the fact that like, you know,
not polished games can get on to steam. Because I like the fact that there can be like, you know,
it's like a big old, it's a big old marketplace that term implies a lot. But I don't really mean
like that. But it's like, you know, it's a big old space, where even even maybe some of the
unpolished, maybe some of the amateur stuff can rise to the top. If you know, if it's if it's good
enough, people reviewed enough, I think that's cool that you can be independent and it can and
it becomes successful. I don't want quality crowded out, obviously. But I mean, that strikes me as
just like, you know, like, I would put the curation in the like, what's promoted, like what, you know,
maybe like user votes or something or staff picks or, you know, I would use things like that to
put things to the top. That's, you know, that's that's what I'd like. But then if I want to play
some bullshit, then I just type in the name and no, it's weird. Yeah, it's we I don't really
understand steam because like it's not they don't just allow everything. And yet some of the some
of the cruft that is on there seems like it could only be there if they just allowed everything.
Are you talking about low quality games or like, you know, like questionable content sort of?
No, I'm talking about low quality shit. I'm talking about shit that just seems like incompetent.
I think steam will allow anything that fucking runs and like passes their generic like, you know,
green light test. Well, I think they've changed their process a lot. Like, I mean, I think getting
on to steam used to be a bigger deal. And maybe maybe it is that now, I think now it's like,
to get on steam, you have to you have to pay like maybe $100 like application fee or something.
And then and then I think it might be a community thing, like you need a certain number of votes
on green light or something. So now maybe it is that literally anything can get on there as long
as it has enough like community support or whatever. Yeah, I don't know. I've seen a I assume you've
seen like, the Jim Sterling like digital homicide. I'm familiar with it in general. Yeah.
Yeah, like, I mean, the digital homicide games are just their trap, their asset flips. They're
not illegal, per se. But, you know, they basically only they only made sales by promoting themselves
with like giveaways and like some like dodgy like, like, you know, reward programs and stuff like
they would like give you steam credit in exchange for buying their games or some weird, some weird
shit. Yeah. And I mean, but you know, I've never really understood look, it's fun. I totally get
Jim saying that they're terrible games in talking mad shit. But I've always like, what's the real
problem here? Are those games being promoted above games that deserve it more? Is that like the
issue? And are consumers being taken advantage of in some way? I mean, I don't know who's to say
that like, you know, that they are, I think like, like terrible and no one wants to play them, you
know, I don't know. I don't think that was with digital homicide. I think the real problem was
their like frivolous lawsuits against a guy for criticizing. Well, that okay, I get that I get
that in that case that that's what like the controversy was other than the fact that they're
just I mean, yeah, I think it was like Jim played the games, shit talk them and then like lawsuits
ensued and that was bullshit. Like he's allowed to shit. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. Well,
that all sounds fine to me. You know, I don't know. It is it is kind of cool that it is kind of
cool that just any old fucking thing can get on there because sometimes, you know, sometimes an
amateur piece of shit or not a piece of sometimes an amateur project that's made with little technical
still can skill still have like a cool aesthetic or like a cool idea somewhere in it that that that
can indeed, you know, resonate with people and that and that's neat. So I don't know. I guess,
you know, to achieve that steam kind of had to sort of bite the bullet and be like, okay, well,
we don't really have any quality standards. Yeah, in terms of what's allowed in our plan,
but you know, they can still curate in the sense of what the total opposite of Epic's approach,
where like they're, I think it's Epic anyway, like they are curating like they want good big games,
like only on their shit, which, you know, that's fine. I'd be interested to see who does better
long term just for the sake of is Epic like the is that like the four? Yes, that's correct. That's
correct. Okay. Oh, there. Yeah, they're they're getting involved in the in the distribution of
games game. Oh, dear. Oh, dear. They're they're big. They're they're doing well. Was there anything
else I was going to say on that? I can't wait for Disney to own Fortnite. When the buy out it when
the buy out Epic games. Disney's buying everything. No. What? What's wrong? What? What don't you like?
Ben? I don't understand. What wouldn't you like about about Disney owning? I can't wait to see
Mickey flossing. Oh my god. Yes. This is a perfect segue. Yeah. Perfect segue into my life. Do the
first tunnel. So sorry. He sort of unlocked new Keyblade Orange Justice. You know, that's a Fortnite
thing, right? I don't know, but it sounds right. Did you know that Sora does do a big old dab
in Kingdom Hearts Dream Drop Distance? Fuck. Yeah, no, I didn't know that. He does it.
He's a killer. He's a killer through and through. That's true.
Well, speaking of big corporations, I paid my taxes this week. The United States,
the corporation that it is. Well, I'm just mad. I'm just mad that I paid more than Amazon in
taxes. That's all I'm saying. That's all I'm just throwing that out there as a point. Argue
amongst yourselves about the justice inherent in that. It's not that you, well, like, what do you
mean? What? What? Say it. Well, I'll kill you. Okay. Amazon provides value through its commerce,
like, and so they make deals with particular constituencies to, you know, get like their
costs mitigated because, I mean, you know, why does the state make this a deal? Because Amazon
provides them value and like, they're getting something in exchange for it. So, you know,
instead of paying money. Yes. And the end result is that they make $11 billion in profits and pay
no taxes. And I, Ben St, internet, indie content creator, make, you know, you know, struggle and
scratch my way up to crack the fucking five digit mark and pay more than them to the American
government. So that's pretty neat. Well, good stuff. Good stuff. I would argue if that's as
much of an injustice as it is being framed as, but I know we disagree on these, these topics
to a degree. Apparently, apparently so. So we did that. Also, so I was like, gone from the internet
for a while. Like, I, yeah, everyone thought I was dead. Everyone thought yet, right, because I,
yeah, I was like, yeah, desperately trying to get a hold of it. Everyone was trying to reach me.
I was off the internet. I did. Hold on. Okay. You were off the internet, but why didn't you
answer the calls that Nate sent you? I mean, Ben also just doesn't keep his phone. I don't look
at my phone. I wasn't looking at my phone. I did my taxes. I reorganized my room, which was a very
gratifying experience. He gives the mental map of your room. Well, my bed is now it's not in the,
it's not in the far left corner. It's in the near left corner and it's vertically oriented
instead of horizontal. I understand. Yeah. So I have a lot more, I moved, okay, okay. I had like
my dresser sort of tucked into a tiny little alcove, little corner part of my room that was
completely inaccessible. So I moved that out to my actual floor. So now I can actually keep my clothes
in it and access them. Oh, nice. It's great. It's really, it's really great. I no longer just have,
my clothes are no longer just in a big old fucking pile on my floor. They're actually
endorsement. I have a quote unquote clothes closet, but what that is is a repository where I dump all
my clean clothes in this closet and I have never folded them or attempted to organize them. I sift
through the pile for clothes. I'm surprised. I know. I'm surprised. I think people would be surprised
about the some of the slovenly aspects to my life that I don't broadcast publicly very often,
but this is one of them. My room is actually pretty neat. By doing all this, I opened up a lot
more floor space in front of my windows and now I realize that I need, much like the dude,
I need a rug. I have this empty floor and I need a rug. I'm looking at the space right now and it
would really tie the room together. I watched The Big Lebowski just the other day again. It was
good. It's very good. It's a good, it's a good film. Yeah. I just got this, this void, this empty void
of hardwood on my, well, it's, and it's just, it just cries out. It cries out to be covered with a
decorative item. Get that, get some sort of killer print rug or something, you know.
What print? A killer print? Yeah, you know. We don't sell rugs. Yeah, unfortunately. Red
Bubble does everything. We sell, we sell throw blankets and tapestries, which I now sleep under.
I now sleep directly under my giant cop killer insignia, drawn by, drawn by slimes, that good boy.
And it's a good, it's a good time. Anyway, my, my life feels less cluttered and I feel a little
less stressed to just exist in my living space. I was, I was pretty stressed about taxes as well.
I don't know, I keep my apartment relatively clean, but taxes was weighing on me, but it's all out
of there and it's done and that makes me feel good. You know, okay, okay. So I was doing my taxes
right. I go to mass.gov and I, and they're like, click here to go to an internet website where
you can do your taxes online. And you're like, Erin at website never heard of it and you stop.
I'm suspicious. So I do that and I go there, right? And it's getting late in the day. And, but you
know, I still got time. Like I'm assuming I have until midnight and then the fucking website goes
down at like 8pm and it doesn't come back on until like half till midnight and I'm late.
Yeah. And I'm, and because of that, I end up being late. I don't send it out until like 2am and I'm
like, fuck. However, however, so I was at the Boston comics round table this Thursday and, you
know, after announced, we're all just kind of shooting the shit and someone, and I'm talking
about this and someone tells me like, Hey, actually, due to, I don't remember some legal
technicality. She's, she's like, actually, technically, you're not, you're in the clear as
long as you got him in before the 17th. And I'm like, all right, if you say so, I'm going to choose
to believe that. And that means everything's great. So yeah, did my fucking taxes like a good boy.
Well, that's great. We all did them far too late, though. We got a next year, January rolls around.
I can't, can you believe that people do them in fucking January? You know who does it there?
Who doesn't in January? Jesse, Jesse did his like in January, right? As a new year hit.
And I'm just like, well, shit, I gotta, I gotta get on that, man. I had all the paperwork ready.
I just had to fucking organize it. It was just too lazy. So I, yeah, you know, like,
there was nothing stopping me from doing it early. On the other hand, there were no consequences for
me doing it late. Lesson learned. So what, so what's the lesson here really? Ask for forgiveness,
not for permission. You know, just proceed until apprehended. Did you see that tweet that I made
munchy about that? I did. I had no idea. I learned it from my mom. So I thought she invented it,
but I guess she didn't. Nate, did you see that? It sounds familiar, but I can't remember about that
lady. Yeah. Oh, yeah. The Navy lady, whatever. The Navy lady. Yeah. Okay. I always thought that
that quote was from Teddy Roosevelt because it just sounds like something he would say, right?
But in fact, it was the better to beg better to ask forgiveness than ask permission was from
God, I want to say Gail Lord Shuler, but it's definitely not her. Gail Lord Shoemaker. Gail
Lord Shuler. Grace Hopper, who I don't know. I, God, who was it? It was, I was watching some
fucking YouTuber. It might have been Cosmo, Cosmo, not Cosmonaut, Cosmo Kramer, something. I don't
know. Okay. Whatever. It was some YouTuber and they mentioned it offhand. And I, they mentioned
this person. I was like, wait a minute, that wasn't Teddy Roosevelt. And it looked her up.
And she's so fucking cool. She's like a mathematician. She's like a 1930s, like
mathematician woman who like was fucking a rear admiral in the fucking Navy and did it
till she was 79 and like helped invent like early computing code. That's right. That's right. And
then I found this quote about her that one of her, her like contemporaries says, she looks all Navy,
but when you reach inside, you find a pirate dying to be released. And I was like, whoa.
And I thought that was pretty much the coolest thing I'd heard about in a long time.
Yeah, she's pretty cool. I remember hearing about it a while back. Computing pioneer. Yeah,
pretty cool. Yeah. Cool. How, I don't know. Fucking neat. I think in my computer science
education, she came up if I remember correctly. Oh, really? I think so. Oh, right. Yeah. You
got like, you went to like school and shit for that or whatever. Indeed. Yeah. Well, I mean,
early computing is pretty dope. You know, there was another lady like in like the 1700s. Her
nickname, her nickname is grandma cobalt after like cobalt, the language. Yeah. That's cool.
That's cool. That's cute. I thought there was like another lady of like the 1800s or something
that like developed what was effectively like a very early computing language with like weird
like animal like before computers existed or something. I don't know. That's crazy with that.
Could be women doing things, like having thoughts. I meant more so the 1800s part,
but also no, no, that wasn't purely my expression. That was not mocking you. No, no, no.
Yeah. No, but that seems pretty early to be making proto computer. Yeah, I might be a little
fudging the numbers there. I remember there was something like that. I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah. I don't know. I've heard that like ancient, God, I don't know. This could be fake. I've heard
that like ancient peoples have like clay jars or something with like metal, like a specific kind
of metal rod inside. And it was like, if you filled this thing with like vinegar or some sort of
acidic substance or something like that, it would have like an energy imbalance to be created.
And it actually would create like a small electric current. And I think it was used to like
electro plate gold onto other metals. And I don't know how that works at all. But yeah,
I've heard that there were like relatively ancient peoples that had this sort of rudimentary way
to create electricity and do like some weird like pseudo electrical shit. Okay, big if true. Do you
guys ever think I like, okay, this is like a weird and I have no idea what people I'm even talking
about. This is like a barely remembered factoid. Not an insignificant part of my life. Just like
thinking about it is like comprised of like thinking about like ancient humans and about how we
arrived at this point. I think about it like every day for like hours. Possibly because you're
effectively a caveman displaced in time, sent to the far future. Yeah, it might as well be. I'm
in Neanderthal. Yeah. Okay, I think about whenever I'm at a restaurant and thinking about like,
this is impossible. There's no way this could possibly have happened. This isn't how like like
earth was meant to be. Not as like it's bad, but just isn't like this is insane. This is
fucking crazy that I'm a rough God's plan. Yeah. And I just I just often think about like how like
fucking like insane it is that we do any of the stuff we like like who was the first person
to like even do stuff like as like as in like like fire, right? First person to put like meat
over fire. Like why? That's insane. That's insane. That's madness. That's God actually. Yeah. Okay,
I understand. So, so have some respect. Yeah. Why would you think to do that? Yeah. I mean a lot
of us could have just been accidental and that people just learned from it. Well surely like
but just like I don't know like there's so many things like we've we've so crawled up from dirt
and grime and nothing. Yeah. You know, you know, I was thinking about that as like I was eating an
avocado the other day and I was like what is it some natural instinct that made the first person
like pick a fruit and like eat it like what made them like okay you're you're you don't know shit
about the world you've been born into from nothingness and you're and you're clueless and like
you're sure you're hungry but like how do you know to eat a thing? Well, there's an answer to that.
There's an answer to that. How do you how do you look at like a wild fucking a piece of like wild
mustard seed and think like I should put that thing in obviously this president for eating but
like you know it has to start somewhere and obviously started like a like literally like like
like the cell level first right and evolution you know bake that into us as it went along presumably
the cooking thing. Well, here's what I'm if you were like just born I mean I guess if you're just
born and like no one tells you anything and you're just a baby right yeah I guess you'll probably
just have a natural instinct. Well, you'll also pick it up from people around you. Claw your way
towards a fruit and eat it. I would think so humans humans aren't the blank slates that we sometimes
think of them are you know there's some instincts baked in there yeah even though we're you know
again off God's path but uh uh sure you know like like monkeys yeah dude fuck hell yeah monkeys I
if I remember correctly I believe monkeys in some areas they do like brew alcohol like there's some
like again I don't I don't think it's like intentional I think that there is some area I
think I think I heard about this on Joe Rogan at some point that like there's some monkeys that like
cater to like fermenting fruit and it like generates alcohol that they enjoy because it you know gets
them fucked up or whatever uh I could be crazy but I I remember hearing something like that and
that sounds like the sort of thing that's kind of a happy accident that they've you know adapted to
or you know they're they're what limited intelligence they have you know I know monkeys are pretty smart
I guess but like yeah they they appreciate okay I looked it up apparently apparently they they
extract sap from a raffia palm trees and then they let the sap ferment creating a palm wine
there you go and it seems I mean the wording of this article seems to imply that they're
doing it on purpose which yeah I guess so shocking if true so I mean tangentially related to this I
also often think about like going back in time or bring people into the future to like explain the
way the world is and it's about how weird it would be to do that this is I don't understand why I do
this again takes up like vast swaths of my life and I don't know why I think about it so often
you know I always think about like bringing historical leaders into the president being like
here's what a plane is and they're like oh my god that's so crazy I'm like I know right and that's
like the end of the thought uh thinking about it all the time every and then pick a new historical
figure exactly literally exactly I think I know everything would have been relatively normal I
think like uh uh if you brought George Washington to up up to like spend that all the time like like
the 80s or you know a little before like the 60s or something well maybe even a little bit before
that George bring George Washington to like uh let's say the 20s or something they have like he
would have seen he would have seen people doing the twist and had a heart from the sheer impropriety
of it all yes exactly it uh uh like up to that point like they started to have like telegrams
and telephones I think around then so like the world was starting to be connected no when was the
telephone uh the telephone well depends on how about telephone but like like telegram 1800s
like a second half okay okay so that that happened pretty cool oh well you know what how did how did
they play the game of telephone before the telephone wasn't damn that's a good question no idea um uh
well my point is like humans were relatively stagnant I think until we started like even if
with like guns and stuff again that's still you got to go into a field and march around and shoot
people you know whatever you gotta make your way off base say your point but it makes no sense and
it's wrong once we got like telegrams telephones and now at this point we're at the point where
imagine explaining like the concept of social media that we all like we're we're basically
psychically connected to every other member of the human race on the planet yeah through these
kind of like opt-in systems of like Twitter and you know YouTube and all this stuff it's a totally
that's the biggest mindfuck it'd be like if like you know like 50 100 200 years or whatever
us going to a future where literally everyone lives in VR like all the time and like the earth is just
like a caretaker for our useless corpses that bring our consciousness to the data realm or whatever
uh strikes me similar to that um but yeah I'd be pretty kooky pretty cool man like the thoughts
interesting right I don't know it just it's on my mind constantly thinking about how different we
are from what we were like I don't know programmed to do I mean that's where anyone thinks that like
I don't know like I'm not pooing at it at all like even slightly it's just an interesting thought to
see how far we've come from what we were you know this thing I've been saying of like escaping from
God's plan is is is true in the sense of like we like there's like a certain you know god of like
nature whatever it's like you get to a certain point and like evolutionarily you're basically
doing the same thing that like your other apes are doing but just at some point when over the tipping
point and we just had like I don't know they say like the agricultural like the ability of humans
to like settle down and grow food I think was like the first thing that like allowed humans to really
flourish and like save up stories for when there was famines because like without that you know
most humans would have continually died off when there's like a bad season or whatever uh so you
you know we just we get a little bit ahead you get a little bit up in the game with your stores
and you're able to breed a little bit more and spread out a little further and then you're just
over the hill your crew and interest on your vast sums you know it's basically capitalism at work
only human capital you got a little bit over the top it just interests it's paying for itself
it's human centered capitalism yang 2020 it makes sense um yeah yeah I don't know it's just cool
it just it's interesting to me that like bringing like Genghis Khan I don't know what year he lived
bringing him to like you know 30 hundreds if I recall correctly sorry when was that when was that
1300s bringing someone like him to like George Washington's day would not be that big a difference
uh but bringing him to our day just uh you know a couple hundred years after that that's a huge
difference and I guess it all shows up in like the the way that like the graph of like technological
advancement is just like it's gone fucking you know parallel wait hold on no George he would be
shocked and appalled if he went to george what that was like that like the industrial
revolution that yeah it would have been insane it was well I question like if they had the
fucking cotton gin but they did not have the kind of those are like economic and like they oh okay
they didn't have okay they didn't have the cotton gin but they had like I mean it's just that those
strength me is like economic factors and like well-being of man factors well okay there are
many factors that would shock and appall him it completely different culture completely different
technology completely different almost like like terrain like everything they had they had
factories I mean I guess for some reason not my mind focuses on like the the communication
well I mean in in george washington's day they had no I know I know not in this they did they did
but they are different like mechanized yeah yeah yeah sure well uh things are I mean I think the
I think like a city like like the the concept of the city was just like structured completely
differently well like George Washington's day versus like what they was for for okay hold on I just
want to say that like okay look there's there's many different things as opposed to like Genghis Khan
the Mongol emperor to George Washington in America there are so many like of course Genghis Khan would
be like what's the city and then burn it down I'm kind of think of like the human well no you know
I'm saying that like you know I know that he would know what it is but like the it's not the same
right he ruled over a lot of cities I'm like he's generally like a nomadic guy he comes from that
background if you just want to see it you know if you just killed George Washington and put Genghis Khan
in charge and like he you know he knew what was going on like I think that like the world had not
changed so much like his understanding of like men and like okay he'd have to learn about guns
probably but okay you can learn what guns do like I feel like he could adapt but seeing either of
those adapt to like modern technology I think is is a whole nother ball game no completely disagree
I mean completely wrong enough face and retarded well well boomers can't even adapt to today's
yeah there you go they're they're they're they've just figured out facebook just in time to watch
crumble you you underestimate how much has changed just constantly throughout like like I suppose
I'm gonna kind of go with Nate here I think that the well okay it has changed more rapidly
it's accelerated sure okay okay if your point is if like
like like like it's it's changing faster now I definitely agree with that I'm saying well you
know okay I guess I shouldn't say that like the um I just meant your specific example I thought was
off base but you're like your idea that like you know it changed slower that's definitely true I
know yeah that that's that's the main point I don't know whatever let's you know what let's go to
fucking voicemail okay wait wait I feel like I had I feel like I had something else like maybe there
was one of any other of the famous quote unquote events in your life oh fuck off dude yes my events
you don't even know what that meant uh I don't wait did it mean something uh wait what did it mean
well that's open to interpretation wait what did it mean well what did it mean though I mean uh the
the joke that I was making I guess was that like your life what did it mean no has few things that
would be considered legitimate events uh yes uh something like that yeah hold on wait no I got
that I got that I need to retract a point for my own for my own personal well-being because I know one
of those one of you motherfuckers are writing a comic about how Genghis Khan of course you notice
it is yes obviously I know that he fucking you roll over like literally like you know like all
like northern China I know I know he noticed our vast audience of history he's seen a lot of people
in one place I know what he knows what I meant was just that you know comes from a nomadic background
he'd probably be a little bit shocked by like the way the cities had progressed at that time
uh uh based on guys I know well that's what I that's what I said like the the way a city was
structured would just look it would I mean the art it would look different like you know they didn't
have modern you know like building techniques and shit yeah I mean not to mention the the culture
and and stuff and just I got it I am smart please no no no no no no Nate I'm not I'm not cheating on
you at all I'm just I'm just saying for my for my own point I don't want anyone to make fun of me
in the comments that's literally right yeah no no no I gotcha you guys you guys watch that uh you
guys watch that they're uh Jordan Peterson versus Slavo Gizek I hope I'm saying no of course no I
don't think so who's Slavo Gizek you know I wish I knew more about the guy he is uh he is kind of a
he is kind of a cool Marxist guy but he's also very yeah those are your synonymous dude right
he's he's like he's like a he's like a Marxist psychologist philosopher but he's also very
like anti SJW okay which is okay I think I heard of this guy I don't I have heard of him a lot and
I I kind of want to dig into his stuff more now uh I don't know okay never mind I thought me I kind
of thought maybe you guys would have checked I would have thought that Nate would but it's the
it's the sort of thing I watch uh you know and and it's very like uh Jordan's all like hey here's
why capitalism's good and Marx's and Erdon Marx Gizek is like well here's the problems with it and
you know it's it's uh Gizek's is very just a very like entertaining guy he's he's very he's very
charming as uh Jordan points out that's uh mr. Peterson uh ask doctor doctor question on the
honorable please the the the rya arbald the lord mayor of kekistan you know I kind of I kind of
expecting I kind of went into expecting to be like rude and hardcore against dr. p and being like
yeah fuck you sure and I mean I didn't really agree with him I still didn't really agree with his
opinions but like I didn't like get mad at him during it or anything it was all very fine and
you know reasonable discourse I guess you know I obviously haven't watched this I've watched a
bunch of Peterson stuff over the years uh you know I'm sure some people disagree I mean I hear people
like I don't know I hear things like some people just like call him like a transphobe and I'm like
what I don't think that's an accurate statement I don't think you're assessing the the situation
oh you know what I forgot because like the original controversy was that he didn't want to be
like whatever he didn't want to be like forced to use pronouns that he didn't think legitimate or
whatever uh so I again I can follow the logic to get to that conclusion but I don't know uh so I
get it obviously I'm not one of those peeps who might take a personal issue whether anything
but like he's always strike me as a as a relatively honest actor and I suppose you know if one was like
a hardcore Marxist he is a devout capitalist and you know enjoys making money and profiting off
his ventures so like I could see people being like ah he's you know a fucking fraud just trying to
make money or something but I don't know he seems pretty seems relatively legit to me and I mean
you know I mean I mean I think he's he's he oh man Anthony Fantano made a tweet like today I've
seen some of his I think and it was like you know uh Peterson is a I don't think he called him a
shit yeah but basically he's like he is he he just like he caters to you know he caters to like
these like guys who just want their own biases regurgitated back at them you know sprinkled
in with like you know a small amount of like you know good advice aren't we all like that though
and I mean like yeah I think that's probably sure sure uh and uh yeah you know he he loves he loves
he loves capitalism and I'm not as and I'm not its biggest fan um and I mean you know so he's
so fuck that guy that's that's fair you know when I like I've seen Fantano really shit on
this guy in the past in various times and like look I get it uh he disagrees with him politically
and you know I would suspect that like he kind of gets into like a more personal like finding the
guy to be like fake like if you already don't agree with the guy's ideas the fact that like
he markets himself well that's probably gonna rub you the wrong way like I get it but you know why
would that be I don't I don't know if I I mean it's possible maybe he doesn't really believe the
things that he says and he's just saying them because they make him a ton of money I mean
that's not the craziest thing I've ever heard I don't think I mean I'm not you know I don't think
there's like a you can prove that you know yeah you know and I think a lot of people they they get
kind of in the space of like they they want that to be true so they read into various things like
ways to it and like I can't even say they're wrong they're probably correct it's just I very much like
to be charitable in my interpretations and like like just for example if you're like trans and you
feel attacked by what the guys say I mean I could argue all day that like you shouldn't feel attacked
that's not his point but like you feel how you feel so what can I do you know I mean I mean I think
that probably and like this isn't just about him but about basically anyone like anyone who's like
you know pushing a political position or an ideology or something like if if you say something
and it makes and and you know people respond to it and you end up making money off it I think
that most people will probably I don't think it's generally you you won't be like sitting there rubbing
your hands to go like ooh I don't really believe this but I'm gonna continue to say it you know
because it makes money what's more likely to happen is you're gonna say like uh I said this
opinion and I had it validated you know by you know people's responses to it and by you know
the the amount of like capital that it generated for me you know and that's that's just gonna like
convince you more and they're like yeah what I said was right you know this I am right you know
and I and you know I have evidence like the evidence that I am right in what I say is mounting
and mounting indeed you know confirmation buys the work etc etc confirmation bias yeah and and you
get uh what's the thing it's uh the um the affirmation the affirmation gang we're like okay I
think I can glean what that means but yeah you like you you're like a you're like a thought leader
and like everyone you know you got your crew that all it looks to you because like you say the thing
you say the thing that is right and everyone wants you to keep saying the thing that is right so
that they can like stand behind you and be like yeah this guy's an expert and he says the thing
that's right and I agree with him and holds you up as their champion or whatever and it's like yeah I
gotta keep gotta keep saying this thing that's right because these these guys all tell me that
it's right and I mean of course it's true at any time someone who just fundamentally disagrees
like you know if you've just got like a hardcore Marxist or whatever like someone can come out and
just be like uh you know everything you're saying is wrong like you're like you're just getting swept
up in this like cult of personality and you're just like letting your kind like you're just saying
what you want to believe like again like um uh something like uh I mean just for example like
someone like Ben Shapiro whatever he like straight up doesn't believe in like being trans or whatever
due to religious and whatever like you know you could say all day that like you know this is
his firm belief but somebody on the other side could just say that like um you know he just he
wants to believe this so he's like convincing himself it's true or he doesn't believe that he's
just saying it anyway and at a certain point you just get you're into mind reading and I don't know
I I hate being in the business of mind reading uh like I don't know say say your I don't know I
think I think about this a bunch like say your say your Dr. P right and maybe at some point you're
like you know yeah I would Dr. P I'd wish I was Dr. P P and then I would get a sick uh Dr. Mario
uh you gotta change your name to Dr. Peter Peterson maybe Dr. P P uh classic patreon.com
slash bansane for quality jokes of that caliber uh the uh maybe at some point you're like you know
I'm a guy I'm successful I'm an academic I think capitalism is pretty good maybe there's something
maybe the communists have some good ideas but generally you know I think I like capitalism
and then you know you say all this stuff and people respond to it and you're like and you're
like you know I think you should clean your room and stand up straight and people respond to that
and you're like wow the stuff you said changed my life and then you write your book and it's a best
seller and then like the letters come flooding in and you're like the stuff you said changed my life
and I mean you know it doesn't matter how many like maybe there's people that disagree with you
just as much but you're hearing I mean you're hearing the haters but in your mind you gotta
dismiss like well those are just the haters and then you're getting all this positive
information people like the stuff you said changed my life it means everything to me you're a genius
and you're like well I mean of course you know you're gonna you like no like forget about Dr. P
if you're anyone like if this happens to you like this is you're of course you're gonna continue
to do what you're doing because you're getting this kind of a response from it that's definitely
true and and I just say that that's that's possible however it certainly remains a possibility as well
that despite all those things on you know undoubtedly happening he remains you know intellectually
curious and attempts to examine his own ideas and simply believes that he still is on the
right track and that this makes the most sense despite the ideas he's coming up against I mean
that's the most charitable way to interpret it yeah maybe I don't know yeah so I mean everybody
just has to judge for that whatever that's like to anybody um and I don't know but generally like
when I when it comes to listening to people like this I like to listen to and I admit it like you
know I was listening to destiny the other day the thing I don't like about destiny is just how mean
he is I don't like how mean he is and it makes me not want to listen to him because it's unpleasant
and maybe like I'm a pussy because I can't take the heat yeah but yeah definitely yeah I mean that's
for sure that's for sure but it's just I I'd rather go listen to you know uh uh some fucking like
Joe Rogan um and I don't know like anybody else anybody's on his fucking show just because like
they're respectful and nice and you know they'll they'll challenge each other and I can think
for my fucking self about who's right and wrong and I don't even think I'm as smart as destiny
especially when it comes to like a debate format or whatever it's like I'm not even saying he's
right or wrong but like I definitely am attracted to positivity so I like steel manning I like like
attacking your opponent's ideas at their best at their strongest and I try to do it as well myself
so I don't know I don't know what I'm getting into I'm just saying that steel manning yeah yes it's
good what a what a it's nice that's funny uh okay well I don't know uh would you recommend
that uh the the Peterson and Zizek debate thing or whatever yeah I would say so especially like
I didn't know much about Zizek I mean I kind of want to hear like a nice Marxist who I can
take seriously and you know listen to his ideas and see if I'm wrong in some ways I think you I
think you would I think you would appreciate him because like I I don't know much about him I've
heard about him a lot but I've never looked into him and like seeing him in this debate I was like
you know I should maybe like look into more about this guy because I don't know he seems
interesting and I don't know I think you would find him you know reasonable if nothing else yeah okay
I love politics that okay that wasn't really political that was that was as light as it could be
okay all right well is that p is that p you know bro oh yep there it is uh well
well shall we go let's go to the voicemail ladies and gentlemen uh let's let's hop on over here um
okay now now uh public service announcement we are getting an unforced review but by the way
maybe we should say that hippo is gone for technical difficulties in case you've been
wondering where that's true he had connections issues and they unfortunately his connect his
connection died a long time ago it was in and out for a while and now it seems like it's just dead
so that's why he's gone indeed indeed uh so have no fears ladies and gentlemen um excuse me okay so
public service announcement here it is uh a bunch of people are just leaving like a lot of messages
I don't know like like fat fuck faggot who left a whole slew I messaged my favorite like I'm gonna
play some because they're good what what happened he's he's spider he's he people are training his
spider but for fucking voicemails now why what did spider do the comments a thousand times oh
you meant you mentioned him in the yeah last episode that he'll just leave like four comments
right that's right on a video which is fine I don't know it's not I don't see the problem
what I mean the right or wrong I basically just I mean just because I'm busy I don't check really
the comment sections of like any videos of mine I check all the comments most most weeks most
weeks I will read through uh the comments I would if I just had the time I find it pleasant and I
enjoy you know and I do look a little bit I do look when like the episode first comes out I'll
just be curious to see what people are saying so you know I don't know if this is clear I don't
ever said this but like like if you're wondering I always read the comments in case you aren't
aware like I read everything I might not always respond but I I generally do um there I just
so I mean we're watching for episodes that I'm on obviously I definitely want to hear if people
had to say anything about the shit I said yeah that's a little good all right see there you
I gotta find my enemies indeed okay I gotta keep so here's the end of my public service
announcement it's just so people like just you can leave a bunch but you're just making my life
more difficult so like if some people are spamming I might just start skipping you I'll tell you that
that was my temptation like when I see like like six or seven messages from the same person I'm just
like is this really did this person have like a mission this episode and they're here like to
make sure I hear their quality thing they've thought of or they just spamming in the hopes
that something will be good and maybe something's good so give it to me straight how many how many
voicemails I mean it's just like 12 I think no 11 we have 11 so nothing nothing crazy but
I did have to cut through a bunch so so people try to you know work on it work out ladies and
gentlemen anything you've got to say you can say in what is it like a minute and a half is the limit
for and I anything you've got to say you can say it you know some people actually some person left
a message I forget who it was I didn't grab it but someone said like hey here's the real life hack
to be on a pcp episode in the voicemail just leave like a million messages and you know one of them
will probably be good honestly if I were you Nate I probably I would have been tempted to just not
look at like the messages that were posted like like six messages but you know that you know I'm
just saying I'm letting people know I might do maybe the first one so far maybe the so far I
haven't missed a single single voicemail I've listened to all of them I've heard all of the
depravity so okay anyway that out of the way uh let's hear what fat fuck faggot has to say okay go
do you must be hurt you must be hurt
jesse why don't you like emulators that makes no sense okay I also like emulators
fat fuck first of all lose some weight second of all does does jesse hate emulators he was
running about it I think I think you don't need a voice modulator to ask a bullshit lame question
this is people are looking for axe munchy I mean this fat fuck faggot left like eight messages so
you know yeah what's the point of a voice modulator like there's no gimmie to make it more interesting
for us I guess you weren't like oh fat fuck I just destroyed a fucking 10 pound chicken what's
your opinion on fucking emulators it yeah do do better do better fat yeah fat fuck you know what
you're out of the league you're not pcb fan anymore I'm just a crude it you're not pcb fan
wow you're out of the league fair out of the game harsh but fair but I agree emulators are great
why wouldn't you like emulators what the fuck what the fuck yeah they're pretty great I like free
video games though they're harder to get these days there's a fucking emu paradise got shut down
they don't host any games anymore oh well I'm all about the emo paradise am I right
fellow I'm into that emu paradise you know the large ostrich like bird you know I'm just living
in emu paradise I say a depositing for uh 4 000 rounds of ammunition to a field of uh of emu
who isn't killing one I straight up I straight up thought that emu paradise was named after the bird
for a while uh I mean maybe it's it did not dawn I mean oh like emu later yeah emu maybe it's actually
pronounced emu paradise and we've all been saying it wrong I don't I don't know well it doesn't look
like it uh hard to say no uh hey are those things that big fat people wear are those also emus are
they called no moomoo's okay all right moomoo paradise that's right I'm making that my home page
homers moomoo in the fucking uh that one where you got one that was a good one okay more than
so that being said uh we've got one more message from fat fuck faggot let's uh let's go I hope it's
better this is fat fuck faggot over here this is this is a digi impression so anime is a japanese
colloquialism this guy fucking sucks this guy fucking sucks name mo dude he said weed
you're a tyrant you're a fucking tyrant man this is this is like okay imagine you're the king
you're the king of a country and you bring up the most retarded baby onto an altar and say laugh at
him laugh at this retarded baby I mean perhaps this is all a grand conspiracy where's the quality
control perhaps you're steam you're the steam of the pcb all right I just said that but yeah
could this be a conspiracy to get someone else to do the voicemails so I just don't have to do them
for no additional pay uh you know that's that's up only the stars know only the stars know the
answer to that okay um I guess I guess we'll never know okay next one uh this is from all your
favorite things suck uh all right good
uh
okay Nate okay you know you've made your point you've made your point
message received can you please just throw out all the shit okay can we just
I hear the front loaded us with all the shit ones I think thank you so that's what the people
want so that's what they got oh god I shouldn't have said all you have to do is have a voice
module later on you'll get on the show because yeah exactly like this and like the instrument
thing is happening yeah they're figuring out like they're just like with the steam library
taking any and all comers so too does the pcp voicemail section uh and our curation staff
let's just say very simple algorithm very very simple yeah and the people are figuring out just
like that uh what not bloody dead man fucking uh you know the guy that jim sterling had that tiff
with he just found out how to hack the system and make piece of shit acid flips you know whatever
okay anyway uh that's the one my favorite game developers bloody dead man didn't wish it digital
homicide he probably does work at digital homicide well not anymore did they shut their doors have
they been shut down are they not I think they like I think they keep just like changing their name
starting up new like new fake companies and the genius behind it all it's got to be the bloody
dead man uh okay moving on it's on brand coming for the next like um so what's your favorite anime
but like sad and like a like a kooky voice module like there's a bunch of wall yeah that's that's
what I want that's what I crave uh and on that front uh next message is from swear I'm not a cuck
okay go all right pcp I've got a real question for you so I've been dating this girl for a few
months and she's got a really interesting job now she uses a website called seeking arrangements
and meets with men for money now she doesn't have sex with these men she just goes out in a public
place has dinner maybe sees a movie whatever a casual date and she gets paid thousands of
dollars for this I'm talking four thousand dollars a month just for meeting with men my question to
you is would you be comfortable with your eso doing this for money right okay uh any any thoughts
would I be comfortable no do I think it's like abhorrent or like morally objective not really
I okay well this is interesting and I'm very confused yeah uh what is this this is a real thing
this is a real thing I'm on I'm on seeking dot com right now and I'm signing up and I'm gonna be and
I'm gonna be a yeah see this is this is the real tester we we're signing up for a date with your
wife so uh are you comfortable with that are you comfortable with that does that sound good
yeah uh this is the real test you're absolutely right well uh you know people are lonely Ben
people are lonely they want to hang out with women even if it doesn't mean that okay listen
this this is something don't really understand because like people will say that you just want to
hang out with women for you know like like uh you know like you know for fun you know people
will say that but like you have to be eaten up inside like this obviously like like it plays into
like a sex thing right where it's like you know obviously if they just want to have sex they would
order a prostitute but you know some people just want to hang out with people and just you know
just go on a date with them and feel that like like you know a fake romantic connection there they
want to have that experience right but like you know I don't believe it's purely like a platonic
or just a romantic thing like surely they must be like eaten up inside like oh maybe if I play the
long game maybe they she'll actually fall in love with me and I'll be able to have sex or yeah maybe
sugar sugar daddy benefits for sugar babies per sugar daddy the odds are in your favor with
thousands of attractive local women looking to meet now no strings attached redefine the
expectations of a perfect relationship ideal relationships upfront and honest arrangements
with someone who will cater to your needs sugar baby benefits find a mentor establish sugar daddies
offer valuable guidance for long-term stability date experienced men date real gentlemen who
don't play games be pampered indulge in shopping where pamper expensive dinners and exotic
travel vacation okay no hold on so you is this like a no sex website or it depends on what you
want I think there's the way that this is it just like the way that this girl does it I'd imagine
so I'd imagine so and I assume she's up front but you know so so they're oh god so these guys are
paying to go to date with a girl to like just go eat dinner with them they said go to a movie or
something or you know something like that oh boy I mean the answer to the answer to this question
for me would I be comfortable with it could not be simpler the answer is no uh not in a million
years would I be in a situation such as this uh but I mean you know I don't know yeah like well
do I sit here in judgment I mean whatever do what you gotta do to get by you know it's fine
everybody's I I want to like twist language a little bit way because I feel like the word
cuck needs to be defined here a little bit okay because cuck you know like like literally in the
dictionary is like you know it's like a sexual thing you like it I think the spectrum for sure
for sure I think the way that I like you're only a cuck in the way that we mean being a cuck if
you don't like it that could mean as in it's a surprise you as a girlfriend shielding you or is
just as in like no no way or or or that she wants to be in an open relationship but you don't want
to you're just like um yeah you know I guess we could do that um I guess we could be in a relationship
that's fine yeah you're like here's what I think on honestly I think I think it depends on how much
you trust her right like I think if you really trust her that like she's not doing anything
untoward with any of these guys and it's all completely above the belt platonic then I think
yeah I probably would be okay with it it's just that that is like that just like you're always
gonna wonder right you're always gonna be kind of well that's what I mean if you're like really
if you really know her and you really if you think you can really trust that it's not there's
nothing else going on then I think it is I get that Ben I mean it's a little crazy thing to think
I think but the thing is like maybe you trust the girl but how much you trust the guys and I'm not
saying like they're gonna like rape or anything I'm just saying like are all their intentions like
totally pure like is she never gonna get any kind of a little bit going beyond my my answer to that
is like I mean imagine you know imagine if you will dating a girl you know hard difficult I know
but like stretch stretch your mind out a little bit um you're dating I mean she's gonna have friends
she's gonna have her own friends and some of them you know could very well be guys and like
you know that like thinking about it yeah probably at least some of those guys are like
you know well you know they're not gonna do anything but like maybe if you guys broke up
then maybe they try maybe you know or maybe yeah that's for real so like so like how is how is this
any different I'll tell you how like you're not you're like you're not you're not gonna say oh you
can't hang out with your guy friends because what if they like you what if they'll try I mean well
first of all that kind of depends on the situation again like that's when you mean it depends on
the situation I would never like force anyone to do anything they want however I would absolutely
set ultimatums of look I'm comfortable with XYZ if you don't want it then we'll just break up that's
all I mean again it depends what those things are hold on like what's XYZ I mean I don't know dude
like if she had like a really like okay I like I knew someone okay I mean maybe there was like a
particular guy who like creeped you out for some specific reason this is this is just easy follow me
from this like I know a person who knows someone or something like I heard of a tale that like uh
that this is not the other gender side of it that there was like a girl who was dating a guy
and the thing was this guy had like a long time best friend who was female and they would do such
things as sleep in the same bed now they both say nothing ever happened but it's like well that's a
little odd uh that's kind of strange and like it like you know if you broke up with them do you
think that nothing would happen uh probably not probably some moves would be made um and and
incidentally just in this particular situation the girl the the friend who is a girl in question
like once spoke to the girlfriend of the guy and said like is this guy making you guys uncomfortable
and the guy was like oh no this is totally fine like it's totally full time don't worry about it
but even the girl in the friendship was detecting some vibes of probably like you know some kind of
beta-orbidiness around her despite being sure okay well like yeah you say like I would judge it
you know I don't want you sleeping in the same bed as this person well that's all I mean I would
judge on the specifics that's that's all it is yeah okay okay makes makes sense well that's what
I'm saying is like if you're like I don't know it just comes down to trust I guess is is the
is my final word on the subject and that's maybe all there is maybe I'm a caveman stuck in the past
but I would absolutely say that like cuckoldry is 100 a spectrum and to me to me it's not so much
about what the person wants it's about like kind of the value signified by it like it just strikes
me as like if you're a man who is dating a woman who let's just say is a porn star for example
like I'm sure there's a pride that can be gained from that of a certain kind but on the other hand
she's literally having sex with other men like maybe you're also having sex with other people
but to me like to me this signifies kind of like a weak relationship like a weak bond and you know
what maybe that's presentive uh it is presentive and I don't care I stand by it I think I think
I mean you know maybe all right you're dating a porn star right she's having sex with other guys
because that's your job maybe you're having sex with other women or whatever sure but maybe just
you know maybe the sex is not like what your relationship is about look I mean I'm sure that
there's maybe maybe you're both you're both doing that under other circumstances and like your
relationship is founded on other there's there can be a massive difference between sex for porn
as opposed to like you know make it look call me a dinosaur and maybe I'm just wrong it could be
proved wrong but I believe that like sexual intimacy is like important to a relationship and isn't
really something to be treated trivially uh so like you know like two people dating each other uh if
they're like both fucking other people but they say they love each other like okay I believe them
it's just like it would that be as strong a bond if they didn't fuck other people I suspect no but
again I'm no fucking expert here I'm just saying you I mean uh you know it's a I think it's
up to the individual and I'm gonna I think it could be I think I think it could be just as I think
it could be just as strong or opinion on someone else's relationship look people can do whatever
they want obviously I'm just saying this is where my mind goes all right I think it could be fine um
but and to me see it's a it's a very hot I I hate to repeat myself uh just I just
like you like this situation I would be okay with it if I trusted that there was that it was all
totally platonic and that in in the situation which is really fucking weird that is an extremely
high threshold of trust sure that would have to be hit because this whole situation is just so
fucking sketchy right um my my thing is again it's only a cuck if you're not okay with it like
if you're dating a porn star I would say that's you're not a cuck because you know like if you're
if you're if you're like if it's the boundaries are clear you have clearly ordained it and you
have made peace with it internally then like no you're just comfortable with something that other
people wouldn't be and I don't think that's a cuck thing yeah I think well yeah if you if you have
no qualms about this you aren't a cuck well okay but the question is should he have
quality here's the question here's the question that comes to my mind wouldn't it be great
for this man like would this person in any way prefer a situation where everything's the same
it's just the girl has a different job earns the same and isn't you know selling her body
effectively you know not in a sexual way she's not selling her she's not selling her attention
if it's okay let's say she is because my answer would be the same and and that's like that you
know you sure he could prefer it but if he doesn't have a problem with it then it's fun but see that
right there that preference is the spectrum of cuckledry at work in my opinion my my read on this
situation and this guy and I could be wrong but what I what I infer from it and I guess is that
the problem is that maybe this is all not platonic right and that is the source of the
yeah consternation he wouldn't be asking this if he didn't have doubts and I think the fact that
you do you might have doubts in any way is that it's not okay yeah that that yes the fact that
you're even asking this question I mean I mean look we can speculate all day about like trust
levels I'd be out of there in a fucking second dude I'd drop it like a hot potato and be gone
I don't I don't know like just imagine a situation where you find a girl who doesn't do this there's
plenty of them let me let me let me just let me just say my piece imagine like you know maybe you're
like maybe you've been friends maybe you've known this girl for like years and maybe maybe you guys
are like soulmates maybe you guys tell each other everything you're like super close she just and
then you know she starts doing this because it makes good money and she's totally open up front
with you about it and she's like none of this is all platonic I'm not comfortable with doing
anything beyond that it's just that it makes good money and like you know it's not hard work so I'm
gonna do it and maybe she does it and maybe like you talk about maybe she tells you funny stories
of these weird guys and you laugh about it together or something and like there's no any there's no
and you have no doubts at all that everything she's telling you is the unadulterated truth
I don't know that seems fine my only response to that is that uh uh uh oneitis is the deadliest
virus known to man that's all I've got to say about that what just move on get another bitch uh no
problem wait what the what the I'm just okay well then let me only semi move on and just
can we talk can we talk about this service because I'm still really confused I mean you just look
maybe I should I mean it's you could think of it like craigslist only for semi sexual acts too full
on sexual acts I think you just go there you like find the listings and you're like oh I want to do
this and then you message him and I think you just talk about and stuff is it just is it just
rich guys wanting to feel us mostly I may not rich guys but people also sugar babies who want to
find a rich guy to you know pay their bills it as I mean that makes sense right well I yeah you're
right that's probably look you know what I think seeing the range is a little more broad I'm sure
that there's probably just people who just like want friends and they just go on there like I'm
not I'm not casting judgment on the website frankly I don't give a shit it's you know friends did you
say they go on here to find me yes I think so like it's a huge spectrum of like that's that's not
how they that's not how they've branded maybe I'm not not friends in the way you know more than we
do Ben at this point you've gone to the website I have seen the homepage so I know I'm pretty much
an expert you know what Ben please everyone in the show notes there's gonna be a link to this dude's
wife please utilize her services she's gonna be really she needs it she needs it test test
and don't be afraid to get a little rough with her we I hear that she's down for that so okay
I will just say that on the spectrum of cuckoldry I would say that normal committed relationship
zero cuckoldry things like your your girl being like a sexualized snapchat model is another thing
doing the kind of like patreon ludes as so famously are done it's absolutely on the spectrum
then there's like porn stars in there somewhere I'd say and then there's full on getting cupped
like down at the deep end that that's a big jump down to that but we're all we're all on the spectrum
we're all on the spectrum and I'm and I'm just saying if you got you if you got what you're
comfortable with and you are fully convinced that those boundaries are not being crossed then
what's the problem yeah I was Ben I was Ben but again like don't be afraid to trust your instincts
if you feel uncomfortable I'd say that's very normal yeah and and I mean and I mean whatever
and and like set whatever boundaries you want yeah right like I'm not saying like like if your
boundaries are you know that you're not comfortable with the dates at all even if they are supposedly
platonic when it comes when it comes to or if your boundaries are farther than that that's fine
I mean sure if you're comfortable with that yeah yeah yeah yeah whatever they are you know I think
our culture likes to push inclusivity in some of this stuff when it might feel wrong for you
so like I don't know like hey man everybody's in a polyamorous relationship don't let that you know
don't let that I mean no there's nothing that I would not judge or think there was anything wrong
with not being okay with this yeah right I mean just as it's okay to feel okay about it yeah so it
is on the contrary as well so and it because it's you man it's you so uh do whatever you want do
whatever you want okay well that was that was an interesting question yeah there's a lot to unpack
there um that was a good that was a good question it didn't have a voice modulator and if only
when someone was looking out for the quality of these questions if only if only he had ended the
question with a piano yeah then he really would have a reclinch unfortunately he's being deleted
sorry you're not a pcb fan anymore okay we've got that that's fair uh we're gonna have none left at
the end of this episode uh another message uh oh sorry first message from mr cactuar okay this one's
real short so let's say what a name use one pokemon move to describe your last shit
water shot water water sports water sports is the one for me um string um wait hold on um slam slam
mud mud sport oh yeah explosion oh i had you probably an ice in a fire blast did my fucking
shitter ice beam you know feeling having some issues down there dude i got some slushy
shit let me tell you oh a sludge bomb sludge bomb for sure yeah i was gonna um god damn it um
oh man i like i'm sure there's a million great ones and i'm just how about how about fire spin
i'm just radiating heat a hyper beam uh uh oh what's that what's that uh uh signal beam
i'm casting signal beam down to the bowl and it's just you know um a lot of beams beams worked very
well for this uh uh shit well so i got uh dragon force uh you know try whatever it is my favorite
outrage outrage um oh god oh that's it you're five four three you didn't make a joke quota one
oh that's it that's all the time sorry ben's no longer a pzp member i was gonna say i was gonna
say sludge bomb natin you fucking snuck swiped it snatched you sniped it up what's well what's
another muck centric one uh minimize very yeah um i would describe my shit as uh vapers three page
22 posted uh uh earlier today that's what i'd describe it as yeah where was it on on on on
well you see but it was posted on patreon.com slash uh been saying oh interesting oh my favorite my
my homepage my go-to destination for all things entertainment on the internet my my hub my hub
for con for indie content yeah my hit my my hub for underfunded indie content and let's let's keep it
that way ladies and gentlemen all right guys guys tax guys taxes were fucking brutal are you are you
gonna get a refund though oh no really you're not like under the threshold or whatever well here
i don't i don't know how it works exactly here here's the thing that all my income all of my income
was um what what do you call it self-employment so with self-employment income so i okay my expenses
brought me well under the uh the taxable income like level but that doesn't matter because with
self-employment income all your income is taxable with self-employment with a self-employment tax
even if you are under the threshold that can't even if you're under the threshold if it's
self-employment tax you still get tax that doesn't mean that's crazy it's like oh like the self-employment
tax is like applied after the the deductions you're made and like it doesn't matter if you if you
you you get you get taxed on like all of your income including the stuff that is under the like
deduction oh you know the like the via the generalized deduction yeah yeah that like 1400 or
whatever the fuck it is it is 12 is 1200 in in my state anyway yeah yeah yeah so like my my overall
income minus expenses was well under that threshold but it because it wasn't zero it all got taxed
under the stuff it was fucking well okay i don't i don't get it it's like it's like 15 fucking percent
i thought it was more i mean i remember looking up like i put away 25 of all my income specifically
or all my all my online because of my my job like already gets taxed uh i put it i just put it away
for tax paying so i'm i'm happy if i pay extra or if i put away too much fantastic couldn't be
happier that's just extra money i'll save i mean i do i save most of my money like it's not like i
had spent it all and i had nothing you didn't pull a digi yeah i like yeah like i yeah i could pay it
but boy did it hurt um so yeah that's me out i didn't i did not real i did not realize that
i did not realize it worked that way i thought oh i'm gonna be under the threshold i'm gonna be
fine i probably won't have anything wrong wrong last year okay last year because i didn't
technically get yeah i made less overall and also the um the kickstarter like i did not get
the kickstarter payout until january so that was not so i did i did pay a little last year but it was
it was a lot less um i mean you think that that kickstarter income like that should all get eaten
up because like it's all goes to expenses and maybe there's some leftover as like income but like
you know ideally you'd think that it works that way but not not all of it yeah i mean not not all
of it and anything that wasn't um anything that wasn't eaten up with expenses i mean just a similar
example like the radcon three like that money came in like this year and like that was income in my
name so i put that on my taxes and stuff but like all the money got distributed to you guys and got
eaten up with stuff so like none of us made a profit at all which you know was fine but like so
theoretically like you'd think i wouldn't get taxed on that uh and i hope that's how it works out but
i guess we'll see if if it's if it's all if it all goes to expenses then it all gets deducted from
your taxable income i think is at least how it's i'd imagine so i mean i think so okay anyway all
right let's move on uh uh uh uh uh okay message from racism the only race i care about is nascar
okay go okay okay think about this nascar like the cars they they turn left i think that's the
direction they go because it's like a circle and they just go fucking left every time and left is
politics and uh nascar is propaganda thanks ted talk that that was my ted talk fuck you
you i think slovo zizek would love to hear you should uh you should write about all politics
in eva louis benz left like nascar you guys yeah but we got it we got it you know nascar is doing
god's work shifting that over to window we got to shift it left boys uh hashtag turn it's only it's
it's the right thing to do uh okay next up we've got a message from spike monster bang uh okay grand
go spike monster bang spike monster bang spike monster bang oh spike monster bang spike monster
bang it's up for the mic they drink spike monster bang and other shit too energy drink american
oh yeah i just like the american ooze at the end i mean the whole thing that that's great that was
incredible once you uh had your mic on i mean we weren't hearing you were performing that live
from antarctica you're pretty far from the mic when i start to play i mean if you're holding
like your guitar like below your mic or something i could see why it's like far or something but i
just i just cranked my head yeah i had to do that too your voices exploded my eardrums when you
started talking it but it was worth it for that american munchie did you coin that phrase that
term american ooze was that you sounds like something i would say no idea no okay all right i i think
that's an original um spike monster well that's a great one i love it it's fantastic american it's
good it's good uh i want to show you some modern day potion but oh yeah that's true modern day
potion american be careful with your spike don't drink it too fast you will pass the yeah is it that
strong i told you i had drank i i drank it thinking it was regular and then i i started
getting like legit i started getting dizzy because it's like just the caffeine
yeah yeah well there might be other stuff but mostly it's just okay okay uh all right next one
this is from voicemail anon i think there's like a public service announcement one okay go all right
so every episode you play the voicemails people send in and some of them are really great like
the them snakes skates voicemails yeah for example yeah them snakes i would like to listen to them again
if i could find them but i can't find them and i i know they exist on some uh fucking sound cloud
but i can't find this fucking sound cloud and i i know it exists because i've seen it before
like some a long time ago but i can't find it now i've gone through my google history and
everything all right so my question to you okay where's the voicemails guys hashtag where's the
voicemails yes good okay good there is only unlike the question of where's the podcast this
question actually has an answer i believe it does okay so i look this up ahead of time so it's sound
cloud dot com slash the dash pro dash crastonators those aren't underscores those are dashes and also
it'll be in the show notes although i thought it was in the fucking is it not in the general links
i guess i guess it must not be uh okay it's going to be in the show notes soundcloud.com
forward slash the dash pro dash crastonators that's the soundcloud but i also brought this up because
there's there's there's a thing going on um the soundcloud is full and so i'm being forced to week
by week delete old weeks voicemails to make room like we could pay for like a pro account and keep
them or something but like this one's free and that's pretty great so i'm i'm all about that uh
so we are losing history the voicemails are in the show they are the voicemails are they're all
embedded so like there's not much being lost so like i thought i don't i don't see i don't see
preservation as a problem okay i'm glad i'm glad to hear you say that because i was i was wondering
if anyone's concerned by that but uh okay great that guy felt like he was about he was like on the
verge of going into like a total screaming rant for a second there like he was going to go into
like like like labrin strom first thing you just scream his head off he's got that back his voice
where is the voicemails in the soundcloud i'm looking everywhere for it and i can't find it
he's just biting back his anger i guess yeah well fair enough uh question answered okay next up
we've got a message from the king of the cosmos go hello my pc princess oh yeah thank you so much
for all that you've done rolling up this delicious podcast
much but i have one last request if you would please send me fan art of the delicious girl
version of endless war then i the king of the cosmos can sleep well okay all right all right
all right here here's who you're gonna have to go to that who's the person that who's the person
that made that made the uh it was the i'm gonna get for you here's maybe you're gonna add on discord
gabriel the star man hashtag no don't do it don't dox that man he doesn't deserve it no it's not it's
not gabriel the star man i think he's talking about endless war from the day well he is but but but
gabriel made porn of him of her rather oh really okay okay okay what was it okay yeah i mean he's
the original you know creator in a way right i mean i'll endorse gabriel the star man but um
i want to find i want to shout out the guy who did isn't it that girl isn't that girl with
like the round purple art you know i'm talking about i don't know if it's a girl or a guy uh
asha my asha i mean yeah isn't it asha am or something like that no no no no asha did not
do the specifically of did she do the art of digi in that though she did right wait i found it i
found it the endless war artist for the dating sim specifically is at draw kaya that's d r a w k
you want to put that in the show notes should we do that uh yeah okay post it in the in the
links i mean i yeah uh but uh so so anyone who makes art that's the answer go on make fan art and
then uh at tpcrasnators and if it's good we'll retweet it so do it and also and also play the
day yes to experience the magic i still haven't done oh one piece of shit you haven't okay me and
munchie played it on the uh endless war good the it was so great playing it on the endless war
that's great maybe i'll watch that i mean i want to play myself too and then and then uh the the man
himself or the woman heard the woman himself came on and we all fucking lost that's great yeah
that's great from his last we could oh it's like that that one moment yeah yeah yeah that's such a
legendary moment i went back and watched it and like i swear to god the same frame sands appears
we are already screaming like it's such an instant reaction like there's no delay whatsoever
i made a little thing okay anyway moving on moving on we got riddle my ass batman
waiting again it's time for our favorite show of the week and let's get to it it's gonna be someone
who's not even here yeah fuck you wall oh good you're here munchie i just wanted to let you know
that episode 75 you were talking about legal world and bang oh sorry batman i was aiming for the
riddler oh fucking idiots you fucking idiot you shot me in the eye this is why you don't use guns
batman spot on my god because i fucking urge you're lucky i'm batman oh that might have killed me
fucking idiot munchie take over for this okay riddler oh wait i'm batman okay
go ahead with your next riddle uh very well riddle my ass batman i mean munchie
suicide is that's all i need to hear i'm so confused wow okay release him
am i that much of a one trick pony yes now help batman
well why don't you and the batman be able to say that we're really really
we're really members of the pcp do the next time i find out same pcp time same pcp channel
well listen i didn't i didn't you know i didn't want to spoil my appearance here we recorded these
back in june and we've just been waiting for them to be released and it was an honor working with
batman and riddle my ass batman uh to make this wonderful project you know it was a great
collaboration yeah it was great a good work munchie yeah yeah yeah how many uh how many do we have
left we got only have like three or four probably it's gotta be like four i love the pause that he
does to turn the page i don't know if that was like was that real intentional fully work or if that
he actually had script uh i've got a spoiler for you it wasn't intentional i don't know man there's a
lot there's a lot of thought clearly put into these there's there's this deep it's it's really
run deep uh and the attention to detail like that is what elevates it about that that's true you
know he doesn't resort to gimmicks like a piano solo or a voice monitor it's just pure quality pure
storytelling just the raw the pure pathos yes everyone the immersion he's you know what he's
got you know what he's got that the other ones don't enter gauging
damn i'm right enter gauged every single time i hear riddle my ass batman wow enter gaugment
spike off the charts and i applaud him that should be the title of this episode is pcb episode
151 that's true i'm right i'm making a note of that okay uh moving on let's go you're welcome tom um
i'm gonna have to shoot you again like i shot batman you know just on accident quote unquote yeah
don't worry about it it's fine it's good okay uh we've got one last fucking thing to do oh my god
there's one more and this one's got free today yeah well this one's simply called yo nate it's called
yo nate uh sure let's see what he's got ready and go you all got a question for me uh is your girl
retarded because you look like that for nico they would take advantage of a handcuff bitch and she
looks retarded please what i literally could not understand i literally could not understand the word
of that uh so he was asking if michelle's retarded correct yeah i mean i think you're the kind of
person who had data retarded first so okay so in this indecipherable accident he calls up and
he's just like hey buddy you know what is your girlfriend retarded just just thought that would
be in character anyway see ya for the first time ever i think i need to hear that one more time
for clarity's sake we're gonna repeat this one yeah yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna really okay so editor uh
listen up prick up those ears and splice that shit in okay here we go and go you all got a question
for me uh is your girl retarded because you look like that for nico they would take advantage of a
handcuff bitch and she looks retarded it was like you look like the kind you look like the kind of nigger
who would take advantage of that kind of bitch i believe and he says and also she looks retarded
okay i believe that's what would said um well it takes another waiting we're waiting for your
answer wait what was the question again like would i no no no is she retarded is she retarded
simply post so so what uh you know i mean i really think retardation is a spectrum and is first of
all yeah second of all it's in the eye of the beholder uh it's a social construct uh these
things can't be defined by modern day language uh you gotta understand the context there's the
there's an odd spectrum of retardation spectrum the cut the cut yeah you gotta take all these
factors seriously okay we want a steel man here so so let's take let's take his argument and
struggle okay good so so so here is what he's pausing she he's asking you if your girlfriend
is retarded right here is the evidence you look like the kind of nigger that would take advantage
of that kind of bitch and secondly she looks retarded okay well okay so let's and let's
analyze both of these arguments you look like the kind of nigger that would take advantage of that
kind of bitch that's right do we think this is accurate because i okay well let's okay aesthetically
like visually definitely 100 yeah definitely a lot of goodwill from this man so i'm i'm inclined to
to you know take give him a lot of leverage in this debate in this yeah you know so that
definitely checks out definitely think i mean you know my my my my answer my answer i am that kind
of nigger that's all i can say that's that's really all there is to say uh and and secondly uh she
looks retarded yeah i mean it's guilty is charged ladies and gentlemen i mean there's no there's no
getting away from that one uh check out both of those i mean i think we just have to conclude
i mean after presenting his argument as best we could i think he's just he's got a point here i
think he's just unequivocally correct and that's all there is to say one more time i beg you one
one more you know what all right let's hear this one more time for the road ladies and gentlemen
all right this is this is the surprise sleeper hey yo nate the the little known uh wonderful
you know voicemail maker okay one more time here we go go you got a question for me uh
is your girl retarded because you look like that for nigger they would take advantage of
fucking cow bitch and she looks retarded please handicap type a nigger who'd take advantage of
a handicap bitch he says it really fast be saying take advantage of a handicap yeah this is a work
of art on the one hand there's like the the casual like you know racial slur thrown at me
which i appreciate in value so like on the one hand i'm down i'm vibing with this guy and on
the other hand there's the casual like refer reference to my girlfriend as a bitch and you know
just like calling her just just hearted just the sort of casual insinuation that you are right
that i am and taking advantage of the mentally challenged by a colloquial yeah a colloquial
i just gotta say i've like i've encountered a few saints in my life but i think we've stumbled
upon another one right here ladies and gentlemen yo nate you know i'm calling it guys i'm using
my executive privilege if i ever get if i get one i'm using it now inducted into the fan hollow
fame yo yeah welcome yeah yeah yeah agree agree agree welcome hi hall fame a star a star is born
so we need to document that we need some documentation we need like a soundbite to play
when's a new star like oh it's like like when a new angel is inducted into the pcb hollow fame like
a star streaks across the sky and a new constellation is formed in the sky the we should just play the
bang spike monster game to uh to commemorate it i agree i agree okay well that's it ladies and
gentlemen that's the last voicemail we've learned we've learned we've learned that nate you know is
a type of person who would you know i'm the type of nigga i'm just that kind of nigga you know what
i've been i've been avoiding the n bomb a while but it just feels good to just be a
downhole nigga in the episode in the episode we go ladies and gentlemen all right he said it first
he did it it's his fault yeah we blame it on yo nate okay uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators
for all your racial slur homes that's the place you want to be we got bonus episodes there's one
coming out i think like like four or five days have to hear this so get excited for that it's
gonna be great it it should be good i think it's gonna be good uh follow us on twitter at tp
procrastinators send us your fan art of sexy or not sexy endless war fem bot version that'll be nice
that'll be good um we'll we'll retweet that you'll you'll you'll see good things to see what you
want to say you know how um how like in fandoms there will be like a you know the fan arts will
take a character yeah and then put them in various different alternate universe you know versions
of course of course so so you know like there's there's trickster john agbert for existence
i want a fan of the pcp but like like explanation point like to differentiate different universe
all of us as if we we were the type of person who would fuck a retarded person
so so nate we say exactly the same i mean you know damn that down syndrome look real good on you
girl that's all i'm saying you definitely look like a handicap bitch i would follow them so well
like that the hairpin of the girl is like an extra x chromosome like inner yeah oh okay all right
it's x chromosome chance uh we love you everybody hope you have a great time listen to the pcp uh
give us your money on patreon.com slash the procrastinators really appreciate five dollars
one dollar it funds nate's horrible horrible addiction picking up people at the mental
institution uh you know they need love too man they need love too um that the admin four percent
is going right to fucking the looney band that's where it goes it's right it's going right to
to seeking.com seeking arrangements with the local mental institution yeah i'm just you know we can
get about we can get a mutually beneficial arrangement a real uh what's the word a conveyor
about of pleasure for all involved that's what we need pledged pledged to our patreon so we can all
be sugar daddies on seeking arrangements dot it's the ethical thing to do experience you know this is
like way experienced wealthy guys who know how to totally get money if we like we're like hey guys
if you want to hang out with me you can pay me like 20 dollars you know okay dude dude it's true
let's start let's literally start a pcp account on seeking literally yes and get like i already
feel a little bit like a whore when i just stream on twitch i just interact with human beings because
like i'm there for their pleasure you know and this is uh this is just pushing it we'll get back
to you it's just the logical conclusion of what we've been doing i mean you're right friendship
simulator interactive twitch you know streams and whatnot what are youtube videos but you know
sexual stimulation i ask you that okay uh that's it everybody you know you know the deal uh we'll
see you next week another episode thanks for being here um we're done we're out go play the dating
simulator uh we retweeted at tpcras or at tpcras news go play that uh let us know how it is art
fan art give us fan art i demand fan art the answer is great and we'll see leave a voicemail
speak pipe link down below and have a beautiful night bye
i am an asshole i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it