I'm gonna bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello, um, whatever.
Hello, uh, uh, I'm back.
The PZP is back, um, uh, and better than ever.
I don't know about that one.
I'm sorry, I'm feeling, you know, you ever have one of those days where you're like, uh, don't bother me till I've had my coffee, but then you get your coffee and you still don't want to be bothered?
Yeah, that's, that's cold every day.
That's me. I've been up for exactly half an hour.
And I got, okay, my big, the big news for me is that I got new internet, which means, um, it's time for me to start, to try to start streaming soon.
I'm gonna stream.
Hooray.
Hooray, I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to stream, I'm gonna stream, I wanna stream the whole, uh, Battle Network series.
This week, sometime this week, I'll try like a test stream.
And if it works with no problem, then I will announce that the Battle Network extravaganza will begin.
Uh, and then I'll be doing that for God knows how long.
I'll make sure to stream exactly the same time to pilfer viewers.
Yes, we should divide and conquer, they say.
They mean it about yourself.
Um, I'm just looking, oh, and I'm just, and I'm just, and I'm just seething.
I'm just seething because this is my first time trying to discord call with my new internet, and it's working fine.
It's working great, except that the little green ring that says I'm talking doesn't, isn't, isn't working.
And I, I can't stand it.
I mean, I can see it, so I guess your discord's a little cringe at the moment.
Inexplicable, inexplicable.
Yeah, um, well, you know, uh, frickin, uh, the, let me, let me complain about other problems.
Um, the internet seems to be working good except for this, but this seems this is probably not even a real problem.
But there is another real problem, which is I had a, I had a torrents.
My torrents were downloading, and I had one torrent I was downloading, and it has stopped downloading since I switched networks.
And I don't know if it has anything to do with the network itself, or if maybe there's just no seeds seething the torrent anymore.
It would just be a coincidence.
Uh, but I got this big torrent that I was downloading for weeks, and now it's stuck at like 70% done.
And it was only gonna be, it was gonna be maybe another week, and I just want it.
I just want it so bad.
And I, and I don't know what to do.
I'm lost.
What are you torrenting?
What are you stealing?
Well, I'll just say it.
Since I had thought that I might do a history of Digi or the history of the PCP sort of lecture,
I was torrenting the DigiBro archive just to have everything.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I mean, it's a lot.
It's like, it's like, it's like, I think it's almost like a hundred, I think it's like almost a terabyte, all told.
Like the entire archive in all five parts.
Are you gonna watch it?
No, god, no, I just, I'm just putting it in a folder to just have it for reference in case I need stuff.
But yeah, the first parts one, two, three, and five are done.
And part four is all, is 600 gigabytes.
And it is, about 500 of it is done.
And now it's, it's just kind of stuck there.
And it's just, I just, maybe I'll ask Tarbuck, maybe I'll ask Tarbuck if he can seed again or something.
Because I see zero seeds.
So might not have anything to do with my internet actually.
I kind of imagine that many people are seeding that specific thing.
No, but there were, no, but I mean, it did get, it did get this far.
There were people seeding it up to, you know, to get me this 70% done.
So, you know, it's, it's, it should work.
Why would it stop now?
I don't know.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's all, that's all.
The last week, sorry for not appearing.
No, no problem.
No problem.
You got it.
You got a, nobody's perfect.
Yeah.
But the last, this whole last week I've been mostly, I have been mostly binging by binging
by a cool soul.
You ever heard of that?
Yeah.
I watched the first, I think like three seasons of it.
I watched it up to when it was current, when I watched it like three or four years ago,
I think.
So, I never finished it.
Have you finished it?
I mean, it's finished and I'm getting, I'm on season, the last season right now, just
beginning.
Okay.
So, we might, we might be pretty, I might have gotten to about the same place you have,
or something like that.
Yeah, it was a good show.
I did like it, but I never, yeah, it wasn't done back when I watched it.
And I've had a meaning to finish it ever since, since I heard it finished and everyone says
Kirk is such a genius.
And La-de-da.
Bob Odenkirk is such an actor.
I mean, I like Bob Odenkirk.
He's great.
He's an actor.
He's a good comedian too.
You ever see Mr. Show?
I didn't see Mr. Show, but I did see him on Tim and Eric's awesome show as like some of
the Cinco product stuff.
I think, I think Bob Odenkirk might have been like one of the guys who sort of like, who
sort of like backed Tim and Eric in their early days.
I think he sort of might have been there like patron.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I've heard that somewhere.
The lineage of these things.
That's just, that's just something I heard.
But anyway, Bob, yeah, I better call Saul.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I think Breaking Bad is a better show.
Wow.
But I think, I, well, this is the thing.
People say-
I've heard people go both ways on that.
I mean, I was sold on Better Call Saul being like way better or not way better, but like,
it's better than Breaking Bad, bro.
Yeah.
I'm like, hmm, well, it's the same show guys, same writers, you know, but probably good.
It is very good.
Gilligan, right?
Vince Gilligan.
Like showrunner?
Yeah.
I have one major problem with it.
It's not like a deal breaker, but it is undeniable that this is not actually-
a Saul show.
It is two shows.
It is a lawyer show about the rise of Saul Goodman from his lowly status.
There's a little boy behind his nail salon.
Yeah.
And then it's also the story of Mike Ermentraut and his introduction into the criminal underworld.
Mike is the old guy, right?
Yeah.
And I like these shows, but I think they sort of take a little-
Mike should have had his own show?
I think they take a little too much away from each other because they don't really meet up
until like season five.
They sort of like have passing like interactions here and there early on and then, you know,
season three and stuff.
But like mostly it's like Kim Wexler, Jimmy McGill, Chuck and all that lawyer stuff.
And then separately, almost completely separate at points is Mike and Gus and the Salamancos.
And that's- I think it's just made for the show being like very slow paced.
And I was like, when are they gonna do something together?
And it's like right at the end of the show and it's like now it's ramping up.
And I do like all the seasons.
I don't have like problems with the show, but I feel like it was overhyped in that sense.
Because like if you watch Breaking Bad, seeing how Gus built his empire or like-
Yeah.
It's interesting.
It's cool.
And Mike is cool.
And it's like cool.
Yeah.
But it's sort of like fan service in a good way, but like it's still fan service.
It doesn't like propel the story of Jimmy McGill.
It sort of like takes away from- it sort of pauses his story to talk about this thing for a bit.
And then very slowly, both stories-
That's what- that's the pacing.
That's the pacing issue I have.
That's my major issue.
It causes a pacing issue.
Do you think that like the Gus and Mike backstory, do you think it like doesn't really add to the characters
that were already established in Breaking Bad?
I think in Breaking Bad, the characters are very well established.
And this is just sort of like, it's like ancillary material.
You know, if you want to know a little bit extra, it's like behind the scenes, not behind the scenes, but like extra content, DLC bonus episodes.
The Gus DLC, sure, I understand.
Yeah.
Because like everything, obviously Breaking Bad is made to be contained.
So like every character in there is explained just enough so that they are compelling and you care about them and you care about what they're doing.
And all the while, Walter White is a far more insane protagonist that drives the story forward a lot more quickly and everything is connected to him.
And I think Breaking Bad just makes for a better viewing experience overall.
But do like Better Call Saul, don't kill me, don't kill me everyone.
It's very good.
I like all the cinematography, it's perfectly cinematographized, great acting.
I love Kim Wexler, she's the best character ever.
Which one's Kim Wexler?
The Ponytail Lady.
What does she do?
I do remember her, I kind of am.
She's Jimmy's best friend, lawyer lady.
Okay.
What does she do though?
She does lawyering.
Okay, that's good.
And she's a friend and she's a strong character.
She has sometimes not more protagonism power than Jimmy, but like I feel like you could have a show about Kim.
Probably.
She's got enough like gumption for that.
That's cool.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, I'm looking at a weird video of a Pokemon.
That is as usual.
And it's fucked up.
Do you want to hear some great news?
Some great news, yes.
Some great, some incredibly, some incredibly, well you know Ben Hughes, right?
On Twitter.
No.
You will.
He's the Team Eor stared at Idiolops, a prehistoric cesiosaur synapses that lived in southwestern
United States early Paramin period.
Team Eor, which is Team Eor and his six girlfriends.
What is it?
Ruth Powers, Laura Powers, Alith and Taylor, Ruth Powers Jr.
Who's the other two girlfriends?
He's got six girlfriends.
I believe it.
I mean, I'm a big Eor fan and I've been a lifelong, lifelong Team Eor.
So, you know, I get it.
I can't remember the names of these two even more obscure characters than Ruth Powers Jr.
if you can believe it.
They are Simpsons females.
Yeah, Simpsons females stared in awe at the platyhysterics, a prehistoric Temnospondyl
amphibian with sailbag.
Anyway, the great news is, turns out Team Eor got married on New Year's.
They got married on January 1st, 2023 and now the six girlfriends have become six wives.
Hell yeah, Eor.
I guess I'll get it, Eor, because I saw him posting about Eor and his wives, a.k.a. Team Eor.
And I said, I didn't know they were married and he told me, yeah, they got married on New Year's
and I said, congratulations.
I almost said many happy returns because I know that in Winnie the Pooh, at least in the old Winnie the Pooh,
they say many happy returns to Eor.
I think it's to Eor on his birthday, but it turns out many happy returns is specifically a birthday thing.
You don't just say that on like any happy occasion.
You say it on your birthday, so I didn't say that.
Why is that?
What does it mean?
I hope you'll return to the same date next year.
Yes, I think it basically means I hope you'll have many more birthdays that are happening.
Yeah, if you say that during a wedding.
Yeah, it'd be weird.
So I dodged that bullet.
I wouldn't want to embarrass myself in front of the venues, the Simpsons ninjas, no sexy for me and free guy.
I should draw him some ninjas.
Did you draw him some ninjas or did someone else?
Someone else did.
I can't remember if I, no, I don't think so.
A couple people have.
I kind of would like to just for fun, but also I don't want to.
It would be difficult to not draw sexy, no sexy.
I mean, I would not struggle with that part of it.
I'm saying I would.
I would just struggle with just motivating myself to do anything part of it.
Bro.
That's so relate.
That's so relatable.
Artist problems.
Look at the blank page.
Me and where SpongeBob looks at the blank page and it has the big fancy the written on it.
At least he wrote a the.
Yeah.
At least he wrote a big.
Well, what have I ever done?
But yeah, then it's like January, it's cold.
I could have started the new year being like hitting the ground running and being like, okay, it's time to work.
But it's cold and it's, I don't want to.
I'm just, I'm not going to do that.
I'm going to binge medical soil till it's warm.
Yeah.
Then I can come out of my cocoon.
I said that I was going to have that stuff done by the end of the year and it's two weeks into the new year and it's not done.
I, it's, you know, that's have no make no excuses.
But yesterday I did work on it some more and you know, it's it's coming along and it's just really, I think I've complained about this before.
So I won't go into it too long.
But you know, it's I'm just, I'm just literally like taking blocks of text and moving them around just trying to make them fit on as few pages as possible.
And it's just very tedious and it's very dull work and I don't like it.
And I've been procrastinating like the name of the podcast and I've been playing Noida again.
I've fallen back into my old ways of playing Noida, which is a terrible thing.
Noida is a bad game for me.
It's a good game for you, the listener, and you should try it and play it.
But for me, it's bad because I understand it too well and it's just like playing solitaire now.
It's just, it's just like playing anything.
Yeah.
It's just, it's just going through emotions.
I mean, solitaire can be fun, even if you know how to do it.
Well, I don't, well, I don't play it.
I don't actually know how to do it.
But sure, it's fun.
It's fun, I guess, but it's ultimately a waste of time.
It's not that bad.
I mean, most things are, if they're like a video game experience, it's just like whatever.
I mean, I've been doing that.
You're right.
I play like Picross on like a random Picross generator and I've like, I fail over and over again.
I, it's just like, well, I mean, I'm spent, I'm sitting here.
Like, what am I actually doing?
I'm sitting here listening to something and clicking cubes, clicking squares.
Clicking cubes, like an addict.
And I'm like, and I'm like, oh, really, I should be doing some other game, you know, a better game.
But then, like, every game is just clicking squares.
When you get right down to it, when you get right down to it, it's true.
It's true.
It doesn't really matter.
Like if, like, there's this, I don't know, compulsion, this feeling of like worthiness,
like you need your time to be filled with the best shit, like the absolute best stuff ever.
Yeah.
And I have all of these games like, oh, I could, I could play that game again.
I could be experiencing the classics, the canon, the masterpieces.
I know.
I could go to the, oh, criterion collection.
Let's see what they got.
I could be, why did I waste, man, in the time I've spent playing Noida, I could have played The Last of Us,
the only, the only video game to tell a story in ever.
That wasn't, I was an all right video game.
I enjoyed that one.
Yeah.
I could have played it like 200 times.
But then, but then I go back to like, oh, I'm just going to hop on RuneScape and click some, some coal or get some coal for like an hour or three.
And I'm like, wow, I could have done it other games, but I don't know.
Do I need to worry about that?
You could have been mining that coal in real life.
You could have, you could have that much real coal.
Yeah.
We've got an energy crisis right now.
There's the fuel prices through the roof.
I just need to go into like the mines and get some free coal.
What we have give is a crisis of democracy.
Instead of playing video games, you could have gone to Ukraine and defended democracy against the East, against the insidious Orient.
What do you have to say for yourself?
They're transphobic.
They wouldn't give me a gun.
That's true.
All right.
You know what?
You got a better excuse than I do.
There's, for me, I have no good reason to not go over there and join the Azov Battalion.
Specifically them.
It's the only one I've heard of.
So yeah, I just signed, I just, I checked the box on that one on my sign up sheet.
I mean, you are a grizzled veteran.
You know, you have all the qualities.
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, I'm Slavic.
I'll fit right in.
I'll just, I'll just change the spelling of my name.
Just change the I to a Y.
The PCP from the fucking trenches.
Radcon 5, live from Keef.
We're being, we're being shelled.
Oh yeah, it's Keef, all right.
Keef's mostly all right.
Oh good.
We should go to the front lines.
We should get the real action shots.
Yeah, we should do it.
We should get shelled.
It'd be like Redcon arena.
We do get shelled.
Redcon's real arena, but in real life with real guns.
Oh God.
Yes.
We get the GoPro's back.
Finally, finally, these GoPro's are paying for themselves.
Did you see, I have two, now I have two things.
Did you see like the Miss Universe pageant?
Did you see the Ukraine Miss Universe?
I don't know.
I've never watched Miss Anything.
Okay.
Well, the Miss Universe pageant, I guess, was this week.
And I saw some clips of some, there was one thing where they all just came out on stage
wearing this huge elaborate like costume that like represented their country
and America's was fucking stupid.
Was it a burger?
No, it was the moon.
Well, because they went to it.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's, is this supposed to be like a dig at Russia?
Like how we beat you to the moon idiots?
Because I don't like, what about America?
Why would they be like, oh yeah, America, hmm, it's 2023.
What has America done?
Well, we went to the moon.
That's pretty good.
It was a while ago, but yeah.
The flag's still there as far as I know.
Probably.
Has another like landing of a human person taken place on the moon since the first one?
Well, a bunch of, I think America has been to the moon a bunch of times.
But like, as like a landing expedition.
Because that's more, that's more confusing than like a satellite or like a little robot collecting samples or whatever.
I, I want to say I think so.
There's been a few.
Hang on.
But anyway, I just bring it up because Miss Ukraine just looked so fucking awesome.
I'm going to try to get pictures.
Yeah.
Here I find a freaking picture of this goddamn bullshit.
Oh, it's contra points.
It kind of does look like contra points.
You know what?
Oh, this is a contra points like, like costume in a video.
Yeah, exactly what she would wear.
The Odessa Journal reported on it.
She got a sword this school.
She's the Archangel Michael or she's dressed like the Archangel Michael.
She looks like some of those like.
I'm sorry.
Powerful Alliance priests in World of Warcraft.
Yeah, it's a bit, it's a bit, it's a bit, it's a bit 40k.
It's a bit Warhammer 40k looking.
She looks, she looks like a sister of battle who would be leading like a space marine battalion or something.
I mean, I'm sorry, but like it's, it rules.
It's awesome.
It's my aesthetic.
I like it.
Yeah.
Now I'm just imagining Miss America, like just wearing like a sphere of the moon with her head popping out the top.
Well, let me try.
Is that what it looked like?
No.
Because that should have been, that should have been it.
She should have rolled on to stage.
No, it looked like a freaking this for some reason is what they decided to go with.
I'm sure that I'm sure.
Oh, freaking Miss El Salvador look was a Bitcoin, which is like even worse.
So like in terms of like cringy costumes.
Oh my God, it's she's mega mind.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's Miss USA.
Here's Miss El Salvador on the left.
I don't know what country that is on the right.
You know, kind of funny.
It's it's it's it's a it's a mega punks giant brain.
You mean the moon?
The moon.
It's just so it's a very funny bulbous thing on the top of the head.
I'm I'm think it's got to be like a weird like fuck Russia thing.
Why?
Who fucking cares about the moon?
Yeah.
The Ukraine one, the lady comes out and the announcers.
Yeah, it's about like, you know, like the Archangel Michael is like aiding them in the in the fight, right?
Like references to their fight their fight their battle.
So it's like Russia.
And I mean, frankly, just made me think that maybe the Russians were right.
Maybe Ukraine's got to go if they're if they're going to if they're going to be a little pussy about it.
I'm sorry.
It's not true.
It's not what I actually thought.
I just like the costume.
All right.
She looks like she looks like the fucking alien from American dead.
Yeah, looks so fucking silly.
It does.
This looks like a giant, especially from from the straight ahead angle.
Yeah.
It looks like she's got a big gray head.
Fucking fucking good.
Good for her.
Who gives the best head?
It's it's her.
The moon.
The moon does.
Well, how did I even get on this subject of this moon lady?
You brought it up.
Oh, we were talking about Redcon 5 and Redcon 5 live live from life from Donbass or whatever.
Yeah.
If we go if we get costumes like this, then it'll be good.
That'll be part of the stretch goal for the Kickstarter.
I get the sword and wings and I fly over and go.
I don't want to go into too much detail, but did you see what did you see what Nate said in the in the PCP all business chat?
Is the the dojin almost finished?
Is that what he said?
Well, the dojin is is almost finished.
And also the OVA is like almost finished.
Oh, yes, the OVA.
That's what I meant.
Yeah.
It's like I'm not going to give like a hard date or anything, but it's like mostly done.
So like we might be releasing that in maybe the next couple weeks.
Perhaps.
Hell yeah.
I'll make you imagine.
Watch it.
Can you?
Yeah, I don't I'm a little scared.
I might not be actually able to watch it myself, but oh well.
Cringe.
It'll be cringe.
And you know what?
We deliver eventually.
It's I it's it's and then we get our Radcon money finally.
Yeah.
So that'll be good.
Oh, make sure to buy it like a business expense thing so I can take it off my taxes for this
year.
Like what?
I don't know because if I'm going to get a big lump sum of Radcon money, I need like
something to offset it.
I need to.
You do?
Well, they're going to take me with taxes.
They're going to tax me.
I don't want to be taxed.
Put it.
That's so scary.
My money is going to go away.
I need to buy like a like a cool thing that I'm going to buy a car.
You're absolutely right.
When you get whenever when you get paid, you go like, oh shit, I can't I can't let them
tax me.
I got to spend it.
I got to spend it immediately.
I got to get rid of it.
That's the thing.
When you get paid, you got to make sure you get rid of the money right away, lest you
be taxed on it.
I mean, it's true.
I'm not going to get rid of all of it.
I just want to get under the threshold because then I'll have like things that I, you know,
if I need things, I should buy them.
I mean, yeah, if you need to buy things for no reason.
That's silly.
That's speaking of speaking of buying things for no reason.
I did.
Here, a Botster commission.
Oh, yeah.
It looked really good.
It's the Clarissa Gunsmoke 3D experience.
Let me get it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Let's show that.
I wanted to get one of these, but they always sell out so quick.
Oh, does she have have limited slots?
She has limited slots like every month she takes on like four and I keep I kept missing
it over and over again.
I would DM her.
She said, oh, just too late.
Finally, this time, yeah, I managed to get in.
Actually, she let me in because she was feeling pity on me.
Well, take what you can get.
I guess.
Yeah, but it was it's great.
It does look it does look really good.
Do you I'm kind of curious.
Do you mind talking about like how much it costs?
I mean, her prices are public when she puts the thing.
It's like 500 bucks for this animation.
Yeah.
You can get just the model, which is cheaper, but I wanted the I wanted the
shooty gun. I wanted the cool animation.
OK, I see.
You can pay even more to get like a more elaborate animation.
Yeah, like a simple one.
So this was the simple animation.
OK, yeah, still quite right.
Like really nice.
I mean, yeah, animating.
Yeah.
I see you could like pay extra for like a game ready like source files.
What is that if you if you wanted to get the model with like
everything rigged because to animate it, you've got to rig it anyway.
Yeah. So I mean, I feel like she's got the model rigged, right?
Like she had to have made it to make the animation.
Yeah. Yeah.
So like if I if I wanted to turn it into a game, I would need to.
I didn't pay for that extra bit just because I don't have like plans
or really the know how to make a video game.
All by myself, that model.
I do like the idea, though, it would be cool to have a little
Clarissa like shoot game.
I kind of assumed that like somewhere in your head, you were like
if it may be not necessarily going to be like, OK, this is for a game,
like I'm planning a game, but you must have thought like I could put this in a game.
I did think it for a while.
It's just a little it was like some how much extra was it for the game ready?
It's like it's like two hundred bucks or it's like two hundred ninety.
I think it's two hundred ninety.
And I was just wondering, I don't really know what goes into it,
but it made me wonder, like, is it is it like more work to like
make them quote unquote game ready?
Like this.
Do they does it have to do something to the or is it just like
for three hundred dollars, she'll she'll hand over the file.
She already has law.
I I'm not sure.
Yeah.
I'm hoping that in the future, I can say, hey, can I if I need to,
like I can say, could I pay for the the file if that's OK?
Because if she I assume it is some other work.
I wouldn't be maybe if I like inverse kinematics or like various other things.
I don't even know whether that's necessary,
but like game ready means drag and drop and it's working.
So probably something.
I mean, I don't really know how to use 3D model data.
So I have no I really have no I have no idea what would what goes into like it.
I mean, I assume.
I mean, she has something.
She has some model and some rigging.
She must have it in order to have made this animation.
And maybe it might be like incomplete.
Uh, uh, maybe I don't know.
I don't know what would be different about a quote unquote game ready version.
Yeah, I guess I'll have to ask.
I was I was just curious.
I was just curious about that because I saw that option and I was like, damn,
three hundred three hundred dollars just to like.
I mean, I mean, I guess I don't know.
I thought the analogy I thought of was like,
what if you what if you commissioned like an artist to draw a art for you?
And then I don't know.
They were like, well, for some extra money, I'll give you the like
Photoshop, you know, layer files and stuff.
Like sometimes people do that.
I guess I guess I'm going to do that.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
I think I think a lot of it could be that if you have a game ready version.
Then that's more than just a cool animation and like an image
that has been made for you.
It is work that you can then go on to make money with if you build a game around it.
Yeah. So it's like more industry, like, oh, I've I've been commissioned
to make a product for like an asset for your game,
which is different from making a little video file.
I believe that there is probably more stuff that's involved.
In that, like I say, I don't really know how to do any of this stuff.
But the animation just looks really good.
Yes, exactly.
I wanted the little the little pixelated smoke cloud.
The most with the squares.
Yeah, yeah, I just I just.
Boss boss is pretty good at what she does.
She like she like got the.
Oh, she got like noticed or something.
Is she big because of the the the the the the bloodborne stuff, the PSX bloodborne?
I yes, I think she made PSX bloodborne as a joke.
Well, not as a joke, just as a little fun thing.
And then it turned into a big thing.
Yeah.
And she posted like dev updates on our Twitter.
That grew.
Just because, oh, my God, bloodborne, but like PS1.
That's I mean, it does it does look good.
It does look good.
And then more recently, she's started working on a race here.
Bloodborne cart, which is a little occasionally she'll drop a new like
racer and it'll be like, oh, it's it's the crow ladies.
I lean the crow.
The latest one.
I got Gerriman, you got the the guy with the.
It makes his face.
With the cage on his head, you know, that guy.
I mean, is it like blood wig?
Yeah, Nicolash, the scholar or something like that, the insane boy.
Yes, the guy who runs away.
Yeah.
I I was looking at I was looking at a video of bloodborne cart
and I was watching your little racer like turn right, turn left, whatever.
And I was thinking, you know, it has such it has such crunchy pixel, right?
Like these are these are polygonal models, but they are they are they are
displaying in such crisp pixelated.
You know what I'm talking about?
Well, you mean fidelity is too high for.
No, no, no, this is this.
I mean, well, I just mean, what do I mean?
It's the way you're looking at the carts and they're crunchy and crispy.
They're they're crunchy and crispy.
How do I even explain what what I'm seeing?
It's like, I don't know, man, you can just see the pixels, you can just see the pixels.
Yeah, you can.
That's the idea is I know, I know, I know.
But like, but the the poly the polygonal model is is built on math, right?
So like like the polygon is like theoretically perfect.
Yes, just a it's two points in between them.
What? Yeah, yeah, exactly.
So what I'm saying is like to achieve that kind of like pixel display, like that pixel.
Is it like, is that what's called a shader?
Is like, do you apply a shader to a model in order to render it in a way
that is like sort of crunched down into pixels
that match a certain a certain resolution or something like that?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I mean, I'm not I'm not sure because if you had an example image,
I could tell you exactly what it is.
But I think there are a few shaders going on with the footage.
Sometimes she has like a CRT like filter that makes it look like
it's on a CRT, I think the textures she uses are very low res anyway.
So they just have pixels in them because that's how big they are.
Yeah. And the you know, low polygon count means there'll be hard edges.
And I assume if you're talking about like how the edges look,
they would be aliased instead of anti aliased.
They would be you draw a diagonal line.
And yeah, I guess I guess you would use some shader to like
to have like the resolution, the resolution of the final image be like
two forty by four eighty or whatever, rather than ten eighty P.
I kept, you know, it then blown up when I was.
I guess what I'm saying is when I was making Phantom's Revenge,
now I'm a I'm a hack and I didn't know what I was doing.
And I know there must have been an easier way to do this.
I pretty much just fucked this up completely.
I could have simply I'm sure there would have been a way to just
have the window, have the game window itself
be displaying a pretty like lower resolution image
in what do you call it, a lower resolution image
just at a higher like the
size to just like kind of blow up a low resolution pixel image.
I didn't do that.
I just I pretty much just had everything.
I just multiple everything's pixel count.
I just multiplied by three.
You know what I mean?
So like every every pixel in the game is like is actually three pixels.
Oh, and I like manually like, yes, bigger.
Yes, I just manually drew everything bigger.
I multiplied the size of everything.
And I just tried to make sure that everything's positioning
at all times was a multiple of three so that there wouldn't be any like.
You know, you wouldn't see any single pixels,
like only half overlaid over each other, like like a pixel mismatch.
Yeah, I think there are ways to do that, but I don't know them.
I'm just imagining that it must be a real technical challenge
to accomplish that with polygons.
Potentially, yeah, I think it's.
Relatively simple.
I mean, a lot of they're probably are just methods to do it.
I think in a lot of modern video game development things, tools,
they assume that you want to make Assassin's Creed.
So like every like, there's a lot of things that are just default.
Like, oh, easy drag and drop like lighting.
Oh, it's sunshine and shadows, dynamic shadows.
You want that, right?
Yeah, if you're trying to make a polygonal PS1 style game, you don't want that.
So, yeah, there's there's a lot of.
Not a lot, but like a bit of finicky,
like programming around what the the the tools would
were expecting for Pumpkin Alley, because it's we wanted it to be like
lower fidelity PS2, you know, experience.
And they wanted to have like lens flares and they didn't put that in.
But you know what I mean?
Modern game stuff is just very easy to click.
Yeah, drag and drop, we call it.
Is it is it shaders?
Am I is shaders the word for like modules?
Just yeah, just stuff that you can just like put in the game
and it's already sort of pre made and has a certain behavior to it.
Pre fab or an asset. I don't know. Yeah, pre.
Oh, do you know, do you know, Tio?
Yeah. Did you see Tio's like the gif of his game?
And like the lighting system that he's got for his sort of for his sort of.
What's the word?
It's that like Maple Leaf, Metroidvania, anime girl.
He has he has a game that he's building that kind of looks like Momodora.
And he posts this was maybe two or three weeks ago.
Well, his personal kind of Tio the creator and then his work account is Tio devs here.
Look at this.
Look at this like lighting system that he built.
And it moves around and looks all crazy and shit.
Animated the light emulated day night cycle.
Yeah. So. Yeah, that's definitely would be a shader.
Yeah. How do they?
Yeah, how do they do that?
I guess these 2D things aren't as 2D or maybe it's like a value thing.
Like it checks the value of the pixel and then decides whether there's like a finds the edge.
I don't know. I don't know. That's cool.
It's pretty pretty cool looking, I thought.
Yeah.
Uh, that's a yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what a shader is, LaMau.
But I think I assume they're involved in getting a game to look the way you want it to look.
That's all. Yeah, like like you've got like models and like
stuff, got 3D stuff.
You got 2D plane stuff with images on it.
Shaders are like on top of something.
You can apply it to make it look certain ways.
That's that's my basic understanding of a shader.
Is that you're it's like a thing you add to something.
Yeah, I mean, I know I'm familiar with the concept of like a like
like what would you call it in like Photoshop, like a a correction layer.
I imagine a shader as like a correction layer that you apply over
an asset as it's being drawn on the screen that like adjusts the way that it's drawn.
Yeah, yeah.
But it can interact with game code.
So like when like you can have like a shader react to something based on a player input
or like a game state or whatever, you know, you can like animate a shader.
I think punk's fire breath is like it's a 3D model of a fire that wobbles
and grows and it's like a shader thing.
I didn't really understand it because it's too complex.
Charlie handled that.
Yeah, all according with him.
So I'm stupid, you see.
I looked over his shoulder a lot and I'd be like, hmm, yeah, I think I get it.
And I really don't. But I think I get it now.
It's like it's like, hmm, a Boolean interesting.
A Boo, a Boolean.
Yeah, it's like nodding, nodding along like, yes, I I I understand shaders now.
It's like he's just like tip, tip, tip, tip, tip, tip, tip, and then and then bam,
look, the game works and you go, ah, yes, I see.
Yes, makes I could have I could have done that, I think.
Yes. Yeah.
I got you. I got you.
I don't know.
That's just what I noticed the most looking at a bloodborne cart
is just how crispy the pixels are and like, hmm, how they how they do that.
How do they do that?
They probably have like if you go through their dev threads,
they probably explain like early on how they approach
all those things because that's they they get into like some amount of detail.
Like, oh, this week I worked on this thing, blah, blah, blah, that.
Is it just Botster or is it like a team?
It's just so she she she was in like the the gaming industry
is like working on indie games and stuff, animated for other people.
And then she's like, fuck it.
I hate the industry.
I'm going to do my own thing. Interesting.
I didn't know that.
That's pretty cool. And she made bloodborne PSX.
Did she work on any games I would have heard of?
I don't know, actually.
She made a game that I haven't played yet.
It's it was in one of the bundles like for Palestinian relief or something.
And it's like I should get around to playing that.
She's it's like a first like indie project that was completed.
Arceus Arceus, but not the Pokemon.
I think it's something else.
The game starts with an A. OK.
All right, did I talk about the guy at the party
who told me I should pitch Clarissa Gunsmoke to Adult Swim?
Did I talk about this all the role already on the show?
That does not ring a bell.
So I'm going to say no, I don't think so.
OK, so the Christmas Eve party,
one of my dad's friends.
I mean, I know him, so I guess we're also friends.
He's seen my comic before.
I showed him before and he's like, you should really
like I can get you in contact with like some people.
We can work it out.
And I'm like, I don't I can I assume you know some stuff.
I mean, you definitely know more than me about the industry.
Who is this person?
It's just a guy.
He's in my dad's band.
Played. He was the bassist in the when I did that gig.
Yeah, OK.
So he's like he works in TV.
He does things that I not entirely show what he does.
But like that's cool.
You know, that's something. Sure.
Maybe I can utilize his his connections.
And he was talking about the Rick and Morty people.
It's like you could you could put this to Adult Swim.
Oh, Rick and Morty, there's a show that's doing well
and is not seeing any difficulties at the moment.
Yeah, but you know, whatever.
Sure, sure, sure, whatever.
So it's like it sounds silly.
But maybe maybe I could like make a pitch
for Clarissa Gunsmoke, the animated series.
Did you see I could go to fucking I could fucking fly to LA
and walk around and put it under someone's nose and say, look,
look, animated.
Did you see Cheezy's video about how to pitch your show to Adult Swim?
I did. I forgot what it what it said.
The I don't want to spoil it, but I will.
It's a funny video.
It's about. Well, it's about that they there was this.
There was this live stream that you could basically call into
and you could pitch your show to these two guys.
And I think one show one show eventually did sort of get picked up
and like, I don't know if it was has been produced yet,
but there was one show that seemed like it actually worked out somewhat.
But anyway, the long and short of it is they had this live stream show
where you could pitch your show to them and they would give you feedback on it.
And what's his name?
Rebel Taxi did it like once or twice.
And the Rebel Taxi's show is bad and his work is bad
and his characters and his concepts are bad.
So it didn't work.
Long and short of it is the show doesn't exist anymore.
The show has been canceled and you can no longer do this.
Lamal. Yeah, I mean, I imagine.
Like free and open access to anyone who wants to try
is always going to be a little harder to get like noticed.
Then then like going through like, oh, I know a guy who knows a guy.
Maybe this guy does know a guy. I don't know.
He just put it in my head like you should make Clarissa Gunsmoke animated series.
You know, you're working on this comic.
Looks great, but you should make it like you should put it to Adult Swim.
I'm like, what? Really?
I mean, it would be cool.
Sure, it would be cool.
Look, I don't want to be a hater.
I'm not trying to be a hater, but like, don't you work for that studio
that's like trying to get their animated series produced?
Like, oh, yeah, I'm going to talk to them for hard, right?
It is pretty hard.
Yeah, it's
but like, I don't know, I've got cool characters.
What if what if I was better than everyone?
What if I'm actually the best and I just didn't I just didn't believe in myself until now?
What if Clarissa Gunsmoke is exactly what they want?
Well, she shoots people they day.
You can't put that on like CBBC.
Can't you?
I.
I mean.
I mean, yeah, hey, do it, hey, do it.
Oh, I'm going to I'm going to try and let me know what happens.
I guess I'm going to get a little pitch together.
I'm going to like, OK, figure out how to make it into like a appealing
little story with a synopsis and a characters.
I mean, I'm going to make a little thing and I'm going to I'm going to
go to LA, I guess.
I don't know who are you going to pitch it to?
Well, that's why I want to talk to this this guy again,
because he says we can we can workshop some ideas of how to like get it seen.
I'm like, all right, you know more than me on that.
So I'll meet up with him.
I mean, I wonder.
Yeah, I wonder who this who this guy knows and what.
Because he's done he's done very he talks about doing like all sorts
of little things and it's like it's it seems like really cool.
But I don't know how like connected he is.
But I can't like I can't know until I figure it out, I guess.
He doesn't seem like a liar.
He doesn't seem like a jokester.
I don't know. It's kind of.
But it's sort of like a natural thing to exaggerate.
It's kind of it's kind of a big claim to be like,
I know someone at Adult Swim, I can get you your pitch.
He didn't say that adult swim. OK, he didn't say that. OK.
He says he knows like people who could like help bring it into get seen
seen by somebody who would pick it up.
And he said I'll swim would like it because he likes Rick and Marty, I think.
I mean, who doesn't?
Yeah. Well, yeah, I guess I don't know.
I guess that could mean any number of things.
So I don't know. I'm curious.
It's it's something I'm going to I'm going to see what happens.
Oh, because of the moment, I've been like, oh, I got to draw
should have not been talking to my microphone.
Oh, wow, so loud.
I have not been like really drawing any more Clarissa gun smoke,
even though I said I should. Oh, no, one to two.
And I'm like, oh, come on.
One more panel.
Come on, come on.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
Come on.
I think once the once there's more sunshine,
once I can go outside and feel the sun blast onto my face,
and I'll like get all that photosynthesis.
Yeah, that's what I need.
I need sunshine and rainbows, and then I can feel OK.
And then I can draw.
But in the meantime,
why not follow up this this idea?
What if I what if what if I?
What if Clarissa guns go smoke becomes bigger than Rick and Morty?
Well, then, huh?
Well,
um, then I'll be I'll be fucking I'll be a I'll be eaten crow.
I'll be I'll have my you'll you'll rub it in my face and you'll say,
I told you, Ben, you said I could never do it.
And I said, no, I didn't.
I was careful not to say that.
And you'll say, yes, you did.
And then I'll just crush you.
But it's my boots.
Yeah.
Tired of the train tracks.
Well, somebody had to do it.
Yeah, let me know.
I'm curious to hear how curious to hear what happens with that.
That's interesting.
I'm watching a very interesting.
Look at this.
Look at look at this gift.
Look at this video.
Look at these shaders.
Talk about crunchy pixels.
Oh, I saw this.
Oh, this looks pretty.
I'm I'm transfixed by it.
This is like a first glance.
This is reminded me of like the town with no name, the old DOS game.
I'm not familiar.
It's like a a.
Choose your own adventure kind of where you walk into a Western town
and it's on DOS and it's like made by some guy.
Maybe as a project or just for fun, very odd obscure game.
But you go in there and you have to talk to the people in the right order.
And then there's a shootout and you got to do it real quick.
And it's very it's very easy to die.
That's what I remember from that.
OK, all right.
But it's not like a roam around.
It's like a click and point move from screen to screen to screen.
Yeah, but it looks similar to this this color palette and stuff.
Yeah, I can.
I'm like, this is cool.
I love the West.
I love the Wild West.
Whatever happened, I love the West.
That's why I love Ukraine and I need to defend democracy.
Whatever happened to the Wild West, they paved it over with grass seed.
And now it's all nice and green.
Where's all the desert gone?
Huh?
Filled it with cactuses and stuff.
They filled the desert with disgusting solar panels.
No, I'm farmland.
They killed all the birds with wind turbines and solar panels.
And they got those like gargantuan monolithic, like water sprinkler systems
to like make a huge circle of crops grow in the middle of the desert.
Know those?
No.
You know, from space, you can see like American
crops grown in circular patterns because it's a very efficient way to water.
They have like a huge.
No, I didn't.
There's a huge pipe from the middle and it rotates on.
It's got a wheel on one end and then water sprinkles down in like a,
I don't know how long it is, but it's very long and it goes around in a big circle.
And that's the most efficient way to water.
And so there's, let me just see if I can get.
It's not crop circles, but it is a circle of crops.
Right. I have.
No, I have not seen the thing you're talking about.
That's what the farms look like from the space, from from high up.
Get a closer one.
That's how they do it.
Oh, so is it just like one big central like spigot
that just shoots the water in a big circle?
No, it's like it's like a it's like a tower in the middle.
Yeah. And then there's a pipe that goes all the way along to the edge.
And then there's a small like another pole with a wheel at the bottom and the wheel turns.
And the pipe turns and the road and the water comes out of like holes
along the pipe down. Yes. Yes.
And so it goes around like that.
And it's like, hmm, that's that's that's how they get you.
That's how they get you.
I see. OK.
And what about all the corners?
That's what I want to know. Wasting animals live there.
Yeah, I can see.
I can see they put buildings there.
They could put buildings and like stuff.
These are really wasted space.
They're really big now.
They're very funny.
Interesting.
What was I was I talking about or have even?
How do you even get here?
Talking about the Wild West, you were looking at a gif.
I don't have anything else to say about the Wild West.
Did you get to the part of medical soul where
soul is in the desert and he gets thirsty?
Oh, gosh, I don't think so.
Right. Well, that's a spoiler, but it's not too big of a spoiler
because they are in New Mexico.
I don't think I've seen that part.
But that's in season five.
Yeah, I think I might not have made it that far.
I would recommend watching the rest.
I should watch the rest. It's good.
Breaking Bad was pretty good, even though I didn't really love
I don't like the final season as much as I like the rest of it.
I like the final season on a rewatch.
I think I feel like Breaking Bad.
You get so hyped up with like everything working well.
And Walter is like he's getting more and more money,
more and more power, and he's getting away with more and more.
And it's like he's gone from this little shitty van.
Now he's working for Gus, but he's scared of Gus.
And then he does the whole like, I got to kill Gus because I got to be
the main character of this enterprise.
And he fucks everything up.
And because of his ego fucking everything up,
everything is just fucked up for the entire rest of the show.
And it's sort of like a tragic tale of like everything is depressing
and it only gets worse until everyone's dead.
Well, like, but like thematically, like on a second watch,
I'm like, I can appreciate how that's that's all done.
It's it's good.
It's a tragic tale.
It shouldn't end in a good thing.
He's making math.
Yeah, I mean, you're right.
Math is good.
I don't know.
He made Sonic the Hedgehog math.
Um, it was blue and it looked nice.
So, you know, that's cool.
Yeah, you ever smoke math?
Nope.
You ever eat it, inject it, speedball it?
Uh, sniff it, snort it.
I looked at it. Don't abort it.
I looked at it so hard that it went into my eye.
Yeah. Yeah.
Woo, I love math.
You ever see you ever see a there's like a subreddit for math?
It's like an r slash math.
Do they like it?
Yeah, they're just like, hey, guys, you know, did some math today.
You know, I'm at work, you know, feeling good.
Love math. I love math.
Why don't they get in trouble for such things?
Um, admitting to taking a drug, I guess.
I don't know.
I guess the law is like, you can't be, you can't have it.
You can't sell it.
But if you've already done it, the only thing that's going to stop you
is like, you can't do a sports event.
Is it illegal to be under the influence by itself?
I don't really know.
I don't really know the details of the math laws.
Maybe maybe you could be like, oh, yeah, I did math.
It's like, oh, so you bought math? No, I didn't buy it.
Just found it.
Just found it on the side of the road.
No crime took place.
I just immediately took it so I didn't I didn't have it.
I inherited it.
I inherited this math.
It was passed down to me.
Uh, it's non-taxable.
Also, saw this go fund me.
I saw this like memorial for this family that was murdered by their dad.
Terrific. Yeah, I saw the obituary.
Yeah, I was I saw the obituary for the dad and it was like.
Damn, people were commenting like in memorial of the dad
saying like nice stuff about him, saying like he always spent
he always like made time for his kids made time for his family and stuff.
And it's like, damn, what? What the fuck?
He literally murdered them.
Hmm.
Do they know him? Is that why?
Yeah, I have the go fund me right here.
And it's really it's kind of funny that like in their family memorial picture,
like it was a picture with the dad.
So they edited the dad out and they put Jesus in his place.
They just put Jesus over the dad.
And and then in the statement underneath,
like they have like statements by the family members about like in memorial
of all the not the dad, but of all the other the wife and all the kids
about like memorials of them and stuff.
But then they also make like a pro gun statement, like they're really like,
hey, listen, don't don't use this incident to enact like gun laws.
Like we need to protect guns.
Yeah, so important, so important that we protect guns.
And then the.
There was there was there was a separate page for an obituary for the dad
where I saw people people were apparently posting like about what a what a good
what a good dad he was.
So what happened?
He killed them all and then himself.
Yeah, yes. Yes. Yeah.
And now I can't find about any of this.
I just saw people were people were reposting the link on Twitter.
Hang on.
I'm going to follow my book, my guy, Jack, my guy,
Wack Nicholson on Twitter was was posting about it.
That's a little bit fucked.
Oh, no, I've brought the mood down.
I've ruined I've ruined another podcast
with my morose bullshit.
Damn it.
All right, yeah, this this was the original tweet,
like reporting on the fact that, like, the obituary exists and stuff.
And I think some of it might have been deleted.
I think some of the comments might have been removed now,
but, like, I saw people posting.
Yeah, posting comments from friends and family about, like,
what a cool guy.
Twitter is insane.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Here we go. Here we go.
Posts to screen screenshots of these posts, which I can't find any more.
They OK, they locked the obituary.
Yeah, the obituary has been locked, so, like,
you visitors can no longer view it, but.
We don't know the wise and house, but I do know it's not our right to judge.
And the Lord loves Michael very much.
It's not our right to judge.
God damn, that's a that's a fucked up thing to say.
Genuinely, a fucked up thing to say.
I mean, maybe had a good reason for killing his whole family.
Maybe, maybe. I don't know.
How do you know unless you've walked a mile in his shoes?
God forbid you haven't had to walk a mile in his shoe.
OK, I did. I saw this yesterday.
You know what? I'll tell you the truth.
I'll tell you the truth. I was a little bit.
I was a little bit high.
I was a little bit high on marijuana.
Oh, my God, when I read this, when I read this, it's so much worse than math.
It was worse than math.
Being being a tiny little bit high on a small amount of weed
and reading this article, it was like, oh, my God, the world is ending.
It felt pretty bad.
Is a really truly a dreadful experience.
And I just wanted to share it with everyone.
Yeah, good job. Share the love.
OK, well, I'm glad.
Oh, the wife had filed for divorce.
The wife couldn't have that.
Yeah, I'm looking at some of the comments.
Here's here's here's a news article.
Is there like about the incident like a like a police report on like what's
been found out about the what's happened?
Well, why do you do it?
I just linked an article that is like,
yeah, father killed his wife, five children and his and his mother-in-law
before turning the gun on himself.
Michael Hade, 42, shot his wife, Tasha, 40 weeks.
After she filed for divorce, her wife of 40 years old,
weeks after she filed for divorce.
He is also thought to have killed their three daughters and two sons,
aged seven, 12, 17, four and seven.
Police have not confirmed that he was motivated by his wife's divorce.
Well, how would how would police confirm that?
Again, what are you going to ask?
Are you going to ask him?
Get a say on this.
Less than one month after remark ten years since the Sandy Hook tragedy,
another mass shooting has claimed the lives of five more children in Enoch City.
Enoch City, the morning with the Enoch City.
You talk to me. I guess it's near Sandy Hook.
Yeah, whatever.
This is your brain on on Mormonism.
Actually, they might not be Mormons.
I mean, they put that Jesus.
No, Mormons like Jesus.
Mormons like Jesus, too, right?
They're like, yeah, I think so.
Aren't they like a sect of Christianity?
Um, oh, wait, no, no, it was it was like one guy who said,
I'm actually the coolest guy and I'll write a book about it.
And everyone's like, cool.
They're like sort of Chris.
They're like a they're like a weird Christian offshoot sect.
Because, yeah, like, I think they do believe that Christ was the the the redeemer and all that stuff.
But then they have this other guy.
What's his name?
Jimmy Joe Bomson, the the Messiah,
too, who supposedly was he was not he was just a prophet.
He was just a prophet.
Yes, said like all this weird shit that they believe like that Jesus lived in America and stuff.
La Mal literally, literally epic.
I remember learning about that in school and being like,
I wonder how I could start a religion if I just write a book, would people believe it?
Because that's what he did.
Yeah, I wonder like what was what was the PR campaign?
He can't he can't have just written a book and like that was it.
There must have been no he was getting it out there.
He knew he knew a guy.
His dad's friend was a basis and he knew a guy.
He put it in front of some people who like to talk to God, you know.
Yeah, I know a guy.
His name is God.
Have you ever met him?
I can introduce you.
I got his number right here.
Have you heard about his redeeming blood?
It's good for you.
It's good shit.
It's good shit, man.
Check it out.
Don't sleep on this.
Cracking my crack in my elbow.
You should put Mormonism on adult swim.
Food for thought.
They should put Ukraine on adult swim.
Why is nobody on the adult swim talking about the war in Ukraine?
I don't know.
Is there like a new Rick and Morty season coming out?
Maybe Rick said something.
We got to defend democracy, Morty.
We got to defend those Ruskies.
We can kill the Ruskies, Morty.
The integrity of NATO is at stake, Morty.
Yeah, that's exactly what he was saying.
International trade.
It's Europe's bread basket, Morty.
It's driving up bread prices.
They produce 10% of the world's wheat supply.
I'm not talking about marijuana.
I'm talking about wheat, Morty.
I'm talking about wheat.
You eat it every day.
Have I talked about how much I love oats?
Have I talked about how delicious oats are
and how there's such a treat?
Get that clip and then make it be phantom horror and saying it.
I have become...
No, I don't think you have.
They're just so delicious.
You talked about your cold brew oats with better stevia.
Here's what you do.
Go to Hanifords.
Sugar-free maple syrup.
You just dump a bunch of that into your oats
and you add almond milk and you add some salt.
And it's like ice cream.
It's like ice cream.
It's so good.
It's decadent.
And it's got macro nutrients.
It's got macro nutrients, Morty.
The macro nutrient profile is insane.
Some basic rolled oats from Quaker.
I recommend better than rolled oats, quick oats.
Quick ones.
Which are just rolled oats, but they roll them even harder.
And I feel like I haven't seen them quick oats.
They're so quick they fly off the shelves.
They're like cryptids.
They're like those insects that move so fast
that the human eye can't see them.
They're like, yeah, ghost insects.
You know the ones.
Ghost insects?
Yeah, you know.
That doesn't sound appetizing at all.
You gotta eat the bugs.
You gotta eat the bugs, Morty.
You gotta get in the pod, Morty.
Eat this cricket flower.
You put it in your smoothie.
Hey, I've been playing Disco Elysium.
You play that?
Oh, I bought it on sale.
I was gonna play it.
I also bought it on sale.
I've been playing it for a couple of days now.
It's good.
I was watching a friend play it on a little Discord stream,
and I noticed that the main thing was that the guy,
the narrator, has a big, booming voice, very deep.
Is that?
Yeah, I think that guy's in Hades, too.
I've definitely heard that guy voice some other stuff.
He probably does the Arby's commercials.
He's probably like...
Like a delicious food, and then he goes on to make a video game.
Did you play at Hades?
Nope.
Hades nuts?
No.
Okay, I guess the guy's name is Lenval Brown.
I'm like 90% sure that he's in Hades, too.
Or maybe some other game.
Astria ascending, Disco Elysium, and Black is Belza.
What the fuck?
Disco Elysium, narrator, who recorded 350,000 words of dialogue
and has never acted before.
What?
What's going on?
That's just how he speaks.
That's just how he goes.
I'm sure it may be so.
I mean, yeah, his voice is great, but I was like a million percent sure.
But I'd heard it somewhere before.
Maybe it's a voice many people can do.
You just got to have huge lines.
I don't think so.
I don't think...
You got to have like a frog throat to fit that vocal chord in there.
I don't know how that works.
Yeah, okay, well, I guess I'm freaking stupid or something.
But anyway, I was really struggling with the format, the genre of the game.
I found it really annoying at first, because I don't really play games like that.
It was a lot of reading, which is okay, because the writing's pretty good.
I think the writing is good.
But I was kind of annoyed by the fact that you never heard someone say it's like a book
with its pages stuck together.
The game is pretty much just there to make you work in between making you read stuff.
What do you mean, work?
I mean, okay, the game is basically writing.
The majority of what you do in Disco Elysium is read and or listen to text.
And that's fine, but you have to just walk between places and find stuff,
and you have to bring things to certain places in order to get that text.
Why is it not just a book?
Why is it not just a freaking book if you just want me to read?
Why do I have to walk back and forth across town just to read what happened?
Your input has like changes in the story?
Sometimes that's true.
You know, I kind of got over it.
I moved past that it stopped bothering me after a while.
It was kind of just like the first day I was playing it.
I was like, why is it making me work so hard just to let me advance the story, dog?
It was not helped by the fact that I had a couple of deaths early on
that made me like re...
I didn't save for a while, and so I had to like redo a bunch of stuff, and it was really annoying.
I'm not gonna say that was partly my fault for not saving enough, but you know, whatever.
The game does autosave, so I kind of just assumed that the autosave function would
prevent me from having to redo like large sections, but no, it didn't.
Yeah, I feel like I would probably enjoy it.
I don't mind a reading game, but I do, like if there's like mysteries to uncover and like
deducing to do to like figure out what the hell is going on, that's stuff I like.
I'm not saying I minded the reading.
I'm just saying that I felt like if I'm here to read, just let me read, and all the stuff I had
to do in between reading just felt like a lot of busy work.
Are you able to like goof around?
You mean in the game?
Are you able to like bunny hop and throw things?
No.
Then there is no point.
Why would they do that?
There's no...
I mean, if they allowed you to like fuck around in between like story bits, then that's okay.
I like being able to fuck around a bit.
Well, the only like...
I've seen...
I've sensed that it's a very serious game where every action is important.
So I'm like, ah, I gotta have to role play.
I'm gonna have to be like sensible, but I want to throw shit.
I mean, you've seen the game.
You know it's not the kind of game that you can bunny hop and throw shit.
But I want to though.
That's what I like.
No, I mean, there basically is no gameplay other than moving, going to different places and
selecting which thing to interact with, which just triggers text.
Do you think it would be a better game if it was like
points and click, like click your map to go to the new location rather than walking around?
No.
You know, it's not really that...
No, it's not really that big a deal.
It's not actually that hard to like get places.
It's just maybe like a minute or two of walking.
I'm trying to decide if this is an actual problem that I have,
or if I don't actually care that much.
I think you just had to reload and you're still frustrated.
That really did annoy me.
I'll be sure to save.
Definitely save often.
Yeah, that's my takeaway.
I get the feeling that you can get a lot of different...
I don't know how many like actual different outcomes there are to things.
I know that you can have...
There's a bunch of sort of different paths in the game that you can sort of choose and
sort of like how in like a Mass Effect, there's like, you know,
you can do the Renegade option or the Paragon option and just go Elysium.
It's like there's more of them, but there's still like clear cut.
Like this is the Communist option.
This is the Fascist option.
This is the Libertarian option, et cetera, et cetera.
This is the like, I don't care about anything and I'm a Nihilist and I hate myself option.
Did you pick that one?
I've kind of been waffling between that one and Communism.
Just like real life.
Just like in real life.
I'll go Full Fascist.
I'll do it.
The Fascist one.
Somebody's got to do it.
You know, I don't want to really comment on it until I've gotten to the end.
At the moment, I'm sort of like...
I'm a little bit unsure.
The game's politics are a little bit...
I'm not really sure.
Like, I don't know.
I'm going to wait till the end.
I feel like I shouldn't comment on like,
what is it saying about any of these things until I've gotten to the end and I've sort of seen
like what it actually says.
Although, I will say that a lot of the responses are very cartoony.
Like, a lot of the...
Sometimes it is a bit...
I think it's trying to be...
It's funny on purpose.
Like it's deliberately silly, but it's very much like when you do the Communist option,
a lot of the choices are just like very bloodthirsty, just about like how many people you want to
send to their deaths in the gulag and stuff.
Which is fine.
But it's not that compelling.
Like, it's just a little ha-ha joke.
Like, Communism, a 14 billion dead of Venezuela.
Vuvuzela.
Yeah.
Yeah, a lot of very cartoony dialogue options.
And the game tells you like, it's okay if you say weird stuff.
There's...
The framing device of the game is that you are a complete...
You've woken up and you've lost all your memories and you have no idea who you are.
So that's the reason why.
You can pretty much just say anything and it's sort of justifiable.
Because like, you are pretty much a blank slate.
Do you have to start...
Do your options lessen the more you learn about yourself?
They have not lessened for me.
I mean, you know, you learn very quickly that you are a cop.
Like, you have a job as a cop.
But you can decide like, well, yeah, my job is as a cop.
But I've decided that I'm still going to be like a communist revolutionary,
even as I do my cop jobs.
Yeah, your memory, I guess your memory doesn't come back.
You just learn new information.
I think...
Old information.
Yes.
You can still act however you want when the guy's of like, I don't remember stuff.
Like, you are an alcoholic.
You are an alcoholic.
You have drug problems and all that stuff.
You can fall back into that if you want or you can try to not do that.
I'm staying clean.
Just like in Lisa.
Hell yeah.
Drugs are bad.
Meth is bad.
Don't do weed.
They have blue meth in that game as well.
Oh, the joy.
The joy.
It's blue.
Yeah, it is blue.
Hell yeah.
And they have a bald guy too.
Just like Walter.
And it's in the desert.
Oh my god.
It's just the sequel.
There's a lot of funny racism in Disco Elysium.
And by funny racism, I mean that you meet people who are racist, but they're very silly.
They're like, there's a guy called Measurehead who is like,
he sees himself as the perfect display of his ethnic identity.
And he's got full body tattoos showing how perfect his skull is and stuff.
He's just really into skull measuring and he loves it.
Yeah.
The writing's good.
It is cartoony sometimes.
That's egg behavior.
Huh?
Egg behavior?
Get a tattoo of skull measurements on all of your body.
How is that the term egg?
I'm fucking joking.
I mean that doesn't, I don't get the connection, but sure.
Cause like shapes of skull between men and women differ slightly.
And some trans people get a little obsessed about their skull not being the right shape.
And so they have surgery to change it.
Oh, I see.
I see.
No, this guy's got the perfect skull.
No, he would never change his skull.
He likes it.
And that's it.
That's all I have to say about him.
He's a funny racist and I'm a big fan of him.
You can choose to adopt his philosophies and befriend him in order to get him to do stuff for you.
But I didn't do that because I'm nice.
I'm a nice and I'm a communist and I don't like racism.
I think racism's bad actually in real life.
What do you think?
What do you think about it?
Very interesting.
Sorry, I just happened to be yawning.
Oh, boy.
Good.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
No, racism, that sucks.
Do you denounce racism in the middle of the yawn?
Why did you hesitate?
I was in taking oxygen.
I'm sorry.
We'll see about that.
I don't know.
People tell me to play Disco Elysium for a while and I'm finally playing it.
And I'm bringing up gripes, but I do like it.
At the end of the day, the game is mostly about reading stuff and the writing is pretty good.
So that makes it like pretty good at what it's doing.
I know my character's name now.
You don't know your name when you wake up, but I know it now.
So that's pretty cool.
I know some stuff.
Insane.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Anyway, that's another.
Yeah, like I said, I haven't been working.
I've only been working a little bit on that thing that I was supposed to do by the end of the year.
Instead of that, I've been playing Noida, which is bad.
But I've also, you know, I said you can play Noida and that's a waste of time,
or you can play the classics.
You can play something that's edifying and good for you.
And I think Disco Elysium is more on that side of things.
So I don't feel that bad about it.
And also it's $9 and it's probably not on sale anymore.
So sorry if you missed it.
Oops.
Oops, but it'll probably go on sale again.
Yeah, yeah.
Ben, I heard that there is a steam version of Dwarf Fortress out.
Yeah.
Like an updated new, it's like with graphics.
It's like the new version of Dwarf Fortress.
Have you played it?
I mean, I have not played the steam version.
I did see people talking about the steam version.
And I guess there was a big,
a lot of people are giving Dwarf Fortress a try for the first time now,
which is pretty cool.
Have you played it before?
No, I hear about your things and I had been meaning to get around to like giving it a go
I mean, it's fun.
And I do recommend giving it a shot to see what it's all about.
I have not played it in a while.
Although I do have some funny stories from old fortresses that me and some friends ran together.
The the yeah, I haven't seen what the text.
There already were like fan made texture packs that you could apply to the game to give it like
sort of graphics.
I'm not sure.
I haven't seen what the new with the steam versions graphics look like.
But I guess people like them because people seem to be responding positively to it.
Do you know that like the guy who made Dwarf Fortress has like cancer and like the reason he
put he did this is like to pay for his cancer treatment.
Oh, yeah, I didn't know that he that's terrible.
It is.
Yeah, he's he's he's had cancer for a few years.
And I think, well, what I mean is he I think the idea I don't think I don't think he would have
cared to put it on steam.
But I think part of the reason why he did is because he needs to make money largely for that.
And so it's kind of good that like it's sold like millions of copies and he's made like millions
of dollars off of the steam version like I'm like good.
Yeah, that's that's great.
I mean, it was it was free the whole time, wasn't it?
Yeah.
And I mean, it's still free the original version, but like the steam version with like the the
pack and all that the graphics is I don't know how much it costs.
But you know, a lot of people bought it.
How much do you check how much it is?
Yeah, I didn't think it was too expensive when I checked.
I forget.
I assume the original version is still free.
It's all it's always been free.
Okay, it's 30 it's $30.
It's $30, which is you know, whatever.
I have a dwarf fortress.
I mean, I would say.
As I've given you $30 worth of entertainment.
It's definitely.
Yeah, of course, definitely.
You don't even need to play.
You don't even need to play the game for to give you.
You should buy the game even if you'll never play it just because it's it's
the stories you'll hear from other people.
Yeah.
Are worth the 30.
Do you know that there's a YouTuber called Krug Smash who makes these really?
Yeah, you've mentioned him before.
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't caught up with his stuff in a while, but he's made some really
some very cool and good like narrative like series about like the stories of his dwarves
and the fortresses they build and tournament arcs and stuff like that.
So cool rules.
And yeah, did I?
Oh, man, I don't want to repeat this.
I feel like I might have.
Did you did you listen to last week's episode?
The one that was the Ben cast?
I think I got halfway through.
I feel like I might have talked about this on that the story of like
or maybe I talked to you about it.
The one about the cats poisoning themselves.
Poisoning themselves.
Gosh, I hope.
Yeah.
Okay, there's this interview with Tarn Adams, the guy that makes Dwarf Fortress,
and they asked him and he's talking about the game and he's talking about like
stuff that happens when he's when he's fixing bugs, right?
And the story is basically that there are taverns that there was like he had just added
taverns to the game and in the taverns, the dwarves would go to the bar and they would drink.
And then if they wanted to stop drinking, they would just throw their mugs on the ground
and the alcohol would just spill on the ground, which is fine.
Like that's okay for Dwarf to do that.
That's normal dwarf behavior.
But the alcohol interacted with like a previously added module that accounted for like the effects
of like poisoning and alcohol is considered a poison that causes, you know, a certain effect.
And so what would happen was cats would walk through, pet cats would walk through the bar
and just the way that like fluids work, cats would walk through these puddles of alcohol
and they would get alcohol on their paws.
And it would consider that like an entire mug of alcohol was like stuck to their paws
when they walked through it.
Okay, flashback.
Flashback to another thing.
Dwarves have to clean themselves.
When dwarves get dirty, like every individual part of their body will get like the substance on them,
right?
And the dwarves have to clean themselves and they have to like take soap and they have to wash
like their hand, they have to wash their arm, they have to wash their upper arm,
they have to wash their face.
And if they would get something in their eye, they would have to take like a bar of soap
and like individually wash their eyeball to clean their eyes out.
And it's like, that's weird.
So they changed it.
They changed the behavior so that the dwarf's eyelids interact with their eyeballs
in such a way that if the eyelid blinks, the dwarf's eyeball is cleaned of any substances
that are afflicting it.
Okay, flashback.
I didn't know individual dwarves had like variables for every single other part of their body.
Well, I've told you that one of my favorite stories of a fortress I had is that is one guy
in a fortress and the fortress was attacked by a wear giraffe.
And a dwarf warrior was defending the fort and he got the wear giraffe like
punched him so hard in the face that he died, right?
And he got buried in the catacombs.
And one of my other dwarves would go to, I kept seeing him going back and forth between the
catacombs and the place where the guy got killed during the battle.
And he kept going back and forth, back and forth.
And when I looked into like who this dwarf was, why is he going back and forth, back and forth?
He was a friend of the guy who was killed and he had buried the guy's body in the catacombs,
but he kept going back to where he died because when the guy got punched,
the punch had shattered his face and sent all of his teeth flying.
And so he kept going back to the battleground and finding more of his teeth and bringing
the teeth to the catacombs and putting them in the coffin.
And then he'd go back and find more of the guy's teeth and bring them back to the catacombs
and put the more teeth in the coffin.
Why would he do this?
Because he wanted to put all the pieces together in the coffin.
He wanted to bury all of his friends' body parts.
How do you even write code that would allow for this situation?
But anyway, the ending of the cat story is that, okay,
so there's this self-cleaning behavior is added to creatures.
Creatures' body parts clean the other.
And so the cats would walk through this alcohol on the floor of the bar and track it on their paws.
And then the cat would do a cleaning behavior on the paw.
They would use their tongue to clean the alcohol off of their paws.
However, because of the way that it was considered to be drinking,
then, this alcohol that was stuck to their paws.
And it was considering that an entire mug's worth of alcohol was stuck to the cat's paw.
And it was drinking it as it cleaned it with its tongue.
And therefore, it was considering that the cat was drinking basically an entire
dwarven mug's worth of alcohol whenever it would clean it off its paws.
And this was like too much alcohol for a cat to drink.
And therefore, it would interact with the poison module.
And the poison module would consider that considering the cat's small body weight,
drinking this much alcohol raises its blood alcohol level
to a point that it enters the lethal area.
And it triggers the lethal effects of alcohol, including respiratory failure.
And so the cats would clean their paws and drink so much alcohol in doing so
that they would respiratory fail and they would die like right on the on the bar floor.
So cats would just get poisoned and die in the middle of the bar
from cleaning the alcohol off their paws.
Lamal. Oh, no.
So. Hey, Dwarfs, just don't throw it on the ground.
No, they come on. They gotta. They gotta, though.
So that's the kind of game Dwarf Fortress is.
Yeah, I feel like like if I play it, like, is it a difficult game?
Well, it's like Tetris, right? You just go until you lose.
OK, it's difficult. I mean, the difficulty of it is pretty much just like knowing
how to do certain things. But like there you pretty much just it's about navigating menus,
like telling your dwarves what to do is just about navigating menus to find like how to tell
them to do X thing. And so it's useful to have like a wiki to tell you like, how do I tell
my dwarves how to do this? How do I tell my dwarves how to do that? Like, what do I need to do?
I mean, the basic what you basically have to do is first you have to you dig out.
You dig out a fortress. Usually you'll you'll dig out like an initial settlement to live in.
And then once everyone's all settled and has like beds to sleep in,
you set up beds and then you'll start digging like a bigger fortress. And then in the you'll
set up workshops where the dwarves will start making stuff. And yeah, making stuff in the
making stuff in the workshops is like a big that's like where you get most of your stuff.
Digging out the fortress and digging out like mine shafts to find materials
to then make stuff in the workshops. And then you make stuff and then you trade anything you
can't make you trade with like merchants that pass by. You know, you engage in trade to get
stuff you need. And then setting up a military setting up a military is pretty complicated.
You don't really I mean you you can get by for a little while without a military but like you
will eventually need one or you'll die pretty quick because like threats will escalating threats will
come to attack your fortress pretty much the bigger and more successful your fortress gets the more
like dangerous and like legendary monsters will start coming to fucking get you. And so you'll
need a stronger like a weird dress. Where yeah, where creatures will just wander by sometimes
just randomly. I mean, there starts to be things like there are things called forgotten beasts
that are like sort of randomly generated like timeless creatures from like before the world
began. And some of them can be really some of them can be like pathetic and not even a threat.
And some other ones can be like really, really dangerous. It sort of just depends on like what
random attributes they're given. And I mean, you might have where where where creatures will
wander by and yet if they if they bite of a dwarf in the course of the fight, they might infect
a dwarf with lycanthropy and then you won't know until the next full moon. And then suddenly one
some of your dwarfs that got bit will go crazy at the full moon and they'll start rampaging
they'll start biting other dwarfs. And then you might have like a lycanthropy infection.
And that's a problem. You can have the same thing with vampirism. Sometimes sometimes a vampire
will join your fortress and you won't know who's a vampire. But your dwarfs will just sometimes
find other dwarfs like drained of all their blood and dead in their beds one morning and they'll
be like, Well, somebody's a vampire. And then you have to quarantine everybody and question them.
You have to. Yeah, there are some tells that you there are some tricks you can know to like sort
of figure out. Oh, it's garlic bread day, everybody ever ever get your garlic bread.
I've heard that one thing that can be a big giveaway for a vampire is like,
like you'll look at a dwarf and he'll look like you can't just see that he's a vampire until
someone accuses him of being a vampire. And like they write like it doesn't share that information
with the player. But a vampire will be really, really old most of the time. And so a vampire will
often have like a huge list of like people that they know. And so if there's if there's like a
dwarf that seems young and yet they know like tons of people, especially like from lots of faraway
places, it might be a tell that like this guy's probably this guy's older than these seams. He's
a vampire. Could just be a very so it could be a socialite. Yeah, you never know. You never really
know. But your dwarves will sometimes have like they might have like family and friends from like
yeah, from like other fortresses or like other countries and stuff. And like they might have
different gods they worship and like different different dwarves worship different gods and
stuff and like different cities might have different gods that they like. It has a whole it has it
simulates a whole like a whole like nation a whole like national history, which is really awesome.
One of my favorite things to do is to have my dwarves mint coins and just see like what images
they they they press into the coins that they mint. And they'll do like symbols of their nation or
like symbols of of their city or like pictures of like the rulers of their of the dwarven empire and
stuff. Yeah. Um, for just so freaking cool. But also it's kind of a hassle. It's kind of it's
kind of a hassle to play. And like, yeah, if you don't know how to play it, you pretty much need to
have a guide to like look up to tell you like how do I what menu do I go into to like build a
like woodworking shop if I want to make like beds? Yeah, I mean, that's how Minecraft was. It
doesn't explain anything. You have to have the wiki open. I mean, at least in Dwarf Fortress,
like the menu is right there. You can just kind of like look around in the menu and see what's there
on your own. Theoretically, yeah, you you can just
it does tell you like everything is right there in the menu, you can just see it and it's like oh,
this is the but like how to like actually do it is a little can be a little bit complex and a guide
can be useful to sort of like talk you through it. Yeah, because there's a lot of options that are
like, I mean, if you really want to when you're making a military, you can like get really down to
the minutiae and tell you like your individual soldiers like what weapons you want them to
wield and like what pieces of armor you want them to wear and stuff. Can you like create a rank and
then assign bits of armor to that rank? Yeah, you can. Yeah, you can make like you can make
different like squads that have like different like uniforms basically. And or you can I think
you can even tell and you can tell an individual like soldier like okay you can like assign them
as like captain or you can say like okay I want this guy to wear that I want this guy to wear that.
You can you to give them like usually it's to give them like
legendary or like artifact equipment that you have that you want them to wield.
You know. You know.
I do like managing a system of individuals. Yeah, I've talked about Kenshi before. Kenshi is like
not similar to Dwarf Force Triss but like you have your squad and they have their own individual
inventory and you can build a town with resources that you can get from buying or like mining them
from the wasteland. And it is it does get a little overwhelming if you get too many people.
But I do like that that management stuff. Kenshi. Kenshi, yeah. It's like you have talked about
it but I have not I have not played in. I would recommend that. That's a that's a real good
post apocalypse management RPG where there's no goals at all. It's just don't die.
Interesting. It's like an army kind of like simulator. It looks sort of like an RTS.
No, it's it's action. It's like it all real time.
Everyone has stats. They do things and they get better at their stats. Different races have
bonuses to different things. Robots are immune to acid rain and stuff like that. You can you can
if you get a leather crafter who can craft good leather stuff, you can get like acid
protection gear and then you can go into like cursed like weird
like it's post apocalypse. It's a very unique post apocalypse. Whereas like yeah,
clearly thousands of years ago, there was like a super advanced robot technology. But then
there's like these completely horribly irradiated ash filled like dead zones with giant beasts.
I love giant beasts. And if you can go in there, you can go collect stuff and get secret knowledge.
And you can bring it back and then you'll be so smart. But that's absolutely the game is like
you're just somebody in the wasteland and to survive, you have to band together with people.
And if you get strong enough, you get large enough bands, you can make your own base.
You can defend it from attacks. Cool. And and and slavers and bandits.
And gorillos, they have gorillos. Gorillos.
They're different from gorillas. Like gorillos pickle.
Yeah. Lol. He'll rip your limb from limb.
Intriguing. What else can I say? I'm trying to think, I feel like I had more to say about
Disco Elysium, but like maybe not because like I'm still like working through it. And like,
I guess it's kind of long. And I sort of only am like partway through it. So I'm still,
I'm still thinking about it. Your partner Kim is such a swell guy. He's just such a
little sweetheart. Love him. That's it.
Racism is bad. That's what I've learned from Disco Elysium.
I'm glad you finally get it. I used to think that maybe it was a little bit
based, but Disco Elysium taught me that it's cringe, actually.
People will cringe at you if you are racist. And you don't want that.
No. I wouldn't say so.
I don't have any notes. I think we said this before we started recording, but there's no,
there's been no new One Piece chapter in two weeks now. It seems like.
No. That's maybe one's going to come out tomorrow.
Maybe. Yeah. I thought I was going to, I didn't look last week because I was like,
no, no, I'll save. I'll save the One Piece discussion for when Gibbs back. But I guess
there was there was none anyway. So Oda's getting lazy. He's getting sloppy in his old age. He's
losing his touch. You know, maybe you should pitch maybe you should pitch Clarissa since they're
like clearly One Piece has fallen off to show and jump. They need a new one. Oh, wait, I guess
you already did that. I already did that. That's the Tezuka challenge. Right.
I got a note from a curatorium. He said this fucking sucks. Get better at drawing. And I was
like, right. But you know, but you know what? But you know what? If there if there wasn't any hope
for you, they wouldn't, he wouldn't have even bothered to tell you that it sucks and you need
to improve. So that's good. It's good, actually. It is good. Well, I'm just saying that One Piece
is falling off because it's gone two weeks without an update. So I think Oda's probably finished.
He's toast.
This 2023. Did we even talk about the new year? This is the first one? No, I've been on for the
new year. Yeah, I guess I guess I guess fuck the new year. It's just another year. But wait,
no, you didn't we record one? No, you were on we recorded one on the second.
Yeah, because there was two weeks ago.
Did I? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, you know, yeah. Look at the calendar. Look at the calendar.
I'm looking at it. Yeah. 2023, though. Huh. About that. Yeah, I know. Right. I saw you tweet
that like the January is just like the start or it's just like this practice warm up. It's
a warm up. That's it. Yeah. It doesn't it doesn't feel like like I'm ready to do anything yet.
It's just sort of like, yeah, I mean, yeah, I get it. Yeah, I know, like we did the whole like
2023, but like, come on, it's not actually the new year yet. That's how January always feels.
You get to the end of January like, wow, that was yeah, I know. It was quick.
Halfway through it already. Well, we almost two, two thirds of the way through it by the time
this episode's out. Think about that.
I hate it. I just don't care for it very much. I want to get back on the wagon, the drawing
comics wagon. Oh, yeah. Well, that's what I need to get going. Just just make chapter four. Just
make chapter four and then post it and then people be like Pog because at the moment, I don't know
if anyone's Poggin. I don't know if he's Poggin and it's a big problem. Nobody's Poggin about
Clarissa Gunsmoke. I mean, maybe now that the the 3D thing came out that the commission that did
that did make him Pog a little bit. Yeah, makes me Pog a lot. And like,
like I think partly it's just because it's been so long and also most people haven't even read it
yet because I didn't I didn't push it as hard as Beldrape maybe because maybe it's just because it
wasn't finished. Yeah, I guess it wasn't finished. And that was the thing. Chapter four is the next
chapter. Yeah, it still won't be finished. I'll have to draw even more pages. But I should do that.
I should I should do chapter four by the end of the month. I think I can do that much.
I really should. I'm not going to I'm not going to say I'm not going to complain more
about how I haven't finished the book yet. I really was yesterday. I was having a really good
I made really good progress yesterday. I'm really I think I think I've got everything. I think I've
actually collected everything now that I need to put into the final like index. And I don't think
I need any more. Pretty much the index just needed everything to tell the complete story pretty much
the complete story of Chris Chan's Chris Chan's interaction with Endless War to give the background
for the rain and stuff and like how that happened. I just wanted to put in context for like why that
happened. And I think I've got everything. What I had to do was I had to go through the the discord
logs itself and find like when she joined the server, when she got killed, the various times she
got killed, the things she said in response to being killed, which were very funny. Her like
making up commands like Moxby dash and goddess protection and stuff. I forgot that was her.
That the people made like the people were doing that. Yeah. No, it was funny. That was a funny meme.
It's you're there's some you're in some of like the chat logs because like there was like you
asked her like what her slime Sona would be and she replied with the the the card that was like
her like goddess Sonichu form and it's like I am immune to the slime and I move at bullet speed
so the slime can't catch me. Oh, there's a part there's a part after that where like what is it
hang on it's like she said she said oh god.
Yeah, you say like make a slime Sona and like and and and can he said if you if you die you can
revive in the sewers and Chris is just like I'm just visiting for now but I protect and I protect
myself and I dash as I am needed and you're just like nice and and Smirik says all ever
and all right and everyone's just like okay cool very cool just just the way that she the
literally the way that she's just like um actually uh I'm invincible actually like actually the rules
of the game don't apply to me like actually I just win honestly um this is very it's pretty it's
pretty funny uh and then she gets mad uh when she when she she she revived and then Dupati killed
her immediately and then she and then she she revives again but that this time she revives
and does goddess protection and goddess healing and says uh well I won't read the full text but
she wrote this long thing about like um I'm not actually in the server like I'm not actually dead
you didn't actually kill me uh you can't because I'm invincible uh by moxby dash
you know that stuff and I think the point is I think it's so juvenile but it's it's very funny
so I think I think I've I think I've fully collected all that and I'm like okay I'm done
I'm done I have everything I need uh and now now it's literally just like
fitted into the pages and I'm doing like a color coding thing where like different people's
taxes and different colors to like make it look nice and make it improve readability so I just
gotta do all that formatting and stuff and I won't I shouldn't complain I don't want to complain
about this anymore I talk about this too much I too much I'm too much talking not enough action
you know uh like that Elvis song just just like Elvis did I ever tell you did I mention that guy
who like Elvis Presley yeah the guy the kid who like lived in my old house
for a month or two and he like didn't know who Elvis was I I don't remember like he'd never hurt
there was I think his name was Jerry and he was a Chinese kid like he had grown up like half
he spoke perfectly good English because like he had spent much he had grown up somewhat in America
but also somewhat in China like he'd sort of been back and forth and he we had there was a for
summary our neighbors had an a party for like an older relative of theirs and they had an Elvis
impersonator and we were out in the yard like just you know observing this and Jerry did not know
who Elvis was and I just think that's remarkable
it is kind of like I remember in cartoons and stuff there would be like oh it's the Elvis
parody character Elvis is like a pop culture icon that Elvis Elvis is a people will know what it
means Elvis is a pop culture I don't do that anymore the shows do that does it did adventure time do
that um I can't remember if adventure time did it I mean adventure time is kind of old at this point
like a little bit nowadays nowadays these kids getting like these like teen dramas these cartoons
with okay serious stakes and they don't make Elvis jokes anymore not like the good old days not like
the good old days of adventure time like I mean Elvis was already old by the by the time adventure
time was out uh yeah of course he's he's my feeling my feeling is that Elvis is I mean Elvis was
already old by the time like I was growing up and like I had there were no shortage of Elvis
stuff I don't know I just I feel like he's a ubiquitous cultural icon who well pretty much
never completely go away I mean I know I'm from growing up but like I don't see Elvis
things so like I think it's quite possible you just don't come across it right now
unless you like the music and you continue to listen to the music I I you know honestly I would
have to be I can't really say because I don't like watch shows I don't really watch that much media
anymore so like maybe maybe Elvis references have ceased to be a thing in the time that Jerry was
growing up I feel like maybe maybe not just in shows but like a lot of entertainment is through
YouTube and what YouTuber would drop an Elvis reference I mean perhaps perhaps perhaps maybe
they'd reference memes Elvis doesn't have a meme that's the reason he doesn't have like a
big text low bottom text meme we used we used to call memes jokes back in the day
even Freddie Mercury had a meme yet that like hand like pose it turned into a rage comic thing
hand pose it's like he's got his hand way up and it's like fuck yeah it's like
I did it Freddie Mercury I saw that in rage comics maybe that that's definitely not used so much
anymore might have might have seen that if you if you want to live through post death if you want
to become an icon you've got to become a meme yeah it's like you know unfortunately Elvis died
before rage comics existed so there was never any hope that he would be memorialized unlike
Freddie Mercury who who was just born just in time just in time uh man the the the the feeling
I get I get a feeling uh from Disco Elysium whenever they talk about disco
uh I I feel Elysium no
no uh I just I feel the groove no just whenever the way they talk about disco as like basically
a trend that came and went uh I feel like I guess I've become old enough that like I understand
I understand the feeling of like hey that thing that I used to like that is completely like
everyone's over it and it's not a thing anymore really like I I now feel like I know what it's like
uh and I don't know I can I can relate I can relate that feeling to something like um I don't know
what's another what's another trend that came and went in my lifetime uh I emo scene kids I skateboarding
yeah skateboarding was like the huge skateboard culture in the nineties but now it's like
yeah I don't know sometimes you see somebody skating that's it yeah in real life that's all
I think I think so I was watching I saw a clip of some freaking uh some freaking hippies
some freaking hippies uh back in the day and I saw this clip of it they were being interviewed
and they were asking them like hey what's all this hippie stuff about and there was these three
white people that were they responded they were they were sitting in a big field
you know just hanging out lots of people were there white people and they were just like yeah
I just don't want to be like my parents you know like I just you know uh uh it's not all about
money it's not all about working it's about money it's just about living it's just about being
being in the vibe it's about vibing and like uh I agree I I get it and I agree with that but but
this tweet was presented and the kind was like you know like a lot of these hippies all went
on to become Reaganites right like these hippies that were all like a lot of them the white ones
in particular I mean I guess hippies being they weren't really black hippies no they were no that's
not true but like people like being a hippie pretty much meant nothing like politically like what do
you stand for it pretty much meant nothing it was just a cultural thing it was like a a a
a hedonism thing like someone like the black panthers would have had like a real like political
agenda but like the hippies were just kind of there to do drugs and have sex
and then they went on to vote for Reagan yeah and it and it's truly despicable
hippies these days vote for yang it still sucks I nothing's changed yang spoke the language of
the welfare state like yang made it sound like he wanted a more a a a an even velveteer glove
on the um on the budgetary policy and I like that it but it was all smoke and mirrors he was
just obfuscating his weird stupid tech bro thing I was I was fooled I was fooled but he deliberately
tried to fool me okay fool me once shame on him that's what I'm saying it's not my fault talk
about the the tweet where like yang was like sucking up to elon musk on twitter was that recent
I don't think it was recent but it was something that happened it was like okay yang whatever
um I don't remember that we already knew you were a little little bitch but now this is embarrassing
uh what do you say was it was it like post twitter takeover I think it must have been pre it was
wasn't that recent honestly I've seen like I've seen people like being I mean I've seen people
criticizing elon including people like mark cuban and stuff like even even fellow billionaires are
like um which is funny but I've also seen people being like oh like Stephen king was like way too
nice uh after like that after musk like Stephen Stephen hasn't had a brawl in his life he didn't
have a brawl uh uh no that's what I mean he's like oh yeah just like oh the slightest confrontation
no no no he's a lovely man I'm sure like yeah yeah didn't want to didn't want to start anything
terrible elon was being such a little bitch and and then for Stephen king just be like oh it's fine
oh he's just like no he's acting like a little pussy he's acting like an annoying little little
bitch to you call him a little cunt it's still funny to me that like Stephen king's comment about
it's too expensive and then elon was like what if I change it what if I lower it to eight and then
that's the number yeah because Stephen king turned it into an eight dollar thing that is funny that
it's just because Stephen king said it was too expensive that's pretty good um damn I can't believe
it anytime I see I can't believe the kind of accounts that I see subscribe to fucking twitter
blue I don't I genuinely don't understand I'll see some people with like with like 50 followers
that are subscribed to twitter blue it's like why what are you spending that eight dollars for
they like the check mark I is that literally is that literally it I mean I don't know I think
twitter blue has a bunch of like fluff that it says that you can get if you subscribe so like
stuff that doesn't matter at all yeah on honestly I would kind of understand I don't like it but I
kind of understand if someone is like like a business account like if someone is like livelihood
is like some business that they run and they promote using their twitter account I could
kind of understand that like you know if if twitter blue promises like greater reach or
priority to your tweets or whatever I can understand who'd be like well if I don't get that it'll hurt
my sales or whatever yeah but if you're just some guy with like a hundred followers
why what what would you even get out of it it's either dick sucking or yeah it's like it's like
virtue signal it's like a kind of virtue signaling yeah it's like I'm doing my part to make this website
be the uh the uh starship troopers I'm doing my part um catching yeah
I want to ah no no reason to bring this up I just I had a big nostalgia thing a few days ago
about a bunch of British shows but of course you don't know any of them so is your point
bring it up I probably don't I mean unless you want to just throw some names out and see if
I've heard of any of them uh yeah I mean there's no way they're like well now I'm curious yeah uh
Bernhard's watch no show about a kid who has a watch that stops time and he does things when
the time is stopped and I remember the cinematography being like wow how do they pause it how do they
pause real life it's very compelling uh no they things didn't have gravity when they were paused
it was like 90s or late 80s like visual effects I remember liking that just freeze just freeze frame
just freeze frame and green screen yeah and then you can move around in them uh that was a fun one
there was uh my parents are aliens my parents the aliens come to earth they disguise themselves as
human adults and uh they get some kids from the orphanage and they have a wacky fun time it's a
sitcom interesting and and the parents don't know what human life is and the orphans have to the
the kids have to explain to them and they have to make sure no one finds out that their parents are
I think the joke is that oh your parents are cool or your parents are like a little odd but nobody
ever suspects alien I did read um my my teacher is an alien which was a series of books as a kid
you know those nope you know they're a series of of you know young fairly young children's novels
but you know they're they're like they're like animorphs but like aimed even younger uh and
you know I actually follow the author of those books on on uh on twitter you know I realized
thinking back I feel like I might have said this before but I'll say it again uh I saw that guy on
twitter his name is Bruce Coville and I was like oh he's the guy who wrote those books that I read
as a kid and I remembered I remembered that like uh those books kind of have a pretty like they sort
of have a pretty like big business bad uh uh they have a pretty like leftist uh uh like politics
sort of current under cutting them especially in like the the the last one it sort of gets like
the it talks about like how the aliens like see the earth and like all the all the problems that
are on earth and a lot of it is like yeah resources are being hoarded by like you know individuals
when there's enough to go around but it's not being shared due to like economic reasons
and I was like oh wow wait a minute Bruce Coville is based actually he told me that communism was
good when I was a little child he groomed me and I appreciate it um so yeah oh and now he just
tweets about how like you know republicans are bad I'm like yes thank you Bruce you're right
good good man keep keep doing what you're doing what were you saying uh here's a show that I think
did come to America but it's under a different name or maybe it came from America probably that
way direction uh jungle run put a link uh jungle run is like they're in the jungle and it's a bunch
of kids and they have to do obstacle courses to get the jewels in the crystal caves and the monkeys
are gonna throw bananas at them and they have to like it's really cool is it like um did you ever
see a legend of the hidden temple yeah I think that's the I don't know if they're like directly like
the same show but like ones from the UK and ones from the US like the same production company sold
the rights or whatever yeah it but it's not the same name so maybe not I mean it's a it's a
different uh different set and everything yeah it's all filmed in the UK or or somewhere
and it's like this is from 2002 yeah oh this was I mean I think uh I don't I don't know if
legend of the hidden temple was still running in 2002 yeah maybe is maybe it's a spiritual successor
perhaps but I really love jungle oh that kid fell in the water ha ha ha lol he fell in the brown
water gross you that water I really that they had a thing where at the very end of the thing they had
like a big monkey head and based on your success in the trials proceeding it uh you had a certain
amount of seconds oh my to go in there and do a puzzle and collect uh one of three monkey statues
there's a bronze a silver and a gold one and if you did really well on the puzzle and if you did
if you had a lot of seconds in order to do you know really well you could get the gold one but
then you had to grab it and you have to run out before the monkey mouth closes and when the monkey
mouth closes um the show acts like the children are locked in there forever and they'll die because
they they took too long they got like too greedy they got freaking uh uh Aladdin like giant jaguar head
yeah uh the mouth closed the mouth closed and they're like and the presenter would be like
ah looks like they're not coming back and I when I was a kid I was like no they're dead I was so
scared I didn't want to apply to this show that's awesome I really wanted to do it but like what if
I died that was my thought process I remember that very specifically but like what if I died though
what if I die in the monkey head I don't want to risk that damn I really like this show but like
all those kids freaking die on it all the time like that's a bummer Sid and Elvis the fucking
orangutans those men and like those people in monkey costumes are so awkward looking
yeah they're pretty cheap looking yeah just throwing shit
oh and why are the kids why are the kids and the host all wearing these like weird costumes
with weird rubber masks oh wait they're just British oh dear tragic um
um jungle no I never heard of that I want to play this in real life I want an escape room
that's like a real huge jungle that I can run through I think I think I would I think I would
find that escape rooms annoying if I tried them in real life I don't know I don't think I would
enjoy them I I don't think so either I think there's something about it being just a room
and you're usually with a group of people but when I'm doing like a point and click escape room
like like a game yeah it's like oh it's spooky and I'm not trying to figure out all of the stuff
and I'm pondering to myself and I'm thinking and I'm finding clues but in an escape rooms that I've
seen you got a group of friends and you're like oh what's this what's that and I would feel so annoyed
if I wasn't the guy who found the clue I was just looking in the wrong place I was like okay well I
guess we're moving on I think I would feel the same way the fact that you're doing it with the group
all also the fact even if I was doing it by myself the fact that like I know that I'm being observed
like like the people that like hosts but like the people that make the room would are like watching
you and like they give you sure you're not jacking off and they give you hints if you need it and
stuff and like I think that would just really unsettle me and like really take me out of it
just knowing that and then also yeah but you're doing it with a group is like even more so like
I have to like I can't just like focus on the thing I have to like also be interacting with
this group and I think it would take me out of it and I think I would just be like rolling my eyes
I think I would I think I would find clues or whatever and I would just roll my eyes like oh
okay they're doing a oh it's a murder mystery oh I found this the murder note uh they the the
theme uh corny but then find it really corny I think my my my gamer brain and my socializing
brain are so different like I feel like trying to do one or the other would like ruin something
like if I tried to play the game I would be so anti-social yeah if I tried to be social I wouldn't
be paying attention to what's around me yeah that makes sense I think I I definitely I think I would
feel pretty much the same about that um anyway British people in the comments comment shows
that you remember and also if you remember the ones I said and say oh my god childhood unlocked
click uh well I don't believe it I don't believe any of these are real they're this proof they're
all too real unfortunately uh Bernard's watch give me a fucking oh that's that's like a fake show
that I would make up if I was like writing about all right let me fucking type in Bernard's watch
I see it I see it here um another one art attack and brom art attack art attack is legendary
dick it oh I see dick and dom and de bungalow I type my parents are aliens I type my parents
are aliens and it gave me a bunch of related searches and yeah I see yeah it's the same
it's the same oh brum oh that's like baby childhood the story of Tracy beaker Tracy beaker
that's another big one they roll on like it was like cbbc and c itv but like itv and bbc
children's programming slots how many how many letters how many letters are you lgbtq people
how do you how many letters do you need they're two different networks I see it i tv c itv
is the children's version of itv which is usually channel three and then bbc was channel one and two
mm-hmm and cbbc is a different channel the children's bbc and we switched between them
because they had everything there was no ads well i think on c itv there were ads but
it was just a bunch of cool shows all in a row very rarely was there like an american show
maybe just keep your mind keep your mind pure arthur came in arthur was a big one
um
wasn't arthur like no i was canadian wasn't arthur british like wasn't the
original author actually i don't i don't even know that uh no i'm just probably probably not
arthur developed by kathy wall animated educational television series pbs
i was created no created by american author mark brown nope i'm wrong yeah
there's um rupert bear who looks nothing like him but he has the similar jumper
not familiar not familiar yeah he's got a he's got a jumper on i don't even remember what rupert
bear was like i remember having like a color like a watercolor children's book of him and he was a bear
and boy howdy he wasn't quite winnie the pooh but he was something he sure was
is rupert bear older than winnie the pooh the character is six years older than winnie the pooh
whoa original bear 1928 he's he's the original bear yeah
okay okay now i've seen this guy i've seen this guy somewhere
paddington bear is another one
not someone's hacking up a lung out in my hallway uh is paddington older than winnie the pooh
no paddington's a lot younger okay
yeah 1926 was rupert bear paddington was 1958 he was a 60s bear or almost 60s
when and when was winnie the pooh uh 1932 um no no the the the latin translation is from
the the fifties lull uh okay 1926 yeah the 20s uh so damn he's almost a hundred he's almost
100 years old yes i mean rupert bear is 100 years old he's 103 102 he's just fucking christ
and what has he done with that time wait a minute a winnie the pooh was edward bear in 1924
what hang on this is a this is a we got to go down this bear hole yeah the the first winnie the
pooh story was called when we were very young but the bear in it is called edward even though it's
definitely the same bear fictional anthropomorphic teddy bear created by english author a.a nilne
we got like a monopoly on bears over here we made paddington as well
what bears have you got you got like um we have like uh we have we have teddy we have teddy
roosevelt the the the original teddy bear the theodore that's pretty big one yeah sorry sorry
idiot yeah which president was he or uh that would have to be um who was who was the one who like
didn't talk much uh donald trump never spoke a word that guy
coolage calvin coolage was he or uh who is rabbit which american president is rabbit um
oh man i'm trying i'm trying to think if there if there's a if there's a an american president
no is it andrew jackson he was cantankerous i don't know anything about american presidents
except that lincoln had a beard um the the the story and it's probably apocryphal but the story
about calvin coolage is that like a woman he was he was famously a man of few words and at a party
a woman said to him uh like my friend my friend bet like i bet my friend my friend bet me that i
couldn't get you to say three words to me and he replied you lose uh
that's fun yeah it's a funny a funny anecdote who knows if it's true or not
he could have said fuck off yeah fuck you better
he said die and he pulled out a gun
uh um um who's the tigger uh bill clinton um who's the who's the rue uh taft uh uh
what about the kanga uh hillary clinton oh wait
owl i forgot what the hell is like uh well i was gonna say smart but
actually no he's just pompous he's pompous and he thinks he's smart but he's not
and christopher robin is joe biden autobiography christopher yeah he's christopher robinette biden
this is like this is the new um the new like instead of you never heard people say that like
the winnie the pooh characters are all different like mental disorders uh yeah i think i heard that
yeah like pooh is adhd uh eeyore's depression uh owl is like narcissism or maybe uh
it's not a disorder it is narcissistic personality disorder is uh it's like a b cluster or whatever
you call it might yeah um i don't think of it as a disorder but i guess so it's a it's a personality
disorder like uh like like bpd it's one of those big penis discharge what does that mean
borderline borderline personality disorder not by not bipolar disorder that's not bpd
borderline personality disorder and that they borderline have a personality borderline personality
disorder i don't know it's just one of those it's just a particular kind of shitty personality
that you might have i don't know i'm not exactly sure what what what's the line between like when
are when do you have a personality disorder and when are you just have a shitty personality
and i maybe there is no difference maybe there is no line yeah uh although i know that people
with with like personality disorders like that i guess like they i've heard they's like they have
to manage their symptoms right like people like like apparently like you can have narcissistic
personality disorder but you can have it but you like you just have to like keep in mind that
you have it all the time and like adjust your natural adjust how you behave to like go against
your natural inclinations just based on knowledge of like okay i know that i'm just my disorder
thinking makes me feel like i should do this but i know that that's like a narcissistic thing to do
and so i should do this other thing instead um so i mean i don't know sounds i don't know
so you're you're just remember that you're depressed all the time and just try to be happy
okay and just smile instead smile you're you're pretty when you smile okay i guess uh well he
you know he he comes he goes up to the clouds he goes up to watch the clouds when he's happy
yeah and now he's got six wives and now yes and they've cured his his depression
i wonder um okay at least two at least two of his wives are like mother and daughter
possibly more that's weird right that is weird but is it illegal is it fucked up i don't
i don't know that it's illegal well well i mean hmm is it fucked up i mean they're not they're not
married to each other they're married to you they're they're like well yeah i guess i don't
know the terminology for like polygonal polygonal polygonal um polygamous marriages like what do you
say to to the two wives what are they to do each other i mean sisters but not really in yeah in like
Mormon polygamy i've heard them call each other sister wives and i mean i guess they are like
since they each parallel lives i mean your if your sibling married a woman they would be your
sister-in-law so if your spouse marries a woman well okay if you're that'll be your lover-in-law
are you are you also okay okay i think i think are you your own sibling uh if you are if you are
your own sibling then i think i would say that you are also your spouses that you are also your
spouse's in-law as well as their spouse and therefore your spouse's spouse is another of your
in-law so you are sister-in-laws well i think as well as fellow wives with your spouse's spouse
well i looked up the word sibling sibling is a relative that shares at least one parent with
the subject so it's it's it's your your only a sibling in relation to someone else i mean sure
you can't be your own i feel intuitively i feel like yeah i mean i guess technically you're not
your own in-law and you're not your own sibling but like you have you have you other than the fact
that you are yourself and not another person you meet all the criteria of being a sibling
with your own siblings and all the criteria of being an in-law with your in-laws you know what i'm
saying i guess to me it intuitively makes sense that you would that you are that if you are you
and another woman are both married to the same guy you are sister in-laws even though a tech i guess
an in-law is your sibling's spouse or your spouse's sibling and your spouse is not your sibling your
spouse is not your sibling unless it's not de facto your sibling well okay but if your if
your sibling if your sibling marries someone they become your in your sibling in-law so i feel like
if you marry someone i guess you wouldn't become a sibling in-law because you are not your own sibling
they just become yourself in-law because you are yourself i have no idea what you're getting at
i'm saying it's like you're even i just feel like the relationship of an in-law is satisfied
if you marry i feel like you you you you you are your spouse's in-law and therefore your spouse's
spouse is another of your in-laws and therefore you are in a certain sense a sibling in-law
of your fellow polygamous wives i don't think you ever thought about this hence the term sister
wives i think so so is so is it incest no is it incest if you marry a mother and daughter you are
are you or are you merely rendering them are you rendering them siblings in-law of one another
and is this is this evil or is this good it would be it would be like adjacent to evil but not
literally evil can we arrest your why did he do it he's he's tearing the powers family apart
with his with his with his pure riz he's so irresistible to these powers women that he's his
charisma is destroying their family we've got to do something about it i keep i mean he is like a
little stuffed animal it makes sense that they all want to hug him so cute what i maybe they have
like a maybe they have like a uh uh uh what's the word a platonic marriage maybe they don't
fuck uh yeah maybe hmm has your ever fucked in the show don't i don't think so uh not to my
knowledge not to my knowledge did kangaroo make roux did she be pregnant are you asking if
ira is roux's dad no i'm just saying to these animals is is uh conceit conception possible
i know they're all plush toys and it's all in on christopher robin's head except it's not it's real
it's real it's real um i mean i guess the implication is that rue is she gave birth to him
even though that never actually happened who's the dad that's the that's the new show that's a new
episode here here's here's what i'm confused about okay in the in the eor group one of the
wives is laura powers and one of the wives is ruth powers and that is ruth is laura's mom but
there's also someone called ruth jr ruth powers jr but like who the fuck is that it's probably like a
flashback episode younger version or i mean i can't find any um i can't find any reference to
ruth powers jr granddaughter that's not that's not how that works i don't know who is this person
i don't see in the image died died i gotta find it i got i got to find it again ben hughes
all right here we go here here in this one he mentions ruth powers jr eorn is wait he's only
got four wives ruth powers laura powers ours and taylor and ruth powers jr wait a minute so what happened
to the other two because there were six he had six girlfriends but he only married four of them
what did the other six do wrong where's this on the timeline i was this yesterday yeah this is
he divorced two of them already i don't i think he just didn't marry them but didn't wasn't there a
thing with his six wives like wasn't that i must have misread he no he had six girlfriends but
according to the suite he only has four wives and i just want to know the whole story okay i just
want to i just want to understand laughed at captain caveman's battle cry and the director
said hey that's funny maybe okay maybe he has six wives but only four of them were just included in
this scene yeah maybe he has more wives i think i think he probably married he did marry all six
i mean i i'm gonna i think i should assume that until proven maybe on january first okay i'm gonna
scroll back to january first and see if i can find a reference oh okay eor and his six wives ruth
powers laura powers alison taylor laura powers b what ruth powers junior and alice and sister the
babysitter what the fuck laura powers b and ruth powers junior oh oh oh under the the tweet you
posted somebody said this is epic ben but is it really okay for er to marry a kid ben replies it is okay
oh okay thanks for clearing that up thank you for clearing that up for me i wasn't sure
holy fuck uh this is this this changes everything it's just cutting right through the bullshit it
is okay it's okay if you were wondering oh i found it i found the canon
eor and his six girlfriends got married wait a minute there's another one
there's a whole bunch of stuff on the first eor and his six eor today is eor and six girls's wedding
i can't i can't believe it um oh it's it's it's remarkable he didn't say he didn't say she's not
a kid he said yes it is okay to marry a kid for eor to marry a kid i just i want okay who is ruth
powers junior who is laura powers b that's uh that's the mystery that's the mystery laura powers
b i died no idea maybe i should just ask him yeah it is okay that's that's incredible all right i'm
i'm probably gonna ask him like who who are these two other people are they like alternate
timeline versions maybe it's like maybe it's like ruth as shown in like a flashback episode
i can't get over his his filmmaking style of like playing a clip pausing moving to another
tab where he's prepared the reaction shot in a different video yeah plays that pauses next one
like does he know that he could put these clips into like a free program like vegas and he could
just like he could cut i feel like he would enjoy it i think he would he would enjoy the the product
of that more i i don't know i feel like that's a whole lot of steps it's easier just to set him
all up and then get your phone out record him i guess i mean i think he could do it
well see you know i see no reason he wouldn't be able to do it so well i is it maybe this is just
yeah this method of record different tabs with my phone maybe that's that's good enough that
that gets him where he needs to be he just made a tweet and he says elephant race period yeah it's
a picture of elephant race yeah it's not like it's something he edited it's just a picture
uh well didn't he put like um oh yeah it is just a picture there was one from my show
there was one where he put yeah yeah uh team i like this one a lot team eor at the burrow race
with ruth powers laura powers and arison taylor as racers and eor as the starter
he's at uh he's at uh uh what's that cat's name
uh hang on did you post that or yeah yeah i just posted it oh um oh yeah i know it from
hannah barbarus stuff i don't remember what he's from he like edited a smile onto one of the
is that ruth powers b
is it because she's wearing a different outfit is this like a different time different episode
okay it looks to me i just i just don't know
no one of his girlfriends is just the same as his other girlfriend but wearing a different shirt
he just likes the fit he can't he can't decide he has to have both two people this guy's got a
type this guy's got a type and it's this specific family lineage from the simpsons
it looks like in the burrow race like cut off of the torso cut off at like the crotch area and then
just standing yeah alison is just standing there she's got her full her full feet good for her
i like that they're on a blue background to sort of blend into the sky it's good it's a good effort
it's that's attention to detail that i appreciate that is and you could do vegas stuff well so vegas
isn't free it's not a free program no you have to pirate it uh you've had it for so long you forgot
yeah i did okay i mean fine windows movie maker then if you're just gonna cut clips together
yeah that they're perfectly serviceable yeah i should go to the bathroom i'll be back in a second
all right i guess i'll go as well okay i'm back you there mm yeah um what's up uh
uh you know let's explore that
oh i played um i played the madagascar ps2 video game
yeah what was that like not too long ago it's good it's like a good little platformer is it
like a collectathon yeah you collect some stuff uh you basically you got some levels where you got
to do the events of the movie and you got like uh all the characters from the film and they're
not voice acted by their voice actors but the voice actors do a very good job of impersonating
uh they got they got the old uh dan castellanetta impersonating robin williams uh syndrome
huh well you know in in um you know the genie was robin williams but then in all the non in all
the like sequels and all the adaptations he's voiced by dan castellanetta doing his best robin
williams impersonation yeah well it's not because robin williams is like fuck you pay me maybe it's
not uh it's not really about that he didn't get paid it's that like he had a sort of weird kind
of like uh thing where like he he really i don't know i don't know how if i should really believe
this but what i've heard is that he just really didn't want the movie to be like super like
commercialized and he didn't want to like make the movie about him and he didn't like want it to
have any sequels and so when it had sequels he didn't want to like come back right like i think
i think they did a commodity or whatever i think he liked the movie and he wanted to be part of it
but he didn't want it to um like be he didn't want to like sell the movie like on his as like a robin
williams product or something or he he didn't like i don't know that's what i've heard and that sounds
like it's honestly as i say it i'm like that sounds like some robin williams like apologia
that sounds like some very like oh he's just such a he's just such a visionary he didn't
like the commercialism of it like robin williams is not bill waterson maybe he is i don't know
i heard he was cool but i don't know i i never met him that sounds very flattering it's probably
more like there was beef it's probably there was beef for some reason and the and the the robin
williams side the pro robin williams side of it is he didn't like the way that it was like marketed
and and and he didn't like the idea of there being sequels and stuff so he just didn't come back for
them i think that's fair perhaps but uh the i looked up because i was the you know um chris
rock does the zebra in madagascar martin zebra yeah um the voice actor in the game
was exactly like chris rock i was like did they really get because this game was like
it's sort of it's a ps2 a licensed game and it's pretty small scope like it's got a bunch of levels
and then you play them and then you win and as one does and you know the animation's great and the
graphics are quite good and it's like nice and the voice acting is like how do they really get
the voice actors and i looked it up and it's not chris rock it's actually a guy who does i need to
find him um he did the voice of sam ray jack and like a like a billion other things uh i probably
would have heard his name uh phil lamar hmm okay sounds sort of familiar phil lamar did a trillion
voices in video games and cartoons and it's it was so funny not funny it is cool uh being like wow
he's that and this and this i forget exactly what it was known for pulp fiction was he pulp fiction
oh he's hermes and futurama oh that's like uh was it fry fry being voice was also voiced by
he was voiced by ren stimpy was the name the name's like billy something i don't know voice of fry
billy west yeah billy west was also a ren stimpy oh he was he was the name the voice of kit fisto
and jar jar binks on the lego star wars game oh only in the game not in the movie no the lego
star wars game yeah yeah yeah exactly they didn't have a lego star wars movie holy shit
that would be cool no i mean playing with lego yes i know but i mean that he didn't voice those
characters in the movie they got him for the lego version of the game yeah
it's just so many oh kit fisto is that the the the boundary no he's a tentacle headed
green lightsaber guy jedi oh yeah right okay sure
i don't call him kit fisto because he's into chicks if you know what i mean
i don't that's what this is a plinket said i remember okay yeah in the original samurai jack
he did samurai jack and basically every other character on that show
really did they um i'm not sure if he did aku but like he did did they like bring samurais jack
back for like a final season yeah it's called samurai back really no oh uh yeah i saw someone
talking about the last season of samurai jack and i think i had forgot but like i think i think
like they brought it back like later and they did like a more like adult uh uh like sort of like
final run of episodes kind of like how they brought future on back but i'm not sure i just
saw people talking about it and i was like maybe i didn't catch that part i'm scrolling oh my god i'm
still in 2016 i'm sorry but like look look at this one look at this 18 er in scooby-doo and guess
who it's the who guess who it is did you know um some of these in at least one of these uh
er is no longer friends with like christopher robin and the the hundred acre wood crowd like
he's moved he's moved out of there and he's he's he's cut his ties dang yeah i i guess i don't know
if like maybe he didn't like how like they bullied him or something he didn't like tigger like breaking
his little stupid little shack they didn't like him being having a polygamous relationship with six
women yeah but he converted to Mormonism and they're like dude isn't that like a cult and he's like
fuck you fuck you uh uh uh what's his name what's his name was the prophet
what's the guy's name uh uh joseph smith joseph sorry i'm looking at garfield yes joseph joseph
smith jr is the founder of Mormonism he did stuff for the apple of three he did voices for this and
that so many games like i'm scrolling there's like hundreds of things that he's had a voice in
they're not always like the main character but sometimes it is and it's like wow
what a guy what it that guy works that's that's a working that's a working man
good for him you know yeah it was marvin and pulp fiction who's marvin
probably a small role but i can't remember is it like the guy in that like couple that tries
to rob the cafe uh no oh he's the guy who
yeah he's he's the guy who um i think he's the guy that the jewels gives the like uh gives the
speech to about like uh the the don't fucking don't fucking fuck with my boss or whatever
that is one tasty burger you know yeah
oh seeing john travolta's face reminded me uh you know i'm breaking in better cool soul
you know the he has those gaggle of of film students he has running around
to do help with like stuff film like tv commercials and yeah yeah yeah yeah
the makeup girl has john travolta's face i just want to i just want to see if anyone else
sees what i'm seeing because i don't see people talking about that it's john travolta
why aren't people talking about it it's a makeup girl let me know can you show me please uh
okay um i don't want to look it up myself uh okay this is the makeup girl in better cool soul
on set that's what she looks like and she has like oh i see it distinctive sort of larger lips
maybe nose maybe a sort of a jawline like that i the eye placement just feels like it's john travolta
i kind of see it i kind of see it yeah i like her yeah just lend that that that be known
john travolta's cool she's got a big she's got a big mouth she's got a mic jagger lips
yeah i see it uh i'm trying i'm feeling like i'm feeling like maybe we should go to voicemail
soon i'm trying to think if there's anything else that i wanted to mention
probably not honestly i probably said too much already i probably incriminated myself
more than is necessary on this podcast over these past what are like 370 episodes
yeah why not more crime at this point yeah well i'll try
hi do you want to do voicemails yep okay um where uh i had a tab open whatever i also open a new tab
all right uh send us a voicemail speak pipe comm slash pcb voicemail uh whatever it is uh
where okay rolling down it looks like our first voicemail this week is damn someone's cooking
pizza someone is cooking pizza downstairs in my kitchen and i'm smelling it and i'm thinking i
should cook my pizza i should cook my kirkland brand supreme vegetable pizza when are they gonna get
back to nate when are they gonna get back to him uh okay i think i get it because in naruto
oh that's yeah that's what i did when are they gonna get back to seski this uh i yeah this is the
filler arc sesk uh nate's gonna come back yeah this is just this is just the filler arc he's gonna
have the renegade when he comes back is that the this the big red eye no it's the special super eye
that's like a bunch of spirals yeah well the the sharring gun sharring gun super duper okay the
the red one is like it's like a red a bunch of concentric red circles am i thinking of the right
one i think it changes uh like you can unlock higher levels of the sharring gun and it it's
like red and black and it has a different symbol depending on how cool it is okay i did not get
that far in the show so um anyway yeah but yeah he'll have it you just won't see it because he's
got those sunglasses on like he pulls them up and he's got the eyes he he you when when the um when
when the ova drops and the dojin drops uh you know that will be nate's big return he'll come back
and we'll you know they'll return to the glory we'll make the pzp great again uh it will return to
our former or mythologize past etc etc he'll come back and smite all our enemy best guy is coming
best guy is coming and he's gonna bring food and water and smite our enemies it's like that's what
bart says about crusty in uh in in the camp crusty episode of this season classic season three
season three classic possibly my favorite episode um anyway the next voicemail it's another image
yeah oh boy i can't wait to look at it i'm looking i'm gonna look die
i'm so white knight protecting mage someone is white knighting yeah i don't remember what
i imagined of this hypothetical commenter saying i guess i imagined they would be defending mage
for me uh they should die mage this is very happy with what's going on a little devil horns i wish
i had a knight wish i had a guy with a shield to block attacks directed against me that's why you
need large stacks of cash so you can buy one exactly a knight in armor bodyguard
cc mentions poo's adventures you remember poo's adventures uh is that different from poo general
poo's adventures of was like a sort of like trend among people that don't know how to make videos
where they would like crudely cut together footage of winnie the pooh with like other cartoons
in order to make like poo's adventures of the little mermaid which is just basically you
like cut reaction shots of winnie the poo into the little mermaid to sort of pretend that like
the cast of winnie the poo is part of the plot of little mermaid for example i've never seen that it
i discovered this rabbit hole a while ago a long time ago years ago actually and
you know i considered trying to make like a video about it or honestly i wonder if there's like a
i wonder if there's a lecture in that you know what i'm gonna make a note i might look into this uh
i'm gonna put it in my little uh uh uh uh word document uh all right next one is um
more image more there's so many images i'm so tired so tired of images the treachery of images
did you know in order to prepare for his role as a deranged killer in the movie joker
actor Joaquin Phoenix joined the pcp minecraft server and you too can become a deranged killer
link down in the description uh to join the pcp minecraft server discord server which will explain
to you how to get it set up and oh yeah since my internet works now uh we should do uh we should
do a stream soon we should we should hop on the pcp minecraft server baby have a little have a
little mine a little craft we should have a little mine yeah we should we should craft a mine or two
i think it could be good um i'll do it did you skip one did i i don't think so uh i think i think
you skipped uh this oh the homogenous this one oh oh homogenous i do get it do you get it
yeah it's geno it's geno but it's not geno from super mario uh legend of the starry boy no no no no
no no not not the same guy not the same guy no relation but i do get it though so the next one
um yeah okay mage's dreams versus ben's i hate cheesies i mean it's just true
yeah is this relating to something you said last episode or is it just no it was a couple
episodes ago i just had i woke up from a random dream in which i just was on twitter uh no not
on twitter on discord just saying how much i hate cheesie manfredo and then i woke up and i
thought why did i dream of that i said that um you looks like such a sack of potatoes yeah
beard beard's coming like a fake purple onesie beard's coming in good though
beard's coming in good this is nice this is a nice drawing it is a nice drawing is that is
that is that who's that goblin watching me i thought it was batman i think it's a goblin
in shadow batman doesn't have pupils when he's wearing his cowl oh yeah not in his animated form
anyway um this is just funny what's with that maze it's like a distant like hedge maze on that hill
yeah i don't know i thought it was just decorate they could be a maze volcano in theory in theory
amage's dream is more interesting it's more fantastical but i would argue that a hearing
the minutiae of it is not great but you know what the different strokes for different folks i guess
and streams are more psychologically damaging yes they're more about the human heart and
conflict with itself which is the only thing worth writing about as they say um okay why don't
we keep posting this one uh fuck in hell all right the next one is otjdern dot jpeg
i mean what am i what am i supposed to say to this uh i mean are you pogging or are you cringing
you look pretty mad they they trapped you looks like i look like i'm cringing but i think i might
just be pogging too hard that like my face doesn't know what to do anymore i look terrible in this
picture i look so bad at redcon too holy shit and i read that's redcon three
yeah you're right well i look bad there too you're wearing the worst there yeah what is this backdrop
just a random it makes me think of breaking bad but it might just be a random desert shot i guess
it's not even the desert because there's trees who won't somebody somebody please
help me remember who these girls are they're from old comic i just i want to know what the
comic is it is it called are they called jenny jenny and benny i might be thinking of i think
they're called jenny does this is such a mystery and somebody knows because they keep
oh i think yeah yeah somebody knows oh god uh okay no i searched
hmm yeah no i searched jenny boob's comic and i got some
interaction results seems to be yeah different this is not what i this is unrelated this is
not what i was looking for okay um you got to keep coming back to the pcp so eventually we'll
find out what this is that's the that's the long-running hook we got right the moment like what the
fuck i just where are these people from i know that it's a thing that people have seen because
i've seen it and there were threads about it it was mentioned in threads on something awful
and i just uh but i uh i can't remember one of these days one of these days um okay anyway
next one is i like apple right three two one go favor fruit favor fruit aesthetically i
like the taste of apple yeah quite a lot um um i think raspberry probably is my favorite because
of the sharpness i mean i like like raspberry like candy i kind of don't really like eating
raspberries on their own because they have they're so mushy they're like a mushy consistency
okay they're good with like an ice cream thing yeah or just cream um i like um passion fruit
but i don't know i've never like eat just eaten one and i kind of think that it's like not great
to just eat but like the flavor of it like put into other things is my favorite um
is rhubarb a fruit definitely not definitely not it's a rhubarb fleshy it's a stem
it's a stem of of what of the rhubarb plant oh it's yeah it's very sweet i like rhubarb crumble so
oh sure that's where my mind went sure but i mean it's it's sweet because they add sugar to it but
like the actual no the i mean i guess you've never just tried raw rhubarb but it's yeah i
guess not but it's literally just the stem of of a plant and it's just like sour oh well i like
the sour part sure it's good i like it too you know when you add something sweet to it it makes a
nice a nice blend of flavor uh kind of like how lemons are really sour but it's really nice if to
make lemonade out of when you add sugar to it um i guess i like sour but it's but it's definitely
not a fruit because a fruit is like it contains the seeds uh and a stem is not stem is not a fruit
i don't think the rhubarb plant doesn't even have fruits or maybe it does maybe it has like
flower little flowers that make little seeds at some point just we don't eat them
i like lemon flavor i'm trying to think of my favorite fruit to just eat is and i honestly
oh grapefruits oh no definitely grapefruits i love grapefruits i should try grapefruit
well you you never tried one no i just never got around to it i was just like my video games
that's gonna be like a long list of fruits i haven't gotten around to yet you know you know that would
that would disturb me greatly except that i have met other people who have just like never had
grapefruit and like i guess it's some people just don't i can't i like them a lot they're my favorite
uh they're juicy uh uh sometimes they're bad okay sometimes they're bad sometimes they can be a
little dry if you get a bad one that's like dry that sucks but if you get a nice juicy one
uh it's perfect oh it's perfect some people put sugar on theirs i don't understand it i don't think
they need additional sugar did i tell you did i mention what happened that guy who has like moved
in to my house uh who cooks in the kitchen and i made fun of them when i called him a famine
i remember you talking about that last week there there was i listened to that part yeah
well there was a funny story uh that guy like i guess he was eating Cheerios and he was trying
to put sugar on his Cheerios deranged thing to do in my opinion but i know that but i know that some
people do it um but apparently he he saw my like gummy ingredients on the on the shelf and he thought
he was putting sugar on his Cheerios but he had actually uh picked up my citric acid and he and
he sprinkled pure citric acid onto his Cheerios and ate them uh and i sour Cheerios yeah i imagine it
was not what he hoped it would be uh that sucks as well because sour milk is spoiled oh that must
have been sour that must have been discussed oh yeah it must have curdled the milk probably
maybe well it would it would make you think it's sour like spoiled yeah because of the sourness
must must have been gross um what was shit what was they even what was they talking about um
sugar oh favorite fruit yeah that's my answer passion fruit or grapefruit grapefruit is
whatever i answered already okay i like uh blueberries as well those i've been putting
blueberries in my um in my my oats my overnight oats uh and they're okay i kind of have the same
problem as raspberries i sort of don't like i wouldn't just like eat them i wouldn't just like eat them
straight yeah yeah um i don't think i eat any fruit straight because i'm gay a great
a grapefruit i'll just eat raw okay people the like normal way to eat a grapefruit is you cut it
in half and then you scoop out the sections with a spoon and that's fine and whatever i just like
tear it open and like pull the sections apart with my hands and just eat them like that like an orange
what's one of the sections yes yes except they have a okay an orange you you sort of the sections
sort of come apart because they have that like membrane in between you know what i mean yeah
and you eat it you eat it with the membrane a grapefruit has like the membrane is like thicker
but also it sort of separates more easily so you actually kind of i like pull open the membrane
and like ins and then i kind of scoop the like the pulp out as like a as like a section i pull your
hand i pull it out of the memory i mean yeah it comes apart if you if you pull it apart um
yeah i pull i pull this i pull the fruit out of the membrane and i eat that and then i just kind of
tear it apart into pieces and it's great and it's delicious uh the next voicemail is called Gibb's name
three two one go hey Gibb uh feel free to refuse an answer of course but what the what's your family
call you what's your at-home name uh they call me my birth name still because i haven't changed it
but i ain't i ain't telling you that i ain't giving that out for free i mean i know what it is
yeah so i mean it's been out there okay um
all right uh that's what that's what i thought um yeah i have been dabbling i have been dabbling
though with like with using Amy as a name hmm i don't know whether i truly want to commit to
using that so i've been using it as like when i play a video game and it says what's your name i put
that in hmm well i mean at the moment that's my video game name okay uh i mean um yeah i mean i
i just call you gibb anyway so like uh yeah on the internet yeah gibb is fine and dandy yeah
all righty uh next one is called moo three two one go do you think it's theoretically possible
for an ai to perfectly imitate a human yeah sure whatever yeah i mean give it enough time i mean
you can have an ai create an image that does look like it was drawn by a human like it like you can
do it it does it can't do it all the time oh they didn't say drawing an image they just said
completely replicate a human like oh just like just the way humans do things it's called there's a
video game you should play it's called mega man x that asks this very same question um
because the artificial intelligence really that's smart i mean theoretically yeah because like
i mean if a human brain exists therefore it would be theoretically possible to construct
one that would do the same thing right yeah the only way you could hypothetically get there is not
by micromanaging everything about the brain but it's creating a machine that can learn which is
what ai generally is and so yeah given enough time yeah i think it might make sentient robot people
it might not be possible to do with like computer hardware as it exists like like it might not be
possible to do with like transistors the way that like a computer is is constructed um like you would
need to like like some sort of nanotechnology needs to be invented yeah you would it might be that like
just the the the technological substrate that a computer is built of just like can't uh like
functionally replicate like what a human brain does at like the microscopic level so yeah that
it might need to be a different method uh or or like silicon based yeah or like quantum computer
run with like a superconducting material or something like that or rubber bands inside
so i would say theoretically yes but that doesn't really mean much in terms of like
will will we do it um next one is called happy new year three two one go hey i'm the man who had
gay sex i told you guys about it and uh i had no gay sex and it only gets better that's crazy
dude i love you guys and i love everyone and i hope you guys have a great 2020 being this
distinct and give it it goes it goes it goes it goes it goes yeah i couldn't make out some of that
no they're having a good time that's good that's nice okay yeah true uh next one is called ben's
periodic reminder to look in the mirror and call himself at a handsome devil calm uh okay uh have
you ever done that nope ah you got to get on that that's part of your list of things yeah all right
i'll put it on my put it on my whiteboard uh next one is an image it's an image it's peter parker
uh people who defend human art with an ai ai art people who enjoy speed runs people who
enjoy tasks for some reason the first two constantly fight each other well well a task
is made by a human i don't i don't really see the connection between these two things the first
two constantly fight yeah they're not really equitable a task is still like an impressive
feat for someone to to derive i mean uh like a strategy for how to do it and then seeing it
play out it's just like pressing play on like a video like it it it's not like um like if you
record your drawing and then you play back the recording that's not ai yeah a speed draw like a
human when you see a program running do you think oh a human didn't make this program like a computer
is running it a human a human didn't write it because a computer is running it like that's
what a task is a human wrote the instructions the computer is just executing them so this is a stupid
stupid example um next one is okay well there's a an image and a minute 30 long voicemail so let's
look at the image first does mid journeys license allow for commercial use of imagery generated by
the platform yes but if you're working for a bigger company than a million dollars in annual
revenue we ask that you buy a corporate license did you see consent from living artists or work
still under copyright no there isn't really a way to get 100 million images and know where
they're coming from it would be cool if images of metadata embedding them a copyright owner
something but that's not a thing there's not a registry there's no way to find a picture on the
internet then automatically trace it to an owner and then have anyway okay so this is just mid-journey
admitting that like no we don't have any method in place to prevent the use of
like someone else's intellectual property in order to generate the images we make cool
at least they're honest about it this this this pretty much renders anything that it makes like
suspect okay okay what's the audio then yeah uh three two one go
hey uh just checking in once more about the like AI art uh debate thing uh just because
ben mentioned something like he um assumed quite reasonably honestly that creators of art making
quote unquote AI would always insist basically that their models were ethically sourced
I did not I did not I did not assume that they would insist on that are like in the in public
domain or like whatever right like that are fair to use even for monetary gain or something
I would insist on that but in fact for commercial purposes and I'll link the tweet but there is an
actual interview with David Holtz the creator of mid-journey or the founder who just says like
well we know we literally don't know like yeah where we're getting our fucking images from he
just says like no there is really not a way to get a hundred million images and know where they're
coming from so like he's he's literally admitting to theft practically speaking like and the funniest
these same model makers too they have a very different approach to like AI for making music
because the laws are more stringent and more like actively pursued so they're afraid of
getting sued for that one but not for art because artists are like weaker yeah yeah
yeah all right what if you put like like you couldn't easily get like stock photos without
paying for a license to remove the thing um and stock photo companies they make a lot of that
and they're very they're sensible about protecting it as much as they can they probably don't put
that in the mid-journey thing they just go for whatever is as easiest to get so just things
are online i mean yeah i have apps i have no idea what like what method mid-journey uses to like
accumulate it's it's a image library it could be as simple as google image search that's that's
like my naive assumption is that like do you just google image search and it puts stuff together uh
maybe i just i just don't know but like yeah i definitely did not assume that AI generators
creators or people that use it would insist on that i that's what i said that would be my criteria
for like is this is this good actually at least like in terms of like commercial use
like with like without that assurance it's it's like it's a it's a hard no and like okay i just
yeah we definitely don't have that assurance maybe i don't know maybe there are other ones that do
a more um a more ethical job of it uh just to be clear though like for non-commercial purposes
i kind of think anything's fair game like fuck it steal other people's art and mash them up
if you're if like as long as you're not like selling it like who cares
yep um okay next one is just one more at gmail.law so a picture of a guy
let's see let's see this guy just looks like a guy
there he is okay i'll play the voicemail three two one go
no also i'm sorry but like i just looked at um the Forbes article that this excerpt comes from
and it has a picture in it of what mr. Holtz looks like and i gotta say i was expecting a
little bit more of a brad garling house looking type but instead first of all he looks like a
fucking hobbit he looks he looks like he's about to go oh oh mr. Frodo
mr. Frodo i have a beautiful new image it looks very creepy
it looks it looks very odd a machine created it oh my god and also am i crazy does this his
fucking face look ai generated it's fucking weird i mean i know we're like Mark Zuckerberg
unreal like artificial human vibes jesus christ i think he looks what a fucking goon i think he
looks pretty normal i think he looks pretty normal i i assumed when you posted the image that this was
like an ai generated face or something and i was looking for things and i think his his right eye or
his left eye that's looking a little sus but then it's a photo of a person so i don't think it
i think people are just asymmetrical sometimes yeah i think it's just a shadow or something
no you know i found that i'm asymmetrical in a way that i wasn't real i didn't realize before
it fucked me up i looked in the mirror i was like wait what's wrong with my face what's wrong
with my eyes i look like this oh my god i'm i'm definitely a little asymmetrical in like a little
bit in like my jaw in my my ear my my like hairline uh it's like a little bit yeah i'm
i'm asymmetrical in a bunch of different my my glasses actually kind of rest like a little
bit crooked because like my ears are a little asymmetrical i'm fucked up i'm fucked up that
also you know what else is fucking me up is uh still discord is not is not showing me like a
properly timed green circle it like still is not capable of of like just displaying when the sound
is being produced like it's it's been it's been like three hours now what the what and i'm and
i'm getting angry about it all over again just don't worry about it right now discord after this
okay next next one is uh okay it's another one wait did i just download that one we just listened
to no but i will okay the next one is unrelated from prince isolation okay three two one go
completely unrelated um i just wanted to clear up one small thing about um tom the tin can man
uh i don't know if i brought it across completely accurately in the voicemail that i was talking
about him but i just want to make clear that i like him in fact i love him and i want him to keep
calling into the pcp just to make sure tom mr tin can man whatever your name is i love you
and genuinely keep calling into the pcp we got great in fact get a tinnier microphone please
get him get a tinnier one the smoke more weed before you call in well please already okay
we already had him ask us so what our favorite fruit is so you know wish granted
uh next one is called by definition three two one go
uh there he is so the man himself older movies classics that i needed to watch and
basically is jesse literally bitter juice no jesse literally bitter juice what are you what
am i supposed to say that the answer is no okay if you say his name jesse jesse jesse
uh something happens something something happens okay next one is from mage of light
regard okay it's in two parts regarding ai art part one okay three two one go
so regarding the ai art thing i think it's i i said this on the bank court
or like a lot of time ago i think it's interesting to like you said to see what what it can do like
the machine learning i think it's the name of it yeah like to put words and see what it speeds out
like how does it think how does it connect concepts or shit like that i think that's
that's funny that's interesting but also like the problem with with it is that i have yet to see
a single ai art app that is not monetizing some way like they always heard like buy premium and
do more things or shit like that and it's like that is the fucking problem if it was just free
for everyone it would be like okay you know what do whatever the fuck you want you can already do it
it would take you a lot of time you know image editing and all that but whatever you know it's
the internet you know that it's like that but the problem is that it is just why why do they have to
charge for it it's the problem that's the that's the main problem to me like that shouldn't be like
yeah like that
i mean it's a guy with headphones who looks like a hobbit who's like oh what if i do this then i
can make money i mean i can i can pay for my my um uh what do i have apartment uh the fact the fact
that um the fact that he the guys made a program and he's charging for use of the program is not
really like the problematic part of it because like that's normal when you i mean i don't like if
it's like subscription based but like that's a separate problem if he had the program and he had
a website and you could go to the website and generate something for free but maybe he gets
paid through traffic like is that better i mean yeah i mean yeah yeah it's better it's better
but i don't i don't begrudge someone for monetizing their work
quote unquote there well well yeah i mean they made the program i know i know but that's the whole
problem is that the the the resource is mining is the problem with the work is that what it produces
is a a theft machine uh he built this machine and that's cool but like what the machine does
it's what the machine does that is like the the the ai problem not that like he's selling the machine
you know yeah i guess i guess if if it was free if it was a free thing that you could
generate an image based off of stolen work you could still then use that image to make your own
money so it would not solve the problem of art being taken without consent yeah it's it's i yeah i
think it you you said it you said it um there was um well okay let's listen to part two because
there's two parts of this one uh three two one go also if you think that you can just input something
into an a art machine and then that is you doing something other than just stealing shit i want
you to know that you are worse than fucking mary weather who actually pays people for the work
or even fucking more logic the wonderbread guy you're worse than them okay okay uh there's um
all right there was a thread going around on twitter the other day of it showed these like
shoes that were uh they were these like baroque sort of like like like oh yeah i saw those they
look so cool they looked really cool i'm trying to find them i can't find the they're in my likes
yeah if you could find those for me i would appreciate it because i'm i'm coming up blank
on a search um and yeah someone pointed out that they were they were ai generated they are they were
nice looking designs there they are there they are nike ex balman rikoko i mean beautiful who's
balmain i have no idea is that the name of the guy who's saying i invented this by typing it into the
ai generator is it like some other thing because i assumed i assumed it was like oh a fancy designer
had a collaboration with nike products to make yeah a series of like extremely expensive
designer shoes that are you know fashionable like that time xbox made a gucci like combo thing
there was like gucci and xbox made a gucci xbox controller or something with a weird like lavish
like controller case it's like that sort of thing these are pretty gorgeous shoes i just um
i think you know i think a human could have come up with this i i guess it's nice that
like the computer did such a good job you know putting the pieces together to design these
shoes like i guess that's something that it did pretty well but i think a human could have come
up with these ideas i guess maybe it's saved on like design work but like i mean the fact that
somebody a human came up with the prompts implies that you could come up with this right right yeah
true and and also just like you know these images are fine but they're just images like if someone
if someone wanted to make these shoes like you would still have to make them uh like i said i
don't i don't have any problem with someone using an ai to mash images together and in the and maybe
if it comes up with something if it puts things together that like looks cool like use that
like it's a it's a cool idea but you would you would then have to actually make these shoes
and like you know because these shoes don't exist and an an AI can't do that and i think that he i
think that a human could have uh could have conceptualized them i guess i guess it would
have been very work intensive to like produce images like this of a theoretical shoe with these
designs yeah i want i wonder how much like work had to go into like refining refining the prompts
and stuff and training the ai in a particular way to get it to produce such uh such high quality
you know renders i want to buy them somebody should somebody should just take the designs
steal them from the ai because you know i don't want to buy them because i know these are going
to cost like nine hundred dollars yeah but then somebody should make them and then i should be
like ah cool i wish i could have that uh i can't i'm glad somebody else will buy those so that i
don't have to yeah the the the creation of such a thing the the world happiness gone up perhaps
what's the bike thing perhaps yeah the shen uh the total happiness in the world increase total
happiness the world increased but like not in a stupid way um i don't know why i brought these
i think just mage of light mentioned like it's interesting to see like what the computer comes
up with and like yeah here's an example yeah i mean i wouldn't say that it's ai generation is
like inherently gross it's just the practice around it yeah yeah the the practice the practice
are okay in in particular what's really irksome is when i see someone saying like i'm an artist
because i put the right prompts in like that that pisses me off no you're not the computer
the computer the program made this image you you merely stumbled upon maybe you had to iterate
but like i don't i don't care like that's not it's not art to like refine a series of image
searches to produce a result that you're happy with like i mean no matter what if you do a prompt in
these things and you get a series of images and you don't like any of them you can use the exact
same prompt and do it again and get different images so it's not like the prompt is exactly
tied to whatever image ends up so it's like you have less creative control than you even you think
you do there's like there's a guy who made like a children's book uh oh the soulless man with no
soul i don't know maybe i think that well maybe i saw there was a guy who's just like ai generated
an entire book and tried to sell it as his own work and he looked like the sort of person who
has never thought anything nice in his whole life i don't know if it's the same guy but there was a
guy who made an ai generated children's book and okay even though i think that was the book was
probably bad i do think that i do think that it is art in the sense that like the the images are
not like he is not an artist he did not produce the images the computer produced the images
but he did select them and curate them and put them together into a book and i do think that is
art i don't think it's necessarily good but i do think curation and like selecting and like
putting things together into a into a coherent work is art of a sort so i do think that like a
book made of images that were ai generated is art just like i think you know harry partridge
said that he used ai to like generate some backgrounds for an animation and like the
animation that he made using those ai generated images is still art the the background itself
is not really because the computer made it well the only difference would be is that he
doesn't ai generate the entirety of the animation just an aspect of it with this children's book
it's an entire like did he animate did he ai generate the story as well i don't disagree with
the curation i don't i don't know i think i yeah no i think ai might have been used in like in
writing i think i think he said that like yeah ai wrote the text as well it's it's kind of like
a collage if you if you take a bunch of artist work and you cut out bits that you like and stick
them together um you've made a collage uh using yeah other people's work yeah so it's creative in
that sense but like yes you didn't really the individual pieces no i i i i i i i i i i i i i
i'll put my foot down a hard line stance is that like if a computer if a computer generates the
image if you you are not the artist you you might do something with it you might curate it you might
arrange it you might edit it into something and then you could maybe say that you have some ownership
over that thing uh yeah um okay next one is a dream i had last night three two one go
hey ben saint and uh i assume there's other people on the podcast this week true i had a dream last
and you were in it so i thought i would tell you so i was in the jungle right because i was on
vacation on this tropical island and i had already gotten a pretty good tan the other day but there
was a monkey in the house but that's not important we were in the jungle and um there was this big
snake and you spotted it slithering in the grass and it had like cat ears like it was like a cat
snake and you were like see the trick to this is and then you like went to try to grab it
and you grabbed it and then it like went around and bit you and um yeah it seems like something
you would do fucking idiot i'm sorry god yeah you see the the trick with these cat snakes is
ah stabbed yeah i can see it
i like the idea of a cat ear snake it's like i can't even even like mistakes that i didn't
even actually make it's like nah ben would do that so let's hold him let's hold him accountable
man there's just no winning yeah the trick to this cat snake i think i would avoid such a creature
it wasn't true but the fact that i thought it could be says a lot about society there's a lot
about society there's a lot about the podcast there's a lot about the state of the podcast
uh next one is an image let's see what do we got it's a cartoon honey could you get the meat out
of the fridge while i'm chopping these potatoes sure thing dear hmm but who is the cuck and who is the
in this scenario yeah yeah it it did seem a little funny i like the idea of a cooking person
that i'm watching two people cooking and i'm thinking like one of these people is getting
played like one of these people one of these people is the winner and one of these people is the loser
the scenario cooking is nice i like the smell maybe feels good sometimes to get some good food made
i'm not i'm not gonna disagree i i think it it's true that it says more about me than it says about
anything else that i saw a couple like cooking and i thought and my assumption is like this guy is
just doing this to impress that girl this guy is just doing this to like yeah as like a a move
okay uh i mean even if that was the the reason like ultimately it's like what's the problem
i i guess i well i'm gonna learn how to cook in order to make myself okay or more attractive
when i would shake my head and i would say no i should be unattractive yeah he yeah he made yeah
he made a delicious meal but like did it did it cost him his soul did it cost him his soul
no no um lamal all right next one i like this i like this one this one's really funny um i should
honestly i should tweet this this is about me i feel like this represents me honestly the next
one is called five skin head three two one go ben you should absolutely give a shit about your
foreskin this thing is super important let me tell you as a kid i was the only peeled person
in my whole family and whenever we would like pee i'd look over what and see that their penises
look different than mine why i feel left out why would you all pee together my mind looks so weird
compared to them you know yeah i mean we feel bad definitely but also that's rough having this
foreskin is just better for sexual acts from like masturbation how would you know to insertion
and everything in between like there's no benefit to circumcision aside from the fact
that it's marginally easier to paint to clean your penis but you know that's such a minor benefit
compared to everything else how do you know and also it is maybe there seems to be possible
to regrow your foreskin oh my god you just have to like train it with tools or whatever what the
fuck pen and tell our bullshit episode about it it's pretty disgusting what and i'm too much of
a pussy to do it no but uh no it's totally possible do your research shut up shut up man
this guy's fucking with me this guy's fucking with me by delivering this completely insane
you can grow it back Ben information you're just gonna dead he sounds he sounds like he
believes it he sounds like he really believes it and it's messing with me okay you just gotta
you gotta get your inner like chameleon your inner lizard to grow that skin back
okay there is there is a pen and teller bullshit episode about circumcision maybe i'll watch it
sometime okay okay um next one is uh image do you think that guy's sincere or is he or is he
joking i mean i don't know maybe he feels very sad about not having a foreskin but he can't
actually think maybe he's hoping that you can regrow your foreskin by training it with tools
right like that's a completely deranged thing to say what kind of tools okay so like a vice
grip like pulling on it like what the hell i i train it with tools get the fuck out of here um
okay this one then will never be the protagonist of tpc then cast 3.0 you cannot procrastinate
there you go you know they said it couldn't be done but uh i've proved them all wrong
that old procrastinators logo always reminded me of like really cheap oven pizza logo
it's so funny that like look at like the angles of the letters
yeah it's like really it's like really fucked it's like the the t i see what they were going for
like they're following the curve of the top like the t is tilted to the left and the c is tilted
to the right and the p is straight but like really like the bottom of the t should be stretched out
as like to follow the bottom curve of the oval you know yep okay no i was sorry i was yawning
again i know i know i must be we must we must have been going to cc says tpc then jiff through
and tricksy guest starring ben tpc now ben and gib and guest starring laser bot uh not exactly true
jeff was never really a main member jeff was always just kind of just kind of just kind of there
uh next um wait no i already okay next one is called thumbs up three two one go
ha ha ha good one i believe him fall next voicemail
uh close but no cigar on that one i can't believe i can't believe oblivion fall
is so obsessed with regrowing his foreskin like i can't like i didn't oh yeah that was
oblivion fall's voice of course yeah definitely he's so distinctive um he's got that he's got that
rich chocolatey uh cadence um did you know that uh oblivion fall actually was the narrator of both
disco elysium and hades that's true look it up look it up on imdb he's also the voice of samurai
jack same guy yep and ren and stimpy both ran and stimpy oh my god uh i can't believe it i know it's
it's hard to believe and yet and yet okay next one is called uh it's ninja link i'll get back
regular drawing soon at love you that vvv oh it's viny oh look at these oh these are cool
it's cup killer oh they actually really like these murder meteor cup killington oh wow
you'll give i kind of cool actually i flip the canvas to make i flip the canvas to make sure
it was balanced and i forgot to flip it back so the progression may seem backwards but whatever
yo gib i annoyed ben in the time i haven't been able to draw so this is more of an apology for
this week why are you saying me yeah what yeah he viny did annoy me because he was like posting
like way too many memes in my in my server oh right he would do this thing where he would just be like
he would find like a completely random image and he would just post it and be like this is just like
when ben does x or this is when ben does y and it would be like just some random shit and i was
viny what are you talking about why do you pose this picture of like a cat and it's like ha ha
this is just like when ben sees a girl and is in and embarrasses himself so yeah okay i think
that's what he's talking about um i really like this meteor yeah i like the teeth they're very like
yeah these are cool i feel like i feel like viny uh this i'm this is the this is like
the best viny art in terms of like art i don't know yeah good good teeth
i see he's using the tablet nice drawing digitally yeah the good good use of color
yeah the the bright teeth on the black meteor that looks awesome genuinely looks really cool
so it's like a cycle natural ben saint to cop killer to murder meteor oh the little arrows natural
ben saint oh i see i see this is your evolution this is your pokemon evolution yeah the apotheosis
of dark ben becomes murder meteor cop killington okay i'm just i'm just looking i'm just i'm just
admiring my teeth that is what my teeth look like i gotta go to the dentist the bright green and
glowing bright green and glowing um one of these days one of these days uh maybe after i finish the
book i gotta finish the book so i can maybe that's why i haven't finished the book because i know that
after i finish the book i gotta go to the dentist you can do with a dentist at any time wrong you
can say to the dentist please make a appointment and they say okay uh you would think so you would
think so but uh it's just not it's just not how it works unfortunately it's more complicated
they want to see the book first you wouldn't understand yeah they said don't they said
ben saint why are you don't even show your face around don't call that book don't call us again
until until the book is out you're not allowed to have teeth
what a thing to say to someone you're not allowed to have teeth you will not we will not serve you
you do not deserve this form of medical care uh oh that's the last voicemail
um we did it yeah yeah
hooray um
well that's the end that is the end um any final do you have any final
shit to say uh well ben's gonna be streaming we're gonna be streaming at some some time this week
i will do well by the time this episode is out i will have already done at least one stream
to i might also yeah i might also do a few streams i've been thinking about it i just
like art stress i don't know about art streams maybe art streams that's the thing i can't decide
whether i want to play video games or draw because like drawing would be would be saving on like a
time i could be doing two things at once but i don't know kind of true kind of true
uh i mean since yeah i'm gonna do gaming because my plan is to play those games on
just kind of the whole point so yeah i don't know i never really i always found drawing on stream
very distracting i always found chat like really distracting from like me trying to actually do
the work you know yeah i guess my streams were quite quiet because i stood them at like weird
hours and for a long time so people would jump in and then leave yeah when i did those well i mean
it's like if the if there's if the chat is not active then it's like why am i even streaming this
but if the chat is active then it's like it's distracting me from drawing i guess i guess that
i i think i think i managed to do more work just because it's easier to work with an audience
it is it kind of like then it is like it like the distractions are outweighed by
the compulsion to not fuck around yeah it's like because people are people are watching you don't
want to like seem like you're just wasting time yeah yeah i i understand that oh you know what i
could do yeah my dark cloud video i could play dark cloud on stream oh i could use that footage
for the video that could be fun oh you mean the one oh i didn't realize you were actually working on
that well the prerequisite is that i need to play the games all the way through and then yeah
tabs on like various things because not everything is in the wiki and so i need to i need to delve
deep and find all the text boxes and stuff and if i have like i play a 100 play through of both of
them then i'll have all the footage i'll see everything i mean i don't know how it'll go
but like yeah when i eventually make the battle network lecture uh i might yeah i could definitely
see myself using some like clips of me streaming it if i have like any like reactions to any like
really bizarre stuff in there like i might use some footage from the streams to like highlight
some shit uh definitely that's the cool you know you gotta do you do you do work you spend your
time doing things that all feed into each other it all it's all part of the it's all part of the
workflow funnel you funnel it all into content you gotta make content yeah yeah oh i love content
i do love content i'm i'm such a little piggy i just want to roll around in my content slop
yeah true it's want to roll and i'm tired of pretending that i care about quality
i'm just want to eat my little content i always want to eat my my content from my content trough
i just want to go up to that trough and just stick my face in there and just slurp up all the
content this just comes down the pipe oh i'm just i'm just a plant in a big crop circle
waiting for the big bar to rotate over me and drip some content on me so i can grow
uh yeah all the plants in the world they see water's content
consume to be yeah to you know if you're a plant imagine you're a plant well to you water would
be like a new red letter media video like you need it to live and if you don't get it you'll
wither and die um oh did you see this did you see uh the news reporting about the new key video
do you know they're they did the one where they finally watch new key yeah i saw a twitter video
of like somebody recording the news where it's like talking about the new key tape
and yeah it's it's got a lot of money oh yeah but okay but what i'm talking about is like there was
at least one news outlet that reported on it and they pretty much like chain they reported it like
like it was a scam like as though red letter media were like scamming people
oh i didn't see that i saw like they said it was going to charity and it was all fine that's an
interesting story moving on the one i saw was like oh youtubers like destroy youtubers destroy
like copies of like a rare vhs tape in order to drive up the price of like their one copy
and it's like god like the video is literally like a parody of that it's literally like a like a
commentary on that like people do that and it's bad and uh yeah fucking but they just reported on
it as though it were being done just like sincerely uh very frustrating i don't feel bad i don't feel
bad for red letter media because like they're fine but it is but it is annoying to see uh the facts
mis misrepresented in such a way you understand it's a soda yeah i mean it's this with regards to
red letter media especially there's no chance of that like false narrative sticking anywhere no
because some some old person who's like i've never heard of this new key before
i thought you were gonna say i've never heard of red letter media before but they probably
knew either yeah yeah yeah yeah um right it's like uh damn uh you know just uh i saw j j was
tweeting about that like this was the way that this particular outlet chose to report on it
it reminded me of reminded me of taylor lorenz reporting on the um the freaking chili neighbor
situation choosing to both sides the chili neighbor thing
oh no yeah yeah no not the chili thing yes the chili thing it will never go away
it will never leave the discourse it'll never leave my personal discourse it dealt me irreparable
psychic damage imagine both sides in somebody giving chili to someone else yeah hmm a person gave
their neighbor chili and some other people got really angry at them about it but like we need
to like like we we gotta like let's hear both sides of the issue let's hear both sides maybe they
got a point maybe they got a point because why else would they be mad there must be there must
be a problem wasn't like there was a kitten punching tweet or whatever but we could but we
could do we could be we could start that discourse oh like punch a kitten yeah and then when the news
reports on it and then when the news reports in it like podcasters punch kitten and tweet about it
and then we retweet the article we roll our eyes when we say uh these guys don't understand we were
doing it as commentary on other people that punch kittens we were doing it ironically to show how
bad it is oh yeah that's why i just don't get it we're being persecuted by the liberal media
mm-hmm
become a patron of patreon.com slash the procrastinators okay are we done getting the pcp
minecraft server do join the pcb minecraft server you don't even need to become a patron to do that
we will that's free stream that soon yep we'll let you know we'll let you know on twitter when
we're gonna stream okay do you want to do you want to do you want to like commit to like
stream like next week at on wednesday or something like like like the next wednesday
after this episode goes live do you want to like announce it ahead of time the 25th i don't know
perhaps that's the that's the next wednesday after this episode goes live um yeah yeah i don't
think anything's happening then okay yeah we will be we will we will do another pcp
live stream on the pcb minecraft server next on january the 25th so if you want to i don't know
make some stupid shit in the minecraft server and then force us to look at it uh join the minecraft
server link in the link down below and make it by then and then join us on the stream and yell at us
to go hey look at this thing i made and then we'll have to do that uh so that's how that works
and it's free now so no excuses okay i think that's the end yep good episode thank you for
listening see you next week bye bye yeah