I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Gibb, you start the shit.
Oh, no, you interrupted me.
Sorry, sorry.
My intro was so good and you ruined it.
Now it's shattered into little pieces.
I've fallen over.
It's like that image of the Pepe Frog.
When they have the lunch tray and they fell over and they're crying.
They're crying and everyone around them is laughing about it.
Yeah, it's that other frog.
No, it's the Pepe Frog.
The Pepe Frog.
No, but it's not Pepe.
It's like the little autistic one.
Oh, yeah.
It's like the slightly melty looking one.
I always think of them as the same guy.
It's just drawn funny.
I think he's...
I think he might be named Pipo or something.
Oh, Pipo.
There's the one that Amy Therese always posts.
Welcome to the Procrastinus podcast.
What can I get for you?
I'll have...
I'll have a...
a Pedialyte.
We run out.
What?
We run out of those.
Can I have a glass of seawater?
Just jump in the ocean.
Idiot.
No.
I want to pay for it.
Andrew Tate said that I shouldn't just drink water because water is free.
I should drink sparkling water because it costs money.
It's rich man's water.
It's piss man's water.
Same with the ocean.
I need to pay two and a half dollars for it.
I need you to put a slice of lemon in it.
Instead of wading out into the ocean to piss,
he wades out into a swimming pool of sparkling water.
I need to go to a restaurant to piss.
I need to piss in my seawater
from an establishment.
I needed electrolytes.
I was...
I think I was depleted of electrolytes this morning.
Oh no.
Where did you put them?
You know, that's a great question.
I've recently learned that apparently people drink Pedialyte
as like a hangover cure.
Even though it's baby food.
It's like baby food.
Are you a hangover?
No, I'm not a hangover.
I just...
I just think I needed some salt.
That's okay.
I ate some Kirkland brand
cauliflower crust supreme
pizza, so I think I'm good now.
Alright.
Yeah. Okay.
Welcome to the Procrastiners podcast.
Welcome to the show. Hey, I finished Medical Soul.
Did you get around to watching any more of it?
No shit.
I have not
got watched any more of it, actually.
I've had a...
I have a lot of things that I
have meaning to
finish that I have not finished yet.
You and everybody.
Yeah.
I could get into those things, but
how is
Better Call Saul?
I like it. It's a very, very good show.
And it was good.
I don't want to spoil anything.
That's good. That's good.
Tell me
what happens, but without spoiling anything.
Well,
let's just say
Saul got a call
and he spoke on the phone.
And he's better.
And he's better now.
Yes. Nice.
I
did not play anymore. I have not made any more progress in Disco Elysium.
Oh, I started that.
I started that today.
Oh, you did. Cool.
How is that for you?
I'm liking it. I like the detective work.
I like the...
I like how when you've got like stats
in various mind
things and body things, they'll come up
in your internal dialogue.
So like...
Somebody says something and then your logic
brain comes in and says, well, what that means
is this. And I'm like, oh,
thanks. I'm dumb. I wouldn't have known.
Yeah.
So I think this has been
much remarked upon,
but it's interesting how
in Disco Elysium, those stats,
they're not just things that you can do.
They're proclivities
of yours. So like if you have a lot of logic,
it's not just that you can
logically deduce things
that you couldn't otherwise.
It's that you will approach
a task with logic, even if another
solution might be better.
So like if you have lots of
stats in logic, you might
use a logical approach to a solution
when like a more emotional one
might have been better. Just because
that's like what you are
geared towards doing.
Yeah, it's interesting. There's a few times
when it's like a part of
my psyche comes forward and says,
how about this? And I'm like,
eh. Yeah.
Nah. And they're like, um,
come on though. Come on.
Electrochemistry is always trying to get me
to do drugs.
Yeah.
And he's got to stop that
because I'm staying clean.
Yeah, I'm playing as
a person would.
Not like a gamer.
Because I've seen that it's
like role playing,
but you're an
amnesiac. You forgot everything.
Yeah.
So I'm as the player learning
this character I'm playing as.
But I'm only doing things
I feel like I would do if I
was also trying to figure out
who I was. Yeah.
It's fun that way.
I'm pretty much doing the same.
I'm picking
the most me
answers to things.
And yeah, generally
that means that I'm apologizing
a lot because I feel bad because
apparently I went on a drug bender
and gave myself brain damage and now
I can't do my job as a policeman
and I'm a huge failure.
It's funny. I've seen all
the sorry options and I haven't been
clicking them mostly because I'm too awkward
to admit that I was I've lost
my memory. Have you are you just trying
to like you just trying to play it cool?
I'm trying to wing it and hoping that nobody
notices. That's good.
The more information I get, I'm like, oh, okay,
I'm on a case and I got this.
I did have to tell my partner
at some point because
I had to radio in say I lost my badge,
but earlier I told him that I had
the badge and he's like, oh,
oh, okay.
And I'm like, I'm sorry. I'm sorry I lied.
Yeah.
I died a couple
time where I lost a couple times and I had to
restart. And I think the first couple
times I told my station that I lost the
badge, but like
I didn't deliberately save scum, but I just
had to do that section again. And so I think
the third time I did it, I told them like,
nah, I'm just going to tell him I didn't lose
the badge and they believed it. So
it actually worked eventually.
Yeah, they made fun of me.
And I was like, yeah, okay.
I need to do,
I need info.
They still made fun of me because they know
I lost my gun, but
they don't know. Oh, I lied about that.
They made fun of me. No, they did.
They know I lost my badge. I lied about losing
my gun. They don't, they don't know I lost my
gun. So it was the same then. Yeah.
Yeah.
I was like, I can't, I can't take
double
laughter. I need to pretend I'm cool.
Mm-hmm.
We'll see how long that lasts.
I died immediately
upon starting the game.
I clicked around on things
and I turned the light on, which gave me
one point of damage and I was like, ah, fuck.
But then I tried to grab
the
the ceiling, the tie on the ceiling fan, and I failed and I died.
I have died twice.
The only time it's happened, but it's funny that, like, before I even knew how the game
worked, I died him immediately.
That's really funny.
Okay, have you met, have you met Measurehead?
No, I'm not too far in.
I've walked around a couple places.
I haven't talked to the rioters or the union people.
I talked to the old lady on the boat.
I talked to the little kids.
You met Kuno and the, and the far, well, I call her the forest girl.
Yeah, I met them.
Um, okay, I've had two losses and they're like, I'm doing a lot better now.
Like I got a bunch of medicine and now I'm like not really in danger of losing anytime
soon.
But like early on, I was very, very frail and I died once.
I won't say anymore.
I'll just say it was a, it wasn't even really a fight.
It was just, I got in like a physical, some in a bit of a physical confrontation and just
like the strain of it made me have a heart attack and die because of my weakened state
and I just died.
And then the other time I lost was, um, it was when the forest girl just started crying
and the rape just started yelling that I was going to rape her and I was just so demoralized
by that, that I lost my morale points and I lost my will to be a cop and I quit the
forest.
Oh, whoa.
Yeah.
I haven't run into a situation where I lose a morale point for some reason.
No, I, yeah, I've had, I've had one physical loss and one morale loss and the morale loss
was a lot funnier.
Yeah, I think.
It was when I asked who's Kuno.
The girl just starts crying, rape, rape.
I'm like, oh God, no.
Yeah, they, they did that for a bit.
I could tell he was trying to get a rise out of me.
He wanted like me to do something and I turned around like, yeah, I don't need, I don't have
time for this.
And he said, ha, ha, you're my bitch.
You'll do, I got you.
Kuno rides the lightning.
He's a little, he's a little, he's a little freak.
He's riding the lightning.
You know what?
Just let him.
Let him cook.
Yeah, let him cook.
Have you investigated his, his, his like area?
I've looked around.
I found a door and I went in.
Yeah.
It's like a little kid's playhouse.
His little shack.
Yeah.
Kuno's shack.
I tried to investigate the body.
I'm, I went, I threw up the first time.
Yeah.
They said, boy, should get ammonia.
So I went, found, got ammonia, bought it from the store, I came back.
Failed again.
Yep.
Then it was what happened to me.
Then you got to get your shit together.
I got my shit together.
I failed again.
And then.
Even after getting your shit together.
Yeah.
It was like a 50% chance and I failed.
And then it was like, okay, well, I just got to go do something else.
I think if you just, I think if you just wait a while, like I think it gets easier and easier
like as the days pass.
Uh, I think.
I'm still on day one.
So I haven't done that much because I think, I think I, I think I investigated the body
on day two and yeah, I got my shit together and I think I also got an extra modifier
because like time had passed and like the smell had become not as like less bad.
That's odd though.
It's already been there for like a week.
Why would the smell get better?
Yeah.
I mean, it would eventually start to get better.
I don't know if it would.
Maybe you just get used to it a week.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe because it had, it had frozen.
Uh, no.
But if it's getting warmer, it would smell even worse.
Did you investigate the footprints?
I did.
I did all the footprints.
I was so smart.
How is he so good at identifying shoe sizes?
Uh, he's a rain man.
He is.
Do you know?
He's got that, that autistic sight.
Do you know your name?
I know the, I'm a clipboard.
There's initials and I assumed that there's a, some, probably my name.
I don't know what it is though.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm thinking that coat that's hanging up is my coat.
The one on like the railing?
Yeah.
It's my coat and it's probably got my gun on my badge in it because I mean, they'd probably
be in that if I leave them anywhere.
A reasonable assumption.
I tried to jump over the thing, but he got, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he
bitch out.
He bitched out.
Yeah.
I bitched out.
I didn't, I didn't make the jump.
I, well, I won't, I won't, uh, I think, you know, spoilies.
I like to figure stuff out.
I think I got to the coat in an unusual way.
I think I got there in a way that I kind of like wasn't supposed to, but like, I mean,
there is a door, but I just don't know how to get to that door.
So yeah.
For sure.
I'm going to, I think my plan right now is to spend my experience points to level up
my endurance or something so I can try approaching the body again.
There's another, there's a couple other things.
I still haven't got my tie.
I failed to get my tie.
You still haven't gotten like from the fan.
Yeah.
That's funny.
It's just up there.
I have to, I have to spend a point in Savoy fair or whatever.
Yeah.
I have to try again.
My, um, I think they were, okay, I've heard that there's like things to do with the tie,
but like I think my stats are just like wrong and I, and like they're not, none of them
have happened for me.
What are your like stats in, by the way, what's what like class did you choose?
I made my own.
I did.
Uh, good.
I can't remember the top two were good and good.
And then it was weak and weak, but you don't remember what the ones were that you like
focused on.
I think it was an intellect.
Um, and I chose the, the conceptualize as my special skill.
I'm pretty good with empathy.
So whatever one that is in, interesting.
And the ones I'm bad at are like, uh, like acrobatics and fucking endurance or whatever.
Yeah.
I'm a nerd, but I'm a smart nerd.
I, I went, I went with thinker.
So I'm, I'm like maxed out in an encyclopedia.
And I think like logic is pretty good and I'm pretty, I'm pretty bad at everything else.
I like the conceptualize cause it comes off occasionally as like, that's like, yeah, I
like that.
I let encyclopedia is fun just cause it gives you like facts that you wouldn't know otherwise.
Um, what are their, uh, what are their like NPCs?
Have you talked to that have been interesting?
Uh, I talked to the manager of the little place.
The whirling and rags, the whirling and rags.
And yeah, I talked to the manager.
I'm not the bartender.
Yeah.
Uh, there was the thing where he thought he made the lady quit cause he asked for her
number.
And when I talked to her through the radio, yeah, I tried to be, I tried to get the way
I'm playing it as I'm like, if I sense that there might be like, if somebody might clam
up, if I say the wrong thing, I try to be cautious.
So I managed to go get some, sometimes they do.
Sometimes you can say something that will like change a person's attitude.
Yeah.
And so I was, I was pretty cautious with the lady cause she seemed like she didn't like
me and it was, it became clear.
That I was, I was a bad guy.
Yeah.
But I managed to clear things up between her and the guy cause she doesn't hate him.
And I told him that it was a good Samaritan.
Oh, that's funny.
Yeah.
She told me like she, she was like surprised that I thought that it was because of him.
But I didn't get any like options to maybe it's because you have empathy and I don't.
But like, yeah, I didn't, I didn't get the option to tell him that lol.
Sucks to be him.
Yeah, I'm buttering people up.
I'm the butter guy.
Butter guy.
Have you, have you been in the bookstore?
No, I saw that.
I didn't go in.
I spoke, I went past it, spoke to the lady on the boat.
Oh, Joyce, Joyce, the, the, the rich woman, wild, the wild pines lady.
Yes.
Yeah, talked to her about state of the, state of the union.
The ultra liberal.
Yeah.
If you, if she will admit to being an ultra liberal, if you ask the right questions.
I, I did not.
I see.
I, I didn't want to like, because I was still, I don't know, early in investigating.
Yeah.
I didn't really want to make anyone mad at me.
So I'm just sort of like nodding, sagely, quiet and not really saying anything.
That could make them upset.
I still, I still haven't really like, firmly picked sides in anything.
I see the things where it's like, haha, yeah, unions are cool.
I hate the rich, you know, things where you can say that.
And I'm like, yeah, but I shouldn't say that to her, though.
I need her for info.
Yeah.
I don't, I mean, hmm.
I did, I did say some, I did say some pretty communist stuff to her, actually.
I don't know if you want to know what she said.
It's not a huge spoiler or anything, but if you want to.
Well, the ultra liberal thing.
She was, she didn't say that to me.
She's, she's actually, she's cool with it.
She just kind of laughs.
She's kind of like, haha, yeah.
It's like, it's kind of charming.
I think she probably is bad.
Like, I think her company.
Honestly, I'm still, I'm still feeling it out.
I think wild pines is probably bad, but she seems nice.
She, she, uh, did she talk about disco at all?
Uh, no.
She and, uh, the protagonist seem to be of an age and seems like they were both
like around when they were younger, you know, disco was the big thing.
She's just like, yeah.
Hey, I remember, I remember disco.
Yeah.
Communism might have been cool, but they lost.
Oh, well.
Uh, very nice.
I like her.
I assume you have not met the union boss.
No, I saw the people shouting and I'm like, okay, well, I still don't know.
Yeah.
I'm still trying to get in to, uh, to, uh, to inspect the body.
So I just, I didn't want to like open too many threads.
So I left them for a moment.
I need to go back and talk to the, uh, the, the right to work, uh, protest people.
There's like, I know there's like, there's like threads there that I have
not followed up on.
And, uh, I guess the last thing that happened was I found a bag and now I'm
picking up trash.
Oh, I was so stoked when I found the bag.
I, I didn't find it until the second day, which.
Was really frustrating because, uh, I really wanted money on the first day.
I was really hurting for money and I saw all these bottles around.
I was like, I just want to collect the bottles.
I just want money.
And I didn't, and, uh, oh, I just, I just had to live with that.
But it was, I think they should have allowed you to pick up a single
bottle with one hand instead of like, if you don't have a bag, you can't
pick up any.
Honestly, what?
And like, bring it, bring it, bring one bottle at a time to the bottle return.
Like if you're, if, if you're like, this is all you got.
It's the only thing you can do and you really need cash.
Like, I think if you're desperate enough, you would do that.
I think that that would know, you know what?
I think you're totally wrong and it's good that they did what they did.
They should not, they should not allow you to play the game in such a miserable way.
Yeah.
No, like if you take your pants off, you tie the ends of the pants, you got a huge bag.
And you go around picking up trash off naked.
Yeah.
Okay.
The thing is, if, if you know what you're doing, like you would just
know where the bag was and you could just go get it, like immediately.
If you just wanted to collect all that stuff, like I didn't know where it was.
I had to find it, but that's okay.
I was like deliberately like not looking up things in advance.
I have other things I could say about some characters, but you haven't met
several of them yet.
So I won't get into it.
I'm sort of being a communist, but like I said, I haven't really like firmly
committed to it.
I haven't like, yeah.
I feel committed to being a detective.
I like figuring stuff out.
Yeah.
I'm going to, I'm going to find this mystery.
Who did the killings and how did they do the killings?
That's my first.
Do you have, do you have any leads?
Do you have any leads on the, on the, the murder?
Well, I know all the work boots in the, the footprints and stuff as the small set
of footprints could be a lady, could be a child.
And there's the, you know, there's like something, but like nothing that I can
really follow up on.
I'm mostly at the, I'm trying to find my badge and gun.
Okay.
So I took to the, what's her face?
Still don't know who called in the body.
And you mean the woman on the phone?
Yeah.
She didn't call in about the body.
And so I need to go check out the phone that was used because it's like one phone
or two phones.
Oh, where's, where's that?
Well, remember that she talked about like people, she didn't call it in.
Nobody would call in because one, nobody calls the cops because the union runs
the town union already knew.
And people call the people, like people steal the copper from the wires.
So there's a union phone that the union uses that is still got its wires.
And then there's one down near the coast.
That's what she said.
So I'm like, okay, maybe I can go find something there.
Come to think of it.
I don't think I have figured out who called in the body.
And I don't think I have, I remember mention of the phone.
I don't think I've investigated the phone.
So thanks for reminding me about those leads I should follow up on.
It's just like we're two detectives.
But you don't know like whose boots they were.
No, I mean, they're all workers boots aside from maybe one of them.
So they're probably a bunch of people with workers boots on.
And there's only like sea people around here, the union people.
The debaude, the debaude's union.
Yes, yes.
Do you I was going to do you know who the victim was?
No. OK, I think I'm on day like three.
And I think I have a pretty clear idea of what happened with the murder itself.
But there's like a bunch of like other like stray details surrounding it
that I like am aware of, but like don't understand.
And I want to, you know, that that's kind of where I'm at with it.
Oh, I haven't found a place to sleep.
You haven't. It's like two p.m. in my game.
That's the thing I need to figure out before it gets too dark.
Yeah. Yeah, you better.
Oh, or else.
They're going to get you.
The night terrors, the old sleep gremlins.
Do you know?
Do you know what the pale is like a bucket?
No, P.A.L.E. Nope.
You know what?
I also don't know what it is.
I've just heard it mentioned and I don't know what it means.
Did I hear it mentioned?
I feel like, no, maybe I did.
Maybe I can check the logs or like if there's a notes thing I can see.
Hmm. Well, well, that's it, officer.
Good over and out. All right.
Thank you for helping me with my investigation into your time playing that video game.
Pleasure doing business with it.
I did not play any more of it because I've been I played Mega Man battle
network on stream, a much worse game.
It's actually it's all right.
It's honestly a bit of that.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you popped in.
I saw you. How long was the stream?
I've done two now and the first one was like four hours and the second one was
like five hours and I think I'm about like halfway through the first game.
Which is there's they're long, they're long.
So extrapolate.
Let's see how many games are there?
I think there's like.
Eleven. Eleven.
So like 10 hours, 20 hours.
Twenty hours. It's going to be like 11. Yeah, yeah.
Well, you know what? It's OK.
I'll just it'll just be a project.
It'll just be a project.
I like the combat.
I like the battles. They're pretty fun.
It I just hate I hate the random battles.
I hate that when I'm in a dungeon walking around trying to figure
shit out every so the random battles come and just interrupt what I'm doing.
And those battles are not fun.
They're repetitive.
They're not they're not very taxing.
They're not very interesting.
They're just they're just fucking bullshit you have to deal with.
And it makes up a significant portion of the time spent playing.
It's just getting through random battles.
Do you get like experience points or money?
You get you get money and you get new chips,
which are basically like spells, attacks and stuff.
OK, you basically use like a deck.
You basically build a deck of chips and that's like what you use to do damage.
So you do benefit from doing them.
But I still don't like them and it doesn't make for a good gaming experience.
Now, I mean, generally in a game with random battles,
it depends mostly on if the battles you have to participate in
helping the pacing of the game overall.
Like if you get to a boss and because of the random battles,
you have a good chance at winning.
If the pacing is fine, then you can just move on through and it's OK.
But if it turns out that so much of the random battles
were completely superfluous and you didn't need them, then it sucks.
I've been trying to flee from as many of them as I can.
And it's I think that's the right move.
I still like I can't flee from every battle.
I have to get I have to do enough that like.
I haven't I haven't I haven't hit any difficulty spikes
that I like have not been able to deal with, so it's OK.
I just think.
I just think the game.
Like the game as it exists now, like if you took random battles out,
yeah, you would never get any money and you would never get any chips
and you couldn't beat the bosses and stuff and like I get that.
I think the game would be better if it were just balanced
so that the random battles just weren't there.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, it would make the game shorter and better.
It would be that difficult to have.
Like I've seen other games, even on the GBA,
we're like you have little sprites of enemies moving around.
And if they see you, they'll run towards you or they're running,
they're moving in a pattern.
And if you can get out of the way of the pattern,
God, I wish the the combat.
That's how Mega Man Legends.
Well, Mega Man Legends is an action game.
Yeah, but I mean, you can you can run by the enemies if you want to.
And if you know how to avoid them, yeah,
that would improve the game a lot.
But I, you know, whatever, I just got to deal with it.
Other than that, it's kind of good.
And it's fun and the battles are pretty fun when they're not just
throwing a bunch of bullshit at me.
So, you know, not not an entirely positive experience,
but it's not a completely negative one.
They say they say the games get better
until like the like five and six.
And I think they say like six is terrible.
I don't know what's terrible about that,
but everybody seems to agree that it's bad.
So I think things might get better before they get worse, Lamal.
I don't know.
Is there anything so far that has been an interesting lore bit
when compared with compared with what you know from Wikipedia?
Is there anything like, oh, interesting?
I mean, the most I mean, that network one pretty much just sets up the premise.
And like the interesting thing about the premise is just what I said
in the lecture that like it's it's kind of what I don't know
if I really went into this in the lecture, actually.
But like the fact that like the world is completely different
pretty much just based on what Dr. Light decided to do.
And that's and that's kind of interesting.
And the the.
There there is a big twist that you only find out at the end of the first game.
And it.
I mean, do you want to know what it is?
I could just say it.
Yeah, I probably wouldn't want to play them.
Well, I mean, you find it at the very end.
OK, I mean, you know that like you're this kid
and you have this little personal computer
and everyone's personal computer has a little program inside it.
And your little program is like what
your little battler goes in and like kills viruses.
And like does it's a light world, dark world sort of thing.
But sort of it's it's sort of like everything interacts with computers
and like the computer is sort of just its own sort of separate reality
that like programs live in.
And your guy is a little Mega Man.
You're your little yeah, your little net navi,
your little interface program is a little Mega Man, Mega Man dot exe.
The the twist is you find out at the very end
that actually Mega Man dot exe is like is your dead brother
who your dad like fucking digitized because he was dying.
Yeah, you used to have a brother,
but he died and your dad turned him into a turned him into Mega Man dot exe
to be your little your little internet slave.
It's so fucked.
More like dot executable because he got he was he died.
He was extremely executable. Yeah.
So, you know, that's that's the
that's like the the the premise.
And I don't know.
I don't know if like that.
I don't know how that impacts later games in the series.
I know in this one, it's pretty much just like a last minute twist revelation.
Oh, my God, you're my brother.
What the fuck have my brother is inside a computer?
Get out of there. Get the heck out of there.
And he says, I can't. I'm stuck in the computer.
And you say, no.
Quick, we got to invent 3D printing.
We got to get him out.
If only if only someone would build like a robot body that like a sentient
that like a sentient AI could like inhabit and it could like walk around.
Yeah. Why couldn't they do that?
If only Dr.
Light had started had studied robotics instead of AI.
Oh, fuck.
Um, Lamal.
Yeah, Dr. Light, you could have been could have been like a
or the Boston Dynamics or he could have got into like chat GBT.
Yeah, it's too dark, dark timelines.
Yeah. He he it's like
looked at in the way that like these are like two versions of the same world.
It's it's kind of interesting to think like,
is a net navi essentially like a cyber elf that just like is inside the network
and like has not developed the technology to like
exit the network yet or or is a net navi more like a robot master?
And that is not truly sentient.
Hmm. Well, if it was a real boy before.
What has become of him?
Yeah, turned into a net navi.
It would be pretty it would be if he's if he's merely been cyberized
like a cyber elf, like that's kind of OK.
But if he's been like reduced in his complexity
to be like a non sentient, a not fully sentient robot master, like that's grim.
That's grim, but if he was going to die, then he would be nothing.
Well, yeah.
Well, sure. Yes.
Maybe it may be a little like odd for the brother to be like,
oh, your family.
Yeah, but you're you're like a machine.
You don't have emotions.
I don't know.
I kind of think part of me wants to say that like
if the option if if if like true true like self determination
and sentience is off the table because the technology is just not there.
And like the choice is like either you die or I turn you into a
not entirely sentient like cyberized like quasi humanoid.
I kind of think maybe you should just let him die
because like the alternative is kind of it's it's ghoulish that the like I'm
imagining like a family member comes back as Clippy, Microsoft Clippy.
And I'm like, oh, no, you've got the face of my person.
I know that's soul.
But you but all you could all you can do is is tell me is recommend me
how to like improve my document writing.
And I'm like, this isn't what you're like.
This is fucked up.
Yeah, not real.
Yeah, ghoulish.
That would be a little bit.
I guess, did he know his brother?
No, he didn't even know he had a brother.
They were I think they were like twins or something.
And like one of them like had like a congenital problem
like when they were born and died like pretty much immediately
or was going to die like shortly after childbirth or something like that.
OK, I guess since he didn't know him before,
it's a little less freaky for that person.
But he didn't he didn't know.
But MegaMan.exe did know that he was like your long lost brother
the whole time and just didn't tell you because your dad like programmed him
not to tell you. Oh, you bet that.
That's.
It's sentient, but he can have his brain altered in the net.
I can have like folders of memories digitized,
but reshuffled and deleted.
Actually, I'm not 100 percent sure if he was like programmed not to tell you
or if just like the dad like just asked him not to tell you.
And he said like, OK, I'm not sure which it is.
I I'll have to find out soon.
And, you know, the sequel series to Battle Network Star Force.
Apparently, it takes place about 200 years in the future.
So about at the same time as MegaMan Zero happens
is when the battle network world like goes to space and like aliens are there.
I think that's zero.
Does zero have aliens? Zero does not have aliens.
No, zero is is like in the far future,
X has become or like the copy of X has become the like emperor
of the Neo-Arcadian Empire and is like ruling with like an iron fist.
Oh, yeah, and like fascist dictatorship.
And then there's the anti-reploit.
The the cop, the copy of X has become this fascist dictator
who is persecuting reploids and the real X has become a cyber.
Ralph, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
There's no aliens.
But in no, in in in the battle network timeline,
yeah, there's a sequel series called Star Force, where they go into space.
And I don't really know that much about it other than that.
I know that you like merge with an alien.
And you become and there are wizards.
There are wizards and aliens and I get.
But it's all the same because it's all on the Internet.
You can't tell. But it's but it's all on the Internet, I think.
I think that like the alien, I think that like you and an alien have like your
you each have like an individual
like data self representation that you put into the Internet.
And then you like merge them together into like a a shared being on the Internet.
You know what, I'm this is like half remembered stuff that I don't even know.
So this is I have to I'll have to discover this seven games or nine games from now.
Oh, those games are long as fuck.
Those games are like 30 hours long because they're like fully realized JRPGs on the freaking DS.
Just like bigger than PlayStation games.
So that's a nightmare.
It's going to be one of those games where like, oh, if you want to if you want to get
some secret extra law, you're going to have to fill out the best bestiary.
And yeah, I'm not going to do that and do like a hundred percent completion.
Then you get a sentence from somebody and he says, I'm Dr.
Light is alive and he's here.
Here he is. No, I didn't even I didn't even I didn't a hundred
percent all like Mega Man games like I didn't even play through.
This probably the biggest thing that I didn't do was I didn't play through
Mega Man X for as zero.
I only played through as X and like zero's play through is kind of like the more
canon of the of the two.
You talked about the the different playthroughs, though, right?
In the lecture, I did.
Yeah, I only played one of them.
I mean, gameplay wise, they're mostly the same.
It's just like slightly different bosses and like the dialogue you.
Oh, well, I mean, zero doesn't collect the light capsule upgrades, but like whatever.
I just I mean, I looked up the differences in any of them all.
But but yeah, that game's two different
playthroughs for the two different characters and I only did one and that's
and I kind of did the wrong one zeros is like
because zeros has like Iris, it has it has the famous cutscene
X's X's play that doesn't even have that cutscene.
Ah, so he was just fighting for something without even questioning it.
Yeah, X doesn't even ask at least zero asks what he's fighting for.
X doesn't even ask.
I just love killing.
He just that's the thing about X is that he just loves killing so much.
Mega Man X is a game series about a robot who just loves to kill.
He's highly, highly relatable.
Yeah, so I'm going to be doing that for a while.
You know what I think I'm going to do?
I think if I'm going to keep doing this, I should make like an announcement
video on YouTube and put on my YouTube channel like, hey, guys,
I'd like to make a follow up to the Mega Man lecture about Battle Network,
but I want to play the games first.
So I'm playing them on Twitch.
Follow me on Twitch.
I think that would be a reasonable way to drive
some eyes toward my Twitch channel if I'm going to be doing that.
Yeah, put it up the next time you go live or to, yeah.
Yeah, live when you're live.
It'd be like, oh, got to go right now.
I probably would put it out like.
I would probably say like I'll be I'll be live this Friday or something.
Like I would pronounce in advance, like.
I'll be I'll be doing it like this Friday.
I kind of want to do like maybe a Monday, Wednesday, Friday,
or maybe just like a Monday, Friday kind of schedule with it is something.
I don't. But I also don't want to.
I don't want to commit to a schedule because I hate commitment.
But also, I feel like I should do that if I'm going to announce it.
And if I want to tell people like you can watch me do this
and like here's when you can here's when I'll be doing it, you know,
like that's kind of the point of like announcing it.
Yeah. So I have to.
I was I was going to stream yesterday or I was going to stream on Friday.
I had kind of planned to, but I just didn't feel up to it.
I just didn't want to.
So I didn't because I hadn't really like committed to doing it on a schedule yet.
And I was the problem. Yeah.
It's like I guess not do it.
I like to be able to just not do it if I don't want to.
But also being on a schedule is good and it makes you do things.
Yeah.
And generally doing things is better than not doing them.
Hmm. Well, I don't know.
What if what if you did nothing?
What if you just laid face down?
Yeah, in the dirt. Yeah.
That's what I'm thinking.
That's what I'm like.
Stream that. No.
CCT likes hot wire, a CCTV camera lying the dirt face down.
Ben St is live.
Why are you why you got a why we got a why we got to make content out of everything?
If I want to just lie that face down in the dirt,
I should do it just for my own sake.
But what if you're lying face down in the dirt
and there's a little jingle goes off, somebody donated.
That would be the funniest clip.
Me like face down in the dirt like.
Little thing.
Thank you. Thank you for the follow.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm not going to look and see who followed, but whoever you are.
Thank you. OK, leave me alone.
Yeah.
Feeling I'm feeling a little I'm feeling a little demotivated lately.
Yeah, I'm trying to push.
I'm trying to push myself with stuff like this,
like stuff like I'm going to start streaming again.
I'm going to make I want to start working.
I need to release.
Well, I haven't really started a new lecture yet
because I've still been trying to grind that fucking the book.
OK, not to not to derail myself,
but I must complain again about how seemingly endless
and never ending and impossible.
The task of like satisfactorily putting the stupid fucking index together
is and it feels like I'll never be done.
But that's what I've been doing.
And again, I don't know, I just got to finish it.
And then I want to start working on a new lecture.
I haven't really started another one, even though I need to.
And I've been streaming and stuff.
And it's like, OK, I got to I should probably commit.
I should probably commit to doing that again.
But I feel I feel overwhelmed.
I feel overwhelmed by all of it. There's too many things.
Now, I feel you.
I mean, at least you're doing a little bit of something,
a little bit of indexing.
I'm trying. I'm trying to I'm trying to chip away at stuff.
I felt I was I seriously worked like all last night on it.
And it. I did make progress, but like I look at the whole document
and I'm like, how have I been?
It's literally been like months.
I've literally been doing this shit for months.
And like, how is it not even? It's not even like.
I guess it's getting there, but like it's not.
I wouldn't say it's like almost done.
It's mostly done.
Nevermind.
That's it.
I mean, I felt pretty overwhelmed as well with.
Obligations and projects and like that's a new year, you know.
Yeah, get to work for holidays are over.
Yeah, got to get something done.
Yes, stupid idiot.
Famously, I said that the book that I would have the book done by New Year's
and it's not done.
Yeah, it's just I don't know what if what if nothing happened?
I'm thinking about it more and more and I'm like, you know what?
I don't want to never do anything ever again.
But but it's it's it's it's not.
It's not doing me any favors constantly feeling stressed out
about everything.
So I don't know.
So are you saying you are stressed because of how many things you want to do?
Yeah. Yeah.
Overwhelmed, stressed, you know.
Yeah.
And it's it's it's not a simple like, oh, just do it or oh, just take a break.
Sort of thing, because it's like can't take a break forever on everything.
Yeah. And doing it.
Is just so hard, especially when it's a creative thing and I need to like focus.
Yeah. And it's like I just.
I don't know.
I've just been playing.
Well, I guess I've been I've been binging medical sore.
That's what I've been doing until that's that was finished.
Now that's finished.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm just sort of waking up.
I'm feeling very feeling very numb.
He's telling you what you're doing.
I'll tell you what you're doing.
You know, you're playing inscription again.
You got to finish inscription, Gabe.
You didn't finish inscription.
Oh, but I don't care.
You didn't get to the twists.
There are two.
Oh, what's the twist?
The butler is the one giving me a card.
Like the butler, two T's.
Yes.
Look, it's a good game.
All right. Look, I know it's a good game.
OK, sometimes a good game.
You didn't look all right.
I just you didn't you didn't you didn't you didn't experience.
It's true. It's riches. OK.
It has it has undiscovered riches.
It's hard, Ben.
It requires that I play it and gosh darn it.
I'm a casual and I don't run away from that fact.
In fact, it's my identity.
I identify strongly with casual gamer.
It's not.
I don't like it when it's a game is hard and I lose.
It hurts my soul.
I don't fragments it.
I don't want to go.
Look, OK, look, I know.
I know I'm trying to keep it.
I'm trying to operate.
I'm trying to keep a cool head, but I must.
But I must.
But I must once again say that losing losing is part of the game.
You're supposed to lose it a bunch of times.
And every time you lose it, it gives you more stuff that you can.
That's what they say about real life, but it's false.
No, that that definitely is not that definitely is not true of real life.
Definitely not.
You're supposed to lose and you get nothing.
No, every time you lose in real life, you get worse and worse
and your situation degrades more and more.
Every time you lose, that's the the the the escapist fantasy of inscription
is that every time you lose, you get better and better and you get more stuff.
You know, what I like.
Only it were like that.
I like playing a fucking catamari to mercy.
You know what you do in that?
You roll around and you get bigger and bigger and then you win.
That's a that's understand.
Well, no, you can we can lose.
Honestly, I've lost catamari a lot of times.
I've found it kind of frustrating when I don't I don't get on a roll and I lose.
Oh, no, I'm too good at that game.
And I guess I'm so good at that.
I'm so fucking good at catamari.
I never lose.
I have. Except I I lose on the ones that are like weird missions
where you have to get one bear, like when you're trying to make Ursa major,
you need to get one bear.
And there are lots of things that count as bears or cows.
There's another one about cows.
And if you get like a milk carton that counts.
And so you have to avoid picking up certain things until you're big enough
to pick up like a big cow.
I hate those ones because it I want to collect everything.
Yeah.
But any any normal mission I usually am fine with.
Like I beat those had missions that are like I just can't.
I can't maneuver around.
I'm not finding the places I need to go where like this stuff is just the right
size for me to be, you know, growing.
I mean, yeah, there's some learning curve to to knowing how big you are
and how big where the where to go.
And maneuvering is like what my my big tip to Katamari Demas years
we're having trouble maneuvering is the double tap, like click in L3R3
to jump over to the other side of the ball, which is basically like a 180
without having to slow down.
You just do a 180 and you can easily change your direction completely,
which is very good for zigzagging, picking up things instead of smashing
into something and slowly turning around and then going at it again.
Anyway, Katamari is easy.
It's that's even if you fail, it's just fun clicking, getting getting little bits
getting bigger. Yeah. Yeah.
I played it and I never got like super into it.
Really good.
I think I just like I think I really rented it at some point.
They made a they never sold the original game in the UK.
So I have only played it.
Well, actually, I played it at in America, I think at Red Con 3.
I think we had it.
Is this think Trixie had it?
But then that's on steam.
There's a PhD remake of the first game.
It's great.
Get that one.
Oh, I just remember it.
I'm supposed to be I'm supposed to be on a on a on a draw cast,
like oblivion oblivion falls draw cast this afternoon.
We're really busy Sunday today.
What what's the the theme?
I think he said that the theme is.
If I remember correctly, it's like you're supposed to first you draw
like an an edgy OC like like a do not like a like a do not steal
deviant are edgy OC and then you like swap with someone and you like fix each
other's edgy OC's or I think that's that's like that.
I feel like I did one of those with them.
I remember I remember drawing a shitty OC.
And then I also drew I think Seatull drew like a Ben Saint OC.
And I drew that I think I can't remember.
I have those images in my folder.
Occasionally, I remember like I see them.
I'm like, oh, yeah, that was a weird one.
I don't know if that became a video.
It probably did.
They still have not finished the freaking art telephone.
I hate my drawing for that.
I'm glad it's not out.
I'm glad it will never come out.
Mine was never to see it.
Mine was OK.
I don't know.
I kind of like.
I always like wanted that to happen and then it like has been like a year
and it like has not happened.
I feel like it's time to just cut anyone who has not completed their freaking
drawing for that.
But maybe it's too late.
Bummer.
Anyway, I'm feeling feeling a little bit
feeling a little pressed, even though that's literally not for like six hours.
But you know how it is.
It's like, oh, no, I got to do something six hours from now or I can't do anything.
Yeah.
I can't start anything now.
I don't only have five hours to do it in.
I think.
The last time I was on a draw cast.
Actually, no, they've asked for people.
Just randomly and they usually record like one a.m.
And I'm like, I don't know.
There's a slot for you.
Did somebody help?
I'm like, I don't know.
It's fucking late.
Right.
Time zines.
Well, what else have I been doing this week?
I don't know.
I found a YouTube guy that I like.
He's called the Burger Creek.
And he made. OK.
He's made a bunch of he's made a bunch of lore videos explaining the lore
of World of Darkness.
Do you know what that is?
Is that the
French designer
SNES game?
No, it's not the guy who made something or is it like
it's the is it the one with the Mike Gruber guy, the little egghead man?
Oh, no, you're talking about
another world.
Another world. I think it's in Europe.
It's called another world in America.
I think it's called out of this world or something like that.
And then there was another game by that same guy who did on SNES.
The like black with like shadow hands.
The black shadow hands and then the kid with the little laser gun.
I know what you mean.
I watched Game Grumps play. It was very cool.
I know what you're talking about, but that's not what I am talking about.
World of Darkness is a like it's a set
of like tabletop RPGs that all kind of like work together with each other.
So like they're all kind of set in the same world and they're like compatible with each other.
The main one is is Vampire the Masquerade, where you play as vampires.
But there's like a werewolf one.
There's one about being ghosts.
There's one about being wizards.
There's a couple others, I think.
But anyway, yeah, World of Darkness is this like set of games.
And this guy, the Burger Creek, he's made a bunch of like lower videos explaining the lore of each one.
And he also has made a bunch of like.
Like philosophy, like history videos.
It's stuff that like I have not watched that.
But the funny thing about Burger Creek is that he just looks exactly like a Jesse,
but he's like German.
Oh, that's cool.
Let me let me show you what he looks like.
You can tell me if you agree with me or not.
Like complete with Hawaiian shirt.
No, he does not dress like Jesse.
He just has his face and hair.
Like I'm like, like, look at this, look at this.
Well, yeah, a little bit.
Yeah, his nose is bigger.
It's kind of got the hair.
Kind of got the hair.
Sort of got the beard.
And he's also standing in front of a very close behind bookshelf.
Yes.
I thought he was British at first because he speaks with a British accent.
But I think he's actually German and I think he just learned British English.
Um, he's talking into a sock.
Yeah, he just puts a sock over his microphone for some reason.
It's a pop filter.
Yeah, easy pop filter.
Yeah, it's funny.
He's he's he's got a bunch of he's got a bunch of videos about like masculinity.
But I think he's a leftoid, so it's probably OK.
Don't worry about it.
Uh, it is kind of on candy.
Yeah. Right.
I think it's something about the eyes, the very similar.
The eyes, the hair.
Yeah, I just I just saw this guy in a thumbnail.
And I saw he was he had like a long video talking about vampire clans.
That was like, I think he he used to do videos
like a couple years ago, and I think he like came back to it
like this year and he had a big hit.
But he did like a like a two or three hour video where he explained
all like the lore of all the clans in in Vampire, the masquerade.
And I guess that was like sort of a big hit.
And then he just he just did more of that.
And that's what you do.
That's what you do on the Internet.
You just play the hits.
Duh, I stopped working.
What was that?
No, my brain stopped working.
Oh, yeah, no, it's fine.
I don't know. Yeah, I've been watching like a bunch of this guy's crap.
They did they did a new GDC or GDQ, rather.
That was there was one like last week.
I didn't even realize.
Game's done quietly.
But now, yes, because I didn't hear about it.
But now there's a bunch of new.
There's a new Final Fantasy 7 speedrun that I watched.
That was great.
You know, I never go into those.
I always forget that I can watch speedruns of any game I want.
I have watched a lot.
I don't usually watch them live.
I just watch the VODs.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, oh, oh, a game I like.
I wonder if there's a speedrun.
Well, of course there is.
But is it fun? Is it cool?
Is it interesting?
Often not.
I usually prefer better than like a like a live recorded VOD
of a speedrun from GDQ.
What's the what's better than that is like a commentated speedrun.
Oh, yeah, those are always nice.
Have you seen the ones about Kirby?
Hang on. I've seen ones where there's like a person playing
and another person commentating what's being done
or like the person playing is commentating.
I like those.
There's a yeah, there's a there's a channel called Sample
and he has he has a video with one point one million views
and it's a commentated task of Kirby Super Star Ultra 100 percent
in an hour thirty five.
And that one's really good because like
the movement tech that he uses in the task is like really interesting.
Like the way that he uses different powers in like a weird way
to like squeeze the most movement potential out of them
is like just really just really neat.
I think I've seen a few speedruns of games that I like
or games from childhood games that I know what it's like to play through.
And I often like ratchet and clank.
I don't like watching the speedruns for that for some reason.
And I think it's because there's so many glitches involved
that doesn't feel relatable.
Doesn't feel like playing the game.
It doesn't feel like I'm watching somebody play this game
that I know with extreme precision, precision that I could not achieve.
Now, they're doing glitches and like skipping past areas.
I'm like, but what if you did that area and just did it really well?
I'd like to see that.
But I don't know.
I guess I need need to specify like glitchless or exploitless runs of things.
I mean, I like especially with like old like NES games.
I do like to see when they like do weird shit that glitches the game out.
Like that is fun in its own way.
Oh, yeah.
Like when they scroll the screen in Metroid, you ever seen that?
I haven't I haven't seen, but I think I know what that there.
There's ways that you can like go up too high on the screen
that it like that it like overflows your position
and like scrolls you up from like the bottom and like just puts you on the bottom
of the screen and you can like skip you can skip like through floors and stuff that way.
Or like zips and Mega Man where like there's ways to position yourself inside a wall.
And when you're in a wall, the game tries to deposit you outside of the wall on the right side.
So we just like shoots you like across the whole level.
Sometimes if you're like inside a wall, that's like really long.
Very funny.
Oh, you know, it would be weird.
I don't know how, whether I'd like this or not, but like speed runs of strategy games
like Fire Emblem.
Like those are not just about how quickly you can do it, but like
you have to know the exact right thing to do.
And there's some some maps and some moments that will probably be like random numbers
will determine whether it's a good run or not, whether you get a crit at the right time
or whether they get a crit.
I think I've seen speed runs.
Oh, I think I've seen I saw a speed run of
Final Fantasy Tactics and they were explaining that like
they were using a route that like didn't involve numerology.
Do you know what that is?
Numbers.
Well, there. Well, there's like a shit.
I think there's like a there's like a particular class or there's like a particular NPC
that has like a unique class that has like some like highly random
abilities and there are ways to like there are ways to like cheese the RNG
that make this like a numeral this numerology ability like really strong.
Like you can you can cheese the results to get like things that are like way more
powerful than it's supposed to be or something like that.
But they were like
they had like developed a route that like didn't involve that
because that like trivialized the game or something.
So yeah.
There's no.
I'm trying.
Yeah, game is like games is like strategy involves
or like, I mean, you ever watch Pokemon speed run where they're talking about like
I've seen so many challenge runs and I've seen glitchful speed runs,
but not like yeah, just regular speed runs of a Pokemon game.
They're the way the way they route it so that like
they'll they'll use like one mon and they'll like
like they know they know like which which NPCs have like AI that they can exploit
to like get an opportunity to like use all the like X items that they need
to like steamroll through the rest of the of the party and stuff.
Or like they'll know
like based on their EVs and based on like the moves, power and stuff,
like they'll know exactly like like when they'll be able to out speed
in one shot, everything and they'll like they'll carefully plan their route.
So like they get there at the exact time that they that they can do that without any risk.
It's interesting. Those are like really long, but they're fine.
Now, I watch a lot of speed runs.
Oh, I just remembered like a.
A tactic in Fire Emblem or at least in the Fire Emblem
on GBA that I remember.
I want I remember it's such a weird it's a random number like manipulation tactic.
That you can use to guarantee high stats on a level up.
It was like in which game Fire Emblem 7 on GBA.
I guess on Fire Emblem 8 as well.
It could be other ones like the because when you when you level up,
you gain like a random bonus to a bunch of different stats.
Yeah, you gain random bonuses to a bunch of different stats
and you want like a high role on each one of those stats.
Sometimes you get like plus one to health and that's it.
Sometimes you get plus one to health, speed, strength, skill,
defense and you know, everything.
And what you can do is since again, I don't know why this is the case.
When you play a map, the the numbers that are generated
are like they're set in stone kind of.
You can see what they are by doing some actions
and then load your point by like turning the game off
and then coming back to wherever you were.
And then it's hard to explain.
But like the series of saves saves coming your level up basically.
Yeah, you save like every every action is saved in Fire Emblem.
So if you move a unit, you can't like undo it.
You can't set a load, a point from that map that it's always saved,
which is always a cool part of like if you turned the console off,
it would remember because it's constantly saving,
which is to prevent saves coming.
But because of this, there's a way to check the random numbers
that are about to happen in the game that you're playing
by having a unit, selecting them and then moving their cursor
like a certain number of tiles away in a diagonal direction.
And then the arrow that indicates the path they'll take.
If it's two different potential paths to that one square,
the game will roll a random number to generate which arrow is shown,
whether it's go up and then right or right in an up.
And you can tell
whether it's a high or low number
based on whether it does one or the other.
And then you can write down whether it was a high number or low number.
And if you get like 23 like random numbers later,
you have like a high, a long string of high numbers rolled.
Then, you know, you turn the game off
and then you count up to that number.
You spend those random numbers, you generate them again
with the same arrow method, and then you level up, you kill an enemy,
you level up, and then they use the next set of random numbers
in the list that you already have predetermined.
You already know what they're going to be.
And so you level up and you get like a bunch of random numbers
that you've seen from the future.
I see.
It's it was so complicated when I was young.
I was like, what?
What the fuck?
But I remember spending like hours and hours trying to understand it.
And I think I've worked a couple of times.
It was just so time intensive because you had to like.
When you're ready to level up,
you have to like get into a position where you can kill an enemy and level up
and then do the arrow thing until you get a good string of numbers.
And it could just take forever until that happens.
Weird.
It's very weird.
How do you reset the timer, though?
Like or reset the numbers?
You can you just turn off and turn it on and like,
do you like save scum the numbers, basically?
You you you can leave the map or turn off the console
and it will have saved at that point.
I think the idea is it uses random numbers to generate the arrow,
but it doesn't bother saving after that point.
So like generating those arrow numbers, the game doesn't update.
It doesn't save your state.
So you can return to before you generated those numbers.
And for some reason, those numbers generate the exact same way every time.
Weird, weird.
So it's RNG manipulation.
That's my that's my big trivia about that.
That's fucked up.
How could you let that happen?
Because I was a nerd and I.
Fire Emblem was a very important game to me, but I sucked at it.
I lost so many times.
I was like, how do I become the strongest?
And they said, you do this.
Well, that explains it.
Video games, I watched them.
I've seen I've now seen every every video on Hazel's channel.
You know, Hazel.
Uh, she makes anime videos.
Oh, wait, I think I know all of them.
I never watched their video.
She did because it's because it is anime.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
So some of them are about anime.
Some of them are about like RPGs.
Some of them are about just like lost media in in general, but mostly anime.
Oh, she did one.
This one about the time Tokyo pop made a weeaboo reality show.
That one's really funny.
I'd never heard of that before.
Oh, I watched the one about.
Oh, the the the the the backstory of I can.
The like weird big boob anime by which I hear this one specifically
specifically this big boob anime.
Oh, this one's this one was really good.
Oh, yeah, I love that big boob anime.
No, you don't know you don't.
Was that the one, you know, I think when I was really young,
like 11 or 12 or whatever, I found something like this.
Maybe it was this.
I've seen this character somewhere and it was like, I was like, oh, my God.
Like I typed in boobs on Google and she showed up.
Yeah.
And I learned about it from that.
And I was like, oh, my God, you can watch that.
The funny that was there was a scene where the main character was like,
well, I tripped and I put my hands on the big boobies and that's wish.
That's what happened.
And I was like, I was like, oh, my God, that would be so cool.
It was before I realized this was a stupid trope.
I was like, I wish that could happen to me.
That's so funny and awesome and cool.
The funny OK, the takeaway that I learned from this is like, OK.
This anime exists.
It only exists because.
The guy drew the biggest boobs that had existed in anime up till that time.
That's the only that's like the only interesting thing about it at all.
It is the original manga has it legitimately has like dog shit art
and looks like garbage and the guy can't draw and it's shit.
And also the guy sucks.
And the next manga that he did after this was called like my bride is 12 years old.
But it's just about marrying a fucking grade school.
And there was a big like freaking there was a big freaking
political backlash against it.
Basically, basically Japanese legislation.
Remember when like freaking Joseph Lieberman and whatever?
We're all like, oh, doom is making kids shoot up schools.
Basically, basically Japan did that, but they did it with my bride
is an elementary schooler.
And they said like manga is turning our generation into like weak degenerates
and destroying traditional masculinity.
And you know what, God damn it, they had a freaking point.
They were in this one case.
The grade schooler.
I mean, how many grade schools got married as a result?
Huh, it was stats.
Well, I mean, damn, you got a point there.
But I don't know.
It's very it's very it was very interesting to learn what this freaking guy did.
This freaking big boob anime man.
Wow. Mm hmm.
Japan, huh?
I have watched them.
Oh, I learned something.
She she was using she used like video game level
as like background art in some shots.
And I looked she she she cited like where she got that from.
And it was this thing called let me find it.
Yeah, it was this thing called no clip, the note that no clip website.
And on. Oh, I've seen that.
You've seen. Yeah, I found this from her.
And if you can just go and you can freaking like put a camera anywhere
in like all these like old like PlayStation and Wii and GameCube games.
And you just put them anywhere in like a level in a video game.
And you can like film a little like Zoom shot.
In a video game, I'm looking at Okami.
I'm looking at the Divine Spring and Okami right now.
It looks great. I've also clicked on Okami.
I love it. I think I forget about it every so often.
And I'm like, yeah, what?
How does this work so well?
This is just the map data in a browser.
I'm leaving this frickin this frickin tab open.
I'm leaving this tab open forever.
We can get Fes. I mean, I'm in Cousa village right now.
Oh, I'm looking at Fez.
Oh, yeah. Fez. You can use WASD.
Use WASD Banjo-Kazooie fucking.
I like that they have like some of the models in there just sort of hanging out.
Oh, I was looking at the Jet Set Radio.
They have some of the games they have like textures for objects.
Also, not all of them.
Like Banjo-Kazooie has like little little eggs and some of the enemies.
Do they not have games from the original PlayStation?
I see PlayStation 2.
Maybe they're weirder like map files.
Xbox PC, Xbox PC.
Wait, what was Okami? Experimental.
Was Okami on the Wii?
Yeah.
I guess they just have the Wii version.
But that was on the PlayStation.
It was.
You saw it?
Maybe they can rip it from the Wii better than other things.
I mean, I guess they have a somewhat limited selection here.
Psychonauts.
The one level in Psychonauts that looks like a black velvet painting.
Black velvetopia, black velvetopia.
There we go.
I can zoom in on like on like the far off depictions of places from Del Fino Plaza.
I can see the low poly Del Fino Harbor stuff.
Oh, some of these.
Some of these actually look kind of bad.
Like some of them.
Some of them you look at and like very little of the level is actually textured.
And that's kind of disappointing.
Look at this.
Only so much you can do.
Well, how does it look good in the game if this is what the model looks like?
Like what is this?
Games that from?
It's from Psychonauts.
I'm not familiar.
But I guess there's lots of things that are not like rendering like in Super Mario Sunshine.
There's no heat wave for distant objects, which would obviously obscure stuff.
This is like basic models, textures, lighting sometimes.
Probably not procedurally generated, just sort of like like painted on or pre rendered
lighting shadows and stuff.
Is it like what the hell is this?
Is it like a lot of the like untextured areas?
Is it just like was there would there have just been like a flat texture like behind
like a skybox?
I don't know.
Yo, it's fucking Metroid Prime.
Sometimes there's just like shit floating around.
Look at this.
This weird image that says channel one.
And I don't know what that is.
That could be.
I assume they would have put a gift there or something or some kind of animation animated
texture.
Yeah, I'm not familiar with the game.
I played it a long time ago.
I don't exactly remember.
It could be an animation.
It could be like a video feed, like a camera that shows what's happening in game.
I mean, there definitely was not a yellow checkerboard that says channel one.
Would I have PlayStation 2 here?
I feel like maybe.
Okay.
You ever seen?
There's a Kingdom Hearts.
Yo, there's a I'm going to go to fucking.
Okay.
The Destiny Islands.
There's a there's a channel on YouTube that does this.
It like breaks games and it goes it like goes around in the levels and games.
And I remember I watched a video where it was exploring the levels in like it was Simpsons
hit and run.
And it's like, is that boundary break?
Yes.
Boundary break.
And it's literally like parts of the level just have like flat textures.
And they're like just like hidden inside walls and stuff.
And it like the way that it will do cut scenes is it will literally just like take the in-game
camera and just put it in a place in the 3D level that just shows the image in the form
of like an in-game texture on like a flat plane.
But like that texture is just is just floating somewhere in the level.
And they just move the camera to point at that image and like that's how they show the
image.
Do you know what I mean?
I guess.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
It's I think just because it's easier to move a camera's position that it is to load in
an image to show on screen, they just move the camera to wherever the scene needs to be.
That's why they have like, like, I don't know.
I can't remember if this is actually in Simpsons hit and run.
But like levels would be like just far below.
Like an interior would just be a little like model set that would be below the real level.
Yeah.
There were, I was looking at some of these levels and you know, Kami, I saw there were
some levels that, yeah, like one area will actually have multiple different like areas
in it.
And they're just sort of like separated.
But like it's one map that just has a bunch of these like kind of rooms sort of built
into it.
And they're technically the same area.
You're just like positioned differently inside of them.
And they may or may not even like have any relation to each other in game in context.
Oh my God, I love video games.
I do love video games.
Do you?
Okay.
Do you ever watch?
Do you ever watch any?
Okay.
Well, there's two different things.
Any John Boyce documentaries and or Bobby Broccoli videos.
I think you talked about John Boyce.
He did the baseball stuff.
He does.
He does many sports related documentary type videos.
Okay.
But you, but you haven't, you're not familiar.
No.
You don't know Bobby Broccoli?
Nope.
Okay.
I think it, okay.
I think, I think it was Chip Wiseman that turned me on to this, but I could be misremembering.
But yeah, I noted that like Bobby Broccoli makes videos that are basically the same.
Like he uses the same like format as John Boyce did.
And I noticed that like there's only these two channels that I'm aware of that do this
very particular style of video making wherein they'll have like a graph or they'll have
some sort of a data.
What do you, what do you call it in infographic?
They'll have like, they'll build like a graph or an infographic showing some information.
And what they'll do is they'll have, they'll have, have it in like a 3D space and they'll
kind of swoosh the camera around to show the graph.
And then maybe they'll have like, you know, points appear on the graph and you'll sort
of watch them like animate and like appear and the data will appear and it will, you
know, form some pattern and they'll talk about it.
And yeah, they, they do this thing and they swoosh it around in the 3D environment.
And I mentioned this and someone, and I think it was Chip Wiseman said, yeah, they, Bobby
Broccoli made a video that's just explaining how they do it and the video is called how
to make videos like John Boyce.
So Bobby Broccoli is explicitly like, yes, I stole my method from John Boyce and like
good on him.
You know, I admire the gumption.
And it turns out, and I couldn't fucking believe this, you will never, they actually make the
videos in Google Earth.
Like Google Earth has like video making tools in it.
Well, like, did you, like, did you know that?
Like, like you can set a key frame and a camera move in Google Earth.
Yes.
And you, and you can load 3D models.
You can load 3D models into Google Earth.
I, I assumed the, okay, John Boyce made the first thing I ever saw of him was 17776, which
is that sort of like almost, it's a bit homestuckish, but not really.
It's a comic, but it includes videos and it's set in the future.
And he'll show like a, like a Google Earth landscape, but in Google Earth, he will have
these like, he'll have like fantastical structures and like things that don't exist sort of placed
on top of Google Earth.
And it's like, oh, in the future, this, this thing is here and it's some weird building.
Turns out, and I assumed he was using Google Earth and then like taking Google Earth footage
and putting something into it or putting superimposing an image or maybe loading Google Earth models
into some other thing like Blender or something.
No, you can just straight up load 3D models into Google Earth and then use like fricking
video tools and key frames and stuff in Google Earth to like record in software footage in
Google Earth.
That's what Bobby Broccoli does too.
He just loads Google Earth, turns off the Earth, so it's just in like a black void.
And then he just puts these infographics into the Google Earth software and that's it.
That's the whole method.
And I can't fucking believe because it's so good.
It's like really good.
The result rules.
Yeah.
Why would Google Earth have that built in?
I guess they anticipated that people would want to make videos using it, but like I've
never seen anyone do it other than John Boyce and then Bobby Broccoli.
But they don't, I mean John Boyce will sometimes, he'll use the Earth itself and he'll use it
as like, he'll show a location where he's talking about it.
Bobby doesn't even use the Earth.
He has everything just floating in a void.
And it's just, it's amazing.
It's amazing to me because I'm sure that they did not, I'm sure that the creators of Google
Earth did not intend for it to be used to make documentaries, but they put these video
making tools in it and just because of the way that they built that into it, these documentary
videos became possible to make and John just did that.
Well, what were the, like what did they expect?
Like if they had video making capabilities.
Well, I don't know.
I genuinely don't know.
We're a business and here's our video.
You see, we want to build our new structure on this straight here, swoop.
Maybe.
Look at it with the, it'll add to the skyline.
Maybe it was assumed that like, yeah, using rendered footage from Google Earth would be,
yeah, just useful for like, showing the locations of things or showing like, geographic data.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's maybe the biggest question that leaves me with is why does Google Earth have
this functionality?
Google probably doesn't know.
You could, I mean, you could theoretically just like, just fricking use a screen capture
software to record Google Earth footage.
Does that mean I could put like a little model, like a little punk model in Google Earth and
have her destroy all the buildings?
Bobby Broccoli has a video explaining step by step exactly how to load 3D models into
Google Earth and make videos with them.
So if you can make videos, can you make an interactive something or other?
That would be so cool if you could like make a game, because you can already make.
I mean, you can't like program like game logic into it.
No, but it would be so cool if you could take the Google Maps, like when they do like 3D,
like the little 3D versions of instead of just a flat image, and you can have a little
character run around and jump on them.
That'd be cool.
I mean, you would have to animate it and then load the animation into the into the Earth.
Yeah, it wouldn't be the animation software.
I'm thinking of like somehow getting the data to do that.
Because what's the game that uses, what's it called?
GeoGuessr.
GeoGuessr uses Google Earth data to make its game.
Hmm.
I don't know.
You know GeoGuessr, right?
Sort of.
It's a game where it plops you down in a random Google Street View area and you have to guess
where you are.
And it knows the location, so they have the Google data and they make a game out of it.
I don't know anything about that.
It's fun.
Hmm.
I'm sorry, I'm trying to find this video.
I thought someone linked it to me in the PCP, frickin, in the PCP server.
Kirby Return to Dream Land.
Cookie Country.
Yo.
Yo, what the fuck?
Wait, what?
Kirby Return to Dream Land, two-dimensional game, you know, with a 3D background.
And now you can go into the 3D background.
Return to Dream Land is so beautiful.
I found the video.
Raising Road.
It's called How to Animate in Google Earth Like John Boyce by Bobby Broccoli.
He posted it two years ago.
Well, this is interesting.
The Kirby Return to Dream Land is just the background.
There is no level.
Are you still looking at what's it called, no clip?
Yeah.
Mario Kart.
Oh, I can pretend to Mario Kart.
I'm going so quick.
You can just use WASD and go...
Yeah, WASD and then like right arrow, right mouse button.
Mm-hmm.
Aw.
Bobby says in the comments of these,
it was pointed out to me that the best way to animate scrolling without zoom outs and zoom ins is not actually to use a path.
Paths have weird camera restrictions.
The easier and more versatile method is to just record yourself manually pressing the arrow keys to scroll.
Well, that sounds inconvenient.
Holy shit.
I wouldn't the tool be better, but okay, sure, whatever.
Did you try Pokemon Platinum?
No, I still haven't played it.
No, I mean like in no clip because the entire map, the entire game is one big model.
What?
Hang on.
The entire Sinnoh region or whatever.
I'm flying over it.
Is that on the DS?
Yeah, I think so.
Sinnoh region and underground.
Wow, yeah, there's only two maps.
Let's check it out.
These little Pokemon Sinnohs are so cute.
Oh, it's in 3D.
Yeah.
Oh my god, it actually looks great.
What are these big black beams coming out of a...
Beams?
What is that?
There's these two like black beams emanating from...
Are they like spotlights?
They're coming out of...
Let me get a little image that kind of shows what I'm talking about.
All the trees are slanted in the direction of the camera, that's funny.
This.
And they have like the flat...
Oh, they have the log texture just flatly on the ground underneath.
Oh, because you only see them from up above.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, lol.
Because the tree is just a sprite.
Yeah, the tree can shake, right, in the wind.
Oh my god, they're all tilted.
They're all like a tilted flat sprite floating in the air.
The log is just a flat texture.
Holy shit.
That's so fucking funny.
Amazing.
I love Pokemon now.
That's hilarious.
That's so stupid.
Oh, no, it's great.
The boulders in these pits.
Also a flat angled texture.
Games are just fake.
Games aren't real.
The artifice is disgusting.
They tricked me.
No, I like it.
Because it makes me feel like this is like a little paper.
This is like a big...
You go sound someone's basement, they've made this in paper and cardboard.
Yeah.
And they got their tiny little Pokemon trainer walking through it.
It really does just feel like, yeah, they cut out little paper dolls.
Is there a Mega Man game in here?
Metroid Prime?
If there was, it would probably be on the PlayStation 2.
No.
No, I don't see anyone.
Dang.
No Mega Man 64.
Oh, that would be awesome.
Well, not 64.
Legends is better.
Sure, but like if it's not PlayStation, that's what the only other one would be.
Yeah, 64 would be acceptable.
Ah, well.
Honestly, those would be fun levels to zoom around in.
In no clip.
Get on it, no clipper.
Honestly, yeah.
It's a beloved game from a beloved franchise, so you're just missing out.
Oh, you can't see anything from down below.
Like most of the textures do not draw if you see them from below.
So if you go, it's kind of spooky if you go below it and look up at the map.
Oh, in the Pokemon?
Yeah.
Let me go back to that.
Here, I'll show you what it looks like.
This is what it looks like in, if you're a Diglet.
I thought you were going to say if you're Giratina.
This is what Giratina sees.
Is Giratina of the Void?
Yeah, he's in like the, um, what, he's in like, he lives in like the hell dimension.
Ah, hell.
Distortion world, distortion world.
Hmm.
This is fun.
This is a cool little thing.
Oh my God, I'm zooming around on grand level.
I really wonder what goes into something like this.
Cause like, it's, it, there's no way it's just as simple as getting the file.
You've got to do a lot of stuff to it to make it just work like this.
Like in a browser.
Oh, you mean into building this, this website?
Yeah.
Um, God, yeah.
Like imagine if it was easy, they would probably have like tons of things, but.
Yeah, I mean, you think they have to like, they must have to, they must have to like
build it from like, sort of from scratch, right?
They must have to like take the game parts and like, uh, yeah.
Or there must be some, maybe there's some kind of algorithm for like, reading the game files
to sort of like, generate a sort of basic like map shape and then maybe you might have
to go in and like manually apply textures or something.
Yeah.
It's cause it's like, not, not every game is exactly the same, even among the same console
of how they load in everything.
There's probably like juggling like emulating technology and their own thing.
There's probably tools that will get you like much of the way there that can like read the
data and sort of interpret it into like a level geometry.
But then you, there's probably a lot of like going through it manually and like checking
everything and like if, if something's texture didn't load, right?
You have to like manually replace it.
Oh shit.
I'm going to go to Halo.
I'm going to see if the Halo is, is, is, is real.
I'm going to see if Halo is real.
Big ring.
Yeah.
I've never played a Halo game.
Not even a little bit.
I mean, barely.
I remember playing the campaign on PC of the first Halo game and it was fun.
I liked the aliens.
I liked shooting them.
Yeah.
Well.
But multiplayer, I was never good and I went to a friend's house once and they were playing
multiplayer and I died over and over again.
They were laughing.
Yeah.
They have it.
They play it all the time.
And I'm like, okay, well, yeah, I'm just going to go back to my Game Boy over here.
Yeah.
I'm not, I'm not super good at first person shooters and I often found them kind of frustrating
because I would lose at them.
I know I loaded the wrong map.
I'm still, I'm still zooming around in, in Sinnoh.
It's for, it's pretty fun.
Link in the description, of course.
Everyone should be like swinging, flying around with us.
Yeah.
As they listen.
Hot tip.
Use the mouse wheel.
Pull up your mouse wheel and you will zoom faster using WASD.
What?
Mouse wheel adjusts your camera movement speed.
It's true.
That's fucked.
Yeah.
It's fucked.
How fucking, uh, I see the halo is merely a skybox.
No.
I've broken the illusion.
Is that on Xbox?
I don't know.
PC.
Oh no.
It's on experimental.
Right at the bottom.
Hmm.
Halo.
Wait.
Oh, there.
Why, these are not in, uh, these are not in, in order.
Uh, what'd you mean?
I mean, why is halo at the bottom of, why are they not in alphabet, they're not in alphabetical
order.
What the hell?
What is the, what map are you looking at in halo?
Blood Gulch.
Campaign halo.
This is the first level of, when you land on the halo and you get out and you're like,
oh shit, aliens, get him.
Campaign.
Oh yeah.
I'm tired.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Well, I'm Gibb and take.
I had to wake up a little earlier than I wanted to today.
Do you have any idea what that's like?
Yes.
No, you don't.
If I had my way, I would wake up when I'm asleep.
Never.
You should watch some John Boyce document.
I remember trying to read.
They're so good.
I remember trying to read 1770, 1776.
And I got like little ways into it and I was like, oh cool.
Yeah, I guess I'll read the rest of it later and I never did.
Yeah.
You know, I like 17776, but it is a bit of a, it's a bit of a tough read, I guess.
You kind of have to like really sort of focus.
And the premise was interesting, like a satellite that was just realizing that it was a satellite
communicating with something else that was like really far away.
Yeah, that sounds right.
There was some time stuff like, oh, it's been a long time or like transmissions take a long
time to travel or something.
But then they were talking about baseball and then I died.
You mean football?
Football.
Yeah.
It was one of those spherical games.
For, okay.
Well, I mean a football, an American football is not.
It's not even a sphere.
It is oblong, but you know.
See, that's why I much I know.
Yeah.
What's a, what's a good one?
A good, good John.
Okay.
I mean, it's kind of a long series, but the series about the Atlanta Falcons is pretty
good.
That one's pretty fun.
Interesting.
What's, what's, what's like a short-ish one?
Just like a one-off.
That's really good.
Oh, it's another series, but the story, the story of Dave Steeb is really good.
The story of Dave Steeb was like, I saw a list of like best video essays of like the year
and yeah, the series about Dave Steeb made it on that list.
I think it was a Kotaku list.
There were a couple other videos on that list that I wanted to check out.
There was one where like a guy is giving like a live tour of like a real world bridge, but
he's doing it like in Battlegrounds 3 and like the people he's giving the tour to are like
these other players in like Battlegrounds and they're just like fricking World War 2 soldiers
or whatever.
And he's just leaving them around.
Or maybe not Battlegrounds.
Some armor.
Some war game.
Some like some World War, it might have been a World War 1 game actually.
But he's just leading them around this map in the game and like giving them real world
information about this bridge that has been recreated.
You know what?
Let me, you know what?
Let me just find that video because I didn't get all the way through it.
But I started it and I was like, what the fuck is this?
Like why?
I kind of meant to get further through it because like maybe there would be a point
and I'd go, oh, I see why this exists.
But I like the video or like the bridge.
The video.
Maybe it's just like you want to know some history.
I got a virtual tour.
I got to be honest.
I didn't really, I didn't immediately understand why I should care about this bridge.
Here's the video.
It's on Vimeo of all things.
Actually, you know what?
Here's the, here's that list that I found.
No, it's not Kotaku.
It's Polygon.
These are like 10, 10 video essays.
And yeah, one of them was a John Boyce.
The Captain Ahab, the story of Dave Steeb by Secret Base is on there.
So they must have somewhat decent taste.
Oh, and then they have a Jacob Geller on here and I'm on the record.
I don't like Jacob Geller.
I'm on the record.
I'll put it out there.
The 10 best video essays of 2022.
What a pathetic theme for an article.
You say, I mean, you say that and yet, and yet, I mean, looking through the list, I
was not familiar with most of these channels.
And so I thought maybe, and so I thought maybe I should give them a chance.
I find, even though it's like hypocritical of me, I find the idea of caring about like
video essays like dumb, they dumb.
It's nice and I like them.
So it's really just, it's just like a weird snobby thing I have.
I don't care about them as a medium, but I mean, I don't know if I would even describe
the story of Dave Steeb as an essay.
It's sort of, it's sort of an essay.
It's sort of a documentary, but it's, um, yeah.
I mean, I guess I wouldn't, you couldn't, I wouldn't say you can't call it an essay.
It is one, but there's more to it than, than just that.
And I mean, this, um, deconstructing the bridge seems like it's more of like a lecture than
an essay.
Oh yeah.
University level lecture.
What makes an essay?
Exactly.
I mean, it really just comes down to like, it is a video presentation with probably a
question at the beginning and explanations with evidence or something.
I guess, I guess all it really takes to be an essay is just that like you wrote it and
it's like written.
Yeah.
Like it's meant to convey musings on a point.
And the good essay has a good interesting question that you want to know.
That's why I feel like view source videos are the best video essays because they're like,
I like that.
He's good at speaking and he has nice questions.
Like I don't really give a shit about, uh, a bridge even if it may make me feel smart
to know about it.
Maybe there's a, maybe there's a, what does it say?
Yeah.
It's more of a university level lecture set in the least academic form imagine a session
of battlefield five, uh, within the battlefield five map is a recreation of Dutch city of
Nijmegen, Nijmegen, the site of a decisive battle during World War two.
Total refusal takes viewers on a survey of the area in virtual form and in the process
they delve not just into the history involved, but also the entire concept of war, tourism
and recreations questioning how culture remembers these events.
Maybe it goes somewhere.
Yeah.
I could take or leave a thoughtful topic essay on something.
What do you mean?
I don't find them, like I don't find them to be something I need to spend my time finding
and watching as opposed to like, oh, there's all these cool shows and films and games.
Like I feel like I should get around to those things.
But like video essays are like, hmm.
Yeah.
Sure.
They're a good ones.
Yeah, it's reasonable.
What is it?
What does it say about me?
What does it say about me that I might be more drawn to a medium about discussing things
than I am drawn to actually like watch or experience the things themselves.
Because I hate shows and I hate art.
I think it's not a bad thing to enjoy a video essay.
Like to have, I mean, it's just sort of, it's a more direct than an art piece.
And art pieces like could be anything.
You're to be entertained usually and feelings are elicited.
Like an essay sets out with a goal.
Here's a question and we're going to try and we're going to figure this shit out.
And you're going to learn about it.
And I'm like, well, okay, I can, I can, I'll learn about that.
Yes.
I know exactly what I'm going to get out of this.
And so it's easier to approach maybe.
There must be something wrong with me.
It's just a matter of finding out what.
I mean, I don't watch too much stuff either.
I only watch things that are like everyone's saying, you got to, you got to watch it.
Yeah.
Like eventually I do.
And I'm like, okay, that was good.
I guess, I guess I'm the same way.
It's like, if I, if enough people recommend me, like Ben, you got to watch this thing.
You got to play this thing.
If enough people tell me that, then I'll, then I'll do it.
Oh, speaking of hypocriticalness, the, I finished medical soil and immediately I went for video
essays or like episode analysis of various things.
And I found this guy truly logical.
A logical has really good, like on a higher level than like your generic, like, here's
what we know about this scene.
Yeah.
Like it.
He's, he's a little more clued in.
You can tell he is a little more of a smarty pants about like themes and use of color to
denote theme and stuff.
And, you know, use of shots.
He spends a long time.
Misunseen.
Yeah.
Whatever that you said.
He spends a long time going over certain shots and the usage of those shots and why and the
character bits and is like, ah, yeah, you know, that's why beyond what I would have
brought out of it, but just watching it.
But now that I know the story, I can really appreciate those added details.
And there are some things I did have questions on.
Like some scenes are just a little, a little obtuse.
He breaks them down.
I'm like, oh, yeah, that's so smart that it, it does the thing.
And I get it.
Now I'm smart.
And that's why I like videos.
Very good.
His name is all logical.
All logical with an O at the beginning.
The two L's.
Oh, no.
One L.
Let me just get a random, a random one.
Hmm.
What does the blue flower mean?
Oh my God.
It's a Game of Thrones reference.
Yeah.
It's so, so good.
That's a spoiler for you though.
You shouldn't click on that.
I probably shouldn't click on it.
I should watch better.
I mean, I've watched all of Breaking Bad and most of Better Call Saul, I think.
So I should probably finish it at some point.
Yeah.
I mean, I do like Bob.
Who doesn't like Bob?
Oh yeah.
Everyone loves Bob.
And then the best thing about finishing a show, especially a really good dramatic show,
is that now you can watch all the bloopers without being spoiled.
And you can see the characters that have been so expertly played.
Be a little silly.
Finally.
You see Gus going, wah!
Gus Fring going, woohoo!
And jumping like Mario.
Perfect.
That's just what I want.
That's the only reason you should watch any show, is so you can get invested in a serious character
and then you can see them be a real person in an interview.
You're going to build them up so you can break them down and watch them go, ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
Oh, Jollity and Gaity.
How I missed you.
You slap your head off the forehead and go, oh my God, they were just acting this whole time.
I love that.
Yeah.
Jonathan Banks.
What a sweetie pie.
What a cutie pie.
But in the show.
Jonathan Banks.
Who's that?
Mike Herman Trout.
Oh yeah.
And so he's like, he's a grizzled, like I listen here, Walter.
You're going to take your pants off and you're going to piss right on my face, Walter.
Like that's what he says in the show.
But in reality.
It's the only way to get the poise now.
I got stung by a jellyfish, Walter.
You got to pee on it.
Pea on it, Walter.
And in real life, he's a nice, he's a nice boy.
He doesn't want to get peed on in real life.
Oh, good.
What a relief.
You see, when we were filming that scene, I didn't want piss on me because I don't actually
like that.
But I thought, but I thought, you know, I was going to do it for the part.
But I thought, you know, the, you know, Mike, the character, you know, I thought he would
probably want to get pissed on because like, you know, that's what it would take to like
keep his daughter safe and like his grandson safe.
So he would say piss on me.
So that's what I said in that scene because I was playing the character you see.
He would need to be pissed on.
You see, there's this thing called acting.
You see, it's like playing pretend, but on a, with camera, they film you.
Put it on TV.
It's wild.
My impression of him is morphing into a Sylvester Stallone.
I'm trying to think of, did I, did I, did I experience anything else this week?
No.
Did you have feelings?
Did you have touch and sound the site smell?
I felt depression, despair, despondency, the three D's.
Nuts.
Devastation, disenfranchisement, denouement.
Denouement.
Yeah.
Is that like a, like a French thing, like meaning the end?
Oh no.
The French, the French are ending.
Um.
But they made so much good bread.
Yeah, well, it wasn't enough, unfortunately.
Oh, um, I think tomorrow, I think tomorrow I'll be able to restore, add, add revenue functionality to the channel.
Or if not, or if not tomorrow, shortly thereafter, the nightmare.
The nightmare is almost over.
Um, Lamal, sorry about that.
Uh, it's okay.
Yeah, it was a mistake that I made and I won't make it again.
Cost us like 150 bucks, but I got probably at the 80 bucks out of the, of the account.
So, you know, costs like 90, like seven bucks.
Sorry.
It's all coming out of your.
It's all, it's all coming out of your.
Uh, I don't know.
This week felt really long.
This week felt really long and yet I can't remember anything that happened.
God.
There's a thing with the Scottish parliament trying to get.
Trying to get that gender reform, gender bill through.
And that's good, right?
Scotland is the good guys.
Yes.
They want, they, they realize that the, um, the way to get gender help in, you know, the UK is evil and distressing on purpose.
Yeah.
And, uh, it's, uh, bad.
So they're going, they want to change it.
They want to make it easier.
They want to remove the requirement, uh, for a doctor's note, uh, to determine that you are trans.
You can now self-identify or at least that's what they want.
Was it, was it the thing where like to be like legally change your gender, you have to have like a doctor's note, but like the doctor won't like acknowledge it unless you've already been on hormones for like two years.
But to get on hormones, you have to have a doctor's note saying that you're trans, but the doctor won't say that unless you've been on hormones.
It's not like a criss-cross thing like that.
It's, um, if you want to get on hormones, you need, uh, to be certified trans by a board of people who determine whether you're not you're trans, uh, by interviewing you.
And the waiting, the wait for the interview, uh, takes usually two years, um, sometimes longer.
And it's clear they just don't put the money in to staff it correctly.
They have thousands upon thousands of people waiting.
And so the queue is extremely long.
And the people in there don't seem to give a shit.
And they're horrible and demeaning from, you know, stories I've heard.
And they just, you know, it's very clear that the system doesn't like trans people at all.
What's nothing to do with them.
So what's the Scottish legislation?
They want to cut out all of that bullshit to get a gender recognition certificate.
They just want, they want it to be.
Like in Scotland or would it apply to the UK generally?
It would apply to Scotland, as far as I understand.
But the UK is, was concerned that people would go to Scotland to get a gender recognition certificate.
It can be easier to get one, like to be able to change their gender for stuff and then come back to the UK.
And they'd be like, nah, we can't have this allowed thing.
We can't allow it to happen because it'd be confusing because we won't do that.
We won't recognize that as a legitimate thing.
So like if you're a Scottish national and you get your gender changed and you go to the UK,
they will not recognize it if that were to go through.
So they said, no, we're just going to block it entirely.
And now Scotland is going to have to go to court to fight it.
And it looks like they want to.
And it's a big sort of like thing.
I'm wondering what's going to happen.
I've seen JK Rowling has been like, she seems agitated.
She seems agitated about it.
And the way that you can tell that she's agitated is she's like gone.
The last couple of days, I think she's been like even more so than usual.
Retweeting people with like a thousand followers being like this person wants to commit violence against women.
This person wants to kill women.
Yeah, it's great.
She's a real ghoul.
She's a real demon woman.
It's pretty sick.
And I know she has her claws in the BBC.
I know she has her tendrils all over that place.
BBC is like sort of consistently painting the Scottish Parliament and what's her name?
The important lady at the front of the top of it.
Is it Nicola Sturgeon?
Can't remember.
That's a lady.
Like the leader of the Scottish Parliament.
Nicola?
Nicola.
Nicola Sturgeon, the first minister of Scotland.
Like if Scotland had a prime minister, she would be it basically.
I see, yeah.
Are they going to do separatism?
Are they going to do a secede from the Union?
Is it going to be civil war?
They have wanted to.
Scotland has wanted to be allowed a vote to leave the UK because for such a long time,
they always vote for a left-leaning, good, nice human person stuff.
I did not know that about Scotland.
No, they're cool people up there.
They vote left-leaning.
They're more labour, far more labour than conservative.
And they just want to leave because every election, the majority is always conservative because there are more English people
and most English people are conservative.
I kind of thought Northern UK was more conservative and Southern England was the more urban, liberal centre.
It's actually not so much.
Urban is generally more liberal, but there are lots of urban areas that are extremely exclusive,
upper-class, super-white areas as well.
Ancient areas that only extremely wealthy people and really snobby people go to.
So it's not like the urban environment is integrated smoothly through all the places.
So there are pockets of left-leaning stuff in London and stuff, but there's a lot of conservatives in the South
as well as some parts of the North.
The North has historically been more left-leaning, more labour, worker-focused.
I see.
In America, you look at maps of which districts voted for which presidential candidates.
There are blue states and red states, but if you actually look at it by district,
the blue centres are always clustered around the major cities and the red districts are outside of the major cities.
Blue states are just states that have a bigger urban population,
and 90% of the time that's how it breaks down.
That's the real split.
I would say that's the same in the UK.
It's not like city areas, just adjacent to cities that have lots of mansions in them
and big suburban, rich suburbs, but big house suburbs near London and around London, some in London.
I think I understand.
It's a little bit of this and that, but Scotland has always been not happy with things like Brexit
and other various conservative decisions that are awful and terrible.
This seems to be a linchpin moment.
It seems to be a turning point where if they go to court against the UK,
it could set things in motion for another attempt at seceding from the kingdom.
That'd be so fucking funny.
It would be funny, and honestly, I want that for them because I hate the UK.
The UK, the England part, it sucks.
I mean, frankly, your people need to be punished for their transgressions.
They need to suffer some consequences.
They fucking voted for Brexit, and they're just generally idiots, and I hate them.
If Scotland manages to secede, I'd move.
I'd go to Scotland.
I know it'd be probably difficult because it's moving to a different country is always difficult.
Like, fuck it.
Maybe you should move now before they break officially.
Maybe you could move before they officially announced they had actually left.
I could try.
But then probably once they split, they probably would need new paperwork or something.
You'd be like, you haven't lived in Scotland for that long.
It'd be suddenly like, oh, you're here, but you're a UK citizen,
so now you're going to need a visa or something like that.
Yes, it's always going to be a thing.
But if Scotland secedes and they're their own nation, they'll probably join the European Union,
and they'll be so embarrassing for England.
They will have gender thing, and I'm like, fuck it.
I'm gone.
I'm going to be Scottish now.
Damn.
Yeah.
That's pretty wild if it shakes out like that.
It'll be pretty fucking wild.
And then the Union flag will have no blue in it.
It'll be red and white.
Would you think they'd change the flag?
Because it's the symbol of the countries that are involved.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I mean, I guess, yeah, if Texas seceded from America,
I guess we'd need a new flag with 49 stars on it.
So, LeMalle.
And then it would be so much less cool of a color scheme.
So it would just be the big middle cross and the red X behind it.
It would be the big middle cross with the white outline and then the diagonal X,
the red X with the white outline.
I guess it would just be white.
So it would just be red Xs.
It would just be a red cross and a superimposed on a red X.
Uh-huh.
Hang on, hang on.
I wonder if someone's mocked this up.
UK flag without Scotland.
Oh, my God.
Well, someone has this one, and I think this one includes like whales,
which like whales is like not represented on the flag currently.
No.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
I never really thought about it though.
Because I always assume, you know what?
I don't know what the diagonal X cross is for.
I remember learning about it once.
I know the horizontal big cross in the middle is England
and the blue is Scotland.
Gee, I just don't know what that other one is.
Oh, that one, that second one sucks.
Yeah, they should, it needs the white bars.
It needs the white bars and breaking up the, I mean, here's one that's kind of...
No.
Oh, dear.
I think the first one just without the green is probably the best.
Okay, now I'm curious.
Okay, the Union Jack is the flag and...
Oh, my God, it's complicated.
Fuck.
Vexillology is complicated.
Okay, the flag consists of the Red Cross of St George,
Patron State of England, which also represents whales,
aged in white, superimposed on the salt here of St Patrick, Patron State of Ireland.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, St...
Oh, so it's the Irish part.
So if Northern Ireland leaves, then you would get rid of the diagonal.
Oh.
If Northern Ireland goes back to becoming part of Ireland, then that part would leave
and then it would just be England.
There'd be no kingdom, except Wales, I guess.
Wales is the only one left.
And then it would just be, it would just be, yeah, the Red Cross of England,
but like the bottom two quarters would just be green.
I think the Union Jack came together pretty well in its current state.
I think it looks pretty good.
Yeah, it's three different saints.
St George, St Patrick and St Andrew.
See, look at this.
Wales is not represented in the Union flag by Wales as Patron St David,
because the flag was designed whilst Wales was part of the Kingdom of England.
Wait, it's not, their patron saint isn't St George,
even though they have a freaking dragon on their flag?
No, that's the English one.
St George is like a saint who slayed a dragon and Wales is a guy they like.
They is the dragon.
Oh, fuck.
Your dragon can't be on our flag.
We killed your guy.
That might literally be it.
Here's a suggestion.
Slay the dragon could mean like, oh, we took over this kingdom
and this is the flag we both fly under now.
That's hilarious.
Cucked.
Wales cucked.
Wales, you know, if the dragon was more prominent, it'd be even cooler, I think.
Wales should be the important one.
I have mixed feelings about the dragon.
On the one hand, the dragon is cool and like the old school like design of it is cool.
But also, I kind of feel like busy drawings are kind of weak flag design.
I think that I think they're not very iconic.
I think the Welsh flag is I think the best way that sort of a type of flag has been
because it is iconic.
It's only got a few colors.
Yeah.
And it's like unique in that it has an animal.
It has a depiction of a creature.
No, you're, yeah, you're kind of right.
You're kind of like for that type, I think it's good.
Generally, I feel like if you can if you can have a strong and iconic flag design without
just like fucking draw in a thing on it, I think it's better.
I agree.
But I think the fact that most other flags don't have a dragon or some sort of elaborate
creature on it means that it is allowed to stand out in a way that that is like not because
if everybody drew stuff, it would be very confusing.
The fact that it's the only one means that it's good and it's fine.
I, yeah, I agree.
I agree.
Have I showed you the Massachusetts flag?
I've probably seen it before, but no.
It sucks.
It's dog shit.
I know the New Mexico flag because they show it in medical soul a few times.
The, or wait a minute.
Yeah, it's the the the Massachusetts flag is this weird like shield with a Native American
like brave on it and then the freaking like sword arm.
I don't know if it's meant to crest.
I don't know if it's meant to be like, yeah, we freaking like killed these guys, but it
kind of looks like, yeah, we freaking conquered these dudes.
I think it's actually not meant to mean that, but the sword over them is really grim.
Yeah, like he's about to swing around, chop his head off.
That's what it looks like.
Yeah, that's what it looks like.
There's some like Latin, some Latin phrase or whatever.
This is the sort of thing you would put on like an official document, not like a flag.
I think it's, it's, it's a, this is a crest.
This is not a flag.
No, of course.
Yeah.
But if it counts as the flag of the state.
This, this is the official.
Wall flag of Massachusetts.
Although there is also a.
Yeah, the New Mexico flag is great.
I really like the Maryland flag a lot.
What's the New Mexico flag?
That's like, yeah, that one's pretty good.
It's like the sun because it's hot.
And it's yellow.
It looks like it looks like one of those Japanese like district flags.
Yes.
The you, you have probably seen this because it was flying everywhere at Brony con, but
the Maryland flag is like this.
Oh, and it's a little busy, but like it's really striking.
I think it looks awesome.
Yeah.
The black and yellow makes me think of driver, the video game series.
Crazy taxi.
But the white and red part is like medieval looking.
Yeah.
For sure.
Like nights on bikes.
By jousting on.
Yeah.
I'm trying to.
I'm trying to read up on like why what is like the the symbolism of the
Massachusetts flag meant to represent.
Yeah, we killed all those natives.
The shield is meant to depict an Algonquin native American with bow and arrow.
The arrow is pointed downward signifying peace.
However, the face of the figure is modeled on a photo of Ojibwe chief Thomas little shell.
A white star with five points appears next to the figure's head signifying Massachusetts as a U.S.
state.
Okay.
I mean, it's not like any of the other state flags have a little white star to be like, yeah,
we're one of the stars on the American flag.
Yeah.
A blue ribbon surrounds the shield bearing the state motto.
This is weird.
Above the shield is the state military crest, the bent arm holding a broad sword aloft.
The sword has its blade up to remind that it was through the American Revolution that Liberty was one.
The sword itself is the copy of one belonging to Miles Standish and signifies the philosophy
that one would rather lose their right arm than live under tyranny.
Holy shit.
Pretty cool.
Kind of cool, but there's like a lot of just a lot going on.
Just a lot freaking going on.
What if you did a cosplay as the flag?
I like that would be racist.
No, you dress up as a shield with a blue ribbon around it and you wear it like you have your
hand like holding a sword above your head the whole time.
And you've got a white sheet on underneath.
Sounds a little, I don't know.
I don't know if the message would come across.
Yeah, I mean, I guess the Indian is just there to just be like, yeah, these guys lived here.
It's like, OK.
Chief Thomas Little Shell.
I wonder what his deal was.
Do we like him?
Do we stand Thomas Little Shell?
Let's find out.
Yeah.
Chief of a band of the Ojibwa Chippewa tribe in the second half of the 19th century.
Little Shell attempted to sell his remaining lands for $1 per acre and be allowed to have at least
10 million acres of remaining lands in Montana.
OK, it seems like he refused to negotiate with the United States about seeding more land for
almost another 30 years.
Little Shell refused to negotiate with the United States over land.
Together the Anishinabeg occupied an area.
I mean, OK.
He seems like just he was chief of the tribe at that time and we had relations with him, some amicable and some not.
So neutral, I guess.
So we put his likeness on a shield.
So we put his likeness on a state shield maybe to be like, we respect those guys?
I guess.
I guess you had to be there.
At the time, it made perfect sense at the time.
Yeah.
Yeah, seems like it's...
I think people...
I think there's been a bit of a movement to change the flag, but I don't know if it's like that big of one.
You know, I think some people say that it's a bit of like a, you know, the Washington Redskins situation, but there's a little antiquated.
Yeah, but I don't know if there's like that.
But I just kind of think it's just kind of think it's ugly.
I think it's an ugly flag design.
I'm not sure if I think it's like bad representation or appropriation or whatever.
What would you, what would you as a Massachusetts, what would you have on your flag?
God, I'm the wrong person to ask.
There is like another...
Okay, well, there's a there's a Massachusetts naval ensign that just looks like this.
I don't know if I am super into it.
It's a tree.
Just a pine tree.
Yeah.
We got those all over the place.
There's also, yeah, that was like, well, that was like when we had a state Navy and we don't.
Ooh, the Massachusetts state flag, according to a survey, was the 38th, ranked 38th best flag in America.
So not very, not very high.
Oh, 38th out of 72, which included US state, US territorial and Canadian provincial flags.
So it's mid, it's mid.
I guess it can get worse.
What's that like extremely embarrassing one that looks like Microsoft Paint with like the trees in the river?
Yeah, that wasn't, I don't think that was a state flag.
I think that was like, I know the one you're talking about.
Really bad flag Google.
Immediately.
River G County, Liberia.
Actually, if I can see a picture of the Liberian flag, like a photograph of it in real life.
Oh, no.
No, they only show the, the star and bar part of it.
I'm, I'm learning so much.
Okay.
So, okay.
So there's a flag called the English Red Ensign, which is the civil ensign of the United Kingdom of Great Britain.
And Northern Ireland, it is one of the British ensigns.
What does that mean?
What is a, in British maritime law and custom and ensign is the identifying flag flown to designate a British ship.
Okay.
So.
Just the Liberian G County.
God, what the fuck?
That's not, that's not the one I was thinking of.
It's the one I was thinking of.
Well, there's that one that has like, it has like a freaking like gradient on it.
Yeah, I don't know that one.
Wait, is this?
I'm going to search shitty flags.
There's like, there's, there's versions of this flag.
Some of these are not that bad.
This Liberian flag.
They just look like someone else drew it.
But like, which one is the actual one?
Is it that one?
Oh, this is, I found a list.
I found a list of shitty flags and like, this is dog shit.
Some of these are like good, actually.
This is like, this is like a joke list.
This is garbage.
Okay.
The Liberian flag.
Yeah, I see that one.
What's the one that has the freaking gradient?
It has like a gradient and like a full sentence on it.
Oh, you know, I think I know that one, but yeah, I can't remember it either.
I think it was from somewhere in like Utah or.
It was like anim.
It was like, it was like a city flag.
I can't, I can't find it right away.
All right.
So, so, so check this out, right?
So this is, this is the red, the English red ensign, which you flew to designate that your ship was English.
And then to that, they added this freaking Massachusetts naval sign to make this was like the flag of New England.
They added the freaking Massachusetts tree on it.
So that's flying in the wind.
You can see the red, you see, okay, it's an ensign ship.
And then that tiny little bit of green right in the corner.
And then they, and then they took, they took off, I think this was post-revolution.
They took off the British ensign part and they just made it this and this, and this became the flag of New England.
And okay, look at this shit.
That looks like you had a PNG of a tree, but you didn't know how to cut around the white.
You didn't know how to cut out the white around the tree.
Oh my God.
Wait a second.
You're going to love this.
Okay.
This was, this is the, I'm about to show you the first flag adopted by the state of Massachusetts after independence.
And it's called the pine tree flag.
And it looks like this.
This, this really does look like MS paint.
That's so sad.
An appeal to heaven.
What are they asking for?
I, I don't, I don't quite get it.
Please put us out of our misery.
It's what it seems to be saying.
Please.
Yeah.
A simp emoji.
Heaven, please.
Heaven, please swallow us up.
And then, and then this one's a little better.
Reverse side of the flag of Massachusetts.
The reverse side looked like this.
It's a little better.
It's a little more iconic, but I really, I really don't like that green on blue.
It's very dull.
It is pretty dull.
I think an actual shield like that would be pretty cool, but on a flag, it's like, it's too small.
The colors are too similar to each other.
Yeah.
So I kind of appreciate what they were going for, but I don't know if this really, this one really does it for me.
Is that not symmetrical?
Yeah, it's not.
Yeah.
The tree is not quite symmetrical.
I noticed that too.
It's, it's so annoying to me that like.
Yeah.
Why wouldn't you just make it?
It's not just that it's not symmetrical, but like the top of it seems more jagged and flat.
And then that one part in the bottom left is like really loosey-goosey.
Squeeze.
Yeah.
I, I, I don't understand.
I don't.
This is why they need us up on that crew.
Everybody needs an us up.
If you, if you can, when you get right down to it.
Well, that's a, I like flags.
I like symbols.
Yeah.
And signs.
We should have a flag.
We should have a PCP flag.
Hmm.
The letters PCP drawn and quartered.
No.
Apparently, you know how they, they put the tree, they put the tree in the little window there.
Apparently when you add another symbol onto an existing flag, it's called defacement.
So we defaced the British red ensign with the, the tree of New England.
Good job.
Defacement, parentheses, complimentary.
Oh, you know what we should do?
You know how like we all had in the PCP, like a color association.
Yeah.
I had like that turquoise greeny blue because of my Gibb and takeo scene.
You had like gray or black.
I was usually like black or white.
Yeah.
We should make a flag that's our two colors because we're the only ones left.
You know what?
It's a great idea.
And I mean, I think I'm, I think I'm solidly purple now.
Purple?
I think I've, I think I've, um, what's, what's the word for like, uh, oh, I learned from Burger Creek.
When one vampire like fully drains another and eats them to gain their power and take their domain over.
Um.
Voir.
Diablerize.
I've, I've diablerized Mage and taken over her purple domain and now I'm the purple one.
I see.
Purple and purple, black and white.
I thought you'd be purple, black and green.
Yeah.
But you're green.
So.
Um, I guess so.
I feel like, I feel like, I don't know, it's to be confusing if I'm like one shade of green
and you're another slightly different shade of green.
Uh, true.
Honestly, I don't really use the Gibb and take pony that much.
The color is like a historical color.
I don't really know if I have like a color.
Like thing anymore.
Yeah.
Um, I was, um, you know, I was going through, I was doing the book, the, the, the book, uh,
index like editing formatting and I had, originally I had your text in a couple of relevant messages.
I had it in like red, like red man, but, um, I, I, I eventually like, there was a couple
of like, uh, uh, messages that like a canny had posted and canny is red and I thought
it was bad to have two reds.
So I, I, I made yours, uh, the teal color, but then that was very similar to the bright blue
that I had, uh, Christine's text in.
So then I like changed her blue to a different blue, like a more like mild blue, but then
I had, then I had to go through and like change all of her texts line by line.
Oh, is this why the book's taken so long?
It's, it's, it's, um, a heap of reasons like that.
That's just one in a long list of like little, little things that I'm like, I got to change
a bunch of stuff to make it all fit, make it all fit on as few, on as few pages as possible.
Um, yeah.
So color shit is bad.
I kind of want to design a flag, but I'm kind of, I've never, I've tried to do it before
and I'm like, I don't know, put the colors.
Honestly, you know what?
Fucking there's a shape maybe.
I think it would be cool if we came up with a new PCP symbol to symbolize that it's just
you and me now.
Uh, cause the old one is just the, the gray tombstone version of the old one.
Right.
Yeah.
And that's not cool.
The time for, I feel like the time for that is over.
Um, we'll take submissions.
Yeah.
Got any, got any ideas?
Cause I don't right now.
Uh, not off the top of my head, but if anyone has any ideas and they want to submit one,
I mean, I'll take a look and uh, we'll gladly steal somebody else's work.
It could be a pirate flag.
We could put like skulls and evolved.
I like skulls.
You like skulls.
I guess we both like skulls.
So.
Okay.
Yeah.
Skulls are good.
You know what?
Yeah.
We need them.
We need a Jolly Roger for our, oh shit.
That just, that does remind me.
Did a new one piece chapter come out?
Oh fuck.
I don't think so.
I think one's coming out this week.
Uh, 1072.
Is that the one?
Uh, oh shit.
I, I don't remember.
I read 1072 already.
Oh no, I don't think we talked about this one.
Ah fuck.
The weight of memory.
It's a, I remember reading this, but I forget when I did, but it's, it's got Kuma in it.
Hey, give me a, what website do we use that isn't shit for reading one piece?
TCB scans.
TCB?
Yeah.
TCB.
The coconut brothers.
I assume.
Definitely.
Um.
Yeah.
It's, it's one about Kuma and, and Bonnie.
1071 starts with, that should start with the, like the scientists band.
Wait.
No.
I read, I, okay.
I read this one.
I'll, I'll, if you want to talk about it, I'll have to read it right now.
Uh, well, we'll, we'll save it as like the last thing we talked about before question,
for voice mails.
Okay.
I mean, I feel like we're getting on towards that point.
Yeah.
Shall we do the one piece now then?
I could.
Um, unless you have any more topics.
Uh, I don't know.
Um, not really.
Um, I'm depressed.
My life sucks.
Uh, but what else is new?
No, that's it.
Nah, I'm just gonna throw that out there.
I don't want to follow up that up with anything.
I mean, I'm also depressed, but I've been feeling all right.
It's just sort of, I've been very numb, you know, like I'm thinking about things that
make me sad.
And I'm like, you know what?
I'm not, I'm fuck feelings.
No more.
And then I woke up and I was like, I guess it's just a day.
I don't feel good, but I don't feel bad.
I feel nothing.
And I went through a few days like that and I'm like, this is fine.
Uh, and I just sort of had no response to anything that was happening.
I had no, no reaction to stimulus.
And I'm like, this sucks as well.
Actually, I don't know what to do about it.
Hmm.
I mean, I'm dying.
Yeah.
I'm over here.
I'm just like, um, uh, yeah.
When I say, when I say I'm depressed, I don't mean that I'm like sad constantly.
I just mean I'm, I'm just like, uh, what's the point?
What are we doing?
Yeah.
Same.
Uh, okay.
Well, what else is there really to say about it?
Yeah.
When two depressed people are saved, what's the point?
What is the point?
Yeah.
Hey, you're right.
I guess at that point you just move on.
Yeah.
All right.
So let's read one piece.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm reading.
Genuinely a best reaction.
True.
Okay.
Should I, should I like react as I read or should I just, uh, I've read it already.
So you do whatever you feel like.
Okay.
Yeah.
So 10, 72.
Oh, there's the one piece corner, everybody.
What do you have to say about the, the three scientists on the, the front cover?
Oh, um, oh, that's, um, that's, uh, uh, frickin.
It's Caesar, um, the Sanji's dad.
Judge.
And, uh, is that, did we, we never figured out who the big guy is, right?
I was told it was queen, which made sense to me as queen was, was like.
Um, one of the, you know, it's the scientist engineer, uh, person of.
I guess he's wearing, I guess he is wearing the same pants.
Yeah.
I think it's pretty clear that he's supposed to be queen.
He's just, he wasn't as fat back then.
He really does not.
And he doesn't have any, like he dyed his hair and turned it into like a long ponytail.
Maybe.
But I mean, if that's supposed to be queen, it does not look like the same guy.
Yeah.
It's a little harder to tell compared to the other two.
The other two I can, I can at least tell, but, um, I don't know, what are they doing?
They got a fruit.
They got chemicals.
Mass producing deadly weapons.
Oh yeah.
Queen's got, well, the artist potentially queen, uh, has.
Bottles of secret evil poisons.
Yeah.
And we know queen did that with the disease disease stuff.
George has a weird laser spear and we know he has that weapon.
And then Caesar clown has the devil fruit.
And we know Caesar clown was working with smile to create artificial devil fruits.
So I guess they're, you know, they're in.
They're a little science nerd group and they're chuckling about all the things, all the people
they'll kill with these things.
I'm okay.
So Bonnie just like whacked Vega punk and turned him into a kid and like fruits exploded out
of him.
Uh, fruits or like little jewel bits, little little gummies.
Yeah.
Is that how it usually works with her?
We have not seen her use her powers for anything other than shape shifting or not shape shifting,
but changing her own age.
She turned herself into like a beefy, like muscle monster.
What does she say?
Distorted future.
Like in a potential future, I could have been this and she can somehow do that, which is
pretty cool.
I see.
It's like everything everywhere all at once.
You ever seen that?
Yeah.
It's like she got a future where, uh, wait a minute, where she was a sumo wrestler or
like a regular wrestler where she's jacked.
Is there's, is there's another, um, oh God, is there another thing where like someone
uses like the power of like the potential future to like become like a theoretical alternate
version of them?
Is that the thing someone doesn't like Jojo?
Oh, it could be.
I haven't read Jojo.
That sounds, that sounds familiar.
Someone being like drawing on, drawing on the power of like a potential future version
of myself to do something that that version of me could do.
I don't know.
Well, that's exactly what happens in everything everywhere all at once.
Like the, is it?
Yeah.
Um, but it's not like potential, it's, it's divergent presence.
So like, yeah, that's not exactly what I'm, that's not exactly what I'm thinking of.
That's like when you, when you jump to another version of yourself in it, in another, well,
that's like jumping into a different timeline.
Yeah.
No, no, that's when you, they do that thing to like, to like, no, they like learn a thing
that like that alternate self, you know, because they inhabit the other timelines
mind temporarily.
Yeah.
I only saw that.
I only saw it once.
Right.
Maybe, maybe, I don't know if that's what I'm thinking of, but that is kind of what they
do in that movie, I guess.
Yeah.
I guess this is different in that she is going from the present into a future where she's
jacked.
She doesn't look older though.
So I don't know.
Yeah.
She doesn't look that much older.
Maybe it's like she's, maybe it's like she's seeing an alternate version of herself that's
like two years older, but it's like, what if I spent two years just like getting really
ripped and working out a lot?
Yeah.
This is very funny.
It's actually, it's actually a pretty funny use of that fruit.
Yeah.
And then taking someone's age, it's more powerful than I had considered because I never really
think about jewelry bunny and her devil fruit, the idea of like her changing age.
Yeah.
Kind of seem like a throwaway power.
The ability to change someone else's age, maybe change the age of like a metal thing to make
it rust.
There's lots of potential there.
Yeah.
Isn't that kind of what, wasn't there one of those, a ninja that did something like that?
The one that would make things rot.
Oh yeah.
The ninja would be.
Shinobu.
Yeah.
What did she do?
She had a power that could make things, I don't know if it specifically made them older or
if it just made them like wither and rot.
Now if I type in Shinobu, I get so many other things.
But she ended up, didn't she end up like becoming young again?
Or was that just like in a flashback?
We saw her young version.
Blah blah blah.
What happened?
What happened in that whole fucking arc?
She's such a small part of it.
Too many fucking things.
Yeah.
Relationships, blah blah blah.
Abilities and powers.
Njutsu, marksmanship, Delafruit.
The juku juku juku no mi gives her the ability to make anything she touches rapidly mature.
So yeah, like rotting, like getting older, but really quick.
I think it's like she calls it maturing, but everyone else calls it like rotting.
Yeah.
What was the name of the fruit?
Juku juku.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Well, there must be a translation.
Not in the little bit of Wikipedia I'm looking at.
I'll look it up on the wiki.
The juku juku no mi.
Further information.
Okay.
It seems like it just means mature.
Juku comes from jukusura, which means too mature.
Its English name is ripe, isn't it?
Okay.
She could turn grape juice into alcohol.
She can use this power to physically age living beings, although they do not mature mentally.
Oh yeah.
So she turned a little boy, Momonosuke, into an adult.
That's a big important thing.
I forgot all about that.
But hers is permanent and Jullery and Bonnie's is temporary, right?
Yeah.
Well fucked up.
Like if she got her hands on something, just makes them really old.
They can't do anything anymore.
So Jullery, Bonnie turned a punk into a tiny old baby.
Yeah.
He's gotten a little further.
I think he's got like Kuma's memories there in like the paw paw orb.
I'm reading.
I promise Kupa, Kuma, that I will keep his secret from you no matter what.
Power can take something intangible like pain and give it a physical form.
Not only that, but what is fucking up with the paw paw fruit?
The paw paw fruit is freaking stupid.
It's, I mean, it's pretty fine.
Not complaining, but like why the fuck can it do all these things?
You know, it's probably some sort of pun with paw and I don't get it.
Yeah.
Like what is about a bear's paw that can do any of these things?
I guess it pushes really hard.
Pushes it so hard that it pushes feelings out of you, pushes memories.
So I'm wondering if that same logic could be applied to other nervous signals.
To determine whether things like imagination and memories have massive volume as well.
So you want me to pull out my memories and show you.
Please, it will help me advance science.
Okay.
I see.
Whoa.
There's nothing, nothing there but pain, he says.
Okay.
So Kuma, holy shit.
So Kuma took out his own memories and they're in this orb.
He's a crazy robot now, but his memories are there so he could theoretically become his old self maybe.
He could.
Maybe.
But right now he's like climbing the red line and he's getting shot at.
And they said that he was able to, didn't they say that he was allowed to give himself like one directive?
Like they would, they would program him one command that like he got to choose himself.
Yeah.
And he was to protect the, the, the sunny.
The sunny go.
Yeah.
Okay.
Holy shit.
All right.
I'm fucking, I don't know what's happening but I'm, I'm excited.
For one brief moment, I forget about the misery and tedium of my actual life and I inhabit the world of the blue, of the, of the red line.
It's glorious.
One glorious moment.
It's like I'm there.
Okay.
Reading.
The seraphim.
Two against seven.
Yeah.
So the seraphim are up there.
They have, have the CP zero taking control of the seraphim because they got rid of.
Sentomaro.
Sentomaro is, is down still presumed dead.
I think they got him or at least knocked him out.
He's bleeding.
But Vega punk still has authority.
So if a Vega punk is in like hearing range of the seraphim, they will obey Vega punk instead.
And I assume all the different Vega punks count as Vega punk.
Yeah.
As we're hiring, we can turn, he says we can turn the seraphim back to our sides since we're hiring the command hierarchy.
That's assuming we get in there to holler our orders at them.
Okay.
So they should be able to turn the seraphim back.
And Sanji and Frankie are going to fight as well.
Gonna be a brawl.
Why does Frankie call Sanji swirl of him?
What's the joke?
I think Sanji, they're talking about seraphim over and over and then he says Nami's orders are absolute for mere of him.
Yeah.
Okay.
So they're riffing on it.
Fair enough.
Oh my god, it's Kaku. I love Kaku.
Kaku. Oh yeah, Brooke doesn't know them.
He's never met them.
Yeah, that was before.
The guys before.
They fought him in water, was it at water seven?
And he's lobby.
Okay.
Which is directly after and then directly before a thriller bark.
Wait, are you sure?
Didn't they fight CP nine at water seven when they found Frankie?
Yeah, no, they did, but like it was very brief.
They fought like Bruno.
And then they all got on the train and then everyone was, Luffy was like stuck between the chimney and the Aqualagano was coming.
It was like the big wave.
And they got on the train and they left with Robin.
Sanji saw them.
And Sanji got on the train.
And then everyone else, I want to stop, I think it was also on the train or something.
And then the rest of them got on the puffing Tom Frankie edition.
And they followed.
And then like they, they, they, yeah.
And then they, I think they caught up to them.
And it was a whole bunch of stuff on the train.
And then they got to Annie's lobby, which they only managed to fight CP nine.
CP nine after they got over the, like the drawbridge into the other island.
The other, you know, the castle at the end.
Hmm.
Okay.
All right.
I remember it very vividly because I love that fucking arc.
Kaku looks freaking.
Kaku's awakened.
Zoan is pretty cool.
Uh, who me?
I'm just putting him to sleep.
Wait, did she just, she just bit, she's bite Kaku drink his little giraffe blood.
It's a little giraffe blood.
Yeah.
Clone of miss, clone of miss Buckingham.
Stussy of the rocks pirates.
What?
Mads first successful clone.
Unit zero one.
Stussy.
Oh, oh, okay.
It's Stussy.
Do we know Stussy?
Does that, should I, should I recognize that name?
Stussy is the person that this lady has been the whole time, but we didn't know she was a clone.
Yeah.
Okay.
She's like a freaking vampire.
She's like a freaking succubus vampire.
Yeah.
This is, this is a revelation.
This is a weirdo thing.
So like,
Definitely weirdo shit going on here.
So this is so much.
All right.
So she is a clone of a rocks pirates member, which was.
And that's, that's the, that's with the, with the, the other, the emperors, um, big mom and, uh,
Keido.
And I think white beard was on the crew at some point as well.
Yeah.
Sounds right.
They're like, and I forget the, the captain of the rocks pirates, very important guy that we've only heard of in like brief mention and, and stuff.
Uh, but yeah, rocks pirates, very important pirate crew.
She's a clone and MADS first successful clone.
And as far as I understand MADS being the science like group that we're seeing in the, in the.
MADS was on that ship, right?
It was on, it was that, that, that like little boat with all the stuff.
Yeah.
That ship that had, that had all the scientists at Vega punk had, um, uh,
George Caesar clown and potentially queen.
Yeah.
And that guy with like the glasses and like the, the, the, the streaks in his hair.
So they're like, they made a clone of one of the strongest pirate crews ever and she's it.
So I don't know whether this means that, um, Miss Buckingham Stussy was a vampire devil fruit user.
Or they gave her.
Or they gave her vampire power.
Yeah.
And, you know, that's one thing.
This has got to be like a vampire bat zone.
Right.
Yeah.
Probably something like that.
But like that's a whole lot of stuff.
But then on top of that, she is betraying CP zero.
And now Kaku and Luchi look like they're going to be like, they're the ones who need saving at this point.
Because the seraphim, they might like, I don't think they are going to follow.
They're going to follow.
They're also going to follow until Vega punk is there, whoever has the controller.
And I think she had it.
Yeah.
She, well, she's part of, I think all the CPO.
Have it.
Okay.
Maybe it's not a single item.
I.
Yeah.
I think it's just any anyone in CPO has like a command.
Shit.
That was my understanding at least.
So they might just like equally obey both of them.
Or maybe she's got it.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But yeah, this is like, like what is her deal?
If she's with Mads and Vega punk was on Mads.
Is she aligning with Vega punk?
Is this like a sneaky?
Yeah, maybe.
And like, how long does this con go?
Because she, she is in like, she is in the highest level of assassins.
It's like, I'm really intrigued.
I'm really intrigued by the freaking Paw Paw memory orb.
Yeah.
Freakin legitimately, Kuma has done some like light Yagami, like remove my own memories of
Death Note.
Shit.
What has he got in there?
What does he, what does he want to forget?
Maybe he lost in a video game.
I mean, it seems like it's just all his memories.
But like, why specifically?
Like in this flashback, it looks like it's like a nothing in particular.
Like, oh, it would help me advance science if you let me take your memories out of your
head.
That'd be so cool.
And he's like, that's far too personal.
But like, I guess he ended up doing it because Bonnie recognizes it as a memory thing.
It's okay.
He must know something.
He knows something really important that that Vega punk wanted to learn about.
And I guess it's, I still don't know why he wanted to become a robot.
But I guess he was like, all right, take my memories out.
So when you make me a robot, I can like come back for them later.
I mean, it's got to be some shit about like the void century, right?
He must know some ponyglyph shit, some secret government stuff.
You know, there's a potential here for like a fake out like Lunarian secrets.
There's a potential here for this to have been like a Vega punk, like prank bro.
Like Kuma didn't do any of this of his own volition.
Vega punk just really wanted the science.
And so he tricked him and he doesn't want Bonnie to find that out.
So he says, don't touch it.
Please don't touch it.
I did it.
But she's going to find out.
She's going to know.
And then she's going to kill him.
She's going to really, really hate him.
But it's probably more serious than that.
Given the weight of Kuma and like what he's doing right now with his buddy.
He's, he's just climbing red line.
So he's going to marry.
He's going to marriage war, right?
He's going to marriage war for some reason.
I don't know why he can't like poor, poor fruit his way up to the top.
Yeah.
That's I don't know.
Maybe it doesn't work like that.
Maybe it only goes horizontally, but like it doesn't.
It goes up as well.
Maybe it's exactly it's exactly like building up horizontal speed in Mario when you want
to go to a parallel dimension.
You can only.
Yeah.
You can only move horizontally building a vertical speed is like a whole different
thing.
Ah, did you?
All right.
This is there are vertical parallel universes in Mary 64 as well.
Yes.
I was aware.
And they're like different.
You have to get stuck under something and falling and then fall down onto one.
Yeah.
So I mean, I guess I don't have that much more to say about this other than I sure am
intrigued by all these mysteries.
I like the bit where jewelry is like throwing Vega punk when he's a child version and he
calls it child abuse.
Yeah.
She just.
She just punched out all these little little frickin little what do you call them little
Mike and Ike's.
What are those?
You know those little like hard candies that are in the shape of fruits?
A little fruit.
I don't know.
All right.
Gummy winegums hard candy in the shape of fruits.
They're not gummies.
They're like.
Oh, Runtz.
I think they're called Runtz or rascals or nitwits.
I guess they have a bunch of different names.
The years just turned into these.
I just noticed the one panel where they see Kuma climbing and it's like, look, Kuma's
trying to climb the red line.
There's no way he'll make it all the way to the top.
Impossible.
It's just something funny about that.
There's no like like first panel, little meme guy eating cereal.
There's no way he'll make it all the way to the top.
And then he does and he spits out the cereal.
That's what I'm imagining.
Wait, why is he eating cereal?
You know the meme where the little guys eat cereal?
It's like, there's no way.
He will never reach the top of the red line.
Yeah.
Next panel.
No, I got you.
Yeah.
I don't know, man.
I kind of think he's going to probably do it.
I kind of think Kuma is capable of such a thing.
They got all those marines with like mortar bombs and bazookas and sniper rifles.
They're shooting at him.
Oh, yeah.
He'll be fine.
This is just like in Drum Island when Luffy climbed up the fucking thing.
This is just like in Dragon Ball when Goku climbed up the tower.
The Karin Tower?
Is that what I don't remember what it was called?
I can't remember.
I think it was Karin or Karin or something because it's the name of the cat at the top.
The one that made me really mad because when he gets to the top, the cat says like, he
says like, oh, you've gotten stronger.
You've gotten faster and you've increased your endurance.
So you see, you've tripled your strength and it's like that math doesn't make any fucking
sense.
Just because you just because you increased three things does not mean you tripled it.
You fucking moron.
He's just a cat.
He doesn't know.
He doesn't even know basic math.
Yeah.
All that guy's good for is that bean shit.
He's got that good shit.
That is all he's good for.
That is genuinely all he's good for is his bean shit.
He's on his bean shit.
He's in his bean arc.
I hope he stays that way.
Hey, one piece freaking ruled again and I have a feeling the next one will rule also.
I love egghead.
I love egghead arc.
Oh, yeah.
It's hits after hits.
Bunny did do the thing that I talked about oil breakdown.
She touched something.
I guess it was plastic and turned it back into oil.
So that it's crumbled.
It fell to pieces.
I think that's what that implies.
I wonder if it will turn back into plastic later because she says the power is temporary.
Yeah.
Whereas didn't the ninja turn something into oil?
Why do I have the weird memory of that she turned a dinosaur carcass into oil or something by aging it millennia?
That probably didn't happen.
Who?
The ninja with the ripe, ripe fruit.
Oh, a dinosaur into oil?
No, there's no way.
No, I probably had it.
Maybe they made a joke about her doing something like that?
Maybe.
I mean, the only dinosaurs were people and nobody died.
Nobody was turned into fucking oil.
Am I crazy?
Did she threaten to turn Queen's bones into oil like a dinosaur would be?
That sounds pretty fucking cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Or some other dino, man.
God damn.
One piece is better than ever.
How do they do it?
Somebody on this page, somebody on this page down in the comments posted this always relevant meme from Bakuman.
Every fucking week.
Oh God, fuck another banger.
Damn it.
How does he just keep churning out the hits?
So fucking Kaku is just defeated.
Like as far as we know, like he's out called and she just bit him.
Yeah, seems like he just got owned.
She put him to sleep.
And then look, she's like, oh, oh, no, I'm so outnumbered.
I'm sweating.
I can't believe the vampire was evil.
Did they know she was a vampire?
I don't think we've ever seen her do anything like that.
We haven't seen her do anything, so they might have known.
It was already a revelation that this lady was there at all.
No, no, like the first time you see her, she's like, oh, she's an underground kingpin of some sort of business at Big Mom's, the wedding for pudding and Sanji.
Right, right, right.
It's so hard to remember.
And she's like, oh yes, I'm evil.
That's why I was invited.
But then she goes off and does something sneaky and she's like, actually, I'm a secret agent.
I don't know whether she mentions she's in CP Zero at that point, but now she is in CP Zero, but now she's also a clone, actually, of a famous pirate.
Yeah, that's about the size of it.
There's a lot going on with Stussy.
So like there's going to be the Seraphim and Zoro, Brooke, Sanji, Frankie, Luchi, Kaku, and Stussy in this area, and something's going to happen.
And also the warships are coming and also the Admiral.
The warships are coming.
Yeah, I kind of think maybe you're right, and Vegapunk is going to betray them and he's evil, because like things are going a little too well.
I mean, it's just, I don't know.
Why is a clone of the Rocks Pirates even here?
And if it's Madd's first successful clone, who's to say that she's aligned with Madd's?
Maybe she's just being the new Rocks Pirates.
She could be the Primordial Seraphim.
Like she's a clone of a famous pirate.
Just like the Seraphim are clones of the Warlords, but she doesn't have green blood.
She has normal blood.
It doesn't look like she's got green blood.
But she doesn't have a thing.
She does not seem to have a green blood armlet.
Who knows?
At this point, it's just too mysterious.
And then in my mind still is the knowledge that nearby this island, Garp, is going on a rescue mission to save Kobe from Blackbeard.
Oh, right.
And the reason...
Is that nearby?
I don't, I remember that that is happening.
I believe there was some...
Yeah, like Helmapo said, we're close by to Egghead.
Why don't we just get the Seraphim to go save Kobe?
You know, that's what Helmapo mentioned.
So they could go here to get a Seraphim.
Maybe they'll turn up.
I feel like Grandpa Garp's in trouble.
Oh, what's going on?
There's a lot of shit happening.
A lot of shit happening.
But it is happening.
What I mean, I don't know.
It still feels like it's moving fast.
Oh, yeah.
That is great.
Yeah.
Damn.
Well, another successful one-piece chapter in the bag.
You think we should do voicemails?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
So I'll be back in a second, then we'll do that.
Okay, I'm back.
And I got ice cream.
From the toilet?
Yeah.
Delicious.
Okay.
Our first voicemail is called Krabrawler.
Oh, wait.
If you would be so kind to include a time stamp
for when the one-piece discussion begins and ends,
I think some viewers might appreciate that.
So if you would please stop setting the show notes.
Thank you.
Okay.
First voicemail is called Krabrawler.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, what are your thoughts on Krabrawler?
I've been playing a lot of Pokemon lately.
Boy, howdy.
Let me tell you.
I love Krabrawler.
It's okay.
Oh, yeah.
It's not as cool.
There's like a crab.
There's a new crab.
There's a new crab in Scarlet Violet.
This guy's from Sun and Moon, I think.
Yeah, I remember him.
I remember having him in Sun and Moon.
Okay.
I think Obama...
Is it Obama crab?
Krabomable.
Krabomable is not that good.
Like Fighting Ice is not a great type combo.
And like his stats are okay.
So I kind of don't...
Don't really care for Krabrawler.
Krabomable.
There's not much to recommend him, honestly.
He's... yeah.
I think when it comes to like Sun and Moon Pokemon,
he's like pretty alright.
He's okay.
He's got little funny punchy gloves.
And I guess like a slick back hairdo that is pincers.
He's got like...
I think he's got like a Sylvester Stallone, like one eye.
Like a lazy eye.
I think that's what that's supposed to be.
Yeah, yeah. Boxer.
Or like he's got one black eye or something? Yeah.
He's fine.
Yeah. No real complaints.
I always find like Kingler is the coolest crab they ever made.
Yeah.
That might have a lot to do with the episode of the Pokemon anime
where Krabby turns into a Kingler and saves the day.
The new crab from Scarlet Violet is okay.
Whatever he's called.
Crabbitch.
Yes.
Much, much better.
Okay, that's all I have to say about that.
Next one is Am I Right? 3, 2, 1, go.
What are you saying?
Do you remember that political take you had 30 years ago?
Do you want to discuss about it when you said...
Yeah.
He's right.
It do be like that.
Okay, next one.
Next one is called...
Oh, well, there's an image, but there's also a voicemail.
Let's listen to that first.
3, 2, 1, go.
I've been clicking through random on the RFCK borough looking at art
and I simply need to ask,
what did Gibbon take mean by this?
As a Dutch person, I'm very disturbed.
Wait a minute.
I didn't do this.
I did.
I made Green Man.
That's my original character is Green Man.
But I don't remember.
I don't think I put this thing behind him.
It must be listed as artist Gibbon take because it has your character.
Yeah, like that is original artwork.
Of Green Man.
You'll have to ask someone else why they put them in the Netherlands.
Okay.
Mystery solved.
I remember...
Let me get the original image of Green Man.
Because Green Man is like Green in terms of save the trees,
save the environment.
Is it 2020?
Yeah.
Do you have all your drawings organized by date?
By year.
So yeah, like 2020 folder.
I go back in there.
Don't use toilet paper, save the trees.
Save the trees.
Looks amazing.
I have no idea.
This doesn't answer why he's in the Netherlands.
Maybe they don't use toilet paper over there.
Yeah, I think that's probably true.
Almost definitely.
I'm satisfied.
Next one.
A couple more images.
Let's check them out.
I used to think my life was a cringe compilation until I realized it's actually a try not to laugh challenge.
That's pretty good.
Um...
Yep.
Next one.
Let's fucking look at it.
Let's look at it.
Let us look.
Uh-oh.
Oh god.
Hi, few things to start off with.
Yes, I add you because you're a Pegasus to reviewer.
Tis an awesome thing to see.
I'm Phantom Horn.
Don't be intimidated, but I'm not a stereotypical guy like my brother.
Anything.
I'll be the one in the kitchen.
Jenny Knit sent us so many subscribers.
Wow.
She's overflowed.
Why is that her icon in the Sonic hat?
This is what the internet was like back in the Brony days.
We were still using AIM.
Is that AIM?
I think it's AIM.
There was me back in the day.
So much potential.
Before I squandered it.
I'll be the one in the kitchen.
If I was a lady, that's what I would want to hear.
But you wouldn't be in the kitchen.
That would be effeminate of you.
That was before I had my hard MRA turn.
Yeah, this is what I would have said back then.
That's what I mean.
Now I know that you should never go in the kitchen.
Period.
Because there's rats in there.
They ate my tortillas, by the way.
I accidentally left a package of tortillas out in the counter.
And I came back and it was ripped open and rats had eaten it.
Can you imagine how fucked up that is?
Do you have any fucking concept?
I had a little bit of a concept.
Did they climb up to the counter?
They must have been on the counter.
Gross.
Gotta spray that.
Gotta spray it down.
Yeah, I can't eat anything that's been in contact with the counter.
Alright, next one is a Vokeroo.
3, 2, 1, go.
Guys, listen.
Planks are totally worthless and I don't care.
You just do this unpaid job.
Then you'll have nothing to complain about.
I don't get it.
Do this unpaid job.
And then he whips us.
Slavery.
You know, I don't really remember what we were talking about.
So, I don't know what the take was.
Exactly, but I get it.
Slavery.
Very good.
Alright, next one is...
An egg woman.
Let's see.
As a woman.
I can get away with murder.
True.
True. That's why my egg cracked.
I saw Frisco. She said, I'll do evil things.
And I'm like, I love that.
I want to do that.
Love that for you.
Next one.
Wrestling Battle Royale.
3, 2, 1, go.
You probably won't ever play.
Just look.
I rumble verse the game.
It's the most fun normie shit there is.
I feel like he's recommended this before.
Maybe not.
Rumble verse.
Free to play Brawler Battle Royale.
Yeah, Battle Royale.
You know, I've never played a Battle Royale.
I think I've said this before.
I like the idea of them.
I think the idea of last man standing multiplayer.
Deathmatches are fun.
They are.
It's just the fact that.
In a, you know, like mathematically you join a game.
And there are a bunch of people.
And only one person, like a handful of people get to experience the intense stress and exhilaration of being one of the last few and trying to be the last one.
But most people die instantly or die really quickly and they just have to wait for a long time or leave.
Well.
And like statistically, you're going to have a lot of games where nothing happens and then you have to load another match and it's a lot of waiting.
And I don't like that.
But if you die, doesn't it just like put you in a new game somewhere else?
You don't have to like wait for the old game to conclude, I hope.
No, no.
But like if you're doing a bunch of matches.
Well, yeah.
But I mean, if you die fast, at least it's over soon.
At least it's over quickly.
Yeah, so still don't feel like good.
I'm not good at these sorts of games.
I mean, obviously it's better to win.
I like games.
I like multiplayer games where you can respawn and like it's like a back and forth like team versus team struggle.
So like if you're losing, it's not instant death.
It's not the end of the world.
You can come back.
You can make a comeback in a game like this.
You just have to play perfectly until you win.
And then I don't know.
I mean, it's kind of like it's a little bit like a roguelike.
You know, that's why I hate it.
You start and you go and it's like, OK, this run, maybe you'll do good.
Maybe you do bad, but sometimes you have a good run and then you win and you're like, yes.
Yes.
Honestly, I get it.
That's probably why I dislike it.
But I haven't really played games like this.
TF2 is the best multiplayer game ever.
Well, you can add me because I can defend myself.
OK.
All right.
I got you.
I hear you.
All right.
Next one.
Another image.
Gold.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't have a name.
It's just an image.
Oh, what is this?
The procrastinator is dating Sim, but there is the Sims.
Sloth.
I don't know what Asidia even is.
OK.
Tom Sloth.
Yeah, maybe.
Munchy Lust.
I'm not sure about that one.
Nate Pride.
Yeah.
Trixie Gluttony.
Yeah, I could see.
I see the case for it.
Ben Wrath.
Yep.
Flattering.
Davoo Envy.
I'm not sure.
Maybe.
Jesse Vainglory.
First of all, that's not a...
I guess so.
Seven deadly sins and they're trying to like turn it to nine people.
What is Asidia?
I've never heard that word before.
I typed it in.
It's like Asidia has been variously defined as a state of listlessness or torpor or not
caring or not being concerned with one's position or condition in the world.
So like sloth, but like a little more specific.
Yeah.
Dictionary.com says it's spiritual or mental sloth apathy.
So.
Yeah.
And then Mage letting others speak over you and bitching about it later, but never just
speaking up, fuck.
I mean, yeah, the worst crime imaginable.
Straight to hell.
No, no, no chance at salvation for that one.
Who's Wrath?
Where's Wrath?
Me.
Oh, you.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
What's the seventh one?
Uh.
Is Vainglory and Asidia like neither of those are?
None of them are greed.
Greed.
Yeah.
Where's that?
There's no greed.
And I mean, technically greed is split into, well, I mean, in Dante's Inferno, in the Purgatorio,
greed comes in two forms, parsimony and prodigality.
One is like extreme spending and the other is extreme hoarding.
So you could have split that into two, but instead we got Asidia and Vainglory.
Um, I mean, good, good vocab words.
Did you, did you learn those?
Did Mr. Willaker teach you those in your high school lit class?
You fucking hack.
No, they Googled it.
Yeah.
They typed in thesaurus.com.
That's what I would do.
They typed in, they typed in Asidia to find out what it means.
And they were like, yeah, I'll call, give that.
Uh, okay.
Pretty funny.
All right.
I had a laugh.
I had a little laugh.
Uh, next one is called What You Think About That, huh?
Three, two, one, go.
She said, past the weed, bitch.
I don't like to pass the gas.
Slowin' bubble, blowin' zaza.
She got big old titties.
I said, Goo Goo.
Goo guy got it a zoo.
Monkey ass niggas.
Ooh, ooh, I'm playing with me.
When the money talking, I cannot hear what you're saying to me.
Little bitches.
Uh, what do I think?
Uh, you know.
I think it's time.
Guys be farting.
I think it's time to toke that fucking blunt.
It's time to fucking smoke up and escape this world.
Escape this cycle of, of yearning and dissatisfaction.
We've got to escape the Dharma and achieve Nirvana.
It's time to free myself from the shackles of this mortal coil.
But first I'll have another scoop of ice cream.
Was that your like, like, was that like, uh, your like,
your like, rep rebuttal?
No.
Put a beat on that.
That was just Buddhism.
Nah, there was a beat there.
There were some bars in that.
All right.
Damn.
It's only because you rhymed Nirvana with something.
With Dharma?
Yeah.
I think that's just because a lot of those words just kind of,
kind of have this end in the same vowel sound.
That's the secret.
That's the secret of rap.
Find those vowel sounds.
You know, you know, the thing about rap is that it's not really a creative medium
because all you're doing is rhyming words,
but like the words already rhymed, right?
Like it's not like you invented those words and made them right.
No, you just found them.
They were already there.
You just found them and put them together.
You're not really making anything.
You know, you know, and, and, and when you get right down to it,
you know, baristas, they don't even actually make coffee, right?
They don't even actually make coffee.
They just serve it.
Okay.
They're not actually doing anything.
They're just enriching.
They're just enriching the billionaires.
They got.
We should kill them.
They got that acedia.
Acedia.
Acidic.
They got pure acedia.
They put, they put, they've put citric acedia all over their freaking cheerios.
They're putting citric acedia all over the cheerios of society.
You know, you know exactly what I'm saying.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
The cheerios of society.
Yes.
Thank you.
That's what I'm saying.
In meaning that like society could be normal, regular, or it could have honey all over it.
Or, you know, I learned something.
I learned that the state drink of Rhode Island is coffee milk.
Coffee milk.
Like, like not coffee with milk.
No.
Coffee milk.
Coffee milk is, it's, I mean, you know, you put chocolate syrup in your milk to make a
chocolate milk, right?
Yeah.
Well, they have a similar thing, but it's coffee flavored.
Um.
Is that not a latte?
Well, no, you don't really get hot.
Cold latte.
Well, what is a latte?
It's an espresso with a lot of milk.
No.
You pretty, listen, there's no actual coffee.
It's coffee.
It's coffee derived, coffee flavored syrup that you put it in milk to flavor your milk.
How can you be coffee flavored without it having coffee in it?
I mean, it's probably, it probably has coffee in it, but it's like a syrup.
It's a syrup.
It's a sugar syrup that's, that's flavored with coffee.
And you put it in your milk and it's not a latte.
It's coffee milk.
And, um, uh, there's a brand.
There's a brand of this stuff called Autocrat.
The brand is called Autocrat and it's from Rhode Island.
And it's the state drink of Rhode Island.
And, uh, you could put it on anything.
Can you believe that?
I guess I can now.
Can you fucking believe that?
Wait, what were we talking about?
Um, wrap.
Let's move on.
Wait.
I swear I had a point.
A seed oil.
The honey.
Citric acid.
Honey.
Cheerios.
Put it on your cheerio.
That's a fuck.
Let's, okay.
Next one.
Next one is called Did You Miss Me?
Did I download that last one?
Yeah, I did.
Did you miss me?
Three, two, one, go.
Oh no.
God.
It's farting.
I stopped it.
The guy's just playing the record button when he's on the toilet.
I don't think we need to play this, but yeah, it's just, it's the sound of shitting.
It's the sound of shitting.
Have you stopped?
No, I'm still playing.
We don't have to, don't actually play it.
I did listen to the whole thing just to confirm that it's just the sounds of shitting.
My Christ-like sacrifice.
I have taken it upon myself.
I have taken it on the chin, so our audience doesn't have to.
I saw a tweet the other day that was like, it was an old tweet, screenshot it.
And the screenshot to tweet was like, we should just pin all the debt that everybody has.
We should pin everybody's debt on one guy and then kill him.
And the response was like, this is Christianity.
This is literally just what Christianity is.
Yeah.
And it's true.
Pretty good.
Okay, next one is called Two Mean for No Reason.
Three, two, one, go.
Thoughts on the YouTube comments of these?
Did you understand that?
No, but I think somebody was too mean for no reason.
Thoughts on the YouTube comments of these?
The YouTube comments of these?
Maybe the guy feels the people being mean about him.
I felt like there was voicemails about him.
Did people comment?
All right, next one.
I need other people to appreciate how bad this video is.
Three, two, one, go.
Remember Nate's Mickle video from way back when?
I do because back when it came out, you know, obviously it was trying to communicate some
very simple ideas in an overly complex babble that just goes in one ear and out the other.
But when I recognized that, I was like, okay, well, I don't remember any of the arguments
he even said.
So let me go back and try to parse what he's actually saying to figure out if there's any
worthwhile meaning in this whatsoever.
And when I did, I realized that the video isn't just bad.
It doesn't work on any level.
He constantly introduces terminology under one definition and then later in the video
just contradicts that completely or otherwise misuses terms.
The whole point of the video is that he's making this math formula to represent these
ideas that he has, but he visualizes, you know, this is how the graph would change
in these different contexts.
But if you plug in the numbers from those contexts, the graph doesn't change like that.
So it doesn't have the relationship he's describing.
Why even bother with the graph?
And then he has a second graph that he says is different, but it's the same thing.
It's just the same formula with different letters.
Every time I think of this, I have to obsess over it for a while because it just drives
me insane.
It is.
It's like staring into the abyss to the point that I'm like, I attempted to make my own
video response, breaking down all of the ways that Mikkel is ridiculous.
But I can't justify the time.
So instead of making a voicemail.
Exactly.
And I'm not saying this to be like, you should be an attack dog and attack Nate, but I would
be interested to hear someone point out like, here is just a list of the things that are
wrong.
I would be interested.
Ice.
Here's what's wrong with it.
I have similarly had like, I watched it the first time.
It's like, huh?
Huh?
Like I didn't get it.
It's sort of like incomprehensible in a really like compelling way.
Like I want to figure it out.
I want to figure out this, this, this, these words, these, these hieroglyphs.
I don't think I watched the entire video, but I remember the equation.
And okay, I don't exactly remember what you mean about like he introduces a new equation
and it doesn't have the relationship.
I'm not exactly sure how that goes down, but I remember thinking that like all the, all
the, the graph really is, is just like anything that like Adam toxic, Adam tautically approaches
asymptotically approaches a point.
Like it's, like it's not hard to come up with a formula that asymptotically approaches a,
a discreet value.
And you could do that any number of ways.
And there's nothing really very remarkable about it.
Like that's, like that's all he's describing is that a, is that a value asymptotically approaches
a predefined value and cannot exceed it.
And that's just, and that's just the, and that's just the 80 20 rule.
It's just, that's just, you know, the first it's, it's multiple layers of weird beyond
that because like the value that it can't get higher than is like game quality, which
is not a value you can, you can even like measure or like cap.
It's not measurable.
I mean, you can assign it a value, a subjective value, like if the game is good, you can say.
But like it's a graph that can't be finished because like you, how could you ever say that
you found like the most quality something can have and then plot everything in, you know,
the gaming sphere on that graph.
It just feels like a, it's like not useful for anything.
It's pretty weird.
It's pretty weird to like correlate like technology with quality like, like, like that like technology
somehow determines like the highest possible level of quality as though, as though we didn't
all lose our fucking minds and say that Undertale was the best game ever made when it's like
some fucking RPG maker shit.
You know?
Yeah.
Kind of just a weird premise.
The weirdest part.
A weird premise and like the attempt to like justify it mathematically.
Yeah.
I would say just kind of doesn't, doesn't really do anything.
It's, it's just the, the, the most like memorable part of it for me is that it was meant to
like launch a series of merch off of the idea and it's like the most poorly thought out
formula as well as I don't know.
It's crazy.
I would, I would like, I would also like a video explaining.
I, I, I say this with love, but I would watch a video that like point by point explained
why Mikkel is nonsense.
Yep.
Um, um, the, the, I think if you were doing, if you were doing Mikkel Apologia, well not,
not really Mikkel Apologia, but like Apologia for that video and especially for like the,
the, the, the sort of campaign that preceded it, I think you could maybe call it satire
in that, okay, hang on.
Mikkel is about like technology and like the level of quality that like technology makes
possible.
It's not really about hype, but like the, the, the lead up to it, does it, is it about
hype also?
Isn't it sort of about how like hype can never truly reflect the game's quality?
Because technology limits quality in a way that hype does not respect or reflect or something.
Another complication is that the video is about multiple different gaming, like topics
and opinions he has, um, that are not related, but are nonetheless under the Mikkel umbrella.
Like they don't, they don't have anything to do with one another.
I, I think, I feel like I remember that in some portion of the video, he is talking about
hype culture and, and hype, and on that level, I feel like the, the, uh, like the, the campaign
ahead of time could be taken as satire because he sort of was doing like a hype campaign
for a video about hype.
Only that's not really, that's not really the main thing that the video is about.
No.
Uh, yeah.
So it's a bit, yeah, it's a little-
That feel when sometimes video games don't do what you like.
I almost dropped my empty ice cream tub.
You know, uh, I, you know, there, there is, there is a lot to unpack in that video, honestly.
There really is.
Honestly, not the worst idea.
Someone make a video dissecting it.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I, I would, I would watch it.
Same.
Um, the, the next one is, uh, it says, Nate, is that you?
And it's a, an image.
What is this?
Oh, it's a, it's an AI generated version of an image that already exists.
Well, it's the, it's that, um, that like sad Wojak.
The sad, like doomer Wojak.
The sad doomer gray defeated Wojak with the prompt, my beautiful wife who loves me.
Haha.
And it just became long-haired Nate.
Long-haired female Nate.
Right.
Like biting her lip.
It looks like.
Yes.
I think so.
The teeth are a little weird.
Uh, AI is not good at teeth.
AI is not good at a lot of things.
Yeah.
But, uh.
This is a very odd hairstyle actually.
Now I'm looking at it.
Like that one strand pushes back.
Weird.
The rest sits behind the ear.
Teeth, teeth in particular.
Like if an AI, if an AI makes a face and something is wrong about it, it's usually the teeth.
Like especially if it has like a mouth, it's like its mouth is open.
A lot of the time I see like there's multiple rows of teeth.
Oh yeah.
I can't exactly tell where the teeth end and the mouth begins.
Yeah.
Or whatever.
Teeth and fingers.
Definitely.
Yeah.
Teeth and fingers.
And uh.
Yeah.
Um.
Don't.
It says don't link to it.
NSFW.
The next one is an image.
So maybe you won't.
I just got text under the thing.
You'll want to click on the link.
We'll have to read this.
In Ben's stream today in Mega Man, the water was hacked and undrinkable.
But Ben St. wasn't worried.
Okay.
Vinny is obsessed with me like drinking sweat off of Celestia's huge wobbly ass.
Vinny will not stop.
He just won't stop.
That's it.
I mean.
Looks pretty good.
Looks like a nice full glass right there.
I don't want to contribute anymore to this campaign.
When Ben was playing Mega Man Battle Nightmare, Ben St. had a Princess Celestia's big fat
wobbling ass sweat to drink when there was no other liquid he could consume.
Ben St. couldn't help but let it slip in front of his impressionable young new ball streaming
audience, one of his most darkest desires in life.
Did you say that, Ben?
Is this true?
I say a lot of things.
Gotta go to-
I say a lot of fucked up things when I'm streaming.
Gotta go to twitch.tv slash-
There's only one way to find out.
Is it Ben St. on Twitch?
No, it's St. Comics.
St. Comics.
Or is it?
I think it's-
Yeah, St. Comics with an X.
That's right.
I've themed the whole channel.
I've themed my whole channel.
I made a new banner.
I've made thumbnails for the episodes.
It's all Battle Network.
It's Battle Network all the way down from now until the end of time.
Wow.
Yeah.
Next one is Crooked Beetles.
OK Hand.
3, 2, 1.
Go.
Search for Crooked Beetles.
On TikTok, whatever.
The best thing the community ever did.
It looks like my little pony things.
What are these?
That's just some sort of pony meme stuff.
With comics, with art done.
OK, I mean-
Looks like it could be funny.
It doesn't seem like my sort of thing.
OK.
I've still watched two of them and they've been amusing.
All right.
Next one is Vokeroo.
Let's freaking go.
All right.
3, 2, 1.
Go.
I did it.
I am enabled.
I am loved.
Everybody likes me.
We're best friends already, right?
We're hanging out.
Bad and Gib.
Yeah.
But actually, at this point, I think you recognized me already,
but I have something I need to confess.
It's really hard to say, but...
Haha, just kidding.
No.
It was me, Oblivion, fall the whole time.
Oh, you fell for it.
Oh, you're so gullible.
You're so gullible.
I don't believe it.
I believe this is there in Cahoots.
It kind of been Oblivion Fall just far away from the mic doing an exit,
and it kind of been.
It must have been two different people.
I don't think Oblivion Fall would lie.
I think-
No, I feel like Oblivion Fall is the ultimate liar.
No, you're right, though.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
Well, I didn't see that coming.
There's no way all the voicemails are a whole module news.
There's no way there's all the same guy.
There's different people, I swear.
They're all different people.
He's been doing a bit this whole time for years.
Every single viewer is the same.
It's all Oblivion Fall.
I believe it.
I believe Oblivion-
He just spams the refresh button to give every one of our videos like a thousand views now
just to give up the illusion that anyone is still listening.
Just to keep us trapped in our little fishbowl for him to tap on.
Next one is called A.I. Ramblings.
Three, two, one, go.
I find A.I. generated images very fascinating.
The thing is, you know, the A.I. struggles with generating hands
and if you're in a dream and you look at your hands,
then they look fucked up and I'm not making this up.
They look fucked up.
And the thing is, right?
Get away from the microphone.
The A.I. is similar to my unconscious brain.
It's dreaming. The A.I. is dreaming.
This is a common comparison.
Does that say that the A.I. is unconscious?
It's like an unconscious mind.
It doesn't have a soul or something.
That's kind of a crazy idea.
What are you talking about?
You know how you don't remember your dreaming when you wake up?
What if when you're a child, you're just dreaming.
You're in a dream before your soul comes into your body
at a certain age and then you wake up
and you don't remember your dream anymore.
Kind of a crazy notion.
But I find it really weird that I was able to talk
many years before I could actually remember what I said.
Like, why the hell was I fully conscious and intelligent
before I was able to form memories?
What the fuck?
That is kind of interesting.
The idea that you may have been dreaming
before you came out of the womb, but you forgot it.
Even after that, I don't remember when I was like one, two...
No, yeah.
I don't really have memories until I was maybe like four or so.
And yet you probably had input.
Yeah.
But I mean, there's lots of times in my life that I was conscious
but I don't remember them.
I don't remember my whole life.
No, yeah.
If you get drunk and you black out and you don't remember the next day,
were you dreaming?
Were you just dreaming?
That's why it's really important to use recording technology
to record babies and drunk people so they remember it.
And you can show them later.
Yeah, this is when you were so young
that you didn't know how to fucking not cry, you idiot.
I'm going to blackmail you with this.
I'm going to show everyone that you used to cry when you were a baby
and you used to throw up and you didn't even say you were sorry.
You're such a rude baby.
You didn't even pay rent.
You got to pay it back at some point.
Do you have to pay rent while you're in the womb?
Do you count?
Do you have to do that?
Could you be charged rent while in the womb?
You could charge anyone anything you want.
It's like Calvin's dad.
Calvin's dad says like,
there's one stripper he tells him that it costs like $10,000 to raise a kid to adulthood
and that's a lot of money.
He says, like, is that a gift or is that a loan, Calvin?
It's like, that's kind of fucked up.
Yeah.
Calvin's dad.
Calvin's dad is usually cool, but he's got a bunch of boomerisms.
He's got a bunch of like shitty, like reactionary boomerisms.
His shovel the walk, like labor builds character thing sucks.
His like, should I make you pay back what it cost to raise you, Calvin?
Like that sucks.
This was an investment and I expect to return.
Yes, exactly.
What was I talking about?
Is the AI dreaming?
I don't know.
AI is dumb.
AI couldn't beat me in a punching match.
I've never noticed.
I've never noticed my hands looking weird in a dream,
but I guess I've never really like tried to like carefully examine them.
I mean, AIs do, like, yeah, they do kind of look like a dream
because it's sort of like, sort of makes sense when you look at it,
but then when you try to examine the details, it's like, wait,
what is that?
Wait, this doesn't make any sense.
Yeah.
I have enjoyed like the technology like in its infancy being like fucking weird
but still recognizable kind of like a really blurry image of a bunch of stuff on a table
that all looks like it's fine until you recognize that nothing is a real object that you would ever see.
Did you see those images of like people partying that were AI generated?
No.
There were some, I think it was like last week, there was a set of images going around
and someone posted them like, AI generation is getting really good.
They posted it like, it's really good.
Like, these aren't, these are not even real people, believe it or not.
And it was like pictures, I mean, I'll find them.
I'll find them.
There was that one website that was like, it purported to completely generate a fake human using AI,
but then it came out later that they were only sort of like changing like an entirely real photo of a person
but just changing some small aspect of it.
Okay.
I saw that thread and like, I thought it was a hoax.
I thought the person who was posting those images and saying like,
this is basically just like, it was like they were faking it.
It wasn't, or I saw at least one thread where like, it wasn't actually doing that.
I don't know.
I mean, they had like, they had the AI generated version and then the image it was based on and it was very, very similar.
It was like the AI had not really taken aspects of the face.
They've taken like almost the entire face.
So it's like technically AI generated using input, but like, it was more successful because it was using such huge amount like percentages of images rather than mixing and matching.
Yeah.
I have seen some that like, they come out and you can kind of be like, well, this mostly just copied another image.
Anyway, yeah, it was these, it was these pictures.
Say I'm like, oh, AI is getting so good.
And like, yeah, they do look like photographs when you look at them until you like, I mean, look at the teeth.
Look at the teeth and look at the fingers.
And it's really scary.
It's really uncanny.
Like you can, it looks like a picture, but you can tell there's something wrong.
And it's only when you like start to look for what it is that's wrong, you know, you start to, it starts to get really like uncomfortable.
The second one is just like a hand floating in air.
I just noticed that.
Like with a bit of a thumb, like hovering next to it.
Yeah.
Ew, that's disgusting.
That is, that is the most disgusting part is that these are teenagers and they're partying.
True.
Yeah, you know, I, it seems weird.
The first one you posted and then I click on it and it's like, wow, that is a fucked up looking face.
Look at those teeth.
They just keep going.
Yeah.
Yeah, they just keep going.
The other floating hands.
She has, she has Michael Jackson, like surgery face energy.
Honestly, I wonder if the, I wonder if that thread was, was like, they deliberately picked pictures that were like a little bit wrong.
And because I feel like you could, if you really wanted to make it look like the technology is really good, you could find some that like did look almost like undistinguishable from a real photograph.
You could cherry pick some if you really wanted to.
They must have known that these don't look quite right.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, like these pictures.
All of them, all of them have something noticeably wrong with them.
Maybe they're, they're just being like really, really generous and saying, oh, that's getting so good.
Like there's only like seven extra fingers.
Maybe.
Yeah, it's, it's, it's hard to know.
There's a lot of people who want to be very generous to AI technology because they stand to profit off it.
I have, I have seen people talking about it that just clearly have like no sense of aesthetics and no sense, no, like feeling of like when something looks good or not.
But.
That's human story being the case that like the point of this thread is that it's meant to get generated engagement by you say that it's good.
But then the examples you give are like, it's not that it's not really that hard to see that this lady holding the camera has like nine fingers.
And that one with the two guys, they look like they got the big slicked hair.
I like the, the twisted Bop it looking thing on the table.
Yeah, I, I don't know what that is.
It looks weirdly in focus compared to the out of focus bottles right behind it.
And that, yeah, that cup is like floating that cup is clearly not on the table.
Oh, yeah.
If you look at the background, it's funny, like there's a door.
And right next to it, there's another door kind of and then.
Yeah, there's two doors right next to it.
And there's a really flat, weird door with a dark on the other wall.
Yeah, it looks like it's around a corner or something.
The doors are fun.
Um, anyway, yeah, this is, this is what I was talking about.
Like it's bad, it's bad at fingers, it's bad at teeth.
And something about just the face to the eyes are like the eyes and the skin is like a little too focused, but I don't know.
Some, some bits are fine because like in real life, like if it's in shadow, if somebody's eyes are in shadow because of an overhead light.
You can't see what their face looks like properly anyway.
So like, yeah, like AI can make certain parts of images look sort of like they are real.
It's just not, not that great.
I mean, on that first picture, the girl on the far right looks pretty much fine.
No way.
Looks, yeah, like a couple of, like.
Oh, her neck.
Fine.
Yeah, yeah.
Then something's, it's like she has two, she has two, I don't know what you call it.
Colour bones.
The little like divot in between the clavicles where the two like neck tendons connect.
She's got two shoulders.
She's got two of them.
She's got two right colour bones and two right shoulders.
You just can't see him.
And her dress just doesn't, it just keeps going down.
Oh, no, you're looking at the one on the left.
Or no, are you looking at the one on the right?
On the right.
Because they're both kind of fucked up in the clavicle regions.
Yeah.
Intriguing.
On the phone or whatever is being held on the left.
It's just a finger with two like ends.
Yeah, yeah.
A finger with two.
Yeah, that one.
That's this guy.
Those fingers are like really.
Fucking four dimensional hands.
It's like, it's just like those creatures, the crawl knee in the, what do you call it?
Frickin, to save her.
Jennifer Diane writes, pastel defender heliotrope.
And the other one.
The ones that are like higher dimensional beings.
And so like parts of them like don't even connect to each other.
They're just kind of like floating like blobs.
Because like they connect through like a different dimension.
Yeah.
It's like part, it's like a little portion of it is just peeking out into the third dimension.
And that's the like disconnected bit of that, that fricking hand that most of a hand and piece of a thumb just floating in the void there.
Yeah, okay.
So anyway, the next one is called circumcision.
My least favorite topic.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, I'm sorry to leave another voicemail like this, but concerning circumcision.
Yeah, please get away from the mic.
You're too close.
On some circumcisions, they take all of the foreskin and other ones, they just kind of fold it back.
It's pretty disgusting, but um, yeah, in theory, if you like stretched it out, right, like twice as the skin, like twice as normal length.
Or it's modified length, I guess it's not normal.
You could have like the foreskin covering the penis again.
Or at least what's left of it, which would be better, I guess.
I saw this great presentation by Eric Klopper.
I think his name is about circumcision.
I don't know, changed my mind on a couple of things.
Well, haven't seen it, haven't heard about it.
I guess, I guess it makes sense that like, I mean, but if the circumcision left some foreskin, then like, why do you need to like, I mean, you just still have some foreskin.
You don't need to like stretch it, it's still there.
Once they, you know, tasted the bit of the sun, you know, they got a taste for it, they need more.
I don't know the expression.
I guess.
Was it like Icarus, you flap your toes, gets that sun, gets that tan.
I don't even know what happens.
What?
What do you think the story of Icarus is about?
What do you think they were trying to do?
They were trying to get to the sun, I don't know.
They're trying to fly really high.
They were trying to escape from an island.
No, I remember, I remember.
I think Icarus and his dad were trapped on an island where they tried to fly away from it.
They were trying to, they were trying to escape and they thought the only way out was through the air.
They made wings out of birds feathers and wax.
Yes.
And they flew, but then he was like, oh, this is great.
I'm going to fly to really high because I'm so cool.
I'm rainbow dash and then he got too close.
The Greeks didn't even know that like he doesn't get hotter when you go up in the sky.
Yeah.
Why do they think the birds are not like cooked when they come down?
They're close to the sun.
You can close to the sun because hot up there.
The sun's warm.
It makes sense, but they just didn't know.
They didn't understand.
Maybe they didn't bring candles on mountain expeditions in case they melted.
And that's why we don't talk about them anymore today because they were outdated.
Those Greeks, frankly, they're stupid.
They were so stupid and so embarrassing.
Nobody likes them.
Here's another Imgur link for you.
It's not loading in the chat, but.
I see it.
That's okay.
Ah, the Amazonian cat head, great on a toast.
See, the trick to these things is.
Oh, it's the dream.
It's the dream someone had.
Oh, from last episode.
Did someone have a dream that I got bit by a snake?
Like a cat-eared snake.
Great on a toast.
I mean, some people eat snake, I guess.
That's me.
Whenever I see any animal, I think that look, that would be delicious.
That thing looks tasty.
Get over here.
You little creature.
See the trick to these things.
Hubris.
I love it.
Exactly.
Can't get enough.
That's pretty good.
I got what I deserved.
Next one is called My Head Cannon.
Three, two, one, go.
Babe, babe, I'm sorry, but you can't come over for a while, okay?
The thing is, I don't know if you saw, but that guy, he gave me a really evil eye when
we were cooking together.
I get the feeling he's like the school shooter type that never got the chance to do it.
I feel like he's going to hurt me if he thinks I'm not a sigma male.
I think I got to show that I cook on my own as well.
Then I'll just pretend that I cook for myself all the time, and then he won't hurt me.
Then you can come back, okay?
Okay, babe, thanks.
Sorry.
Damn, that's true.
I can't believe.
That's right.
I can't believe I fell for it.
I can't believe a trick worked on me.
What the fuck?
Just let him cook, Ben.
You got to learn.
You just got to let him cook.
Well, I just got to let him cook.
That was my mistake.
Hang on.
I was just seeing him breaking bad recently where Walter says, let us cook.
I thought, is that where it's from?
I'm not sure.
Does he say let us cook or does he say let's cook?
He says, let us cook.
Like he's telling someone else to just let us cook.
Yeah, it's like when he kills Gale and he's the only chemist Gus Fring has left.
He says, come on, Gus, just let us cook.
We're cooking.
Yeah, you know, I was thinking too.
I'm not sure if let them cook is like a breaking bad reference.
It might be, but it could just as easily not be.
I'm not sure.
There is a point later in the show where like Jesse is cooking in Mexico.
Maybe they say let him cook there because he's...
Even if they don't actually say it, it could still be like what people think of when they
say it and it could be part of why it caught on.
Honestly, someone make a freaking video essay about it.
Or Google it.
One or the other.
Yeah, one or the other.
Either way, it doesn't matter to me.
Next one is called Head Cannon Continued 321 Go.
Oh God, I really have to speak this plan up.
I really have to make sure that he sees me fucking make my own schnitzel.
Because, babe, I think he just tried to poison me.
He put fucking citric acid in my cereal.
I thought I was going to die.
What if next time he put cyanide in my milk or something?
I was going for the cyanide, but I got the citric acid instead.
This guy's a menace.
Next time.
He's probably called Dennis.
Alright, next one is another Imgurlink.
Oh, if you want my comic, you can read it, but you'll have to find it first.
Did I say that this was found?
Yes, you mentioned on your stream and then I went and found it.
I went to the site and I read every single one.
Actually, I read a bunch of them.
I think there's too many to read.
Do they continue into the current day?
I don't even know.
I didn't actually go and read them.
There's a bunch.
There's really, really a lot of funny ones.
Someone called RustinRobot went and found it and it is called Jennifer's Show.
J-E-N-N-F-E-R.
It's the person who makes them calls herself Jennifer J.
The non-cat girl is Jennifer and I think the cat girl is J.
Something like that, but anyway, yeah, Jennifer's Show.
It's just a comic about-
They have a YouTube channel.
They have a YouTube channel and it's a comic about these two characters who are in lesbians with each other.
They're in lesbians with each other, yes.
And they have huge boobies and it's just wholesome and that's it.
Sometimes it's funny in an unintentional way and sometimes it's funny in a deliberate way,
but the joke is very odd and that makes it funny in a different way.
There was a really good one.
A spork posted a really good one in my server that was like,
Jennifer drinking wine and being like, bring the popcorn, honey.
It's time for the Kiwi Farms.
Time to watch the movie of our Kiwi Farms thread roasting us again and it was pretty funny.
It's like being made by someone who is not good at drawing.
I love how so many spelling errors all the time.
Yeah, yeah.
It just makes it seem more like a deliberate parody and it just is not.
It does seem almost like a deliberate parody.
Here's the one that I'm talking about.
It looks like she's drinking iodine or something.
So basically we found the one piece.
Yeah, we found it and now I can read it.
I'm crying in this image.
Quick, Jen, get the popcorn soda, the drunk movie night,
goaning to start in Seven Min over at Kiwi Farms Discord page.
True.
This person is a little weird.
Their YouTube channel is a little bit unsettling.
Yeah, I didn't really watch any of their vlogs.
Yeah, I didn't really want to watch much of it,
but it's a couple of very strange videos of her in a huge stuffed shirt
with some fake glasses that kind of look like the ones she draws,
big oval pieces of cardboard or construction paper,
just waving around, just flopping around and looking a bit awkward.
There was a few that were just like,
this is like a sweet brown hella Jeff comic.
It's not even slightly dissimilar.
It's exactly what a sweet brown hella Jeff comic would be
just with less NS paint fuckery.
But the methods of drawing, sometimes with outlines,
sometimes they'll use a slanted pen that use for calligraphy.
Sometimes it'll just be with photographs as the backgrounds.
It's just great.
I love it.
It is.
It kind of is great, but it's definitely done.
There's no irony to it at all.
It's not done in a knowing wink wink ha ha way.
It's meant completely sincerely.
Yeah, it's amazing.
It is kind of amazing.
I actually should probably go and read through some just to see.
I haven't done that yet, but it's been found.
Resting Robot found it.
Appreciate it.
Mystery solved.
Good illustration here, though.
Good joke.
All right.
Next one is an Imgur album.
Let's freaking go.
Oh, it's a Mega Man G Fuel blue bomber slushie.
As an energy drink.
I've seen this before.
I think it's just the flavor is called slushie.
Like it's not actually a slushie.
I guess you'd need it to be ice in a can.
I saw this when I was looking for that e-tank cup that I bought to drink out of.
I did see this and I considered buying some just to see what it tastes like, but it didn't.
I wonder if this person actually found it in Walmart.
If this person actually found it in Walmart like in current year, I'd be shocked.
And I would think that was amazing if it were like still being sold.
Maybe.
They're making a new Mega Man.
They're making a new one with the highest budget ever.
Who knows what it'll be.
Next one is called four skin forever or in my case 10 in one half skin.
Why is it always four skin coming back to the show?
Wait, it's not playing.
It's not playing for me either.
I think it's because they know it annoys me.
Okay, it's playing.
Hey, dude.
I was just listening to your podcast and I heard this funny voicemail about regrowing your four skin.
You know how dudes like gauge their ears and stuff?
Well, basically you could gauge your four skin, not with like an ear gauge hole gap, but like a disc that will stretch your skin so that it can basically become longer and more pronounced like how you would with your ear lobes.
But instead of your ear lobes, it's your four skin.
Try it out, dude.
I got a sweet 10 and a half inches right now.
I mean.
Congratulations.
Just keep going.
Stretching.
It's like jelking, but just the skin, not the whole dick.
Yeah.
You know about jelking, right?
I think so.
Is that like a suction pump penis thing?
No, it's like a thing.
It's like a technique.
It's like a thing you do to basically stretch your dick out.
You basically damage your dick a little bit.
You fucking squeeze it in a way that causes it to be damaged a little bit and then when it heals, it theoretically lengthens it.
It's like you like freaking squeeze and stretch it to the point that it like causes harm and then it heals and maybe it gets longer.
Yeah.
And that's jelking.
That's a weird, like I remember seeing it as like a thing discussed, but it looked shady and scary.
So like I don't want to look at it.
I've heard people say that, yeah, it's not good for it.
I think it's an act of desperation.
It might work to a degree, but like probably at what cost, I think is the question.
It's just like, if there is like an increase, it would be very minor, like minuscule to the point where it really is not worth the effort.
I learned.
You can't gain an inch from like a weird technique like that.
That just doesn't know how it works.
I doubt it.
I learned from Little Joel recently.
Did you watch Little Joel?
Oh, yeah.
Love Little Joel.
Did you see the one about the lady that cut the guy's dick off?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I'll say it for the audience's benefit, I'll say that I learned from that.
Yeah, that lady that cut her like rapist husband's dick off, he got the dick repaired.
But then he went back to have her dick surgically enlarged and the dick enlargement surgery destroyed his dick.
Yeah.
He wasn't having the dick cut off by his wife that destroyed his dick.
It was his, what's the word?
His elective dupenus lengthening surgery, complications from it resulted in total dick destruction.
Why would you fucking, why would you play with fire after all that?
I know.
He was so close.
He must have felt invincible.
He was like, haha, nothing can destroy my dick.
If it lived through that, it can live through anything.
Foolish.
Like you could just take it off and then add another length of different penis and then stick the other one on.
Like you're building a block tower.
You got to get a donor.
You got to find someone with compatible blood type.
He'll donate most of their penis and you chop your dick.
Well, that's one way.
You could find a dick donor to chop off an inch of their dick to insert in yours, in the middle section.
Alternatively, I mean, why don't they just do, actually, it kind of is what they do.
When people like, the thing where they put the thing in their leg and it lengthens their leg bones.
That's kind of like jelking.
That's kind of like jelking their leg.
Jelking their bones.
Why don't they do that with their dick?
Why don't they put a freaking brace in their dick that they crank it every day and it lengthens their dick?
Because it's not a bone.
No.
It seems like it would actually be even easier to do if it wasn't a bone.
No, but like it's like soft tissue, soft tissue that stretched to a damaging degree would also heal.
Well, maybe.
I kind of feel like that.
I feel like if jelking works, that would work even better.
Super jelking.
A brace on your dick that you crank a little bit, you crank it a little bit every day.
You do that for like several months and you let it heal and your dick's longer at the end.
I don't know.
I don't see.
If jelking works, if leg lengthening works, why not on the dick?
Because I think it's the fact that the bone, when it grows back in smaller increments, it's more rigid.
It's a fixed thing.
Your bone can't shrink back to the size it was before because there's just more mass there and it's harder.
It's different.
I just feel like it's different than your penis.
That kind of makes sense.
You might be onto something.
Because the whole thing with the penis is that it's like a balloon.
It can shrink and then it can fill with blood.
Stretching it doesn't necessarily increase the area that the cells.
Maybe it rips certain things inside.
I feel like if you very slowly extended it with a brace, then at some point the tension of the stretch would be traumatic.
But if you very gradually increased that, the trauma would be introduced gradually and then it would heal.
It would heal itself while in that stretch state and it would heal itself with additional mass or length in order to close up the traumatic micro-fishers.
I don't know.
It's so fucked.
Get me a freaking doctor on the line.
Get me the freaking patent office.
Get me the Guinness Book of World Records for longest dick.
I'm going to have it soon.
I'm going to use my method.
Did you know, Ben, that you can apply like a gel, testosterone gel, and that makes your penis grow.
It's temporary, but they do that sometimes before.
Testosterone gel.
Yeah, because it's a hormone-based organ.
When you take estrogen, it shrinks a little bit and testosterone makes it grow.
Like how much?
I don't know how much exactly, but I've heard that before some trans women have the surgery to turn their penis into a vagina.
Oh, they put testosterone on it to make it bigger so it's easier to-
Yeah, because it makes more mass in the penis so that when you invert it,
it's deeper as a vagina because that's what they do.
Well, but hang on though, then wouldn't it shrink again afterwards?
I don't know.
I think once they tear it to shreds, it acts a little differently.
They cut it into sections and then invert it so that it's the linings of a vagina.
But like you said, it's a temporary increase, so the amount of mass-
I could understand if you made it bigger just so it's easier to manipulate surgically the pieces of it.
When I say it's temporary, I think what they mean is you add the hormone and it responds to the hormone,
but then it will revert to whatever level it was before.
I know, but that's what I'm saying.
Once it's been surgically changed, it no longer reacts to anything, it's just-
But it's the same tissue.
I don't know how it works.
I'm just saying I've heard that that's a thing that is done.
It makes sense.
I could see a surgeon just having an easier time chopping and slapping it, so to speak,
if it's just bigger.
It's more room to work with or whatever.
More specifically, I heard it was like changes the depth.
You don't have to rip it and tear it and crank it.
Put it in a freaking immersion blender.
Put it down the freaking garbage disposal.
I actually don't know what happens when a man takes extra testosterone.
It's probably not that good for them.
People do it, like older men do it, to maintain muscle mass, I think,
because I think when men get older, they produce less testosterone,
so I think older men supplement with it to keep themselves more muscular.
That's an old person thing just generally.
Yeah.
Just taking testosterone?
Even women?
No, I mean hormone production slows, so they need supplements.
Definitely.
I think some people do it.
I don't think it gives you any steroidal benefits.
I don't think if you just take extra testosterone, you get buffer or anything.
No.
Maybe you do that.
I think some people do take it, but I don't know if it has any benefits
unless you're already deficient.
There's one more voicemail.
Oh my god.
It's an image.
Here we go.
Can I mention the growing you'll be receiving?
Oh, this is AI upscaled?
We're just anime-ified.
These styles are so different.
These have got to be AI.
Yeah, yeah.
They're like four eye face.
Wait, is it?
I feel like the second image.
The second image, I mean, yeah, it's clearly weird.
Why did it interpret her having an arm pointing to you or the cat?
It's her tail, I think.
It's clearly just like struggling to interpret this figure.
It made it more legible, though.
It made it more sensical.
That's funny.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't know, the workings of it are mysterious to me.
Okay, this cake in the bottom,
I like the weird candy color fruit.
The blue raspberries?
It's like neon green something.
It's extremely fake looking fruits on this cake.
I want this cake, I want it.
The hand disappears.
The hand just disappears into the plate.
It struggles so much with the hands.
It works in the middle one because it just didn't bother giving them fingers.
Yeah.
How did it interpret me as a cat girl?
Okay, I think this is just an AI that is designed to turn anything into a cat girl.
I think that's what this is.
Yeah, it's odd, I'm not sure.
I have not seen this before.
The face in the first one just rules.
Like both faces?
In the first one up top, my big polygonal mouth.
Yeah, that's artistic.
That's awesome.
But then the girl is like an alien, like a bug person.
This is what's good about AI interpolation,
is when it just makes some fucking weird shit.
Bizarre.
I like how on the bottom one,
they've turned you into a big booby anime lady,
but they've also, where your hand is, they've just drawn a circle.
Because they don't know what that is.
What is that?
What does it think that is?
Like another person's head?
Is that some boob poking out of a hole in the fabric?
I don't think so.
Does it just turn my hand into a hole?
It just turns your hand into a-
Hand like a hole!
It turns your soul.
And it's got a little bit of hair.
Wait, wait.
Or is that the hair from the top?
I think that's just...
Well, I mean, to me, that just reads as my long hair
kind of going down my back.
I like that it...
Like what is it, that middle cake?
Where did that middle cake come from?
I wonder if it's like saying,
oh, there's cake here, therefore there's cake everywhere.
Therefore, anything else, we must interpret it as cake.
Yeah, but why?
There's nothing under your hand that could be a cake.
Yeah, there's nothing there.
There's just a little bit of white, and it's like,
well, it must be some cake.
He must be reaching for some cake.
Also, why is the cat has blue hair in the middle one?
Why did they give the cat blue hair?
They gave the cat purple hair.
There's weird logic at play.
And it's also weird because the perspective
is slightly different, and...
Well, maybe not that different.
Actually, the lines on the floor are very similar,
but you, as a cat person, are a lot closer
than the image of you.
Why did they notice that you are a figure there
and then increase your size to be closer?
Yeah, it's like taking the image
and it's like recognizing figures,
and then it's like creating new figures on top of them,
but in a way that distorts it towards some ideal,
towards some specific sort of image
that it wants to make out of anything.
I don't know.
It just thinks that the figure should be closer.
I can't...
I'm trying to make sense of it.
Your cat face is so fucked.
It looks like it's Uboa.
It's Uboa.
Uboa?
Yeah, you know the...
Hang on.
From Yumi Nikki.
Yumi Nikki.
It's this...
Oh, yeah, a little bit.
Yeah, Uboa cat.
That's me.
This image is titled Not So Pog,
but it's a little pog.
Yeah, it's pretty pog.
I am pogging a bit, actually.
Also, okay, the first one,
look at my eyebrow.
Look at what it gave me for my eyebrow forehead.
Yeah, it's like...
It gave me like a huge caveman brow.
Perfect.
You got like curly hair coming down.
Yeah.
I kind of look like a Pokemon trainer.
Yeah, like a Pokemon trainer or a professor.
Yeah.
But also with like crazy freaking like color swatches
for my eye holes.
I'm having fun.
This is a fun generation.
Love it.
Very confusing.
Makes me just gotta say...
All I can do is speculate and wonder why.
Why did it...
Why did this have to happen?
Oh, okay.
Last thing...
Yeah, it turned the mall
into like a traditional Japanese like dojo.
It's got like the sliding Japanese doors.
Yeah.
It's just like making everything into Japanese cat girls, this one.
Like that must be like specifically what this one is for.
Maybe this is not just put the image in and it'll interpret it.
Maybe the person added things like an explanation to go along with it.
Or maybe just like with the cake, right?
It recognized that there was cake and so it added more cake in other places.
Maybe it recognized the cat ears on the one girl
and so it just gave everyone cat ears.
Yeah, that's probably what I thought.
Also, the cat girl in the middle has three ears.
Yes, I noticed that.
She's got the two black ones and the one blue one.
Like it didn't quite know which angle to go with.
So it just went with both.
Delightful.
Yeah.
That's the end of the voicemails.
All right.
Wow, is it nearly, is it nearly fucking February?
If there's a week and change left.
When this episode's out, it'll be the 27th.
That's right.
Crazy.
That's 30.
Yeah.
I should, you know, I know I said this last month,
but I should really try to get that book done by the end of this month.
And I should actually do it this time.
And every time I say that, it gets more and more likely that it will happen,
that this will be the month.
So you're playing the slots, you're rolling the dice again.
Every single, every single time, every time.
And one of these days it's going to pay out.
One of these days it's going to pay out.
Just like crypto.
You know, I'm sad to say Bitcoin had a big day yesterday.
It like jumped up like 30%.
Jumped up, jumped up and got down.
It went down a little bit, but like, yeah, it had a big,
like a 30% jump yesterday.
And I hate that.
It makes me upset.
I got a fucking notification from one of the apps I was using
that I had put money in a long time ago.
And it said, you've got like a few days left,
final chance to take your cash out because the app is not going to exist.
I'm like, oh, okay, cash out please.
So that should be...
Did you do that?
Well, I hope you did it after this jump.
That's like 30%.
It wasn't in Bitcoin.
I think the app, I had specifically got it to put some in Dogecoin,
just because Dogecoin at the time was going insane.
And I just missed it.
I was like, dang.
Well, maybe next time and I never happened.
Well, these cryptos tend to like rise and fall together.
Like...
Yeah.
Ethereum also jumped up yesterday.
I just took everything out.
I think overall, like the money I put in, I think I put 200 pounds in
and I took out 283 pounds.
So it's not a big jump, but like it's not a loss.
So fuck it.
I'm not paying attention to those apps anymore.
Dogecoin rose yesterday, but only a little bit.
Yeah.
Um, frickin...
Dick Masterson just came out with like...
Okay.
I guess there's...
He had his like, quote unquote, Patreon alternative, which is just...
He manages your money for you.
And he just said...
He's announced a new one that's like that, but it's crypto.
Well, and I don't know, it just seems so stupid.
It just seems like, first of all, he already had one.
First of all, he already could just do it himself.
So I don't see what the benefit to this new one is...
Unless you already are in crypto.
If you have crypto, it's the same as the old one.
But if you don't, then it's just the old...
I think it was called New Project 2.
It's just that, but you have to invest in crypto before you can participate in it.
And I just don't fucking...
I just don't get it.
What was the idea with New Project 2?
Well, the idea is that some creators and some people were banned off Patreon and stuff.
And basically, Dick...
Pretty much all it was was like, people could just pledge to New Project 2
instead of pledging to Patreon.
And that's just the same as sending your money to Dick.
And then Dick just gives these people...
He pays them out.
He's basically functioning as Patreon for these people who were banned from Patreon.
That's pretty much the gist of it.
Which is fine, I guess.
Yeah, and the new one is just that, but crypto.
Awesome.
Stupid.
Crypted.
More like, more like, crypt off.
Get it?
No.
You get ripped off.
Oh, crypt off.
I get it.
That's good.
Yeah, yeah, thanks.
Next week, I won't be depressed anymore.
Mm-hmm.
Hello.
Well, is that true or is that a lie?
Find out next time.
Find out.
Only one way to find out.
Next time, my book will be done.
That's...
Yeah.
It could happen.
Next time, I make no promises.
All I'm doing is existing.
You should make promises and then just break them.
No, what's the point?
What's the point of saying, oh, I should work on that and then not doing it?
Maybe I should just forego the saying, I'll do it.
Hmm.
Well, that's not very Sigma grind set of you.
I feel like something has to change with my, I don't know, situation slash attitude slash mental state.
Yeah.
Before I can really, because I don't know.
This is like Clarissa, that's the thing hanging over my head.
There's still some other things.
Mm-hmm.
I'm like, got to do it.
Yeah.
I want it.
I genuinely don't want to do anything.
You're saying you need a change in your outlook, mental state, attitude, what have you, before you can get that done is what you're saying.
I don't know.
I think it may also be a mistake to be waiting or, you know, hoping for something to change before I do anything.
To, I don't know.
I'm just sort of like, I'm numb right now.
I'm numb to everything.
I just sort of like enjoying like media and feeling mostly nothing.
And it's like, you know, whatever.
Okay.
I think it was a while ago, and I think I showed it on the show, but I posted, I guess you could call it a meme.
But it was a bunch of like, it was sort of like art, like it was kind of self-healthy, but not really.
It was sort of like memes or like jokes about like, it was basically like comparing like two different ways to like look at the same thing.
And I don't remember what all of them were.
But do you remember the one, it was like, the artist is like looking at the blank page.
And in the one panel, he says like, he says like, I'll work on this when I feel better.
And then in the other one, he says, if I work on this, I will feel better.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
I think if you're troubled, I know it's hard, I know it's hard to get yourself out of a rut.
But if you're troubled by the fact that you haven't worked on a thing, then probably you might have to simply force yourself to do it, even if you don't feel like it.
And you might find that in doing so, that that's the only way to push past that.
Yeah.
It's just a tip for you.
It's just a little nudge, because it sounds like what you might need to hear.
I don't know, because I mean, probably, I'm not discounting that advice.
But I did try to force myself, I guess it was a few months ago now.
And I did get a bit of work done.
And then I immediately was like, that sucked.
I don't want to do anymore.
So it didn't make me feel better.
And I don't know.
At the moment, I'm just sort of like, what if, you know, fuck everything?
What if all the things I do, like that doesn't matter?
Just fuck them.
I'm genuinely at a point like that.
And I don't really know how I feel about it.
Well, I mean, it sounds like you just told me how you feel about it.
Well, I don't know.
You're like, fuck it.
I guess so.
It's kind of sad though.
And that's the end of the show.
No, I get you.
I don't know.
My light at the end of the tunnel right now is the book is done.
And I can kickstart it.
So I mean, I've got that going for me.
If I didn't have that, I don't know what I would do.
I would feel very little motivation.
I guess I'm just sort of feeling like the things I do don't really matter to anyone that much.
And so like, if I finally get closer to chapter four done, like, it's whatever.
Like, it doesn't excite me.
And that's annoying.
No, I don't feel like anything I'm doing is exciting.
I definitely feel, I know exactly what you mean, but I don't know what advice I have to offer about that.
Because I know all too well that, yeah, I don't know.
I guess you got to just step back and look at the big picture and appreciate.
I mean, there's one of two options.
Either the thing is worth doing, in which case you could step back and consider and take a broader perspective and see,
no, I should do that because it will have, because I will be glad that I did.
Or, I mean, I guess you might look at it objectively and you might conclude,
and I'm not saying this about Clarissa.
I'm just saying this about endeavors in general.
You might be like, no, that's not worth doing.
What I'm not excited about it is because it's a waste of time and I should do something else.
You know, those are the only two possibilities.
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't really want to bring it up earlier because I didn't really have a robust thought about any of it.
It's just sort of like, wow, I really am in a malaise right now.
I guess we'll see what happens.
You know what?
I mean, yeah, me too.
I also didn't get too much into it before.
I kind of just let it go, but it's good.
Honestly, if you had gotten on this, if you had wanted to talk about your malaise,
I probably would have started talking about my malaise and then we just would have had a malaise cast.
Yeah.
Next time.
No, next time.
That's the teaser for the next episode.
Right.
I mean, I don't mind.
Do you want to wrap up or do you want to explore this more deeply?
I feel like we've gone on.
We've had a full episode at this point.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I don't know what I would say.
I feel like my work has been good generally, like my body of work.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I don't feel like doing it right now.
That's it.
That's where my mind is.
No.
If I damn, I wish I knew the solution to that problem because that would help me also.
And I'm trying to think about it from the point of view of like,
what would I tell someone else who feels that way?
Because kind of that's sort of how you have to, when you have a problem,
sometimes it helps to think about what would I tell someone else that came to me
and they described a similar problem.
And what you're describing to me is a similar problem to what I think about.
And now I'm like, well, can I think of something that I would tell someone with that problem?
No.
I have nothing, no solutions to offer.
But let's think about it.
Let's contemplate.
Maybe next week we'll think of something.
Yeah.
We'll have the answers.
All right, you want to wrap up?
Yeah.
Do you?
I don't know.
It would have been cool if you had the perfect thing to say and I'm like, oh my god.
I know.
That would have ruled so much.
I would have been the man.
My therapist told me you should try to create something.
Even if it's not good.
I think Clarissa, I want it to be good so I'm not doing it because I don't think it's good enough.
That's one aspect.
Your therapist said you should try to create something.
Was that her specific advice for you or in general?
For me because I'm a creative person.
I'm obviously in the past have been very passionate about certain things because I'm depressed at the moment.
I'm sort of closing off.
I'm not with it.
If art is fun, creating things is fun, then I should try to do something that I want to do.
Even if it's bad, even if nobody wants to see it, even if I will never show it to anyone.
I was like, okay.
That's some sort of actionable advice.
Try and work on something that I want to do and then I was thinking about it and I don't want to do anything.
That was the roadblock.
I'm like, well fuck.
I don't have a single thing that I'm interested in doing right now.
I don't know.
Yeah.
If I need to reignite a spark of motivation or passion, I don't know how to do it.
Sometimes somebody will ask me about the next chapter of the champion or the vapors or something.
Generally, my answer is like, yeah, in general I'd like to do another one of those, but I don't have a story that's in my head right now that's like, I know what I'm going to do.
I know what it's going to be and I want to do it.
It's like, I would need to really have, yeah, like a specific thing I want to make, like a specific story that I want to tell.
I can't imagine, like to motivate myself to do that.
I can't imagine.
You know, mangaka, they're working on a freaking deadline every week.
Every week they got to come up with some new bullshit for their characters to do or whatever.
Can you fucking imagine?
I can't.
I mean, I can hardly think of anything.
I can think of that being like a good recipe for like continued ability to work.
Like if there's a deadline, well, you've got to draw something.
And if you've got to draw something, then even if you don't have a good idea, you'll just throw something out.
And that's like a, I don't need to, I don't really need to worry so much about everything being perfect.
Sometimes a chapter is kind of lame.
I mean, it doesn't have one piece, but he's very, very well like honed that craft over the decades.
And he's got a lot of ideas that he's already written down.
But like for some mangaka, they have off weeks.
Sometimes you can tell.
Where it's just, so I don't know.
I need to maybe just make Clarissa chapter four, even if it sucks and then put it up there and maybe I'll feel better.
But yeah, no deadline and no like, no nothing.
This makes it difficult.
Yeah, this is kind of a depressing thought that I have a bunch of the time.
But I wonder if like, hey, if I like worked for a magazine or something, if I worked for Shonen Jump or something like that.
And I was like, okay, I need to make a chapter because I need to fill my quota.
I need to, because it's my job and I got to do it.
So I do it.
I don't know.
Would I, you know.
Just makes me wonder like, what would I have done?
What would I have done if that was my situation?
Like what work could I have done under those circumstances that I haven't and never will now because that was not true?
That really makes me sad.
Well, that's the show everybody.
What if we made like a like a procrastinator's jump?
Little little manga magazine, the weekly this and then we would put we would put like a the latest chapter of Clarissa and or any other comic or whatever.
I don't know if I have the, I don't know if I have the chops to do anything weekly like that.
I mean, neither do I really, but maybe not weekly, but I think some sort of structure would help me in my situation.
Yeah, the moment it's it feels like the the barriers to Clarissa existing are my own feeling that what I'm doing is for a good reason.
Like people care about Clarissa and want to see and I know people do.
People have told me they want to see, but like, I want it to be good.
And so, yeah, I don't feel like I'm good enough.
But I don't know what if I had a deadline, what if I had to make it?
I mean, that's how I made the first few bunches of pages because of the Tezuka thing.
It was a very hard deadline.
You had to have the comic ready by this time.
Otherwise, it would not be submitted.
True.
You're on you're on to something.
You're probably right.
What would you contribute to a weekly one piece, a weekly manga magazine on the procrastinators brand?
God.
Obviously, you got different types of projects.
That's genuinely like a scary question.
That would be if like, I feel like I would be going over a cliff to like hard commit to doing any such thing.
This feels like I'm asking to fail.
I mean, yeah, it's going to suck.
Yeah.
The only thing that is like makes sense to me is that if I try, if I try to make it, it's going to be bad.
Well, it's I know that I'll be able to make it.
It'll just be bad and people will say, oh, this sucks.
They'll spit upon my grave, but at least I'll make it.
It would be it would be Biscopades.
I would pick up Biscopades again and finish and go do that until it was done.
Yeah, that's actually it's an easy answer.
Yeah, we should make we should make a little.
What's the name?
What's a good name?
Shonen Jump.
We don't really want to copy jump, but yeah, something.
I'm trying to think of like a pun with PCP or procrastination.
Pro comics.
Pro comics publication.
Based.
Epic win.
You there?
No, I'm just thinking.
No, that was my serious.
My serious answer.
PCP.
Wait, wasn't that like a thing in like that's the whole like backman thing.
The pro crime.
Yeah, well, the perfect crime party.
Yes.
Perfect comic park tea.
Perfect.
Honestly, yeah, perfect comic party is not bad.
We're the procrastinators.
We have a show called the PCP in a comic called the PCP.
No confusing at all.
And our acronym is TPC.
All right.
I feel like that's worth submitting to the board.
I feel like honest, you know what?
Honestly, you know what?
Honestly, it's a little bit scary, but I could honestly, I could do.
I feel like that'd be better.
Something like that.
I don't know.
It would need a little bit of infrastructure, but I would feel better doing it like that
than just fucking posted my shit on Twitter.
Posting Biscopades on Twitter was like depressing.
This shitty platform for such a thing.
But I have like no audience on like Tapas or Webtoon.
So that was even shittier there.
Yeah.
Okay.
This is cute then.
We can have a little cute little comic.
It is cute.
I guess we'll draw the comics and then put them together in like a PDF or some sort of
way people can read it and then link the PDF.
It's like, oh, it's the new episode.
It's the new thing.
Maybe fans could like write articles.
Maybe the, what's the RFCK news?
Where'd that go, huh?
Oh, the Slime Times?
Slime Times.
You could have a Slime Times article.
Just spitballing.
Obviously, initially, it'll just be me and you.
I think we'd better, on the one hand, like a downloadable PDF is cuter.
But I mean, Beescapades is GIFs.
Beescapades was like in a GIF format.
So it couldn't exist as a PDF.
Yeah, that's the truth.
Although, I guess it wouldn't have to be GIFs.
This is not that essential a part of it.
Maybe you could just link like, hey, this new episode.
Could just be an HTML website.
Just be a web page.
A web page.
Like, I want it to be cute.
It could better just be a zip file.
Could you be a zip file with images in it?
It could be.
I just like the cute little idea of it having a cover with a barcode
and all those things they have on a comic book you would buy.
And the big old title, name of comic but cool looking
with our characters doing like a shonen jump.
Oh, look, this one's got Clarissa in it and Beescapades.
Oh, my God.
My two favorite characters, Clarissa and Beescapades.
His name is the Beast Hustler.
If I even remember correctly, and I do.
And it could be like a little weekly comic.
I could do a Redman comic for it as well.
Oh, right.
Redman.
Yeah, that's the funny.
So that's the funny is at the end.
Do you have still have a bunch of Redman queued up
or did you finish those?
I finished those.
I could just make border.
True.
I think I prefer making it on the spur of the moment
and posting it rather than making a ton of them in one go
and then queuing them because like some of the jokes
just don't land when I write a bunch of them in one go.
Although sometimes that is how I wrote them
because I just thought of something funny until I had a good one.
But yeah, I could do a Redman comic.
Those don't take much.
I would just need to finish the next Clarissa gun smoke.
I wonder how long, I wonder how I could do,
maybe if I said like one day a week aside,
I could do a few panels of Biscopades a week
and it probably wouldn't even be that hard.
You know, I feel pretty good.
I really did want to finish that,
but I've just had so many other things that I have popped up
that I've been like, I have to do this first,
I have to do that first.
I think this is good because...
I have to spend five months making a Mega Man video.
I think this is good because it pulls on those collaborative strings,
those collaborative heart strings,
that got me so into like making videos, like pony videos.
That's what I was going to say.
No, I was working with people,
but I was working with people in tandem
to make a review of the new My Little Pony episode.
That's what I was going to say.
And so like instead of...
Like I have to deliver.
Yeah, but instead of making the same comic,
we're making those same product in the magazine.
You know what?
I kind of like it.
Using our comics.
The more I think about it, the better an idea I think it is.
The perfect comic party.
I like that.
It's a callback.
All the way back to the roots.
Then...
Okay.
We should call it one piece.
That's the one place.
All the comics are in one place.
I left all of the good comics in one piece.
It's exactly like that Imgirlink.
You can read my comic,
but you'll have to find it first.
We add like a comic from Jennifer and Jen.
We should just steal...
Yeah, we should just steal that.
We should just steal Jennifer's show
and just put it in and pretend she's a contributor
and not tell anyone.
Yeah.
I dig it.
I think I'm in.
And we could put Fana,
that appears on the Progress Natives podcast.
Oh, true.
Or Fana just appears.
Where would we publish it?
Well, we have a Twitter account for the channel.
We can put it on the freaking...
We have a freaking WordPress.
Oh, we do.
Yeah.
Which I've been meaning to update
and I keep telling people I'll update,
and I haven't done it in like three months,
maybe longer.
Well...
Okay, so making a PDF
is something that I know how to do,
I think, pretty simple.
But with Biscopay's GIFs,
do you want to make a version of Biscopay's
that would appear in the magazine,
or do you not like the PDF idea?
Because otherwise it's like a series of web pages
that you click through to the next one.
That's like PDF better.
It's a file.
Honestly, I don't...
I don't really care that much about
discarding the GIF format.
Maybe...
Maybe if there's like something I really wanted to animate,
I could just have like a clickable link in the PDF
that would link to a website
that displays the GIF or something.
Yeah, I think if you can do that,
if you can have links in PDFs,
then you can just link to where...
You can host it on St. Connex,
and you can just link from the PDF to it.
Yeah.
Maybe the same for me.
But I'll also put it in the PDF.
Alright, fuck it, I'm in.
Alright.
This is fun.
Yeah.
We'll post it on the WordPress.
I'll update the WordPress.
I'll get it up to date.
Yeah.
We'll think of a logo.
Maybe some...
Maybe we can steal...
We can steal someone's logo.
Someone submits a flag.
Someone submits a purple and green flag.
It's got to be purple and teal,
and it's got to have a skull.
And that's it.
Jump Comics, PCP,
Perfect Crime Party.
We just copied their logo
that they used for the fake...
One of these.
Do they have a logo? Let me see.
Oh, that's just letters.
That's dog shit.
Yeah.
It sucks.
I mean, we could just take that
and make it better and make the colors
fascinating.
I like...
I just...
It's amusing seeing them hold a phone
saying PCP like they're listening to it.
They are listening to the...
Excuse me, darling.
I'm listening to the PCP right now.
It's so interesting.
It's just so funny how many times
it says PCP on this cover.
PCP. PCP.
PCP. Yeah, three times.
Perfect Crime Party in the back.
We can have guest contributors.
Yeah.
People can contribute if they're...
Maybe Cheesy wants to put one of their comics
in the magazine.
Sure.
A new alien girlfriend.
Or just...
I mean, I was just thinking like...
Any old fucking idiot
sends this shit.
Any old fucking loser.
Any fucking loser.
I mean, it would...
Little scribbler, little scribe.
It'd have to be a little bit good.
It'd have to be decent, but...
Nah, we'll do it like the voicemails.
Any old shit.
You know what? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right. You're right.
Open it up in submissions.
No submit...
No approval process.
Just anyone...
It has to be a comic.
That's the only rule.
Okay.
Single panel comics.
Based.
Like Beast Capades are allowed.
Yeah.
Cause you got like...
A panel and then text under.
My...
Page size...
The Clarissa and Beast Capades
have different page sizes.
But...
I mean, whatever.
Yeah, I was assuming it'd be like...
Two...
Two panels per page or something.
Yeah, you could figure that out.
Figure it out, yeah.
Hey, that feels good.
Hey.
It's good.
Feeling good about it.
Yeah.
Shuffed.
Nice job.
Hey, nice job.
Thanks.
Hey, thanks for offering solutions.
Instead of just wallowing.
Yeah, it's funny.
Cause like I feel...
I feel in the same like...
Area of depression.
But I don't feel like wallowing.
I just feel like nothing.
But this was like easy to think of.
Like yeah, that could be fun.
Wow.
Yeah, let's fucking do it.
It's very impressive.
I'm so smart.
You're very smart.
Thank you.
You did a great...
You did a good job.
But I mean it though.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's make it happen.
We'll work on it.
We'll workshop it.
And that's the episode of the
Procrastinators podcast.
That's the episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
Become a patron.
Wait, shit.
We should make a patron exclusive.
Oh, but I don't want to.
No, I don't care about that.
I'm gonna make my comic...
I'm gonna make my comic like free anyway.
Ah, fuck.
Yeah, me too.
This is a motivational tool.
This is not a money-making scheme.
Yeah.
Fine.
Alright.
I'll make...
I'll have to make money some other way.
Like a chump.
Maybe...
Alright, how about this?
Patron exclusive benefit.
You get to be one of the supporters in the comic.
In the magazine.
Yeah, that's true.
Support a page.
See, that's true.
A thank you page.
You know, why not?
We can do thank you pages.
It's not a bad idea.
Yeah, okay.
That makes sense.
The coolest members are...
This guy.
They will be ranked in terms of money.
Yeah.
Alright.
Good.
It's all coming together.
I don't know how to make a PDF.
That's okay.
I'll be in charge of making the PDF.
Okay.
We should work together on the logo and stuff.
Alright.
I'll think about it.
I'll work on it.
Yeah.
Alright.
Sick.
Exciting.
Exciting stuff.
It's all work on the next chapter to get it ready in time.
Not necessarily for next week.
Do you have a deadline?
I think it would be cool if this could be a February thing.
We'd launch it in February.
Hmm.
We got new chapters of the thing and it's the first episode.
Probably.
Issue one of the perfect comic party.
I'm sure I could do something by February.
Alright.
Sounds good.
Base.
Alright.
Let's end the episode here.
Right now.
Yeah.
Anna.
Become a patron.
You'll be in a thank you page of that thing we just talked about.
Probably.
That's the end of the episode.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
That's the end of the episode.
Send in speak type stuff.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Link in the description.
Bye.
Goodbye.