Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and we're joined today by Hippo Gibbontake.
Boy, howdy, bitches.
Ah, Munchy.
You know, some shows have theme songs that have cute little jingle catchphrases,
and we just have Nate saying hello in the exact same tone of voice every single time.
I don't know how we do it.
Munchy, we have a theme song.
We have an opening jingle.
Or something right?
It's not memorable at all, it doesn't even count.
I mean, who would remember that?
I remember that it's like guitar strums.
Munchy, literally everyone remembers the theme song that I made like four years ago.
Not that one.
I mean, that's true.
That's our outro now.
That's our outro song.
Is that the outro?
I don't even watch it.
Yeah, we use this as the outro song.
Listen to the PCP once in a while.
Okay, that's Ben, and also Jesse.
Yep, that's me.
Tom's here.
I come before all of you, a changed man.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
Tell me.
How's that?
Tell me more.
We're going to get into it later, I guess.
No, cancel.
Tom's kicked.
I don't want it.
Do you have an adamantium spine now, like bullseye?
Did you finally?
God, I wish.
I was hoping for that.
Okay, let me just say that first of all, last week was the Pony episode, and everybody
loved it and especially loved my story about the roller coaster.
So, if you haven't heard that, go listen to it.
You know, I'm thinking about bringing back the Highlights channel just for that story.
The Razorback?
The Diamondback.
Diamondback.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everyone, praise me, praise me.
I appreciate that.
You know, I always think about that.
Like, oh man, we should cut out the good parts and upload them on their own.
I mean, we definitely should.
And then I think about how we have that Highlights channel, but then I think about like, no,
if I'm cutting out my good parts, I'm putting them on my channel.
Fuck those guys.
I mean, that's the problem.
Anything said on the podcast is the intellectual property of all of us.
Communism in the PCP.
Oh my God.
No.
Communism, that's capitalism.
That's the same way you-
Wait, no, no, no.
If we-
Immediately.
We're immediately into this.
Why?
If we all-
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm just saying the definition, if we all mutually own the means of production, that's capitalism.
I mean communism.
Oh, you slipped up.
That's the same line you dropped on me when you took my hilarious, I'm just being cool
joke and put it on a t-shirt and tried to reap the fucking benefits of it.
Yeah, it was on the show.
That's my intellectual property.
Well, guess what?
Now we all own it.
So there you go.
Yeah, that's-
We don't.
I'm gonna sell a better version of the shirt someday.
Hey, I've got a small announcement and that today, August 18th, the day we're recording,
is my dog Sessho's second birthday.
It's his birthday today.
Oh my god.
And he's two years old and he's sweet.
Time to put it down.
I just came-
Now how is his diet coming?
Because he was just so unbelievably chunky and just like honestly fat.
Like honestly-
He's not fat.
Use the word fat.
Obeseven.
Like a sausage dog.
I don't know about obese.
It's fucked up of you to say.
He's not obese.
He was double his size.
He was double his specie size.
We all know that BMI is a terrible indicator.
You need to use more advanced metrics to determine dog obesity.
You need to use skin fold calipers.
That's right.
And measure the waist and things of that nature.
Why is it considered wrong for a dog to be fat?
They don't have to do anything.
They don't have a job.
They can be as fucking obese as they want.
I mean if they're fat enough, they'll fucking die.
I want my dog to be fat.
They'll fucking die.
That means he's well fed.
It means no.
No.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm convinced.
Here's, I guess, here's a progress pic.
Give it a second.
It's uploading.
He's, you know...
Oh my goodness.
Lay on his side.
Emotionless.
Progress might not be the word I would use in this.
Are you sure that's not a picture of a dog corpse?
Listen, I want it to be known.
That name.
You think of Nate in your mind.
He lifts.
He runs.
He's a fitness sort of guy.
His dog, the fattest dog on earth.
He's built like a faucet.
It's not his fault.
Nate, I just have to assume that he gets kibble.
Just lines in every one of his pockets and he's just,
oh, Seshaw, just come over here
and then just fucking pour his kibble down his throat
as hard and fast as he can.
It's his birthday.
You're not allowed to fat shame him on his birthday.
He's doing everything right.
Can you even pick him up?
We were, he is kind of hard to pick up.
He has a,
Are you saying it's a two man job?
It's a two man job to lift.
You have a system of police when you need to get him off.
We just went to PetSmart.
We got him his birthday toy.
We got him some birthday treats.
And then we went straight to the dog park.
We were there hanging out for a while.
We just left.
Oh, it's a beautiful place.
He's sniffing.
He's hanging out with the other boys.
He's going around having a good time.
And I'm going to go pick up Michelle and him later
after he's had his fill.
He's just the best little boy.
He's doing so great out there.
Pick them both up from dog and girlfriend kindergarten.
He's thriving.
He is thriving.
Dog parks are girlfriend kindergarten.
Can we get some dog emotes in the chat for Secho's birthday, please?
Thank you.
But I just want to let you all guys all know,
as I'm sure you'll remember from our famous episode on Furries,
there was that one fur suitor of a kangaroo
that had the giant, giant stomach.
I'm going to get like a really shitty thumbnail to show you guys,
but then a living fall will be able to show like a real image in the show notes.
But just take a look at like this.
I think this is the perfect representation of what Secho will become
if he were turning into a fursuit.
I mean, this is just like...
Oh, no.
That's not right.
That looks like an ancient like Roman torture device.
Like you put someone in there and you boil it
and you make it and they burn.
Oh, dude.
You know what I mean?
So inside there, like there's a human inside there, right?
But like the belly is some sort of like bomb.
I remember like...
Yeah, so the iron ball or something.
I'm not sure if it was this one,
but there are many suits like this as I'm sure you can imagine.
It's extremely arousing like 90% of the population.
And so I made an edit of one of them where it's two robs
on either side of them from the subspace emissary
and they're pulling apart the giant subspace bomb that is his stomach.
So that's what I was imagining.
That's disgusting.
Yeah, suiting in that count as vor,
like he's big and fat and there's a person inside there.
Is that...
I don't know, dude.
Was it deleted?
Did someone delete it?
Why was it deleted?
No.
Oh my God.
In the gross disgusting audio links.
Oh no one can make fun of my fucking dog.
Oh no one can know the truth.
I have a fucking force feeding him four.
All my dog can be able to eat me one day.
I watched this movie many times.
I just watched again the other day,
the movie Seven, directed by David Fincher
starring Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman,
great detective, weird psycho story.
And the guy, the bad guy kills people
based on the Seven Deadly Sins
because he's trying to, whatever, correct society or whatever.
And the first one they'll find...
It's the edgiest movie I've ever seen in my life
and I absolutely love it.
I watch it all the time.
It's so good.
I am Jesus Christ and Satan in one body.
And the first kill they find is a super fat guy
who, there was a gun to his head
and he was forced to continuously eat spaghetti
until his stomach exploded.
His skull shut and just kept feeding me.
He fed me.
Pretty much.
That's pretty much how it went down.
That's what you're going to do to your dog
on his third birthday.
Well, no, what's the rationale behind that?
Okay, I'm going to force this person to eat more,
like, obviously, eating more to get him more fat.
Oh, well, I'll tell you why.
Like, most of you are just making the problem, really.
No, no, no, no.
Okay, the guy was already incredibly fat.
Sure.
The bad guy was aware that he thinks that, you know,
Gluttony's a sin.
He doesn't like this big fat guy.
Did he also, like...
So he comes to his...
Aside from being fat,
did he, like, do anything else that was bad?
No.
His crime was simply being really fat.
Why that guy?
That's correct.
Yeah, there's lots of really fat people.
And this man would kill them, I assume.
It's one of those where the villain thinks he's deep
and that he's not just a crazy asshole idiot.
Like, another thing he does is he goes to, like,
a model's house and he cuts off her nose
so she'll be horribly disfigured.
But he, like, he bandages her so she won't die.
And in the one hand, he gives her a telephone
to call for help.
And in the other hand,
he gives her a bottle of sleeping pills.
So she can choose to kill herself
so that she won't have to deal with being scarred forever.
Or she could call the cops and live,
but she'll be disfigured and she kills herself.
Because society's fucked up, man.
It's so fucked up.
It's about, like, so superficial.
Every time I watch that movie, I just really...
I hate John Doe so much.
He's such a hypocrite.
And, like, I guess that's the point.
Because, like, the whole movie, you know, he's trying to be deep.
Like, he thinks, like, oh, it's your fault I'm killing you
because everyone is so bad.
That's why they have to...
But, like, I...
Not to spoil it, but his final victim
totally did nothing wrong at all.
Yeah.
He is willing to kill innocents.
He is.
And that's not exactly what I do.
And, like, he makes up some...
He makes up some flimsy...
It's not the coolest thing.
He makes up some flimsy justification
for how it could fit his stupid guidelines
and his dumb gimmick.
And he's like, oh, no, because you'll be so mad
that I killed a totally unisted person
that you'll be Wrath.
Yeah, yeah.
And the kill will be the true villain.
His final one.
And that's, like, yeah, makes no sense.
You're just an idiot.
Let's...
Let's spoil it a little...
Okay, spoilers the next, like, minute or whatever.
So, the point of the movie is
he eventually...
He creates Wrath out of his actions
out of one of the two police officers,
which is Brad Pitt, who's, like, investigating this guy.
He turns him into Wrath
as his final masterpiece of the final sin.
And he, John Doe, is Envy,
who envies the cop in his simple life.
And he kills his wife and chops off her head
and as it delivered, like, to their final, like, showdown place.
And it's gonna...
So it's still has to trick him into becoming a murderer,
which he succeeds at,
because society, man, what?
It's kind of...
It's what?
Is that even a society problem?
I don't know about that one.
I hate how Morgan Freeman is, like,
trying to stop him from shooting John Doe,
because it's like, oh, don't do it.
Don't do it.
You'll fulfill his prophecy.
You'll play right into his hands.
Who cares? He's gonna be fucking dead.
It doesn't matter.
His prophecy is fucking stupid.
It's that old JRP trope of,
if you kill the bad guy, you're as bad as him.
You're automatically as bad as the bad guy.
The only thing that I wish had been different
is that before Brad Pitt shot him,
he leaned in close and said,
you know this is fucking stupid, right?
This makes no sense and your plan is wrong
and didn't shot him.
I fucking love that movie.
I watch it all the time.
Like, just so you know,
I'm gonna kill you,
but I don't feel like I'm wrath.
I don't feel like you succeeded.
I think you're a failure. Goodbye. Bam.
Well, that's why he should have let the courts take care of it.
He should have let society deal with this guy.
That's what Morgan Freeman's saying.
Morgan Freeman's disgusting.
He doesn't deserve my taxpayer money
to pay for his trial. Fuck him.
Well, that's...
I mean, he probably would have got off
in an insanity play anyway.
I don't even think Brad...
What would Brad Pitt have even been convicted of?
I mean, he did kill a man
who was not...
Yeah, but like in circumstances,
he would have got off with a slap.
He's a cop. Come on.
He did just kill his wife.
I think if your wife's severed head is in a box,
I think they put you in court
and they're like,
okay, we can all see why you did that.
He'd have gotten like six months of community service.
You know what he'd probably fucking get?
Remember in that other Samuel Jackson movie,
A Time to Kill when he kills those two guys
who raped and mutilated his daughter?
Is that the one?
Yes, he deserves to die and I hope they burn in hell.
Yeah, and even though he literally did it,
everyone knows they did jury nullification
and just said, no, innocent.
He gets to go free.
You know Brad Pitt's going to get that shit.
No one's going to convict this guy
of killing like a serial killer who doesn't kill the wife.
He's going to get like a month of mandatory
emotional counseling or something.
When you respond in,
in like some sort of like code in your DNA,
there's some sort of like constant tornado
of trash and filth just all around you,
constantly blowing and picks up speed.
And that's weird old like movies from the 2000s
that you're just bringing up the PCP.
It was last samurai.
Now it's seven.
It's going to be some,
it's going to be fucking,
how the Grinch did Christmas.
I watched a lot of starring Jim Carrey next.
Yeah.
I watched a lot of movies.
What can I say?
You know, the Grinch,
the Jim Carrey Grinch is a great film.
It's so good.
I'm so interested in it.
It's revisionist history and that it wasn't good.
I'm so sick of people.
Was it actually good?
It's actually kind of good, yeah.
It's great.
People have always pretended that it's not good
and I don't know why.
Me and Ben watched it.
It's leagues better than the cartoon.
We watched it like last time I was here
like a couple of months ago.
And I expected it to be like kind of like boring
just like another kid's movie
because I remember it being really funny.
I wanted to watch it
because I thought it was going to be really funny
and it was.
And it was just incredible
because Jim Carrey as the Grinch
is the best like typed cast person
like in the world.
Like it is just the perfect combination.
I feel like after the events of the Grinch
starring Jim Carrey,
that interpretation of the Grinch
went on a grand like America Trek
and found in Slime City
and was the original man
and started the original film.
What's the connection?
He just looks like the kind of guy
who he does have that look about him.
You put that Grinch suit
in like a business suit on top of it
and had him smoking a cigar.
He might be the founder.
He might be the final boss.
He might be N1 or N0
at the head of Slime Corp.
Jim Carrey is the Grinch.
Jim Carrey.
I like how every single shot
in live action Grinch
is a Dutch angle.
Like it's just constantly skewed.
Like they cannot center the camera.
They cannot like focus
or balance it whatsoever.
The camera is like in a centrifuge
the entire time.
Well maybe that's to symbolize
that the whole movie is taking place
inside a twisting falling snowflake
which you see at the beginning.
Wow.
It was really fucked up
how the Grinch just tied up St. Louis who
and he just shoved her through
the fucking trash compactor
in the postal office.
She didn't deserve that.
That didn't fit into his theme
of killing only the fools
who deserved it
who liked Christmas.
She didn't even like Christmas
at that point in the movie.
What the fuck Grinch?
That was, you know,
I would have called it a gizomed
Coots Verk if it wasn't for that one moment
but it really broke my immersion.
You know, I wish that at the end of 7
Brad Pitt's character had said
oh yeah, well guess what?
Secretly, I'm you the whole time.
I'm Tyler Durden.
You killed your own wife.
So, how do you like that?
Bitch.
And maybe Christmas isn't so bad after all.
And then Brad Pitt carved
the stuffed who beast.
He got the greatest drift of all
that Christmas.
His wife's sever head in the mail.
You know what?
Kevin Spacey just wanted to teach him
the true meaning of the holidays.
You know what is like
the worst, most decadent convenience
that we have?
Yeah.
By which I mean it's a good thing
but I lack the self-control
to have it in my life.
It's having YouTube
on the PlayStation 4.
On the TV.
Because every night I lay down
and I'm like oh boy,
I'm gonna watch a movie.
What great fucking movie
will I expose myself?
I'm gonna expand
by cultural palette,
by watching a great movie tonight.
And instead it's like
oh no wait,
I better listen to Noah Caldwell
Gervais talk about
Baldur's Gate for three hours.
Yeah.
Damn.
Hey, you know on that
I just watched the first time.
Totally worth it.
I just watched it.
Yeah.
After all the...
It's worthless but I like it.
Yeah.
It's great.
I want more of it all the time.
The new Quentin Serentino movie,
Sharon Tate,
what's his name?
What's that?
Roman Polanski.
I went and I watched
Rosemary's Baby
with Michelle just the other day
and it was great.
It was like the first
like modern horror ever made
or something.
It was pretty fucking dope.
Way into it.
Highly recommended.
I've always been like
for a while there
I was just totally enraptured
in the typhoon of YouTube content
and I would basically consume it
to the exclusion of all other things
but I've recently like
really flipped that around.
I'm almost exclusively...
Like I do watch some YouTube series
there's a specific one
that I think Hippo's also watched
about a guy walking across Wales
in a straight line.
Fantastic.
I like that a lot
but like I barely watch
eating like vlogs
or anything like that now.
Now it's all movies
and all like real pieces of art
that I actually enjoy
and it's fucking fantastic.
It's so good.
My audible has never gotten
as much use as it has
in like the past like two months
and it's fantastic.
I should get into some of those books.
On the one hand there's like
oh don't consume like
easy to consume content
because it's not as rich as
the rich content that you know you like more.
It's good.
Yeah but like
I have had this sort of like
in the back of my head
in the back of my mind for like ever
that I should get around to
experiencing every video game
that I have
whether I got it in a sale or for free
I should experience all of them
in my library.
I should you know
watch all of these movies
that I've been meaning to watch
all these TV shows
and I found that it's just like
it's just stressful thinking
that I have to do that.
100%.
Like I would much rather
not give a shit
and then be like
oh yeah I'd never seen
like Die Hard.
I still haven't seen Die Hard
and I'd be like
oh what the fuck
you'd never seen that
and I'd be like yeah
what are you going to do?
You want to fight about it
or kill you?
Kill me?
100%
because that's another project
that you'll have in your mind
you'll get more and more
an option overload
you'll get more and more things
like oh gotta do this
and I gotta do this
and we'll just clutter up your mind
you really gotta reduce
as much clutter in your brain as possible.
You know what I think is the
the issue with that
I think we all as human beings
we perceive the world as though
we're immortal
we really from like
as soon as possible
should start to rationalize
like okay I'm going to live for 80 years
like did you did in that one big
vlog where he broke down
like I've got like 80 years to live
I want to consume like
every anime ever made
I've got this much time
I'm going to sleep for this many hours
I've got exactly this many hours
to like work
and this may to enjoy media
like what am I going to
slot into that time
makes a lot of sense to do things that way
sounds like the worst possible way to live
I mean maybe, maybe
it seems to work for him
specifically with his career
and the fact that he just does
like watching anime a lot
but like for me
I guess when people give you money
for watching anime
yeah it makes perfect sense to do
80 years watching anime
I could technically
I mean get paid to do
like to experience media
and then tell you about it
it's just that I got bored of that
and I stopped
you know
like it's something that I'm not
as into
I think most people will eventually
and like it just
it weighs on my mind this idea that
I don't know
I should get around to certain things
because so much of what I do consume
is people telling me about
video games that are good
let me tell you
you don't have to worry about all that
because anything you're thinking about consuming
is nothing but a trick
is nothing but a lie
placed before you
by the capitalist hierarchy
in order to siphon power away from you
and towards them
don't trust any of it
oh my god
what about this copy of Das Kapital
especially Das Kapital
yeah
no
unironically agree
I feel constant guilt
every time that I consume
any piece of media
because like
I've consumed enough fucking media
I've seen everything
I've read everything
I should be
instead of
continuing to watch movies
and read comics and shit
should I not be like
in Budapest right now
or like seeing something for myself
you know
traveling the world on camelback
yeah
no I feel ya
as opposed to like playing the new JRPG
which I feel
probably would get a lot more out of like
I don't know
visiting Myanmar
visiting China
seeing
I don't know India
probably you know
but of course
but you don't have
but you don't
but you can't have the freedom
to do cool stuff like that
because you've got loved ones
who go
where'd you go
why aren't you with me
this
so you know
all you can do is just
waste your fucking life
continuing to consume media
and wishing you were other places
god I hate my loved ones
you know
it's the ultimate trap of capitalism
having loved ones
I agree
Tom Tom
hey
travel's never done anything for me
with all these things
you gotta look at
your own personal
sort of situation
that you're in
like for me
I think we talked about this
on an old PCP a while ago
but I
only
I built a very tall empire
I didn't really branch out
of the few
stories and movies that I had
and I basically just
watched them over and over
so I'm pretty
immediate illiterate
and so I feel like
you know
I can't really travel
anymore than I already have
I've already
went on this giant fucking
globe-trying adventure
last month
for 30 days
where I raced across
and over and over again
but you know
I can't do that anymore
and I'm gonna be in college
for a while
I'm just gonna buckle down
with some movies
because I only watch
YouTube videos
that's not good
I'm gonna get something
I'm gonna get something else
in my body
there's definitely
what you do specifically
there's definitely like
a trap
that I fall into a lot
which is like
all or nothing
for a thing
like
ah man
media sucks
I should do everything
other than media
like it has to be
all good or all bad
so whatever is bad
it's all good
but traveling is often
really annoying
and when you get to a place
unless the view is nice
unless it's actually
a nice place
it's just the same
as where you were
there's a pavement
there's a car
there's a guy
maybe he speaks in gibberish
but you know
it's just
it's mostly the same
some nonsense gobbledygook
because humans have like
you know
they've made the world
the same place
basically
it's habitable
you'll survive
you're talking about
traveling right now
traveling yeah
like
like the thing
that the reason
the video series
about the guy
walking in a straight line
across Wales
is so interesting
is because
he is like
I thought you meant like
Wales
yeah yeah
it's like the same word
or something
it must be tough to like
get the Wales to like
form a straight line
oh my god
it is
that's my favourite part
um
that's literally what
I thought you were talking
about before
I just didn't say anything
cause I thought
I thought like
everyone knew about it
and I'd be the only one
like ah this guy doesn't know
about the dude walking
across Wales
what a fucking dummy
the thing that's so great
about it is because
it's in a straight line
he has a little GPS thing
he has to go through
people's property
and he has to
sneak past
farmers
and their houses
and he has to like
um
you know
constantly be on the lookout
if there's like
a cold river
there's like
a raging torrent
he has to cross
and it's like
he has to like
make a decision
whether to cross
this very very dangerous
river
or like
deviate like
20 meters from his path
and go around
20 meters
and go
go around to a rickety bridge
and it's like
it's
turning this
it's turning
the world that we live in
which is very
you know
um
it's all chopped up
and all like
managed and
sorted out
and there's paths everywhere
and there's road signs
everywhere
and you'll never be
perfectly alone ever
and he just
bucks the trend
by smashing through
all the boundaries
that we've put up for ourselves
all these fences
and barbed wire
and it's such
it's like a real adventure
even though
um
Wales is a very small country
and he's going not that
very far
but it just feels so epic
because it's
it's a
it's an aspect of travel that
you know
you would never
you would never bother
to like go over a fence
when there's like
a fence gate
like a couple meters
down the road
that's the genre
of human madness
that I can respect
I agree
I mean
I love
I love the straight line
Wales guy
as much as another person
I've
I've watched
like every video
like on repeat
for like every night
for the past
like two weeks
that's like my one
that's my one YouTube
that I watch exclusively
basically
it's great
but I will say
that I completely
disagree with like
everything is like
the same
I know you're
saying exactly the same
but like
it's even the pavement
even just the buildings
yeah
they are buildings
yeah there's hospitals
everywhere
but even that
there's so many different
unique things
all right
sure
what I meant by that
not that everything's the same
like you go to India
and it's like
I could have done this
at home
like you obviously couldn't
there's definitely things
to see in the world
but you don't
like seeing things in the world
doesn't take very long
and if you stay
in a place for like
more than two weeks
you're like yeah I get it
like
I disagree
the reason to stay
in a place
is not just to be
in the place
I mean that's
maybe you took that
as like part of it
but a lot of the time
travel doesn't include that
because I don't know
people in the world
and I'm like
I can't talk to strangers
but like
if an opportunity arises
where I could go
meet somebody
in a different country
that would be
way cooler
a lot of the reason
I agree
is because I like to
explore the place
I mean it's all about
the place for me really
I mean I just like
well surely the culture
of the people
like I'd like to see
this built by
the gaps and
yeah
well I mean
it's all tied together
we all have different
acclimation times
you know like
some people like
be in a space for like
an hour
they're like
I get it
whatever I'm used to it
other people can take
weeks to really
getting gross
and like the subtle
differences
it really depends
on the person
what I love
going to a new city for
is I love
getting all in the nooks
and cranes
and all the dense
parts of it
and all the local places
that I know
and we're all in a big
unbroken series
of dominoes
falling
oh my god
I'm obsesion of the world
I exclaim
like every three seconds
living in Boston
I'm with you
and it's great
I mean definitely
I get that
I've just never
never found that like
compelling
it's not that I don't
it's kind of interesting
like oh yeah
and then I just
don't give a shit
and I go back to watching
I definitely feel that
sometimes
but like
I don't know
I've been to quite a few
places
it's nice
but like
I guess I just
never feel comfortable
enough
like I always feel like
like home bases
like home
home
and I can't really like
relax
and
like I like exploring
but only for like a day
or two
and then I'm like
it becomes a chore
it becomes like
there's so many places
to see
that seeing all of them
is impossible
and so I have to like
map out like the perfect
places
or maybe hire
a tour guide
and I'm like
I don't care about fucking tours
even though they're probably great
I just hate the idea
of paying someone
to just walk me around
when I could do that myself
like when I was in Japan
basically the most
interesting places I went
like I walked around the city
plenty
and since I like
wasn't with people I knew
I didn't really know
the sites to go to
it's like you're just
walking by like
a bunch of closed doors
and you're like
not talking to anyone
you're not engaging
but when I had guides
like for example
one person I met
was like a native
a Japanese dude
I was in my little friend group
while I was there
and he like
knew Kamiket
and he took
which I don't know
if you guys know
like did you
it's like the biggest
yeah it's the biggest
dojin thing in the world
in this big famous
place in Tokyo
like he was our guide
and he's like
oh you guys want to go
I will be your guide
and he helped us
get to Kamiket
I went there
had a great time
and like
I wouldn't have known how
or like
why to do that
if I didn't have a guy
or like
when I went to
Mount
with the Kuro Tamago
the black eggs
on these hot springs
on a mountain side
which was like
the highlight
it was like
the naturalistic highlight
of going to the place
which is just this amazing
hot spring covered mountain
obviously because
there's volcanic activity
underneath it
where they just
hard boil eggs
and they turn black
from the sulfur
and it was like
a magic religious experience
it was so fucking cool
but it's only because
I had a guide
who like knew the area
I was able to like
even know this place
existed
let alone get there
but that's amazing
that's the sort of like
that's the sort of stuff
I live for
just being able to
get on something local
and get and just
really experience
what kind of people do
in other places
just like
and this isn't just like
for a broad thing
I feel this in America too
I mean I was just going up
and down California
and even though
you know
America's very homogenous
in a lot of
a lot of
a lot of ways
just going to different towns
like for instance San Francisco
one big thing about there
super vertical
it's not like a adventure too
it's real life
and it was
it was just like man
it's so different here
and over there
here's a really historic pier
oh my god
it's existed for a billion years
look at those seals over there
I'm in raptured
in euphoria right now
like it's like
I have no like
reservations about
feeling not at home
I like just
like immediately
wherever I am
I sink into just a sense of
I want to know everything
like what's the temperature like here
is it a little bit different
it's a little bit of humidity here
look at these buildings
they're like a different
architectural style
than I've seen before
and it's just
it's just a constant stream
of just joy
whenever I travel anywhere
just constant
I know what you mean
you're saying all the right things buddy
I remember when I was in Rome
I was with my family
and you know
I loved them dearly
and we did all the coliseum
all those sort of tour stuff
but my favorite parts
were just walking around the city
because they were just
a bunch of beautiful
bridges we could go over
or really just I did
because I was walking alone
and I would sketch things
in my sketchbook
and I would talk to the people
I must have done this
on the PCP before
somewhere
but on the last day
we had Mr.
and we were had
an extra day in Rome
that I could spend in
and I was sketching
the alter patriotism
which I've talked about
many times before
because it's got a kick-ass funny name
and there's this
there's this like Muslim girl
next to me
who was in hijab
and she was like
oh you draw an anime
I was like
yeah
and then we talked about anime
for a little bit
how she's going to become a manga artist
oh wait
where was this
this was in Rome
this was in Italy
I was sketching
like a big monument
and then we had a nice little conversation
and then she had to go with her dad
and I said goodbye
and it was great
it's just great talking to people
just strangers
yeah man
that's like the
that's awesome
I have a story
when I was teaching
physics in Poland
all my students
were
they were all from Saudi Arabia
and
one day I come into the classroom
late
as I often did
Lamal
and
they're like doodling
on the
whiteboard
and one of them
one of like the most
talkative ones
who I like
I talk to the most
he's like doodling on the white
and he's drawing like
an anime girl
he's drawing like an anime
and I'm like
hey
I think like after class
I like talk to him about anime
or something a little bit
like I asked him like
I don't even remember
what we were talking about
but it came up
and he was like
yeah
yeah I love anime
but you know
we're not technically allowed to watch it
because the king
fucking banned it or whatever
and I'm like
what the fuck
are you fucking kidding me
it is subversive
it should be banned
yeah our literal king
we
from a country
king
just decreed that like
yeah no anime
I mean Gibbs got one of those
almost
yeah I don't think it's the same thing
it's different though yeah
I forget if it was Iraq
or Iran
but in one of those countries
music was banned
for a little while
like just music
oh my god
that can't be true
that can't be right
I've seen
I've seen Footloose
actually I haven't
the true story of
I don't know
the Arab Emirates
or whatever
yeah I think so
I think so
well
they got jet packs over there though
that's pretty sick
what have we learned
anime is universal
and brings people together
across cultures
it literally does
well
and like media
so we must destroy it
like media with
universal human values
brings human beings together
what a shock
imagine that
just like my favorite movie
by David Fincher
Brad Pitt
fucking goes the shit out of that guy
get the whole thing
it's all just been
secretly the movie topic
oh hey hey
it's not a left turn
of a little bit of a story
from yesterday
it's not a long one
it's very short
but it's just
I was going to pick up Michelle
from work
and me I'm going
doop de doop de do
walking out the store
locked the door behind me
from de dump de dump
I realize
oh no
I've locked the door
and I don't have a key
I turn around
and I go back to open the door
it's locked
I think to myself
no big deal
perhaps Michelle is a key
call her real quick
nope she left her key
at home that day
okie dokie
I go doop de doop de doop
over to my landlord's house
knock on the door
knock knock knock
no answer ok
give him a little ring
ding ding on the telephone
phone
sorry I'm in Michigan
right now
I say whoop de doop de doop
I've made a mistake today
what do I do now
so I call
I call a locksmith
I Google locksmith in Cincinnati
and luckily
I don't know if you guys are aware
there was a thriving
extremely competitive industry
of locksmiths
for exactly people
in this situation
and these people
a lot of dumb people in America
a lot of dumb asshole retards
such as myself who locked themselves
out of their house
and every possible check and balance
gets fucked up
so I just call the very first one
and I'm like hey can you come
like pick my lock
and let me into my house
and they're like
yeah we'll be there in like an hour or two
got another appointment
so here I am
dump de dump de dump
waiting for this guy to show up
and by the way
this this doop de doop
there's no payoff to this
to this bit I'm doing
that's just not just happening
so whatever
like Michelle comes home
we're just waiting for the guy
to show up
so whatever
he just picks the lock
he gets in
it's effortless
this man is definitely a criminal
these people have way too much power
and you know I wasn't thinking
about this at the time
but when like the locksmith shows up
Michelle's just kind of
sitting in the entrance way
inside
and the guy goes in
and like he picks it
he goes inside
Michelle had like gone into the bedroom
which I thought was a little bit rude
I was like don't you want to like
thank the guy
and then afterward I'm like
hey you know that guy was here
I didn't want him to see me
because I don't trust locksmith
they have too much power
he could do
he could do anything
he could do anything to this place
he could know where I live
and that's totally fair
that's totally fair
he was a good guy
but I don't trust anyone in the world
that reminds me of him
who are you
and how'd you get in here
I'm a locksmith
and I'm a locksmith
is that Leslie Nielsen
yeah
that's a good one
I had a
when I rented a car
I moved my stuff
from Georgia Boston
I called a
I locked myself out of the rental car
and I called a guy
and the guy just had these fucking
he had a thing that he just inserted
into like the
the side
like the gap between the doors
and he just inflated it
and like the balloon pressure
just like squeeze the door open
like bent the door enough
that he could slide like a
what do you call it
like a fucking like wire thing
and like blow the lock up
like this guy can just get into
literally any car
you know
I had a tool
I could have easily gotten into this
but by the way
like while we were talking
he just one of the things
he asked me was like
hey so are you a student
I guess I look youthful
oh thanks for saying so
I just
I'm like no no
I actually
I came out here
working with like a
there was like a program
he asked you because you looked dumb
and he thought you needed
to learn a thing or two
yeah that's probably
he's looking for an apprentice
I just had
no I mean I was
I was a computer programmer
but I actually just quit
the other day
and now I'm a YouTuber
okay
what did he say to this
I mean
I answered his question
he didn't know before that point
that a stranger
could be disappointed
well he just
like as he was leaving
he was like oh yeah that's
interesting and then as he was
leaving he's like hey man
like where do I
where do I look you up
and I was like oh well
I'm best guy ever
on YouTube you can
and but then I realized
what am I doing right now
I'm like giving this guy
like if this man wanted to
he knows where I live
and he knows what I do
you just doxed yourself
I guess I doxed myself
to this one man
I probably just shouldn't have
to anyone else
it would have been fine
but to a locksmith
to a locksmith specifically
like what if this guy
is a crazy obsessed fanboy
or just like maybe
maybe he hates me
stop stop
stop right now
you think your locksmith
is going to go to your channel
like oh best guy ever
that guy from early on
let me look him up right here
have you seen
my favorite shows dude
oh my god don't act
like I'm getting a big
fucking head or something
no we gotta
we gotta fast forward
fast forward three weeks
in Nate's life
he's just
he's just sleeping
soundly
and here's a rattle at the door
and all of a sudden
he turns over
he goes back to bed
that couldn't be anything
and all of a sudden
there's his eyes
staring at him
he's just like
you fucking asshole
where the fuck is best anime ever
goes to the shell, Nate
you fucking assholes are acting like
this is such a crazy thing
to be concerned about
literally having like
a public platform
and you know
telling people about it
and like telling them
how to break into your fucking house
that one person in the world
knows where you live
and that you have a YouTube channel
it's funny that the person
who's the most worried about it
is the one who doxxed himself
and we're all just like
yeah whatever
I never make a mistake
now I know
now I fucking know
it probably
god damn it
you people are assholes
shut up shut up to the locksmith
watching this episode right now
thanks for the story dude
no I'm with you
I understand
okay thank you
because like absolutely
nobody in the real world
knows anything about what I do
and that's the way
it's going to stay forever
that's mine
nobody in my family
they all think that like
I don't know that I
what do you do I'm not like
no one
I don't associate with people
who understand what YouTube is
that's the way that I keep
my life right
I do not associate with
the YouTubers
yeah I'm with you
everyone in real life
thinks I'm a failure
and they're not far off
what the fuck is that
are you not aware of that
I think it was originally a vine
that was an Indian boy
using an impolite word
for the African American community
saying
I do not associate with
you know
and then he said a bad word
but it was really funny
you know
both of you guys
Nate and Ben
yeah
maybe this is
maybe this is like
a cultural thing
or a class thing
but that's the first time
I've ever heard a
locked myself
out of my something
story
that ended with
I called the locksmith
and not
I smashed my own fucking window
and broke my own fucking door
down
and threw a fit
because that's how
we handle those situations
in my world
it crossed my mind
but like
my apartment's weird
it's on like a second floor
I did not know that
locksmiths were a people
that you could call
in such a situation
well well
okay maybe I should have
because this fucking fee
this is a hundred and fifty
dollars
what the fuck
what
yeah
so I was right all along
I didn't call a locksmith
I called
well I called AAA
okay AAA
it was my call
Nate you should have done
you should have just gone
to Udemy.com
spent fifteen dollars
taught yourself how to
pick locks
and then be good to go
I okay
let's not act like
I didn't spend a twenty
minutes on YouTube
trying to find techniques
to pick my own lock
alright
cause I did
they just didn't work
or I didn't
could you
my dog was inside
and it was getting close
to midnight
and it was his birthday
it was his birthday
in like one hour
I had to say
happy birthday
I couldn't wait
please it's my dog's
birthday
he's fair
okay
the house that I live in
right now
when I moved in
my friend John
he gave me a key
but I lost it somewhere
and I was like
well shit I don't have a key
but I realized that
like our door sucks
and I can literally
just like Jimmy
the outdoor lock
with a credit card
and so for like
months and months
my key to my house
was just a credit card
that I would jam into the
doorway
and open the lock
worked easy
every time
Nate called a locksmith
he's like
I gotta get him
it's my dog's birthday
and he's like
oh Lord Shoshesh
this guy ever
is that you
I've been following you for years
look around
no that's
he just
he just casually says
Seshio
he's like I didn't tell you
my dog's name is Seshio
oh shit
I remember
the room I'm in
you could have looked up
like how expensive
it would have been
to replace the window
rather than
to hire a locksmith
it may have been cheaper
you call the locksmith
you tell him what's up
you say
all that happens
he says oh Lord Seshio
you say
I didn't tell you my dog's name
so I know
I already let myself in
and you
and he slowly opens the door
and you look inside
and the locksmith is in there
him and Seshio
both wearing
he's wearing your clothes
he's with Michelle
you know what
he's better than me
he knows how to pick locks
and I don't
the room I'm in right now
I was locked out
of mere months ago
I'm in
Kazzy's dad's bedroom
right now
and so
we got locked out
me and Kazzy
and a peculiar thing about this
is that there's a balcony
there's a balcony
we're on the top floor
so we got locked out
our phones are in there
we can't call
for anyone
her dad's out
I can't get to my computer
or my phone
or anything
so we're just
I'm faced with the prospect
of watching TV all day
which sounds like
literally worse than dying
so I think
okay
what am I willing to do right now
watch cable
or risk suicide
I think I'm going to go
with the suicide option
so I go to the top floor
and I'm getting ready
to throw myself off
the roof
and onto the balcony
trying to angle myself
so I can get in a side door
like a patio door
into my bedroom
and I'm like
I'm heave hoeing
I'm getting ready to do that
um
you know in Kirby 64
after you beat a level
and Kirby like heave ho
heave hoes
we're getting ready to throw
himself at whatever food
if you angle in the 64
correctly
I'm getting ready to do that
but eventually
I just look up
like a long enough
YouTube tutorial
where I like fully dismantled
the door knob
and it's just ease
outside from the socket
and there's
ease nothing there
like a plank of wood
that eases the door
and I just like
like break it open
and then I'm back inside
of my glorious
glorious phone
and then I break the cable box
just for good measure
way to go
yeah cool
so all I'm saying
is I didn't have to have
a locksmith's worry about
you know
learning about park road
dude 91
or spirit silence
and you know
trying to take in my identity
smart move
you know
speaking about like
media
right
is it like
watching media is like
who cares
you've you've seen enough
or like you know
we could cut down
on the amount of media
but like
is that then
immoral to be
a person who aspires
to create
more
yes
yes definitely
to add to the pile
100%
yeah
all right
no I'm gonna go hard no
why so Nate
why do you think
that was a joke
I didn't hear the question
that was the most in tune
Ben and I have ever been
about anything
you said is it moral
to create more media
with more
yeah
in a world
where there's too much
distraction
is it immoral
to make
that's complete
false equivalent
I don't even understand
the question
I mean it's a fine question
I'm just throwing
that sort of like
thought into
I'm just throwing
sand
available
well actually
I actually like
the shirt
that has the character bio
of the guy who likes
Greg Poupon
and is retarded
I like that guy
the most actually
but okay
like in a world
where like
you are distracted
by too much for many
is it like a different
question
than like
is the amount of media
bad
yeah I mean
my thought process
would go to
I get the other side
but my thought process
would be like
this is something that
as the world
like we can't
we can't
unless we're willing to like
suppress the world
it has to be something
that individuals
like control in their
own lives
I mean maybe
there's a way
we could like limit
how much media people
are able to consume
and then we just give them
like the best and most
useful stuff
but it's gotta be
the individuals
hold on
okay okay
we mean by like
like what do you mean
by this Hippo
is that like
people watch too much
YouTube right
is that the basis
of this
like this was totally
like a devil's advocate
sort of like
thing
I don't actually
I would still do it myself
I'm not like
worrying about that
so I haven't thought about it
to such a degree
I'm just trying to think like
I do it
I do it in the first place
because it's immoral
hmm
that's what I like about it
there's no contradiction
of like
you being an artist
and you not consuming art
with like
every single moment
of your life
like
it's not a matter
if you're
if you think to yourself
like okay
listen
I really like media
but you know
I gotta do other things
like myself
or I gotta go to work
and I gotta do this
this and this
like I can't
like I get distracted
too easily by media
that's not you saying
like
media is bad
and other people
shouldn't like
like
what I was implying
okay
that was what it was
like a potential
like is like
media on the whole
bad for humanity
no
it appears in the human
condition
I mean that's
no
I mean
I totally agree
that too much
media consumption
is bad
here's the thing though
we have to understand
that the problem
isn't even the abundance
of media
it's the facts
that the vessels
we have to deliver us
these media
are being designed
like with teams
of psychologists
to get us addicted
yeah
okay
like there's no
people are gonna
make stuff
and show it to each other
right
no matter what
there's basically
no point
I mean
art is fine
it's capitalism
that's bad
well
just to think
think of how much better
YouTube was before
it started shoving
recommendations
in your face constantly
it was just your subscriptions
it was never
taking over your life
it's not art
that's the problem
it's this
sort of
fake art
or fart
for short
which is
you know
created by teams
and corporations
and stuff
to turn you into a drum
think about it
if there were no profit motive
anyone
would anyone make
a like
fucking
I don't know
top 10
would people make top 10
list or would people make
whatever
there would be a smaller subsection
yeah I mean
did you would
they would only use people
like them
okay
okay okay okay
well
yeah but would there be nearly as
there would be like
one thousandth of as many
watch mojo would not exist
I mean
it's popularity still a thing
because people
really like them
a lot of people
really really like
top 10
yeah but nobody
but like
people don't make them
okay maybe did you
makes them
because he wants to make them
but like most people
don't make them
because they want to make them
I mean
in this scenario
people still want to be
popular
liked and have their video
right like that's
like we're saying
like there's no money
there's no incentive
but I think
I mean just as one example
popularity is the incentive
over money
so if it'll just
like one real life example
even now
he never got a lot of like
Patreon support or anything
but he was pretty popular
and had popular top 10 lists
so I mean
I assume the goal was to
eventually make more money
off of it
nobody's like talking about
Sai and how cool he is
or
well yeah
but they did watch his videos
you know they were popular
I mean people clicked on them
well his videos were
widely seen
it remains to be proven
whether anyone actually
watched them
well
okay
maybe just
you know
view-botted and
sub-botted
unlikely but I mean
people definitely saw them
but whatever
I agree
well why are we talking about Sai
I mean I feel like
more and more
like I remember
like you know
for a while Hippo
you were off
YouTube
and off Twitter
and then I'm off Twitter
I'm slowly getting back into it
and I wasn't really
off YouTube
but I'm curbing it still
I feel like
I've
like retained the same
sort of thing
and you probably would agree
that it's not like
any of those things are
inherently bad
like one of those things
is just like
I'm being forced to do this
not by like
an outside force
like with a gun in my head
but just like
like my brain
really wants me to do this
oh god
oh well I have to take this off
cause it's just so bad for me
it's like a tool
you know
it brings me joy
which is why I want to do it
it's just
you know
too much joy
and too little time
means that you're not gonna
have time to do things
that actually matter
it's just a matter
of like
you know
focusing your time
it's not a matter of
like any of those things
being bad or you know
it's just a matter of
outkitting
speaking of Twitter
we're talking about
my booming new
Twitter business
of selling yang 2020
shirts
on Twitter
they're everywhere
they're a sweep
in the nation
I've got celebrity endorsements
everyone is getting it
everyone is getting on
this train
I got
Boogie2988
Monkey Jones
I got
Christine Weston Chandler
Best of All
Lightning Bliss
they're all yang gang
they all say
in unison
in one voice creepily
by Ben Shirts
on Twitter.com
sort of development
I think like three out of
four of those people
are like in the midst of
PR disasters
yeah
and it was so important to them
it was so important to them
that they get this message out
because UBI is the future
automation poses a threat
to the modern worker
it's the war on normal people
and the opposite of
Donald Trump
is an Asian guy
who likes math
you can take that one
of the bank
my friends
Ben
did you Photoshop those images
what the fuck
get the fuck out of here
who the fuck are you
how fucking dare you
that's libel
libel
oh no
didn't MagiChan
have something to say about this
I don't know
MagiChan is a pretty reliable source
okay
no I want more answers
for MagiChan
right
because
I tweet out
Christine's
heartfelt endorsement
CWC
endorses yang
for 2020
because she needs the UBI
as much as anyone
so
Christine
so I tweet out the endorsement
and MagiChan
okay
MagiChan
he must be a boomer
or something
because he
he doesn't like
he tries to come in
and libel me
slander me
saying that the image
is photoshopped
right
he's in the pocket
of mainstream media
he wants to bury yang
just like they did
at the first
at the first debates
by turning off his microphone
so I ask him
like why don't you
support yang
like what's
what's the deal
what's up with that
and he tells me
right he tells me
that Lisa Simpson
yeah
and I am intrigued by this
and I just
I want to know
what's Lisa's platform
what's her stance on UBI
what's her
was she gonna
eliminate college debt
is she gonna build the wall
and
and I'm trying to get into
cause like I'll switch
right
if I find a better candidate
I will switch to supporting Lisa
just like
I just
I need answers
I need it
and I feel like
MagiChan is the only one
who can provide them
well then
like your shirt sales
have not just impacted
the lives of you
when your many
old customers
who have bought them
it's also impacted
the man that you represent
Andrew Yang
I don't know if you know
the spin
but minutes
after receiving the call
that your shirt sales
have broken
23,000
in the first two hours
Andrew Yang was found
celebrating
in Charlottesville
he was found dancing
in Jazzercising
he was so over
was that in
Charlottesville
I think so
I don't know
was that a meeting
with Christine herself
maybe
he was walking down the streets
and then
Chris Chan came over
and said hey
listen
you know about this guy
Ben Saini
he was like I watch the
PCP all the time
then he broke out and he
danced
he started doing
orange justice
he did the floss
man
all because of you
when do we have a gang
on an episode
it's about time
we've got to call
them that favor
eventually
well okay
no no no
he went on H3
he went on Rogan
why not us
no listen
Elon Musk too
aka Andrew Yang
was on H3 podcast
and on Joe Rogan
we've got to get
Elizabeth Warren
on the PCP
you guys come on
it's the next logical step
that makes sense
I don't think Ben
would be able to restrain
himself from murdering her
on site though
her boomerness
is through the fucking roof
no Warren's not that bad
Warren's basically
basically diet burning
which is
okay
it's fine
alright
anyway
buy my shirts
yeah that makes sense
teespring.com
slash yang
dash 2020
dash baby
link in the description
don't you want
don't you want to be
like boogie
everybody wants to be
Ben
like the amount of
mental pirouettes
and physical pirouettes
you must have done
in order to make
the eternal fencer
take a hard stance
take a side
how did you do it
you just can't argue
with math
okay
Andrew Yang
likes math
UBI is the future
the numbers don't lie
1000 is more than 0
okay
it's not that hard
of a decision
what's the debate
I literally don't
it's hard to argue
so
that's what I've been
doing this week
will you finally
stop all the other
bullshit you're doing
like comics and streaming
and finally
just dedicate yourself
to Andrew
Yang
absolutely
finally
finally I'm
accomplishing something
simple life
you know I've got
just on this general
side
I've discovered something
while we were talking
somebody turned me on
to this the other day
I haven't watched these yet
I haven't looked into them
but
I'm afraid guys
my time was up
I was in
the people thought
I was the gurren login guy
for quite a while
but I'm afraid that
a proud
YouTube junior
a guy
up and coming
to destroy me
and make me look like
a fool in an old boomer
has come on the scene
to reveal that
I've been wrong about
everything all along
with this video
first of all
why you should be
leftist
about gurren login
and I mean
I wanted to watch that
what the fuck
I haven't watched it yet
I'm interested too
shit yeah I saw that
and I thought
I gotta see this
and then I forgot
I need to watch it too
I'm not even shitting on it
I have not watched it
I'm interested to see
because I know this exists
in response to
to my videos
and I think
digis as well
but it's followed up
by another one
don't surrender gurren login
to Ann Capps
and I think this one is
even more
so directed at me
he's by the same guy
they are shonen ronin
I don't know this guy
he seems fine
obviously a leftist
that's cool
but
I just like to go on the record
I joke about being
an anarcho capitalist
it's really funny
I'm not actually
an anarcho capitalist
just to be clear on that
but
that's it
that's all I have to say
on this subject
I will watch this
I could be more heinous
a politics person
and an anime person
you know
not to be
not to shed on anybody
but I couldn't agree more
bringing
I'm aware that my world view
informs my thoughts
on anime and stuff
but to make it a hard line
you know me
don't like talking politics
in such terms
and you know
like this title
why you should be a leftist
I think we could agree
there's attributes
that are positive about that
I won't let you do this
Nate
you can't pretend as though
you're not
you don't also engage
in any political discussion here
you're not like half of it
well
I mean
what's the title of like
my video
it's just like
why Gurren Lagann is good
no I don't know
I'm not thinking about that
I'm just saying that
you are
you are a political
just talking about it
we do this all the time
on the piece of paper
well okay
now that's certainly true
but I'm not an anarcho capitalist
you could call me a libertarian
you know what my political views are
here's
here's my political stance
Andrew Yang
sounds like a fucking
mortal combat character
yeah
that's all I got to say about that
and he's as static as fuck
I don't know who this
Andrew Yang character is
but this Andrew Yang person
that's in real life
aka outside my apartment
so he's hanging out in the
salt splash beach
he's been just terrorizing
the citizens lately
and I'm really scared of him
have you seen that
have you seen this
so there's the Andrew Yang
platform
where you gain a thousand dollars
not even a good
mortal combat character either
I'm talking like
ultimate mortal combat 3
like one of the random
I think I know what you're
gonna say
I'm gonna say that
there's also the competing
platform of Andrew Yin
to the Yang
where you lose a thousand
dollars if you elect him
to the presidency
tough tough call
it's a tough choice
it's a tough call
Nate what if
we pose your hypothetical
what if you make your
you make some
not you
someone anyone
makes a video right
titles it in some
perfectly apolitical
X is good way
and then in explaining
why it's good
they implicitly endorse
a certain
a certain political
political or economic
worldview
I mean I would totally agree
to that but
I mean like
let's just take my video
for example
like what's my
like my main thesis
of the video
is that line about
like ask not for
lighter burdens
ask for broader shoulders
I think that's pretty
clearly like
not a leftist view
of the world
that is very much
so you're saying
it is political
no I'm saying
that I mean
there's explicitly
political where
you're advocating
for a specific
like team
which I think
saying why you
should be a leftist
is doing so
I find it
I don't really like to
talk in those terms
when I talk about these things
I have absolutely
no clue
what you're trying to say
I mean
you can advocate
for a worldview
without saying like
that's why you should
vote Democrat
or that's why you should
vote Republican
so your problem
why are you saying
problem
your problem is not
with something
being political
it's with something
admitting to
being political
well first of all
who's got a problem
there is no problem
against what
you're saying that it's
you're saying there are
negative aspects
to a title
like why you should be
a leftist
no I'm saying
I don't want to do that
so I don't
that's what I'm saying
it's that time again folks
it's time for this
there's no political
discussion here
it's just
it's interesting to say
there is
there is Nate
I mean to label me
an ANCAP
I didn't do that
even though
you could probably
make a pretty strong
argument for it
but I'm not doing that
I mean how do you
resolve that with me
just saying I'm not
because I think
maybe you are
agreeing to many leftist
positions
well I mean
maybe
I don't know
you seem pretty in line
with that whole thing
you seem to be all about
personal responsibility
but I don't believe in
anarchy
I don't believe in anarchy
okay so
alright fine
okay alright
we did it
but that doesn't matter
you totally move the goalpost
did I
yeah we were talking about
something else
and then you say
okay but I'm not an ANCAP
and then the conversation
becomes about that
well I don't care
I don't care about that
okay
I want to know
I feel like the way
Nate moves the goalpost
is like
completely in a
klutzy way
he has no idea that he did it
he doesn't
what is
what's
how do you feel
okay how do you feel about this
why you should be a leftist video
I mean I think it's
well first of all
the why you should be a leftist
okay first of all
I haven't watched
either of them
I have not watched
either of these videos
okay me either
in the description
well rather in the comments
I see people being like
don't surrender to Nate and Digi
I see in like a couple of comments
so I'm inferring
that there's discussion
of our positions
I mean I know Digi's a capitalist
I'm sure of that much
as am I
no he made a video
like the other day
like saying that he doesn't like
ascribe any specific political
oh that's fucking dumb
he has he believes in things
on the left or the right
I mean I guess he's a capitalist
oh yeah
I don't fucking know
I think it's
oh yeah I have no
I have no opinion about anything
no that's not fucking it
he has opinions on
I just think everything's fine
as it is
I don't really think
that's the position
I am a neoliberal capitalist
Ben that's such a fucking straw man
that's the typical
centrist boogeyman
that people just make up
yeah that's what it means
it's not
when someone says they're a centrist
or that they don't believe
that they don't take sides
it doesn't mean that
they just believe in nothing
and they have no opinions
it means that their opinions
aren't fucking rigidly held
to one fucking moral standard
on one side of the fucking
coin or the other
yeah
if they have different beliefs
about different shit
did she didn't say
he believes in nothing
he just was like
making it clear
that he's not on the left
or the right specifically
if you're not on the left
or the right
then I'm sorry
but you're on the right
you're a neoliberal
that doesn't make sense
it literally does make sense
because the overton window
has shifted right
oh my fucking god
that is so dumb
it's not dumb
it makes perfect sense
if you understand
how neoliberalism works
can't you have complex views
of various political things
that put you neither on either side
you can want some things to change
but not the other side
are you saying that if you're
if we don't believe
that's not what I'm saying though
are you saying if we don't
agree with your perspectives
that we're on the right
is that
I mean like
when it kind of boils down to it
I'm saying
that if you take no position
you implicitly endorse
the status quo
you're not taking
no position
no one is taking
no positions
then
if you say you're not
it could just mean like
I think that people
should be allowed to have abortions
and I think people
should be allowed to have guns
that's two positions
it's not taking no positions
you have different opinions
about different issues
and you take them
one at a fucking time
right
those are both
conservative positions
oh they're not
what
having a being pro
oh sorry
I misunderstood
look
they're different axes
to be left or right on
I agree
the thing that is just
you're reacting
to my oversimplification
of a thing did you said
in a video
and you haven't seen the video
so just
I would rather people
like
don't
like make big assumptions like that
like
you know
yell at me I guess
don't yell
don't yell at didgy
for having things like
your case
we don't want to make any assumptions
that's just like
I don't want to make any assumptions
about the contents of these videos
I just thought the titles were funny
and I know that they're directed at me
and possibly did you to another degree
isn't that funny you guys
I'm gonna watch this later
and see what I think about
I think it's funny
I will also
agree
okay I understand what you're saying
about
okay I guess what you're saying
is that didgy says
he's not on the left or the right
because
he has
like
individual views on particular topics
and he is not entirely on one side of it
like yeah like
everyone is like that to a certain extent
that's all that anyone
ever means when they say
I'm not on the left right
north or south
I'm on the fucking
I'm on the fucking underbelly
that's what
that's what side I'm on
fair enough
well
there it is
I got a new thing to talk about
I made my first
rowdy fucker's cop killer
slime girl character
wait
oh god wait
I have one more thing to say
about what we just said
no no
the politics
the politics is over
slime only
one last thing
okay I understand that thing
about how you can have bits and pieces here
that are more
more conservative and more liberal
okay
but if you say
I'm not a capitalist
then what are you
if the answer is
nothing in particular
unless you have a specific thing
that you are
that is opposed to capitalism
then you are just saying
I already
then you are just endorsing
the status quo
no you're not
Ben
who is a capitalist
just with limitations
therefore a democratic socialist
or whatever
Ben how was he
well he's a capitalist
I think the
I guess
the thing there then
is that I
interjected incorrectly
because did you
I don't think said anything
about capitalism
he was talking about left or
right in the video I was watching
okay
well I already
solved this dilemma
like 50 episodes ago
when I invented
my political philosophy
and our co-fascism
right
you
legalize it
it's already a thing
I'm sorry
it's not already a thing
I invented it
it doesn't make any sense
it's not okay
first of all I take
more offense
drag has talked about it
I fucking set up
before god damn drag
who is drag
I don't care
never mind
I don't
I invented it
it's not a thing
well there you go
drag can go fuck himself
tell me about an
our co-fascism
oh my god
tell me
I already did this
on a previous episode
of this
can you summarize it
in a line
what's the
what's the thrust
it's cool
that's what it is
it's just what you're being cool
it's the philosophy
that the only
political systems
that will ever be
right and fair and just
are either
complete anarchy
or complete fascism
and everything in between
is a worthless
half measure
which makes everything
unfair and shitty
I invented that
it's my
thing
and I'm
I'm less offended
at you saying
it makes no sense
than you saying that
someone else said it first
maybe they have
a different definition
or something
I don't know
there's nothing new
under the sun
man
okay
slime
anyway
tell me about slime
I made a slime girl
I've seen
there are slime girls
in rfck
you don't do anything
gameplay wise
to create them
you just draw them
and then they're canon
yes
how does every single thing
in rck
sometimes
no some of them are
slime oids
that exist in game
oh yeah
that is true
true
yeah
but I made
I made one
and I think she's
pretty fucking cool
cause she's not like
the typical
beauty
slime
like fuck toy
slime girl
like all the others
slime girls
they're all just
fuck toys
they have
they have feelings man
they're all
even the sexy
it's no special
they have a sexy one
they feel
they're all sculpted with
bedroom eyes
like permanently locked
on their face
I saw this
in community service
when you first posted it
and I thought it was really nice
and I liked your fallup
gun girl comic
what do you have to say about it
I don't know
I apologize
okay
I like rfck
can we talk about that
just a little bit
oh we can
I'm afraid
you know
I don't know
I'm afraid that the more
we talk about
the more people are gonna hate it
who are on the fence
I have a feeling that
like the vast majority
of PCP heads
like know what it is
and they're like
oh god this should get
now I hate it for no reason
I think quite a few
have come to a decision
that they don't know
what that is
and they're not interested
in looking into it
for whatever right or wrong
you know whatever reason
I think a lot of the time
it's just because it's
mostly munchy and Ben
who are like
advertising talking it
yeah I suppose
it up
when is PCP university lecture
rfck
literally next time
we're literally next
oh my god
there you go
okay I should talk about it
if I want to
about the PCP lectures
alright so
like part of this whole
like
Christine Weston Chandler
endorses yang thing
which is canon
it really happened
it's true not photoshop
of course
like I was
I was reading
post time skip
post transition
sonichu
right
and this shit needs a lecture
like the desert needs the rain
okay
this shit is
fucking
oh I'm so glad
I'm so glad
fucking insane
I saw the Nazi
it requires charts
okay I'm literally
I'm gonna have to
need to draw charts to show
you know that song
you know that twin
is it twin perfect
who made that
that song
about the different dimensions
different to other
world dimension
yeah of course
foggy town
they all look
just the same
yeah we need
it needs one of those
for the son
for the sonichu canon
we should look into that
yeah okay
so and then
like a huge amount of it
is basically delivered
in like text dump
plus visual montage
okay and like
that works
fucking like
time traveling
Nazis come into it
and like
this whole other canon of like
this fuck some like
fucking visual novel
about like
CPU goddesses come in
and like
no explanation at all
in the text about
like what he's gonna talk
you have to know neptunia lore
to get that shit
there's like new
yeah okay it is
it really needs
some explanation
and I am the man
I am the man for the job
I sense I feel it in my bones
you know I'll just say
I too have a lecture
ready to go
cocked and ready to be black
I could do it today
if someone demanded me
of it I could do it today
so I'm just saying
when that next bad boy rolls
around
I'm ready to go
Brad cunt for when
one of these days
hey would you guys
let me know in the comments
would you give money
for radcon for kickstarters
oh no
would you do that
would you give us money
is that the official name
for radcon for
radcon for when
would you give us money
please
I think we have to abandon
the radcon for ever plan
the devourage
we suggest it
because it's not forever
it's far from it
it's
it's very limited time
only
if we can't
then high five rfckhq
happen way before pcbhq
and we're real and we're
actually cool
what's rfckhq
bam
I mean we both
we live in the same place
and now rfckhq is
only in person now
it's rfckhq
is it
boston
that seems a little bit
cheating
it's like
a city
why is it
cheating
how is it
an hq is not
a city
munchie
do I have to explain this
to your puny baby
the point of pcbhq
was never that
we would all live in
the same house
it was that we'd live
in the same
it was initially
the same house
it quickly became
gas
also can I
I know I'm not involved at all
but you have to
change the name from
rfckhq
to rfckapital
oh you know
that makes sense
what
die
uh oh
hey
weren't you in
who was that who just drew
a picture of tom
and rfck
that was
acro
that's right
it was sick
you were
weren't you the general
of the juvies or something
yeah I think it's
cause did I say that
in the last
rowdy fuckers copular stream
that was on
that I mentioned that
yeah
that would be tom oliver
king of the juvies
that's good
to worship juvie hova
take it
you know what
you can have it
no one wants that crown
it's yours for the take
the crown weighs heavy
just like the man himself
back in the day
he was
disrespected
but his legacy lives on
past everyone
it's a true crown of thorns
I'm thinking about
I'm thinking about continuity
I'm thinking
I'm thinking that
rfck
probably
takes place
in the same
universe
as a sonichu
c197
I'm thinking
I'm thinking tbap
probably does too
this is all like
I'm thinking
there's no reason
why these dimensions
can't like
you know
connect with one another
I did I see no reason
why
and also in my head
ever since
like the first
crossover
that I felt was
important
I can't remember what it was
but it was a pony thing
ever since then
I've always been
in my mind
like spinning
a web of like
connections
to connect everything
I've ever done
and like
and all my friends
all together
in a cool like
yeah you know
that could work
and you know
considering the unusual
amount of slime
grime scum
and villainy
in the city
the unnamed city
I believe
I'm thinking that
the movie 7
by David Fincher
probably takes place
in the same universe
starring Brad Pitt
Morgan Freeman baby
all fictional characters
exist in dimension
C197
and our dimension
dimension 1218
is merging with it
to create dimension
C
dash
whatever
it doesn't matter
our dimensions are merging
like zoos will be real
slime city
will be real
it's all
the movie 7
will be real
David Fincher
will finally at last
be real
yeah
so I will all live together
in harmony
the putty cast
and the pony cast
sail in the same ocean
oh yeah
magic hand says
that the
that the dimensional merge
is coming soon
and let's not forget
arm retrieval and potty cast
have a crossover
therefore all of homestuck
so that
so that all of homestuck
is canon 2
one piece
it's all in there
are you stealing your dads
I've always thought
that they're like
parallel universes
to rf2k
they're very similar
in a lot of ways
slime never existed
but oil did
well I
I imagine it's almost
like if
if stealing your dad
is like in the far future
from rf2k
where like
slime city just becomes
slime everywhere
like slime world
and then like
after it all progresses
slime is all dried up
but morals and society
is still fucked forever
and that's when
stealing your dad
takes place
okay that sounds good
boy
this went way off the rail
guys I'm so mad
let's bring it
I have to bring it back
to the political thing
I hate to be the bad guy
and bring it back to that
but because
because Ben brought up
that like
my hilarious and cool
political ideology
has been bow guarded
by smooth brains
all over the internet
you know I went on google
just to fact check
and make sure
and sure enough
there's an urban dictionary
for anarcho fascism
and just listen
you know
you heard how I defined it
you heard my cool
philosophy
what the philosophy
actually is
as created by me
global icon
and national treasure
endless jest
listen to how
these fucking
smooth brain
political fucktards
have butchered
my political philosophy
anarcho which
yeah
okay go on
sorry sorry
anarcho fascism
is based on the premise
that in post capital
in parentheses
cryptocurrency centric
societies
racial identitarianism
loses its stigma
anarcho fascism
or national in parentheses
nationalist anarchism propounds
what the fuck
propounds is not a word
I refuse to believe that
that only ethnic cohesion
can form self-referential societies
in the wake of capitalism's collapse
in the absence of
identitarian action
national anarchism believes that
capitalism specifically
global capitalism
will collapse into Marxism
the exclusive precursor
to 5G
in parentheses
fifth generation warfare
what the hell
they've butchered it
they've ruined it
yeah
what the fuck
that sounds very good
it doesn't make any sense
you know you know
it's just
how is anarcho
this is how
it was like a bunch of noise
it was noise
it was a bunch of meaningless
drivel and words
this is the problem
the world has been so fucking
poisoned with politics
that when someone comes up with
something that is pure
and hilarious and cool
like my anarcho fascism
wait
like a political system
yeah
what's the deal
immediately the world just takes it
and they just add words to it
and they add bullshit to it
and make it mean nothing
and make it a stupid meme
it was a fucking
it was a cool meme
I made a cool meme
and they made it stupid
because they added
what the fuck is this
is this like a real thing
I do hate when people make things
too grounded in real politics
Jesse what's the date of this entry
does your
June 19th
oh wait 18
I thought it was 2019
I don't know
does that predate
doesn't predate your state
it might but mine is better
my idea was so much better
my idea was pure
and it was funny
and it was cool
is a political ideology
how can you make it
too about real world politics
it's not a political ideology
it's me being cool
well I like Jesse's funny
definition better
that's how
I choose that one
between the two
you know I'm over here
you need to do
you gotta
you gotta make a shirt
like in clerks too
when randall is trying to take back
porch monkey
you have to make a shirt
I have to take back
anarcho fascism
you know I'm over here
I'm over here
just being cool
okay
I'm just trying to be cool
I'm just doing cool stuff
saying cool things
having cool ideas
and you know
they're simple
and anyone can understand them
and you hear them
and you go hey
that's pretty fucking funny
and everyone has a good time
I'm just here
making sure people have a good time
and over here
if you're gonna sell
a narco fascist shirts
please put them on a different site
don't put them on the pcp
teespring please
too late
why
because
Ben can't be associated
with his mortal enemy
yeah
I'm really sorry
that I don't want the pcp
selling fucking fascism
on t-shirt
I mean look
I don't thank you
I don't really give a shit
no one's making a t-shirt
you're getting nothing to do
with anything
I thought you said something about shirt
okay whatever
if Ben had the good graces
to put the yang thing
on his own thing
then let's keep all
political shirts
you know
my point is
no idea can just be
pure and funny and cool
someone has to take it too seriously
and turn it into a thing
with words
like identitarianism in it
and propounds
I sympathize
I truly do
with people
who are very concerned
about politics day to day
and they worry that the world
is going in bad directions
but certainly
we could all agree
that sometimes
you just want to be cool
and you just want to
hang out
and suck your own dick
if you don't
if you don't feel
like thinking about
real world politics
then maybe
maybe don't
talk about
an arc of fascism
like that's
that's
talk about something else
Ben it's not
it's not real world
politics
no one even believes
in an arc of fascism
you just described
real world politics
I did not
these are not real words Ben
what the hell does
identitarianism mean
well I literally
know the answer to that
but I don't want to
get into it
what the hell does
based on the premise
that in post-capital
cryptocurrency
centric society
is racial identitarian
loses its sigma
that's not words man
yes it is
it means
racism becomes cool
and everyone forms
that is not my
well that is not
my anarco fascism
that doesn't even
I know and that's why
I don't want to fucking
associate myself with this
that doesn't even
that doesn't even sound
like it should be called
anarco fascism
that should have a different name
like my
I really don't get the
anarco ass
okay you know what
I don't care
well it's anarco because
it's not imposed
from the top down
the whole point of
my bit is that
like it is
what it sounds like
like the words
are opposites
and that's why
it's funny
that's just what I thought
I was like
what is this
this is
this definition
that I'm looking at here
does not sound like
that
this is a measurable battle
this is a battle
which you can win
and the way
you win
is by getting
your definition so popular
it becomes the
number one definition
on urban dictionary
that's how you win
the battle
once again
society has conspired
to ruin one of
my bits
that's how it always
I'm a bit machine over here, and I'm just cranking out cool stuff and and hilarious
Witticisms and slogans and and and I'm making people have fun
I'm creating fun for the world, but the world just can't handle the world doesn't want fun any world in anymore
The world doesn't want fun the world just wants like weird political shit that they can argue about so they took they take all my fun
Bits and they and they corrupt them and they pervert them into this and it just makes me sad for humanity
You know when a character gets drunk in a party in a movie and the camera starts like wishing around
It's like a zoom in and out just like tilting over and over and over again
And then like the screen starts to fade black and the character falls on the floor. That's been me for like 35
All right, all right speaking speaking of UBI I've decided I no longer need UBI because I've found a way
I found a way to give myself a thousand dollars a month, okay, and it's fucking fantastic. Yeah, so it's called crying
With UBI you could have two thousand dollars. I guess I guess but but we all
You got me back on the train, but um so I
We've we've been long discussing the the energy drink wars, you know, we got the bansters Roman streets, of course
We got the C4 heads. I'm a newly formed C4. We got the rain
Fucking I'm a rain. I'm a rain now that 7-eleven offers two for one rain
You're a rain cyst. Are you saying you're a rain?
I'm a rain cyst. Yeah, rain. Rainsy rainsy rainsy in economics, baby
I've dabbled a bit here and there and all these these newfangled
Zoomer drinks, but I'm still I'm still clinging hardcore to the OG Red Bull
Red Bull is the best dude. So it costs like eight dollars a can. That's my point
This is the problem the big problem with Red Bull is that it comes in an 8.4 fluid ounce can on average
But it costs the exact same as a 16 fluid ounce can of any other energy drink, which is shit
But yeah, it is yesterday
I was crippled in my bed because I can't move anywhere and I needed groceries
So I decided to order Instacart from Aldi and Aldi has yes red
Thunder which is Red Bull, but not and it's you get a pack of four for three
Dollars and it is that has instantly given me like a thousand dollars a month back because I no longer have to spend like
60 to a hundred dollars on am I crippling Red Bull addiction? I can spend a fraction of the price
I have seen I have seen red Thunder at Aldi. Aldi is really good. I work if you like monster
I recommend gridlock. I also did I got the red one is the best one
I've not seen the red I got gridlock ultra-white and which pretty good
Yeah, but I'm still red ones hard. I'm still on team red Thunder for life. It's the best. They got the sugar free
It's good. Yeah less than a dollar a can like God intended instead of this three fifty to four dollar
Scalping that dude original does
Straight up super glad to hear you're an Aldi boy. Yeah Aldi Aldi is the shit
You know this is we actually buy quite a bit of Red Bull
I don't drink that much, but like Michelle, and I'll get it fairly really why I
Because it's it was there and we think Red Bull is good, but but now here
There's alternative energy drinks that are cheaper for more red Thunder
I'm looking at his red Thunder. It looks exactly like Red Bull except it was made by like a college student with a design instead of a
Professional, it's like okay. That's like that's like Aldi stick in general. They also have
super cheap
Slim Jim knockoffs. Okay. I bought like
36 of them for like seven dollars super cheap knockoffs of stuff. Yeah, it's the best
It's the best store of all time
Uh, it is the best and a bit and the only the only price you pay is that the place looks really ugly on the inside
And you have to loan them you have to loan them one quarter to use a shopping cart
I fixed that problem too because I got it with Instacart, so I paid three dollars and someone came to my door and gave me everything
That's worth here's the other the other trick about Instacart Tom is that you can get them to shop at like Costco and
BJ's and like places that you need a membership
They will shop at these play at these like bulk places for you and you don't need a membership for it
It's fucking so every time I use Instacart or the other time the whole time well
It says your shopper is now getting though. I go dance puppet dance for me. Oh, yes
Yesterday my cheap goods yesterday
I bought like five pounds of sausage and like big-ass bags of like mozzarella cheese and almond flour from Costco
Normally that would cost me like a hundred dollars or whatever for like a year's membership at Costco. Mm-hmm, and I fucking tricked them
That's this is fantastic. It's amazing. This is capitalism working as intended. All the amazing Instacart fantastic
Yeah, and now I have so much more money. The only thing that sucks about Instacart
It doesn't take my ebt card and then I could totally destroy the system for real. Yeah
Yeah, they don't you have to go it you have to go in person to use
It's because they the delivery fee and stuff doesn't count like you can't pay that with ebt
Yeah, I mean I they would just they would need the card they would need to have your card with them
It's sad sad, but true. I mean, you know, I think you can actually just like withdraw ebt from an ATM
That I'm pretty I haven't I haven't tried it, but I haven't tried it
It does it sure does
But I think it says somewhere in the literature that like you can do it
I think I think there's a different program. There's an ebt cash program
I don't think that's a standard ebt card that is that is different, but um, I'm I don't know
Maybe I'll try it at some point and like get back to you on it
But I think it said that like you can do it even with the food moral the story red thunder brings brings red bull back into the game
Hardcore it's a real competitor now and everybody needs to get on it
I like the system
Yeah, that ebt card issue makes me think that like wouldn't it be more practical if I don't know like maybe like
There's a lot of like, you know, layabouts, you know a lot of a lot of bums a lot of grifters and drifters
Couldn't we just like make them our property and just like give them purpose and have the state and force them sort of
Death explosion collar on them if they don't go get our groceries then we give them our ebt cards
We'll call it a slavery that sounds good and then we'll just you know make that be the system
Seems like
Uh
Well anything else or should we get to the voicemails? I'm down. I'm ready shit up. Let's get to the voicemails
Yeah, Ben. Oh, no, I was thinking about was there something else that we talked about before the show
No, I think it was mage. Yeah, mage asking who is CWC. We're just too many people too many people and I said shut up
Shut up. We'll talk about it on the show and then she left. Yeah
But scared off by our whatever I touched on that whole CWC time for everyone's favorite second
The voicemails now you may be thanking yourself all got a strap in for some really terrible audio content
Well, never fear. I was the one who picked out the voicemails on this one. So we only have five and
Frankly, I'm fine to like skip like this one
I just want to play it because this guy is another like I want to like publicly humiliate him because he's another one
The long string of people who just are I'm gonna do them the pathetics
So this guy's another pathetic who wants to come in here and like guys
How do I be like a baseline like level zero human being?
How do I like understand simple childlike concepts? Please explain to me how I can stop being such a like
Comically bad person. So let's go. Let's go to this guy with this society
You know, I got pretty like big list of friends and I'll like ask one of them to hang out
Uh-huh, and they'll be like, no, I got a girlfriend can't hang out. Sorry
Like I can barely
Logical because he has a fucking girlfriend and then I have another friend who's got like work and that's like, you know
More reasonable, but he's like, oh, I have to work all the time can't can't hang out
Sorry, and like, you know other stuff like that like just friends that are busy like all the fucking time
And I'm so busy with doing nothing like I don't have
Any of that and I just want to hang out with people and I rarely ever can so I gotta make new friends
New friends
Hey, man, you oh, he's still going cut it off cut it off. I've had enough
Look, man, you being an underachieving need is not your friend's burden
That's that's true. Yeah, that's 100 percent. This is sounds like you need a job in a girlfriend
Maybe maybe yeah, you should get a girlfriend yourself and then you too can know the joy of
Of ignoring your other friends of someone. Yeah, the the the best part about having a girlfriend is
Not being not being allowed to see your friend. Yeah, it's having an excuse to not talk to anyone
There's that I think you need to realize that uh, you know
If your friends wanted to hang out with you uh work in your girl and their girlfriends would not be an excuse
We're a hundred percent of the time like it seems to be with you. So it's obvious that you are busy being doing nothing
Obviously you have nothing contribute to them none in terms of monetary or anything like that
But just in terms of you know, you have no personality. You have nothing going for you
It might not be that he has what do you have that is that can supersede their monetary and sexual needs
That's what that's what comes down to uh
Just you gotta
Literally just be cool up your cool level. Just go grind your coolness by doing fun things that people aren't hanging out with you
Actually get an interest and a job or a girlfriend get anything just you know, stop doing nothing like a fucking freak
Why would you think anyone would want to hang out with you? You obviously have no redeeming aspects
Why would you go to the show the fact that you're watching the pcp right now and not slamming a fucking puts into the ground
That's like really upsetting to me and honestly
That's true. I am disappointed at every single one of you listening to this podcast instead of slamming a pus or yeah, that's fair
So this guy society you're going in the voice channel. I fucking hate you. You're another pathetic
You're just another one of the pathetic's lining up speaking of the pathetic's
We got another pathetic following up on his last pathetic display. So come on dance for me pathetic
Oh my god, we really went hard on that poor boy
Hi, I called in last time basically for emotional support because I was anxious about going to a movie alone
Going to see millennia mattress. Oh, right and thankfully might hear a munchie told me to kill myself
I didn't have to go to the movie and uh, maybe I'm used to discover that it was almost all other men who were alone
Who looked basically exactly there you go. There you go. Also millennia mattress
All right, so see we're making a positive different people's lives. Listen, you come on the pcp
You get the tough love you need. I tell you to kill yourself and then your life's fixed
I mean, I think there's no that I think it's just a win-win for everyone
No, it's a three-step process come on the pcb munchie. Tell us to kill yourself. That's it. You're probably solved
You don't clear in your reborn again
So that's I listen, you know, he came on here with like a pathetic like baby tear question
Oh, how do I like exist?
How do I breathe and fucking move my legs to the movie theater to sit down on my fat ass and munch popcorn
And not be scared that people are looking at me. He just did it and it was fine. There was no problem
He had nothing to overcome literally at all. This is what this is what the other guys gotta do
You know, you it's completely fine. You and your friends just hate you just stop being someone who they hate and then you'll be fine
Like it's not a big deal. Yeah
So no more pathetic. Let's give this something like normal people like like something just like a normal thing that like you like a real question
Toot the room other fuckers. No gimmicks or anything. I just got a totally normal ass question for you
What is the most human core thing ever?
Oh
Now I don't want I already know the answer, but I don't want to reveal it right now
Instead, I actually want to see what you guys think it is. Maybe talk about it a little and
I'll get back to you next week and I'll tell you what it is. I know
Only humans do this
Okay, nothing else does it and every human does it. Here's my here's my answer
Applauding in the crowd at a wedding as they just said like I do and everyone's applauding as they kiss
In the in the little thing up there
I've got another one
Uh thanking thanking your bus driver
I'm saying saying thank you when you get off the bus. I have like they did you a favor
I have what I believe to be the answer. I don't think it's going to be his answer
Yeah, but uh
The most the most human core thing that has ever happened is probably the 1980s charity collaboration song
We are the world
Yeah, that's pretty good. That's pretty good. That's very human core
I hadn't gone on their speech about this if you want look I I if I if I remember called the exact number of this
I'm gonna be a fucking genius episode
104 the one where I go to hawaii about sea turtles. Um, but my answer is collectively bread and dogs
Dogs are definitely up. I was thinking like
Bread is a great answer bread is it's a food that we invented. Yeah out of nothing
It's it's it's like an agricultural thing
Which the reason I describe that as human cores because we as humans have gone above what other animals are able to do
We are made able to make agriculture and farm
It's a collective thing and it's just high in dense and calories and we feed it to other people
It's collaborative group effort project the normal bread is like the most
enduring
Thing that is still used today from the dawn of civilization. Yeah, it is civilization
Uh, you find that's it. That's the answer why fix why fix what ain't broken
Uh, he okay. Um, maybe because I'm fucking keto because I've evolved beyond it. I know better
That's true. I mean, that's true
Whatever bread works for for bread does what it's supposed to do. That's true
Okay, I don't know if I agree that bread is human core because to me
What is human core is not simply doing what humans do
It is doing like a it is it is like a
Well, hold on
Okay, I think to me human core is indulging in a human impulse that is uh, never that is detrimental
To two humans actual ends. Well, this goes this goes to I mean this I mean it just depends on our definition here
Just depends on our definition. I don't get human human core. I don't know
It's not being human core to me is not the same thing as simply being human
Well, I don't I don't think I like I say bread just because people eat bread
I say it because I think it's emblematic of like a very like human thing
Which is agriculture and like collaborative eating and and farming and surplus and stuff like that
That's right. Yeah, but there's nothing wrong with those things. Well, I don't think
I mean to me human core is is a derogatory not to me
The most human thing is discussing politics online. There is nothing more deplorable
That's pretty human
And I agree that is very negative
Shit, I had another thing I wanted to bring up the you can do it
I will
human core is like
It's so strange that I can't even like decide on which definition I agree with like really doesn't
It's so vague that I I I can't like I can't even I can't even come up with my own like idea of like what it means to me
To be derogatory or is it meant to be?
When I use it and I invented it so so this is me when I use it, I mean it as
Yes, I did. Okay. No. Well, as we saw ben when you invent something cool
It will be perverted by the world
All right. Well here like like the guy who invented the the gif to try and tell everyone no actually
I always intended it to be pronounced gif
Here's me the the true and the true and honest creator christine weston chandler telling you that human core is an insult
It is not to be used to just describe
Anything that humans do it is it is uh, it is the like the worst human impulses. I mean, I think sneakers are pretty human core
And they're pretty cool
There you have it, you know, my uh
Dita's walk to concrete doors and walks all the concierge floors
Anything that you would be embarrassed of as a human core is is yeah, okay
So if yeah, if you'd be embarrassed of your love of sneakers, no, I'd never be embarrassed of that robot
Something very human core is just being like
Doing nothing in particular than all of a sudden being paralyzed as you remember something cringy you did like 15 years ago
That is pretty. He makes you discuss it. That's human cores. That's true. I'll agree with that
Yeah, I but I guess we'll have to wait for his answer and I hope he has something impressive
I'm sure none of us have said what he was
What was interesting about what he said he said that he said that it's it's super human core and that every human does it
What's up? No, no, no, no, no, he didn't say every yeah, he said only humans do it
No, I don't like though
You know, I don't like he's gonna have a chance to listen to our answers and say like he's gonna be able to change
His secret he didn't like write it down
You're right email it to so we would know what it is. I had a time here's my answer
It's it's episode episode 11 of season six of my little pony
That's human core. That's the most human core thing. Which one is that?
I can't remember and I don't know
Okay, yeah
Hey speaking of my little pony as you all know, we all went to bernie con except for you tom
What a fucking moron. I hate that guy. Anyway, moving on
There was a guy who went to bernie con who just wanted to give things so so let's give them. Let's let them have things
Shall we?
Thank you everyone for bernie con. Thank you me for stories from jacuzzi. I know what this is for
Thank you just
For calling me the myths of man. Oh, yeah
Thank you hippo for being sexy
Anyway, any other flyers
Thank you munchie for the fair and art. Thank you ben. Yeah for eating my sausage
And john for the autographs asking for my autograph
So
Thank you
For an rsck crew
Thank you everyone for making this play con
Awesome
Thanks a lot. Sorry. This is a week late. Thank you riddle my ass batman. It was
That was that was in fact riddle my ass batman. Yep. Did we mention we met him?
Yes, we did. We did. He did me riddle my ass batman. He gave me a he gave me a little phantom horn
Drawing he did which is cool. He wanted fan art from from he wanted me to draw my favorite moment for a riddle my ass batman
So it was me I drew for him in his sketchbook an image of digi plunging into the dicking piranhas and being really happy about it
So
Have you ever you guys ever heard uh
The classic Leonard Nimoy bilbo baggins song where he's like he wrote on a barrel
Uh, he he battled the trolls
He riddled with riddle my ass batman a magic ring. He stole
Yeah, yeah, that's that's that's what my adventure was at at brony con
I did all those things and riddled with riddle my ass batman
If we if we haven't wait, I have I had I remembered one other thing
I wanted to bring up and I should have done it before the voicemail. Okay. All right. No problem
um, did anyone anyone anyone tune into the uh,
Portland protests. I know unaware unaware. I have no idea what that is
You know, it was like anti-fabris of the proud boys or some shit. Yeah, the proud boys is that a real thing?
Yeah, believe it or not the proud boys are some fucking like
Identitarian
I think they would push back against that. Yeah, they would push back against that like any fascist would
Um, they uh, they're well, I mean, okay. They're not all right. They're not all like that
But like they definitely have like like a strong vein of that running through their their bones and their blood
Okay, got it. I don't know the point. Okay. I watched some streams of it yesterday just to see what was going on
It wasn't that interesting
But then afterwards I see fucking idiots on twitter like charlie kirk and andy know and these fucking morons tweeting about like
specifically they're like as a video
Of like a bunch of antifa guys like banging on like a bus that like the proud boy people are like get like these people are
Leaving in a bus and they tweet it with a visual like
Antifa thugs antifa thugs like smashing like like attacking
These these guys with a hammer and there's a video and like yeah one of these antifa guys like has a hammer
And he like breaks one of the wind or he's like swinging it the thing is okay in the video in the exact video
You can see that one of the people on the bus
Brings the hammer out and starts swinging it at the antifa people
Out the bus and one of the antifa people grabs it and pulls it away from him
And it makes me so fucking mad. There's that's the context that seems they're just fucking lying through their teeth
And this is what they do people like like andy know just go out there and just like fine
Just like oh, I gotta I gotta find I gotta find anything that I can frame
Right. I got any fight that breaks out
I got to only film the part where like antifa is fighting and not film whatever happened before it
Put that out there so everyone can see that. Yeah, maybe maybe I'll get maybe I'll get punched
Maybe I'll get punched again and make another two hundred thousand dollars. Mm. Fuck. Yeah
I see your point, but uh
Defending antifa is not a good look and I just associate with this completely
All right, cool. Go how go have fun with being antifascist or being a narco fascist or whatever
I'm over here with antifa and tifa's cool. They've been smeared by the media
Trump's uh, Trump's an asshole. Trump's an asshole calls them a terrorist racist one the cool one
I'm sorry. Who's a terrorist? Who's a trump trump? Yeah, Trump said Trump said antifa is terrorism. Oh, I mean
Aren't they
No, no
No, I mean, I've seen plenty of videos of them like mobbing on old men and beating the shit out of people
I think that's yeah, okay. They've never killed anyone
They've never killed anyone
Yeah, but if you're if you're in a gang and you're assaulting people and beating the shit out of them
Just because you didn't kill them that doesn't mean you're not
Hang on there. The far right fucking shoots up mosques and drives cars into crowds of people
What in news? Are you blaming us for news? Like, sorry, I don't know why I said us. I am not on the far right, but like
In new zeal. That was a new zeal. Yeah, but ben ben. Yeah, that's that's far right extremism
Antifa is far left and they don't kill shortly. They can both be considered terrorism
Yeah, but there's no equivalency
Does there know about that guy? No, it's not no counter protesting is not terrorism. What about that far left?
Elizabeth Warren guy who just shot up in Dayton, Ohio near where I live
Was he far left? Yes. I don't know about that
I wonder I mean, I okay. Look ben. I'm with you. I agreed. There's absolutely lots of people
I'm not even trying to do a both sides or bad thing. I simply think that that every side
Tries to find the most damaging thing about the other because they you know, they've got a team and you know, it seems normal
Yeah, okay. Well, sure. Yeah. Well, the point is that like this video
This thing with a hammer really demonstrates that they will they will smear them. They will like just they'll just lie
Like they've just do you really think that's not a lie never lied or never never like put themselves in a
Better situation than what they actually are. This is just
Political I guess. I mean like yeah, everyone's lying about everyone else. Everyone's trying to play gotcha and just making shit up
That's the way the world is now. I mean just like with confirmation bias
It's the same thing of you only analyze the sit any given situation to get enough detail
To paint your political or idealized opponent as the bad guy and then you stop analyzing the situation
and like we all do that it reminds me is it's like um
When the thing first came out about the uh, the trump hat kids who were supposedly like harassing the indian
And uh, yeah, everyone was against them and then after a while everyone is like, oh no
Here's it from another angle and they were actually harassing the indian
So then everyone, you know, kind of switch sides. You mean the the indian guy was harassing them. Yeah, that's what I meant
They were the indian guy was harassing them and so that but but then even after that
I would see other videos being posted of the kids early in the day
Actually like calling out to people and kind of harassing them. So everyone's bad. Everyone's lying. It's all a big fucking shit show
Everyone should die
Basically, that's why we need fucking either anarchy or fascism either put them all in jail or destroy all laws so that I can kill them
One of the reasons
Yeah, one of the reasons that I personally hate uh, like identifying with any particular group is because I do think like
Everyone is fucked up in their own way including me. I'm no fucking saint and like I'm just aware that when I attach my name to any group
I will be associated with the the negative things about any particular group if I said it was far left
They'll say that I'm a communist and I want to kill like two million
20 million people in russia or whatever if I say I'm far right, they'll say I'm a nazi and I want to kill jews or whatever
Problem, right? Here's here's my problem, right? Antifa is not a centralized organization
They are like a loose coalition of people that show up to counter
Let me let me what do you mean? What is it? What do you mean?
How can you label something like that terrorism that if you label antifa terrorism?
That means like literally any counter protest movement to any far right event is automatically terrorism
If you'd have to examine you don't have to be organized to be a terrorist
Like one dude can just like say wake up like I'm gonna fucking bomb something and it's an act of counter protest is not terrorism though
It's just a counter protest by default isn't but terrorists you can do terrorist acts during a counter protest
It's just so tiring how like everything then at the end of the day antifa bad proud boys bad all of this bad
Oh my god. No, you are totally wrong. Okay. Yeah, there's been violence, right? Fights have broken out people have been punched fine
Yeah, it's not that's not great. That doesn't mean antifa is bad. What they're doing is good because fascism is bad. Okay
Okay, what you're saying you're literally calling for like, oh, don't pro don't protest fascism. No, like don't
Yes, you are. No, that's what it is. No, that's all
That is such a charitable interpretation of what the group is
Well, what do you think it is? I think that's a bunch of people who disagree with the
Right inclinations in the political discourse and go out of their way to make that known and get violent and aggressive
It's just it's it's that's that's only the worst
It's angry people who are lost and confused and sad about their lives and want to fuck shit up
That's all any of the groups are. They're all the fucking literally just people are angry
It's literally just anyone who hates fascism
It's anyone who hates anything anyone who has hate in their heart joins some fucking goofy group and starts fucking shit up
Ben Ben surely you would agree that the definition you're using is the most charitable version of the group
Isn't that fair to say?
Um, I mean, that's what it is though. I mean because you're aware that some people who identify as like the fact like the
Okay, like the like the fact like the fact that some people have died here the fact that some mostly because
Mostly because saying Proud Boys bad Antifa bad is like Ben said a false equivalence Proud Boys are worse
But but why but Antifa is not good
But I don't care who's because their ideology is fuck is a nightmare. They're not but they're okay
Yeah, I don't like when people get killed anyone else
The fact that some people have been punched by Antifa does not mean that Antifa is about punching well Ben
I'm definitely with you in the sense that I don't trust any group of people that are named like a fucking mad max gang
From like the fucking first movie like right before the apocalypse
But it's just so I guess my point is that it's so tiring when everything that you see in here
A week later you see in here that it was actually the opposite and you were lying to and then a week after that you see in here
But no that was the lie and this is the true story. It's just
Nothing is real. Nothing is true anymore
We've killed truth completely
Everything is a fucking slant and a fucking lie and a meme and a joke. So fucking everything is just fucking
Everybody has an agenda or another so there's no way like there's no way to fucking parse through it anymore
There's no strainer to find the truth. It's just impossible. So here's here's here's my here's what I think
Here's what I think. Okay. You got you got two groups, right? You got one that's out there
Promoting an ideology that is about like
Identitarianism, right? Like even if they're not overtly, there's they're supporting there's they support fucking racist policies
Aren't you just they want they want the political overture window to slide even further right towards fascism, right?
Even if they're not overtly fascist themselves, even if they say they're against fascism
Uh, they're doing that and then on the other side you got people that oppose them and don't want that to happen
And even if shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up
And even if both sides were equally violent which they are not but even if they were
I would still say that the that the antifa is better because what they stand for is better
Okay, I have nothing further to comment on who gives a fuck. It don't matter. None of this matters
Boy, oh fucking boy next voicemail, please. Oh my god save me from this nightmare
That that that was the last real voicemail this last one's just uh, it was just gonna be uh, it's by teen cp
Who made a other voicemail last uh last week and then we put him in the voice gel not knowing he's a teen cp
And then he and then he made a funny little skit like oh, I'm gonna break out a voice gel next time on teen cp
I'm gonna fucking kill munchie or something. I feel like the mood. I feel like the mood for that is not in the air
Aren't you on the teen cp? Yes, I am
My munchie play what are you gonna not play it because we had a political discussion fucking play that shitty piece of shit
I'm playing it right now. Good
Datalog from the voice gel day six. My name low pussy is put here eating with
aka
Teen cp
I've been man raped. Well, I'm not really raped. I was talking but other than that. It's been miserable in here
I need out. Luckily, I have an in with one munchie tiny hats
Next teen cp episode
I bring the topic of in-depth security details of prisons we control once I have the info I strike
I tried to reach out to the japanese man
You just to find a bushido blade sharp enough to slice my way out, but he just grunted and shin chin
I'm expecting a package from the lost tape archive once he gets out of solitary teen cp
signing off
Godspeed godspeed teen cp
Is
Is it proven that that is in fact a teen because it sounds like a seven-year-old?
He's like 12. No. Yeah. He's really young. He's really really young
Oh boy. Are we going to jail guys? Are we going to jail cancel them?
I'm glad I'm glad we put a child in jail
Next time by the time you hear this you will already watch the third episode of the teen cp
Except I'm not on that one and what he just refers like it was recorded like just like a bit ago
And I just I'm gonna post it but next time after that time then you'll be able to hear the conclusion
Tell that young lad if he wants to be taken seriously. He needs to pick a side right now antifa or proud boy
Yeah, that's what all the adults are doing teen cp. They'll reply
Okay, that's it. Uh, wow, we have shirts I guess
We have shirts
We got red bubble. We got the links below. You can see them on the fucking app to what was that tea spring?
Yeah, they do tea spring. Just be cool. What's that other one? Oh, yeah the group piss. I love that group piss shirt
Uh, what else is going on? Oh patreon.com slash the pro crass donators one dollar
Discord five dollars bonus episodes. Uh, there will be a one out shortly after you hear this
That I won't spoil for you, but it's going to be exciting
Uh, get your hooves up for that one, which has nothing to do with the content of the episode, but do it anyway
Uh, yeah lots of episodes at tbcrasnators for updates on twitter
That's all there is to it people give us your money in whatever way you choose to but as long as you do you're a good person
Okay, that's it. We'll see you next time everybody. Thanks for being here. See you next week. Have a good time
And heckles for shekels was a few days ago. You already missed it, but maybe next time. All right. Bye
Oh