I want to bless that guy. You're a son of a bitch.
Imprive practice exercises. Start with a little SCREAM start with a little scream, yeah yeah
Just to get loosened up.
Ah!
I can't scream.
Yee!
I was trying.
I think last night, I stayed up.
I stayed up all night.
But so last, yesterday afternoon,
I was trying to like squeal.
I was trying to make it the most high-pitched sound I could.
And I'm getting afraid that like my range might be,
I might be too old and my range might be decreasing.
My vocal cords might not be what they used to be.
Let me try.
Oh, no.
Eeeeee!
That's actually, you know what?
Excellent.
That's pretty high.
It got to a point where Discord couldn't tell
that it was a person speaking and it cut you off.
Really?
You know what?
I think maybe it was just like late at night
and I was just like tired or something.
Nah, baby.
These pipes, these pipes are as good as they ever been.
I can do a really high-pitched squeak,
but I don't know if I'll be able to do it on command.
But I got to do it now that I've mentioned it.
What if I started shooting bullets at your feet
and make you dance?
Could you do it then?
I don't know why it cracked me up so much.
I did it.
The mic probably didn't pick it up.
I literally could not even hear it at all.
It sounded like a fucking dentist drill.
It was actually bad.
I don't like it.
Discord could not recognize that you were making any noise.
Well, I made a squeak.
I believe you.
Viewers at home, I'm sorry.
It was very high-pitched.
Speaking of dentist drill,
I still haven't been to the dentist for years.
I should probably go.
What stage are you on the big book of British smiles?
Do you remember that Simpsons bit?
There are, oh yeah, yeah, I remember that bit.
I, there are a couple of spots on my teeth
that I think probably need a veneer or something.
I'm hoping I don't need any like crowns
or like root canals or anything like that.
I'm hoping I don't get it.
There is a sensitive spot.
It's not on my tooth.
It's like, I'm not sure if I'm just imagining it.
There's a one spot between the two of my teeth
on the left side of my mouth
and I can feel it sometimes and it doesn't hurt.
It just feels a little weird, a little sensitive
and sometimes it bleeds a little bit.
So that's bad.
But I mean, it's not like tooth pain.
So I don't know if like they have to drill it or anything.
I don't know.
You have to bite a bullet, literal.
One of these days, one of these damn, damn old days.
Speaking of ruining your teeth,
I tried a different gummy thing.
Okay, okay, I looked up a recipe.
I looked up the ingredients for orange slices.
You know the candy, orange slices?
I think so.
We might have a different name for them.
They're like chocolate orange.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, no, all right, I don't know.
I'm thinking of like a jelly candy,
almost like a gum drop,
but it's just shaped like a slice of orange
and it's orange and it tastes like an orange.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, I looked up what's in those
and I was intrigued to see that there's no gelatin.
Gummies are made with gelatin.
I'm like, hmm, so what do they make it with?
And it's like just sugar.
It's like just corn syrup and sugar and
there was like modified corn starch
and I was like, I have some corn starch.
I was like, okay, I'll try it.
So I did try it.
And I tried like just mixing up sugars
and like cooking them down.
And it did, I was able to cook them down far enough
that they became like a hard candy.
And that was like, okay, that's cool.
But not a squishy candy.
Yeah, well, I was like, well, how can I get them squishy?
So I added some more water and they did come out soft
and I was able to bite them and chew them.
I was like, yeah, that's something, that's something.
But then I put them on my shelf
and I came back to them later
and they did not hold their shape at room temperature.
They had like, they flowed very slowly
but they had like just collapsed into a thick, hard puddle.
And I was like, hmm, okay, that didn't work.
But I tried it again and I added some pectin this time
and one of them is still too mushy,
but the other one that I added more pectin to, it did.
It kind of, it stayed, it kept its shape.
It's hard, it's kind of tough to bite,
sort of like a starburst, which is good.
I don't know, like the chewy, the consistency is not,
it's not jelly-like.
It's like a starburst.
Well, it's as chewy as a starburst.
It's as like hard, you know, like if you had a giant one
and you sunk your teeth into it,
it would be like, oh, my teeth got stuck in it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so I made something like that
and the consistency, it's a little bit grainy.
It's not like smooth jelly, like a gumdrop.
It's kind of grainy and I don't really like that
and I don't know how.
I wonder what starbursts are made of
because I feel like you could pull and stretch them
like taffy or something.
Yeah, I think I looked them up and well, you know what?
Let's find out.
And chew-its, I remember chew-its.
I've never had those in a while.
You got to chew-it, chew-it.
I remember the advertisement.
Starbursts too are, yeah, mainly corn syrup, sugar.
There's no, oh no, there is some gelatin in them.
There's some gelatin in them.
Modified corn starch.
It's funny, you read candy labels
and a lot of them have the exact same ingredients,
just like kind of switched around
in like a slightly different order.
But like it's the same shit.
Tapioca dextrin is interesting.
This is my attempt to make a cheap alternative
because gelatin and corn fiber are expensive
and those are the ones that I make for me
that I can make them low sugar
and I can eat lots of them and they're good for me.
I mean, more or less.
But I would also like to make a cheap version
that is just made of sugar
and so that's what I'm working on with these right now.
What if you made a gummy that you could vape?
It was a vapeable gummy.
Damn, but you could chew it too.
You could chew it or vape it.
Or you chew it and you swallow it
and then once you swallow it,
though you breathe out a big loud.
Yeah, it's like a little vape capsule inside, crunch it.
You know what I wish?
Unfortunately, I looked into it
and it seems like no, there is no way
to make colored vape clouds.
I wondered, is that possible?
And it seems like the answer is no.
No.
Or not without it being toxic.
It's because a cloud would need to have
like tiny particulates of a certain color.
So you could do it with paint and stuff
or like a chemical burning in a certain way.
Could you not just do it
with like, I mean, okay.
I mean, you can take water
and you can add like food coloring to it
to make the water, you know, pink, let's say.
Yeah, but the water.
Could you not then evaporate the water
and like have food?
You'll separate the food coloring from the water.
The water would evaporate.
The food coloring doesn't.
Well, what if you got,
what if you got some kind of coloring agent
that had the exact same, you know,
fusion points or what do you,
evaporation point at the exact same evaporation point?
I mean, could you keep them like dissolved in each other
as a gas or as a vapor?
If it's a gas, as far as I understand,
gases that have like colors to them
are because like they're, you know,
visible to the naked eye because they're big enough.
The particles are big enough to be seen.
Yeah.
So it would need to be big particles
and also evaporate at the same time.
Yeah.
So it wouldn't be like in the cloud.
No.
I mean, if you ever tried to paint a cloud, it's difficult.
All the time.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I guess that makes it.
I was disappointing.
Disappointing to realize that that wasn't happening.
You could do it if you shone a light through it.
That's how they do it at music festivals.
Sean, I love that word.
Sean, past tense of shine.
It's great.
It's great conjugation.
Uh.
Next step is caffeinated dummies.
Caffeinated vapeable dummies.
Yeah.
They do sell caffeinated vapes.
They do sell caffeinated vapes,
which is very funny.
Injectable.
Oh yeah, you don't even have to chew it.
Don't even have to vape it.
You don't even have to enjoy it at all.
You just put it right into your bloodstream.
It just clogs up your arteries with sugar chunks.
Yeah, let's just skip.
Let's just skip to the good part.
So I was-
Gummies suppositories.
Yeah.
Let's, we all know why we're here.
Let's just get right to the point.
So I was,
I was working on my secret video project
and I was doing work for that prep,
work for that stuff for that preparation
and I couldn't stand it anymore.
I got so sick of it,
I had to take a break from it, step away from it.
So I've switched back to
prepping the slime and punishment book,
which is good because that was what I was doing originally
and I had originally intended to finish that.
So it's good that I'm trying to finish that now.
It is good.
You're getting shit done.
I've made pretty good progress.
I have a three ring binder here
with printed out black and white pages
and I'm kind of rearranging them and reorganizing them
to settle on a final exactly what the page order is gonna be.
Oh, I finished the notes.
I finished writing the footnotes.
There's like 23 pages of them.
Like and infinite jest,
they're not really like the infinite jest footnotes.
Those are much more interesting,
but it's that style anyway.
There's 23 pages of them and I finished writing them
and I handed them to some RFCK people
to check and proofread and they did
and I took their input into account and I edited them
and now they're basically done.
I might still add a little bit more to them.
But that's good.
That's progress.
That's measurable progress on an important front.
I also was thinking about,
I was thinking about like merch,
like sets you could get with the Kickstarter,
like instead of just letting people pick like,
oh, any one, pick one pin,
pick a coin or whatever,
I was gonna offer like a package bundle,
like maybe like add like $15
and you can have like a set of like four or five things, right?
So I got like-
Of the different RFCK pins?
Yeah, exactly.
So I've got like a little,
maybe like a killer,
a little killer bundle with a patch and a pin
and a my face and maybe a gun girl
and a juvie one with like mega slime
and slime corp and a poedron and a slime heart,
map of the city, you know.
I've been organizing,
I have them in little piles on my bed right here.
Thinking about how many pieces,
how many pieces do I group into one batch?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like thinking about stuff.
You ever like think about stuff?
I do, I do think about stuff.
Whoa, that rules.
I hope soon to be back on like the productivity road.
At the moment, I'm still trying to like do normal things,
normally.
Yeah.
I got-
I had a pretty bad like two,
like last week was pretty bad.
This week has been like not great,
but like okay, I feel like not terrible about it.
So that's a win.
That's a big win for me.
Yeah, I got some,
I never had like antidepressants before.
I went to the doctor and I said,
oh, I'm depressed.
X, Y, Z and they said,
well, I'll try on this.
It's weird because like I feel like
I've talked about being depressed a lot as a teenager,
but I guess my parents just never thought
it was like worth worrying about.
It's like, oh, you're just tired of school.
It's like, I didn't even know
you could just get antidepressants that quickly.
I thought you needed like a proper full like thing.
So you just went to a therapist or a psychiatrist?
Just my local, my doctor.
Like I called them up, I had an appointment
and I said, I'm explaining my problems.
And they're like, sounds like you might need,
you want some antidepressants?
I said, yes.
They recommended me a thing.
Well, they didn't recommend,
they just said they were gonna put me
on this thing for a month, see what happens.
So did you just say like, hey, Doc, I'm depressed.
And he was like, well, I have just the thing for that?
Yeah, essentially.
Wow.
Huh.
Pretty crazy.
I didn't think like a regular doctor
could prescribe that for you.
Might be different in America.
I'm not, or it might not be, I don't actually know.
Yeah, I've never really done that before.
I've always had the sense that you need like a,
like more proof.
Like a psychiatrist, like you would need
like a psychiatric evaluation or something.
Like you need to have sessions with your therapist
where you talk it out and then they might come
to the conclusion like, I see,
you have clinical depression and I will give you.
I think that may be how it used to work
when depression was, I don't know, taken less seriously.
Maybe it's taken more seriously.
I assume like after COVID,
loads more people were depressed than were before.
That's probably true.
And so like, it's just easier to get it now
because yeah, we all get it.
We all get it.
So I've been taking that
and the only thing that's happened so far,
I mean, I feel all right.
What are you taking, if you don't mind me asking.
Oh, I've got it right here.
It is a CetaloPram.
I've never heard of that.
CetaloPram tablets.
Isn't that the name of like a, no, the CetaloVision.
Wasn't the CetaloVision like a Nintendo console
that included like radio connectivity or some shit?
And you could play like Mario 2 with like a radio play.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Is that like a Game Boy like add-on?
What, I have no idea.
Okay, I'm pretty sure I learned this from a gaming
historian video.
There was a console called the CetaloVision
and I know that you could play Mario 2 on it,
but the version of Mario 2 on the CetaloVision
included like audio drama tracks in between levels
where like Mario and the other characters
like had conversations with each other about,
I think you had to like download,
I think you had to like download the game
through the radio waves or something.
I don't know.
What the fuck?
It was some shit that they did in Japan
that they never were like,
well that didn't really work so we're not.
Downloading Mario 2 through the radio.
I don't know, it was some shit like that.
That's fun.
Some like weird like you downloaded stuff
but not through like an internet connection.
Like it was like broadcast.
I might be confusing it with something else.
Look anyway, it just sounds like that thing you said.
Yeah, so I have to take a tablet every day for a month
to see what happens and it's made me feel woozy.
It's made me feel like I might throw up
but I'm not actually going to.
And it's made me feel very yawn-y.
I'm not sleepy but I am yawning a lot
and my throat is like feels like I'm straining my muscle
like under my, on my neck, like under my chin.
You know when you're like, you're holding back tears
or you're trying to yawn really hard
and that part of your neck is like er, filled with blood.
I, my, neck?
It just feels thicker.
Like I don't know how to describe it.
It's just sort of like the yawn muscle under your chin.
Oh, like maybe?
Like around the Adam's apple area.
I don't, I don't really think I am familiar
with the sensei, the particular sensation.
Well try to yawn, try to force a yawn
and you'll see what reflects.
Oh, the one that kind of bulges out
right underneath your chin.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's feeling a little like in constant use, I guess.
And it's like, it's nothing on its own is like too bad.
And they said there will be side effects
and you'll get used to them.
Your body will acclimate.
So I'm just, I'm just taking that
and hopefully I'll feel good.
I feel all right, but I also,
I'm aware of the fact that my low productivity
is not just because of depression.
It's also because I don't wanna do anything.
So I've also got to work on that.
But yeah, that's basically my week
is that I've just continued to be a layabout.
Have you been a piece of shit and play all these games?
I, yeah.
I finished watching Breaking Bad.
That's a good show.
You ever heard of it?
Yeah, the ending is not that great.
I didn't like the last season that much.
No, all right, so.
I thought everything after Spoiler,
I thought everything after Gus,
after Gus died was kind of like,
it never quite got as good again.
Kind of like after Elle died in Death Note.
It's like, well, the show has lost something important.
I felt that way the first time I watched Breaking Bad.
Watching it this time,
I appreciate a lot more of what's going on
because here's the thing.
My brother said this
and it was something I really agreed with.
Halfway through, because the fifth season is split into two.
They released it in two things.
Season five, part one, part two.
At the end of season five, part one,
Walter has all of his money
and he's left the meth business.
Jesse's out, Mike is gone, I think.
Or Mike is dead, but Walter killed him
and he's just pretending that he left.
And it's like Walter's family is fine
and it's all good.
And then Hank stumbles upon
Gail Bedaker's signature
or writing in one of the books
in Walt's bathroom that he picked up.
And he puts the pieces together
and realizes it's the same writing as there,
as Gail Bedaker and he's like,
oh my god, and then it cuts.
And then that's the end of the first part.
Gail is the billionaire guy.
No, no, no. Gail is the other chemist,
the nerd.
The nerd?
The other guy who's like Gus's guy
who's cooking the meth.
Oh, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Walt has Jesse shoot him in the head
and then Jesse's traumatized.
Yeah.
That moment there where Hank
suddenly puts the pieces together
and he knows that Walter White is Heisenberg
is where that season ends, half a season.
And my brother said that would be the perfect way to end the show.
Instead of like the big
bombastic like machine gun thing,
which they set up at the beginning of the season,
having it be like, oh, everything's fine.
We did it.
Jesse, I killed Gus and I got the money
and everything's good and nothing bad is going to happen to me
and then immediately Hank.
And it's like, oh, he's going to get caught.
And instead of seeing it, we just imply that like,
no, actually, it's fucked.
Yeah, yeah.
But then there's stuff.
I don't mind it too much.
I just feel like it doesn't stay long enough
to be built up as much as Gus
before it gets destroyed.
I thought that the like,
what if they like some biker gang or something
or like the bad guys in the last...
They're Nazi white supremacists like criminals.
They got like swastika tattoos everywhere.
I just didn't care about them.
Yeah.
They're, I mean, they're threatening.
I think it's Todd, the like psychopath boy
who has no remorse for killing children.
He's like the villain of the season,
even though he's not like in charge of stuff.
And he's kind of scary,
but he's also like, not always the focus.
So it's like, when Gus is gone,
a lot of the shows sort of like,
it feels like the epilogue,
like the first episode of season five
feels like an epilogue because like,
oh shit, what's gonna happen now?
And stuff happens.
True.
I still like it though.
I think the machine gun ending
and the whole like,
Walter going to New Hampshire
and with this barrel of money
and being like, oh shit, I can't do anything.
And then he sees Gretchen and Elliot
from Grey Matter on the TV and they're saying,
oh yes, Walter White, the notorious Heisenberg.
He founded with us in our company,
but he's not involved.
In fact, he didn't really do anything
and his legacy, you know, we are shitting on it.
And then Walter was like, fuck you piece of shit,
you will shit on my legacy.
My ego is so big and that's the whole problem
with me as a character.
So I'm gonna come back.
Oh darn, I could just let it be
if not for this darn tragic flaw of mine.
Oh well.
Yeah, gotcha.
It's been a long time since I've watched it.
Yeah, I started because I just randomly
on YouTube that gave me clips for Breaking Bad.
I was like, oh yeah, I remember that.
Oh yeah, I remember this.
And he just watched like a ton of clips
and I was like, okay, man, let's watch the whole show again.
It was a good time, very good.
I couldn't play anymore Mega Man.
I barely managed to force myself to
suffer through the end of X6
and I was like so fucking over it.
Mega's not looking so mega anymore.
X6 was bad.
I guess next I could either play
the fucking X7, which is when they switched,
they made a 3D one, which I hear is real bad.
But it might be funny,
but probably not for a whole playthrough.
It would probably be really tedious and agonizing.
Or I could play regular Mega Man 9,
which is when they waited seven years
and then they made a retro one in the old 2D style,
which is probably pretty good.
I remember when that came out and people were like,
oh my god, it's Mega Man.
On YouTube at the time I followed a bunch of YouTube poop people
and they always made YouTube poop music videos using Mega Man music.
So they all loved Mega Man.
And then the new one came out.
Not the new one.
Mega Man 9 was like 2008 or 2006 or something.
That's what I'm talking about around that time.
They did make two more after that.
9 and 10 they made them and they look like they're on the NES.
They look like that.
And then 10 years went by and they made 11
and 11 is the 2.5D one.
And I think they were all supposed to be pretty good,
pretty as good as the old ones used to be.
I remember seeing footage of Mega Man 10, I think,
with a football, like a soccer themed stage,
with soccer man, sports.
That doesn't ring a...
Oh, um...
Strike Man, the one who's a baseball.
Yeah, I don't know what he looks like,
but I remember the soccer balls on the stage.
His... I haven't played that one,
but yeah, there is a guy called Strike Man.
He's basically just a baseball.
His body is round and he has a catcher's mitt.
So that's probably what you're talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I rewatched that Brian David Gilbert.
You know who that is, right?
What did he work for?
Did he work for Kotaku?
No, Polygon.
No, he worked for Polygon and he made a bunch of videos.
He made a bunch of videos.
And he does like standing in front of a board
and he points at it.
Yes, he did the one where he went through
how useful are all the robot masters.
And that's a good video.
He does skip over a lot.
He doesn't really discuss half of the robot masters
because half of them are just designed to kill.
And so he just kind of put them...
It's like those go in their own category.
There's no need to discuss them.
You know, Napalm Man and Blade Man.
They basically all do the same thing.
Yeah, I mean, Blade Man could be a chef.
In fact, Napalm Man also could be a chef.
I mean, apparently...
I didn't know this. Apparently,
Blade Man and a bunch of the robots from 2
were actually sort of wily,
sort of making his own version of the robots
that he stole from Light in 1.
So like Metal Man is sort of wily made his own cut man.
But instead of Cut Man, who is designed for, you know,
felling trees and he just reprogrammed him to fight,
Metal Man is like, he's that, but he's just for killing.
He's just for, well, not killing, but combat.
Yeah, so the biggest thing you could do,
the best thing you could do is to put a forest in his way
and you wouldn't be able to cut his way through.
Yeah, Cut Man could get through that, but Metal Man couldn't.
So it's his one weakness.
Although I wonder if that's like,
I wonder if they had that in mind when they were designing the robot.
No, they couldn't have because they did that thing
where like people would submit bosses
and they would accept submissions.
But they can't have been like,
oh, what if we made one that was kind of like Cut Man,
but a little different?
Oh, I know, Blade Man.
They could just pick ones from the submissions
that would fit the criteria.
Maybe that came into their judging.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Which one would fit with the world we're building the best.
Yeah, possibly, yeah, possibly.
It's hard to know developer intentions.
They're crazy.
Sometimes things will be canon.
For instance, Shadow Man.
Shadow Man.
I mean, in Mega Man 3,
I don't believe there's any suggestion of this at all.
In Mega Man and Base,
you can find his data card or whatever
and it says like, oh yeah, Wily didn't make him.
Wily found him in like a trash can
and he fell from space
and he's made of some metal that came from space.
So, you know, make of that what you will.
So it's like, okay.
Did they know that when they made three
or were they just thinking of like
factoids to retroactively apply
and they were like, hey, what if this guy
actually fell from space?
Okay, that's where it changes backstory.
I feel like that may probably be it
because like if you don't make it about,
I mean, for that character in particular,
if there's no instance of him
like being a space dweller or anything,
it's obviously not part of their character document.
He's from space and they don't make any effort
to make it clear that he's from space
and why would they make that part of his character?
They'd probably retroactively just do it for some reason.
For no reason?
I think they do know things that like,
it's tough because like those games
have so little data to work with
that they definitely had things in mind
that they didn't put in the game.
So they did know more than went into the game
but it's like, well, okay, but how much more?
Is that one of the things that they knew about them?
Like, they never mention role.
Like role appears in the end of Mega Man 1
but they never acknowledge her anywhere
in the first game at all.
They never say like what her name is
or what her serial number is.
And then later on, but they had to have known
because they do give other robot serial numbers
and there's one missing, like number two is not listed
and I mean it's role but they never actually say that.
So they just didn't have like space
or they just like didn't have anywhere
that they could conveniently put it in.
They don't know. So secret.
It's so secret.
You're gonna have to go to Japan.
And it's impossible to know what they knew
and what they made up, what they knew at the time
and what they just making up later.
They'll never know.
What does it matter Ben?
Who gives a shit?
I care, I care because in my opinion,
because it, okay, here's why it matters
because if they were just making Mega Man in base
and they're like, oh shit,
I got to think of something to say about Shadow Man.
I don't know.
He's made of like meteor metal, whatever.
If they just made that up later,
then that's basically like J.K. Rowling being like,
oh yeah, there's Jews at Hogwarts.
Anthony Goldstein was a Ravenclaw, you idiots.
Like obviously.
And I don't accept that.
I don't think retroactively doing things
or making meaning out of things that were once meaningless
is a bad thing.
I just think J.K. Rowling is like doing it for points
and it's really like bad of her.
I think, okay, I just think there's,
I don't know, it feels different to me.
To me, it makes a difference in how I think about Shadow Man,
whether or not they knew at the time that he fell from space
versus whether they just came up with that later and said,
yeah, sure.
Well, I mean, you'd never be able to know.
And even if you asked them, they probably wouldn't remember.
Because to me, what that says is that in Mega Man 3,
he didn't fall from space,
but then later they changed it so that he did.
So if you were playing 3 when 3 was out,
that fact would not be true.
It only became true later.
So to me, it's kind of not really true
if it wasn't true in the game.
But when you say your thoughts about Shadow Man change.
And I think about Shadow Man all the time.
What does that really mean?
Like facts aside, like...
I don't know, it's just a different...
Does it take you out of the experience?
No, it doesn't take me out of the experience.
No, I mean, in a way that you're thinking about the developers
more than you're just thinking about this world that is cohesive
and it has rules and stuff.
It's not about affecting my experience.
I'm not trying to protect myself.
I'm not trying to protect my experience.
I just want to know...
I don't know.
I just think it's different.
No, I get it.
I just want the truth with a capital T.
I just don't want to be lied to.
The impulse.
I don't really know where it comes from either.
I think it's just sort of like a sense of the creator not caring.
But I care so much.
What the fuck?
It's kind of like the story of the development of the series then.
That story is different in the one scenario.
It's like George Lucas.
Things would be different if he knew the story of the prequels
back when he was making the original Star Wars
versus the reality of the situation,
which is he came up with all the prequel stuff.
He came up with that shit later.
He was always making it up as he went along.
I feel like that's important.
It's important.
It's important to understanding the story of the franchise.
I think that there is nothing wrong with learning the story
by going back and re-looking at it and being like,
okay, so this thing that I didn't mean anything for,
I could use and it would be retroactively set up.
You didn't plan for certain things to happen,
but with what you know and without contradicting yourself
by checking, you can make the future.
You can make new things.
I think that's fine.
I think that's the same.
But I think that if in my mind,
if I had the knowledge, oh, Shadow Man fell from space,
I feel like in that situation where they made that up in base,
I would feel like I did not have the true story.
I only had an incomplete.
The true story is that originally that was not the case,
but then later it was made the case retroactively.
I feel like there is data that is lost.
If I just looked it up and found out the fact,
oh, Shadow Man fell from space.
That's not the whole story.
So part of the story of Shadow Man was that...
Well, no, not...
I don't know what you're saying.
I'm saying...
Well, I mean, canonically then,
in the canon of the story, Shadow Man fell from space.
But in the meta story of how the series was created,
only after a certain later point did that become true,
but it was not true at his debut.
Also, your concern is if somebody were to tell the story
of how Mega Man were developed, that would need to be included.
Yeah, if you just said...
If I was describing to you the plot of Mega Man 3,
and I was like, okay, and then there's Shadow Man.
And Mega Man went and he fought Shadow Man,
and Shadow Man is a master of ninjutsu magic,
and he is an android from space.
He's made of meteor metal while he found him in a scrap heap.
Okay, and then Gemini Man, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I would be like, that would be like a lot.
I think that would be wrong.
I would be leaving something out,
because that's a retcon that did not occur until much later.
But is there any contradiction,
or would it ruin anything if it's like...
It would ruin my commitment to the truth, capital T.
I mean, if you really wanted you to just mention
that it is unknown whether he came from space at this time,
but it was then later confirmed by Data Log in this game.
In my opinion, I think there's a difference here.
If they did not intend that originally,
but then later they said it and decided that it was true.
In my opinion, it's not that it was unconfirmed,
and then later was confirmed.
It's that it was initially false, and then later became true.
But I... okay.
That's very important.
I feel like this is exclusively affecting you.
I mean, who else is it going to affect?
I don't know.
I think these are important details.
If you want to know what's going on in a story,
I feel like this makes a difference.
Okay, so if it was true
that they retroactively decided this fact,
and you knew that to be the case,
then you could apply that logic to some other thing.
Now you know that the developers are willing to do that.
Would something else come to light?
Well, I mean...
I'm trying to figure out exactly why it's important.
I don't know.
It's just important for its own sake.
Knowledge is just important for its own sake.
Truth is just important because it is the truth.
Ben, Mega Man doesn't exist.
What?
Good thing I did my improv scream practice before we started.
Good thing I practiced being as high pitch as I possibly can.
I'm distressed.
I would just say that to me...
It's two different stories.
There's the story of...
Okay, Mega Man 3, Shadow Man fell from space,
versus Mega Man 3, Shadow was made by Wily,
but then later in Mega Man and Base,
they say, oh, he actually fell from space.
I don't know, those are like two different things.
And only one of them can be true.
Understood.
Okay.
And I like to tease this sort of thing out.
I wonder about it.
Because it's like...
I don't know.
It's sort of like death of the author,
because it's like, okay, what's in the game?
What's actually in the game?
In 3?
Is there anything actually in 3 to suggest that Shadow Man fell from space?
No?
Well, then I guess he didn't.
I mean, Base says he did,
but okay, is that a new invention for them?
Or was there an intention there
that the developers had known that,
they just didn't put it in,
but they thought it?
I think it's neat to think about.
You ever just think about things?
No, yeah, I'm trying to think myself.
If it was things that were scrapped for time,
why Shadow Man,
what significance does Shadow Man have
in the rest of the series post this information
that he came from space?
Where from space?
It would make me wonder why they did that.
Actually, honestly, either way,
I have to wonder why they decided
that this would be a thing that is true of Shadow Man,
because he has no significance.
The one connection there is that
Mega Man 3 does take place
across different planets.
You might not even know that
if you were just playing the game,
because it's not even important.
But it is true.
So you do travel between different planets.
So I guess there's kind of a space theme
going on there?
So when they say he came from space,
is there ever any information beyond that
that we learn in other games?
I'll tell you exactly.
Who built a Shadow Man?
Maybe it's Metal Sonic.
The thing about that, though,
is that actually a lot of robots
just come from space,
and that's all we know about them.
Oh, you know what?
It's home stuck again.
They come out from the meteor things.
The ectobiology.
The bad guys in Mega Man V on the Game Boy
are the star droids who are just from space.
Who made them?
Nobody knows.
Duo from Mega Man VIII
and Power Battle and Power Fighters.
Duo is just a robot cop from space,
and apparently some interviewer asked Inafune,
okay, so what's his deal?
He's a cop from space.
Is there a police force?
Does he belong to an organization?
Where is he from?
Inafune was just like,
man, I don't know.
It's like an action game.
Who cares?
Yeah.
That would lend credits to the idea
that they came up with that thing retroactively.
Wouldn't it be cool if he came from space?
Yeah, it would be cool.
But why?
But why make that change?
You know what?
I didn't even think about this,
but I kind of think Shadow Man,
he's not just a ninja.
I think he just seems like the kind of ninja
who fell from space.
I don't know.
He just looks like that kind of guy.
That is exactly how it happened
in the writer's room.
That's exactly how it happened,
but in Japanese.
It's...
Hang on.
I'm looking...
Here we go.
Shadow Man.
Here we go, Shadow Man.
Skilled Martial Artist,
Master of Ninjutsu Magic.
Uh...
Damn it.
Okay, his...
His Shadow Blade is coated with a special
and deadly liquid?
What?
No, that's not it.
Do what if Mega Man and Roll
and Proton Man
and Axel and...
I don't know, the characters.
If the characters played Suburb,
what would happen?
It would be cool and fun.
It would be like they're robots,
but they're playing Suburb.
Okay, I don't even know where this comes from now.
I guess it's not from his Mega Man and Base profile.
Where does this information even come from?
The Shadow Man's body does not match
any material found on Earth.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
What?
I think it's from...
It's from, like, a fan newsletter
that, like, kids in Japan
had to, like, sign up to receive by mail.
That's where that comes from.
So kids were asking,
well, what the fuck's with the Shadow Man?
No, they weren't asking.
They weren't asking.
They just got a little pamphlet.
They didn't ask for this, but here it is.
They just got a little pamphlet in the mail
that's like, hey, here's some profiles about some robots.
Let me tell you about Shadow Man.
He's made of, like, space metal
and evolved for space.
So an intern came up with it.
He was just like, you gotta write something.
Yeah, that seems like...
The metal of Shadow Man
does not match any material found on Earth.
My conjecture is that he may have been created
and left behind by some ancient civilization
on another planet.
Then it's likely that Wiley remodeled him
to suit his own maligned purposes.
How can I even believe?
Can I even trust this pamphlet?
I mean, if that's the only source.
This is what I mean.
The wiki just tells you it like it's a fact.
Like, it's just established canon.
Don't trust me, bro.
Just trust me, bro.
Shadow Man is an alien.
But then you look into it,
and it's like, this is where that comes from.
They don't even say alien.
They say ancient civilization.
On another planet.
I would...
Yeah.
You know?
So I've arrived at probably the best answer I'm gonna get.
And now it's just a matter of interpretation
of like, do I think...
Do I think that a monthly newsletter by mail,
circulated by Konami or Capcom or whatever,
is that canon?
I don't know.
I think you'd have to look into who wrote it.
Or like, check out a pamphlet to see what other kinds of facts they give.
And if this one is in line with those,
or if it's like an outlier and like, way too strange.
I don't...
It's not that it's too strange.
It's not that this piece of information is like,
doesn't fit in the canon.
Like, it's...
No, no.
I mean, like, the...
It would be weird to get your information from this pamphlet
because they come up with so many wacky things.
That the games have no...
Like, how many of things in the pamphlet are represented in the game?
I think there's a lot of stuff like this that is not in the game.
And the only way you would know it is if you read a pamphlet like this.
Like, for instance,
Proto Man's Whole Deal.
Proto Man's Whole Deal is like, not explained anywhere
until fucking Mega Man the Power Fighters 2,
which was an arcade cabinet game.
And that's...
Yeah.
You'd have to draw a line somewhere of...
If you're going on the game's franchise,
games are made by multiple people,
do you include any and all of the people involved in the official making of
merchandise for the game,
or do you draw the line at just what's in the game,
in which case there is no story for a lot of these things,
or does it have to be written by a specific author or writer?
Yeah, I mean...
Because this pamphlet, it may have been...
Like, they may have consulted Inafune,
they may have consulted the team about the answers to these questions.
But they'd probably be busy.
I feel like it may have just...
Some of them could be just written like,
come up with something.
Probably the team was consulted.
Sure.
Yeah, but they might have just come up with something.
But where do you draw that line, Ben?
I think...
I mean, okay, what's in the game,
what's in the game is, you know,
inarguable, unless two things contradict each other.
And then...
That's a split timeline.
Yeah, then it's a split timeline, obviously.
I would say that developer intention is important.
I would say that if the developer says,
oh yeah, that's true.
I didn't put it in the game, but it's true.
I guess I would accept that,
unless something in the game contradicts it,
and then I would probably have to say,
well, what's in the game takes precedence over
what the developer says was supposed to be in the game.
And then...
And then when you get to supplementary materials like this,
I mean, my...
Okay, I guess my instinct is to say,
I would say that this is canon.
I'm gonna say this is canon.
It's just...
But again, the question then is like,
well, but was it the intended canon when they made it,
or did someone ask later, and then later they're like,
ah!
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Never mind.
This can't be where this comes from,
because the question that this answer is answering,
the question is, is it true that Rockman 3's Shadowman
is an extraterrestrial robot?
So there must have been a clue about this somewhere else.
But where?
You go deep dive.
Okay.
The column all...
The translator has made a note here.
The column also addressed two of the most mysterious robots
to ever appear, Shadowman and Quint.
Even Dr. Wright seems to be at a bit of a loss
surrounding their origins,
but after the event knowledge of Quint...
No, I don't even want to get...
I don't even want to get into Quint.
That's...
That's too...
That's too deep.
No, he doesn't really say anything.
Where?
Alright, well, never mind.
I've actually learned nothing because...
The actual story of Shadowman
must have originated earlier than this.
Archaeology is tough.
You really got to go digging.
As Shadowman is possibly an alien in origin,
he may be a precursor to other alien robot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can do wild speculation too.
No problem.
See, the thing is...
There's...
They could always continually expand upon Shadowman
in the future.
I think...
With a lot of creative stuff,
when you're building a story with many characters
and large backstories and all this...
this world building,
you won't have a perfect answer for everything all at once.
You will have the main plot.
You will have the main character.
You will have the antagonist.
You'll have large parts of it all fit together very nicely.
And then the rest could be vague.
And you'll come up with an answer once somebody asks you,
like, what is the deal with this?
That's just how a lot of these things work.
At the end of the day,
it has no impact at all on anything else about the story,
whether Shadowman is an alien.
I just want to know.
I would guess that it was just retroactive.
Because you can only go off of what they put in the game.
Unless you have access to some information
or notes or developer sketches
that show Shadowman being an alien,
you will have no proof either way
to prove what they were trying to do with him.
So you can only go off of what is in the game at the time.
Okay, well, this pamphlet...
this pamphlet...
I'm leaning more towards Canon, actually,
because this pamphlet is from 1994,
which was...
okay, that was four years after Mega Man 3 came out.
So, okay, so the clues about that might have been dropped in
any number of other games, so...
I think...
I do get the impression that the team probably had a lot of thoughts
and ideas and sort of lore about the characters
and the robot masters and stuff
that didn't make it into the games
just because the games are small,
the NES cartridges have very limited data, etc.
This is...
I would believe that they had an idea like this about him.
Like, it's not crazy that they might have.
I just...
So I guess I would default to assuming
that they did...
that this is their intention,
unless I had some good reason to think that it wasn't.
And I mean, I guess the fact that it's mentioned
nowhere, anywhere at all until, like, years later
would be kind of a clue that maybe no, they didn't...
do this until later, but then it's like a question of how many years.
And it's very...
His design, if he looks similar to other robots that come from space?
Well, the thing about that is that
most of the other robots that came from space
don't look any different from any other robots.
So, not really, no.
Well, I could imagine that they have this idea.
They had this at-the-time idea that some robots come from space.
Not all robots are made by Dr. Light or Dr. Wiley or whatever.
Some robots come out of space, like they have that idea,
the vague sense of there being more robots out there
and then not having the time to really flesh that out in the game,
but knowing that some of them could be,
and then they decide later Shadow Man was one of them.
It's the... I mean, since 3 takes place on other planets,
again, like, yeah, it wouldn't be that crazy
for one guy to be like,
oh, well, this guy is from an ancient civilization on another planet.
It's just that there's literally nothing about Shadow Man
that seems like to indicate that or hint at it
or tie in with that at all.
He's a ninja.
Maybe they mean ancient civilization as an allegory for ancient Japan.
It's like an ancient Japan planet.
I don't think so.
Yeah, maybe.
Ancient civilization, another planet.
Maybe our Earth is where real Japan is.
No, Mega Man Earth.
Mega Man takes place on Earth.
It takes place on Earth in the city of Monsteropolis.
That's not true.
That's what it says in the guidebook for Game 1,
but only in English.
Is Shadow Man explained in a pamphlet,
in a how-to-play booklet?
The booklet, it does not have a character bio on it.
It just lists him as one of the bosses.
I mean, the Japanese one might have more in it,
but probably not.
It's just the same text, but has the word alien at the end.
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute.
It might be in...
No, those lore books came out years and years later.
It wouldn't be in one of those books.
You would need a proof at the time for during development
to answer this question.
You would need the developer notes.
There is a...
A little sketches.
That's funny.
Something that I found...
I found that...
This is maybe the biggest piece of Mega Man's...
I found this and I was fascinated by it.
The more I thought about it, the more doubt was cast upon me.
At first, I found this and I was like,
Oh my God, it's so clarifying.
This explains everything.
And that explains less and less.
There's a note, like a piece of paper,
that some guy found at a Rockman 20th anniversary.
Not like a convention.
Some kind of convention or party or something.
And a bunch of developers were there and they had a...
And apparently, just some Japanese guy on Twitter
posted that at some guy's table,
some developer's table, he found a piece of paper
that had a little flowchart written on it in ballpoint pen.
And it sort of sketched out the relationships between
Dr. Light, Dr. Wiley, Mega Man, X, Proto Man, Zero,
the Maverick Virus, Sigma, Dr. Kane, etc.
And it's all there and it's like,
Okay, makes sense.
And I think it is generally...
The wiki seems to just take it at face value.
That like, oh yeah, the developer had this.
So that means that they must have been working off of this document.
This must have been an early design document for when they're making it.
But it's not true. It does not have to be that.
What if he wrote that at any point in the future?
This is not necessarily proof that,
oh, they had all of this design from the beginning.
This could have been something that he sketched up,
you know, 15 years later.
Maybe just to like, remind himself how it all worked
or just maybe to illustrate it to someone who didn't know
and he wanted to show them or something, right?
Like, it's not...
It's really not strong proof of anything
other than that it's what he thinks now.
Clearly, it's what he considers to be canon
as of whenever he wrote it.
But we don't know when he wrote it.
It doesn't prove that this was the plan all along, right?
Uh, no.
Okay, because the games are just so vague in so many regards
that it's sometimes be like,
but did they mean it to be like that?
Or did they just bullshit me?
I don't know, I've probably been thinking way too much about this.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's fun to think about things a lot, so it's not a problem.
Yeah, you like think about things?
I do, I do think about things.
I like thinking about things.
Cool, we should like think about things together sometime.
Yeah.
I have to pee, I'll be back in a second.
Oh yeah, well I have to pee, I'll be back in a second.
Aw, shh.
A few moments later.
Mega Man.
Shadow Man.
Shadow Man, da-nah-da-nah-nah, da-nah-da-nah.
Da-nah-da-da, da-nah-da, da-nah-da,
Shadow Man!
Oh, I've said enough about that guy.
Damn, we've been going for an hour.
Babbling about Shadow Man for an hour.
Yep. We're shadows of our former selves.
Well, shit. What else have I got going on this week?
I'm trying to get a contract signed for my new place.
I saw a bunch of houses. I don't want a house hunt anymore.
I'm just trying to get the one that was the most palatable.
I'm just trying to contact that guy and just be like,
please just sign me up. Please just sign me up for September.
Get me some residence, please.
He told me he was going to send me a contract to sign,
but I haven't got it yet, so I'm still waiting on that.
I hate it. I hate moving. I hate house hunting.
I hate moving. I hate talking to my landlord.
I know that before I move out, there's going to be some bullshit.
There's going to be some fucking bullshit confrontation.
My stupid landlord, that's coming. I can feel it.
I won't escape.
You're going to have to fight?
Probably, yeah.
Probably. I'll have to argue about something.
She will try to pull some nonsense and try to get me to pay extra fees
or give her more money for something.
Tell me that I broke my contract somehow and now I owe her something.
Some crap like that.
Just remember the golden rule, you don't have to do anything.
I don't have to do anything.
And if I do have to do something.
You just walk out. You just leave.
The only way she can compel me.
The only way she can compel me to do anything is by taking me to court,
which will not be worth the effort.
I think I can probably get away with a lot if I'm just really stubborn about it.
Back in the day, house hunting was so much easier.
You would get around with your guys.
You would bang your putts and pans together.
Get your clubs and spears and you would hunt that house.
You would throw a spear right in the window.
You would catch it and you would roast it over the open fire and you would eat it.
Those were the days. Delicious.
That's funny. That was a funny turn of phrase.
It is kind of like a hunt.
You have to be the first one to get your prey.
Otherwise someone else will eat.
Yeah, pretty much.
Then you'll starve to death on the streets.
This place that I'm moving to is going to be slightly more expensive than my current place,
but not by a lot.
It'll be like $50 a month more, so whatever. It's fine.
The location is a little worse.
It's a little bit further away from everything, but it's not that much further, so it's fine.
It's just like a 15-minute walk anywhere instead of a 10-minute walk.
Who cares?
You should buy a scooter and scoot around.
I was thinking about buying a Vespa.
Maybe I should just buy a Vespa.
You know, like in Fooley Cooley?
Oh, the little yeah, yeah.
I have considered buying a Vespa.
Maybe I should just buy a Vespa.
That'd be funny.
Does that have like a license required, like a motorbike? Is it classed as that?
Or is it not technically a motorbike and it's sort of different?
You might need a separate license than a driver's license to drive one.
It might be operateable with a motorcycle license.
Maybe? I don't know.
Curious, curious.
I should look into that.
I don't know.
I was thinking maybe I should get back on Tinder.
I haven't done that in a while.
I can roll up on your Vespa.
This is unrelated to the Vespa.
But sure, yeah, also that.
I found Tinder really annoying.
The last time I used it, it was like, it must be like over two years ago.
I found it really annoying.
My results were dismal.
I got really frustrated with it.
Just pissed me off.
So I gave up on it.
But I never canceled my subscription.
I've been paying for it for like once a year.
Even though it's free.
I got like gold or whatever.
Whatever.
It does like all dating apps thrive on people not getting together.
Yeah.
The longer you're on the app, the more money you're spending.
True.
True though.
It always rubbed me the wrong way.
Those sorts of things.
Kind of like gyms, which they operate on selling you a gym subscription
and then hope that you don't use it.
LaMalle.
Yeah.
But anyway.
And they make sure you don't come to the gym by putting spiders all over the equipment.
And then you don't want to touch them.
They love that.
They love their spiders over at Workout World.
I still have a small little blip on my credit history from when I canceled my card
rather than continue to pay Workout World their fee for the rest of the year that I had signed up for.
Fuck them.
I'm done.
I got nothing.
I got nothing else.
I'm empty.
I'm feeling a little lightheaded.
Do you want to do voicemails?
No.
There's going to be something I can say.
Oh, Boris Johnson.
He's resigning.
Oh, fucking the Shinzo Abe is dead.
That's not Boris Johnson.
No, but they're both Prime Ministers.
Oh, I guess so.
Well, that's the news, everybody.
Did you see the gun that the guy shot Shinzo with?
Yeah, it was made of plywood and like gaffer tape.
Yeah, hit him with a contraption.
Very, very good.
Like a slingshot scout with bullets in it.
Yeah, built out of like 3D printed, whatever stuff.
See, America, you have no excuse.
It is so sad that Japan has had two gun related deaths this year and one of them was the Prime Minister.
Well, the former Prime Minister and we have fucking 200 every fucking day.
And it's never a politician.
It's always children at school.
Children at school and I don't know, random people at parades.
Yeah.
I mean, never the important people who do bad.
It's embarrassing.
By existing.
It sucks so much.
It's so sad.
I think if we were killing 200 politicians a day, things would actually get done.
That's all I'm saying.
Direct those bullets in the proper direction.
You got to get a bullet mirror.
I reflect them.
I retweeted on the endless war account a post showing, you know, the guy pulling out his like weird giant like homebrew gun.
And the caption was the stranger there among them had a big iron on his hip and he did.
This is big iron.
It's great.
Did anything else interesting happen?
No, no, I mean, interesting things are always happening, but we're used to them.
So they're not interesting.
Like the Ukrainian war is still happening, but nobody's talking about it.
Oh, right.
Yeah, that's I'm over that.
They occasionally check the news to see what has been happening and it's like Ukrainians being pushed back a little bit more.
Oh, dang, it looks like Russia is going to get the Luhansk region or whatever it's called.
Oh, dang.
And that's sad.
But they're still fighting.
So, you know, it's just sort of like the same.
Well, yeah, there is no news about it.
They have been bombing.
There was like a talk in Kiev and they bombed somewhat.
No, wait, it wasn't in Kiev.
I don't know.
They just do in bombing.
They do in bombing.
Oh, did I?
I mean, yeah, I know that it's still going on, but it's so like I have nothing to say about the war in Ukraine.
But did I mention last week that that that indie apocalypse thing came out, that thing that featured my game in it?
I don't know if you mentioned it on the show, but I did see it on Twitter.
Yeah, that guy, pizza pranks.
The this month's this month's issue of indie apocalypse is out on itch.
You can buy it and it's, you know, it features, you know, a little write up of my my game and that's pretty cool.
This guy, this guy, this guy gives, he gives basically all the money that he makes selling his, his zine to the, you know, to the people that contribute games to it.
So he seems pretty cool.
I was, I was going to be on like a, I had, I had signed up to be on like a, like a, I guess not a, I don't know if it's a live show, but sort of like a discussion show.
I was going to have like a little segment, just like a little brief, like creator interview segment on like a little show, but I like didn't see the email in time for when it was happening.
So I missed it.
Yeah.
Oh well.
Is it discussing the game?
Yeah, I think he was, I think they were going to like, you know, ask me stuff about the game or something.
So, well, maybe next, maybe I'll be on the next one or something.
But seems like a really cool guy.
And I just think it's really neat.
But he's like, you know, he's selling his zine, but like he's not out.
He's not making any money off it.
I should be.
He's doing all that work, organizing things.
He's just doing it for the love of the games.
Yeah.
He's very pure.
He's pure of heart.
He won't last one second in this industry.
Well, I mean, he's been doing this for years.
He'll die by the end of the day.
I'll make sure of it.
Oh, he's weak.
I bet we can undercut his market.
Yeah, we can buy him out.
Revs up chainsaw.
If he's if he's not gouging, then we will download the zine and sell it at a markup
and then bully him off the site.
We'll download his digital zine and we'll mint it on the blockchain and we'll sell it as NFTs.
And then we'll print it on paper and we'll sell physical copies in real life.
I think I saw like somebody, an article talking about like, what if you could have a physical
version of your cryptocurrency?
That's like making like little coins or little paper.
That's what slime coin is.
It's the first cryptocurrency that's in, you know, non-fungible physical token.
Yes, that's what it is.
There's like a little, I think it was on some Twitter that like crypto bros taking L's.
Yeah.
No, it's just like, yeah, Bitcoin, but like paper version.
Look at this.
We've got like a thing on it.
There's coins.
It's like, oh, wow, interesting.
Stupid.
Fascinating.
You have this piece of paper and then the value of it fluctuates.
By the time you're handing it over to the cashier, they said, oh, this is not enough,
actually.
This is the...
Not enough to pay for the thing you were just about to buy.
No, because the price just fluctuated.
Yeah.
Right.
This is like...
You just stand there for a few hours like, it'll go back up.
I'll just wait.
No, it's...
This is like the mindset of people that reinvent vending machines and call them bodega boxes.
I've heard of bodega boxes.
What are they?
They're just vending machines.
They're just like bespoke vending machines that are like horizontal.
Like you lifted them up like a treasure chest?
Someone just invented a vending machine but like shaped it differently and thought it
was a new invention.
What was that?
Wall.
You ever see that thing, juicero?
Juicero, yeah, I know that.
Yeah.
The guy who sold packets.
The thing that Casey Neistat really liked.
Oh, god, really?
He had one in his office for a while.
He's just like, oh, I love this thing.
What a fucking moron.
Juice is great.
I know.
Okay, wasn't the thing with juicero that like it's literally just a machine that you
put a pack of juice in and the machine just like opens the pack and squeezes the juice
out of the pack of juice that you bought?
Yeah, if you puncture it, you can squeeze it out yourself.
Or you could buy our proprietary machine that will puncture and squeeze a juice box
for you.
It's just so stupid.
Insanity.
Casey Neistat really, wow.
I mean, he doesn't look too hard into things.
It's like, oh, cool, new tech and I love juice.
I always get a juice from the local juice place.
I haven't thought about Casey Neistat in a while.
Yeah, I don't know what he's doing.
I think he may just still be doing Casey Neistat vlogs.
Yeah, sure.
He's a celebrity.
Why would you ever have to do anything else?
Yeah.
Good for him.
He's juicing.
He's blogging and juicing.
Juicing and blogging.
Yeah, I mean, I only heard of juicero after it was already a meme.
I didn't know about it when it was a real thing.
I didn't hear about it as like a cool thing,
but I only saw it in that Casey Neistat thing.
It's like, dang, he's so rich.
He's got a juicer.
I didn't know that it was a stupid idea.
I just thought, oh, I guess he's a rich guy.
He has rich people things.
Damn, I wish I could afford juice.
I just assumed it was like better than normal juice.
No, man, juicero juice is like, this ain't your daddy's juice.
I guess the idea is, oh, freshly squeeze,
like you squeeze it and then drink it immediately.
Yeah, but.
But it's already a juice.
It's just in there.
He just reinvented a juice box that you can't open.
It's a fucking capri sun.
Yeah.
A capri sun that you need a contraption to get at.
Oh my God.
You're going to hit him with a contraption with the thing.
How many times, how many times have you done the put the the straw
through both sides of the capri sun when you're trying to drink?
I mean, I probably did at least once as a kid.
I've done it a lot of times and it's very like I have to be very sure
that the two sides are not touching when I start piercing the thing.
I can't even remember the last time I had a capri sun.
Well, I guess it hasn't been.
It's been a while for me as well.
Maybe.
Maybe I had one.
Probably been at least 10 years since I've had a capri sun.
It hasn't been that many for me.
The last time I had one, I was struck by how small it is
and how thin the straw is.
Yeah, it's very small.
I guess, yeah, it is very child size and child would not have so much of a problem.
There's just not that much juice in there, actually.
That's like, I feel that way about cereal boxes.
Like a box of cereal, like a normal size box of cereal is like so small.
It's like a couple of bowls for me.
Yeah, yeah, the bowls keep getting bigger.
Bowls keep getting bigger.
I stay the same age.
I don't know what that means.
That's the opposite.
I keep getting older.
Bowls keep getting the same size.
Bowls keep getting bigger, but I stay the same age.
It means that during one year, the bowls just increased.
They're just new bowls and they were bigger than the previous bowls.
I'm just getting hungrier, I'm just getting hungrier all the time.
So I'm pouring myself bigger and bigger bowls of honeycomb.
The honeycomb is already big, but the bowl also has to be big as well to accommodate
how many honeycomb I want to have in one sitting.
It's a lot.
I had, oh my god, I had a genius idea.
I am a genius.
I've been related to the current topic of conversation.
Do you want to know my G?
Wait, before we move over, here's a fun hypothetical.
Would you rather eat a cereal that is very tiny, tiny and is like millions of them
and you have a giant spoon that is like the size of a bowl in and of itself to eat from
or would you like cereal that's large and bulbous like pieces
but a tiny teaspoon that can't like lift even one of them without it falling off?
Which one?
I think in either scenario, you just eat it with your fucking hands.
I guess the big bowl spoon with the small pieces
because you can kind of just like drink it like a soup, I think.
Small pieces?
You said like the cereal is made of like tiny, tiny little bits, right?
Yeah, tiny little like almost like sand.
Yeah, well I think in that case you could just kind of drink it out of a big bowl spoon like a soup.
Yeah, yeah, I guess.
Versus like the tiny spoon with like a cereal is big.
It's like, well that's just tedious.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I'm going to go with that one.
No question.
Comments down below?
Tell us what you think.
Big spoon, little cereal?
Big cereal, little spoon.
Only choose one.
My genius idea.
What were you thinking?
As I mentioned, I have gotten back to progressing on the Slime and Punishment book.
It's getting there.
For the Vapors 2 Kickstarter, the stretch goal was the pin.
Well, there were a few but there was the pins and then there was just money.
Just everybody gets a dollar back.
I still have my dollar somewhere.
You still have the class war dollar?
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
It's in my wallet.
I might do something like that again, but I was thinking instead of the pin, what if I included,
what if I put a podron in?
What if I gave everyone a podron?
I could put a green crystal.
Ooh.
I could get a green crystal.
Like a little 3D printed plastic green thing?
No, I was thinking like an actual, you know, crystal stone.
Like a real stone crystal?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Like some, um, uh, fluorite.
Green fluorite is nice.
Adventurine.
Uh, I'd have to look into what looks good.
But yeah, you could just buy some.
I just give everyone a little po- crystal.
That would be cute.
I think that would be pretty cute.
And then I have a second idea.
Wait a minute.
What if I, what if I gave everyone slime?
What if I could give you some slime?
What if I could make you, it's a little like, a little bottle of like candy.
A little bottle of like, a little green, like candy slime.
Make a pear flavor or something.
Holy shit.
That's a lot of intricate work.
So you'd have a tiny little plastic or glass bottle with like a cork stopper?
Well, I think it would be screw on top.
Screw on top.
Well, I'm just thinking about the size of the thing and like, how many screw on tops
are that big?
Well, here's the thing.
That's more, I mean.
Well, I, well I buy flavorings in little glass bottles with screw on tops.
So, I mean, I would just, I would just have to buy in bulk, you know, maybe a few hundred
little, little glass or plastic bottles with screw on tops.
And I'm sure that that's the thing I could get.
And then filled with tiny little green, or not tiny, but like gummies of slime?
No, I think if it was just, I would just make like a, a sort of like viscous green candy goo.
Just put it in there.
With a, with a little label on the, on the front that says corrosive or like danger slime.
Yeah.
Danger slime.
Why not?
Uh, I looked into it.
I'd be, okay, the book is going to be big enough that like, I will not be able to send
it like an envelope.
Like I saved, I saved on postage with the vapors because it was thin enough that I could send
it as an envelope as opposed to a package.
The, this book will not be able to do that.
So I might as well put it in a, in a box.
And if I'm putting it in a box, like I might as well make use of the space that affords
it to throw a bunch of extra shit in there, like rocks and bottles of slime.
Fuck it.
Uh, so maybe make those, that'd be a cool stretch goal, I think.
Get real slime.
So what would it be made of?
Would it go off?
No.
Uh, I would use, um, it would just be, it would be the same thing as a gummy, basically.
Just, it would be like a corn syrup, sugar, water, acid solution, uh, with flavorings
and colors.
And, uh, I would, it would, potassium sorbate makes such things, uh, theoretically, infinitely
shelf stable.
So, no.
I'm just wondering.
Last forever.
It's meant as a food.
Yeah.
The customs might be, there might be some complications with all that.
Internet, international maybe.
I mean, I just-
You could just say it's not a food on, when you write it down, but like, if people are
to eat it, it should be, uh, it should be able to survive transit.
Okay.
Here, here are some thoughts.
One, I could probably make it with nothing.
Like, nobody, like nobody's allergic to like sugar, right?
Uh, well, if you have ingredients on the back.
Yeah.
People can judge.
Um, so I might be able to make it something that is like, you know, basically there's no
possible way anyone could have any kind of a reaction to it.
There's no, nothing in it is, is allergenic at all.
Um, I could just make it a non-edible.
Like, it wouldn't have to be edible slime.
Uh, if I, if I went with the slime idea.
Um, I did do a quick Google to see if you are allowed to send liquids in the mail, and you
are, uh, as long as they're in like, you know, a watertight container.
Uh, although, yeah, internationally, you know, it's hard to say if there would be complications
with that.
Probably, it would be fine.
I mean, Amazon must ship bottles of stuff in the mail.
No, yeah.
Other countries.
It's, it's, it's just a matter of declaring what is in the box.
Yeah.
And it being true.
And then when they open it to check, if they're like, I'm not sure about this or is this slime,
this viscous, uh, edible liquid, they look at it.
Yeah.
And like, if they'll determine just randomly, depends on who's looking.
Uh, whether or not they're going to seize the package or whether it's fine and they
can go through.
Uh, I didn't have, the only problems with customs that I had were like, because I declared
that the value of the contents were what they were, it ended up being like expensive because
I declared the value, which is a problem I can get around by just, just lying about how
much cost.
I think the idea of declaring the value is that you can get reimbursed if they lose your
package.
Yeah.
But it's such a hassle to ask for that.
Oh man.
So I finally got, I mentioned before, I have some packages that were returned to my PO box.
Um, well, I got, I finally got access to the Kickstarter backer report and I cannot find
these names.
I, I have looked through my Twitter DMs.
I have looked through my PayPal records.
Names of who?
These are, um, the names of, I think it's two people that bought, uh, Pleven the Wee
and two people that bought a Road to Radcon or, or I, or I thought that maybe they were
like backers, like Kickstarter backers that had, that I owed a Road to Radcon book to
or something like that.
No, no, that wasn't, no, yeah, that was, was that a Kickstarter?
Yeah.
That was a Kickstarter.
What, the Road to Radcon?
Yes.
That was a Kickstarter.
That was like, that was a stretch goal.
Yeah.
It was, it was two, two blue, two blue rays and two of the Road to Radcon.
So I thought I could find, because I have their names and I have their addresses, but
they were returned to sender.
So I thought these addresses must not be valid anymore.
So I was going to go contact those people, but I couldn't find their contact info.
Uh, and then I got access to the backer report and I can't find them.
I looked up their names in the backer report and I can't find them.
There's, they still elude me.
Hmm.
Yeah.
So I, I, I'm no, I'm no closer to figuring it out, but it's a bit of a bummer.
Uh, if I, if I, if it's, if it's, if it, if I just can't find anything, then I will probably
just put them in the mail and send them again to their original location and just hope that
they make it this time, because that's the only thing I can think of.
I guess so.
I mean, can you, you have like their name on the envelope, but you don't have what like
username that corresponds to like, you don't know who you could ask on like discord or
Twitter.
I, I don't know.
I don't, I lost that.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, you could dox them.
You say, um, excuse me.
Is anybody called this name?
I looked through, like I looked through cause like, you know, they had to give me their
address on either they had to DM me on Twitter or they had to include it in their PayPal order.
So I looked through all my Twitter DMs and I looked through all my PayPal orders looking
for these names or addresses and I came up completely empty and like, I, I wonder if
I'm forgetting some, somewhere, but I can't think of anywhere else that like I would have
gumroad.
No, nobody, no, nobody bought.
Oh wait, maybe.
No, I think, I think I checked the DMs on the PCP account too.
I think I checked the DMs.
Did I?
Maybe I should check double check the DMs on the PCP account cause it's a separate account
with separate DMs.
I don't know.
That might be worth double checking.
I just want everyone to get the shit they bought.
Yeah.
And, and, and also there are two people whose addresses I know three people, there's three
people whose addresses I do have.
I know where to send them.
It's just that I don't want to make the trip to the post office until I can get until I
have all of them and I can make one trip.
So there are a couple that I could have sent but I haven't sent because I'm waiting until
I find the other addresses so I can go all at once and it's been weeks and weeks.
I can't fucking find these, these people.
Yeah.
So.
It's way too hot right now to just go outside.
I, I need to send a Lord of Ghost or two.
I will wait until winter.
I just wait for a really long time.
Yeah.
I mean I, I can, I can, I can pop things in the, I guess, I guess in theory I could just
post digit myself and put it in a mailbox instead of going all the way but I like to
go to the post office because if it's international mail, I'm never confident that like I've
postaged it right.
I'd like to just give it to them and have them weigh it and have them tell me, okay,
it's this much, just pay me with a credit card.
This gives me a lot more confidence that I didn't fuck it up.
I've been talking into the microphone.
I feel like my, my voice is not being.
No, you've been talking into a brick wall.
I think maybe I'm, I've been sitting further away from the mic or not facing directly at
it this week.
So sorry, Eleazar.
Maybe you got to maybe boost my levels or not.
It's up to you.
You might have to boost my levels as well because I think my microphone input is lower
than I expected it to be, but I didn't want to change it halfway through.
Yeah.
I don't want to move.
I don't want to move mine halfway through either.
Uh, so I won't, uh, the, uh, yeah.
I was thinking about, thinking about stretch goals again.
Slime.
Ha ha.
Podrons.
That seems really fun.
I think that would be really fun because, because I've, I've, I'm already because I know
postage is going to be expensive.
Sending these packages is going to be expensive.
I'm, I'm, so I might as well just go crazy with it.
If I'm going all in and sending like boxes, I might as well use that box space.
So why not crystals and bottles and, uh, whatever the fuck.
God, it's going to be, I kind of want it, but like shit, how much money could that be
to, to, to cost?
Um, hmm.
How much am I going to have to pay for the whole package?
I don't know how much the book is going to cost.
I'm hoping that I can sell the book for like less than like $35, $30, but I don't know
because I haven't like finalized it and send it to a printer yet.
That's a lot.
This is full color.
It's like a million pages.
Yeah.
It's cause it's, it's going to be like 220 pages or something.
And yeah, full, full color is like full color is really rough, man.
I guess that's why with, when they, when people make comics, they have like an issue
and it's just a little bit, just a little bit, just a, just a couple of pages, one page.
Yeah.
And then when they sell manga volumes, uh, it's always in black and white.
They never have a single bit of color on those cause there's so many pages and so many volumes.
Yeah.
Making real small.
It's just, I think that's what I will do next time.
If I make like a large thing, I'll try to make a manga volume of it.
What do you mean?
Like if I make a, like a Clarissa or, I don't want to do bell jade cause bell jade is in
color, but like anything that's done black and white, I want to make, make a manga volume
size of it.
If it becomes long, like if I come up with like, oh lord of ghosts chapter act three and
further adventures of lord of ghosts.
You mean you wouldn't print one, you mean you would print one that's bigger than the
one you already printed?
No, no, I print it smaller.
Like the, you know, manga volume size.
I mean, that's like a couple hundred pages, right?
No, no, no, like, like physical like height and width.
Oh.
Yeah.
Like page size smaller.
Page size smaller, but more pages.
Yeah.
It would be easier to, to, to send to people.
And also it's cute.
Yeah.
I see.
No, I kind of, I kind of want, Slime and Punishment is going to be kind of a big book.
Like the pages will be kind of big.
It's in full color.
So that's, that's expensive.
So, you know, and then it might be kind of heavy.
Dang.
Postage might be.
Bruh.
I don't know.
Postage.
What was, what was Postage?
You're looking at a premium luxury good here.
God.
I mean, yeah, true.
Let's see.
USPS Postage Calculator.
How much do you think like a, how much is a book cost?
Or way rather.
How much like a, like a, like a, like a kind of thick book, like a Homestuck volume.
Homestuck volume.
A pound?
I don't know how much a pound is instinctively.
Wait, wait, hold on.
I'm going to weigh it.
I don't know what, what a gram is instinctively either.
You know what?
I don't know.
Freaking anything.
Okay.
I'm going to weigh this copy of secret in the basement by Ululilia.
All right.
I'll be right.
I gotta go to the kitchen.
Okay.
Let me Google secret in the basement.
Secret in the basement.
I don't know how to spell it.
Ow.
Okay.
It was 27 ounces.
And a, a pound is, is 32 ounces, right?
Trying to find an image of the secret of the basement as a physical thing because I don't
can't imagine the size of it.
It is fairly thick, but at the pages are smaller.
So I figure it would like actually probably this is underestimating the weight because
these are going to, because it has like, you know, regular white tech, black text on white
page, interior pages, whereas slime and punishment will have, you know, like color printed pages.
So it'll probably heavier.
What, what thickness?
Do you know the thickness of the pages?
Uh, I, I don't have a bunch of pages changing the thickness by like a micrometer or whatever
is like going to do a lot to change the weight.
That's true.
Yeah.
I mean, I want them to be sturdy.
I mean, don't, don't have like flimsy, but like as small as is reasonable.
You should go for.
No, I do not want a flat rate box.
You sick buck.
If you want, you can go to like a craft store and check out the pages, the paper they sell
and they might have like, like descriptions of what the thicknesses are.
Oh, you know, I ordered a sample of some, not from Mixam, but from some other printing company.
So I do have like a little box of like sample papers with like number, you know, like paper
weights on them.
I don't, yeah.
I'm just, okay.
Then to the United Kingdom, the value of the item being made.
All right.
Let's just pretend it costs nothing.
Calculate based on size and shape.
All right.
We'll say it's a package.
I'm going to say it costs, let's say it's three pounds.
We're going to overestimate.
Yeah.
Three pounds.
Like the, the podron and all the other stuff in there.
How much is this going to cost?
Oh my God.
Oh no.
Is it like 400 pounds?
It's $42.
It's what?
$42.
To send it?
To send a first-class international package that weighs three pounds to the UK.
That's just the, this postage.
That's just for the postage.
The cost of, of the, the book and everything.
That's bad.
That's really bad.
Yeah.
I mean.
Okay.
You're going to have less people saying, yes, I can afford that.
I mean, yeah.
Hmm.
That's something to think about.
Well, how, like approximately how heavy is the book going to be?
Because three pounds may be too much of an overestimate.
It'll probably be between two and three.
Okay.
What does it say for two?
Is it basically the same?
Let's see.
Two pounds is, um, $27.
I mean.
That's a lot.
It's better.
Actually, no, it's not that much different.
It's almost 30.
Yeah.
I mean.
Well, let's see.
One, one pound.
I'm going to bet it's going to be like $16 or something.
Wait.
One pound is also $27.
Oh, then go heavier.
Well, let's see how much is, is four pounds then.
Four pounds is $57.
So I guess there's a minimum.
I guess.
I mean, yeah, it's, it's a package.
So it takes up physical space, whether or not it weighs too much.
20 is $27.
Just the, the, the total minimum, uh, they let it cost to send any package to the UK.
From whatever surface you're using, I guess so.
I'm just using the USPS.
Uh, yeah, even if it only weighs 10 ounces, it's still $27.
Dang, really?
I was sending, actually, no.
I was sending the letters, the large letters to America for like eight pounds.
I mean, yeah, 11 letters.
I was sending things as large envelopes, which is a lot less than this.
But sending the, the, the packages with the, the Lord of Ghost plush in and I was only like, like 12 to $15 on this thing I was using.
Let me check.
Let me see how much does it cost to send one to Chile?
Wait, what?
It didn't even ask me.
Okay.
Calculate based on size and shape.
Let's give us, okay, three pounds, three pound package to Chile.
Again, $42.
Is it, is it same if I go for two, $26 for two pounds?
Yeah.
Um, all right.
Well, I mean, that's, that's troubling.
That's troubling.
Hmm.
Maybe a stretch goal could be like no mailing fees.
I, I mean, that would be, hold on, let me, let me check.
Last thing I want to check is how much does it cost to send like in like domestically?
Like what's the difference?
It probably be quite a lot less.
I'm sure it will be more than half.
I think something like 20 or 25% of people that bought my shit are like international.
So like most of them were in the US.
So from my zip code to any other fucking zip code.
And let's see.
Okay.
Let's say three pounds, three pound package inside the US.
Damn.
It's still $18 to send it inside the US.
Okay.
Now, now this is tricky.
Media mail, media mail would only cost $4.80 for a package for a package.
Okay.
The rules of media mail are you have to, it has to be like media, like it has to be
books or like, I mean, digital media is okay too.
DVDs and CDs are okay.
So I could do it for cheap if it was books.
Technically, I would not be allowed to send it if it's got anything else in there.
So the slime and the podrans would be, it would just be a question of can I get away with it?
Which is questionable.
Yeah.
But I mean, that's a difference between $4.80 versus $17.90.
Even domestically, that's infuriating.
I mean, you should definitely use that for anyone who just gets the book.
Oh, yeah.
Could you not talk to them and ask them?
It's technically part of the book thing.
It's like you get the book and you get the little things that come with the book.
Does it not count as like, oh, it's like a collector's edition of a thing.
It's media.
I think.
It's part of the media.
I'm pretty sure that by the letter of the rules, it's like, no, you're not supposed to have anything but books in there.
On the other, I mean, the Blu-rays, they had a case, but the case doesn't count against that rule.
So I feel like if questioned, most officials would probably say, okay, crystals and bottles do not count.
Do not meet the media mail criteria.
Well, is it cheaper then to send crystals and bottles by themselves and the book by itself?
Well, I don't know because there's because then the crystals and bottles, they would still have to go in a package.
And the package still has, you know, these minimum weight requirements.
So it still would cost $27 just to send like a tiny little box.
That sucks.
That sucks so bad.
How can that be?
How can it cost $27 to send any package of any, even the smallest imaginable package from the United States to the UK?
Let's fucked up.
It's a system.
It got worse during COVID, for sure.
Yeah.
Maybe it's less expensive to just drive to people's houses and give it to them.
You know, cross country tour.
Like Santa Claus going around the world, dropping it down people's chimneys.
Yeah.
Slime drops.
Okay, I mean.
You should do like a secret, you should do like a slime drop where like you take a picture of like a bunch of slime and punishments and in a secret place and people online have to figure out where they are and find the treasure.
Media mail and library mail are not sealed against postal inspection.
Regardless of physical closure, the mailing of articles at media mail or media library mail prices constitutes consent by the mail or to postal inspection of the contents.
Mailable matter meeting one of the specific eligibility standards.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, only these items may be mailed at the media mail prices books, including books issued to supplement other books of at least eight printed pages, blah, blah, blah, films, music.
So, I mean, computer readable media, enclosures in books mailed as media mail.
What about library mail?
No.
Okay, so no.
I mean, you can read the label on the front of the slime bottle.
Yeah, you're right.
You know, technically, the bottle is just a vessel for the label, which is readable material, as are the contents of the bottle.
That's just a medium to prop prop propel the message of the of the label.
You can put like, like alphabet gummies in the slime, and it would be a readable slime.
Now I like where your head's at.
If I if I make enough letters that could fill at least eight pages.
And you get like a tiny little chisel, and you chisel like words like Rosetta's zone into the podron.
So that's all like material.
Like like type like writing the entire Bible on a grain of rice.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, now we're talking.
I have to pee again somehow.
I'll be I just gotta gotta get out of here.
Splash.
So I watched a video this week.
I watched the new Patricia Taksin video.
You know her?
No, she is a music person.
She also does some film stuff.
I don't know, whatever.
She's made video essays sometimes.
She does music, but she she made one recently and oh, she did a big video about marble madness a while ago.
That was really good.
And I liked it.
This one was about.
There's not a bunch of stuff, but it was it talked about these two songs.
They were like these horror parodies of like like pop songs.
One was shit.
What were they called?
One was called the boys are back in town parentheses to kill you.
And the other one was.
I don't know.
It was about it was the parody of that one.
Kiss me, need the American twilight kiss me out on the moonlit floor.
That one.
I don't know that one.
You don't know that one.
That's a good song.
Anyway, and I would have it stuck in my head.
I had just just the snippets, just the snippets that she played of this parody version.
Because there's a it's not it's not just the song with different lyrics.
There's like there's pitch shifted parts that like change the harmony up.
She played a little bit of like the climax, the song climaxes.
The whole thing is sort of like a Lovecraft like horror, like a transformation is taking place.
And then the final verse is like, you know, she's become a demon or whatever.
She's become a horror beyond comprehension.
Sounded great.
It didn't even listen to the song.
Just heard like four little like 10 second snippets of it.
But I just have those in my head.
And so maybe I should go listen to the song, but no, I don't want to do that.
I don't know why I don't want to do that.
I just don't feel like that's too much effort to click on something to sit down and click on something and then be expected to sit there while it happens.
Yeah. What if I what if I don't enjoy it?
What if I what if I what if I sit there and I feel stupid listening to a song that's not even that good?
What if what if she oversold it?
What if I want to click away, but how how rude it would be.
But that would be but that would be even more effort clicking away.
Where does it end?
Snowballs.
You understand the only winning move is not to click.
Turn that computer off.
But I have to turn it off.
I've already turned on my computer.
I can't like turn it off.
I can't like leave.
Can't stop reading.
Now that I'm logged on, I can't stop posting once I've begun.
I don't know.
It was a good video.
Just wanted to say I watched the video and it was good.
Dude, I've watched a video, but it was bad.
Oh, nice.
That's just as that's just as good in its own way.
Even bad videos can be good videos.
No, they can't.
That's why they're bad.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
Makes perfect sense.
I got a pain in my side.
I keep thinking.
Oh, is it a kidney stone?
It hasn't been yet.
And I hope it won't be.
It's a liver stone.
I don't know if those happen.
It's an intestine stone.
It's a lung stone.
God, imagine.
Cuffing up like granite like gravel.
Oh, you mentioned.
I don't think I you mentioned the thing about the muscle in your neck.
Neck, chin, feeling.
Yeah.
Engorged or whatever fucking crazy shit you were saying.
It's not like it's like a frog that's gone.
You know, like stretching it all out.
I feel sore in the muscles of the sides of the front of my neck.
It's not it's like a sore throat, but it's not the inside of my throat.
I'm sore in the muscles that like are on the sides of my chin.
Kind of the muscles that like, you know, when you look in the mirror and you
like grimace really hard and like you make the cords like the cord muscles
like stand out on the sides of your neck.
You know what I'm talking like those muscles are sore and I don't know why.
I don't they've been sore for like three days.
Are they you mean like the smile muscles?
No, no smiling too much.
Like, you know, you put your hand on the side of your neck and you like tense
your muscles in your face up.
You screw your face up and it's, you know, the cords in your neck.
Oh, the right of the sides.
Yeah, the like archery part.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's like the part just under my chin.
It's just sore.
It's sore like I overused it.
I don't know what is it.
I have a couple of theories.
I think it might be that I was like chewing too hard.
I might have made some like the gummies I made might have come out too chewy
and I just tried to chew them and I made my jaw.
I tired my jaw out.
Now my face muscles are sore in a way that they are not used to being.
I mean, it sounds like it is probably that.
But they've been sore for like shit been sore for like three days.
It's crazy.
I don't know.
It's weird.
The human skull is a strange guy.
It's a soreness that I've never had before.
I've never been restrained these particular muscles in this way before.
Maybe you make it like an extremely strained, angry expression when scrolling through Twitter.
You know I do.
That's as good a theory as any.
That's the seethe muscle is what that is.
Found it.
I've been working it out.
You could tell when somebody uses Twitter and they see you the whole time.
But they're huge bulging whatever the muscle that is.
They've got to put your hands on their necks.
They've got to put their hands in their necks.
Oh, have you been seething lately?
Oh, wow.
You can really tell.
What's that song called?
Kiss Me Out on the Moonlit Floor.
It's called Kiss Me by Sixpence None the Richer.
Kiss Me by Sixpence None the Richer.
There it is.
Let me look at it.
That's the song that seems ubiquitous.
Oh, I have heard this one.
I was thinking for a second that it was like some American pop song that didn't come over to the UK, but I have heard this.
Maybe I just...
Maybe I didn't hum it accurately enough.
It's an earworm.
It's a mere worm.
A mere worm of a wretched insect.
A hive of scum and villainy.
Well, are we done for topics?
I guess we're done for topics, yeah.
Epic.
You want to do voicemails?
Let's do voicemail.
Okay, we're on it.
First one is called Give Ben St. Page 2.
You see in this shit?
Is it the image or link in the next thing?
I've seen this shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I didn't...
I mean, the one called Give Ben...
Yeah, Give Ben Page St. 2.
I'm listening to it. 3, 2, 1.
There's only one second.
Is there...
Come on.
Come on, play.
Is there anything in it?
It's one second.
What?
The second voicemail is...
They said, oh, I forgot to link in the last one at oops.com.
So I think they meant to put a link to an image.
Fine.
All right, I'll post it here in general, I guess.
Yeah.
Oh, I know who drew this, I think.
Vaping is not a crime unless you do it without me.
Ben St., Internet Cloud Chaser, Twitter user,
Crystorian, Vapor, Comic Book Maker, and more.
Ben St.
You poopin'.
Over here.
Over here, I finally arrived.
Come and give me an American pat on the butt.
That's the only kind I know how to give.
Ain't I a stinker?
Laugh track applause.
The crowd's whooping for sure.
Hey, Ellie, is our play a can laugh track please and thank you.
Okay, I hope you did.
I like these poses.
This is exactly how it was like.
Oh, this is you coming to America.
Oh, great, great.
I forgot that that happened.
It's been so many years.
It has been.
Well, so you forgot the thing you said in that page.
What did I say?
You said give and take.
Why would you yell that at me across an airport?
Oh, oh, uh, yeah.
Give and take.
Why would you yell that at me across an airport?
Okay, yeah.
Ain't I a stinker?
It got covered up.
So I fucked it up.
And then you will respect my authority.
I'll read it like Cartman from the South Park.
Oh, that hurt my throat on the inside.
Oh, wait, this is close up with clarity.
Okay.
Wait, so the same scene from a different.
No, it's the same part of the page but zoomed in.
It's just at the end.
It's a little hard to tell what it was not.
I don't think it really needed a close up.
Like I got the picture the first time.
But yeah, this is great.
That's cute.
Thank you.
I know who drew this.
Very, very good.
Very nice.
I like my head.
I like my face.
Is this a reference to that picture of me squatting next to the
fire hydrant pointing at the sticker that says vaping is not a
crime?
Because if so, that's a deep cut.
All right.
Next voicemail is called Ben.
You are genuinely funny and entertaining to listen to low.
Okay.
Thanks.
Appreciate it.
Next one is called Joe Flambeau Prandon McJason.
Three, two, one go.
Ben St.
Have you ever eaten a nectarine?
Yeah.
Okay.
Next one.
They're not that weird.
They're very similar to a peach, but not as fuzzy and maybe a little
tangier.
Yeah.
Not had them.
Oh, wait.
I was thinking of tangerine.
Oh, no.
God.
Oh, God.
No.
So have you ever had an nectarine?
I guess not.
Oh, well, wow.
How embarrassing for you.
No.
You really put your foot in your mouth on that one.
I guess I'm just not that fruity, Ben.
Turn it around on me.
They're good.
Next one is called for Ben, your daddy at utoronto.ca.
Okay.
Three, two, one go.
Up yours, woke moralist.
We'll see who cancels who.
We will.
That was a fun Jordan Peterson moment.
Did you watch the whole video of that?
I did not watch the whole video of it.
There's some other parts that are equally, if not more funny than
what he said there.
Um, was it the part?
He's just.
What rules?
Precisely.
What rules did I violate?
I saw that one.
Yeah.
I'm sure there's more to it.
It's just like he's going insane with rage, but like presenting
because he got banned on Twitter, but he's presenting himself as like,
you know, put on a little monkey suit and screech about it.
A double camera like like interview is just, he's just raging.
It's so insane.
Yeah.
I honestly, I didn't really get it, but like, I mean, I didn't really think
it was funny.
I just found it confusing.
But then the more I saw people memeing on it, I, I found it funnier
and funnier until, you know, the, the Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
memes have been pretty good.
I've been seeing those the last couple of days.
Oh yeah.
You know, yeah.
Pretty, pretty good meme.
Pretty good.
Up yours.
Like who says that?
Up yours, woke moralists.
I've heard, I've heard people say that.
Yeah, but it's just such a tame thing to say.
Up yours.
Yeah, but that's, I mean, that's the kind of guy he is.
It makes sense.
Can't believe you're defending Jordan Peterson.
I'm just saying it's, that's what I would expect him to say.
Yeah.
I feel up yours is more of like a British thing.
Like I've, I've heard that in my life.
I've heard it.
I've heard it here.
It's not a, it's not that weird.
Up your ass.
I'll tell you where to, you can, I'll tell you what you can do where you can stick that,
stick that in your pipe and smoke it.
You,
Stick that in where the sun don't shine.
Why don't you, you can, why don't you, you,
Why don't you, open your anus for me, huh?
Yeah.
Why won't, why won't you do that?
Why?
Okay.
All right.
Next one is called Happy Birthday Ben You Basterd.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Next one's called Rejoice, Ben's Birthday.
Three, two, one, go.
I would say that Ben Saint is kind of like the closest thing we have to Jesus these days.
Kind of became Irish at the end there.
Jesus?
I would agree.
I would agree with that.
Yeah.
Let me get my cross.
I knew it would end this way.
Knew it would end this way.
Next one is called Son of a Glitch.
Oh, it's a Vokeroo.
Three, two, one, go.
My favorite show on the internet, Son of a Glitch.
Welcome to Son of a Glitch.
Today we're going to be talking about...
Mega Man X.
My friends for the DS.
It's like the original Mega Man X, but on the DS and there's some changes.
For example, the UI has one extra pixel on the side.
I thought that was interesting.
Yeah, and it was.
What's your point?
You making fun of me?
Yes.
Oh, well, okay.
Yeah, I thought so.
Mega Maniac.
That's what you are.
What do I have?
I have played Mega Man's 1 through 8.
I have played Mega Man's Wiley's Revenge through V.
I have played Mega Man X through X6.
I have played...
I briefly played Mega Man's Soccer.
It was a nightmare.
I think...
I mean, I played...
I mean, not recently, but at some point in the past, I played 0 through 04.
So I guess I'll count those.
So I have...
Well, no.
Recently, I have played 8 plus 5 plus 6 is 19.
I've played 19 Mega Man games.
Damn.
And I've only got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
I've only got 13 left.
15 if I count Power Battle and Power Fighters, which I do.
So it's 15.
Is Mega Man 64 just by itself?
Are there any other in that series?
Yeah.
Or Mega Man 64, aka Mega Man Legends on the PlayStation,
aka Rockman Dash, aka Dig Outer's Adventure Story in Halcyon Days.
Oh my God.
Yeah, there's two of them.
I had forgotten about those.
Lemau.
I guess that I'm going for...
I mean, if I really wanted to say I played every Mega Man game,
then I would have to play all the Battle Network and Star Force, I think?
No.
Yeah, the DS things and the...
You know what those are?
I don't know what they are, but I know I've seen screenshots of some sort of a DS Mega Man game
that takes place in the internet or something.
That's correct.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's completely different.
It's like a tactical RPG turn-based grid battle kind of thing.
So it's completely different.
And then that's Battle Network.
And then Star Force is...
It's a post-time-jump version of that in space.
They go to space.
Okay.
On the internet.
Oh, the space internet.
Wait, hang on.
Let me read you something.
This might...
Eleazar edit this part out because I gotta find it.
It might take me like 30 seconds.
Yeah, okay.
Here we go.
If you're curious about the protagonist of Mega Man Star Force,
his name is Star Force Mega Man.
And here's what the Mega Man wiki has to say about him.
Star Force Mega Man, known as Shooting Star Rock Man in Japan,
is the EM wave change of the human Geostelar and the Amian Omega Geese.
Huh?
So I hope that explains to you.
Well, I'll continue.
In Mega Man Star Force III, he is registered under Project TC as number 003.
His appearance is also changed after Geo obtained the Hunter VG
and Omega Geese is converted into a wizard.
Oh, the wizard.
Now I get it.
So now you know.
I hope that clarified things for me.
Good stuff.
So I don't know what's going on with those.
I guess they're neat.
I like tactical RPGs fine, so it could be fun.
Oh, right.
We were listening to Voice Males.
Yeah.
I got to download that vocabulary one.
There we go.
Next one is, will you remove the S in Crastinators if Gib leaves?
I mean, yeah, I guess.
Well, no, you could you could change the meaning.
It would be like the procrastinators podcast and you're the procrastinator.
Oh, yeah, I wouldn't have to take the S out.
I would just have to put an apostrophe before it.
Yeah.
That's that's using your noodle.
Next.
Happy birthday, Ben.
YouTube.com.
Guys.
Is it is it?
There's so many YouTube's on the next page.
YouTube, YouTube, YouTube.
Okay.
Next one is Nate Wurstman.
Three, two, one, go.
I'll tell you, baby.
There's one thing I don't like in this world.
No, not dinosaurs.
I don't like Nate Wurstman.
He kind of seems like an asshole now.
Yeah.
He said asshole in front of a baby.
Yeah, baby doesn't know.
I guess he wouldn't remember.
It's fine.
It's funny though.
Dang, the kid hates dinosaurs for some reason.
It's so Jurassic Park.
It was too scary.
The T-Rex was yelling.
Kids like dinosaurs.
I liked dinosaurs when I was a kid.
Kids these days don't even like dinosaurs.
Kids these days, they're so work moralist.
They're so woke.
Kids these days.
Oh, they cancel dinosaurs.
Oh, the woke moralists cancel dinosaurs.
Now kids don't like them anymore.
Nowadays, kids, instead of reading about dinosaurs,
they go on Twitter and they make 14 tweet long threads
about how it's weird how Mordecai from a regular show
is like a creep to women and it's problematic.
It's weird how he like isn't nice to his girlfriend.
We should cancel him.
We shouldn't give him a platform.
Oh, I didn't look into this at all.
I just saw people going like, what the fuck about it?
But there was some controversy about somebody saying Anne Frank
had white privilege.
Yeah.
It's just like, okay.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
See, yeah.
I mean, okay.
Okay.
Whatever.
Yeah.
It's like, I mean, I guess.
It had no bearing on anything.
It's like, it's such a weird thing to say.
Why would you say it?
Yeah.
It just doesn't mean anything because like,
and that it's like, how is that even relevant to like that
historical context?
It's like, if somebody is talking about like the Jews
under Nazi rule and they're just talking about what happened
to them and then you come over and you're like,
they did have white privilege though.
So it's like, what, what is that adding to any of this?
What is that adding any?
You don't need to say it.
Part of me.
It's got nothing to do with anything.
Part of me wants to play devil's advocate and be like,
okay, but like technically maybe they kind of did.
Cause like maybe in some situations in Nazi Germany,
you would have been harassed for being visibly black,
but you know, you can't tell a Jew that easily.
So in a certain sense, maybe.
But then also like no, because I'm pretty sure that the Jews
were like, they were being specifically targeted.
Yeah.
So like probably it would have, I would think it was probably
harder to be a Jew.
I've got to, I think it was probably harder to be a Jew
in Nazi Germany than black.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's true, but it might be.
I mean, if we're going to like go there, I think that there's
not a lot of documentaries made on the suffering of queer
people and black people under Nazi rule, even though we know
that there was discrimination.
I mean, I think there is.
We know so much more about.
They definitely killed gay people and trans people for sure.
Yeah.
But like the thing that happened to the Jews is so much more
like prominent and obvious.
So it's not even a white privilege thing.
I haven't heard anything about like, did they, did they, did
they Holocaust black people?
Like I don't know.
I would assume that they probably did to some extent.
They probably killed people.
Yeah.
But did they like concentration camps?
The concentration camps are odd.
I don't really know what the idea was.
I want to say almost definitely.
I mean it, like they must have.
Surely they would have been.
I wasn't laughing at that.
I mean, I mean, they, you know, they're doing a, they're
doing a master race thing.
Like, like, of course they did.
So I guess, I guess, I guess the argument is like, OK, well,
theoretically, Anne Frank, because she's, because Jews
kind of look mostly the same.
You kind of can't tell them just by looking at them.
So maybe she could have like pretended not to be one.
And maybe it could have worked.
I guess it depends.
The, theoretically, maybe for some people sometimes.
I don't know.
It just seems like an odd thing.
Just an asinine, just an asinine thing to even like say as though
it like means anything.
Yeah.
As though it like says anything about people or society.
I think that there may be an argument.
Jumbling concepts together into like a nonsense goulash.
There may be an argument about like the victims of Nazi Germany,
the ones we talk about mostly being white.
I don't know what happened to the black people in Germany.
I know there were some.
I think there just probably weren't very many for them to kill.
But I don't even know what happened.
We never hear about it.
I mean, that's a question to us.
Like, why do we not hear about it?
Was it because they were black and the historians didn't care so much?
That could have been a race thing.
But it's like where to bring up with Anne Frank specifically.
As if like you're trying to take like Anne Frank is hogging the spotlight somehow.
Anne Frank's diary did not properly center indigenous BIPOC voices.
It was very problematic.
You could make a more like reasoned argument to discuss this sort of thing.
Without saying Anne Frank had white privilege.
Right.
That's it.
I don't know.
Maybe think about it at least.
I feel like I think you could probably construct an argument for why it's maybe technically true under some readings.
Maybe.
I don't know.
But yeah, my gut feeling is that probably there were black people, people of color that got concentration camped.
There just weren't many of them around.
And so it was not like a documented thing that there was like, maybe they probably didn't have like, you know, they probably didn't have enough that they could have made their own like separate camp for them that somebody could have made a document about it.
Oh, like the African American, not American, you know.
The African German.
African German concentration camp that they was next door to Auschwitz, but they never, you never hear about it.
I guess, I guess the number of people, I'm not sure.
No idea of the demographics of the time, but like, they may have still been second class citizens at the time, right?
Is this the sort of time period?
I would imagine that, I would imagine that since kind of the whole thing was like the Aryan supremacy, I got to imagine that.
Non-white people were not, were not, yeah.
They wouldn't have had much of a say of anything.
Well, whatever.
I would think so.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm just guessing.
I'm just thinking, okay, you ever just think about stuff?
No.
Yeah, I don't want to, I want to stop.
It's a problem.
Next one, hang on, did I, did I download that one?
Yes, I did.
Next one is where is best guy ever?
He's all around us.
They said we're.
Oh, so we are best guy ever.
Thanks.
Was Munchy always a member?
No.
No, he joined.
He joined a little earlier than Munky Jones.
Sometime a little bit before Radcon 1?
Was he at Radcon 1?
He was not at Radcon 1, he was at Radcon 2.
He joined sometime in between Radcon 1 and 2, I think?
I have no idea if there was like an official like thing because we all talked to him.
I think it was just like the day that somebody probably Trixie decided to put him in the call
or in the server we were in.
Yeah, probably, yeah.
That is, yeah, that's how it goes.
The next one is, these text questions are weird.
Next one is Ben's weekly reminder to not play Delta Rune Chapter 1.
Hey, guess what?
I didn't do that this week, although I did do it at some point, so sorry.
Next one, new fan here.
Who is this Nate guy you keep on mentioning?
Never heard of him.
He goes on about stuff.
Check him out on the best guy ever on YouTube.
Check him out.
His name is Nate Saint.
He works in a button factory.
Next one is, who is best guy ever?
He's on the featured channels, but I've...
Are these sincere?
No.
I feel like if there's multiple, it's probably not.
And same with Rebel Pixels.
Never seen him either, and I assume...
Like they're cutting themselves off comedically.
They're people.
I mean, if you want to know, you can click on them.
Yeah, you know what?
Yeah, if you really wanted to know.
I mean, do people know that Rebel Pixels is Tom?
It's Tom's old channel?
I assume his channel links to other channels.
It's pretty much defunct.
It is, but if the About page still links to his Twitter, people would find him there.
Oh, you know, I should actually take Tom's links off,
because he said he's not going to be on anytime soon.
I kind of feel like I should take Nate's off,
but Nate got mad at me the last time I took his link off the linked channel,
even though, I mean, it's not like he ever came back.
So I don't know what that was about.
I feel like it should take it down,
but he got mad last time for what I...
There was no reason that I could tell, so I don't know what to do.
I don't want to get yelled at.
Yeah, he's playing the long game.
He's going to come back, but after everyone's gone.
It's a wasteland.
Be king over the ashes.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Just like Dark Souls 3.
Next one is Ben's Weekly Reminder, play Delta Room Chapter 2.
Well, maybe this is the week, friend.
Maybe this could be the week.
It's a very fun game, and I love my friends in the game.
It's probably good.
Next one, Just Be Don't Try to Become.
Saint Benjamin's Wisdom Corner.
Just Be Don't Try to Become.
Why not?
I think they're saying don't just live in the present.
Don't live in the future only.
I feel like you've gone overboard.
I feel like this is overshooting the mark of trying to tell me to be content.
Just pee.
Don't try to pee come.
Wow.
Devastating.
Okay.
Next one is called All Women, All of Them.
3, 2, 1, go.
Hashtag All Women.
I am going to just go nice and lightly and you just leave me on red.
What the fuck?
Wait, what?
Someone left him on red.
Sorry?
Wait, did I see one on red?
That's why I quit using Twitter.
Not Twitter, a Tinder.
Tinder.
How dare you?
Wait, who did I leave on red?
I don't think he's talking about you.
No, because the thing is Gib broke to my heart at bigcry.com.
Who is this guy?
Maybe the next one is relevant.
Oh, maybe.
They'll give you can do better.
3, 2, 1, go.
So I'm listening to episode 317 and Gib, please, I like you, but please brush up on British politics.
You say so many wrong things.
Okay.
Boris Johnson did have no confidence though.
We do have times in the UK.
Boris Johnson didn't have a referendum against Theresa May.
You say so many incorrect things about politics.
Ben knows more than you about British politics.
It's in Palestine.
All right.
Do some research.
No.
Before you speak about these things.
Like I said, I like you, but you get these so wrong.
I want to push back against the idea that I know more.
I was just guessing that the prime...
I didn't know.
I just assumed that the prime minister had terms because I just assumed they were the same as the president.
It's not four years.
That's all I know.
I'll admit, I don't know.
I don't like brush up on my British politics that much.
But like, I remember we were talking like you just wanted to know what the hell the deal was with Boris Johnson.
Yeah.
And I said...
Yeah, because I had.
And I explained the thing with the party gate, which is true.
And then from there, a bunch of shit was said.
So yeah, I guess I don't get everything right.
I'm sorry.
I will never speak of British politics again because I don't care about it.
I don't like it.
Everyone's so annoying.
So there have been prime ministers that have served like more than 10, 14, 18, 20 years.
Well, I guess they were serving successive terms.
Successive terms, yeah.
I think it's usually like five years, although I shouldn't say that.
I shouldn't say that in case this guy gets mad at me again for saying something wrong.
I mean, how often do you...
Wait, do you elect the prime minister?
Well, there's a vote.
Well, how often do you have a vote?
Well, that's the thing.
It's not every four years.
Sometimes it's not every five years.
Maybe it is every five years.
It's just sort of random, it feels like.
When politicians making moves...
It's probably just random.
Politicians make moves and then an election is happening and I'm like, ah, shit.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Are you going to elect someone?
Do they just call a vote?
Yeah.
Sometimes?
Sometimes they just call a vote.
I don't know why.
They must...
I agree with this person that I can do better, but British politics is extremely boring
and there's no people that I can look at to make it easy to digest.
I have to actually read and stuff and I don't like that.
I thought I could find the answer easily, but I have not figured it out yet
from some preliminary googling.
So I guess it's more complicated than I thought.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, we should all do better.
We should all do better.
Namaste.
Go men asai.
Next one is called therapy.
More like take a little bit of these hands.
Three, two, one, go.
Now tell me something.
How can you act like you're anti-capitalist?
You don't like capitalism, but you don't take every single epic game as free weekly game.
I do.
I'm playing Batman right now, bro.
I love being mentally ill, people.
Every so often I'm like, let's see what the new game is on epic games and I get it.
And I never use it because sometimes it's interesting,
but most of the time it's just like, ah, I mean, it's free.
So it's not like I'm losing anything by not having it in my library.
You're losing your life.
Nah, nah, nah.
You're losing my respect.
Look, if the games are epic, okay, how can you say no to that?
If a guy called Epic Games comes up to you and he says, here's a free game.
Are you gonna take it?
Mr. Game, sir?
Is that you?
Yes, child.
It's me.
Epic Games.
Take Batman and beat the unwell.
Yeah, I probably would, honestly.
Yeah.
Can't say no.
Capitalism?
Good, actually.
Did I talk about...
Oh, man.
Did I talk about that one guy, that Irish economist
that I watch on YouTube now?
Patrick...
You may have.
It was a card churning...
It's that guy.
It's that guy, yeah.
Did I mention the thing that he said that I thought was interesting?
That's kind of like the Blitzkrieg economics
where a company spends tons and tons of money to give people free shit
just for the sake of establishing themselves as the market leader
so that then they can raise prices later and make money
once the demand has been created.
That that's kind of like...
It's sort of like...
Companies just spend tons of money to give people shit for free.
It's kind of just how that works out.
Yeah, I mean, it's a good tactic.
That's how Amazon started.
Well, not literally exactly like that,
but they undersold themselves for a long time.
I mean, it's good when it works.
It doesn't always work.
I mean, most of the time, they just blow all their money
trying to establish a market and then it doesn't work.
And then they basically just blew all their money giving people free shit.
I mean, potentially.
However, Epic Games did create Fortnite,
so I think they've got enough to go around.
I mean, yeah.
They had the money available to do this free games every month thing.
Or every week? I think it's every week.
You just log in, you'd get a free game.
My library is filled with things I will never click on.
Just like on Steam, but I didn't spend any money.
Patrick Boyle. Patrick Boyle, that's his name.
You know what I just realized?
I have not played Noida in weeks.
And like fucking finally, the game is a curse.
The game's evil. It sucks also.
It's bad and it's terrible.
I agree.
I don't miss it.
I've had enough. Had enough of its bullshit.
Where was I?
The next one is an injure link.
It's an image of text that says,
reading the responses to the Abe assassination,
or Abe assassination,
it seems that Japan must have been at war with whatever country
trans flag is.
Yeah.
You know, I'll be honest.
I didn't really know anything about that guy.
You know, I mean, I heard after he was assassinated,
I heard everyone saying, yeah, he was like
leader of like a right coalition.
He's kind of, he's a nationalist.
I was like, okay, well, cool, cool, good.
Like a nationalist and we need to return to empire.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I guess it was very anti-trans.
I haven't looked into him that much.
That fits everything else that I know about him.
It wouldn't surprise me.
Yeah.
But I didn't, like,
I didn't know he was a bad guy before,
because I just, I mean, I'd heard the name.
If you'd asked me who was Shinzo Abe,
I might have just guessed,
was he the prime minister of Japan?
Because like, I don't know, what else would he be?
And you already know all the Nintendo people.
Yeah, he's not a Nintendo guy, I'm pretty sure.
But I've just said he was either,
was he like the composer for Dragon Quest
or the prime minister of Japan?
And I would have been right.
That's how you win. You guess two.
You guess two and then you double your chances.
Anyway, I don't know.
I guess he's dead.
And trans people keep on winning, I guess.
The next one is a high-bend.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
You know, it has been exactly 201 days
since I first requested Best Guy Ever
to send me the instrumental .mp3 track
to the Brad Garlinghouse instrumental .mp3
diss track for me to wrap over.
And I think that, you know,
that's kind of a dick move to not respond, you know.
Baby, what do you think?
No, no, no.
Yeah, see, say Nate?
Nate!
Nate Bestman's a big faggot.
Come on.
No.
Well, I guess he just doesn't want to be hashtag canceled.
But, you know, I remember how things were in 2019.
So I'm going to keep saying that word
and no one's going to stop me.
Get me money, please.
Okay.
It's funny, but please don't actually teach your baby
those words.
Yeah, I remember.
Let them figure it out for themselves
so that they can tell you.
I remember he asked me, as in, Voidgazer asked me,
about, yeah, the instrumental track for Garlinghouse
and I said I didn't have it.
And I think I asked Nate.
I think I asked Nate.
I could ask him again.
You know, I guess next time I talk to him,
I'll ask him again if he's got that track.
Nate's not good about doing stuff sometimes,
but I'll ask him again.
Sorry about that.
Next one is Hi Ben 2.
3, 2, 1, go.
Nate Bestman, you fucking Paul Huck,
and you do not believe the instrumental
to the fucking Brad Garlinghouse lecture.
I will release upon you
the most smiteful diss track there has ever been.
Do it.
Do it, Pussy.
Either you or your Asian wife will recover indefinitely
from my sick burns, and you can count on that.
So, release it now.
Well, now I don't want to ask him.
Because I want him to do that.
Oh, was that the last one?
That was the last one, yeah.
Crazy.
It sounded like halfway through that one
that the baby had tackled into the ground.
Oh, you think so?
Wait a minute.
We just got another one.
Or no, we got one 20 minutes ago.
So there is another one, actually.
Baby.
Alright, I think the last one is called
Serious Question Time.
3, 2, 1, go.
You think milk is one of those inherently lewd sounding words?
No.
Or has it become one?
Neither.
I mean, the glass of milk doesn't immediately
conjure my mind sex,
but it doesn't seem out of place in a lewd situation.
I would say that it's more not lewd.
Yeah, I would say the word on its own.
I mean, it's not like milk
actually does anything in sex.
It merely suggests...
I'm being fucked so much that milk is appearing.
No.
Oh my god, that's how it happens, right?
In certain illustrated genres, perhaps.
Not in the real world of real pornography,
where I live,
milk merely suggests breasts.
It's like two steps away from sex.
Honestly, for me, it doesn't even suggest breasts.
It's not even adjacent.
When I think milk,
I think of getting something out of the fridge to pour in my cereal
or to put in my tea,
or to use in a cake.
I don't really think of where it came from,
either others or otherwise.
It's funny that you, the creator of the big boobies mommy milkers,
server would feel that way.
I mean, I am the big boober.
Moon Koon was the mommy milker.
I see.
So it makes sense.
Not your domain.
It's not my forte.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I don't know.
This guy is bringing his baggage into it.
Like milkers as a word.
Obviously, that's slang.
But I don't think of it as the place where milk comes from.
I think of it as in reference to big boobies.
Milking or other ways.
I think this, just because this guy was talking in this context,
it got me making connections.
No, you got to work.
You got to work to get from milk to sex a little bit.
And I hate work.
So thanks for the voicemail.
That's it.
We did it.
We made it.
I don't know.
That guy's going to be pissed.
Or that multiple people are going to be pissed.
It's not four hours long.
Oh, hey, you know what I did?
I actually upload.
There's a new bonus episode.
Oh, fuck.
There's another behind the scenes bonus episode.
It's another hour and some of us talking about whatever when
we're off the podcast.
So if you're a patron, patron dot com slash the procrastinators,
check the pinned master list for bonus episodes.
I think it's number 59.
It's the one at the top of the list.
It's the newest one.
Check it out.
If you want to listen to some shit, you know.
Oh, listen to that shit.
Yeah.
And that's all I have to say.
Yes.
People.
Well, I say people never paint.
Ask me if I'm going to do more streams with Elden Ring.
Yeah.
It's very hot.
So it would be, I would be uncomfortable most of the time,
but maybe during the night, which would be like six to eight,
nine PM EST, I could maybe do, do a stream here or there.
I've, I've, I've mostly been doing nothing,
but I want to get back into the doing stuff.
I didn't really talk about that, but like, I've still got the commissions to do.
I've still got Lord of Ghost things to send a few of those.
How many, how many commissions you got left?
That's six.
Yeah.
Is that more than last time?
I don't remember what I said last time.
I don't even know if that's the right number, but it's a, it's not like one.
It's not two.
It's more and I'll do it.
All right.
Excellent.
But yeah, at some point I might stream.
I feel like streaming is off limits because I have other obligations,
but I mean, if I'm not doing them, what's the harm?
So maybe who knows?
I gotta do it.
I'm gonna, I will do them.
Ben, I'll do it.
I, I know you'll do them.
I'll do it, Ben.
I know you'll.
Please don't hit me, Ben.
I'll do it.
I know you'll do it because I would be so, so disappointed in you if you didn't.
So I know you'll do it.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll keep making my stupid book.
I can't, I can't let it cost $40 to fucking ship.
It will just be like that.
It's, it's unacceptable.
That's unacceptable.
You can maybe get it somewhat cheaper, but it won't be like lower than $20 to $30.
Oh, no, there must be some, there must be some scheme.
There must be some scheme I can pull off in order to reverse my fortunes.
You will have to look around.
I don't know whether Transglobal Express works the other way around,
but they have good prices for UK to America.
I'll Google it.
I think it is a UK based shipping company, but, you know, who knows?
There might be some service that compares rates of these things,
and there might be a better price than USPS available somewhere.
I don't know.
I'll have to look into it.
Maybe, maybe perhaps, perhaps some sort of like fulfillment service
wherein I just send one huge box of stuff and to some,
I send it in one big box to someone who then distributes it for me.
Perhaps.
It sounds like a thing that might exist.
I think, you know what, I think things like that do exist,
but they are far bigger on scale.
So like for the amount of people you would be sending to,
it would be more expensive.
You'd need to like hire out, and not lease,
but like hire out warehouse space to hold it,
and then like salaries of people to move it around
and send it to all the individual people.
They start as like kind of big things.
Like it would have to be like doing at least like hundreds of units.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I'm not sure.
Maybe it's something like that.
I'll look into it.
Yeah, I'll look into it.
I can't, I can't, I can't let it cost that much.
It's unacceptable.
Anyway.
Okay, I guess that's the, I guess let's wrap up.
Become a patron.
Become a patron, get bonus episodes every month or so.
59 bonus episodes.
We haven't done, we haven't done one in a while.
Surely there's lots of like behind the scenes stuff.
There are nine of them now, I think.
Like made or like ready to be made.
No, like made that you can listen to right now.
Yeah.
I think, you know, it'll be a good bonus episode.
What?
I've been trying to get on Nate's case about the OVA.
I'm trying to get him to hire someone to edit it together for him,
because I know he won't, he won't do it.
Or he'll say he's going to do it and it's going to take him like a year.
So I'm trying to get him to just pay someone to edit it for him.
But when that's done, there's probably going to be a bunch of like behind the scenes footage.
And that'd be good, that'd be a good bonus.
Maybe we could do another like documentary, like you do with Radcom too.
Of the recording of the OVA, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'll try and get something like that at some point.
Also, five dollars or more you get access to the Minecraft server.
Oh, I didn't.
You can mine and craft and catch Pokemon also.
Okay, this week, this week I will set up my Wi-Fi extender.
I promise I will do this.
How have you been living?
I mean, your internet has seemed all right right now in this call.
No, my internet is okay.
Like it's not that bad.
It's just...
It's when you stream.
It's just when...
Yeah, or it's mainly just when I connect to the Minecraft server.
Like it's specifically a problem with the Minecraft server.
The streaming thing was not because I was accidentally using my phone data to stream.
And that's why it was really bad that one time.
Most of the time, it's okay.
It's just, it was just connecting to the Minecraft server was impossible.
Um...
So I'll try, this week I will set up my Wi-Fi extender and I will try it again.
And see what happens.
I've been saying that for two weeks, but this time I really did.
Yeah.
Um, okay.
All right, that's the end of the episode.
That's it.
Goodbye.
Bye.