I'm ready. I'm recording my Redman.
Okay, so you're...
I don't even want to know what just happened over there.
So you're doing the Redman.
I'm doing the Redman, yeah.
Oh, God.
I like it. I like it personally.
All right, if you...
I kind of like the unfinished slight jank of Redman.
Like, I'm watching it right now and it makes...
It comforts me on a spiritual level.
The way his body moves is very comforting.
Yeah, he's...
Yeah, it's so squishy.
It's like a bowl of Jello as a child.
Yeah, yeah, he's like...
I really wish my eyes moved where my direction is,
but they just don't.
It really is just like he's full of blood.
If you popped him, he would just...
And what's more comforting than that, right?
What's more comforting?
Exactly.
It's warm.
It is.
Among other things.
Fuck, well, should we just...
Should we go?
Yes, let's just go.
Oh, yeah.
That was a cold open.
Okay, oh, that was a cold open.
Okay.
Welcome to the Procrastiners podcast.
We got me Ben St.
We got Gibb and Take.
Hey, it's me.
And AKA Redman.
Yeah, well, look at the screen.
It's me.
Guys, Redman's here.
Redman's here.
And sorry, guest, fuck you.
While Redman's here.
Not only is Redman here.
Redman Merch is here.
In the form of the ratty fuckers cop killers,
an endless war of pins.
Pog.
The Pog pins from the kick starters are in.
Eleazar, show them.
Show the Merch.
Redman's there.
You can get him.
I have a tweet.
I will link a tweet.
Where I explain.
If you missed it and you want to get in on it,
you want to buy any of this cool shit.
I have that.
I have spent another week this week fucking doing
envelopes and shit.
It's very cool.
They're very...
They look great.
They look so good.
Okay.
Where Redman?
That's the point.
And we got low art.
Our guest today is YouTube man, low art.
Oh, yes.
Who I did a...
Yes.
You want to introduce yourself?
Yeah, sure.
I am the low art.
I make videos.
I am ashamed to say that I am a tuber.
That's a shameful thing to say.
Are you a Vtuber?
Just a tuber.
Not a Vtuber.
Terrible.
Yeah.
It is terrible, isn't it?
This is a...
It's like a support group for recovering tubers.
It's very important to have that because people don't
understand that it's a disease.
It's an affliction, especially when you review other
people's content primarily.
I just review TV shows and video games.
Actually, a funny bit of lore is that one of my very
first videos on my channel is an orchestral cover of
the PCP theme.
Wait, what?
What?
Yeah, you can find it.
It's still up there.
A PCP fan makes reviews.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, it was one of my earliest things.
Endless Jess commented on it calling me a fucking
hero.
It was pretty great at the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I had no idea about that.
Okay, that's wild.
All right.
That changes...
I got to say, this changes everything.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Yeah.
We were just going to relentlessly shit on you, but now
we like you.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Well, that's...
I mean, you can still relentlessly shit on me because
I feel like that's more fun.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good, good, good.
Stupid.
What...
So what have you...
What have you been...
I'm sorry, I haven't looked at your channel in a little
bit.
What have you been making recently?
What have you been doing?
You know, I jump all over.
I started making more video game stuff.
Hmm.
I just made a video complaining about Nintendo being
stupid, which is like just a cottage industry you can
always complain.
Is it about the Melee thing?
Melee taken down Twitch streamers for streaming a game
too early.
Yeah.
Just that stuff.
I always...
I'm in a perpetual cycle of abuse.
You had like older videos about Fullmetal Alchemist and
then you made like a bigger series about it, right?
Yeah.
I had like a big series, but it was old and shitty.
Okay.
And like it was me figuring out how to make videos and I
was doing absolutely brain dead things like mixing the
background audio in with me speaking and then I was
unable to take it apart because I deleted files and I
was just...
It was a struggle.
So I decided to go back and make it less shitty and that
turned out to be a pretty good decision.
So that's nice.
Excellent.
Yeah.
So what's Redman been getting up to?
Hey, Redman.
Yeah.
How you been, man?
I've been done.
I'm all right.
I exist in the 2D, 2.5D realm.
Look how squishy you are.
Have you been working out?
Yeah.
Your stoutness exercises?
I've been doing those...
What do you call them?
Crunches?
Scrumples?
Scree-crumples.
The Redman crumples.
Yeah.
Doin' squashes.
Squashes, yes, squashes.
It's different from a squat.
I don't know how, really.
Because there's no bones or muscles involved.
It's all fluid hydraulics.
It's all like a...
You ever see Big Hero 6?
I'm like that guy.
Yeah.
The Red.
Blood inside.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like...
When Redman works out, it's actually...
It's to keep his outer membrane supple.
That's the...
That's the goal.
Redman is like...
Oh, man.
Is Redman like...
Okay.
Now, I don't think I talked about this specifically in the JDR lecture.
But there's a thing about the slimes, or the jellies, rather.
The jellies are...
They're the white life forms.
And they're just cellular clusters, basically.
They're just fluid clusters.
And they're drawn the way she draws eyes.
She draws them with this big vertical oval.
And they look glossy.
That's just how she draws eyes.
But she's made close-up diagrams.
And she does anatomical diagrams with the jellies.
And literally, the jellies have vertical strips
of ocular cells or something that go up and down
on the surface of their membrane.
Right?
That's like...
They're literally shaped like that.
Are Redman's eyes like that, or does he just have two eyeballs floating in there?
I mean, it's a very complicated thing you just said.
I don't know.
I definitely have eyeballs, but I can't blink for some reason.
I haven't figured that out yet.
No eyelids.
I don't know if Redman needs to blink.
It looks like Redman has seen so much in his time
that he's forgotten how to blink because he must always keep his eyes wide open for any threats.
Is Pupil's moved?
Yeah, when the face tracking breaks, he just goes to default mode,
which means he stares directly at the camera, which is kind of funny.
He bears into your soul.
You know what?
Man, I think we talked about this when Mary was here,
but I think it's cool.
I wonder if there's some simple way to just have one arm.
If I had a V-Tube avatar, which maybe I will work on one,
but I would like to have a face and a body that moves around.
You can do a full VR setup if you're really fucking fancy.
I would just want one arm that I could just gesture with.
That would be cool.
Just one so I could just make a little Italian like,
what are you talking about?
Like imagining a puppet arm on a stick that you could wave in front to be like,
oh yes, I'm gesturing.
That would be cool.
What just simple gestures?
If I was streaming or something, I could have a PNG of an arm and just move it around.
Oh, bad.
Oh, just click it with a mouse and just like...
Yeah, click it with a mouse on the stream on OBS and then drag it around the screen like,
oh yes, something with my hands.
Just like a flat, open palm hand full on front view and just like,
wag it back and forth like, hi guys.
Yeah.
I feel like you could do it though.
I think you could do it.
You might have to like cover one of your arms in like green or something,
like a green cloth so that the program doesn't pick it up maybe.
I feel like it would be from like a user end.
I don't know if you could jigger the software to do it,
but from like a developer end, I feel like maybe it wouldn't be that hard to,
like instead of like a VR glove, because that's how like ones with more limbs work,
they have like VR gloves and feet and stuff,
you could maybe just have like just something you could hold,
like it's just something you could like hold in your hand,
maybe like a like a fucking Wiimote like like light thing or something and like,
just so we could see where that is and it would just move the hand with that single point, right?
It did not like a fully articulated like five finger hand or anything.
Just a Wiimote dangling in the air.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not an arm. It's just an image of a Wiimote.
Yeah, much better because you're a gamer.
It's your hardcore gamer.
Well, we're all gamer girls here, so.
Yay.
True.
Yeah.
So, um...
Yeah, so I wanted to mention about the creation of Redman VR, VTuber, not VR.
I have to thank Mage for helping with one aspect.
She told me that in the way you make these things,
you have a Photoshop file with all the different layers of all the different things
you want to move independently from one another,
and you input that into a thing called Live2D Cubism,
and they have like templates like pre-made anime characters that you can animate,
which means they have like rigged all of the head motion, the body motion, the arms,
the blinking eyes and the mouth and stuff.
You can just apply a new Photoshop file to those existing rigs,
so you don't actually need to make anything.
You just need to tweak it so that it doesn't look strange.
So what I did, what Mage told me about is you can get like a chibi character that they have,
and I just like mapped the eyes to the eyes, the mouth to the mouth, the head and the body,
and then I deleted like all of the hair and the arms and stuff that I need.
And I just exported it. It was very easy.
When I did it, because I asked Mage about it, and she also told me about Live2D.
Wait, I don't think I used a template, although there is like an automatic,
there is like you can sort of just tell it to like automatically map a bunch of like mapping points onto your files.
I made like a Photoshop file from scratch, loaded it in and then just told it like auto-generate,
mapping points, which it did.
I got mine to move its head and to make expressions with its mouth,
and the mouth worked really well, but he didn't have any eyelids, his eyes,
because he had really big eyes, and I think maybe it made him sensitive,
because his pupils would not stay steady, they would kind of like jitter in place,
even if I wasn't moving my eyes.
And I tried to make his hair like flow back and forth, but it wouldn't.
It stayed stiff, and I never figured out why, but I had it so we could tilt his head,
and I could just like Mary's cat ears.
I said it so that he had like ears that you could control when his eyebrows went up,
his ears would go up, and when his eyebrows went down, his ears would go down.
I should fuck around with him some more.
Yeah, I feel like I need to add functionality, maybe eyebrows, so he can be angry,
but the thing I really need right now is-
It's like a robot.
It's like a robot friend who you can like tinker with sometimes.
You can like step in there and be like, hmm, maybe I'll give him like a more robust set of expressions.
Maybe I'll give him like a soul or something.
Maybe I'll make him sad and loose in the end.
Give him some morale, morality, morale.
Maybe I'll give him a dark backstory and a quest for vengeance today,
and you go in and you abuse him.
Redman has the eyes of a killer, you know.
That's well-
He shouldn't because he's a rowdy.
He's a fucking fusser.
All right.
He's like, Redman has the potential to murder.
That's my opinion.
Oh, no question about that.
Yeah, the lore of Redman, if you don't know, is in New Los Angeles City,
aka Neo Milwaukee, also known as Slime City,
there is two gangs, the rowdy fuckers and the cop killers,
and Redman stumbled in one day and he was like,
hey guys, what's going on?
And he loves blood.
He wants blood and he kills people,
but then turns out people in Slime City bleed slime instead of blood,
and so you're just like, well, fuck it, fuck it, whatever.
Can't do anything around this place.
So he's like, he's kind of a weird pacifist.
He's only a pacifist because there's no blood anywhere.
There's no blood.
Wow, it's like a vampire that doesn't kill just because like, why bother?
I can't get blood from these people.
All there is is this dang useless slime.
What a fucking quirky weirdo.
He's from...
That's a beautiful idea.
Fuck, what's the place in Lord of Ghosts?
Oh, it's New New Biggin by the Sea, aka Neo York.
Yeah, he's from New Biggin, aka Neo York, right?
Originally, he emigrated or something or floated across the sea.
He maybe took the train, I don't know.
The tale of Red Man's journey is a strange one.
He probably doesn't even remember.
Yeah.
It's shrouded in mystery, to say the least.
Yeah, yeah.
And intrigue.
And now here he is.
He's gone on a journey and now he's here, guys.
He made it.
I made it all the way to the PCP.
The top of the pyramid.
I love the sassy little head bobs he's doing from time to time.
Yeah, I really like...
Oh yeah, hell yeah.
Yeah, it's so cool to see him move like that.
And then he looks straight at the camera.
I have to finish one.
Soon.
Okay.
Yeah, so what's going on?
What's going on, dudes?
What do we want to talk about?
Do you got any topics to discuss of interest this week?
You know what?
I'm...
I'll think of something.
I always think of something.
I can't believe you would show up unprepared.
Listen, my life is spent...
Oh yeah, there we go.
That's what we could talk about.
Life is just spent being unprepared.
That's all that being...
Like, my life since...
All of this lockdown crap and everything.
And I don't mean crap as in it's stupid,
because you got to lock shit down sometimes.
I just mean I'm hiding out in my house.
My sleep schedule is abysmal.
Waking up at 5 p.m. sometimes.
Going like, what has happened to me?
What have I become?
Dude, I've...
So how are you keeping yourself sane?
Maybe that's a good topic.
I've had quite a week in terms of like sleep schedule.
You know, sometimes I go to bed a bit late.
Oh, boo-hoo.
Wake up, boo-hoo.
But this time it was like, I almost stayed up for an entire day.
Just casually, just like not even thinking about it.
I went to bed at 7.30 a.m. one of those days.
It was just sort of like, what the fuck?
I can't get a handle on this.
I have gotten completely fucked up.
I finally gave up and put up blackout curtains
so I could just like go to sleep at like 1 p.m.
and wake up at like, you know, 11 p.m.
and just go like...
I'm saying that I'm also just completely fucked up.
Okay, yeah.
It's the worst for me and this was where I felt truly like I had failed myself
was I said, you know what, enough's enough.
I'm staying up a whole night and then I'm not going to sleep
and then I'm going to go to bed at a normal time.
And then I went to bed at a normal time
and I wake up and it's like 3 p.m. and I go, well, what the fuck?
That's literally...
That's exactly what happened to me today.
That's the opposite happened to me.
I was like, you know what?
I should really go to bed at a reasonable time tonight.
I stayed up until 6 again.
And I was like, well, I fucked it up.
I go to bed.
I wake up at 11 and I'm fine.
I don't know how that worked.
I mean, if you're in like...
Well, if you're in like a rhythm, I don't know.
Like when you're in a rhythm, sometimes you wake up at the same time
no matter when you went to sleep.
But I've always been waking up at like 3 p.m. then 4 p.m. then 5 p.m.
I was like...
Yeah.
The days just are nothing.
All I'm learning is that we all need help.
Everything is meaningless.
All I have is my video games and anime.
And my red man.
That's all you really need though.
It's true.
And his warm and his blood to keep me warm at night.
Yeah, it's getting cold these winter months.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
I'm all fucked up.
I'm at odd hours.
I don't see anyone.
I got my blackout curtains up.
It's dark in here all the time.
It's great.
I've regressed.
I've regressed to like...
I don't know.
I guess I was gonna like pick a time in my life when I've also been
just like no outside world, no relation to the outside world.
But there's actually been multiple times.
This happens every so often.
It's completely unhinged and off of any schedule at all.
It's great.
It's nice.
I don't even mind it.
Eventually you have to accept it.
Yeah, I'm at the point where I'm accepting it.
I'm like, I'm staying up real late again.
But you know what?
I'm awake.
And usually at the end of the day I'm like, well, that was a long time.
Like sweat off my brow day of playing video games.
It's time to do some art.
It's time to draw.
And I do a little bit of drawing.
And it's, you know, like if I'm awake and I feel like doing some work
right at the end of the day, I guess I may as well capitalize on that
if that's gonna happen.
So just this is how it is.
I don't have any control over anything.
I'm just gonna like take things as they come.
Well, that's the issue is like prime time for me has become 1 a.m. to 6 a.m.
Like when I'm up at that time, I'm working because if I don't,
I have like this sense of what am I doing wrong?
So you just you just plow through work at those hours.
That's probably when Red Man was created, you know, when I one thing I always
find that if I if I wake up and if I start doing something productive
immediately, I will have like a good and productive day.
And if I don't, I'm fucked.
Like if I if I wake up and I start like, you know, wasting time or doing
this like 90 95 percent of the time, I will continue to do that for the
rest of the day.
So like my my like self hack is like, yeah, OK, if something needs to get
done, just make sure that I do something like immediately when I wake
up and then I'm like, I've like set myself on the right course for
like, yeah, my wife.
I won't wait today.
Yeah.
Like she she scared the shit out of me.
My wife, because all of a sudden she just like the alarm went off and then
she did like pretty much a full front flip up out of the bed, just like
catapulting her body.
And I'm like, what are you doing?
And she's like, well, if I don't do this, I'm not doing anything.
Like it's either I get that with this flip.
That is like just just catapults.
I see. OK.
That is like leave the bed with momentum.
Leave the bed.
Yeah. Get out of the bed.
That's the first step.
I mean, some of the some of the days I'm like, most of the time I keep my
phone on my desk out of reach, so I have to get out of bed.
If I want to check my tweets, I want to see the notifications that are coming
in.
Hell, yeah, hell, yeah.
It was a good strategy.
If you the worst is when I wake up and the pure heft and beauty of my cat
is on top of me and I'm like, well, I can't possibly get up now because I
can't disturb the boy.
I fucking hate cats.
I fucking.
How dare you?
No.
They're like that.
And it's so awful.
It's beautiful.
It's the best thing to ever happen to me.
God, no.
Well, how does your cat appreciate being moved?
That's the question.
That's the killer question.
He accepts anything and everything that we do.
He's like, that's very complacent.
Like if I want to get up, I can do it.
I don't want to because he's so snuggly and nice.
I see.
Okay.
All right.
See, it's all about framing.
It's all about framing.
When the cat is like going to attack you for moving them, then it's like, I'm not
in control.
I don't.
I'm a prisoner here.
I'm forced to feed this person.
He's not like that.
But like the cat I have similar is just like completely complacent.
I can pick her up in any way and she will always find an excuse to start licking
her hand, even if she's like sort of trying to get away.
She's just like sort of normal.
Like, oh, it's a person lick.
It's good.
That's so nice.
Yeah.
The beautiful sandpaper ton brushing across your skin.
Ben, I don't understand how you couldn't like cats.
I used to think like you.
I just don't.
Then you don't use, I don't know.
It's just, it's not that I hate them or anything, but like, I don't particularly, I like them
well enough, but like, I wouldn't want to own one.
Like if I see a nice cat, I'll pet it or whatever.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
There you go.
Yeah.
You aren't out here kicking cats.
I'm not out here kicking cats, but if I, but if I woke up and there was a cat on me,
I wouldn't be like, oh, I'd be like, get the fuck up.
Well, like I wake up and he's wrapped around my arm, like just cuddling up against me.
And I'm like, well, what are you doing?
You know, you sweaty being you warm creature.
Hmm.
It's, it's great.
You know, so this, like this cat shows, shows us, we went to go look at the, at the shelter
with all the animals and he's reaching through the bars, just wanted to have belly rubs.
That's how you find a good one as you go.
And that's why I learned I didn't know this until, until this moment was like, it was
right after Halloween, like a little, a couple of weeks.
And we found him.
And I learned that apparently animal shelters often won't sell black cats around Halloween
because people will like buy them to like, I don't know, sacrifice them or something.
I don't know what's going on in the world.
What?
Truly.
Yeah.
Wait, I thought that'd be like a fake thing, but then people there were confirming to me
like, oh yeah, no, we, we can't sell them around then because bad things will happen to
them.
And I just, what the fuck?
All right.
At first I was thinking, oh, you can't sell black cats because it's like a Christmas thing.
People buy a puppy for Christmas and then they don't actually want to keep it.
Like get a, they get a black cat for Halloween just for their costume.
And then they throw it in the dumpster afterwards.
But sacrificing, like what, what is that?
Like, I guess some, you might be right about some of it.
Part of it might be a weird thing for like Halloween festivities of having a costume
piece.
But yeah, it sounded like some people are out here ritualistic sacrifices to the blood
god.
I don't know what's going on.
Well, if you're talking about a blood god, then it's fine.
I'm sorry.
What are people sacrificing for Halloween?
Black cats, man.
Black cats.
Like butchering them?
I don't know.
I don't, that's, that's a question I still have to this day when they said like, yeah,
we can't sell them because people will hurt them.
And I'm like, uh, I didn't know that we live in, in a world where we're still holding on
to superstitions of black cats so deeply that we would go out of our way to harm them.
Geez, geez, frickin Louise.
My cat's a black cat.
Never heard of such a thing.
And she's like, it's great because she's cool and like it looks like a little panther in
the distance in a silhouette sort of way.
Um, but you can't take a picture of her.
I've never been able to show anyone what she looks like through a phone.
It just doesn't work.
It is a struggle.
They're just black blobs.
Wait, I saw, I saw a really good poorly drawn cat the other day.
Um, and I have to, um,
Was it the square?
Show you.
It was the square.
Yeah.
Wait, I'll encase lower.
It hasn't seen.
I will throw that in the, in the boom, baby.
There it is.
Okay.
I'll check out this poorly, poorly drawn cat.
Oh, I did see that.
I didn't see that.
I really like it.
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
Honestly, it's fucked up that it could be shaped like that to begin with.
I don't know.
That's upsetting.
They're liquid beings.
I guess so.
They're like memory cat.
Okay.
Like, whoa, what the hell happened to my eyes just there?
I think blinking fucks up the thing.
They, when you blink, they like jerk back to neutral.
They do something.
Right?
When your, when your eyes are closed, it doesn't know where to put your pupils.
So it just puts them back in the neutral position.
That's what it probably would be.
It's because you don't have eyelids on the thing yet.
Right?
Yeah.
That they're, that yeah, I need to add like a Photoshop layer of the eyes being closed.
I didn't think of that.
Oh, I just saw them do a little twirly thing.
They just did a little like.
Awesome.
I'm just looking at it.
I'm squished.
It's just, I keep looking at him.
He's mesmerizing.
Yeah.
Like a body, like a bowl of Jell-O bearing into my soul.
It's, I love him.
It's, it's so cool.
I, I really, I'm, I'm happy.
I'm happy that Red Man exists finally.
After all these years, he's finally.
He's finally real.
Oh no, he's, he's frozen.
He's staring at me.
He's stopped staring at me, Red Man.
No, that can't happen.
Oh God.
I'm looking, I'm looking over Twitter.
Trying to remember what, what happened this week?
Well, Ben, you said you had some hot goss.
Oh, well you mentioned hot goss.
Maybe.
Okay.
This is a weird, this is a weird story.
This is going to, this is going to sound very bizarre, but yeah,
something happened yesterday that I thought was very remarkable.
So I'm, I'm on Twitter and I'm, and I'm looking at, um, it's a,
I passed by a tweet from that account who I've mentioned before,
who I really like.
Posadist Trapgod, who lives in Atlanta and he's like a,
you know, communist and he's out counter protesting,
uh, uh, some like, it's some like pro-maga, uh, uh, uh,
what's the protest, right?
There's like some pro-Trump protesting going on in Atlanta
and he's out like, you know, he's on the other side.
He's counter protesting them.
He's like taking pictures of them.
He's tweeting about it.
And then I see another, uh, a tweet from someone else.
I don't remember who, uh, from, that's the same, uh, the same,
uh, protest from the other side.
Like this is someone who's on the, the MAGA side of it.
They're tweeting about the Atlanta protest.
So I, I look and I look at the stream and who do I see in this
protest, uh, this pro-maga fucking thing.
Uh, uh, in the stream, then, uh, then May.
Oh.
You got, yeah.
May's there with Ethan Rao from the kill stream.
Oh, of course.
And I watch, and I, and I watch, and I watch for a while as
she and him stand in a crowd listening to white nationalist
Nick Fuentes give a speech about how the governor of Georgia
must overturn the vote and how President Trump must be
president not just for four more years, but for life.
Uh, and they all clap and cheer.
Uh, that's so bizarre that you happen to find that on some
stream.
That's, that's the really bizarre part of this to me.
It's, it's, it's, uh, it's, uh, you know, I had to, I had to
mention it because I was like, wow, that was a journey.
That was a journey that I went on.
Yeah.
I wonder what they were doing.
That's weird.
That's really, really weird.
Like I could imagine if you asked them, they're just like,
oh yeah, we just wanted to see like laugh at it, you know,
have a bit of fun.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You know, how distance ourselves.
No, no, no.
They were cheering.
Oh, what do they say on that show?
Maga hats and everything.
Disavow, they'd say disavow over and over again, I think.
Which, which, um, yeah.
Like, are you a hundred percent sure this wasn't just some
lookalike?
100 I am 100% sure Ethan did you know that did you recognize Ethan Ralph as the Ethan man, okay
Yeah, and I know yeah, I know who he is. I would like to see this
Anywhere to look
It was the kill it was the kill stream
Which is on D live I think so the footage was from the kill stream that you saw. Yes, okay
Yeah, that was the that was the stream that it that was linked
Yeah
the
I don't know. I don't I don't know what else to say about it other than to
A mention that that occurred
You weren't kidding about the hot goss that is that is hot goss. It's wild, right?
Well, just like because if I was reading a work of fiction and this was a plot point
I would say that is contrived
And like kind of silly that this is how something developed
Um, but then here we are
It doesn't doesn't surprise me as much as maybe I wish it did
You know
She she was all on that Ralph retort thing
For a while. Yeah
Oh, yeah, I did I did like she listened to it or she listened to it. She was on it a couple times
Um, I I remember watching the first one where she was on and she did pretty well
Um, but I guess I never watched it. It was all right
I mean, it was like all right in the sense that it was
I could I could see the appeal, but I didn't like what was being said
And I didn't like the people that were calling in. They were very nasty
Lol, yeah, yeah, the chat was very
Special. I I saw some of the chat
A very very special and nice individuals in the in the killstream chat. I gotta say
Oh gosh, uh-huh
I won't uh, I won't I won't go into detail
Wow, you know whenever whenever they passed by a black person. They were like, oh nice
Oh multiculturalism. Oh, no
Oh, oh god, oh no, ah jeez
Ah jeez rick. Any
Anyway clap clap clap clap for me clap for me for doing this this great investigative journalism
One class. Yeah, like look at you digging deep bearing your soul to the world
Just having you really you put yourself on the line watching that line really really getting the scoop
Yeah, really exposing corruption at the highest levels of our government
That's why people need to go to ben saint.com slash patreon
That's what it is. That's what it is
I'll put uh, I'll put I'll put uh, I'll change my description
Change it from uh comics videos and cringe posts to um
Uh, uh journalism and hot goss
Why did did craig just leave the fucking chat craig just biffed out of here craig you absolute fuck
Well, get get craig craig is our intern silent craig is our but deadly craig is our intern
Craig you sack of shit craig handles everything for us
And then he won't even join craig's having a mood. He won't even come back. I don't
What is wrong with him? What do we?
Oh, no, no bench. What do we what do we pay him for? I don't know why I just left the call
You're so mad you had to leave craig
I demand your presence. Okay. Well, this is maybe I'm gonna try to plea with him craig
Please come back. We need you. We didn't mean to call you all of those terrible horrible things in chat
We didn't mean to consistently insult you in chat while we were speaking
Yeah, like I maybe maybe he's a big fan of the kill stream and was like, you know
I'm out of here. He's like fuck this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and teeth are the real fascists. He said
Oh, yeah, oh craig's back. Yeah, craig. Oh, no by craig. What what is he doing?
I don't I don't understand
It says fail to join if I persistently fail to join and maybe an issue with the voice server
Well issue with no, there's no no, there's no problem with the voice server
There's no problem with the voice server. Is there a particular reason why he's named craig?
I don't know. He's just he's just a recording bot and
I don't know why he's named craig. There's actually two craigs. There's a craig two
But we don't need him. We don't need two of them
Okay
Uh, and I don't know why he's named craig
Probably the guy made one of those things
That's how it goes sometimes
Oh
Craig's back. Okay. I guess he's back even though. I just told him to leave. Oh, he failed he failed
Okay, whatever. Well, we'll just have to see it without him. Yeah, if we're all recording it should be fine
Hope hopefully he captured the early part from the pre the pre show
discussion for that bonus episode patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Probably do a behind the scenes a clip show pretty soon. There we go. He's back
He's back, baby
Now we're recording
Now a recording he says in his fucking robot voice craig. I missed you. We're sorry craig
God bless you craig
You're doing a civil service here. Have my babies craig. Oh, yes. Just get deep inside me craig
Oh craig he's a shit you craig salad
Craig left and I'm revoking my permission for craig to enter me. I um, I did um
So kip kip kip from rfck did a meme
Or did a did a uh, uh, uh, what's it called like a ranked a tier list of sandwiches
I saw this on twitter
And I was like I I have to do I have to do my own sandwich tier list now
Uh, I had to yes, I saw that on germa's stream
There's a lot of sandwiches. Oh, I don't think we use you saw you saw my tier list on germa's no the the sandwich thing
He did it
And he had a lot of opinions
I've realized from from from watching that that I don't fucking know sandwiches
There's all of these things that I'm just like what the hell is that?
Like ingredients I understand but like named sandwiches of a specific kind. I just I just guess I don't know so much
There were a bunch of sandwiches that I had never had before actually there were a lot like the
Tied for the biggest uh group in my tier ranking was never had it
Uh, let me read you all the sandwiches. I've never had okay. You croak. Miss. Do you have an image so we can follow along
Oh, um, yeah, sure. Um
If you insist uh, here, I'll post it in general. I'm bad at listening to this visual
I'm bad at listening to bed saying no all the sandwiches. I've never had croak. Monsieur croak. Madame
torta ham bone puree
Monte Cristo tonkatsu
bocadillo
liverwurst cucumber tea
Italian beef and kentucky hot brown
Are these like common sandwiches because I've I I don't know apparently I'm uncultured. I don't know anything about anything
I have not I
I thought a bocadillo was just a Spanish word for like a sub sandwich
I didn't think it was a specific kind of sandwich. Um, Italian beef
I just I may have had that and just not known I was having one because that sounds pretty common
Like you didn't know that the beef was Italian, but it was beef
I I don't know it must be just a certain things on it
I don't fucking know and I and I know of Monte Cristo
I've heard of Monte Cristos and I've heard of tonkatsu's but the other ones I've like
I've never heard of a cucumber tea sandwich or a Kentucky hot brown
um
Mate, I don't I didn't know about these the croaks the croak
Uh couple croak. Monsieur and croak. Madame never heard of it. I
The biggest struggle for me was where to place egg salad
Because on some days egg salad is definitely in the nice category, but other days it's in the good category. I don't know
Egg salad in my own personal opinion is an abomination, especially if it's being eaten in public
You're a fucking mute. You're a fucking mutant
Egg salad underrated egg salad is highly underrated the scent of egg salad pervades
Everything it has ever been around. I wish I could smell an egg salad right now
This if I know you don't when I smell egg salad I just get hungry and I think I'm jealous. I wish it
It's not scrambled. It's hard. It's hard boiled and chopped. It just doesn't smell good though. It's powerful
Yeah, yeah, I I don't know. That's just something I like but I like it sort of like the smell sort of I don't know
Like I I enjoy an egg egg salad sandwich is just sort of like comforting
You bite into it and it's like a sandwich, but it's also like you're having an egg
I
Love it. I like in my personal opinion
I'd I'd rather just eat an egg or eat some bread like I don't need these things to come together
It's such a strange. It's such a non-strange thing to combine though. It's not like like putting an egg salad sandwich
I don't know. I chocolate ice cream with uh, like
roast beef
I love like I love deviled eggs and an egg salad sandwich is basically just a deviled egg sandwich because it's just
Oh gosh, you brought up deviled eggs and now I need to tell something. Oh gosh. Okay. All right, so
Has have you watched spongebob?
Sure. Yes, like okay, so there's an episode in that where spongebob talks about how
um
There's like there's a pinata with deviled eggs in the episode
Okay, and at one point I was talking with my wife about different types of eggs and she brought up deviled eggs
And I was like I can't believe people put those in pinatas
And she's like
She just looks at me and she's like
What do you mean?
And I'm like, you know people will put them in pinatas at parties. She's like you mean in spongebob. I'm like, what are you talking about?
That's a thing people do and I had this gap of knowledge where I had seen it in spongebob forgot
It was from spongebob and thought people were putting deviled eggs
In pinatas
Dude, I can't believe they put february eggs in pinatas. I mean it's not as gross as this, but it's like if you read that like reddit
That reddit that reddit post about like
My boyfriend like literally will not wipe his ass because like he thinks you're not supposed to or something
What?
Like he thinks it's like gay or something like he genuinely is like no guys don't wipe their ass like come on
Oh, of course
Yeah, but anyways, so like I she made fun of me for that
Well, she still makes fun of me for that and rightfully so because I don't know
Yeah, absolutely. I can't believe we put deviled eggs in pinatas
That's pretty wild man. I like that a lot actually
Yeah, anyway, sorry for derailing the sandwiches, but you said deviled eggs and I had war flashbacks
I don't know. All I had to do was um, all I wanted to do was draw attention to the underrated egg salad sandwich. Um
if there's an
Another one on here is the Thanksgiving
My my lowest my lowest ranking for sandwich is I'd still eat it because like there's no sandwich that I think is like bad
I'm surprised PB and J is down and I'd still eat it obviously because to me like
I don't know PB and J. It's a classic. It's a gooder
Put it in my mouth. It's fine
Like, you know, it's fine
it's not
I think it's I think it's odd how like one of the most classic sandwiches is also like the only sweet sandwich
Like every like every other sandwich is savory. PB and J is sweet. It's like it's it's actually like
Completely different from every other sandwich on this list. That's a good point
Yeah, if you think if you really think about it, it's fucked up like it's fucked up
Like it doesn't it is the only other the only other sweet sandwich I can think of is like those weird little
Rolls where they put cream cheese in it. Do you know what I mean?
Um, they're disturbing. They're disturbing creations. They're more like these fancy little like finger sandwiches
Little rolls that they put cream cheese in. Yeah, it's not good. It's like I don't I don't know what you're talking about
Okay. Yeah, it's it's a basically like a circular looking one and they have like cream cheese rolled into it and then
Sometimes there's like fake cherry shit in there. It's not good like a crepe
Um, you know what? Yeah, it's pretty much like a crepe, but it's like a piece of fancy bread and it's not very good
Okay. Okay. Okay. Is it like a rolled up crepe that's been sliced into like a spiral?
Yeah, kind of like that. Okay. Okay. Like you could you could put it that way. I don't know if I would call that a sandwich
But uh, I don't I got you. That's a good point. Yeah, I'm not sure if it it shouldn't qualify as a sandwich
It's an abomination. I mean this brings this obviously this recall the the ancient is a hot dog a sandwich chart
Everything is the sand of the sandwich alignment. Yeah, I I've seen that
What what Ben what is your stance on hot dog specifically?
um
Because I can't yeah, it's it's a yeah, it's a sandwich. Okay. I would agree the
It depends on the
in the merriam webster's dictionary defines
specifically includes a clause in the definition of sandwich that means it can include um
A filling between a split roll and that's what a hot dog is. It's a sausage in a split roll
So yeah, it's yeah, but like you wouldn't call a kebab a sandwich or a or a hero
um
I don't know. Uh, well that well. Yeah, because that's not a split roll. That's a that's like a wrap
Or a pocket so split so the roll has to be something that you could turn into a sandwich if you split it all the way through
although
Well, no, it is it is a sandwich even if it's merely split. I mean like like in terms of like bread
Things like you can't wrap the bread around the sandwich. It has to be cut into
I don't know. I honestly like I'm a bit I'm a bit of a of a sandwich anarchist myself
I kind of think that like uh, yeah, maybe a maybe a euro or a or a pita pocket is a sandwich
I'm I'm inclined to feel like it is even though I can't give like a robust
explanation
Is a pizza pop a sandwich then?
What the fuck is a pizza pop like a like a pizza you don't know what a pizza pop is
Like a pizza pocket like a piece. Yeah, yeah, pizza pocket pizza. I mean you said I envisioned like a frozen like popsicle
Okay, uh
No, no, I think
What makes
What makes it what makes a pita what makes a pita or a euro feel like a sandwich to me is the fact that it's assembled
Whereas like the fact that like the the the pocket is like sealed in a factory
Makes it feel less like a sandwich to me. What if you made it at like home though?
How you you can't yeah. Oh, yeah, you can I've made them homemade before man. What it's good shit. Yeah
So wait, what what is a pizza pocket? Is it like a pizza where the bread is on both sides?
Yeah, it's kind of like it's it's um
Like the crust exterior and then inside you like put the stuff like a calzone
Um
Kind of you know what now I need to figure out the technical definition of a pizza pocket
We could we could I mean we could go down the sandwich rabbit hole
I mean, yeah, we could just talk about sandwiches for the rest of this is fucking is fucking ravioli a sandwich
I mean the little sandwich is basically just just several sandwiches stacked on top of each other. Yeah
A spaghetti is actually just a bunch of like it's just like a
Sort of three-dimensional. That's where I have to that's where I draw the lines
because
No, but because the the topping the the filling the meat or whatever you want to call it
Can go under and over and all over around the bread
carbohydrate in this case
spaghetti
Um, and I feel like that definitely changes lasagna counts
Um, I didn't say that you said that
Okay, I'm trying to think if lasagna counts because like maybe if
If the top of the lasagna and the bottom of the lasagna are both like
Uh, you know the lasagna sheet
And then you know all of the inside is like the stuff
You can't you can't really have like lasagna with all of the the the pasta right at the bottom
It wouldn't be called that
You know
Well, what I'm saying is what I'm saying is that lasagna is like
Noodle it's like carbs filling carbs filling carbs filling
So it's basically just it's basically just a multi layered sandwich, right?
Um, I don't know I would say that that that checks out just because of aesthetic things like it's it's usually like a flat
plane like a bread
Um, yeah, exactly. Yeah, exactly
But spaghetti I think just because of the fact that it's not intended to be eaten
Um in layers. It's just a mulch. It's just a squelch
Of all the ingredients you you you eat it however you like if you put a if you get a ham sandwich
And it's like little little ripped up bits of bread and little ripped up bits of ham and you eat it with a spoon
Is it still a sandwich? I don't think so
Uh
There's actually people are debating this online apparently I just looked up is lasagna a sandwich
This is a years a years long
Uh odyssey like we're we'll never we'll never get to the bottom of it. Nobody somebody somebody said something interesting
Which is impossible pick it up with your hands and eat it
If you're very cool, you can like me if you if you have if you have to eat it with a knife and fork
I think that's I I do I agree. That's that's kind of disqualifying. Yeah
Yeah, I'll give it. I'll give it that so yeah
Uh pasty what are they called?
What are they called so that I can tell you what they are because they're a british thing pasty
um, oh
Different these are uh yorkshire past no it's not yorkshire
Okay, it's like a it's like a it's like one of those jamaican like beef pockets
A pasty god these look good. Yeah, they're like cheese and beef in a in a thing
And it's intended to be eaten with your hands. It's like a work of food. It's like an easy way to have food on the job
That's the other day. The other day I I learned about the worst british food. I've ever heard of um
It was a spotted penis. Is that the one?
Wait, what no the spotted dick is a thing and people. No, no, no, I don't I I've heard of that
I don't know what it is. Um, no what I am talking about is the this is so fucking funny
Um, um, I'm scrolling back because I remember who was talking about okay, okay
It is the the vegan kebab
The what the weekend the vegan kebab
What does it consist of okay?
This was like a you here. I'll post the video. This is so good. Um
There's a whole video on it. Okay. Yeah, there's a whole okay
I guess I guess vegan I guess vegan is like the name for some part of britain or some like some person from a certain
From we can we can
All right, um
Is that up? Is that a place? I I don't recognize it, but I guess it is. Um
Is is it what it looks like? It's just a pie but with a bun burger bun
It's a meat pie if it's a it's a sandwich, but the filling is a pie. That's the stupidest thing I've ever seen
Yeah, like a pie is basically already a sandwich
A pie is already like meat encased in bread. It's not even a kebab
The kebab needs a wrap for it, doesn't it?
I
I thought if you like skewered through see yeah, I thought that a kebab
I thought that a kebab was about it's about the meat on the skewer that you carve off like I thought it was
It was the meat shish kebab. Wait kebab. No, no, no, no. I'm not I'm not saying like a shish kebab
I'm I'm talking about the sandwich kebab, but I thought what called what was what made it that was the sliced meat
Um that comes from the big piece of meat on the skewer
I think well
I'm not a I'm not greek and I don't know these things
But I think I've had like kebabs
Where the meat inside is you know chunkier
But I don't know it probably probably true donna kebab is is the one where you slice the meat down
Yeah, that's the the german one right um the
the the
Oh, that's that's
Well, then okay. Well, if that's if that's not if the meat from the if the sliced meat isn't what makes the kebab
Then I don't know what it does because then it just seems like it's just a pocket
I think that that that literally is the the thing because it's like the the bread
I think it comes from Greece the the or turkey or you know that area of the word Mediterranean
They use that type of bread the flat bread and they slice it open and put stuff in it and depending on what the type of thing is
It's either like a donna kebab or a shish kebab or
Because you're not you're not really supposed to eat the shish kebab on a stick
You're supposed to put it into the bread and eat it like that
This this video is so fucking funny. It's like he
Like he's not even speaking english
He like okay
They he goes to this place and he orders the vegan kebab and it's just a fucking pie on a bun
And then he asks for like another thing the smack barm pee weight
And and the smack barm the smack barm pee weight
Is literally it's just like it's like a chicken patty
And the and the pee pee wet
In smack barm pee wet what it is
It's just the the liquid runoff from like cooked peas
It's just like the the soup of a pea soup just the liquid part just kind of splattered on to the chicken
patty
And so a smack barm pee wet is like a chicken sandwich with like gross pee water splattered
And he says it's like
It looks disgusting. What do you say?
What do you say? Oh, and then he gets his full order and he's like uh a vegan akimbo with a smack barm pee wet
And i'm like that's not you're not allowed to say these things. You're not allowed to talk like that. You should go to jail
Oh for sure. You should be fast-tracked to the nearest attention facility. Fuck yeah
I I I kind of would would eat that though because like I I love like mushy peas with with with things like class food
It's just it's good. You know, I looks disgusting, but I would I probably I'm talking shit
I'm talking shitty. I don't actually think it sounds that bad. It's like a sandwich topping
It's just but uh, but uh, it's just but it what's gross about it is just that it's called pee wet
Pee wet pee wet a smack barm pee wet with a vegan kebab
And then it's like oh, oh a scouser tries the vegan kebab like ah, yes a scouser
And then he takes a bite and he's like no, that's what I call a buddy and I'm like, ah, yes the scouser tries the buddy
So many layers it just keeps going. I don't know what any of these means. I know I know all these things
I
Know like I know that in America in America. We have the chip buddy, which is a kind of sandwich
So I'm assuming that a buddy is just a sandwich
Oh, yeah chip buddy is is yes like you put chips a lot of fries into between bread and eat it
I'm not too fond of it honestly because it's like it's too much carbs and not enough anything else
But maybe if you put a lot of vinegar and salt and stuff on
Um
Yeah, I've I've had one before I thought it was weird
It kind of reminds me of like spaghetti sandwiches, which I think is another like bizarre thing that people do
Uh, I've never understood that
Spaghetti sandwiches. Yeah, what is this world? I'm learning of it's it's it's weird because it's it's it's it has the same problem
As the week in kebab, which is just that like why do you need to double up? Why do you need to carve like it's like the point
The point of spaghetti is that it's a carbohydrate vessel to carry the flavor of the sauce to your mouth
Yeah, like no like before I was being facetious saying that they should go to jail
But these people do need to be stopped and I don't know what like I don't know what we should do about it
I just know that something must be done
So how has the government let this go on how put pusatist pusatist trap god when he was at the atlanta protest
He was like filming like the the mag of people chanting and he he said like you know
I'm sorry for the tone shift, but it just reminded me
He said like you know, there's a lot of people here who will never be reached
And it just begs the question of what can be done or what what must be done
And so that's not a change in tone. This is very pertinent
This is the same thing. Okay
What can we do? I've tried to make a spaghetti sandwich before and I found it's it was it's hard
Like it's hard to keep together like it doesn't it's not an actual thing
I think the idea like I think the idea the idea is like oh you have leftover spaghetti
So it's like, hmm. What can I do with this? I'll make a sandwich out of it same with like the thanksgiving sandwich, right?
It's like, oh, I have leftover thanksgiving shit. I'll put it on a sandwich that makes sense to me
That actually can make a sandwich. It's not my favorite sandwich. I don't I don't love that
But like at least it works spaghetti. I don't know
I don't like that you're even beginning to rationalize this right? This is how people are radicalized
It's it's like having it's like having like, I don't know like steamed rice in a bun. It's like why
It's yeah, I don't
It's just eat the rice. It's perverse. It's just eat the rice. Just eat the right. Just eat the spaghetti. Just eat the spaghetti
Yeah, yeah, you don't you don't need to do any favorite pie on a farm
You don't need to do anything with spaghetti to like like with leftover. You just eat it
If I see a single fucking in the comments section defending this holy shit
It's fucking broke
Someone's
um, there was a
There was a guy there was a guy who worked at my college
I think we I think people called him the batman because I think he like
Because I think he wore like batman shirts and stuff. Um
he worked at my college a
food dining hall
and he would like
Basically, he was cool and people liked him and you could ask him for like a special
Sandwich he had like he had like sort of a special sandwich that he'd make
um
Which was essentially just a chip buddy, right?
But it wasn't it wasn't on the menu
Like he would he would put fries and like barbecue sauce and like chicken on this thing
And it was like it was like his sandwich and if you asked him for it, he'd make it for you
And it was pretty good, but like, you know, I don't know fries on the sandwich
I mean like it just feels like like makes sense to me
Although I will put I will put potato chips potato chips on the sandwich are good
But like that's because like that ends it like a different texture because it's crunchy
Yeah, like I like I'm like a like a like a tuna melt
It's a bad idea to do it
But it's it makes some sense right because you already have like you'll have fries with a burger
So like who's to say that you can't just combine them, you know, you know, you know
There's a large there's a large segment of the population
Uh, I would describe it as a cult. Um, who believes in the in the myth that like
Dipping your french fries and your milkshake is good
And I don't subscribe to that view at all. I think that that's
Fully unscientific pseudoscience. Uh, I think that it's dangerous rhetoric that it is it is dangerous. I'll give you that right?
Yeah, that's for sure. Um, are you are you guys with me on that? I haven't tried it
I don't think ever because I've heard people say it and I'm always like no no no fuck off
Wait, I've I've tried it and like it's not terrible
Like it just tastes exactly like you think it would and like it's it's whatever. Wait, I missed what we're talking about
I was too busy looking at red man
Dipping your french fries in your milkshake. Oh that I feel like a lot of the time
Yeah, it's just you don't get enough of the milkshake to really get any of the flavor of it. It's just sort of wet. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and it makes your french fries soggy and the last thing I want is a soggy fry
That's that's true. I mean sometimes sometimes fries are just soggy because there's so much oil on them and they're still fine, but
I think that's a problem in and of itself though. Like if somebody passes me some soggy fries
I'm gonna give them a little look and I won't kill them the first time but if it happens again
Well, some some establishments fries just kind of come out soggy or and to be honest, I don't I don't always mind it
Fair enough. Like I guess it can be okay
Like um, um five five guys has some of the best fries out there for like a fast food place
And those fries are not particularly crispy. I mean, I also wouldn't classify them as soggy though
I would say they're soft. Like like now. Yeah, they're not they're not soggy. I like I like them a little bit malleable and not like
Snappy, you know what I mean
Okay, now I'm with you on this. I understand what you're saying. I like it both ways. I like it both ways
Um, um, but I do like the crispy ones. Um
Like I'm extremely salty too. I have like
A very high salt tolerance
Uh, I I I eat I eat the dust at the bottom of a bag of pretzels
Uh, oh what the
Are you are you okay? Are you gonna go into shock?
Are you drinking salt water one time?
Make sure you drink water if you drink that much salt
I'll tell you one time. I got I got an over my head. This was is in um, I was living in northern california
And I went with some friends. We we were hanging out in sacramento one time
And we went to a ramen place. They were like, oh, there's this there's this nice little rustic ramen place
Let's go there. I was like, okay. I've never been to a ramen place before
So I went there and I'm looking at the menu and I'm looking at what I want in my ramen and I see an option
On the menu. That's like you can ask for extra salt
In your ramen and I'm like, oh, oh, and I'm like, oh boy. I love salty stuff like like so, you know
If if if anyone's gonna want extra salt in their ramen, it's me like that's for me
So I got it and uh, oh fucking boy
I
Like like let me remind you I eat the I eat the pot the the the dust at the bottom of the pretzel bag
I could not eat this ramen. It was so the broth was
Inedibly salty. I tried I tried to like mask the the salt with like I tried to put tons of like hot sauce and like oils
And stuff in it and just like drown it out with other stuff and I couldn't do it
I couldn't finish it. It was like it was the saltiest thing. I've ever I've never had something that was so salty
I could not eat it before but this was it
It was disgusting. Maybe maybe because why why do they offer this?
Maybe they're just more used to it because they have soy sauce and that's quite salty
Maybe that's very normal to have a lot of I feel like this was like saltier than just drinking straight soy sauce
People have like died from drinking straight soy sauce. So don't really don't try that at home kids. That's the real
I didn't finish it. I didn't finish it and I think I I don't I think I'd have died if I did it was
I was like
Man, I don't know. I don't know man
There is a level of saltiness where it turns into an assault on your senses like like your body rejects it
Yeah, so I like
That's sad, you know, it was sad
It was uh, uh, actually actually
I
Rather than just eating it straight now when I had when I finish a bag of pretzels
I save the dust and then I use it as a topping
I use it as like as like
Yeah, I use it as salt because it has that pretzel flavor
So if like I sprinkle it on like a grilled cheese sandwich or something that's and then like it just kind of imparts a little
Sort of pretzely flavor to it. Yeah
Whoa
Yeah, it's pretty good. That's that's pretty hot. Oh, it's kind of like saving. It's kind of like saving your bacon grease
Right. It's like, you know, why why waste this I can cook with this later
Dude, did you see that I made pretzel bread pretzels?
They the other day I posted it on twitter or instagram or somewhere
I I was I was proud of them because they they looked really jank, you know, I couldn't roll the dough in the right shape
But it was a really fun
different way to cook bread
because it involved a vat of bubbling
a cauldron of like stuff
and
The the idea to give it that pretzel taste
You know, you make a bread you got dough and yeast and it's very normal
But then you have to before you bake it
Dunk it egg wash, right? No, you have to dunk it into a bubbling cauldron of of like baking soda
Like a lot of baking soda and you keep it in there for like 20 seconds
And then you take them out and then you put them in the oven and they taste like pretzels. They're like big pretzel bread things
It sounds awesome. Oh, it was really good. I saw the image of them that you had you had made and I thought they looked pretty damn good
They they were the best bread I've ever made. I thought they got their flavor from an egg wash. No, that's that's it's
Wouldn't you know it's the baking soda and apparently that's how bagels are made as well
Oh
You dunk a dunk a ring into a thing
And then you cook it and it comes out with a nice taste
Nice, I'll also try that that sounds good. Yeah, look up recipes. It's not that difficult
aside from like there was a moment where
Um, I put the baking soda in and the water was too hot and it was sort of a bubbling too much
And it sort of frothed everywhere and I had to clean that up. It was an explosion
Um, I make um, but yeah, it was it was good when I
Whenever I fry whenever I fry chicken
I make the I have a I have a big like tubs of oil that I reuse
And I'm always I'm always going overboard
I'm always going overboard with the oil and cooking it and it like it's always like right about to bubble over
And I have to like stand there and watch it cook and use a little ladle to like continually stir the top of it to pop all the bubbles
So that because it's like like right at the top
I'm like no and I'm like blowing on and I'm like, please don't boil over
Please don't but and I'll just stand there and just like whisk it around like whisk around the top of it and blow
And it's like no no no because um start a fucking grease fire
Um, I don't know why I don't just use less oil, but I I don't know I always find myself
I always find myself in this predicament
I always wanted to try like deep frying something, but it's like
You have to get a lot of oil to have enough dunking space
And I don't feel like putting a big thing of oil there. What am I going to do with that afterwards do it again?
Where am I going to keep it you?
You save it you you know you put you you let it cool
And then you just pour it like you buy like a big like a big like two gallon oil
thing which costs like six bucks and then you um, yeah, you could you cook it in a pot you boil it in a pot
And then you let it cool and you just put it back and you use it again later
Maybe you maybe you strain it so it doesn't have like, you know
A residue from whatever you were cooking in it. Okay, maybe I could make doughnuts. That would be a cool idea
Well, that would be good. Hell yeah, you know, I'm I am looking at these pretzels
And I do think an egg wash an egg wash would make them darker
So if you're looking to get that
The recipe didn't call for it. I think some of them I didn't keep in the the the mixture for long enough
It's mostly aesthetic. It's it's mostly aesthetic. Oh for the shine. Yeah, maybe
Yeah, to get to make them darker and shinier. Yeah, they tasted perfect and I sprinkled the salt all of them
They look good. They look really good
Definitely gonna do that again
Very nice. I've been watching um, I've been watching this uh, this uh, uh cooking youtuber
his name is uh
His name is my name is andong. You ever heard you're seeing him? No, I don't think so. Nope
He he made um, he he's german. He did a pretzel video. He did um
He he he doesn't he doesn't he does like some more normal stuff and then he does some more out there stuff like he made um
He made like uh, uh chips out of
Other foods by which I mean like he ordered like a burger and fries
sushi and a doner kebab and then he took each of those dishes and like
pulverized them in a food processor and like made them into a paste and dehydrated them to make chips out of them
like
Yeah, to make like a chip a crunchy chip that was made of like a doner kebab
He wasn't that impressed with the burger or the or the kebab, but apparently okay
He he he takes the sushi one and he and he and he takes a bite of it
And then he looks directly at the camera and he I can't you won't see my face
But he goes like oh these like and I was like, oh my god. I'm so excited for you and dung
I'm so happy for you that you that you did it
You've made a discovery. Apparently the sushi like the chip tasted like sushi, which is very funny
um
Yeah, yep. Yep. Yep. He made um, he did one that's like
read like
Making a Naruto ramen like ramen that looks exactly like the the ramen that Naruto orders in the show
Uh, yeah, you know, there's stuff like that big north
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. The idea of making like crisps or chips out of of like anything
Reminds me of that one channel that makes knives out of everything and anything. Yeah, I love watching this occasionally
They're just part of my recommended. I haven't but this sounds extremely interesting. All right. So there's this guy
um
I think he lives in the old the the east and he doesn't speak but he he does these videos where he's like
Gets, uh, you know a concept for making a a knife that can be super sharp the sharpest
X knife in the world. So it would be like the sharpest
Gelatin knife in the world the sharpest chocolate knife in the world
He'll make whatever it is and there's you know, there's no commentary. There's no annoying like hey guys, welcome to another video
It's just like yeah, silence silent like
Like process of like all of these things he's doing. I'm like, what where's this going? Where is this leading?
This is such an adventure to see how you make a knife out of like the bottom of an aquarium like how do you do that?
I've seen him make the one that someone linked me was a sugar
He he makes one out of like candy. Yeah, and and he and he doesn't just make the knife
He makes it and it and he makes it come out so sharp that at the end he like slices paper with it
Oh, he does like show tests of what he's doing with them after the fact
Well, he'll he'll often unmake he'll often unmake them afterwards
Like he'll he'll make it and then he'll like melt it down again
Because like i'm sure i'm sure that a knife made of sugar doesn't like keep you know
Yeah, I wouldn't keep
Wait, though the weirdest one I saw was he made one out of fire
Oh, by which I by which I mean that he he made it
Well, he made one out of soot
From a fire like he burned shit and then he held a pan over the fire
And the pan like collected soot in it and then he collected the soot and like
Yeah, like boiled it down and like reduced it and like crystallized it into a knife and like cut shit with it
That's so unique. I I wish
that
Like that's one of those ideas you hear and it's like it is brilliant that this this person came up with this
Um, and you can't help but hope that one day you'll come up with an idea that is so esoteric and brilliant
It's I mean, what yeah once you have the but by the idea
Do you mean just like making a knife out of anything like just the idea of making a knife out of anything and then pushing it that far
Yeah, like once I mean once you have the idea and you start like
Hmm, what can I make a knife out of once you have the idea like the basics are just like
How can I how can I like collect any given material and mold it right? Yeah, and I'm sure some materials work better than others
It's like as long as you can turn something into a paste or a liquid
Like like any any sort of solid that you could turn into a liquid you can and then you can solidify it
You can morph it into a thing. Yeah, it's like
it's it's like the the
It has like elements of like weapon building tutorials or like those not tutorials those those videos where like
Um, they they restore like super rusted old things
But also cooking like cooking experiments as well because a lot of them are food
It's just sort of all of the things he he makes it uses all the tools
It's just very well, that's what makes it like to me
That's what makes it so brilliant is you're combining so many different ideas into one thing
That's so weird that I never would have thought to ask the question of it
But as soon as you say hey, this guy makes knives out of anything. I'm like, what now I want to watch this
This sounds fun
Oh, oh my god
Oh my god, there it is one of the one of the wait. Is this the right?
Is this the yeah, there it is one of my never had it sandwiches the hamon puree. I was just looking
My name is andong has a video where he makes a hamon puree
Perfect. I'm probably I'm probably pronouncing that wrong because it's french and I don't know how to how to
How to pronounce french words, but damn damn the guy's got a fucking answer for everything
The hamon brulee. There you go. Hamon
hamon
French is
Whenever I don't even like I don't even want to try to pronounce like any french word because it seems like every time
I see a french word. It's like, oh, okay
I have some idea of how it's pronounced and then when I hear it pronounced
It's like, oh, you just like ignored half the letters or just like added some extra ones in like I don't I don't fucking
Understand this at all the thing with french that annoys me is is that you know sometimes
The s is not spoken, but some other times it is and there's no I feel like way to tell
I feel like
I feel that way, but like I don't think it's just s's I
There's lots of things but the s is always like at the end of words you you always assume
Oh, if it ends in any s it's like air and rather than s
But sometimes that's just not the case and I just I look like it looks stupid sometimes
Very stupid very stupid. Yes
Uh
Yeah, pronouncing french
I am horribly useless at it despite the fact that here in canada. I was forced to do it for
Uh, like all of elementary school and I'm just useless. That's right. You're canadian
Yeah, I learned nothing. I learned nothing from french. All I know all I knew was how to ask to go take a shit
I learned um
I I studied spanish like all through high school like middle like middle school and high school and college
Like yeah, I could speak it kind of okay
And then like after college. I never used it and I've like I've completely forgotten like
I mean I can kind of still read it and like have love like I
I generally know like what's going on often, but like I can read it and I can kind of understand it
But like if I had to speak it I'd be like
You know, I because I would like forget the words like until I heard them. You know what I mean
languages are so hard
It's such a
Like you need to know you can't just learn it because uh, you need to use it all the time or it just
There's some serious attrition. It goes away
Yeah, um, all you need to do is just say uh, I can I could speak a little and they'll be like, oh, okay
I could speak a little bit of polish when I lived in poland, but now I remember like
Half a dozen words and like yeah an expression and that's it. Yeah
I I just learned like I just learned a bunch of like kind of functional phrases and words to like get around like
Yeah, you ask people directions like say hi to people, you know, whatever. Yeah, I only know um
Uh, I know one polish word or phrase which is dobranos for I think dobranos dobranos
What is that? I think it's I'm pretty sure it's just like
Good night, and it's the only thing I know so whenever I see my wife's polish family
I just wave and say dobranos no matter what the situation is and and it's like morning and they all shake their head like
Oh, it's that fucking
That's fucking uh, this stupid outsider that westerner. Yeah, they they all turn to each other
They do the they do the Picard hand in head gift
Oh, yeah, oh this actually leads to a this leads to a fun story that you might enjoy
Um
So back when I was in high school. Well, I'm still an idiot, but I was particularly an idiot in high school
Uh, and that was where I I met my wife and I was away somewhere on a little trip
Wait in in high school. You said yeah in high school. Okay. Okay. Uh, so then I was
Wait, wait, how wait, how old are you okay? Because schooling is different like how old are you in high school in canada?
Um, like you you go there until you're like 17 or 18
Okay, all right. So same as america. Yeah, same same thing. Um, so I was away and I had gone to this sort of like
world war two
shop
Like it was kind of weird because at first it looks like a museum thing
But there is a weird amount of just paraphernalia where I'm like, I don't know who's buying this stuff
um, so then I told my wife for a joke. I was like, oh, I bought you a poster of uh
Of of the big Adolf
And it's so I'm gonna bring that back to you and I just said it as a joke right so then I got home
And I was like, okay. Well now I need to follow through so I printed off this really shitty picture
The big Adolf. That's what they called him. That's what they called him back in his old college boxing day
So I I had a picture of him and underneath I put the words. I don't know how anyone could not see you
And I brought this I brought this to her house and I I like just started dating her
I don't know what possessed me to do this. It was really dumb because her family's polish
So I I take this in and I haven't folded up. I'm like, don't show this
Uh, like to anyone right? This is a stupid edgy joke
and
She's like, yeah, yeah, yeah, and as soon as she walks inside her mom's like, oh, what's that you have there?
And she takes it looks at hit and then stares at me and says we don't like that man here
And I'm like, no, no, no, no, I should I should think not
This is a stupid joke. Like it's nothing more than a stupid joke
So then I'm sweating and I go home and I'm talking talking to her and then you're and then you're you're you're
You're then then girlfriend. I imagine it's like, oh, yeah, sorry about my sorry about my hitler loving boy
Well, no, she was like and the parents like, oh that boy the hitler boy
And she was telling me she's like, no, no, no, it's fine
She knows it's just like a joke and I'm like, are you sure?
Like because I don't blame her if she's upset with me. This is like the first time I've met her
Um, yeah, yeah, but you know those nazis there was carrying a bunch of women pictures of Adolf looking at him
Oh, yeah, it's so uh, it's important to them as I'm talking to her a bunch of people
laughing in the background because I was talking to her online and uh
I'm like, oh, what's that?
So then she goes and apparently her mom was showing all her friends this picture because her mom thought it was hilarious
That I'd bring that into the house
But she didn't want to like let me know she thought it was funny because I guess she didn't want to encourage this high school bullshit
um
So that was just a very good way to meet someone. So kids don't very good. Don't do that
Don't make the mistakes I've made
So it was like it worked just
When you meet your your your significant mother's parents, I would say try to avoid
Hitler
You know try to avoid jokes like that on the first time
It did kind of work though because I think she thought it was funny and was like this this kid
You know this guy
Yeah, polish polish fascists are are pretty awesome actually
Oh, gosh, they have they have cool iconography
Because I mean poland just has like cool iconography. They have like the royal eagle and stuff
Yeah, and I've I've seen like some old like polish like fascist literature that it's like
I've seen like they have they have those symbolized things with like the axe
They have like big axes with with like eagle wings on them and stuff. It's like that's that's pretty cool. That's pretty like um
Uh, that's that's kind of warhammer 40k. I'm sold like I I could get into this actually now that you say that
Yeah, a shitload of the fascist
I don't know images and stuff looks like something on a warhammer
Yeah, yeah, yeah, they do for sure. Which is probably purposeful probably warhammer wanted them to like
I don't know maybe look like that or maybe it's just that
You know, you know the thing about fascists you gotta hand it to them
You you just you just gotta hand it to them. Well, they really like painting litter. That's all I'm figurines
What have you gave you see you seen that you seen that drill tweet?
uh
no the
Famous famous drill tweet is like is like uh apologies for my last tweet regarding uh isis
You do not under any circumstances gotta hand it to them
Oh, I do remember that I think I have that in one of my favorite in that fucking drill tweet book that I bought
Oh, okay. Well, I hope I would hope it made the cut. It's a classic. I enjoy that book quite a lot. It's very silly
Just to open it to read tweets printed on paper
I'm looking I'm looking at
Okay, there's a there's a there's a like a fascist polish group called the o n r
And I don't know what that stands for but but their logo their logo is like it's the stylized um
Arm holding a sword. It's kind of neat. It's kind of a neat logo
That looks like an esports team. That looks like a fucking minecraft team
It is no that oh my god, you're right. It looks like minecraft
And when they when they go to battle with their minecraft team, they would say get ready to take this l
I
Hope you'll show it on the screen. Oh, no, what are they talking now?
I'm thinking of a rally with people with diamond armor on
I I guess the it stands for
oboats
Not a dovo
Eradi Eradi colony
National radical camp is is what it means in English. Okay, the national stands for oh, no, we're radical
Dude, I want to go to a radical camp
Is that when I'm a kid when I'm a teen? Yeah, it's like it sounds radical. That's that's really that's yeah. Why not?
Why not? Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm doing like sick kickflips and stuff like
base based as fuck
If only they were actually like that well that fucking was a journey
Hmm said if only they were actually like that
Yeah, then I'd agree with all of that points
I can't I can't believe
I can't believe I didn't see before that. It's just minecraft. It's a diamond sword
I love that
Uh
Lord when we do these shows we usually go we chat for a while and then we go to voicemails. Um
Do you want to hang around and listen to voicemails or uh?
Yeah, I'd be down to listen to voicemails if you'll if you'll have me for your voicemail times. Sure. Um,
We don't have to do that right now, but um
I don't I don't know give what do you what do you think?
um, I mean
I don't mind, but I am wondering about like whether I will have the enough space for all of this red man
footage
We've been going for an hour and a half. So we can go for a little bit longer
uh
So that's no ongoing voicemails. Um, I mean does anyone have anything to talk about for now for for for topic ways
I'm trying to think did anything important happen this week other than
other than other than um
Other than the uh, the the the the funny the funny, uh funny atlanta stream
And uh and the rfck pins uh link link link in the description
Link in the description if you want to order some talk about I don't know if you talked about that on the show
You talked about it before the show
the pins
Actually, I don't remember did I not well I I think I did I think I did talk about it on the show
Um, when it was when I was introducing red man, and I said there's a red man. Oh, yeah. Yeah
There's there's there's a red yeah, there's a red man pin. There's a gun girl pin. Um, there is like 30 other things. Oh, there's there's the uh
negus line lord of ghosts
There's um
There's a whole bunch of other rfck stuff
They there's oh, there's the slime coin the slime coin. Have you you've seen the slime coin doesn't it look fucking sick though?
Uh, yes, I slime coin is is wait so
Oh lower you you haven't seen these I will I will show you no it's a sad life
I haven't seen them, but they I like the slime coin is is a like a big coin like a medallion almost
solid metal
made of solid gold
Solid gold. Yes. This is this is the this is the slime. It's very intricate. It's very cool
Oh, wow
Right here. I'll show you the front and the back
Um, like I've lived this moment till now without it, but now that I've seen it
I don't think I can live without it that being said people must buy this pin
I've never seen anything so beautiful in my life. Please support very fucking go
Very fucking go. Yeah. Well, that's that's the coin and there's the these are the pins in the patch
As you can see red man over on the left gun girl is over on the right
There's endless war. There's a
Canny an investor praise slimer made pizza chan mega slime slime hearts. Yeah, these are very nice
Imagine imagine wearing that that new los angeles city flag patch like on your fucking shoulder
Imagine like walking around looking like that. I I kind of wish I had one
I bought one
Because I do I do have a winter coat that I could put it on
I might just I mean you're just just because you're gay. Well, maybe I'll toss you one
Yeah, I'll fucking I'll fucking toss you you might get one
You may if you're a good boy in your Christmas stocking. Oh, I can't wait
Yeah, um
Well, Santa's gone mad. Well, let us go mad with power fucking
I just I just want to okay. Can we talk about how Santa's just evil?
Go on like, okay. This is the thing that's really bothered me forever. Um
So this whole idea of being naughty or nice, right?
Yeah, you tell kids this and then it's like well Santa's a cop Santa's a fucking cop
Well, Santa is all about that thin blue line
You could argue that Santa is the thin blue line between naughty and between society being naughty and society being
I mean, you're just building the argument even more because I didn't even consider that
Like Santa so you tell these kids, right? Like if you're good, Santa will bring you presents
If you're bad, you don't get presents
In my mind eventually down the long run this equates morality with the amount of money you have so that your parents can buy you things
Oh, I see what you're saying and that like as a kid if you genuinely believe this right like imagine little timmy's been so nice
He's just a great kid
But his parents don't make that much money and he's like I got like one little thing
And then this other dipshit in the class is like my parents bought me a million things
Bought me a fucking car or whatever and it's like damn that rich kid, but it's supposed to have been so much nicer than me
Yeah, I don't like it. I don't I've never you know, santa. I think we need to kill him
I mean, I wonder I wonder
Do you kids kids more likely to believe in santa like think that that's it?
santa rewards the status quo
Mmm. Yeah, like I'm not I'm not necessarily making the argument that kids are operating on this level
I'm just saying that in retrospect looking back at it. I'm like, you know what santa's kind of fucked up. Yeah, definitely
I mean, I
I legitimately wonder like
Maybe kids do have that thought like I just wasn't nice enough that I didn't get the fucking I didn't get the playstation 5
Unlike, you know, josh
josh who fucking uh gave me a swirl at the other day
Uh, he he got it though like damn. What am I doing wrong? Yeah, and I feel like it would be much nicer like I don't know
Just to know, you know, if you know your parents are scraping by if they're open with you about like we don't have that much stuff
I feel like you would be more grateful if they're like we bought this for you because we care about you
It's as much as we can give you not like that big fat fuck gave it to you
I think there are parents. I think I've heard of people who are like
Yeah, we don't tell our kids that santa got them stuff because it's kind of fucked up and like, you know
We want them to know that like, you know, we got them these things because like, you know, we love them
Yeah, and I learned like real quick that santa was a total fraud because uh,
My my parents would always like leave out
Like this was when I was like four or five. They leave out cookies being like
Santa's gonna come and eat the cookies and then they leave out a giant carrot for the reindeer and my dad would eat the cookies
And the the carrot would never get eaten
And they were always just like, well the reindeer wasn't very hungry and I looked at my parents and I was like
Fuck off with your bullshit. Oh, okay. Okay
Why would they do that? Because I was just fun. They don't care, right? They didn't actually want to support even this guy
Okay, okay, okay, but like if the if the scheme is like we're gonna put this thing out
So so he'll you know, so it looks like santa like ate the cookie and gave the reindeer the carrot
Why would you leave the carrot? Why even bother with the carrot if like you're just not gonna eat it and you're just gonna leave it there
Like why even bother? It's a mystery. But uh, yeah, I guess they just didn't care. They probably figured it was kind of funny
That's nonsense. It's like, oh, yeah. Yeah. I'm
It's like if you know, you're not gonna eat the carrot
I don't I don't get it
Santa's weird. There was also like factions when I was in
The younger grades like grade one between, you know, as kids start to realize that this is just not real
Um
Then like certain kids we get very passionate about like guys
You're being duped by the system santa's fake and the other kids would be like, how dare you speak against my worldview?
Um, and like they would get into legitimate fights over this. It was very funny
Preparing them for the future
Yeah
They got to learn they got to learn to hate their fellow man
Eventually you have to learn sooner rather than later. There are dividing lines and one of those dividing lines is labeled ho ho ho
Begs begs the question of what is to be done?
We got to collect all these santo lovers all these radicals and all of these, uh, I don't know
weird like pizza sandwich
Fuckers
And these yeah, these radical these radical, uh, these radical anarchists who say that a choco taco is technically a sandwich
Which is just a lie. That's a lot just just criminal and punishable
Um by a week in the in the stocks
Oh, man
Let's uh, let's do let's do voicemails. Let's do voicemails. Let me let me pull these up. Um, uh, okay this
So, okay, okay, this one this first one and I hope I got I hope I don't fuck the order up
This first one that I will upload now is called josephi
Uh, right hold on. Let me
I'm just gonna you know the fuck of my windows. Okay. Yeah, josephi
Uh, let's give that a listen in three two one go
So, uh, I just started listening to the podcast recently, uh, most recent episode because we're talking about foreskin a lot
No
Hey guys, welcome to the pro circumcision podcast
Welcome to the pro circumcision podcast. We advise any foreskin that's allowed to survive is fucking punishable
Immoral and shouldn't be done. I am not going to listen to anybody. I love circumcision
I hate I hate short nerve endings. I hate sexual pleasure
If any if any others are about circumcision, I'm just not gonna listen. I'm gonna talk. Yeah, what what is going on with circumcision?
Nothing nothing. What nothing is happening. No, no, no, no, no
Just watch the last 10 weeks the last 30. Oh, yeah, what's the last several months of I I have like watched
a bunch of them
And then I always see like I haven't finished them or I'm watching them on a video
And then um people will be in the comments like circumcision talk and I'm like, okay
I guess just you know, they're just they're just they're just they're just this josephi
You're a you're a fucking goof. You're a fucking funny man and a goofball and you're a real comedian clown, mr
I like them. I like I like them, you know, I like his I like his name
Yeah, I like out of his job. Yeah, I like circumcision too. If we get one more here's here's the thing
If we get one more where I'm gonna open the the new like pcp
um forced circumcision clinic
They will be circumcised live on air
Wow, and if they're already circumcised, I'll just put some forescales
We will implement a like mandatory circumcision policy in the uh in the in the
But in the in the pcp in the pcp prison
So like that guy that I sent to prison last week for asking asking about circumcision too much
We will circumcise you we have the ability our only circumcised people allowed on the podcast
Um, they will be okay because I was just about to say like I've got a knife ready. I'm prepared
if uh
Stand by we we'll we'll we'll be using that very soon. Okay, because I could be the first one in the circumcision clinic
I'm ready for
You know, do you want to do all the forced circumcisions on our political prisoners?
I think I should be the recipient of a forced circumcision. Uh, you're too into this. You you were waiting for us to say this
No, he's too. Well, he's too willing. It doesn't that's just doesn't have the same. I mean don't no don't circumcise me
No
Doesn't feel the same. Well, okay. I mean I guess we could if you insist
Next next voicemail is called defund the police, but I am confused. Am I dumb?
Okay, three two one go
Okay, so if there's a hostage situation the police are supposed to come and like help resolve that
Or if like I my house gets broken in two I call them and they help resolve that issue
And there are a bunch of other essential functions that we give them the power to
Fulfill but then they abuse that power and are racist and bad
The current consensus is like, oh, we should just defund the police because they're
Causing the problems here
And like it sounds like it would be great
But my question is about those essential functions like either a we just leave them unfulfilled once we defund the police
I've heard this question so many times
And then what's to stop them from being just as racist and bad as the police are
It seems like it's just kicking the can down the route. What's to stop who from being as racist?
Am I stupid? Is this just an obvious answer to this question that I'm dumb and missing?
Please elucidate
Okay, man
I don't know why I have to answer this question. I feel like you could google this but uh like
The point is the point is to reduce the scope of the police by by defund them
You reduce their scope the point is that they fulfill too many functions like yeah
We should still have some form of law enforcement and like civil protection in the case of like, you know
Someone is like actively committing like violence somewhere. Yeah, like
It's it's not that like it would be reduced to zero
It would just be like, you know defund it
Restricted scope
Greatly the problem the problem is we have over we have over policing in america and probably in other countries as well
The way to think about it is if you expanded their scope to say include the military
The police would have access to a lot more dangerous weaponry
um
That they could just use or like, you know, just give
That they would have too much extra stuff and it would cause even more problems to defund them is to limit the powers that they have
To to you know that the corruption
Would yeah, if there is corruption would you know cause problems the end the end goal
The end goal is not that like literally nobody is there to respond when like someone
When the occasional shooting spree happens, you know, yeah, because there's always that that's sort of like
safety net for police officers that do terrible things they get off lightly
Because everyone this they've got too much
Sway over the justice system that they can get their buddies off
Scott free and it's like they shouldn't be able to have that
Like I don't know too much about this shit, but I feel like there's problems with self-regulating systems
like if the system of law itself is supposed to look after itself
And check and balance itself that kind of poses like
I don't know a problem of who's actually going to keep things in check
Yeah, yeah, the police the like the police like
Is is
To a large degree they are they regulate themselves and like, you know, I think there's been a lot of people calling for like
civilian review boards need to be you know
They like the police need to be more accountable to groups outside of them
And I know I know that they are to a certain extent accountable to those outside themselves
But like, you know the argument is well, it's it's it's not enough, you know
Uh
Overpolicing is the problem like your argument isn't to let anarchy run wild in the streets
Well, the good kind of anarchy. Maybe okay. There we go
Um, the next next one is called a punished sweeper
I like the title of it. I don't I don't know what to make of it. Uh, three two one go
Okay, like fucking so many weeks ago. I said in this voicemail about minesweeper.online
Uh, how fucking cool it is. Yeah, the only problem is that now I fucking spend hours every day
I'm literally every day fucking logging in. This is why we didn't do it shitty fucking
Actually, not shitty awesome. Why we didn't listen
And I'm like I'm wasting away. I'm sitting here. I'm playing it right now as I'm recording this
Oh one oh two
Oh, oh shit. I miss clicked god
It's like it's like that episode of starcraft with the game. This is this is all I am now
Fucking go
Go to minesweeper.online make an account. He's made a terrible case. No
On those minesweeper marketplace and you'll understand my
Struggled my addiction. This is insane. I cannot handle this any longer. He's he's minesweeper
What the hell?
He's trying to pass. I think he's trying to pass the curse on like he's been cursed that he can only play minesweeper
And like to break it. He needs to like have someone replace him
That's my hypothesis. Yeah, maybe maybe this guy's got some stocks and minesweaver online dot org or whatever it was
You know, okay something something sinister is definitely going on. There's something a fuck
There's no way that anyone would just make pzp voicemails to call in to tell us to go to minesweeper.com or whatever
Such a huge audience we have here
Be like a gold mine almost
No, I think it could be you know
The the the the next voicemail is called like really guys. Oh good three two one go
I just want to reiterate like what I'm playing minesweeper
I can't figure out this what
I'm gonna have to use a hint. I feel like I'm worthless beta. I'm sitting. I'm playing evil
Oh, I gotta beat my fastest time try to do it without hints an evil difficulty. No gas mode
This is I have to hold myself to this insane
standard of of
Beauty except it's intellectual beauty as in the the beauty of a mind that is good at minesweeper
Oh my god, come back to me when you're a master of sudoku.com
like me
Oh, I'm I'm guys. I'm guys. I'm doing it. I'm playing I'm playing minesweeper. No
No, we're gonna live. Don't do it. You'll get sucked in. I'm I'm playing I'm playing minesweeper y'all
No, no, no, no, I hit a mine
Fuck this games fucking that's so fucked up. Shit
Fuck
Fucking game designers
I'll never be the same designers too much rng. This is
Honestly minesweeper shit speedrun totally rng dependent, you know, it's just a grind stupid
um
Fuck this game
Next one next one is called, uh, wait a minute. Was that the fourth one? Yes, the fourth one next one is called
All consuming
There it is. Is it about minecraft or minesweeper? Uh, it's both. Yeah, it's about both. It's about what if we put one in the other
Okay, three two one go
Like have you ever played tetris enough that you just start with tetris in your head when you're not awake?
Yeah, just in your every day. I knew it. I knew it
What a piece of shit. What a piece of shit. Let's just go to the next one. Yeah, next one is called, uh, thirsty elephant
uh
three two one go
Well
I want my four skin
My life is so terrible
That's all I hear that's all I hear these entitled spoiled millennials all they do is eat avocado toast and miss their four skins
That's so funny
They whoever sent that in I love you
Yeah, you know
That that person that person gets to to
I don't know what I was gonna do cut their dick off or something. They they they're allowed to live because I was funny
I'm thinking voice grail. I'm thinking voice grail for thirsty elephant
Oh, that's so good voice grail definitely just just to rub it in the faces of everyone making arguments for real
You've you've ascended thirsty elephant. Welcome to the divine to the divine chorus
Uh, uh, the the holy host
Oh, man
This is this is the hardest I've laughed in a while
You don't even have you don't even you don't know you haven't suffered
You haven't suffered like we have over these months like that joke was just impeccably done
Bless you, sir. Bless you
Next voicemail is called, uh
It's uh, wait, there it is. It's called a killer dog. I assume it's from killer dog. Um
Three two one go
So I started listening to the podcast again after a while because oh, hey look guests
Uh, and you know what last couple episodes, uh, haven't been pretty cool
Uh, you got cybershell. You got the one comic lady. You got kazzie always nice to see her on
About jim. Uh, what about jim? But holy moly
Who we the voicemails were uh, were way worse than I remember and that's saying something
it's the the last voicemail I remember before before this was uh,
I think the jewish question guy
Oh, yeah
Yeah, some of you guys need like
A discord server or a youtube channel or friends or something
Um, you complain about voicemails and yet you make one curious checkmate. I'm very intelligent
I don't care about, um
I heard about a guy who's like talking about persona five or something. I didn't hear that. I just heard that
Yeah, that was a nightmare
That was almost as bad as circumcision go outside or like go join like a discord server go join rfck or something like
Yeah, join join a cult do do anything maybe go buy a maybe go buy a pin. Hmm. Hmm. Think about it
somebody called in just to tell you about persona five
There was a guy who like every week for a while he would make like one or two voicemails just like being like
Okay, no guys like I really want to explain how much I like persona five and then you'd call back week next week
Yeah, we just wouldn't and he'd be like all right. I didn't I didn't really explain it clearly
But what I really like about persona five is
Just make a youtube video god damn it. That's right like a hundred thousand percent more use of your time better use
That's true. That's probably somebody who's talked to all their friends about and all their friends are like
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever. Maybe I won't and then they they're desperate and they're like I need I need to know
I've had an impact as far as persona five playing is concerned in this world and sir
Sir, if you are listening or watching this, I have played persona five and let me tell you I will carry the mantle
I will call in every week to try to explain
You know no that under that underrated classic persona five like no one appreciates it. Nobody's played it. It's it's ridiculous
And I and I gotta I gotta do something about it
Uh, uh next next one is called let's go
Three two one go
Hello, and welcome to Bay Saints by Iluzon. You begin with the saga of st. Benedict the need who could
Benedict or benfort horn was a fifth century rich family italian man who got sent to be educated in rome
St. Saint ben is christ was rome disgusting
Everybody just fucking sucking
Drinking and eating all the time. That just wasn't our boy ben's vibe at all
But it is that rather than have a good time hating himself
He decided he'd rather stay a god pilled dumb dumb minimalist in a small village in the middle of nowhere
Well, dad was pretty good living until he got accidentally got famous in the dumbest way possible
Crash when the ceramic sea benedict repaired it, but everybody was like
You
Everybody knows you don't just repair ceramics
He must have prayed it together
Well, and so they started simp and you young ben 24 fracking seven
We're like
He got good at it
He saw only a single path leading to everyone finally leaving him alone
Become a cave living need deep in the heart of the mountains
Um
Did did did I miss something? No, no, I think it's on just wanted to
Deliver us this this the life story of st. Benedict with some with some dramatic flair and and he did it
Yeah, he did it. Wow. Um
Yeah
Well, now now you know everyone. I hope I hope that was uh educational for you
I hope yeah
Okay, next one next actually next one is called. Hmm end me
Hmm
Sounds familiar
Sounds sounds like what I say to myself in secret
Uh three two one go
Ha ha pee pee poo poo stinky
Voice grail voice grail I'm thinking no fuck no no
Stupid stupid. Okay next time next one is a urban dictionary
Uh, there it is. Wait one sec. There it is. Okay three two one go
No one truly misses the topics. We all just really miss urban dictionary. Please bring urban dictionary back
Uh, it was the best part of the pcp. You know what that's fair. You might be like well, but but but episode the
The best part of the pcp is this part and you're wrong. It was always the urban dictionary
You've been lied to episode 23 is just okay
um
The monsters and dreams and voicemails and all this other bullshit. It's all an illusion
You have to go back to the days of urban dictionary. I I agree. You know, I agree
Uh, uh the the idea of like we must have a topic. I never made much sense to me
But we have lost something valuable
In the in the losing urban dictionary. So let me let me let me fix this
Urban dictionary defines circumcision as oh god
To remove a male's foreskin
So that's pretty straightforward. I hope I hope I hope I hope everyone is amused
Wait, are there surely there's some other definitions? There's usually like secondary ones, right?
Are there any funny ones? No, no, wait
um next one
What happens when ignorant parents are jealous of their beautiful child?
Uh followed by a barbaric and cruel act of cutting someone's foreskin off his cock
It's what needs to be illegal except for really really bad medical conditions parents should not have the right to circumcise their son
We circumcision ourselves. We've punked ourselves by listening to yet another opinion
Wait and then and then this this this one has a dramatic reenactment
American christian father when our son is born. We're gonna circumcise to him
American christian mother. I agree. He needs a circumcision
American christian father it would be painful at least he won't remember any of it when their son is born
He got circumcised doctor cut stick baby
The baby cried for two weeks
There okay, can I ask how did circumcision come up the first time?
Just it was just someone asked in a voicemail
about
What we thought about it little did they know what people didn't like my answer what they had done
Yeah, it's
They know they they they know what they fucking did
um
next one is
wha-ba-ba-ba
next
This one's on thin ice next one is called is digi fuda
Oh three three two one go
Assuming digi still has her pymosis cock would she be considered fuda at this point
Just need to do some research so I can get all my galboro tags in order. I
uh
I
I feel like this is gonna
I feel like maybe we should ask digi's opinion about this. I don't know if I feel comfortable saying yes or no
Yeah, I don't this people have different definitions for it. I usually only think of it as like a fake porn thing
And not a real thing
But maybe people do identify as that. I don't know
I'm probably some yeah
I'm gonna say that probably is like uh, I'm gonna say what do you what do you think? What do you think?
Hmm pass it back to the leader leave your leave your past back to the viewer leave your comments down below
Next one is called um it is called
Weird baby dick
Nice three three two one go
Okay, so
Ben you asked about my ex's kids weird dick
so he fucking
He was partially circumcised
I did basically the doctor did was cut off like
The top 80 percent of it. So he has foreskin on the bottom basically
And it's just fucking weird looking
What?
Also for digi
It's easier for me at least
to
suck a dick when I don't have to like
Navigate the foreskin with my tongue
Even though that's kind of neat
But docking is pretty cool docking is fucking epic. Um, okay
Okay, so I first I thought he meant that he cut off like the 80 percent of the dick
But I don't think that I think what he's saying is that the doctor
Didn't cut off the entire foreskin
But only like the top 80 percent of it. Oh, I thought he meant like 80 percent down the shaft
That's what I thought too, but I don't
No, I I think I
Because that's because if you cut down the shaft like that's not foreskin. That's just skin. Yeah. Yeah, so that would be a fuck up
So by botch circuit the botch circumcision here was that he's not circumcised enough
So, I mean, I would maybe consider like
Finishing the job at that point. They're in no man's land
Yeah, um, I mean, I'm sure it
I'm trying to imagine what that would even look like. I mean, I'm sure it works fine
Hmm
Just kind of like a flap on the bottom of yeah
Yeah, it's yeah, I didn't realize people had such strong opinions about this because I have like a weird rant
I have told my poor friends that they have to listen to about how I hate circumcision
But like I'm not going to subject you to that. I just wanted to don't know. We've had enough
Yeah, I just I just wanted to let you know that I didn't realize this was such a hot topic among the people
When I remember when Andrew Yang came out and said that like he didn't like
He didn't think that like circumcision should be a mandatory
I remember there was a certain section of the internet was like really excited. We're like fuck. Yeah
Wait, he didn't think they should be mandatory aren't circumcisions
Not well, no, I mean no, what I mean is he said the thing that's like, um
You know like uh
Parents probably shouldn't make the oh, okay. I see what you're saying like that. Yeah, he said that and people were like
Which you know, I'm fair enough. Okay, um
Next next one. Yeah, it's called. I literally hate you awful mic quality
um
3 2 1 go
The voice grail and the voice jail are a false dichotomy
What always happens is someone will make a shitty voicemail and it'll get sent to voice jail
But you're giving these failures attention and almost always they take that to continue their narrative
Whereas the people who get voice grailed often send one good one and leave it at that
It's a negative feedback loop
The answer to this is just to say this voicemail sucks and skip to the next one because we still have fucking losers
Like maga and that voicemail guy continuing to waste everyone's time by sending their self-indulgent shit
Like no one has a sensible mail. They haven't even made a good voicemail to invest us to them
How does it feel that your sad existence is continued because of people like ben platform hate speech saint
And his laziness you're so bad. I wish nate was back just to beat you like jesus christ
You're a fucking loser artist calling onto a podcast full of other loser failure artists
I dread having to listen to you jerk yourself off every episode
No one cares about your previous voicemails and no one cares about the voicemail voicemails. You're making now
You're actively making the show worse
And I just wanted you to know that there was someone that has genuine ire for your existence
Please get a bit ask a real question and stop talking about yourself as if we know who you are
You're awful
Wow that the vote apart from the voicemails the show is pretty good
trans rights BLM gay rights
Good. Bye. I
I thought he was talking about me for a second there. No. No. No. He's talking too bad voicemail givers
Oh, okay, because when he when he because when he when he said like
When he said like you're a fucking loser artist like like a clawing on to his shitty podcast and I hate you
I thought like oh now he's talking about me
He did say going on to a podcast full of other shitty failure artists. So I I you know
I I I feel I'm just gonna assume he's talking about me. Uh, no. No, I you're beautiful. I think this guy
I think he makes a bit. I mean if you did say we're a bunch of shitty failure artists
And that that is why that they call into this show. Uh, how doubly embarrassing I guess is what he was saying there
I think I think he's right in that the voice jail doesn't really serve as an effective punishment of anything
Uh, yeah, I just I just want to be able to say fuck you in a specific way
Do a person. Yeah
Yeah, it's uh, we probably should be a little more selective honestly
Like if like if a voicemail if a voicemail is genuinely bad
And like we voice jail it we probably shouldn't like keep playing. I mean
I I'm I'm pretty lax with my standards
But like, you know, if I think a voicemail is like actually like really brings nothing to the table
I I am trying more to actually be like, hey ellie's are cut this don't
So what so what that means is that the ones that you hear are actually the ones that that meet my standards
So that that should tell you just how low my standards are
ma'am
Um, any anything else?
No, no, okay. That was an adventure though that
The the one comment I have I don't know if it's my place to say this is I don't know if the shitty voicemail people
Uh, I don't know if they care about your eye or for them
Like oh, that's that might be true. You might that's probably it might that might feed them as well, right? You might have accidentally fed the loop
That's all I have to say
There's probably a certain strain of shitty voicemail sender who will take who will take this as encouragement. Yeah. Oh, yeah, absolutely
It's it's really inescapable. It's an inescapable cycle. Yeah
Um cycle of violence the next one the next one is called irish ninja
Three two one go. I think I know who this is
So you's had the irish samurai on last week
Um, I don't care what kind of gay lore shit is going on. Fuck that guy
That's an offensive stereotype. Terrible accent me and all my homies in the japanese IRA. We're gonna fuck him up
um, my question
What is the most appealing and least appealing accent? I wasn't on the last episode
I do want to say I listened to it and it was anything but irish that guy
It almost sounded Welsh like a like a strange combination of Welsh and Scottish
I was like, this is terrible that you you don't know anything
Well, I mean I I won't defend it too hard
But I will say it was meant to be a a mash-up of irish and japanese was the goal is what it was supposed to be
That was the weird part
There were I I could I could tell that's what it was going for. Okay. Um, okay, but the most and least appealing
accents
I might be a little biased here. I think that one of the least appealing accents is a Providence
Rhode Island accent
um
It's a little bit like a boston accent, but not quite
It has an annoying quirk of like adding r's onto the end of words that don't need them like like
posture
Yeah, I I don't I can't really do a good impression of it, but like
It's not like people from like south boston have like a really strong
Ah, pock the cut like you can really tell the the the providence accent is not usually that
pronounced like it's sometimes hard to identify but like when I hear the when I hear that extra r
I'm like, oh
Um, you guys you guys have opinions. Um
like my my one of my lowest ones is a
A very strong like southern accent. I'm not fond of
at all
um
Well, there's there's different kinds of southern accents
Okay, I might be uninitiated due to my you know being up here in the great north
There's um
I don't I don't really know which is which I've heard people like I've heard people do impressions of like an alabama accent
Versus like a tennessee accent versus like a you know, a virginia accent or whatever and like they're all different
All I know is that there are some
there are some
I don't I wouldn't say that I like love or hate any of them in particular. I think that some of them sound better
When women have them and some of them sound better when men have them, you know, and I'll agree with that
I agree and they don't work as well in the reverse. Yeah
Uh, yeah, I'm trying to think of like ones. I don't like what what accent does sarah palin have?
Oh like uh like oh like I'm like a midwestern sort of uh, like wiskansen like like a kind of wiskansen
I just I just remember being very shrill and
Sharp and I didn't like it
I mean, I know she's alaskan, but I don't actually know if I think she it has like a midwestern like wiskans
Yeah, but yeah, that that's a bad one. That's a pretty bad one. Yeah
I feel like it's less about specific accents and more how accents combine with people's like voice types
Where yeah, you'll hit one where they have this picture like tones their voice combined with the accent. That's just no no good no good
I like I like I like irish accents. Oh, yeah
That's pretty good. Um, I'm trying to think if there's any that I particularly like
irish is good generally
I'm trying to think of like what is they said attractive voices, right?
Yeah, like I don't know
exactly
What what what I think of as like an attractive voice because it's always with a person attached
Right
Even if you've never had you've never I mean you've never had like a
I mean
Surely there have been like people who you you've heard them speak, but you've never
Like garrison keeler has a really good voice
But like I saw that motherfucker like a couple weeks ago. I'd never seen what he looked like before and like holy shit
Do you know who that is? No
garrison keeler is a
He's the like a the end. He's an npr like radio
Guy rate radio personality. He has a he has a very nice voice and he looks like a fucking
He looks like fucking
God
Like down syndrome dwight shrewd. I don't know. Oh, no
You look
I exaggerate but not that much
Yeah, I need to see what that what's this guy's name
garrison keeler keeler is spelled key k e i l l o r
Yeah, all I can think of is like fucking
Like voice sounds and not really accents because I I guess I can't parse american accents, but like
Raven from teen titans
and and like kim pine
uh from the scott pilgrim movie
And and and and and what's her face the girl from b and puppy cat that's sort of like
understated sort of
low-pitched female voice
But that's not an accent. That's just a feeling
Yeah, that's so that's like a like a personality type
I
Is that is that the attractive type to you or the unattractive type the attractive. Oh, yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I guess that's pretty good
um
I
Don't know. I don't know if I have like a voice
type
Exactly, it just yeah, there's not really one type. It's just sort of like things sound good or they don't
And I can't really attribute that to an accent although some accents are very thick
I don't think any thick accent is particularly like attractive
But I do think a lot of northern british accents are funny and cool
If a voice is too
No, the English I should say a voice can sound like too, uh, uh
Strong there are some voices. I don't know what it is like they voice their vowels too much or like they are too like
There's there's a such a thing as a voice that like sounds too strong and I find it off-gooding
I don't know. I don't know how to explain that but there have been voices. I've heard that I'm like, ah
Ah, it's not what I wanted. Yeah
I don't know anyway
Uh, any should we should we move on? Yeah, I think so
Okay, next one is um
Next one is uh, this one is called. Sorry. It is called. How many do we have left?
Only like two I think
Oh, yeah, literally two the next one is called xx the lore destroyer xx
Uh, three two one go
I gotta make this quick because I never know who's listening to me. I'm constantly being watched
I am constantly being
Being
Chased followed around you don't understand what you will understand. Hello. Nice to meet you. I am the lore destroyer
I am a special agent since back in time
From from many decades ago many many millennia so many millennia you will never understand
It is impossible for humans to comprehend a long time. But but point being that that I was sent
Here to this present day so much destroy every annoying
PCP lore voicemail
You hate them. I hate them
It's funny because we know we didn't have any of those this week, but it's okay. It's okay
We we we it's okay because because I'm going to kill every person who makes lore
This is my burden. This is my curse
And I'm I'm I'm sincerely I'm sincerely sorry
For not coming sooner
I have had your services, uh, frank. I've been constipated
I was supposed to get out on my my mission a few
Few weeks ago, but I've been on the I've been on the toilet, man. Oh, it's it's it's what it is
But keep an eye out for me
Um, because I'm gonna be here. We could we could uh
Gucci we we could we could enshrine this we have several options. We could enshrine this in the voice grail
or
We could we could demand
We could basically demand that he make more voicemails by putting him in voice jail
Ah, no, uh, I don't now that the the meta has shifted if that's the case then the jail will be more sought after
There'll people be coming in saying uh, I'm stupid. You hate me now put me in the jail
They'll come back. It's I you say that if that's a shit. I feel like it's always kind of been like that
Yeah, I guess
All right. Look lord destroyer. We will we will we will watch we will be watching the skies
signal
Good good screaming
This is the last one. This is the last one. This one is called cross got my wisdoms pulled
three two one go
I got my wisdom teeth removed a couple of days ago and for the first 48 hours after the surgery
I was actually doing pretty fine, but throughout day three. I've been extremely nauseous and lightheaded
Obviously, I'll feel better by the time you're hearing this but nonetheless
I'm curious if any of you guys have gotten your wisdoms pulled and if so, how was the recovery?
I feel like I
Am I crazy? I feel like I got asked this like not that long ago
I even on the show. I don't think it was on the show, but um
I I had wisdom teeth coming in
And for some reason they said yeah, you can keep them
I was like, oh
Oh, I've all the only like the only situation I've heard of wisdom teeth is that they have to be pulled out
And so when I heard they were coming in I thought that was bad
But no, I just have them now. I just have extra teeth
Well, you just have enough space. You're a you're a good one
I'm I'm one of the bad. I'm one of the good ones
You're a vault
Um, well, yeah, I had my wisdom teeth out when I was like a senior or a junior. I think it was a junior in high school
and um
Yeah, I didn't find I didn't get nauseous
I didn't find the pain too bad, you know, it ached it ached for a while afterwards
But um, I got swollen like my face was swollen for like a week afterwards
Uh, uh, it was very hideous
And it was very cringe because I actually had like a date with a girl
Uh, I don't think she thought it was a date lemal, but I liked her
And then we went and I had to hung it hang out with this girl
Uh with my fucking swollen face
And uh, it was embarrassing. Oh no, um, yeah, so that's that's how mine was. Yeah, you know, I it all worked itself out
I didn't get nauseous from it. Uh
I did get like it was really weird because I got them pulled
And then I was doing like totally fine. I wasn't even sore but for a few nights in a row
I would wake up in a cold sweat like I've never had before like just my body shaking
And I'm pretty sure I was like fighting off some sort of infection, but at the time I was like, it's fine
I'm sure it's fine and I just kind of lived my life and I'm still here today. So
Uh, good luck with your wisdom teeth
I remember like
Not very like like after like the the the teeth wounds had already started healing
I remember at some point like I felt something like
In my the in back there in the teeth and I reached back and I pulled out like a big like hard chunk of something
And I I remember I remember thinking at the time that it was like a piece of bone that they'd left in
But I don't think that was it
I think it was probably actually like a chunk of like maybe blood or something
That had like coagulated it could have been like some healing stuff too because like
At least when they didn't mind they left like little divots kind of and I had to like make sure I cleaned them out very specifically
Yeah, because it would just collect like gross gunk
True. Yeah, I don't know. Um, so I don't know you could probably look forward to like pulling pieces out
Uh, you're basically ruined as a human being at this point. Yeah, it's over
You know with I mean the the the wisdom teeth actually contain many like short short nerve endings that like
Massively increase sexual pleasure. So like, you know, good luck. Good luck having a fulfilling relationship now
At this at this point you're doing it to yourself
You you have been mutilated. You have been mutilated cross. You brought it back around
We've finally enforced for a forced
forced uh, uh wisdom teeth removals in the pcp voice jail by the skin of your teeth
But
That's um, that's it. That's the last one
That's the last one. Oh wow
Wow
And it was some circumcision via ben saint
Right. No, no, no, that's not what I was talking. There was no reference to that
Okay, um, that's the end. Um, if you want to send a voicemail speakbike.com slash
pcp voicemail, um
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Uh for uh bonus episodes, uh, listen to the commentary track
and the voicemail
Bonus episode this week was the commentary track from the old days, uh on the first episode. We've commentated it
I remember to get a a I have covet shirt if you have covet
If you have covet make sure you buy the shirt, uh, otherwise you won't have covet anymore and that'll be a big problem for you
What a shirt. Uh, what a shirt
Any anything else anything else? Um before we before we sign off
Final thoughts final final vibe check guys final final vibe final temperature check. How are we feeling?
How hot are we right now? I'm feeling warm and and toasty just like
You know a man filled with blood would be a red man if you will
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Nice. Nice. Yeah, low art low art vibe temperature. I'm nice and cozy right now
I've been like wrapped up in a blanket this whole time drinking some nice water
Honestly, couldn't be better
um
Yeah, the only thing
Is make sure you listen to my shitty orchestral cover of the pcp theme. Oh, yeah
Yeah, link link in link in the description and um, you know if you like, uh, uh cartoon video game
Media analysis talk, maybe check out low arts other youtube videos as well. Perhaps. Oh, bless. Yeah
Also, yeah, we have a podcast of me and ben saint on there. So you might be interested in that
I didn't we didn't even mention that we did that one
podcast that one time about pooh's grand adventure
Yeah, and it was like as long as the movie itself
It was I think yeah, I think it was longer, uh
Um, don't don't watch pooh's grand adventure. Just listen to our podcast instead. We should have just
track
You know, I never did finish that um
That that pooh retrospective series damn
I I still kind of intend to at some point just I have other stuff
I want to do first well like we we delved into deep topics there folks
We talked about uh rabbits literacy. That was probably chief among the topics. So I yeah lower
I'm so glad I'm so glad that this came up. I want something happened to me last week
And I was like and I was like what the fuck is this my
roommate
Has a mug and I saw this mug
And I looked at it and it said um
I think it said um
Your your brick you're stronger than you think braver than you believe in
The other one. Yeah, remember from the movie it had said that on it and I was like and I was like wait
What is this like is this a poo mug and like it didn't have poo anywhere on it
Yeah, I was asking my my friends like what's going on with this mug like
What about this quote and someone looked it up and they're like, oh
Apparently that's an a.a. Milne quote and I was like no
No, it's definitely it's definitely not an a.a. Milne quote because it's from that movie and that's like way after Milne died
And but then I was like wait a minute
Did they like was that a line from like the old poo? Oh, it probably was yeah in corp
Well, that's what I thought maybe but I looked and no it's no
It's just that quote has just been that quote is out there in the zeitgeist and it has been um
Misattributed to Milne retroactive. Wait a minute. My friend. Let this up. This is it. I'm gonna try and find this right now
My friend we've discovered this
um
There's a blog there's a blog that is entirely about
Misattributed Winnie the Pooh quotes
It's an epidemic. I have I have to look it up and see if I can find it right now. Um
It's an epidemic
Hold on that's such a funny blog to have here it is. It's called. It's called. Yes. It's called poo misquoted
There's a blog on there's a blog called poo misquoted
and um
Okay, it was updating through
Okay, the last update was january 2018
But it went for like four years
And yeah, my my friend
Found this blog and this is where we discovered like
Yeah, people attribute the your braver than you believe stronger than you think smarter than whatever
To milne but in fact, no, it just comes from the movie and milne never said it. Um
So, yeah, that was uh
I'm so I'm glad I remembered because I thought that that was like
Can't I can't believe this I was so proud of myself because I was like, no, that's not a milne quote
I'm sure of it. Yeah, and it turned out to be right. So, you know, you're like, I've watched poo's grand adventure
I know everything there is to know
I know
Yeah, exactly and I said listen to my podcast
Uh, okay. Yes, that is an a a melanchote the a a melanchote is patreon.com slash benz
Exactly
It's truly ahead of his time. All right. I think that's it. I think that's gonna do it
That's it. That's it. Goodbye everyone end of the podcast
Good night
Love you. Love you