Jim Priest is Georgia Tech's kicker, and he's bored.
By the time this game is all over, he will have kicked 18 extra points.
He bested he made a steak dinner that he can kick a ball through the uprights on a kickoff.
But then he went off himself, and he turns on the jets.
Morris Gouger, while lining up for the catch, smacks into the goal post.
The ball bounces off his head and into Priest's arms.
Jim Priest has just caught his own kickoff for a touchdown.
The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever, and I'm here with my teammates on
our team that's going to win the competition. Ben Saint, the forward ball handler.
Professional sports genius. Ben Saint here, reporting in with a lust for victory.
Endless Jess, our powerhouse powerfucker forward.
Light nigger, dark nigger, phone nigger, real nigger, rich nigger, phone nigger, house nigger,
field nigger, still nigger. Yo, OJ's out, everybody. OJ's out. Actually, that's not true.
Munchy, the most powerful defensive man in the universe.
Boss, I got the opponent's wife in my peripheral. I have them. I have them locked inside it.
I'm ready to pull the trigger whenever the game starts. I'm ready to shoot them,
and then the game will start, and they'll be like, wait, I can't play the game. I have to go.
My wife was fucking blown. Her head was blown off her fucking shoulders.
Stand by for orders, Munchy, and lastly our... We got a reverse JFK situation on our hands here.
Code red, code red. Lastly is our diminutive goalkeeper hypocrite.
Football is an American colloquialism that is just wrong. They just got it wrong,
and they're wrong, and they don't know what they're doing. Also, I love basketball.
Me too, dude. All right, let's go. All right, there you go.
There's our highlight, folks. That's the end, you can believe.
So we're talking about sports today, everybody. We're talking... It's sports center today.
Here we are. Okay, let's settle down and get to our public service announcement from Urban
Dictionary, definition of sports. Okay, here's the top one. I can't fucking wait to hear this.
All right, here's the top one that sucks shit. It's one of those... It's like a dad joke.
Sports, America's state-sponsored religion. All right, let's... Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Number two is sport. So singular, but this is still good. The name your dad calls you
by that makes you feel like a total loser, which you probably are anyway, synonyms, champ, chief,
etc. We're really getting to the bottom of what sports is. I know, we really are. All right,
tell me, who's played sports? Who's been a contender out there on the field? Yeah?
I may not look like it, but when I was a little kid, I was a big sports guy. I used to play soccer
every single day of my fucking life. Soccer? I wouldn't have guessed, okay. You seem like a
football guy to me. American football. The only thing I'm going to be able to say intelligently
is that I like watching football on TV. I like doing it. That's what I know about sports.
I've played soccer a little bit. I used to do baseball. I used to do football. I used to do
all that. I used to do fucking tennis, but now I'm an esports kind of guy. So I'm just going to tell
you about how esports is the fucking future and how I'm a god. That's what I really want to get to
at the end of this. Okay, but let's build up to it. I kind of want to talk about normal sports
as well, mostly. Of course. Because E is gay. E-electronics are gay. We can do another episode
entirely on esports. Believe me, there's a lot to cover there. There's a lot to go into with my
personal investment. What's the future of fucking society? Yeah, I agree. All right, hang on. What
were you saying, Jesse? You know, when I was a little kid, like really young, like five or six
or whatever, I was a sports prodigy. This is true. This is a true story. I could hit the
baseball really far and good. I could throw a hoop from anywhere on the court. I could do like
trick shots, and then I got a Sega, and that was the end. E-sports, dude. Fucking esports.
I threw it all away for esports. It's the worst mistake I ever made. He sacrificed being a blast
down on the field for all that blast processing. I sacrifice being a black
for being a blast person. I was like, I'm not black. I'm OJ. Okay. Okay. Well, what about what
about, what is it? It's like NBA three on three hoops, you know? Or no, it's NBA Jam, like the
greatest sports game ever made. I can do one better Mario, Mario sports, three on three hoops.
That's kind of what was infecting my brain there. I like that game. That's a good one.
That is a good game, because it's got white mage and black mage from Final Fantasy and its
character. What about we esports? What about we esports? The greatest sporting challenge on the
modern console? Weesports is probably like the, I think, isn't that like the most popular game of
all time? It's like number one most popular thing. Yeah, exactly. It's up there anyway. I do like
but I want to talk about real sports. I want to talk about when I was a little boy, because we
are sort of doing that. I was into like sports because you had to be, because you had to do
sports for school. And I was actually very competitive and very, very vicious and I didn't
care about it. You're a competitive guy. You've got that beast inside you. Especially when playing
soccer. I wasn't good at passing. I was never good at like a technical like knowing where to
kick. But I did know that if you kicked people, they would not attack. They would just back off
and I was a perfect defender. So I would go around kicking people to make them cry. And I didn't
care. And that's why I didn't have any friends. But I was such a good defender and nobody would
fucking go anywhere near me. And I felt powerful for the first time. If that was too off the field
too. Oh, that's damn dude. That's effective. Especially also in basketball. I'm a very small
person. I've always been. But in basketball, surprisingly, because of how aggressive and
like I just don't I don't let up. Because I just hate people when I'm playing sports. I just
like I'm your enemy team. You are going to die somehow by my hand. So I would leap up at people
even like the black kids who are like really tall, I would just leap right up with them.
I obviously look really stupid while doing it. But like they, they, you know, people are scared
of how how how seriously I took attacking. I love I love attacking people. Yeah, it's it's
the mental game. I fancied myself. I fancied myself more of a tactician, more of a tactical
player than a physical player in sports. Of course, you know, I played my I played my share of sports
in school. I was in I was in like Little League Baseball or whatever. And like one of my one of
my shittiest childhood memories is there was like a big fucking game or whatever. It was like, oh,
we're gonna were we gonna win the game or lose the game? Who knows? And I was playing in the
outfield and I was bored and I was looking at the sky and I had to pee. And I was like, man,
the game's almost over. I'm just gonna hold it. I'm just gonna hold it until the end of the game
so we can win the game. And then but then time wore on and I just had to pee really bad. And it
started to like hurt. It started to like be physically. And I was and I was like, I can't,
I can't find. So I like ran in and I was like, coach, let me go pee. And he was like fine.
So I went and peed and I came back and we had won the game while I wasn't there.
I was like, oh, man, why did I just go earlier or something? But but on the subject of being a
tactical player, being a sports genius. So one day in gym class, we were playing like soccer or
something. And I was like, I know I can't compete. I know I can't compete with these bullies with
these bullies and trolls and jocks and chads, physically, but I can't compete with their brute
strength. But my mind, my mind is sharp like a like a like a whetstone. My mind is keen like a
blade stones aren't sharp you. So I so I so I I engineered what I called the reverse sneak attack.
Wait, which is actually the exact opposite of a sneak attack, because you
loudly announce that you are performing a sneak attack while simultaneously not performing a sneak
attack. So I was just dribbling up the field and a defender and a defender just came up to me
just trying to you know, just being do you know the internet bully and troll just trying to
just trying to take the ball from me like a normal idiot doesn't he isn't seeing like a brilliant
strategy coming his way. And he says he's coming up to me. I just yell in his face as loud as I
can sneak attack. And then I just kicked the ball past him. And he was too dumbfounded. He was too
dumbfounded to do a thing. What I'm saying is the plan worked perfectly and I broke sports forever.
Actually, that technique was banned in professional sports because it was too powerful.
Is that true? Wow, Ben, you're the coolest. Yeah, good story, Ben. I definitely heard all of it.
I didn't leave and then just hear the end of it. Me neither. Let me tell you, Ben, I've had to
I've had to contend with some IRL cyber bullies a few times myself on the on the field of battle.
Let me tell you about one day in the life of a young boy where he transcended humanity and became
a literal sports guide. Okay. So this was in middle school sometime and we were playing this
game called poison ball poison ball. It's a dodgeball type game. But instead of having people
like restricted to to either side of the field, there are actually there is two active balls at
any time. And basically the entire field is in place so you can run around anywhere and just
tag people. And the way it works is like just the two balls sort of act as like opposing magnets
and like where one is basically what you do is you go to where the ball isn't if you've got one
and you just pick off weak people one at a time on the fringes. And eventually it works down to
there's just two people each with the ball and they just matrix duel each other and try to like
fake each other out and shit. Okay. So on an average gym class day, we play this during gym
class, of course, on an average gym day, you could get around four of those games in. Let me tell
you on this one day, something happened deep down in my brain's dick. And I became the god. I was
a I would I had watched the matrix recently. So I'd internalize their their mad skills. My dodging
game was insane. I won three out of four of those games. And I only lost the fourth one. And remember
this is everyone against everyone. There's like there's like 30 people in this class. All right.
I trounced them all. I defeated them all. The only reason I lost the last game was because the two
people who got the ball at the very start of the game before I had a chance to get my hands on it,
because I would have turned the tide. They both they grabbed the balls, they looked each other,
they nodded, and they both marched over to the corner where I was. And like a fucking hero,
I just stood them in the I looked in the I said, just do it. Just do it, you fucking cowards.
You can't handle me and my best. You don't deserve me at my worst. That's what I said to them. And
then they put me down. They was like the end of Braveheart. They put me down because they knew I
was too fucking powerful. If I'd won one more game, I would have literally floated like a god
into the heavens. And and life would never have that those jealous bullies just wouldn't just
wouldn't allow that. This is this is this is them dragging down all of humanity's evolution. It was
like it was like in 2001 space Odyssey. I was that baby in space. And they just they pulled me,
they put their hooks in me. They pulled me back down to earth. And they devolved me back into
a lowly human being once again. That's what happened. But I'll never forget that day. I'll
never forget that day. Jesus Christ. There was the assassination of Julius Caesar, like everyone's
conspiring against him because he was just too fucking powerful. Exactly. Exactly. It was exactly
like that. I have something similar, but it was more like it was more like me sering my dominance
and then everyone like deciding that I should be eliminated a little bit. Okay. So we were playing
soccer. I was playing soccer like happened to Hillary in the election. Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
We were playing soccer and these fucking these these fucking these fucking cowards and these
these children were just trying up not playing the game correctly. And there was being believe
they were breaking the fucking rules. And then I was I was going to allow them to fucking sully
the name of soccer. And so I kept I kept fucking walking over them and like saying if you don't
play the game right, I'm going to fucking like kill you. I'm going to destroy you and your family.
But they they just they just fucking wouldn't they just they just wouldn't and I forgot the
exact move is one of them got it and then like and like fucking like like like somehow like
like like they had like fucking like picked it up and then like moved it or something something
fucking so like obviously like breaking the fucking rules that it had to be dealt with.
So when they kicked it, I jumped and thrown the fucking ball, I caught it in midair,
slammed on the ground like like held the ball to my chest and I screamed the word hell and this
was in fifth grade. And so everyone's eyes like locked on me instantaneously because I said a
swear word. And then I made like I made like a big old speech about how these people need to be
fucking driven from our lands because they do not respect the sport and they must be fucking
eliminated because they do not they do not appreciate the craftsmanship that it has to go in
to creating sports rules. And so I just held the ball I just held the ball in my fucking hands
and let anyone take it until the until they were marched off in shame and everyone like booed them.
Yes, actually, justice won this day. Yeah. By the way, can I just can I just also share a
quick story about the word hell specifically? Just just one time in third this is in third grade.
I was talking to a friend we were we had just read anamorphs. All right, he had read volume one of
anamorphs and I was going to read it that night hadn't gotten to it yet. And when he said the
name of the character Chapman, who I believe was the principal in the book, I say vice vice
principal Chapman that you're exactly right. Vice principal Chapman. I said this exact word
to this exact inflection. Who the hell is Chapman? That's exactly what I said. And they
immediately were like, Nate, what have you done? They pulled me aside. They called my parents and
had them come pick me up because I was disrupting class by being a monster a little swearing monster
while in the most tortured way possible. Yeah, I just wanted to be cool so bad. Stunning.
Yeah, so funny to me because like, hell isn't even a thing like I know it's not even a swear,
but not only that, but I remember like a like a little kid. I think it was like, like, seven or
10 or something like really young. And he got in trouble for saying fuck. And all the that happened
was the teacher yelled at him and made him like feel bad in front of like a class of older kids
like it was like he said fuck. And he got in trouble and he got shouted at and humiliated
in front of another class. And that was it. It wasn't like calling parents fucking parents and
shit. They made it a federal fucking case. That sounds like much more justice than than Nate got
the poor bastard. It's true. One time I was tricked into flipping someone off and then they got me
in trouble. Were they playing a mimic game or something? No, I remember. I remember somebody
telling me to do that and I didn't know what it was and I got in trouble. Yeah, that's what happened.
This fucking stupid, this fucking like like like virgin for life fucking like like twig
like football star. Fuck him. Daniel, Daniel, if you are fucking listening this, I'm I never
forgot about you and you will be fucking eliminated. You know, you know Daniel's listening. Yeah.
I know Daniel is just seething with jealousy.
That you became a member of the PCP and he was left to flounder. He was left to flounder in his
pathetic sports stardom. And this is what you fucking deserved, you stupid piece of shit. You
know why? Because in third grade, I was sitting next to you and you said, Hey dude, check this out.
And like, like, like, like, okay, okay, put up, put out your fucking hand and then lower all of
like, like, pull your entire like, like, make it like a fist, but then have your middle finger be
out. Just, just, just try dude. Wouldn't it be funny if that happened? Wouldn't that be fucking
Larry? So you did that one day? Wouldn't that be interesting? And then I'd be like, yeah,
dude, that'd be really fucking funny, dude. And then I did it. And then he was like, Hey,
teacher, look what Anthony's doing. I was fucking pummeled. I was beat in the fucking street. I was,
I was pulled aside. I was putting like a will or one like, like, like abandoning your post,
like like firing squad, blindfolded, fucking executed in front of my entire class.
They really brought the horrible, whorey hammer of the gods down.
And I'll never fucking forgive you, Daniel, Daniel, ever, ever. You and your fucking yacht club.
Just because you, just because you can fucking, you can count better. Just because you fucking
read Harry Potter while I was reading Diary Wimpy Kid, doesn't mean you're fucking better than me.
All right. It doesn't fucking mean anything. I got aside with Daniel on that one, but you know.
You fucking bastard, you fucking traitor, you fucking broodist.
Yeah, I've been looking for a chance. I've been looking for a chance to betray him.
Okay, let's, let's refocus on sports, I guess. What do we got here? What do you got to say?
All right. I want to talk about sports I like, because I do like watching a few sports,
not the biggest, biggest ones, but I like watching Wimbledon when that's on. And the Olympics is
always kind of interesting. And, you know, horse racing, stuff like that, stuff that's not,
not like the most popular. Horse racing? Horse racing, I believe.
Well, the Grand National specifically, it's like, it's like the big horse race of the year.
And they've never even seen a horse. Is that like NASCAR for horses? Is that the idea?
It's like when they get all the smallest people and all the biggest horses and they just put
them together and see what happens. Okay, all right. And let me tell you, there's some chemistry
out there. Yeah, okay. But I have not watched a sport. I have not watched a sport in years. Like,
I watched the Super Bowl maybe like several years ago, just on a lark, just as a joke,
just ironically, I watched the Super Bowl. And that was pretty much the end. I have not watched
the Olympics. I can't, people, people act like I'm weird because I'm not watching the Olympics.
Like, I feel like I'm supposed to be watching the Olympics, but I'm like, I can't imagine a thing
worse. I can't imagine a worse fate than watching the Olympics. It's kind of nice to just have it on
in the TV, on some TV nearby. Then you feel watching the Olympic girls do the gymnastics is
more sexy than having actual sex. It's the only attractive thing in the world. I gotta give a
shout out, I gotta give a shout out to the women's volleyball team. The volleyball team is the perfect
mixture of like, they wear the least clothing and they're doing the most active activities.
It's the best. Volleyball, that's the way to go. These are like fucking, these are like fucking,
like, buff, like athletes. These are, these are the kind of girls that played softball in college.
But dude, compared to American fatties, they're a thousand times better. There could be no
comparison. I don't, whatever, whatever, man. I'm committing. I'm not, I'm committing. I'm not
feeling it. You know, I, that's a, that's a growing sentiment, I think. People just being like,
bored of the, the, oh, oh, fucking curling semi-finals is up. Just watch it. Yeah, I don't know. Like,
there's a lot of shit. I can't keep track of it all. I kind of like it the way Gib does, I guess.
Just watching it in the background, like, oh, yeah. I guess like, when, yeah, yeah, I'm totally,
so in other words, put it on and don't watch it, which is something that I could probably
have a great time doing. Yeah, because like, because like, whenever there's like a big thing,
when there's like the ashes, which is like the, the cricket tournament between Australia and England,
there's like, the, there's Wimbledon, which is obviously the biggest tennis tournament in the
world, like something big, but like, I don't care. But I'll watch the final and I'll be like,
glancing at the TV because other people are watching it. It's just sort of nice to know that
it's a thing that's being talked about. It's just like, oh yeah, you know, I know what's going on.
You know, Gib, I have never felt a bigger cultural divide between us than I do right now with these,
this, the ashes, I, all right, here's the thing about the ashes. Cricket is a, is a big English
thing and it's also big in Australia and there's a big fierce rivalry. There's, there's other like
actual cricket tournaments that go on. I think, I think, yeah, the ashes is just England and Australia
or maybe it's everyone, I forget. But the thing is the ashes is like, it's literally a thing of
ashes, which is the trophy because of something that happened a long time ago and I can't remember.
I was going to say, do they burn the losing teams and then they become the ashes?
Wait, I remember, I remember from Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, the ashes is like a wood,
like an ancient wooden artifact that was burned and like, yeah, yeah, there's some,
the ashes are like a thing in Hitchhiker's Guide and like the third, like the third book.
It's a, sorry. That's important. Yeah, yeah. Anyone who knows what I'm talking about, comment
and remind me. Might be related, yes. But um, yeah, there's that, uh, fucking,
my, I don't know, this is totally a tangent, but my, uh, my neighbors,
I'm trying to think of like culturally divided, divided things. Like,
rugby is like the coolest, rugby is like the coolest sport in the world and anyone who does it
is like 10 times more of a badass because like there's no padding and it's super cool and they
just run at each other for like an hour and they all die. They are the, the big rugby thing is called
the five nations because it's like, it's England, it's Wales, Scotland, uh, France and Ireland,
I think, and they're all like, they're all big fat, tough, all well-known independent nations,
Wales, Scotland. No, they're all just, they're big rugby people and they're all nearby and they're
just like, we fucking love rugby and eating meat and being big, beefy guys and we want to beat the
shit out of each other with a ball. Why don't you guys invite France to play sometime? That'd be nice.
We did. That's why I said the France is part of it. Oh. Oh no. The five nations you
fuck. Okay, all right. But yeah, like, the cool thing about watching a rugby match is that people,
it's like the same sort of size as a soccer match, but the crowd is so, so quiet and so respectful.
It's like, it's more nowadays, it's, yeah, it's, it's more quiet than a fucking golf match,
sometimes a rugby match. When something's really, like, you know, they don't do stupid
chants, they don't do screaming constantly, it's just like, oh yeah, yeah, we're watching a thing.
Fuck my asshole, fuck my asshole, let's go. It feels the, the manliest sort of thing ever.
I like it. I mean, I do like, uh, when I go to a sporting event, I like to be able to take it seriously
what's happening on the field and sometimes, like, a lot of people I've noticed go to like
football games just for like the experience of going and, you know, buying the beer and getting
the food and stuff. But at a certain point, I do want to be able to pay attention to the actual
game and be interested in what's happening down there. I mean, like, I go to football games
more than anything else, which is to say, like, I've been to one in the last year. Uh, so that's,
that's pretty fun. That's pretty fun. I, I, a while, when I was a little kid, I used to like, like,
like maybe like three or four times I went to the baseball stadium near my house, specifically
because I liked their brand of pizza, like the best. So I, so I went there just to eat pizza
and then like, I would see like, oh, there's a buy ticket to get it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, okay. Yeah. Yeah. And so that was cool. And I had like, like every time I did it. So yeah,
I was just popping against the pizza. Then I realized, but baseball takes like fucking a year.
Like it is the longest sport ever made. And it was, I have been to like two or three baseball
games in my life and never, ever have I enjoyed baseball. Yeah, baseball is pretty boring. Not
a big fan. I think baseball is like the coolest sport, but not one that I ever want to watch.
Like I think, I think that all sports are great and I love them all. I just don't want to watch any
of them. I think that's the thing about baseball, I feel like baseball generates just an absolutely
outrageous amount of like numbers and statistics to analyze. Like I feel like baseball is like,
people just do that. I feel like baseball is like analyzed, maybe like proportionally more
than other sports. I agree. And I don't know why that is. I mean, I'm sure you said maybe basketball.
I mean, I hear a lot of people talking stats with basketball too. I feel like the biggest
sports nerds are baseball nerds. I agree. I agree. Moneyball was a good movie.
I was just, so I was just, all right, so I just put out a video about 17776.
Oh, here we go with the shilling your videos. No, no, no, I'm not saying this to show my video.
I'm saying that like the guy who made that is like a big like sports nerd stats analysis guy.
And I, and I like looked into his work and I went and I watched a bunch of his old
videos. Well, they're not even, they're like a year old. And just going into some like
weird sports happening and his name is John Boyce. And some of them were really fucking
fascinating. He takes one where he looks at Barry Bond's batting average and he says,
okay, this is so fucking good. How and like a lot of his batting average is high because people
just deliberately walk in because they were so scared of having him hit the ball. And so he's
like, how good would he have been if he had not even had a bat, if he had never swung in a pitch?
And like he, he did this to the stats analysis and he was still the best hitter in the league
by a mile, even if he never swung. And there was, there was another one. There was like an old
game in like 1916 that ended in like a score of two, a football game that was 222 to zero.
And he just like walks through the whole game and just be like, absolute incompetence and like,
like wild, wild dogs chased the players in the middle of the game. Yeah, there was, there was
the first play of the game, the losing teams of quarterback got like knocked the fuck out.
The halfway through the game, they brought him back in clearly with a concussion, but like they
brought him in, they snapped the ball, it hit him with in the face and he just, there was, okay,
there was a kicker who kicked the ball and it flew across the field, hit a defender on the helmet,
and then the kicker caught his own kick off of the defender's helmet and scored a touchdown with it.
There was, there was a guy, there was a guy who was just there to impress his, it was a college
game. There was a guy who like, he got the ball, he wasn't there to actually play, he was just
impresses professors, he didn't know what to do, he like throws the ball, runs off the field,
hides behind a fence, but there are, no, no, it gets better, but they're all ready because he was
scared. There were already, no, no, listen, there were already two other players hiding behind the
fence, and, and, and they don't want him to give away their hiding spot, so they throw him back
over the fence onto the field. What the fuck? Okay, all right, so like this, this is some pretty
hot shit, and um, yeah, so sports, so sports, I was watching this and I remembered, I remembered
that sports can be cool. He's just filled with abject terror. Like he tries to escape in the
future. All right, that's the coolest thing I've ever heard. Yeah, I highly recommend, uh, yeah,
that video. What's that guy's channel called again? It's John Voice. Right, okay. Yeah, yeah, and,
and the video is called 222-0. I will definitely watch that, but I was gonna say, what I, the
thing about me in sports is the, the best thing about sports, I do like watching football because
I think the game is fun, and I understand it pretty well, and I like to watch guys, and I root for
the Patriots. I'm a Patriots fan, um, and, and they're the fucking dominating team all the time,
so it's fun to watch your team win, so that's nice. Uh, uh, plus I grew up, you know, close to
Boston, so whatever, I don't make fucking excuses for this. Uh, uh, uh, plus my friend John likes
the Eagles and they always lose, which is really nice, but anyway, what I'm getting to is that my
favorite type of sports are the ones that make the players look the most attractive. So I'm talking
about, that's right, that's right, I'm talking about weightlifting specifically, like, like
powerlifting. Powerlifting guys actually get a little fat though. Yeah, powerlifting guys are
way fat, they're all bare-foot. The best sport, the best sport is competitive bodybuilding,
going on a stage, and flexing your muscles, and showing how cool you are. No, if you think those
guys look cool or good, you're fucked up. They do look good. They don't look, they don't even look
they're heroes. They don't. Yeah. Well, silly. They do look really silly. I would say I'm a bit of
like a traditional bodybuilder enthusiast, if anything, like, uh, like, like Frank Zane back
of it, like before, before, uh, uh, you know, fucking steroids were just like, you know, defined
everything, even though like guys like Arnold, like are, are beautiful and they're on steroids.
All right. Uh, Arnold is like, yes, like, I understand that. I've seen some bodybuilders
that go so over the top that they literally look like a fucking mutant zombie bitch. Yeah,
I'm not into that as much. You know what's funny about those guys is that, you know, they, they
work out, they make every part of their body humongous. What's coming next, but there's no
weightlifting to make your wiener bigger. So they're standing there in their underpants and these
little like G strings and their whole bodies are huge, but it just makes it look like they've got
little tiny wieners. Yeah, true. And their heads look small too by comparison. They, you can't do
anything about either of those. That's why you should never work out ever. They ought to, they
ought to make them take your pants off and judge who has the tiniest wiener and give that guy the
golden. Yeah, guys, there's nothing to do but just to, just to take off our pants and just,
you just got to do it. There's, there's nothing else we can possibly just have to do it naked,
guys. They should just have the who has the tiniest wiener competition. Oh, and also they're
all really big and muscly for some reason. Well, you know what it is? I kind of, I wonder sometimes
why is there not a biggest dick competition? I'm serious. I'm serious. I'm dead serious. It's,
it's so important, right? Like culturally, like having a big dick is so important. And yet there's
no big dick contest. And I understand that it's not much of a contest because someone would just,
someone just has the biggest dick, right? The same guy would win every year.
But like, they do that with like dog shows, right? Like dog shows, like they just show up and like
whoever's got the best dog wins. Wait, maybe you have to train the dog. You can't train your penis
to be larger. You can do some tricks with your dick. Like cock pushups, for example, you know,
yeah, you got a jelk. They're a tick, you know, I'm on board. I'm ready to sign up for this thing.
I thought there was already like a world record, largest dick.
It's, it's, I've like, okay, this is real gay, but I've looked into like I've tried to find like
video evidence of like the biggest dick and you can't like there is none. Like there's like rumors
and theories. I know exactly what you're talking about because I've looked it up too for scientific
purposes. You look up like who has the biggest winner. The guy who has it will show up, but
they won't actually show you it. Yeah, yeah, Jonah Falcon supposedly has a 13.5 inch dick,
but there's no fucking evidence of it. Like, are you fucking kidding me? Because, because all
the pictures have him like with like a sock over it or like, you know, you know what I'm talking
about? It's just because he has a really small body makes it look bigger. Well, this is like,
if you guys are talking about the same guy I'm talking about, this is like an average looking
dude, but he's got this monster cock that actually causes him, you know, a lot of like, it's like,
it's huge. It's like a problem that is so big. Yeah, I was just about to say is his name Mike Mate.
No, it's not Mike Mate. It's some other guy. I mean, it's just fucking, it's just fucking
ridiculous to me that like, there are like, it's so important. Like we talk about having,
we talk about big dicks like so much in our society. And they're just like, you try to find like,
okay, well, like show me, like show me like a 12 inch dick, like with a fucking ruler next to it,
to prove it. And you cannot find it, even though supposedly they're out there. All you can do is
look at porn. I guess that's like the biggest reason. It's all like, it's all like weird camera
angles and like, I just want to know for sure. Like, I just want to see it like laid out performance
so I can be like, Oh, so, so, so that's what it's like. So that's what's out there. But there's
no taboo. There's no fucking cultural taboos. That's why I wonder. That's why I wonder about that.
You know, it's bizarre. I find it bizarre. I'm with you. I'm with you. You probably have to go
in person and us to see it. Well, then he'll show you. Let's go. Hippo come. Well, let's go on an
adventure. Hell yeah. Yeah, we club. I'm ready. The reason I start a vlog series, Hippo and Ben's
quest for the biggest dick. That sounds like a rowdy fucker's cop. You know, yeah, that's a road
trip. So the reason I brought a bodybuilding in general is because I actually do do bodybuilding
myself, you know, as best I can. And I would consider myself a sport guy in that three times a
week I go and exercise and then go running sometimes. So it's not really a sport. It's just
like a training thing. It's just a separate category. That's just exercise. If you're not
competing, it's not a sport. You know, I guess that's fair. I guess that's fair. I'm competing
with myself. I always try to do my best. My favorite sport is gaming this YouTube system.
Oh, that's a good one. I'm not very good at it yet, though. No. I always lose. YouTube is the
ultimate eSports competition. It is. What about eSports? That's the greatest admission of all time.
What do you got about eSports, Manchu? Let's hear it. I love eSports because I can do it without
any work because video games are easy and you're pathetic if you play in them. But have you tried
getting into League of Legends? That's like a month-long endeavor to even understand the gist
of the game and all the fucking games and shit. Honestly, as games, there's nothing I detest more
than MOBAs and eSports. I've watched a few eSports. Mostly because I know the person who
was commentating them was a person I follow. I was like, okay, I'll have a look at this.
It was like StarCraft II, which I got the gist of pretty quick because I know what an RTS is.
It's like, whoa, they're clicking so fast. There are so many fucking shortcuts and clicking,
and moving stuff. It's pretty interesting. I couldn't watch a whole tournament, but that's
alright. The other one was Hearthstone, which is a game that I had played. I don't play anymore,
but I was really into it. That was the most potential you could actually be good at Hearthstone
because all you need is to play the game a lot. I've heard it's really random, though. I've heard
there's a lot of randomization. That's why I feel like I could do it. If I just get lucky,
I just say, oh yeah, I got the card I need, and they didn't. Similar to Hearthstone, I was a pretty
active follower of Magic the Gathering in general back in the day. For a time, I tried to keep up
with professional strats and know what people were up to. This was in college sometime, and I went
to like some tournaments and stuff and just tried my hand at it. I had friends who were far more
professional. I had a friend, actually, who was like a judge. He was a higher level guy. He had
gotten to a place where he could do consistently as well in tournaments enough to make. Because
when you win tournaments, if you're the grand prize winner, you get money. But if you just win
in general, you get a certain amount of the rarer cards from the pool. He was able to get to a
place where he could win enough that he could sell those cards and completely cover all his entry
fees and his transportation costs and shit. He just loved Magic, so it was the perfect
situation for him, and he was only getting better. I don't know what happened to that guy, but that
was that. That was my experience. I would say that esports in general is fine. Things like
competitive Counter Strike are kind of fun to watch, but they all pale in comparison to my
actual favorite type of esports. I would call this a sport, and that is speedrunning in general.
Speedrunning is the coolest. No, it's the best. It's the best. I love it so much. I like speedruns.
I love watching speedruns. I'm the biggest fan in the world of speedruns. Every GDQ is my birthday.
It's great. Well, before we get started talking about speedruns, I just want to say
SalTV, S-A-L-T-V. He commentates TF2 competitive. Some of that shit is really fun to watch
if you like TF2. Are you sure his name isn't Salt-V? No, S-A-L-T-V or something like that.
I used to watch his videos. He hasn't made one in a while, but they're kind of fun to look back at
to see a commentated TF2 competitive 6v6. To explain my background of esports real quick,
I watch esports all the time. I would say every week, if not more, which is more than I play
actual video games. I mainly follow Smash, all the games, and most FPSs. Right now, Overwatch is
big, so I'm watching that even though I'm not the biggest fan of Overwatch. In any FPS, I enjoy
greatly. I fucking love Smash. I know everything about Smash is the greatest game of all time,
and it's the... excuse me. That's actually a party game. Yeah, it's not a fighting game.
It's not really a fighting game, actually. It's a Republican party game. It has more fucking
inputs than anything else in the entire world. It's just a baby game, dude. It's just a baby game.
Now he's mad. Listen to the anger in that laugh. The closest thing to esports ID would be playing
Pokemon Showdown. I've always kind of wanted to compete in a tournament. I kind of don't even
know how to get started with it, but whatever. I would have no problem showing up and just losing,
but I would just kind of like to do it just to do it. Yeah, sounds fun. It's great because it's so
accessible. There are so many games you can play and go esports, and it's so accessible and easy to
do. Obviously, the high level is super resource-intensive and stuff. You have a great computer
and it'd be all technical and with your hands and shit, but in TF2, you can just fucking boot up
and then play for a little while and then go into competitive mode and fucking play, and it's great
and it's fun. Not the Valve competitive mode. You can do the fan shit because the Valve one
sucks. You know what I mean, though. It's super easy to go competitive with games, and I love them
all, and it's great. And you get Mad Dosh. And if you're lucky enough and you play Overwatch,
so you can get on TBS right after a Seinfeld episode, you can watch the TBS tournament.
I can watch Seinfeld and then Overwatch on TBS. Oh my god, it's the perfect combination. They go
together. You make so much fucking Mad Dosh playing Overwatch that frankly, you can't afford,
you, the viewer, cannot afford not to buy Overwatch right now. You could be raking in the
dough as a competitive, multi-shooter bullshit game, worst game in the world. You could be
collecting, you could be making dividends, and here you sit listening to me for shame.
The globalist conspiracy directly prints money from the Federal Reserve and distributes it to
Overwatch players, flooding the world economy with worthless US dollars, inevitably drying us
off of the poverty. We live in a post-scarcity world. We live in an Overwatch-based economy now.
We're going to move on from a petrol-based dollar, no more petrol dollars, it's now Overwatch
dollars, where the US dollars are completely comprised on Overwatch points, and that determines
your pay. What were you saying? I want to talk about that, because Overwatch is such a huge game,
and I have no desire to play it, but the amount of, like, if you want to get big at streaming,
you play Overwatch, because it's the big thing. If you want to, you know, to get, like, if I was
playing Overwatch instead of Minecraft, I mean, Minecraft is pretty big, but I would be getting,
like, so many new followers constantly, and it doesn't matter how good I am. Well, actually,
it probably does. But, like, it's like, it's a game, and you're supposed to play it to have fun,
but there are so many benefits to playing it, like, for an audience, like, monetarily, that I feel
some sort of, like, some pulling in the direction of playing it, even though I don't like it.
Here's what I think about that. I think when you're playing a game, like, super competitively,
like, eventually, you understand the game so well that you stop even seeing the game, and you become,
like, Neo in the Matrix, just seeing the ones and zeros. Like, it all becomes fucking code to you.
So I kind of think, to that extent, it almost doesn't matter what game you play, because eventually,
you'll reach an understanding where you've just, like, gone beyond what the game is even supposed
to be, and it just becomes, like, crunching numbers in your head and doing that. So it probably
doesn't matter to, like, a high-level player what game they're even playing.
There should be an eSports for Undertale, and the contest is just,
the winner is whoever doesn't do Skeletor as Papyrus.
The winner is whoever has the best time and has the best friendships at the end, whoever enjoys it the most.
What's funny about the way you say that is, like, you're framing it like, you know, to make Undertale,
like, a competitive thing, but that's exactly what speedrunning does. It makes any game into a
competitive thing where it's about optimization and strategy, and I love that.
It's a single-player game, and that means it's gay.
It does make it feel sad, though. That's bullshit. It's still competitive. What are you talking about?
The thing that I like about speedruns is that, like, you'll take a game that might take, like,
weeks to beat, like, I don't know, Mario 64 or something, and you watch a speedrun that's,
like, I don't know, beat it in, like, two hours. And what that basically does is take the entire
experience of playing a game and compress it down to, like, movie length, or, like, show length.
So you can, like, experience the entire game in, like, you know, in, like, a digestible
formula. You can sit down, and an hour later, you've watched someone play, you know, the entirety of
Banjo-Kazooie, and you're like, yeah, that was a good hour.
You know, Ben, I experienced Banjo-Kazooie.
I agree that that has a certain appeal to it, but I would say that, like, a lot of what you
end up doing is, like, skipping content. Like, if you can skip content in a speedrun, you skip
that content. Like, that's what you want to do.
Well, that's why you watch specific, like, hundreds of games.
Depends on the cent runs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, 100% runs.
Oh, you know, that's true.
Some of them.
Yeah, that is true.
I just watched a Mario 64 one the other day that was really good. It was, like, two hours.
Just the parkouring was incredible.
It was just, it was just breath, yeah, yeah, it's breathtaking.
I've been getting, I got into this guy recently who's been doing a really good service of making
videos detailing the legacy of the progression of speedrunning world records for various games.
And when it started, like, when people started speedrunning it and how, you know, over time,
people have figured out techniques to make it go lower, the time go lower and lower.
And it's really interesting and really well put together, sort of, like, just instruction,
like, like, like a history, sort of a timeline.
Those are fascinating.
The guy's name is Summoning Salt, if you type that in, you should find it.
Speedrunners talk about, like, when they discover a new technique or, like, a new strategy that
cuts their time down.
They talk about it like, new tech was discovered.
Like, a new technology is created.
There's so much hype.
I love it.
It's great.
Yeah.
And I love all the, like, when you, exactly, exactly, that kind of, that kind of, like,
putting on a pedestal, it's like, it's like giving a little pomp and circumstance to, like,
these kind of, like, these sort of mundane things that you find.
And, like, you build a whole community around those things and everyone's, like, in on the
joke and you can get in on it, too, and be, like, a member of a community and understand
these things.
It's so cool.
I really love it.
It's like, it's like, it's like this cliff here, yeah, the way, the way that I'm about to,
like, you know, do, like, a high jump, backflip, wall kick right here and, like,
glitch through the wall, like, this, like, this technique was in development for months
and it finally paid off, you know?
Like, it was experimented with.
The way that people, like, know that there's, like, a choke point coming up where, like,
oh, this is where I make a break, like, if I fuck this up, like, I lose five minutes off
my time here, I go and they do it and everyone's, like, yeah, I fucking did it.
I really like the community aspect.
I was, I was watching, I was watching a Pokemon speedrun.
I don't remember what Jen, but Worcester was speedrunning and there comes a point where,
because Worcester's making, he's making all these strategic decisions that are going to
save him time later.
And then, like, he's having a fight and, like, he gets, like, it gets low and then he gets
a crit and he wins, he wins the fight when he wasn't, and the crowd goes crazy and cheers
and Worcester is, like, visibly annoyed.
He's, like, really?
You cheer for that?
You cheer for that completely random thing that I had no control over and you don't even
notice, like, all these things that I put months of research into?
Like, he says it, too, and, like, the look on his face is, like, really pissed off.
And I really liked it.
Understandable, but not exactly the greatest crowd reader, but that's okay.
Not really.
Well, I, I, yeah, imagine, imagine my surprise to find out that this professional speedrunner
wasn't a people person, was actually kind of a big fucking nerd.
Well, well, not every speedrunner has to be a weirdo.
I, you know, whatever.
I, I, I, I'm playing up my page for speedruns.
I actually really like them as well, but, you know, I just, I like a bit of, I will say
the greatest thing that ever happened to speedrunning is the video Street 112.
Was it GoldenEye?
What?
Oh, well, there's this, there's this GoldenEye video of this guy going beyond God mode as he's
just, like, commentating on his, like, record-breaking GoldenEye run.
Yeah, it's a big meme, but I forget.
Yeah, but what year is it?
I don't know.
No, no, that's what it is.
Street 112.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I never even seen 113.
And I never fucking will.
But like, about time we got a fucking lucky break in this fucking game.
Look at my, look at my insane pace.
I am fucking clutch.
It's, he's, he's right in the fucking head.
He does some masterful moves, for sure.
Like, he has practiced this for months or possibly years.
I mean, GoldEye's a fucking old ass game.
Like, these guys become little gods of the worlds that they're in.
Like, it's like they, it's like they've lived their Groundhog Day a thousand million times
and have perfected it on a technical level.
It's just like Groundhog Day.
Except they're actually aging and getting older and wasting their one life on this planet.
That is, you know, I mean, it kind of comes back to the thing we said about video games
the other day about how, like, like, video games, like, if you are like a,
becoming a master speedrunner is like sort of finding a way to become a master of something
that's like not real life.
It like gives you something that you can be in control of and get really great at.
And I mean, you know, obviously like you can like, oh, maybe you can like build a business
and like, oh, I got to like economically strategize.
Like optimize my fucking tax, you know, minimize my tax and optimize my income.
But that's fucking boring.
And I want to be Super Mario jumping on Bowser and kicking my shit in as fast as possible.
You know, once again, like when you're playing it at that high level, like,
I'm sure it stops feeling like, you know, you're Kirby fucking bouncing around in Dream.
Right.
Like you start thinking inputs.
You're thinking inputs.
You're thinking inputs and you're thinking frames.
And you're thinking about, I mean, that's, that's how we felt during the,
that's how we felt during the Dark Souls speedrun.
I'm sure like, I practiced that so many times, I was just, you know,
like, I know, obviously I had no longer any fear of the enemies there.
It's just like, okay, this is a guy.
I know I need to like step back at this moment and do X, Y, Z, all that shit.
And the race that is an editing that's coming up, you know, in the future.
Let's keep that under wraps for now.
Race coming up soon, guys.
Race war.
Yes.
Okay.
Do we have anything more to say about sports?
Should we go to questions?
We haven't even talked about sports.
We've been talking about speedruns for the last 90 years.
We've done with the sports.
Sports is fucking awesome.
I'm going to talk about you.
I like to dunk the ball.
Okay, go on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Learning?
Okay, okay.
Here's my like my experience because it was not because like a few years ago,
I was pretty like anti-sports.
There was one of those fucking guys like, oh, it's so fucking boring.
Why would you watch sports?
What are you fucking?
Dude, go read a fucking book.
Am I right, bros?
You didn't even expand your mind.
Hey, where do you work out?
The library?
I was one of those guys.
Damn, damn.
But then I got into esports.
I realized that like the cool thing about sports isn't the sports.
It's the players and how they evolve and like their personal like meta narratives.
Sure, sure.
Cause like, okay, smash.
Smash is like a fun game.
I like to play it.
But the real cool thing about smash is how these fucking gods have like molded these
fucking specific play styles and how they have so much fucking history.
Fucking like 10 years of history playing tournaments together, fighting like fighting
for fucking domination.
Just fucking like what like two years ago, uh, Hungrybox played fucking Jigglypuff.
Like the character that's like not usually considered a top tier until then.
And he fucking won EVO.
He fucking won EVO with like an unconventional character against fucking, I think it was
like maybe something like top tier like Fox guy.
All these so called gods and none of them could beat me with items on.
Oh, true.
So true.
But yeah, it's just like the entire point of it is just to see these people grow and
expand and evolve and that like that is the cool thing about it.
And then they're like they're fucking like like villains.
They're like people who you want to see get beaten.
There are people who you want to like see like fail or like succeed.
And it's all it's all about them and the way they use the game to like tell like stories.
Kind of sports sports is like this weird chaotic crucible or it's like it's like this.
It's like a strange excuse to like put all these elements together and jiggle them around amidst
unpredictable circumstances amidst like the chaos of like a ball flying around and like
weather and like random chance and like all this stuff.
It's it's just this it's this chaotic crucible from which like narrative can like sometimes
be be be what's the word be like distilled out of like that that and also like numbers
like like sports is like it's just a big thing.
It's just a big like black box into which like players and rules are put in and what comes out
as an endless stream of data that can be endlessly analyzed by fucking nerds by sports nerds like
to find to find trends and like make predictions and like discuss things and you know kind of like
kind of like playing video games and speedrunning video games is a way to like exert mastery over
a thing that isn't real like like analyzing sports statistics and looking into and looking into
like the progression of like of like sports players and like and doing like predictions and stuff
like that's like that also is a way that people can like look at something that's not real like
it's not real life it's just sports but they can like analyze this data and be like I have come to
like a great understanding about something and it's important and it's important within like a
certain subset of people it's sub culturally important like to be able to like to know like
what it means that like so and so like has such and such odds of doing whatever you know what I'm
saying these are like yeah I hear these are like the points of interest I think that that are that
are what drives like the continuing interest in sports and why we haven't all just gotten
why everyone hasn't just gotten bored and being like I know how this ends they get the ball to
the end zone and we haven't had football games that like travel the entire distance of Nebraska
and have states is fucking in stone in soon soon we will though uh one one moment one my favorite
my favorite e-sports moment of all time that like like embodies that like like this like the game
itself doesn't fucking matter is one smash moment at the salty sweet where this where this uh player
this player now known as Bizarro Flame was supposed to fight another like he plays Ganondorf
in melee the greatest character of all time and he was supposed to do a ditto of another
Ganondorf guy but he like he like flicked and he didn't show up he was like sandsie yeah exactly
and so they had they got another I've got another guy to like fill in as like the Ganondorf guy and
he was he was like another he was like another you know well-known Ganondorf but but like the the
game itself isn't really the important part it's it's that it's like it's that guy exerting his
fucking dominance over the character it like in real life so it's like that that match starts off
like hey how do you like the company's like hey how do you feel like like like the guy didn't show up
and then he said oh he's a fraud he's a fucking fraud and then and then like like what do you think
about this match what do you think is going to happen and he just said easy money and then he did
like a he did like a real life super special like move to the guy in real life oh my god and then
the match starts out the match starts out like one two three go and then he just does like one of
Ganondorf's like hardest moves to pull off like five times in a row and fucking eviscerates this guy
in front of like thousands of people meanwhile just talking shit about how he's the greatest
fucking Ganondorf of all time and fucking like like blowing him the fuck out it's fucking great
and like the game itself yeah like like a guy who's better than another person like beat him
at a video game big deal but like like the things are like the politics outside of the game is what
makes it legendary yeah yeah I saw zero walking into like a tournament recently and like the guy
behind him was like you know he had a buck and he was throwing banana peels just as he walked up to
the stage because he plays diddy kong of course yeah it was uh it was pretty yeah I like all that
shit I like when they really like buy into their character diddy kong racing yeah it's just me
I'm winning
I was I was interested like in in in like you know what I was gonna I was gonna talk about the
race that's coming up but actually I don't want to spoil it so I'm not gonna get into it but yeah
plenty of time for that in the future but I would say that like a lot of what you just talked about
applies and of course you would agree to like you know normal sports as well and which is
clearly why a lot of people get into it yeah like in principle it's the same yeah that's right
like like guys like bill burr who I've just been listening to him a lot like he's a giant sports
fan he's always talking about like players and like their their role and like oh fucking so and so
got his first touchdown ever yes he's just so excited for this that's uh you know people get into
that I I don't follow closely enough for that I basically only follow the level of like is my team
doing okay yeah brady did it oh my god I mean there's so many there's so many characters there's so
many like secondary and tertiary and bit player characters in sports it's they're all characters
none of them are real they're all characters I guess you got to get into it like you probably pick
out like you know the top players and like the MVPs and like those are the main characters and then
as you get more into it like you start to like pick up on the nuances of what's going on with more
people this is like one of the not a great example because it's just like one of the most famous
guys in the game but like Tom Brady you know like fucking quarterback of the Patriots is like
he has now won like the last Super Bowl they was on the table for him to win more Super Bowl
champions than any quarterback in history and he did it and obviously that was very exciting for me
and I was just like I was totally pumped about that that was really dope so uh no it's that kind of
shit it's that kind of shit yeah you want to see you want to see your guys win yeah uh the best
thing coming out of sports is the little b-song fuck Kevin Durant which have any of you heard of this
maybe I don't know Kevin Durant is basically I have a very limited knowledge but from what I can
understand this song it's a diss track and Kevin Durant is just this basketball player and then
this fucking guy little b who's like fucking like three feet tall just just made a just just made a
song about how he's gonna fucking he's gonna fuck all the NBA girls in the mouth and like and like
destroy Kevin Kevin Durant in a fucking in a basketball match even though he's like two feet
tall and it's awesome I hope he does so I hope he has already done so
probably all right are we going to you guys have like a javelin teacher in school the
javelin teacher no all right I guess you don't know what a javelin is munchie it's like a spear
it's like a spear oh oh oh you throw it no not like fucking joust you don't throw it it's it's
part of the olympics you know you have like you have the discus you have the shot put you have
the javelin yeah okay those three things we got learned them at school I don't know how common
I was but um I wasn't never very good at the shot put because I had weak arms the discus it was
like frisbee and I was terrible with frisbees so I couldn't do that but the javelin I got I got
really far with one I thought now I have the power to kill people and this is great I never
followed up on it but I really enjoyed throwing javelins and from then on if I had a really long
pointed stick I would throw it and see if it's it landed in the ground and got stuck in the ground
because sometimes it did and that was awesome sick speaking of discus I was I was actually
researching discus the other day like like high level discus and I never really thought about this
but they are like buff they're like buff guys they're they're like bare mode discus yeah I mean
everyone's better at sports when you're just stronger in general yeah true and it was interesting
to see them just fucking like go ham fucking throwing because like the discus have to they
have to be like really heavy in order to fly straight so basically they're throwing like like
like rock or or metal frisbees basically interesting very cool all right guys are we
done with sports now I don't know I don't know we haven't even talked about bicycles or swimming
yeah we're at like the hour mark I like it would be appropriate to switch over to questions
if we hadn't just completely fucked up everything up to this point
well perhaps yeah true true no I'm just kidding I'm just kidding I'm having a great time I'm having
a great time here with all you guys my best friends yeah I fucking love ping pong even though I'm bad
at it that's a fun game I was pretty great tennis tennis is cool it's like I like it because it has
to do with your hands it's mainly just using your hands and I like using my hands don't mainly just
using you gotta run around you gotta run around you know you gotta you gotta make sure you hit the
ball with your thing that's that's the hard part the running around isn't the part in infinite
just infinite just taught me the tennis is basically like chess and war combined
tennis is like tennis is the ultimate test of a person's mental and physical okay the only thing
I would say about that is that like literally from all the sports manga I have read which is a million
you can make that case about every single sport ever invented and talk about the beauty of the game
and yeah my god these rules are the best rule like I'm reading um I'm reading robo laser beam
right now which is a uh a shonen shonen jump manga by the guy who did kuroke no basque uh kuroko
no basque um which is about golf this is a golf high octane sports manga and like it too like
because they all do goes on my god the game is fucking beautiful it's nothing is as powerful as
golf uh yeah it's like I I'm just assuming that everyone who thinks their sport is the best in
the world I'm with you well I know that that you know ishield 21 told me that american football
well they were actually correct because that is the greatest sport in the world and ishield 21
is the greatest manga in the world so they were correct it's a great manga I was actually thinking
about this the other day I was wondering whether there is like a chess uh anime or manga and people
said oh no well they they have shogi they have the japanese thing and I was like I fucking hate that
fucking weeb shit where is chess where's the ishield do they even know I don't think they
even play shogi in Japan I think it's just a joke that they if they're all in on them they're not
and they're not explaining it to the rest of us probably probably I want to see like I want to
see fucking little witch academia wizard chess tournament arc yeah I agree I agree bring out
Ronald Peasley and get him to fuck up some guys yo I've actually played bear
he's oh my god you can that good dots you did it he stole my fucking picnic
I hate you Japan why did you do it why did you make yoki bear steal my picnic baskets
is there a yogi bear anime there should be there should be it's called yogi bear
oh right i hate them I hate mammals
uh all right is this guys let's go to character I like these fucking babies that come out of
the pussy holes all warm they're not even laying eggs they're fucking mammals I hate them I hate
bears I hate yogi shogi bear
so I'm gonna pick up my bell it's me yogi bear I'm here to beat my children it's what I do I have
children I think well hey oh it's a me shogi bear I'm Japanese
I'm the Japanese off friend I do stuff with picnics baskets
what do you do with them shogi kill me
excellent uh it is wabbit season but okay
oh
all right it's time for questions all right we're going to the questions all right here we go
everybody sorry about the dickhead of the pcp didn't want us to talk about sports more sorry
sorry viewers yeah i'm so sorry it's it's all sorry about that dickhead of the pcp shogi bear
yeah that's true uh what the fuck did this go uh okay here's a filler question at joji
only likes picnics baskets with sushi in it
okay actually you know what uh here's a slightly better question uh at its judgment day
asks uh what is the oldest work of art that you are passionate about slash would recommend
the oldest work of art that's like good the stone in karta
yeah stone in stone i consider that a nice sculptory sculpt
that's pretty good uh i like wait wait wait the the the the the the the white horse on the hill
things what are they called uh the spanks they're like old uh gaelic uh Celtic
fucking english things they're like hills where they carved in white rock the shape of a horse and
it's like huge whoa uh that sounds like that thing google it guys uh i'm gonna go with uh the
works of Mozart in general i think i'm quite fond of them uh i like listening to him and i i don't
know maybe uh oh maybe the sistine chapel it's pretty cool i never like seen it though i just
think it's pretty cool cave paintings they're so old yeah yeah you can't get much older i'm trying
to be the oldest guy so whatever anyone says i'm gonna say i like something older because
that's like the hipsteriest uh i would say i really like the pyramids of geese because
specifically because they have that love of battleship fifty feet below it so fifty feet
below the pyramids of geese there is there is a love battleship that can only be powered in
times of need so so so for for instance if you need a battle in alien in alien race
trying to overthrow the united states government in the in the 1950s then you a south american
woman from peru can can mosey on over to the pyramid visa and then locate the love battleship
that that is 50 yards 50 miles across and three atoms thick you can you can look at that that
battleship and and you can power it and and and and when once inside using the power of love and
you're aligned chakras you can drive you can drive the aliens from your land due due to
instantly making them all have the black plague that that's my favorite part about it and that's
my favorite sculpture in the entire world that's good i'm gonna say that my favorite uh my oldest
favorite work of art is the actor william hickey this is uh he played he's like this really scary
old guy he's the scariest oldest guy in every movie ever he died in 1994 and he's still the oldest
that's how old and scary he is um he played he was like this old man with like a haunted cat in the
tales from the dark side movie the cat killed him and crawled out of his throat it was really gross
and cool cool he's like he's so he's he's got this like scary tongue he's like he's always got a
scary tongue that's his main feature as an actor he played uh pete and pete's grandfather
on the adventures of pete and pete everybody go look up go go go look up like arty versus the
bowling ball on pete and pete he's the guy like the bowling ball kicks arty's ass and like his
extended fight sequence of arty versus this evil bowling ball and it kicks arty's ass and at the
end of it arty is like laying on the ground the bowling ball is like pinning him it's defeated him
and and like the grandfather comes out and he's like foolish man brave but foolish
is this is this like mystery men uh bowling ball rules where it's you know got its own will
and it's flying around doing shit yeah it's like like they didn't have the special effects to make
it actually fly around and do shit so it's all the actor who plays arty just like pantomining fighting
the bowling ball and it's the best thing ever but yeah the guy who plays pete and pete's grandpa
is my favorite work of art so canonically this character could have a mental illness and actually
just think that he's fighting a bowling ball no arty is a real superhero that is a real evil
bowling ball okay its power was too great for this world uh okay here we go here's the next question
um this is a baffling question that i want to shame this person for asking uh it's uh at dragon ring
34 asks do you think english song are inherently worse than the original song oh that's worse that's
the question is this person playing that every song was not in english i think that's what they're
proposing uh is this like an anime question or something i want to shame you for asking anime
related questions person we don't have to shame let's shame them for asking what we can only infer
is an anime related question but there's no other explanation i have an answer i have an answer
at this man his his his uh accusation is wrong that the english song is worse than the non english
song because on the first gorillas album there's a song called latin simone and it's a song that
for some reason is in spanish and it's just this like spanish guy singing the song and you're like
what is this you skip it every time you listen to the album you skip that stupid fucking song
but then on the b sides album the e p that they released entitled g size right after their first
album there was an english version of that song that 2d sang and it was way better and listen to
it and you're like oh wow this is actually a really cool song i didn't know before because it was in
spanish and ain't nobody speaks that shit so that's why that guy was wrong about that thing he said
just now pretty well he he said do you think english song are inherently worse than the original
song a nice my answer was gorillas right yeah shut up dude that's a bad question okay um here's
okay here's an interesting question i actually like this one a lot okay at hero cactus asks well it's
not a question but videos you would show at a job interview so which of your videos would you use at
a job job uh i don't know mine would yeah depends on the job of course uh it would be the entirety
of the japanese juggalo arc yeah that's good that's good i i would show the ending of my rayman 3s uh
three part uh where i got all the all the people playing the the band but it's oh yeah one shot
and that yeah it's if it's like an editing job i'm saying look look at what i can do with all this
stupid shit i don't i don't know what i'd personally pick but for you gib i think you should definitely
go for uh like why clopping is okay you know sexuality of my little pony i definitely go for
that you know that yeah they've definitely got to know my my stance on that of course it's important
agree god i love clopping jesus christ rose agree i clopped to not even ponies i clopped but not as
in mastery i just i just go to do that's what clop it sounds like probably okay here's a strange
question um at auto jk asks what is biggest letdown in your gaming history what like um i think
you say why do we have fucking well that that's because i'll tell you i have a great action for
that question my my my greatest disappointment in my gaming career was on that digi bros episode
ben owns it at downwell um was the fact spoilers yeah was the fact that i got so close and i didn't
win um it was like it was like right down to the wire but i like just fucking barely didn't do it
and if i had done it it would have been the most legendary performance of all time but alas i came
so close so that was a big that was a big letdown to me and got so far but in the end it doesn't
even matter i was gonna say that because i got killed to me it's too soon dude it's too fucking
soon chester jeez poor guy i was like debating maybe it's too soon but i bet that demon munchie
will say look look i'm sorry the guy's dead but to stop saying the memes that we've been saying
for literally decades now somebody watch told me the next one died don't say it oh no uh yeah i want
is about my biggest gaming disappointment i of course had to bring up my loss in the pokemon
race which was absolutely devastating uh on a deep level everyone go watch that and the other one
the other one that that comes to mind is uh yeah long ago when ben and i were first playing uh mario
rpg legend of the seven stars oh god i know we've talked about this before i i think but like so
we had gone through the whole game i was watching ben play as i as i used to because we were very
little back then this i was like seven or eight or something and ben was playing and we were both we
just both i'd watched him play like the whole game and he was fighting smithy the final boss
and on our we was down to the wire only malo i believe was still alive and on like we there's
this move psychopath that just tells you how much hp the enemy has i don't remember exactly who was
alive but i remember that the last thing that happened was we right we used psychopath to see
how much hp smithy had and he had around like 34 or something and the average attack did like a hunt
like would have killed if we had just attacked we would have won and then he killed us all on his
next turn and we wept we wept like we babes in the crib it was brutal it was absolutely brutal
but even though like we could have just tried again like we were just such babies at video games
then we like didn't it was just so sad to like lose to a final boss because we'd been we'd been
trying like for a long time like we'd been trying like all day i think and we were like so we were
so close yeah yeah and it was and to our little pea brain minds it was just devastating and we
tried and did we did we get our hoots back up and like fight again immediately like later that day
no i think we tried i think we tried again another day yeah i think you're right guys i think i think
that was the end for for that time for that session i agree it was brutal yeah there have been
multiple times where i've like tried like tried really hard and failed so many times i've just
given up and said fuck this game i'll never play it again and then you know a week later i'll pick
it up yeah so but there's not like one specific one that's so notable that i can remember it
i'm just i just know that sometimes i get mad at video games yeah yeah that's all i know as well
that's the only thing i know about video games is that they make me mad sometimes but you know
what easy come easy go you never shine if you don't grow whatever uh all right well okay here's
just a question to for us to go out on at jam skmain something like that asks uh this isn't easy
this is a little fucking lab which pcp member do you think will die first it's bumpy it's obviously
bumpy oh yeah yeah it's definitely he's gonna kill himself there you go um any debate any debate
about this actually um yeah um i think he's uh i think he's coward and i challenge him to do it
and prove us all wrong oh i i i think i at what i don't remember which episode but i i i i i've
got i'm just kidding please god i'm just kidding i i did i think i also said that in a different
episode pen yeah in this in the suicide podcast i think we made bets on this and i believe i
bet that he would never commit suicide it was actually my bet you know you know here's the
thing i would i would say i would say he's not gonna do it i would say that about most people
but you know what then you say that and then they do it and then you look like you then you get
all over your face yeah he wants that you know i've been going around all this time saying
the lead singer of linkin park is never gonna kill himself no matter what else happens in life
and now i look like the damnedest buffoon there is you did in the end it didn't even matter yeah
all right i think the first pcp member who's gonna die uh uh sigh oh yeah by the way official
announcement from the pcp sigh is now in the group uh yeah but not too long yeah too bad he just
died he just died well you know it was a long and storied history well there you go folks
all right we're done thanks for listening everybody uh make sure you send us more
questions hashtag ask pcp follow us at tpcrasnators pledge to the god damn patreon five dollars to
get our bonus episodes best dogs uh uh what are we doing we got we're gonna record one today
so it'll be out soon if you're here oh shit we didn't even fucking announce that uh we had
announcements to make oh we're just we're fucking boring i was in that meeting it was just a bunch
of bullshit no one cares that's true all right here here's the only thing that matters right now
we're gonna do t-shirts people we're going red bubble i don't know the url because i haven't made
it yet we're making shirts people we're making it in the description just check the description
and it's gonna be there we haven't made yet but in the future it will have been made that's right
so just click on there download i i should have done that at the beginning it's supposed to be logo
that i cleaned up but i made it look good so we could edit a bit into the beginning okay well
whatever we'll we'll deal with that afterward okay for now uh go buy the shirts people they're real
i promise you they're real go buy them but it's not just shirts you got mugs you got you know all
the red red bubbles great because they just got a million things on merch find one that you like
with the procrastinators logo and there you go buy that shit and well we're gonna expand our content
with more things to buy with stuff we'll get back to the more details on that in the future and
comment on this video what you would like to see as a merch and we might just do or we probably won't
but you know do it anyway you fucking fag it sure why not all right there you go we're all done
thanks for watching everybody we'll see you next time bye bye i took them out i took out the
wife i took out the wife they're gone they're gone all right start the game start the game
oh