Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever. Today we're joined by Hippocrit.
Mage.
I was ill but I got better just in time for this podcast so you won't get to miss me.
I've become games so much I'm dreaming in code. I'm starting to think in if else statements
in real time.
How long has it been?
It's been months.
It's been over two months.
It's been all I ever needed.
Congratulations.
I remember that the world is a nihilistic nightmare and that you're not supposed to live
it sober.
I'm, I'm, well, you disgust me.
I don't know, what's, what's up with that?
Hey, hey, you didn't introduce me, you fuck.
Oh, oh shit.
Don't you know I have feelings?
In my weed induced stupor, I forgot that Ben Saint is also here.
Yeah, don't you forget it. Don't, don't wear, that's my name, don't wear it out.
Patreon.
There he is.
That's my name. Don't wear it out by not saying Ben ever again.
Here's a thought. Should you ever do drugs?
Yeah.
Like ever.
I think I want to say no.
I want to say no.
I want to say, all right, I was talking to a guy in my discord who was saying fuck alcohol,
I hate it, sucks.
And I was arguing the case for trying alcohol once in your life to at least know whether
you enjoy the feeling of being tipsy and getting a bit loose.
Well, why don't you try jumping off a cliff, go to try it once, you know, see how it goes.
Cause like, it's, it's undeniably does good things if you take a little bit of it every
so often in the right context, in the right circumstances.
Are you talking about like the health benefits of drinking wine or something?
No, I'm just, I'm just talking about like the social benefits and the relaxation that
it brings.
Yeah.
And you don't need to think so hard about everything and you're not anxious anymore.
I wish it had that effect on me.
The most important thing is that when you're at a party, you have something in your hand
and you don't look weird and you don't think you look weird because you have something
in your hand.
I mean, you didn't get my hand at every party I'm at.
It looked great.
You can drink anything.
I, you know, I always am walking around just carrying something to make me feel less weird,
but then half the time what I'm carrying is weird.
And then I get low down.
I'm literally at the shrug walking around.
But I am atlas.
You know what you do?
Here's a, here's a move.
Here's a move that I have never successfully tried out, but one day I intend to do it because
it sounds great and I see no downsides is you go to a party or to a bar or you go to
a bar where everybody's drinking like beer and you, you order a champagne flute.
You order a flute of champagne and then you go around and you toast everyone with your
flute of champagne and you, I mean, I can imagine that you would look like the coolest
guy in the world doing this.
When you say flutes, do you mean like the musical instrument?
Yeah, I was going to ask.
No, God damn it.
You fucking, you fucking Euro trash.
Don't you speak English?
No.
The flute is the musical instrument.
When you see people drinking champagne on New Year's Eve, that's a flute.
Is it a flute or a flume?
It's a flute.
I, I, I just imagine a glass, I, who, what, I'm walking around with a trombone full
of beer.
My brain is just colliding the ideas of a flute and like a glass, it's like, what,
just imagine a wine glass, what thinner.
I, I, I, I'm just thinking, no, it isn't, it's round, a regular wine glass, round.
This has got to be the most boring discussion we've ever had on the protest.
I know.
I guess of all time.
I mean, we've got a couple of strong contenders for that role, for that title.
Yeah, I guess so.
For that dubious distinction.
I had a great dream the other day.
It was a great dream.
I was never saying that, but I was thinking it.
Oh, hashtag kick mage 2018.
Yeah.
Listen, listen, everybody.
You didn't kick me with anything.
I'm just going to make the case that, you know what, let me, I'm just going to get
into a topic.
Here's a topic.
I'm throwing it out there.
Not one of these.
Here's the topic.
I've been saving this for like a month now.
We haven't gotten this fine.
I don't care.
But here's what it is.
In fact, that thing that you've been waiting for forever to come out, examples, Card Saga's
Wars was this game that took literally 15 years to come out.
Are we just talking about Kingdom Hearts 3 right now?
Kingdom Hearts 3, yes.
Here's the, my topic is, those things.
First problem waiting and wanting things to come out.
Just quick interruption.
I actually.
Having emotions and wanting and liking things.
Quick interruption quickly.
I Google champion flute and it's less thinner.
It's longer than, no, you're English.
It's fucking thinner than a wine glass.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Why do you doubt me?
Why do you undermine me, Mage?
Here's what the topic is.
The topic is that those things that you've been waiting to come out forever will be massively
disappointing 100% of the time and that it is never, ever worth the wait and that you're
fucking yourself over to even continue to care like for any amount of time.
Well Nate, you solved the discussion and now we can move on.
Did anyone, I mean, here's like a counter example.
Ridley getting it to smash was the opposite of that and that was a good thing.
That wasn't announced.
That was like said, no, it's not happening and so to cling to it is a meme and therefore
just fine.
Well, that's exactly what it is.
To counter a little bit here, Nate, what about an example that you've done a video
on?
Doom 2016 was in hell forever and then it came out and it fucking ruled and it was the best
thing of all time.
Wait, what was this?
I missed it.
Doom 2016.
That game was in.
Oh, Doom 2016.
Was in a miasma development hell and it almost became Call of Doom and that looked really
bad but then they fixed it and now it looks fantastic.
Okay, it's been two years here, man.
Were people actually waiting for that game specifically though?
Was that happen or was that like a game that they're like, oh God, okay, we've got the
Doom IP.
Okay, I guess now we'll make a new game.
It's been forever but we'll finally make something and then they make it.
The distinction of what you're talking about is when there is a promise and you're waiting
for it to be fulfilled, like I don't know who was waiting for Doom.
I guess maybe it was announced but I never heard about it until it was a real game.
So potentially Doom 2016.
I mean, I was never big in the FPS Doom scene.
I guess I'm still not but I played that game and loved it but yeah, I don't think that
game was announced.
Anyway, the Final Fantasy XV was announced as a different game 10 years ago and transformed
and changed and all these new trailers came out and stuff and that comes out and it was
some people like it.
I have many criticisms of it.
Kingdom Hearts 3, still not out.
I can already tell 100%.
It's not going to be as good as everyone wants it to be in all these millions of ways.
Maybe it'll be good in other ways.
You've got to live your life by the coda.
High hopes, low expectations, always.
Expect the worst.
Never expect it to be good.
Never go into anything like, cause Yatsy Kroshaw, Yatsy Kroshaw broke this down perfectly
one time.
He said, if you go into something with high expectations, there's two possibilities.
They'll be met and you'll be happy or they won't be and you'll be upset.
If you go into everything with low expectations, the two possibilities are that it will suck
and you'll be like, well, I expected this, or it will be great and you'll be like, wow,
what a pleasant surprise.
No matter what, if you go in with low expectations, the odds are always in your emotional favor,
so just never expect anything to be good.
But you're just miserable and you're not as happy as you would be otherwise.
How is it miserable?
Why would you be happy cleaning up on something that ultimately fails?
You're operating under a cynical lens 100% of the time.
I don't consider it cynical to approach life that way.
I gotta go with Digi on this one.
It's like fucking Buddhism.
You gotta release your attachment.
Getting hype for things is just a form of attachment to material things.
And not even this material thing, just attachment to an idea.
An idea that may fail to come to pass and will cause you pain.
Relinquishing your attachment to these things will save you pain.
The idea is not to force yourself to artificially expect things to be worse than you think they are.
It's to strive to have that viewpoint, because I don't think of it like that,
but I do operate on that low expectations sort of thing.
I don't think anything's good until I see a lot of praise by a lot of people that I respect.
I don't see any reason, and I don't like it.
I see no reason to expect anything to be good.
There's nothing that would convince me other than...
Digi people are so depressing.
I don't get how you find this depressing.
Because being hype is fun as fuck.
No, it's not.
It's immoral to be hype.
Super fun.
Being excited for something is fun, and when you're let down, your excitement becomes righteous for you.
Okay, guys, guys, guys.
Tom is like, it's about the journey, not the destination sort of guy.
Digi is more about the destination, not the journey.
You're not taking a journey by waiting for something to come out.
No, no, no, no, Digi.
She's right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I kind of get what you're talking about.
I remember, okay, I guess I have mixed feelings,
I'm mostly on Digi's side.
I wasted two years of my life being hype for Spore to come out,
and I admit that following Spore and waiting for its development was a journey,
but it was a journey from happiness to sadness.
It was a purely masturbatory exercise.
I like being a sidekick.
None of us here can talk about it.
It felt like something was happening, but it was nothing.
It was wasted time, and it was dumb.
I'm just, I just, I don't get why being like naturally cynical.
I don't go out of my way to push down happy thoughts,
and if I am hype for something, I don't like destroy that.
I just naturally through having a cynical lens of things.
Why would you be hype in the first place?
That's the mistake.
Because it's fun.
It's fun to be hype.
I'm very sensible when I'm hype.
Like, I was hype for Dark Souls 3 because I knew Miyazaki was coming back,
and I had a pretty good idea that that was...
That was the only game I've ever been really hype for is Dark Souls 3.
I legit let myself get hype because I was very confident it would be good,
but that's because there were like gameplay trailers where like you can see people play the game,
and I could tell, okay, all the things I hated about Dark Souls 2 are rectified,
and I could tell that just by looking at it for a second, you know?
I'm hype for a bunch of things right now, and I'm not ashamed.
I'm excited.
Tom, you don't have to be ashamed.
You need to replace, you gotta replace the excitement that you get from being hype
with the power that you can draw from looking down on people who get hype about things.
No.
That's why my eyes are as evidenced by this conversation.
You all discussed me.
Look, me-hype isn't a moral action that no one should do,
but we're human, and we sin, and we're flawed.
So like, for example, I would say that I'm somewhat hype about the trigger show Pro-Mare.
That is, it's like the next, you know, girl-logging, kill-a-kill-a-pro-mare.
Let me get an argument in Mayushi.
Okay, I should be the most hype about that show out of anything, right?
Because kill-a-kill and girl-logging are both in my top ten.
Mayushi is my favorite director.
But, first of all, the show looks like it's gonna be in CG.
I'm not the biggest fan of CG.
The details are where you hit questions.
You know, and then I've also known that trigger doesn't always make the best show I've ever seen.
You know, wasn't into Darling and the Franks really.
So, I look at the show and I-
Unpopular opinion.
I didn't like that one.
I didn't like Luluko.
I thought Luluko was really dumb and a waste of my time.
I said it.
It was pretty short, though.
So, what was the waste of much time?
I think Pro-Mare, like on the one, I have high hopes for it.
I hope it's great.
But why would I expect it to be great?
Because that's just setting myself up for potential disappointment.
If it turns out to be great, I'll be like, fuck yeah.
And then I can be hype about it for the rest of my life once it's great.
You know, like, why would I want to be hype in the year and a half leading up to it
when I can be hype for the next 70 years afterwards that I live with the show existing?
Because my life is so empty of meaning and hope and dreams and good things going on
that I have to vicariously live through the excitement of other things that aren't out yet.
People want something to say.
Okay, guys.
People.
Oh.
Well, I think the thing that I'm having, like,
I'm not feeling the trying to think of the way to say it.
I feel this way, but I can't control it.
Like, I just am the sort of person who is more cynical
and expects things to be not that interesting or not that good.
And I see things like that.
I don't think of it as like a thing you can switch off or change.
Tisk, tisk, tisk.
You can't switch it off.
You got to burn it out of yourself.
You got to sear it out with a red high.
What I'm saying is that when Tom is saying, like, how can you live like that?
I'm like, well, how can you live like that?
How do I do this?
Okay, guys.
Let me, let me, let me say how I deal with this.
Then shut up, please.
I'm going to write this down and I'm going to publish a book about it.
And I'm not going to say it out loud ever because it's not possible.
Okay.
But, okay.
So this is how I deal.
And I don't expect anyone else to be able to deal with stuff like this the way I do.
And so this is how I do it.
So I hear about a thing.
And I was like, oh, neat.
I kind of like the idea of this thing.
And then I completely forget about it until it actually comes out.
And when it comes out, I go like, oh, neat.
That's, that's fun.
That's, that's exactly what I'm describing as like the perfect way to be.
I just, because like, what's the point of waiting one and a half years and like expecting
and just being on edge.
It, it, it's not doesn't frustrate me.
It just, it's like, it makes me anxious.
It's just like, I wanted to come out and wanted to come out and just taking the time out of
my day thinking about it.
And like, that's how you live.
But I bet if like your favorite thing was getting a sequel, you would share like, I would
I'm like, I like Dragon Age and I'm kind of worried about it because of what EA's been
up to and why, why are you on stuff?
But I don't spend time thinking about it or stressing over it.
And there's another game, an indie game that's going to come out in like two or three years
called Temp Temps or something like that.
It's going to like a Pokemon MMO sort of, but it's not Pokemon.
And I was pretty excited to see about that.
Yeah.
Like, I don't remember what exactly they predicted the launch or whatever.
It was like, oh, that looks neat.
I really want to play it right now.
Best forget about it for the next two or three years.
It's an unfortunate reality that we've gone into a time in the world where we're, it's
now very common to like be introduced to something two or three years before it will come out.
And that's not even that long.
I got it.
I want to make the argument.
That's a fucking lifetime.
That is a lifetime.
I really look down on people who get hype about shit because of the fact that I think it
is ignorant consumer practice.
We live in a world where most of the time, the shit that they post about something before
it comes out is a fucking lie.
Like either it's not going to be that way, even if it's not necessarily a lie, it just
probably won't turn out that way.
And like after Dark Souls 2, like there's no, like that game literally looks completely
different from the final product or like Watch Dogs or any of these games that had like
this crazy marketing push and the game comes out and is nothing like that.
It's like, if you get hype for a game before it's out, before there's reviews telling you,
you know, that you trust telling you that it's good, like you are just that.
You know what people should keep in mind for this?
I've written down the thing.
The fact that like, okay, the day that Steve Jobs did the demo for the original iPhone when
it was first announced and he showed off so many features that could go all in one.
Like it could do all this stuff at the same time.
He could call people.
He could use these apps, et cetera, et cetera.
Behind the scenes, like this was basically a lie that people just don't care about because
what was actually going on was behind the scenes, they had slapped together this like hodgepodge
piece of shit that technically was able to do just the exact features that were demonstrated.
But if he had done like anything out of sequence, the whole phone like would have exploded
and broke and things would have gone to shit.
Like it happened to work correctly in this one small way that they created the demo for,
but like was this a functional piece that was actually ready to be shipped?
No.
And in a way, there is a deception there, which is similar to how like, for example,
like all these game trailers that are made and all this stuff is made like on super high-rig
PCs and shit that can run these kind of games at way better resolution,
have all kinds of like better graphics and they're eventually going to ship the thing with.
So you've got to know every time there's something like this, you're being lied to at least a little bit.
Hippo, you said you wrote something down?
Yeah, I wrote down my stance.
I now understand what it is until I have experienced a thing.
It doesn't exist and there's no reason to have an opinion on it.
That's the best way to be.
Also, I'm mostly hype about the things that I am going to make or I'm trying to make
because they're in my brain and I kind of skate there.
Yeah.
So I'm hype about whatever I'm doing.
But other things that I don't know the entire backstory of,
I can only really feel anything about it once I have or as I am experiencing it.
The world should work like this.
People, and I wish it worked like this 100% of the time all the time.
A person who's making something is obsessed about it, is deep into it,
and doesn't talk about it to anyone.
They keep it to themselves.
They then release it and instantly completely forget about it
because it just exists as an isolated art piece that can never be touched or edited.
Then they move on to something else and they do it again.
And everyone, they only know about this thing once it's out
and then can actually see what was produced.
Judge it and then we work on it.
Literally unworkable, but okay.
I normally don't know.
Why is that unworkable?
Because we live in a capitalist society where you have to make money,
so the hype cycle is necessary from a business standpoint.
Don't say that.
Don't sound so disappointed, Tom.
You fucking call me this.
I'm not, because I like the hype cycle.
I'm hype for Devil May Cry 5.
I'm hype for the Doom Eternal.
I'm hype for fucking something else.
Metroid Prime 3.
Hey, did you see that?
Let me tell you, Tom.
You're making me realize, well not realize, I was already thinking about it,
but my big problem with what I call hype beasts
and specifically games that get that super hype culture around them,
not just games, I guess, anything,
but what I hate about the hype beast culture is that
so much energy and excitement gets put into something that's not out yet
and it makes it so nobody goes back.
People get so excited about what's coming next
and that's all they fixate on.
It's like, oh man, I can't wait for this game.
I'm saving up for this game.
You're already mentally making space for this game in your life
and it's like, dude, take that energy and just go play an old game.
That's great that you haven't played yet.
You can hype about that.
You can do both.
It's funny you mentioned that because I get the same,
I mean, I'm hype for all these new games
but at the same time, I'm working on a 16-bit retro style game right now
so I've just been blasting, I don't know if you've been hearing it from my room,
but like Mega Drive music like the entire time,
just to keep me in the mindset of it
and one of the tracks came on for TMNT Hyperstone Heights
and I'm like, whoa, this soundtrack is fucking legit
and then I got hype to play that game
and I want to go on eBand, I want to buy it, I want to play it
because it sounds cool.
I've always experienced-
Just get hype for everything.
Just be hype for everything that's cool.
I've always experienced from my friends
but nothing's cool.
Oh my god.
God damn.
I can't even remember the last time I was hype.
That's why you're miserable then.
Here's how I feel.
Like, I see a thing, I see a cool game
and I think, boy, I wish that could make me feel something.
There's some deeper issues there, unfortunately.
I've always been around people who like,
they are just constantly looking forward to the next one
and like, my brother Victor,
he plays dozens and dozens of games.
God damn.
Not at all.
When people complain about modern games-
What's in a century something interesting comes around?
I blame stagnation entirely on this hype culture
because it's always people getting hype about a new thing
and then it comes out and they all play it
and whether it ultimately turns out to be good or disappointing
will be sussed out in the aftermath
but the only reason that game gets played by so many people
is that it was hyped, is that the hype cycle existed
and so there's so many times where people will be like,
oh, modern games, they're so shitty
because every new big game that comes out sucks
and it's like, well, stop making big games,
stop making a big deal about a new game,
just go play something else that is revealed well.
It reminds me of a thing I wanted to,
because it's related to hype culture.
I don't particularly mind people getting hype,
people getting happy about things,
because it's not going to bother me, you know?
But what bothers me, though, a little bit
is pre-order culture, which is kind of like tied with...
I consider that a part of hype culture.
I've never pre-ordered a game and I never will.
Same here.
God damn it.
I was going to say, oh yeah, I'm big on...
Alright, so I'm like a super late adopter of anything.
I really believe in letting other people do the work for me.
That's why you'll be happy someday, Ben.
You're just a late adopter of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't get hype for things that are coming out.
Ben's a late adopter of food?
He prefers to let other people try it first
and then reach into the garbage to try what they've already tested.
Cuts, let me fucking get this out.
I don't get hype for shit.
I'll be like, okay, whatever.
I'll let it come out, I'll let it be out for a year,
and I'll wait, and if people...
I only try anything if I hear it recommended by multiple people.
This is kind of my sort of...
The pattern I've fallen into is that I basically don't check out anything
unless multiple unrelated sources have told me,
like, this is cool, you should check it out.
You're the late majority slash laggard of the bell curve.
I am a laggard, yes.
I am a big laggard.
But at least I'm not a blaggard.
Did anyone fucking get that joke?
Yes, because I know that word.
You guys know that word?
Okay, cool.
What does it mean?
Viewers, if you don't know that word, fuck you.
How dare you?
Laggard.
You probably say viewer...
Hey, I'm calling you out.
You probably...
You probably say blackguard, you bitch.
That's a cool word, too, but...
Yeah, but it's wrong.
Yeah, alright.
All those times you played a Dungeons & Dragons
and you were a paladin and your DM was like,
I'm gonna be real clever and trick you into falling,
you were a blackguard, nope, you were wrong the whole time.
I always play an angel.
You were, in fact, a blaggard.
Get fucked.
Well, I mean, this topic is essentially,
I sure hate how reality is,
wish I could do anything about it,
you know, that's a shame.
I mean, yeah, that was my next point.
Yeah, what's the deal with reality, anyway?
My next point was like the hype cycle,
like Tom was saying, that's like capitalism,
you have to do it, and I'm like, well,
I don't like it then, I don't like the system.
Break the system.
If there's no way to change and there's nothing better,
I'm gonna make video games in the woods
and release them in the woods,
and you can only find them by digging under the trees
to find little cartridges.
Ironically, if you did that and talked about it,
it would generate some hype.
I would only do it after it has fallen out of relevancy,
so they can't pre-order it.
Pre-order your ditch and then you have to go find it.
Um, yeah, I don't know, whatever.
We've talked about this enough.
In closing, Cyberpunk 2077 looks fucking lit
and I can't wait to see more of it.
Get fucked.
I haven't looked into it.
I think it's also that I'm very easily
sated by things I've already done.
Like, I replay a lot of games,
I rewatch a lot of things,
you know, I've rewatched like most of John Grumps
and a lot of Dan Grumps, like multiple times over,
and all that.
I find a thing that I like and I stay with it
and I don't really feel the need to see anything new.
That brings me to a question for everybody.
How easy is it for you to get recommendations?
Because for me, the reason that I go out of my way
to watch every single anime
is that I've never known anybody
with close enough taste of mine to rely on them.
And that kind of goes for all mediums.
I think most people have a critic who they're like,
oh, this guy has the same taste as me,
so whatever he gives a positive score, I'll check out.
Or they more broadly can just go to Metacritic
and whatever is broadly considered good,
they end up liking.
In my case, it's so unreliable
because so often the thing I like
will be talked about by nobody
or it'll be totally underrated,
and then the thing that everybody loves I watch
is fucking terrible.
I've just been like, fuck it, I can't rely on anyone,
I'm just going to consume absolutely everything.
I used to be entirely Metacritic and stuff-driven.
I used to be like, oh, this game got a good review
because I had GamePro and EGM
and all those mags back in the day,
and that's how I made my purchasing decisions.
But there were a couple of times when I've played games,
like the last five or so years,
that were critically either panned
or just okay that I thought were fantastic.
So my new thing is just like,
it just looks cool, I'm going to give it a shot.
I don't care if it has like a one, maybe I'll like it
because they're not me and they don't know
what I would enjoy, they just know what they enjoy
and fuck them, I'm better.
When it comes to getting recommendations,
and I feel like a lot of people
probably feel the same way,
it's incredibly hard for me to like,
even you people,
even anyone in my life,
it's incredibly hard for me to take a recommendation seriously.
Like for example,
I've been doing streams for a while
and there's been people in there saying like,
Nate, watch this movie Gattica
from 1997, this guy Chakuto
and a bunch of other people
were meming me to watch Gattica
and they were trying in little ways to tell me
why I would like it so much.
It's very utilitarian, it's very like,
try real hard and overcome the odds
and I finally gave it a watch.
Battlestar Gattica.
Gattica, yeah, that's it.
Yeah, classic.
It was good and I did enjoy it,
but it took literally months
of these people meming me over and over
to watch it before I would give in.
Whereas, if I just go,
this is what I do, this is how I actually get recommendations.
I go to people who I don't know who they are
so I don't know if I should
or should not trust them, which is just 4chan.
I just go to 4chan,
look to see what anybody likes
and I'm like, that's the thing.
This person, they've got no stake in this,
I'll go watch the thing they recommended
because they liked it.
The best thing, I'll tell you, the best board on 4chan
for recommending things is Mew
and it's because not only do they have
tons of charts for every conceivable genre,
so if you like a specific genre you can use that,
but it's pretty normal
on there to post chart threads
where people will have literally their top 100 albums
and that's such a huge sample size
that if I find someone
who's got 20 of the same albums I like,
I can be like, okay,
I'll listen to some of the shit in this guy's top 10
and see if I'll like it
and even then it's rare that I even find anything
but I don't know,
it seems like I've just got
to traverse this insane amount
of crap to find anything
that I'm going to like
but I consider myself really good
at recommending stuff to people.
I don't recommend things often, but if I see something
I think one of you guys will like,
I'm usually pretty confident about it
and I usually get positive feedback
on it, so I hope I've been
a good recommender.
Music seems like a format
where you'll like,
because it's like brief, you can consume a lot
so I can see why you do a lot.
It's a lot easier to just burn through,
and you can tell pretty quickly
you can listen to the first song on an album
and usually get a good sense
of if this is your vibe,
you know?
I feel the same way about anime though,
I can watch like three minutes
of how contentious.
For me, it's a little hard
if someone comes up to me and they're like,
hey, it seems like you're singing
and it depends on my mood
and how I'm feeling that day,
if I feel like watching anime,
I might give it a watch, but that's a very big might,
but most of the time
the more people recommend something to me,
the less inclined I am to watch it,
so for instance a lot of people,
I haven't watched Evangelion
and people always greet me
like, yes, whenever I say that,
it's like, you haven't seen that.
I don't really think you would like Ava.
That would not strike me as your taste.
I recommend you Angels of Death.
I know you'll like that show.
I don't know about Ava.
Yeah, I don't like Mecha's
and it's an old anime,
which, I mean, all the enemies can be good,
but first of all, Ava's not old
and second of all, it's not really
that mecha-driven.
You know what they say?
Mecha-driven anime of my anime is my friend.
Well, it's just like
the mecha genre
is probably the most sorely
misunderstood genre in anime
because people always say like,
oh, I don't care about mecha
and it's like mecha shows are always about characters.
They're always about...
they're just like any other show.
They're just a show where,
instead of superpowers, we have robots.
That's the only difference.
That's the thing to like...
I know, you said this before
and I did take note,
but the thing is for me,
there's a lot of anime
out there and
why should I force myself to watch
an anime in a setting
that I don't particularly like?
I don't really like sci-fi or robots.
I really think that with anime,
the fetish is the point,
as I've said in my
the purpose of anime video.
And I really would say this about all art
is all basically saying the same shit.
The messages are all pretty
similar at the core of it.
It's either about understanding yourself
or about understanding how you fit into society.
That's a good summary of
my point in my last
We Agua, why manga is better than anime.
Where I just said, look, I just like anime.
That's why I watch it.
I could just read a book about the same shit.
I just like the things that are generally going on here.
Yeah, and that's the thing.
All art
is basically trying to get to the same couple of
points. So the question is
what is it that resonates with you
specifically?
Let's say that there's a hero's journey,
for instance. There's like 10 million things
that are the hero's journey.
But if you
don't feel like you connect
with the broad bell
curve idea of the hero,
then you need a different hero
to take that journey.
So that's why
there's always people who are like...
They try to make the same show
except the protagonist is a girl.
Or the same show except it's a black guy.
Just because it might be easier
for certain people to connect with
even though it's basically the same story.
There's a value to that.
So I think that with anime
it's for autistic people.
If you can't
relate to live action stuff,
then you need something where the characters
are openly expressive
and have big Mimi
hype shit because you're dumb.
So that's why we all...
You can't just like the aesthetic of anime
without being literally autistic.
Why is that not allowed?
Why?
Because have you ever met someone
who liked anime and wasn't autistic?
Have you looked in the mirror, Nate?
My parents' generation don't even understand
what cartoons are
or that you can convey emotion in animation.
But I do get... What am I going to do?
I'm going to watch Seinfeld and pretend
that that gives me all the stuff that...
Like you said, I'm sure there's a live action
movie with a hero's journey in it
that means... I don't know
with themes of overpopulation exactly the same
as like Gurren Lagan. Why can't I
just like the way
Gurren Lagan tells that story
without being literally autistic
because I'm not looking at
actual live actors, whatever.
What's with this obsession
with autism all the time, dude? I don't get it.
What's going on here? You're always bringing it up.
Please explain to me why everything's
about autism. Am I missing something here?
It would take too long. I don't want to go through that again.
Did you watch the Only Yesterday podcast?
Uh, no, but I...
Go watch that. I go on and on
and on about it in that.
But anyway,
I'm sorry.
Point just being that it's all about
the fetishistic elements.
There's no reason to watch one anime
over another other than
that this one resonates with you
as opposed to that one.
There's no real... I don't think it's
defensible to say like, oh
you have to watch this show because
it's deep. It's like, no.
All anime is about the same shit. Ava
is about the same goddamn shit as anything else.
It's an extremely well
told story and that makes it
a great show. I fucking love it.
But if someone's like, oh, I
don't care for this aesthetic, I'd be like,
well then go watch something with
an aesthetic you do care for.
Which is why Mage needs to watch Angels of Death
because it is literally
mage the show.
It has a cute spooky boy with the
scythe and they like it already.
Excellent.
Getting back
to the whole recommendation
thing, I've thought about it
and it's always been really
difficult for people to recommend me things
and I don't think
anyone can. When it comes to like
gaming at YouTube
reviews of things
there's no like gaming
reviewer that I actually go to for advice
or like a recommendation.
I usually just watch them for entertainment
or just like
an exhaustive look at something.
Mathematosis comes the closest
but that's because what he talks about is basically
everything. The only actual reviewer
who's like decent
the only actual reviewer I could actually watch
not for the jokes is basically
Super Bunny Hop because everyone else
will put it like, for example like a
Kadikaris or even a ProJarad. They put
too many terrible jokes in their
content to actually be enjoyable
whereas Super Bunny Hop is like kind of light hearted
but really it's just like a real journalist
who will do the due diligence and I can respect.
I was going to say that
because it's so difficult
for people to recommend me things and there's nobody
out there that really understands
exactly my thing, the way that
I do, that's the reason I
have this whole thing of wanting
to analyze the games that I like
so that I understand
what about them is the good part
and so I can understand that in new
games if I see them. I'm pretty confident
that I could recommend you things
it's just that I feel like you've played
anything I would recommend you
and I don't know if that's because
there's not enough games you would like or if
it's because I don't know enough games
but like I feel confident
I could find you shit you'd enjoy
well maybe. Have you ever played
Shantelies?
I think you'd probably enjoy that.
That's the one with the
I did cool girl games on it
yeah, way back
the biggest failure of my entire channel
I liked the look of that, that was kind of cute looking
yeah I think you'd enjoy that game
it's pretty short too so
if you felt like playing a random steam game
I don't think it would be like your favorite or anything
but I think
well we need a new topic here
I'm sorry I wasn't
paying attention I've been swiping
Tinder sluts
that's what I'm up to bitches
yeah
just a cavalcade
just a cavalcade of fucking
sluts
I wonder how that's going Ben
oh it's just
who's this we got Angela
sounds like a slut
yeah
she's got a nose ring
what? yeah we're in
we're in boys
this is going down
Angela I would like to apologize
on behalf of the procrastinators podcast
for the words we've said against you
so you know
that's what I'm up to
locking them down left and right
back on the games though
I've been
oh god damn it
not more games
last week I was ill like I said
and during my ill time
I found a game on 3DS
and I've been playing it
and it's like it's really mediocre
like it doesn't stand out too much
it has some interesting ideas and stuff
that's what I want to hear about mage on my podcast
tell me about these mediocre games
the thing is like I've been
having so much fun with it
despite like it's like I kind of
wanted to recommend it to someone
but then I thought like
well it doesn't really stand out too much
from other like JRPGs
what is it what game is it
it has a long title one of my gripes with it
seventh dragon 3
code
something something it's like a three letter word code
god what is this is this the next kingdom hearts
spin off kingdom hearts
seventh dragon 3
that's less ridiculous than you'd think
it has a really neat system of like
all the playable characters that you can play
can actually choose the appearance
of the name even voice
I really like that you can choose their voices
and class as well
and you can change those at any time
so
I do feel sometimes
that I enjoy
complete shit
and I don't know why
that's how I feel about music
like sometimes there'll be like
my love of nightcore is well documented
oh I actually made a video about that
the puzzle
the puzzle pirates video is a video about a game
that is kind of terrible but I just
enjoy it so much for no reason
then I think that nightcore
much like Eurobeat
is inherently good
like I don't really
I don't really think you can make
I don't think you can make a nightcore
or Eurobeat song that is not enjoyable
are you sure
you guys are talking about the same kind of nightcore
you could definitely pick the wrong song
I haven't listened to that much nightcore
but like it's one of those things
where like just inherently the style of it
is there all the same song basically
are we I mean technically
all you have to do is to find a nightcore
as speeding up a song and raising the pitch
technically all nightcore is
is just a song sped up
do that and technically it's nightcore
what happens if you speed up a nightcore song
that's a good question
what a nightcore song always is though
is some kind of Japanese dance song
sped up and pitch shifted up
or
come clean by Hilary Duff
recommendation
obviously there's a lot of meme nightcore out there
that doesn't fall into the category of
what I'm talking about but like
the vast majority of nightcore
is just sped up Japanese dance songs
I can't agree that
I want to relate a story
because like of the beats
like being fast
and stuff and it's fun
I wouldn't say
I wouldn't go as far as to say all nightcore
is inherently good
I want to relate a story
from my real life from my real internet life
so me and Munchie
were commentating on the soul cup
on the twitch.tv
slash rowdy frickers cop killers
the stakes were high
I won't go into what that was all about
but it was a Pokemon tournament with incredibly high narrative
stakes and
I've developed a habit
of when people use
weather conditions I play nightcore songs
and when people use rain
when people use rain dance and summon the rain
in a Pokemon tournament
I always put on
come clean by Hilary Duff
because the lyrics of that song are about rain
and it's really
let the rain fall down and break my dreams
let it wash away
my sanity, yes
and it's great
low-fi hip-hop also is a genre
that's just inherently good
and that's when I have very little exposure to it
granted all of you
have watched some YouTube analysis
all of these genres I'm talking about
none of them are ever great
except for
running in the 90s is the only great Eurobeat song
that's a great song
but all of these genres
every song is basically the same
and
none of them are memorable
you just kind of listen to it
and you can leave it on for hours
and it just creates a feeling
that you can perpetuate all day
and that's why low-fi hip-hop is always in a stream
because it's just like a 24 hour stream
of fucking
this vibe
and you'll never pay attention to it
maybe you'll catch an Alan Watts quote here
in there
it's like going into
a restaurant where there's just a guy
doodling on the piano
the room of vibe
of some sort of jazziness
oh no he's doodling on the piano
doodling
incidentally
I know that probably this is how a lot of people
feel about Future Funk
but I would say that Future Funk is boring
and shitty
I got some Future Spunk for ya
how about that
I like the electricity
I should listen more to that
save that
Future Spunk for the Tinder Sluts
let's talk some more about Tinder Sluts guys
okay
did she respond yet
that whore
she did actually
but talking about a real conversation
is a little uncomfortable for me
so let's change the topic on second thought
I have nothing but respect for all women
especially Angela
but moving on
I uh
what
responding to a man on Tinder
Jesus Christ Angela
what the fuck
every time a girl responds to me I just roll
I was like oh god
desperate much
I would have topics but I'm still
like trying to pull my mind back
from the august void
of making a video every day
yeah hey that was something
I mean you've done it before
I did Miyama but better and for free
you know you're not wrong
but I mean uh
people don't like give you credit
I guess just cause you didn't talk about but you did a Miyama
for long before I did
and for what it's worth
you just didn't give it a catchy name
that was your problem
and you did this one either
back in October 2014
the one from last time was like
way worse
cause like by the end
like the whole last week of it was like
horse shit like just vlogs
and like bad memes and
and even before then most of the videos were just like
not that amazing like
with this month it was I was holding myself
to a higher standard I wanted every video to at
minimum be something that you would go back
and watch again conceivably
like not just stuff that was there to
just fill a day
though there were a couple of vlogs that were kind of like that
in our town but um
it was a fucking waking nightmare it was hell
and I regretted it
except that it worked so
I was curious about that how much prep work did you put in
like cause obviously some big videos
zero did it all during that month
literally I didn't have
a plan to do this until like 7pm
the night before
like I just I was sitting there
trying to figure out like what am I gonna do
to resurrect my channel
I have no idea and then I was like
I guess if I did a video every day for a month
that would make something happen
so I just went into my discord and I said
who wants to bet against me that I can't do a video every day
all month and uh
and then I did it
no one has ever regretted to my knowledge
this whole like do a
video per month thing
unless they gave up and failed
or if they uh
I mean you'll feel tired and exhausted
but no one has ever regretted doing it
if they want their channel to grow
like a fucking million view video
that you made in there
I think I could have gotten away with doing a video
every other day
and spent a little bit more time on each video
and therefore been able to make stuff that was like
that had more growth potential
even that
people like
even just like one gap
of a day makes
so much of a difference in like the viewing habits
of people when they're expecting a digital
video every day
and people like PewDiePie
they do it every single day
so we know this is a winning formula
that's what I would love to do
someday if I could eventually get to that point
generate that much content and stuff
though obviously the kind of content I ideally want to make
is a little more high effort
but still
I'm a big fan of this kind of shotgun approach
of like forcing yourself to make content
to a timeline
like you said you would not have made
this fucking your million view video
by the way it was a great video that I was totally
on board with and absolutely loved
I think that the thing about it is that
at some point
I was like waking up at like 3pm
for most of the month
and I'd set myself
like the stipulation
no one really made me do this
but I just kind of took it for granted
that I had to get them out by midnight
so it was usually like wake up at 3pm
and then spend the next 7 hours
in a cold sweat
trying to figure out
what the hell am I going to do by midnight
fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck
and then there's a few times
I'd have to like throw out the thing
and in the meantime
in order to keep my soul in any way active
like usually what would happen is
I would get the video done
right around midnight
post it and then afterwards
instead of working on the next day's video
I would do anything else
creative with my time
make some songs or like do anything else
because like
it was just so exhausting to be thinking about the videos
all the time but then that meant every day
it was like a crunch
it was always like
I don't really get started until like 8pm
and then it's just like a mad dash till midnight
damn son
but I
explained this to Tom on a
livestream last night that I think
what it
the approach that I took to it that made it work
I would advise this to anybody who's trying to like
make content on a timetable
or make content fast is
that
the first thing you should think about is
what can I do
in this time frame
not what do I have ideas for
but like okay I have
5 hours to work with
what can I do in 5 hours
and then like figure that out
and so the whole month was just like
it was just nonstop experiments
and like what is a style of video
I can do that would be relatively satisfying
that can be done in this short of a time
so like a single
episode analysis or
like a reaction
watch along kind of thing or just like
you know any random opinion piece
that I don't require
like editing that would require me to
like go through a show and find specific moments
if it's something that I could just
you know brain blast and then like record screen footage
or hand held footage
like anything that is
easier to create
you know go for that
and so take note of this people this is
important stuff if you want to be a content creator
it's so important to shape
the stuff that you make to the reality
of your life and the world you're in
you gotta think of that first
that's exactly how I fucked up
my career so badly as to necessitate
this because
at the time when we were planning to move to Boston
I decided to launch into doing this
how they marketed thing
and the conceit of that series was that it was
going to take a lot of time
to make the reality like
it was going to take a lot of actual marketing
I was going to pay a lot of people to be involved
and it was like
the videos were going to be huge so it was going to be like
one a month at best
and
that took me away
like it meant that I wasn't putting anything out and so
I kind of disappeared and then
I had to move so that extended
me disappearing and so there's like two months where I wasn't
really doing anything and my Patreon just plummeted
and granted that's partly because
I didn't have everyone's goodwill
necessarily because I was making
videos in so many different styles that
everything I was making would satisfy
someone but none of it
satisfied everyone so like
for instance early this year
in like January or February
I put like a lot of effort
into these two videos that I made on the turntable channel
that have like 2,000 views
a piece so like
you know that's like a lot of
my energy that's me putting as much effort
into those as I would into
probably more into those than I would
into a main channel video and yet
like even among my Patrons not that many people
watched it so from their perspective
I just didn't make anything from their perspective
it's like oh I haven't gotten any Digi content
and so like it's from
that point that standpoint of like
everyone's a little disappointed
that I then was like oh well
I'll make everybody happy again by making
a big thing and then I
disappear to go make the big thing and they're all like
oh I guess Digi's fucked off let's unpatron
and now I'm like oh I couldn't
I can't afford that I can't
afford to make big thing while everyone's
unpatroning and I just moved into a more expensive
place so you know and then that
becomes well alright
because me and Tom throughout July
were planning some like really big
shit that would have also
been like a long time build up kind of
thing and it was a great idea
and I'll talk to you guys about it
sometime but like
it was just like this will take time to make
real that's not the right time
to be doing that yeah I don't have time
like I need money now I am like
you know I am coming at
out of each month with less money than I
went into the month with and that is terrifying
you know so
so like yeah so that's
that's why it became okay let's take
the opposite approach what can I do
in three hours that can get a million views
you know well just one one thing I was
wondering about was just like your Shinsekai
your video is like a 40 minute analysis
video that clearly was like
was like DeVu working on that like during the
month DeVu worked on that literally
the entire month and
still alright that's what I thought
but and you got it up like
so close to the edge right but you did
it was it was late actually but I
put out a I put out a contingency
video right before midnight
that was just like a two minute meme video
oh that's funny and then
and then I unlisted that but you can find
it in the every every YouTube video featuring
DigiBro playlist Nate you'll love that I check the thing
it says it came out the 31st at least on my
on my YouTube it depends on your time zone
because YouTube is
in California time so it was on time
in California time well see I'm not holding
you to any kind of crazy standard here because I got
many of my meme amount of videos out
after midnight but before I like went to sleep
or anything right the nights that I
so day doesn't end until you sleep
but yeah the how
because how they marketed is also like a
fully edited experience and that one
DeVu had finished before the month started
and like I
I had to do a bit for
question about how they marketed
did someone request
an ad for patreon.com
slash Ben saying who
because I saw it and I was like
I didn't what's this
almost nothing that was advertised was
like the person themselves
you know it was like always people asking
it seemed like it was a bunch of a bunch
of goofs a bunch of goofs and memes
for the most part I mean I guess I actually
you know don't have anything that they
want to advertise so I was thinking about
this did you I've actually been seriously thinking
about like how to like increase like ad
presence in my stuff I haven't done anything yet
but I'm thinking about it and what you've done with
with how they market has given
me some very good ideas I'm just thinking
about like I don't know whatever Alex Jones
got banned on YouTube etc everyone's getting
banned if you do bad things I'm like okay
what can we do if like ads
go away main YouTube ads
the solution is pretty clear
and obviously this would take a lot of work to get into place
but like like
like this individual paid ads
during ad breaks that you would otherwise have which
I built into me a math from the start
Arab we ag was that is
and then like you do through
through patreon but like you could do it through any
means and having specific people
advertise stuff whether it's like a dick
shaving butt or whatever the fuck that is
or individual people on patreon or any kind of connection
thing I'm just like this is just such a good
idea to do something like this
makes all the sense in the world and it doesn't
rely on YouTube to like
you suck a lot I mean there is a
thing about that because yeah I think YouTube
doesn't can tell
if like if somebody says
like reports you for having a paid
promotion in the video and you don't list it
and well I would just make sure that I
like it then YouTube can just take your
video down if you're promoting Alex Jones
or something well like something
controversial things then I guess you know
like you have the option as a businessman
to choose what you do and do not use as an
advertisement in your content so I
certainly would exercise that authority
if I was going to but like it's
still you're still under the
jurisdiction of YouTube it's not like an escape
from all that well yeah
but I mean let's if you got well you could do
this on another site like daily motion or
what the fuck
hey the bonus episode for the PCP went live
nine minutes ago is what that
is telling me how nice
there it is everybody
tell him
tell him tell him how fucking cool it is
tell him how fucking cool I made
it you you you friend
friends family listening to this
Ben Saint here you might have heard
him he did the editing
and the animation
for the new bonus episode
what's it about oh talking while eating
talking while eating
five dollars people patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
the editing and the animation
Ben did is truly
I would say
that I would say that I took Hippo's
seed of an idea
for how to make an episode look good
and then rendered it completely
obsolete
no
wrong
see if you can post last episode
make you look stupid
I'm loving this arms race
of increasingly good PCP animation
by the way
that's what made the early PCP
great was the arms race of editing
I still want to try and edit
once I'm back home
do it mage just get
after effects
but in the early days it was mostly about
the intro segments
there was a brief flirtation
with the animated
color bars around the names
and then it was kind of like dropped
and then the arms race was in the intros
and then nobody cared for a while
and then now we're back to being
we're holding ourselves to a higher standard
now now that we're making more money
it's worth our time
what the hell are we talking about
before we got sidetracked by this
we were talking about
your month of videos
and the shinsukai yori and timing
and stuff
that's what it was
I got to tell ben that it was
someone named heavy roman
who paid for that ad
he is not a patron of you
heavy roman
kippo you wanted to say something
well
he's done his part
so he's excused from patroning
did you think of that ad by the way
did you like it
I kind of like
just didn't notice it at first
I don't really remember
the actual content of it
it's just
the four panels of the guy
sniffing that rock and then exploding
oh yeah
all that's right
sent to the metroid theme
did he make the ad
no I made all the ads
oh you made the ad
well I was surprised that you went with beastcapades
but I'm not against it
it's the thing what I requested
it was your suggestion
yes I am happy I am pleased
what was her suggestion
that commands
eat the rain
oh yeah
the thing is
that with your comics
making
I don't know how to convert your art to video
because most of it's black and white
and it's in a page
I don't know how to convey it
with beastcapades because all the images are the same size
and there was more color
I knew it would be easier to
represent
to do a paneling on screen
where they'd all be the same size
and it was just a really exciting page
because it was all visual
there's no text or anything
I remember now
and I remember that
the beat drops or whatever
when it explodes
and I was like yeah
bring back beastcapades right fucking now
no vapors 3 is done
throw it in trash bin
nobody likes vapors it's gone
at least of all me
and yet I am bound
fair enough
it also makes sense because the aesthetic
of beastcapades is kind of metroidish
so
it's the metroid theme
that plays over the comic
beastcapades
is the best thing
and it does render everything else
beastcapades yet
well I mean it's not done
you might as well hold off
I didn't know it was something
that was going to happen
I'm patron from patreon.com
speaking of
like video
speaking of like the whole
loads of videos in a month
I have not been making videos and I'm stupid
but like
where's the videos at
oh you know
there's things coming up
I talk about it
more on my patreon podcast
patreon.com
but
at the moment
the thing that's coming up
is october which is curby month
so that will be full of things
and I will be trying
curby month like every october
every october
I'm really happy about that
cause I hate that literally everyone does
like spooktober
and I'm like I don't like horror
so it just means everyone becomes worthless to me
basically for an entire month
which also means that
I kind of want to finish
belljap in September
so that I don't have anything else
like creative so that's my plan
is to do belljap this month
and then curby month
next month and hopefully after that
I will be making videos a bit more frequently
I'm very sorry
people like him
I want more give and take videos
cause that's like my favorite channel on youtube
I forget
I just do anything on that
what is your favorite
give and take review
video type that comes out
my favorite is chain mail saga
more chain mail videos
I like the stuff that just feels like
a fucking psychic brain blast
where it feels like this idea
just like hit you and you did it
15 minutes and like
and it's utterly like
nothing I could have possibly predicted
that's my favorite type
of youtube video in general
it's just like when someone just makes something
because clearly like it crawled into
their psyche and they had to expel it as fast
as possible
kind of like uh I mean that's sort of
what I forget how to say it's like GMC
fo sho or GMC
GMC fo sho is pretty fucking great
that only he kind of expands that joke and he makes it
a big production it's dope
did any of you watch my video raw beef
probably
I did see raw beef
yeah raw beef is a perfect example of what I'm talking about
where I just like
I just like I gotta make a song about being the raw beef
and then it's just a video
of like a piece of beef spinning around
it's actually a pork shoulder turns out but like
it's just me screaming
about raw beef over like this crazy
ass beat I made and uh that's it
that's the whole video
wait was that like a minute long
raw beef it's like 20 seconds
yeah I okay I think I saw that
yeah
so I want more like that I want more raw
I mean and that that was kind of the premise
of the song what I meant the deeper
coded meaning behind raw beef
yeah tell is that
like that is what I consider that type of content
to be is the raw beef
it's that that uncooked
shit that shit that just goes right
from the cow into your mouth and you get the most
nutrients out of it because
they didn't cook nothing out of it
you get fucking salmonella
I want the salmonella god damn it
this is exactly why it's good to have
something like the the mea math of a style
thing that forces you to not
be afraid of producing
those into a video like how many times this
happens to me less and less but I remember so clearly
being like I'm making a video
when I was making the Ridley video that now is like
110,000 views or something
at many points along
like oh is this actually gonna be good does anyone actually
give a shit is this funny
they're gonna laugh and like it's wildly
successful for my channel like it's great
everybody loves it
to destroy those fears
by just being like I have to make it
I have to put my brain out for people to judge
generally goes pretty well
those are my favorite videos
of yours too are the ones that
like I said in general my favorite is
anytime it's something that I couldn't imagine
anyone else making because it just
feels like it it
blasted right from the back
of your mind and like there was no thought put
into like oh I gotta make
something successful or formulaic or
like something that people will like it's just
like yep how can I realize
my favorite video of yours
is uncovered final fantasy
15 yeah because I returned
to it all the time like I'll watch it
again and again because every part of it is
so unique and none of it feels
like anybody else's video you know
I love that fucking
video and the musical at the end it's
everything like that
just
shoot in my fucking head
what a great time
that video was yeah it's great make
another one for my best bitch
I'm working on it
do it
don't make me sit
in 15 minutes of you explaining that manga
it takes less time to read than anime
I know I know
I know
wow Saab everyone fucking gets it
point pointless
thing to note a
video of mine went big and is now
my most watched
video and I didn't realize it
which one what
it's just it's one of the ones I did
during Igmovo tour didge that I sort of
slapped together which was the
PS2 memory card models video or I just
looked at all the PS2
like you know how in PS2 memory
cards you look at the data and they have
like little 3D models representing
the save files and I just looked at
them and said things about them
and that's got 80,000 views out of nowhere
that's such a gib thing and it's something
that like someone would only make when
there's like a time crunch to get something out
and they have to like think of what to do
the comments for that video were all like this is really cool
and I don't know why more people don't talk about this right
because that was yeah and it's funny that
people are like oh yeah this is a video
that happened my favorite genre was
always PS2 memory card
icons that's my that's the peak
artistic medium it is now because gib
invented it that's right
he started a whole business a whole
thriving industry
I certainly have a very successful video
I think I googled it to
see if somebody else had done a similar video
and they had there was this one guy
who had done it already and I was like
damn but I'll make it anyway
and his video wasn't very good so I'm like
I can do better was his like rating them like out of 10 or
something he did like the top 10 or something
I don't remember I think after watching yours
I watched a couple other ones also about
like PS2 memory cards and I was fascinated
by the whole thing what was the best one
there was one that was like obviously the best
but I can't remember what it was
it was like super well animated
watch the video link in the description
people
I'm just happy that that
could ever happen to me a video
that I thought is done for
suddenly gets views out of nowhere I mean
it's quite kind of died down but that just doesn't happen
I usually just to me I get
a bit of a boost sometimes but it sort of
never really goes anywhere I've accepted
the fact personally that I'm
I'm not super smart genius
who will know exactly what's
going to do great on YouTube my approaches
I'm just going to try to make stuff
relatively fast and throw as
many ideas out there as possible that I think are like
kind of good and just
see what that's when it comes like making like a popular
video I've given up I don't know
what's going to be popular well I don't
really try to do the popular
video I just hope that I do
becomes popular kind of the same
I mean right now I know I should make a video
darling in the Franks I'm 100% sure
that's what I should be making right now in the
DeVoo Bay right now
DeVoo Bay
it's soaking in
the DeVoo goo at this very moment absorbing
all the juices the DeGoo and the good
he just finished watching the show
he posted just now in
the chat like that
the ad on the page
is he listening is he listening
hippo's shirts no
no I didn't know
yeah yeah I saw that that's because
I'm sure you guys are seeing
this but like you get ads now
for like things that you've bought or have looked at
like on the sides of page because like Google is
tracking what you do and if I already bought it why
would I want another one stop
hey here's a here's a thing this is
definitely real this is 100% real
I forget the exact example
but have you guys
like recently I forget what it was
me and Michelle were like talking about something
and like I went and I bought
something it might have been like I was talking
about like the new smash or something and like
talking about how much I love my switch as I all
do every day all hours of the day
and like Michelle
who has never bought a video game
in her life because she isn't allowed to by me
what a fake gamer girl
I know right
like she starts to get ads
on her phone for like
like the switch and like video games
and at this point they're not even
like pretending like they're not doing
they just listen to us
like she didn't search for it they're listening
to us and they're catering to it
by audio they're listening every second
of every fucking day
I'm not constantly getting ads for fucking
like lolliporn like what's going on
I've had that conversation
how come I'm not getting ads for guns
yeah
I should try that
I should try repeating
how come I'm not getting ads for guns
here's a test
I guess like
keep repeating the same words
for like a while and see
dude mage people have done that
people have done that
but not only that
somethings can buy
it is objectively true that this is
something that is happening
there's enough testament to
I mean this is why they had to update the privacy
policies on like every fucking website
because the EU is currently hammering
Google about this
Google is no longer naughty
yeah
they took that out of their fucking thing
they literally took that out
of their company policy
the do no evil they straight up removed it
well this is
all I'm saying is
sometimes evil is
I just can't
you could not
that is the funniest thing that I've heard
all year
is Google literally
first of all it was always goofy that they had that
in their thing but like to have to remove
it because they have to acknowledge that what
they are doing is evil
surely their official
stance is that they took it out
because it was goofy in the first place right
they had it in there
and now they're removing it
now is not the time
have they said why
I mean there's probably a PR
statement on why they took it out that has to do
with like professionalism or we revolving
as a company and you know evil and good
or subjective terms so you know we're just
like it's all good man
like maybe
Satan was right you know like who says God
should reign in heaven above you know
hey Satan gave us
the fruit of the tree of knowledge
everything we've done is all because of
Satan
and Google is used for
searching knowledge so
we were Satan all along guys
are you saying that
Google came down
from the heavens and gave us the Google search
bar the fruit of the tree of
knowledge and we've all eaten from it
and now we're being tracked
okay guys but Satan is actually bad rap
he's not evil he just takes care of people
in hell like it's not a fun job
hey guys
yeah he's like he's like Hades
from like the Gris Pantheon
who was forced to control a little hell
oh god just test it down and he's like
stay there and now everyone will hate you
the apple logo actually isn't that
the apple logo because like the original apple logo
before they made it like actually cool was
way more complicated it was an entire
illustration of Isaac Newton and the apple
falling on his head that was what the apple is
it's supposed to represent
a moment of genius because of course
this is apple we're talking about and they have to be
well yeah of course
you know what's funny wait was there
a biblical reference wait did someone just say
something about like it's the apple of sin
well I was making a comparison
with their logo that now it's
like an apple with a bite out of it seems relevant to
like original sin kind of but it's actually
it was never supposed to be that but
alright yeah
do you know what's funny
is that tell me
scary things
scary things are now funny things
upon hearing
upon hearing that
upon hearing that google is now listening
to everything
hearing that like
google is listening in on us
and watching us fap
all I can think of is
I can't wait for the memes about this
I'm really excited to see all the funny
fucking things I just feel
I feel this is just funny
it is the decadent slide to the destruction
of civilization and I will fight against it
scary things are now funny things
people will meme
into the dystopian future
they will meme all the way down
we are meming all the way to the bottom
that's absolutely true
exerbia just made a funny meme video
about this very situation
that you're describing hippo so
you're right
exerbia never heard of him
exerbia is a youtuber who does
comedic videos about existential dread
that sounds good
and sci-fi
he's like a comedy sci-fi author
with an english accent
his videos are fun
they can get a little repetitive because all of them are about
existential dread
and the smallness of man in the face of the universe
I bet google gives him
tons of ads for existential dread
cause he talks about it so much
we don't need ads for that
speaking of ads
to address the ad situation
in how they marketed
it actually did not go
I don't really like the ads being
I think ultimately it came out
as well as it possibly could
but the way that the video
was planned was not to be like
what it is at all
I cut the first 6 minutes of the video out
there was supposed to be a huge amount of outro
and like
if you remember the finisher fail video
where it was like
the last 15 minutes
were like something entirely else
that was supposed to be how they marketed it
it was supposed to have
more of an intro than go through the main bulk
of me talking about the show
and then spiral out into this whole other thing
so the ads were not actually supposed to be
sprinkled throughout the video like that
they were supposed to be sprinkled throughout the outro section
but because of the fact that
I'm not doing it as
the complete series anymore
that would have come out
I just cut all the extraneous shit
but because people had already paid for the ads
I felt like I had to do them
and if I put them all at the end
people would just click off the video as soon as they got to the ads section
so I wanted it to feel like
they were integrated in a way that made sense
for them to be there and to make people watch them
but like ultimately that
particular video would have been better
without the ads
it's not every time
that I'm like with you on like
I'm pushing bullshit that you're trying
whatever shit that is
but in this case I actually
I saw a bunch of people being like I really didn't like the ad breaks
they really took me out of it
maybe it's because I'm thinking of like from a business perspective
but I'm like I mean would these people have preferred
use like because I would
I would absolutely put like ads in my videos
at opportune times that are like the Google ones
like what's the difference
putting like just someone's paid for ads
because of your ad blocker
well fuck the people with ad blocker
which includes me
ultimately like if you
aren't paying me in any way
if you're not watching ads
and you're not a patron
I don't feel bad for you
I mean for me personally
I just
I'm very particular about like the video structure
you know I want it to be like a clean
just go through and everything's fine
now granted I do think
I could stand to be a lot more selfish
with my videos probably
for my own benefit
but like I've only seen it as like the reason
that I have a Patreon
and that the Patreon is able to be so successful
is that I don't do that shit
that like you know people respect
that I don't put in ad breaks
I don't put in you know
I don't put in shilling or anything like that
but like in this
case again like in the
original context of video was planned for
it would have made more sense and like
how they marketed would have been a video series
about once a month and the format of it
would have lent itself to this and so
it would have continually made sense going forward
I think that
a big part of what inspired the format
of how they marketed was Weagawa
so I think it would make sense for you
because what I love about
Weagawa is that because
there's this looseness to it
and that it has like multiple phases
you can basically throw in anything
like any random
clip any random meme
like you could just toss in there
and it'll make perfect sense and it all flows together
and that's
it's just an excuse to make a video
that's all it is
so like I admire that but
I don't know how to replicate it
in my style
it'd be like making a movie
and then like sticking in like an ad in the middle
and again like
because of the fact that the original format was to have
these super long outros where I could do that
where it would be like
it's already just a random mishmash of stuff
it would make sense for there to be
even more random stuff in there
because like a big part of
how they marketed was going to be that
I would take clips from shows that are
like marketing gimmicks and just
play those clips
kind of like in finisher fail there's like
how they marketed episode zero
and it's just like a bunch of scenes from
Takunomi where they're advertising beer
like in the show and I'm like literally saying
this is how they marketed it
with these beer ads
so there was going to be a lot of like
just random segments of like
funny scenes from shows where they
they obviously made this
scene to market the show
and then intercut with that would be ads
that I made for my fans and like
the only stipulation I had on the ads was that they were all going to be less than 10 seconds
so it's basically just
hey I'm going to and I said
it's going to be less than 10 seconds and I said all the rules
so like don't expect to get
like a glowing review of your thing
it's just going to be a fucking
a little meme that
you know puts the name of the thing you want in the video
it's like a TV ad you know it's a few seconds long
you've got to get your message out fast
and I did them all
just like a TV ad it's a couple
seconds long and it says nothing in particular
about the thing being advertised
I mean you sound like you're making a joke
but that's pretty commonly the case
like you know
TV ads in 30 seconds
well what about those total non-secret
commercial where like they're just talking about a lifestyle
and then they're like Jeep Durango
you know it's
what's the thing
like sure you can make a point that those guys have such brand recognition already
you already know
like what they're selling and they don't need to
but whatever
why is every car
at the same like structurally
because all it does
driving up a mountain saying about
if you can't do this with your normal car
buy this new car
like none of them
they all end with the car
like displayed
at a three quarters angle
and in my brain I combine
every single one of those ads
to the point where I don't know any car ad
specifically
I'm not being advertised a single brand
I'm just being advertised
speaking of cars
was it on the PCP that I shared my idea
for the perfect
way to end the Fast and the Furious series
I don't think so
imagine it
the year is 2020
or 2022
either one doesn't matter
not 2021 now it's not okay
but the year is 20 whatever
and Fast and the Furious 10 is coming out
and it is 150 minutes
of extremely expensive
cars being driven off of a cliff
in one continuous shot
is the most expensive
movie ever made
the only sort of car
and that's it
that's it
why is it 155 minutes
was there some significance to that number
that's usually
you want it to be a decent length for your money
you're paying like $10 to get in there
I thought there was going to be a reason for that
because he doesn't want the number
seems like a reasonable time frame
for Fast and the Furious 10 to come out
okay
the only car advertisement
I'm not even sure if it's a car advertisement
but he had a car in it
I'm pretty sure it had a car in it
I just remembered like this
it was kind of funny
it was shot from the back
it appeared like a very attractive lady
it was walking up to a guy
with a car I'm guessing
and then like boom
actually the attractive lady is a guy all along
and it was
got him, you're gay now
it was
really makes me want to buy their car
for tricking me about my sexuality
you bully
yeah at the bottom
it says buy our car fair
I would remember that
they should do that
you see that one
you see that one where the guy
you see that one where the guy is eating a baby Ruth
and he just like pulls out
pulls out a gun, pulls out an assault rifle
and just lays waste to like
a school
a school playground
he's just standing there eating the baby Ruth
that one really made me want a baby Ruth
that sounds good
I enjoy that
Tom I didn't hear a word you said
oh Ben that wasn't a commercial
that was the actual school shooting
that's just how you're coping
oh is that where I was
on the last full moon
that's a full moon mentor
he's a lichen school shooter
or a school shooter
what is it called
what is it called a baby Ruth
can you explain that to me
it's just the name of the candy
it's named after Babe Ruth
I really don't like the word baby
in any sort of food that I consume
I'm eating a baby
what about sugar baby
I don't want to eat baby carrots
they're just normal carrots
I'm stuck on the
I'm stuck on the where
school shooter
the full moon comes out and he looks at it
and he's like oh no it's happening again
and then an AK-47 appears in his hands
it grows out of his hand
and his virginity regrows
and his registration
to incel is like r slash incels
it activates once again
and his jacket grows
and becomes leathery
you know what
I could believe oh my god I got a perfect
I got a perfect joke and a segue
all in one are you ready
here we fucking go
I could believe that that was me
because I do like baby Ruth
and I would say
that I wouldn't eat one because I'm keto
but if I was asleep
it was a full moon so it was like I was dream
it was like I was having one of my keto
keto dreams you dream of eating carbs
and you wake up because it's a nightmare
and that's it perfect transition
to tell you all know that I am on
day two of a fast
I have not eaten in almost two days
and I feel wonderful
dude fasting does make you feel like you become a god
no I'm not hungry
sometimes I kind of want to eat
because like it would taste good
and it would be something to do
but I'm not like hungry
it's funny you mentioned that Ben
because I'm fasting today
I decided yesterday that I'm not eating today
I decided yesterday too
oh my god what the fuck
guess what I had for breakfast
I did every Monday by the way guys
I had a big ol' slice of cake for breakfast
that's what I had
that is not posted
every week
why do you fast every Monday
I decided like one day a week
would be neat
so I decided on Monday
it feels great it makes you feel like a god
no I hate it
but I go through with it
well
it's fun
it does have its health benefits for at least one day
I'm not sure about two things
are you guys achieving your stated goals
of losing gaining weight or whatever
well I wasn't really
I had lost a bit
I had lost like 10 pounds
and I had been stable for maybe like two weeks
and I was like okay I'm at a plateau
so it's time to fast
time to break this plateau
alright
time will tell
just don't like
I sometimes don't eat
as that much and I sort of like
I'm too lazy to go and
make something so I'm like
I'll be hungry for a little bit
like I'm hungry right now and I could
go and run away
and like eat something
but like I'm okay with just
even after this is finished just sitting here
for a bit not eating
I don't know whether I'm gaining the benefits of all this like fasting stuff
because I don't do it every single day
I very often like it wasn't
that uncommon for me
even like before I was thinking about
what I wanted to eat well
to like well when I lived
on my own it was common for me to just
like wake up
and not be hungry and then
go the rest of the day doing something
and just not get hungry because I was like
focused on other things and I would go like the entire
day without eating and maybe at
night I'd be like oh I guess I should eat something and I need something
well we're talking about food
my fucking oven broke
and it's a
big gay boy and so
I called the seers and
a guy came and I paid him $100
to tell me your oven's
broke
because
apparently what happened is that
the panel broke your oven's broken now you're
gonna be give me a thousand dollars to fix it
yeah well okay so this
this dude's like the panel
is broken that like controls the oven
and to replace the panel and he
points me to some numbers and he's like
here's how much the part itself costs
which is like $360
and I'm already like holy fuck
right and then he's like and here's the
total cost after repairs
$618
and I look at it
and I look over at the stove and I look at him
and I say how much does the stove cost
and he says $600
and I was just like I'll
just buy a new stove
and he's like yeah fuck
that right so then
this one's got sentimental value
no this is
apparently a new stove that was bought
right before we moved in
does it not have any sort of
warranties or anything
apparently they didn't get a warranty
on the guy
fantastic
if it's a new product they have to have a warranty
it's like by law
you have to have a year warranty
the guy said that if there was a warranty
it would have come up when he looked up
the stove in his system
then someone's broken the law federal law mandates
a year warranty on every consumer product
well we don't know how long ago it was actually bought
and put into place or anything
I was told that they had just bought it
not long before they moved out and I know they moved out
in February
I think you need to call bullshit on
whoever said that
you might want to actually call the manufacturer
I might do something because I didn't buy a new
stove because what I
me and May were talking about
and then we're like is it
possible that we can just get a
toaster oven and it'll be just as good
yes
and I'm like
because I didn't want to believe that that was true
because it seems wrong
but then
it does doesn't it
I'm in my page so I told the people
on my page in discord about this oven situation
and this guy Kaisimir
in his 30s and he lives in Japan
is like man I haven't owned an oven
in years
and I was like and then he points out
that in Japan
almost no one has an oven
apparently in Japan
full ovens are just extremely rare
they just use toaster ovens
like they just have like
I mean I know that a lot of okay I've seen like
you ever watched cooking with dog no
it's weird
how many recipes
of microwaving like this seems like
a lot of Japanese food
is like involves a microwave
I think it's just because of space concerns
they just don't have room for full ovens
and then so I'm looking into it and I'm realizing
like a toaster oven is literally just
an oven that's not that big
and like the only reason that you would need
a full-size oven is to
have a full-size
oven and I'm like well I never cook
for more than two people all we really use
our oven for is make a chicken cord on blue anyway
so
so we went to Walmart
and found a $50 oven
that was on sale for $30
and now I have a $30 toaster oven
instead of a $600 stove
and I haven't yet confirmed that it can do
everything I want because if it can't make
chicken cord on blue then I'm going to be a sad boy
I don't know if I want to spend $600
just so I can make chicken cord on blue
can't fry things on toaster ovens
can you do that?
this is like fried egg or something
but you can't do that in an oven either
well did you
did you do your stove?
the stove top still works
it's just the oven
to be honest I almost
I almost never cook in
like my oven oven
I use the stove almost exclusively
back at my old place I used the oven a lot
because I used to eat lots of mozzarella sticks
and like
cheesy bread and garlic bread and shit
but like the only reason I had to use
the oven is that the toaster oven is a little slower
and ours was too small
to like really fit anything in it
but we just bought a bigger one
like they make bigger toaster ovens
this is basically just a fucking oven
I'm sitting here and I'm like I just bought an oven
for $30 and this motherfucker
was going to charge me $618
to fix the one I already fucking
ahhh what is this world
like I just
I never even heard of a toaster oven
I had never even considered the idea
I had never considered
the idea of a living life without an oven
until
that guy said like oh I haven't had an oven in years
and I was like what?
and then I thought about it and I was like there's nothing I make
in the oven I can't make in a toaster oven
so why would I need an oven
if you want to make a big
Sunday roast
why would I ever do that
and even then
you can get pretty big toaster ovens
I didn't go for like a gigantic oven
I was just seeing a toaster oven that was big enough
that you could like bake I don't know a pie
the biggest one that they had at Walmart
was like $100
and it was pretty fucking huge
and it literally advertises that you can cook
a full chicken inside of it
like they had a picture of a full roasted chicken
on there
I think yep
yep
so you never had a toaster oven growing up
but like yes the answer is yes
you can do everything you want
just because I heard the oven
because I didn't want to fuck with it
it takes like 15 minutes to heat up
and I'm not that hungry
apparently the toaster oven
is more power cost effective too
like heating up a stove costs more
this is just another example
of American excess that we just don't need
I guess so
this looks too powerful
look at that fucking thing
that's like extreme
it's got a top one too
holy fuck
whoa
okay well hold on
get that toast out of there
who the fuck is cooking bacon this way
who's cooking bacon in a toaster oven
in like a bacon tray that's a thing
yeah
why not
does that coffee pot say nostalgia
on it
what
wait yes
no hold on
it does
it says nostalgia
where does it say
I guess it's a retro design
obviously it's made by white industries
anyone get it
dude
we've changed
we've changed from using the word retro
now we're using the word nostalgia
I'm nostalgic for retro
that's why it has nostalgia
it's like an oldish
cream plastic
yeah it really is
you used to call that a retro design
now they're calling it nostalgia
retro is too mainstream
it's a toaster oven
now I'm hungry
now I wasn't hungry
and I was totally good with my fast
the fast is ruined
give it 10 minutes it'll pass
well you know what guys we've been talking about some bullshit for a while
I say we change tax
and we get some fucking coal
please god
do we have a fucking
do we have a thing now
this is gonna be awesome
I'm actually really excited about this piece
it better just be someone screaming fuckers in the franks over and over again
that's what I want
did we screen these
or are these just like
yeah but I mean they don't get
automatically recorded we get to edit them
so if anyone says something real bad we can always cut it out
so I'm not too worried about it
what could they possibly say
would it be bad enough for us to cut it
oh I don't know maybe actual
advocating violence against a specific group
who knows I don't know
but it's speakpipe.com
slash the procrastinators
I think the link to the description regardless
so go to that and leave us voicemail
this is why I don't go to the meetings because I like to be surprised
I believe the link is PCP voicemail
what is it
speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail
thank you PCP voicemail that's the one
yeah do that click the link the description is there
and leave us a message and here we go
alright let's see what we got first on deck
okay here we go this is from
Gavin at
her booty poppin
is he wanted us to know that's his name on twitter
let's see what he's got for us
here we go
hey guys I have a question for y'all
if a significant other
had gotten sexually unattractive
to the point where you have
no desire to have sex with them in particular
during the time you've been in a relationship with one another
but you still have a desire to have sex
would you wait it out
to see if they could become sexually attractive again
and if so how long would you wait
until you decide to look for a sex elsewhere
if you're not willing to wait indefinitely
also would you stop dating
or in your romantic relationship with this person
if you decided upon yourself
that you've waited long enough for them to become
sexually attractive again
so is he just saying she got fat
yeah he's saying his bitch got fat
basically
what else could you mean
okay
oh yeah you know my girl
got acid attacked in the face
by a terrorist
for not being a proper
enough Muslim woman
so she's not attractive anymore
but maybe I'll wait it out and see if it gets better
Ben I'm assuming this is a joke
because no lie
if that happened
there comes a time
why saddle yourself
that you're not attracted to
for your whole fucking life
just because something bad happened to them
why isn't your responsibility to put up with that forever
oh yeah
of course
this guy's thing
the only way
that it could be reversible
is if he's just talking about getting fat
he's talking about getting fat
so I don't know
why he didn't just say that
but like
so this literally is not a problem for me
so
the way I see it
if I'm attracted to someone
on
I'm not attracted to someone just because they're thin
if getting fat is enough
to make a girl completely
sexually unattractive to me
she probably wasn't that attractive
in the first place
I don't think there's a certain point
if she gets
if a girl
if a girl got that fat
and you couldn't
steer that ship away from it happening
you have not done your job as a partner
oh come on
it's not your problem
no I'm not saying it's your problem
I'm just saying
right
this had to happen over the course of years
you don't just balloon
to a point of being completely
okay
if you're saying that your girl
is no longer attractive because she gained
like 30 pounds
you need to
your standards are a little too
30 pounds is a lot of weight
I don't think it's enough to make a girl
who has a hot face
unattractive
if a girl is attractive it's not
I mean
he's not saying
my girl gained X amount of weight
is it okay that I no longer find her attractive
he's saying
the only way you can get there
that's all it comes down to
the only way you can get there is
like I said
the only possible scenario where this can happen
is that they gained a lot of weight
because he's implying that it has to be
something reversible
so we're assuming that she gained X amount of weight
if a girl is attractive enough
for me
the weight is not
the biggest factor of sexual attraction
it's her face
it's her
general shape and demeanor
so like
a girl would have to put on a considerable amount of weight
before I would be like
I can't fuck you anymore
and I think that if there's no way
that I would allow that to happen
like at some point
as it's happening I'd be like hey we need to
we need to move, we need to back pedal
and to answer this question
I guess if it got to a point where
you could not correct that course
and she's just let herself go
and she doesn't give a fuck
we're not even having a relationship
because we're not participating together
at that point it's just a breakdown
of communication and issue between
the two people
you gotta say something
if the girl has no idea that you feel this way
that's a huge problem
that means you're failing
but also I feel like
if it is weight
and it's
something that he just let happen
and didn't talk about it, that's one thing
but I also think that if somebody puts on
just a bit of weight
and then you're no longer attracted to them
and you're considering breaking up
I don't think you were that connected to them in the first place
that's how I feel
it's gonna be possible
if you've got a guy who prides himself
on his physique and wants to date a girl
who feels the same way
and maybe they even bonded over their physical fitness
if the girl starts to slip
and it's not
it doesn't matter
but then the person is not doing this thing
that is important to the other person
I'm never gonna judge anybody
for breaking up with anybody for any reason
because this is a voluntary opt-in situation
I feel like this is not something that you would need
to ask for advice from us for
this is something that would be a topic
of conversation with you and this girl
you know why he's asking
it's because he's not attracted
maybe it's not the specific guy
the idea here is he's not attracted
or something like that
and he feels guilty about feeling this way
that's what's going on
I wanna say something
like okay
the circumstances don't really matter
the specifics of how much weight was
gained or whether it was an acid attack
it's all whatever
I'm still on that
acid attack joke by the way
still just ringing the comedy out of that one
if you're
not attracted
the whole idea of
well let's wait and see
if we can get back
let's wait and see if we can
get her attractive again
if she'll do that
it shouldn't be a wait and see
it should be working towards that
it shouldn't be like hopefully my girlfriend
is gonna start losing weight
be like hey I don't want to fuck you anymore
you need to lose weight or this is ending
I think if you're at the point
where you're past the point
if you're not attracted to them anymore
I think it would be kind of
asking for a miracle
I think the odds that
weighting are gonna pan out and be worth it
are really low
I mean you know
he's gotta make that calculation himself
maybe this is a really meaningful
if you're married to someone and then they get fat
it's like well Jesus what are we gonna do here
time for a divorce
sure you might break up with him over this
trying to imagine a circumstance
where she's like
I imagine if you come to her
like hey I'm not okay with this
we need to work through this
like if her answer is
no I want to
be fat then just break up with her
if her answer is
if her answer is like oh I will try to work through this
with you like let's work together
if you do this you will be the bad guy
unfortunately
that's okay
we're talking about breaking up with her
if she doesn't
you just have to be firm on your stance
talking out of my ass
I will break up with you if you don't lose weight
but I'm willing to help
and then if she won't do the steps
that you're trying to take
then you just gotta keep making it clear
you know the problem is
this situation is framed by society
that the person
making the complaint is wrong
because society now is like
healthy at any size
you're just being a shallow, vapid person
but it's not that you're being a shallow, vapid person
it's that this is like Nate said
a voluntary kind of relationship
that both parties entered into
and now one of the conditions
that brought you into it has changed
and so it's not you being shallow
it's that one of the main reasons
you were invested in it to begin with
is no longer valid and so the entire contract
is now null and void and so
it is not rude, it is not shallow
it completely makes sense
you say society but I think most people
would agree with our stance here
I think it would have to
I think even today this would not be
considered unreasonable
I'm sure people would do it
I'm only saying more that society
would say that
the culture would present someone
doing this as being kind of a dick
I mean I think you could
probably spin it
either way
I don't think there's an argument to be made that you're a dick
if you're trying to help them lose the weight
it'd be one thing if you're just like you need to burn weight
or else fuck you
I don't think you should have to
help them
I don't think you should be responsible for them at all
you don't have to
I think if you're in a good relationship
then there should be some
like I'm not saying you have to
literally like take them to the classes
and everything I'm just saying that like
if you just break up with someone out of nowhere
and you didn't mention this was a problem
that would be a dick move
if you're like telling them like hey this is something
that I have a problem with
there needs to be an effort made on your part
then I don't think that's being a dick
yeah
seems reasonable to me
you know
you guys may or may not be aware
that I not too long ago got out of a relationship
and
it's not
but it feels kind of the same
like in my case
it was the personality that got
fat in this case
but you know
there's this great market
my only point is that
you can't like wait for it to get better
like you gotta
you should
9 times out of 10, 99 times out of 100
it's better to cut that cord sooner rather than later
then there's this amazing
there's this manga called
Enclosed Called Fat
by Moyoko Anno
and there's an amazing line
where the main girl is like
fat and
there's a lot of people who wrong her
throughout the story but her solution
to that is to become a cunt
and like she loses a bunch of weight
by just purging and shit
and then like once she gets skinny
she's just like a total bitch
there's a scene where this personal trainer
who had like wanted to work with her
but she like blew off the personal trainer
she didn't want to have to work for it
she just wanted to vomit her way to victory basically
and she meets the personal trainer again
and she's just saying some like some cunty shit to her
and then she leaves the restaurant
or whatever that they're at
and the trainer says to her assistant
the assistant's like oh well she lost a lot of weight
and she goes no
the fat was in her soul
there you go
I think I've seen that panel
like on 4chan or something
I know the comic
and I've definitely seen that panel
the fat was in her soul
you know it just makes me think I know we spent a while on this
but like it just I think like
people will get mad at you
like the thing that keeps coming to my mind is like
what if your wife has a baby
and she gains like a hundred pounds
while having the baby
it's like okay of course
and then help her work it back down
two years later
and we're still
I mean that's a thing
your first mistake was you got married
alright that was your first problem
and your second mistake was
once you have a kid
I don't know pity at all
I think if you have a kid
then you're not gonna be like
so concerned about how sexually attractive
your wife is you're a little more concerned about other things
it seems like a lot of guys
cheat after their fucking wife has
a baby and they get fat and unattractive
like let's avoid it
men's libido doesn't die down
what do you do
what do you expect
what you do is that you're clear to like your wife
in this case that like listen I love you
we had a kid I want to raise together
I gotta tell you though your fat as hell
and hashtag no fat checks
we need to work on this
you said I had like 10 more
voicemails right
look we're not gonna listen to all of them
wait we're not
well I mean we got like
like 50 there's no point
we probably got like 15 of them
that's like way too many to listen to all of I think
I just grabbed some random ones
we could probably go through them faster
I mean we 100% could
should we
play the next one
should we have it that
voicemail shouldn't be for questions
since we already have a question section
I mean
what would we prefer
I feel like if we're getting questions from voicemails
um
then we don't do questions but then that just means
people have to record and we won't take any
I mean we could do that I mean
I don't know I'm just throwing that out there we can think on it
depends on what we discuss it later
leave a comment
alright well let's get to another one here's one from
Mishin
this guy's a big patron guy
see him around alright let's see what he has to say here
Nate
he's pronounced Trafalgar
say it with me
Trafalgar
okay this guy
this guy has been told me that I say Trafalgar
or Trafalgar
Trafalgar
Trafalgar law
there's a character in one piece
that is named after a real person
who is called
he's named after
a battle
where somebody
was a pirate or a sailor
I don't know what I'm talking about
in London there's a place
called Trafalgar Square that's how you say it
Trafalgar
more like Trafalgar
Trafalgar we hold on
now I'm confused
because I go
to the underground
sometimes and I swear
they said the word before
I'll have to listen because I'll be traveling soon
so I'll have to pay attention if I pass it
how they pronounce it
yeah if you're around there let me know
let's get the real shit
Nate am I crazy
or did one of our weird
smattering of ritualistically
sung birthday songs in our family
did one of them mention Trafalgar Square
no way
I don't think so
let's review those
and get back to them
let's go through the entire list
right now
maybe we did
here's another one from
Gamer Dan
oh I love Game Grumps
yeah me too
hey guys
Gamer Dan here
I wanna know your opinion on
diegetic
things in games
they're good
diegetic
diegetic things
what do you mean by diegetic
non-diegetic
he's just fucking joking around
he doesn't mean anything that's not a real question
he's just goofing around
I thought we screened these
what do you mean no
diegesis explicit that we do not screen
I'm coming out
I'm coming out as anti-diegesis right now
I don't believe in it
is the next fucking call
that doesn't mean let's just move on
fucking hero trash you don't even speak
ok next one
this one's from Gazy Eric
Gazy Eric or something
alright what do you got
hey guys
girls like me
because you sound like that
you can't just live in the woods bro
you will be raped by bears
the bears will rape you
stop being afraid of the government
you need to be afraid of the bears
the government
you see the government works for you
but who do the bears work for
they just want to
right and that's why
you need to be afraid of the bears
they make bear mace
this
alright I pause it
this fucking Canadian idiot
there are no bears in the UK
I thought this was so random for you
probably
you really
you really just poked a hole
right in his
argument
you didn't even need to live in the UK
there is bear mace and there are shotguns
they are made to deal with bears
what if they sneak up on you
it's a fucking bear
you get bear dar
alright next one
yeah we sell bear dar
so we got that covered
if only Steve Hornet had that
you know sting radar
that is
alright here we go
Ligma
no PCP
you are stupid for being called the PCP
while your logo explicitly says
TPC
it's incongruent
it's a call out
wait what was that last bit
he said it's incongruent
it is incongruent
we talked about this
we talked about changing it
and we all agreed we should change it
just like everything else we do
we need more follow through
we have discussed this
the idea is that the channel and the group
are the procrastinators
and this particular podcast is the
procrastinators podcast
but we refer to ourselves as the PCP
for short because it sounds better
than TPC
also we can't say the TPC
just be the PCP
the PCP makes more sense
it's a clusterfuck our names are terrible
but
I still like the idea
despite
how difficult it is to say
we always say we're the PCP blah blah blah
I still prefer
the fact that we are the procrastinators
and this is one of the podcasts
we have the procrastinators drawcast
the PCD
we just don't use those abbreviations
and
we have other things
we kind of have a new thing
the races
actually
there's a thing that you'll
by now you'll have seen it already
it's the fucking
backseat gamers
backseat gaming
we should google that
we'll confirm that
you'll know what the actual title is
but this is the procrastinators present
backseat gaming live
there is a
show done by smosh
called backseat gaming
there is no channel called backseat gaming
but you know
it is smosh
so these videos have like a million views each
alright well whatever
here's another one
here's one from
slightly better guy ever
alright
well played
hello
I love that wine
podcast
Nate
in the same episode of the podcast
which is
expressed as a desire for
on the one hand
small government
in a libertarian sense of the word
and on the other hand
the goal of humanity should be
starfleet
I believe
should be pointed out to him
that star trek
is literally communism
no it's not
they're post scarcity
does communism even mean anything
in a post scarcity society
anytime someone says that they are missing
that in star trek you are allowed
to do whatever you want
there is no obligation
whatsoever there are people who live their whole lives
in hollow rooms just
fapping like all day
explicitly stated there are people who just
have escaped into hollow
reality because there is no
obligation to do anything in that world
I hear this too much it's disconcerting how
many times I hear this point so
slightly better guy ever you are in fact not
you're slightly worse guy ever
look star trek exists in a world
just to be super explicit where
like the economic system
known as capitalism and communism are
completely obsolete because there is
no need to control the distribution
of resources because everyone effectively
has infinite resources
at least in terms of like you can generate
food there is no need to worry about it
they've got whatever food generator
things I forget what they're called
to say that we need to still adhere
to the same paradigm as capitalism
or communism it doesn't work that same way
things have completely changed
because they've got the food assemblers
and whatever and like
sure it's fair to say that like I'm sure
big businesses are still out there
but like currency has
not really
you know what okay there is actually something to the argument
because trade still exists
there is still things and items
that you can't just replicate replicators
that's what they're called but like
people do exchange those
god you know what am I wrong here
I'm because like
when they trade with the Ferengi the
the Starfleet has to actually use things of value
like things that can't just be generated
and what is it it's like a gold
gold pressed latinum that's like
the currency that they love
gold pressed latinum
it's gold pressed latinum and you see what they do
is they take worthless gold
they take worthless gold that can be replicated
and they encase liquid
latinum within these gold bars
what the fuck is latinum
latinum is a fictional thing that is very valuable
and is like used for stuff
it's like it's like latinum but you without the
P in it it's valuable for some reason that I
can't remember um so you can use that like
they put it in gold because the stupid
people watching the show will know that it's
gold and shiny and worth something
that's right they encase it in worthless gold
explicitly worthless gold
because the human brain is wired
to respond to gold as if it were money
or something I'm sure that's why the show writers
chose to do that yeah I think that makes sense
in world as well but like
okay but in Starfleet alright if you're
let's say you're a person in the Federation
you've got like for example
there are like shipyards where they build
starfleets they use giant like
they use giant replicators
to produce ship parts that are then assembled
they have to like do that okay
if you've got a businessman who has one of
those and you've got somebody else
who like doesn't have one okay you know what
here's the issue is that the Federation
Federation itself is post scarcity
but there is a whole entire galaxy out
there still operating within
you know capitalistic enterprise in order to
interact with them you have to kind of lower yourself
down to these ancient capitalist
tradition and so well kind of kind of
but like there's like
within the Federation there's nothing
that's for like like communism enforces
you to say no you get this
and nothing else within the Federation
you can be a capitalist
it's just that like there's no point in
trading things like food because
everyone can just get infinite food all the time
so that industry gone doesn't matter anymore
you could trade like minerals and stuff
which you absolutely can do and
people do all the time so it's still
how does the how does how do you
stock a replicator with the
I'll tell you how the only thing a replicator
needs is power because a replicator
what it does is where'd you get that
well I know because the way replicator works
is it doesn't use anything except the
subatomic subatomic particles
that are scattered throughout the universe
in a basically infinite amount
it just reassembles those particles
from like the space within the replicator
just fucking makes it out of
cosmic background radiation
so you've got like
does it like suck up space dust
on the way and then it's got a full tank
of atoms
subatomic particles exist everywhere
all the time subatomic particles
you're a subatomic
tarticle
nailed it there's no amount of
like
stuff that you could make that would like use them up
they're just everywhere all the time
so that's how it works
dude what about a
scared post-it society
where the male doesn't arrive
we could like replicate our
wait shit I missed it
he said a
scared post-it society
where the male
never shows up on time
I have bad news for you
that's a real life
alright that was good
alright I think we answered this question
it's not a cognizant
what if we could replicate our weed bro
the point is like you can still
be a businessman at a federation
like if it was actual communism they would like kill you
if you try to be like
a businessman in a capitalist way
so don't worry about it
alright here's one and this will be like the last one
I think
this is the best idea
this is actually the best addition to the show
I'm the one who did this
I'm making all the credit
Tom's the one who set it up for us
really we'll escape from people
framing their shit exactly like
the biggest problem in the universe
voicemails
hopefully when they see the freedom
that they're given here
this is another one from our good friend
xxx epic gamer 420
xxx
let's see what he's got for us
is it playing?
nothing I don't hear anything
hang on let me disconnect
I'll try this
I did do that right
play go
how dare you insult my god damn
my quality munchie
this isn't okay
I was not dealing with this
I challenge you on the name of the lord
as a battle
on trek super slam
next week 5 o'clock
time zone you do see
okay
this is real shit I'm not gonna stand for this boy
okay I guess our good friend epic gamer
we'll have to pass this along
yeah we'll have to pass this along
also like it's weird that the PCPs come out like a week later
so I don't know exactly what like time
but apparently munchie's been challenged
for the game of epic shrek super slam
was that the game?
it appears to be a Nintendo DS
like a brawl game
that sounds good
it's also on gamecube
I guess
okay that's what he's talking about
and playstation 2
Jesus fuck
how is this even real
here's another one
this is from hentai is a japanese colloquialism
alright
what do we got
this question goes out to all the members of the pcp
if you can switch bodies with any member of the pcp
for a limited amount of time
and do whatever you want
side to body
and why
before we address that question
I just want to point out that hentai
is not a japanese colloquialism
but it is an american colloquialism
because that's true
the way that we use the word hentai
is not how it's used in japan
do they use it that same way
I mean what do they call it
the word hentai just means pervert
or strange over there
but the word ecchi means sex
and when they call something
like an ecchi game
this is like an h game
and I think that because of the fact that the word hentai
is used a lot in anime
especially in the 90's
like characters would call each other hentai all the time
and so like
when they call someone hentai
when in an anime they say
when a boy breaks into a girl's room
and she is naked and she screams hentai
she's actually using that as an adjective
she's describing how pervert she is
she's saying you are a pervert
she's calling him a pervert
now it's an adjective
she's describing the situation with this
adjective phrase
she's calling him a pervert
literally saying you pervert
hentai is mostly an insult to
it can mean pervert
or it can just be weirdo
if you called someone a hentai in another context
you might just be saying they are warped
in the head kind of thing
but it was a popular insult
especially in the 90's in anime
so when that shit came to America
we tried to give a name to porn
and we saw that they were called like h anime
which would be read as ecchi anime
we called it hentai
because we are conflating these two terms
this is how I understand the history anyways
so
hentai as a description of porn
is an American colloquialism
that's true
anyway what the fuck was the question
oh yeah if we could switch
be in someone's body
I would switch with Tom
I would draw something from a top down perspective
much more easily
and then I would leave
I would inhabit munchies body
so I could enslave humanity and bend them to my will
that's what I would do
yeah
I would inhabit munchies body
and then just jump through windows
I would probably inhabit any of you American guys
and eat all the American things I haven't tasted before
like a peanut burger and jelly sandwich
I still want to have them
do it to Ben so he could ruin his keto
it's the baby roost school
shooting all over again
oh that gives me a good idea
I would go into
any one of you American
boys bodies
and I would log into my pokemon go
catch loads of toys
spin loads of pokeballs
stop thinking
it saves on
flight money
and I could be at red corn
for as someone else
convenient
then we'd have to pay for the plane ticket
with your money
I would go into mage's body
and then I'd just look in a mirror and be like ah
this is what mage looks like
and then I'd go talk to biter in real life
I'd be like what's he like IRL
I'm gonna learn
the year you would do that though
because one fourth
of the year I'm in Lithuania
hence no biter
if I end up in Lithuania I will just
use your money that's not my money
to fly back
then you could meet the mysterious
cryptid that is
Grammy mage
see you later grandma
don'ts your head is in the toilet
I'm leaving
Grammy mage behind
goodbye
she's not called that
she's Archmage
she's an ancient wizard
the Archmage beckons
I just really like the prefix Arch
I would enter Tom's body
and commit crimes
because
he's too poor
to sue me
and bring a claim to court that it was actually
me
so he gets stuck with the rat
yeah
if you guys entered my body
would you be able to speak Lithuanian
I'm gonna go with it
I don't think so
oh I changed your mind you were saying yeah
I was bullied
I mean come on
what do you get the other person's knowledge
that's crazy
if you jump into their body
and you gain their knowledge then how much of it is
I mean if I gain their knowledge
then how much of it is she's body
just so I can understand
this is not a headmate
this is not a headmate situation
this is a freaking fighter
I agree
obvious
we've milked this question enough
it's a gold standard
I feel like we've had this question before
I don't remember ever answering
I like their answers better this time
well the problem with the question is that
the only person with a body
there to be in is Munchie
because the rest of us are all like
exactly the same and Munchie is like
like a towering monument
to Carnage
you should all want to swap into my body
to experience
to experience the mental and physical powers
I thought about going into Ben's body
so that I could be a human skunk
and just run people out of rooms that I don't like
Ben when you come over we have to take you to Keto World
that's an exaggeration
it's all the benefit none of the consequences
here's one more thing
if I couldn't be one of you guys
I would also want to be in Hippo's body
because then I could be like
I could have like this British accent
and then record funny stuff
with the funny accent
that's true
but it's not
like Hippo's accent
I like his accent more
when he says things
it's funnier than when I say things
that's of mysterious
that's true
okay here we go
next one from Munchie
you're right mage I can't take Hippo's
that's not funny
alright everyone shut the hell up
Munchie what do you got for us
I'm really passionate about
that land ownership topic
you guys touched on in the last episode
like if you live somewhere
for like 5 to 10 years
or whatever you get to own that place
so why are my parents kicking me out of the basement
this is fucking bullshit
I think
you got a case
just because
I don't have a job
I own this
it's the law
I think he's got a case
I'll give you a review of the aesthetics
of Isis's flag
thank you
I haven't seen that
I'll look that up
I know what it looks like
it's got that minimalism going on
oh
it looks like a fucking
Blackbeard's Jolly Roger
it looks like the cover of a Godspeed You Black Emperor album
yeah I like it
I gotta say
this is really turning me around
look at
I just googled it
it is kind of piratey
it's really piratey
it's sort of
I don't really care for the
font they used
I don't like how imperfect the circle is
what is with this bullshit
I like that
I think this would look
it's got that DIY aesthetic
I think it's pretty nice
it would be right at home in a zine
I guess that's true
this flag just screams India
they're pretty handy
I guess it does
but I will always prefer the Nazi
rigid German
efficiencies
perfect symbol
I know I think
I'm going with Isis
I think I'm going with Isis
it was inevitable
Ben's Isis I'm a Nazi
stay tuned for the next bonus episode
oh shit
not bad
we have to learn the languages
alright
what else we got here
do we want to comment on his whole
I think we all agree he deserves to live there
in the basement
yeah yeah yeah
contact your representative
call up Joe Biden
to join us
you know who I hear is
pretty good about property ownership
is Donald Trump
maybe give him a call
he probably would know how to handle this
you got to call the law offices
of Barry Feinstein
he's absolutely convinced you have a case
he can
probably talk your dad into giving you a small
loan of a million dollars
alright
this will be our last one
I could do these for another hour
but we got to get to the end
the other questions and stuff
alright this is our last one
this is from Shankins
let's see what you got brother
hey during Radcon 3
you guys did a Katamari LP
I paid a five dollars
to ask a question on the
live stream chat
but you guys never responded and ended up
ending the stream without looking at the chat
so I'll ask you guys
the same question that I did back then
again
is there any hard evidence
really hard evidence
just incredibly erect evidence
that the female orgasm exists
please respond
well
I've seen some hard evidence
I think
how do you know it's not faking
we can't perceive anything to be true
I'm going with no
I mean
wait no
I want to hear what you have to say about this
so that I can just
as I can tell you
that it does exist
but
ok but consider this
we can only be sure that our own
consciousness exists
with that logic
you guys' orgasms don't exist
so to say
I completely agree you can't prove the male orgasm
I mean there's like a physical
product of a male
orgasm you know
is it also for the other one
there's no yes
I mean you can't tell the difference between
what even is it
like what is expelled there and what is expelled there
I mean really what are we talking about here
I'm going to stop
by the way
I'm going to stop now
how embarrassing for her
it's because we're getting close to the truth
and we can't
yeah exactly I think we have to call it here
there's no evidence provided to this day
would you be more comfortable if we were debating
the male orgasm
they're equally non-existent as far as I'm concerned
I think that's really
regardless of the gender
orgasm is a social construct
doesn't actually exist
that is true actually
I think that that
well
well it depends on if you consider
we didn't have sex we just sort of came out of the ground
I think there's
a difference between
I think there's a difference between coming and
orgasm and
I think that that difference
are you sure about that
is that based on anything
no I'm not sure anything anymore
oh I'm going to cooom and then you do it
do you have to say is that what makes it an orgasm
it's like a dragon ball of the attack
you have to do it in the name of the attack before you do it
I consider an orgasm
to be when it's like a full body experience
what
well I don't think that's medically
an orgasm this is
what it is
I don't feel it in my whole body
but like I definitely know what it is
and when it's happening
maybe it does exist but like no one has truly
no human could possibly experience it
because it would like explode
like a nuclear bomb
I guess it all just depends on where you draw the line
on what is or isn't an orgasm
I'm just looking at pictures of baby ducks
alright I think it's like the speed force
it's like a force that exists outside
of us that we tap into
when we reach that higher level existence
I think that makes sense
I'm going to run with that
so an answer to your question
dear viewer, no
as fake as you are to us
as we are to each other
it makes sense to me
we're all just phantoms
we're all just shadow phantoms
you're the only thing that exists
we're all humans of each other
but phantoms in a dream
alright with that said
I think that was all the ones that I converted
I have to fucking go through and download
and put them on SoundCloud anyway
I think that was all of them so we're done with that
alright let's get a pity question too in here
wrap this motherfucker up
oh there's a question directed at me
that I want to answer because
it's about my favorite topic ever
Kajiro's bitter story
do you dream about monsters mage?
that's a good question Tom
Kajiro's bitter story
I think
Kajiro, Kajiro, but yeah
mage have you ever had a dream
that predicted the future
like how I saw the title of the next bonus
I dreamed a dream that mage wouldn't talk about her dreams
shush shush shush
I am talking
alright
like how I saw the title of the next bonus episode
talking while eating in a dream yesterday
I was finishing his question
that's cool that you did
yes I actually
I think there were several occasions
but one that I remember clearly
to this day that it still freaks me out
is like okay so like I was like
11 to 12 years old
and I had a dream about like this
amazing park and this big ass tree
that I never saw before I never been there
but I had a dream that I was walking there
and then like fast forward to like two years later
I'm in England
for the first time in my life 14 years old
walking in this park
like holy crap
this is the park I had a dream about
and there we go
and I think
you can continue
oh thank god
I had a dream about 9-11 happening
the day after it happened
because I was so distraught
and I love
9-11
good
you were distraught that it was over
and you'd never get to experience it again
yeah I was too young
it's before my time
it's not fair I never got to see the original broadcast
so that was a pity question
from Twitter right?
no I think that was from the thing
that was from the chat
I see a question here
from Rusty Shackleford were any of you
ever chunebio when you were younger
and I want to say I'm still chunebio
sometimes
when I'm alone I mean sometimes I still
just strike a pose
I'm like conjuring energy blasts
from my hands just to make myself feel good
about myself
I don't think we need to remind you about Nate in high school
with the vampire hunter D hat
and the fucking
you know and when I was a kid
and being completely silent
at all times because he thought
it would make you more mysterious
I wasn't much better
I had that red leather coat
that I got for a red mage cosplay
and then I wore it to school
even though it was way too hot
and more chune I'd say
I mean I guess we were just playing
when I was a kid at summer camp
me and this kid I think his name was David
I can't really remember
we literally said to each other
no no no David, Nate
I have superpowers
wait you did this?
I just lied I just told vicious lies
that I just had superpowers
I said like dude
I'm gonna rub my feet on the floor
and then I'll touch something felt
and it'll be a zap
it'll be nuts
that's clearly me having superpowers
and then I lied about how I one time made a big energy ball
and it was fucking dope
I spent a while believing
that I was God
and that everyone else was just my dream
my brother Victor
I still think
at one point that he could manipulate fire
if he tried hard enough
me and my friends in high school
we were
vociferously researching
developing telekinetic powers
and we were trying to develop them
we were doing research and reading articles
and trying to do it
one time he told me that he did do it successfully
I didn't believe him
but it was an actual
hardcore effort for a while
well that's cool
to develop telekinetic powers
when I was
I respect that
I seriously believed
for like a number of months
after reading
the volume 2
of Dragon Ball the Manga in the library
alone
that Kamihameha could be possible
I've tried many times
I've tried as well
but I realized that that was stupid
and then I thought the much more rational explanation
the much more rational way to become Goku
is just to wear
weights around my feet
and never take them off
and I would walk around all the time
I asked for Christmas as a present leg weight
and I would wear them a lot
and I tried to jump
and I was convinced that it was working
because when it took off the heavy weights
I felt lighter therefore I'm jumping high
remember when Krillin and Goku
wore the turtle shells and they took them off
and they jumped so high
I was actually thinking about Samurai Jack
when you were talking about the leg weights and jumping
when I was like 10 or younger
I think I was absolutely convinced
I will become a magical girl
didn't you
her magic was just knives
and guns
when I was like 15
God damn it
when I was like 15 I was convinced
I was going to become a magical girl
and you did
you know
Hummer is the kind of magical girl that I like
she just uses tons of weapons
that was pretty dope
but she does have like a void closet
where she keeps them
yeah she does have hammer space
it's not like she's totally not powerful
I never thought that I had
powers I don't think
but I did think
that I was like a super genius
who could basically do anything
given the proper
like if I put my mind to it
yeah
and I was pretty edgy
I also made like origami shuriken
threw them around
when I was 8
I told my friends I could see pokemon
which I didn't
yeah I was like oh they're all around
no that was pokemon go that's on the game
yeah that was pokemon go
I guess that was another dream that predicted the future
kind of
it kind of
went really far though
we all like
I don't even want to get into that story
but one of the things we did
that kind of surprised me to this day
that it didn't freak me out
there was like this kindergarten
next to one of my friends houses
and I was like well you see
you can't see the pokemon
but when they died they leave bones behind
so let's try and find all of the bones
that are scattered in this kindergarten
and assemble a pokemon skeleton
and one thing is
in the kindergarten
we found enough
fucking bones to actually assemble
something that looked like a creature
whoa
yeah is this real?
did this really happen?
it was a war zone after all
yeah this like
horrifying ghost apocalypse
that is
what mage forgot to
tell her gullible friends
that she was actually just
assembling all the bones of the corpses
she'd murdered here
and she was getting rid of the evidence
she was getting them to dispose of the evidence
the violent violence does not leave any traces behind
yeah
also
guileful
clever and guileful
in her violence
here's a question
here's a pity question that is intriguing me
from a dank wizard
aka flameonfieri
um
have y'all seen those
new CGI animated
sex ads of fucking fortnite
and overwatch characters
then play almost every porn video now
and it plays a wicked loud
annoying ass song during it
how is no one talking about this
why don't you have adblock?
why are you on porn sites without adblock?
that seems like you don't understand
adblock?
i have adblock
adblock was created to avoid situations like this
i'm gonna go to you porn right now
well apparently it doesn't work
adguard is bulletproof
alright
i've watched a lot of CGI
overwatch porn
but that's of my own volition
that is like the least appealing thing
i can imagine
i just really like CGI porn
overwatch has great porn
not the CGI porn
the source filmmaker
wait
wait hold on
hold on somebody fucking likes CGI porn
what the fuck
CGI porn is like my favorite porn
CGI is like
literally the worst thing porn
i mean it's like that's a big negative
that's a big minus
points in my book
i like it a lot
i'll have to show you
i gotta send you some
i gotta send you some of the really impressive shit
cause there's every
most of it is really lazily done
but every once in a while someone will like
actually go out of their way to like
animate entirely through like a whole
scene you know
like not just repetitive motion but like an actual
animation and that shit is fucking
mind blowing
yeah it can be pretty impressive
it's blowing something besides your mind
alright
okay okay yeah like
like anything i'm sure it can be done well
i have seen some that is done well
but yeah that
alright but i mean aside from the CG
thing just the overwatch
characters i hate them they make me mad
i think diva is so popular
they just make tons of it
it's not so much a matter of that i would
seek it out as that if you are
someone who is trying to find CG porn
and like you think
diva is acceptable then you're gonna end up
watching a lot of it
yep of course
well none of the other ones are hot
they have a question for me but i don't want
to answer it because i feel like
i'll drag out the joke too much this episode
okay fair enough
i think
i think may is pretty hot is she the eskimo
oh yeah the big
the chinese lady
she's not an eskimo she's chinese but she does wear that big bulky coat
she's
like an iso climber
because she's like working at the south pole or something
she's doing like she's an environmentalist
well she's cute i like her
yeah i mean yeah she's pretty cute
although she's
her actual body type is excellent
but she looks like she would
be fat when she's wearing her coat
but she is in fact not fat
that's probably my favorite like great
cucking that happened in recent years is that
like after oh like the fatties were like
yeah we've got fat representation
i feel it until like well into
the game being out like what she actually
looks like under the coat so like fan artists
had largely drawn her as fat for like
fucking eight months or something
don't get me wrong i can understand fat people
like wanting fat representation to feel like
that's fine but i would always prefer just a way
hotter chick i'm always gonna want that
plus it was just hilarious to watch
that happen
agreed
do we want any more questions
we're pretty much
ben what were you saying
i was saying i'm trying to find like
some official image of what she looks like
under the coat because i haven't seen it
okay watch there's a whole CGI short
of her like the official overwatch one
like that is tons of like you can see
i think that you might you might be able
to find an image where
it was like a song festival thing
there was like a spray you could get
that had an image of her like playing
like tennis or something and she was
not fat and i
remember that was like the spark that set off
the whole social justice
fucking insanity
because they were just like she's not
the where the roles i can't do it
and just like thank god thank god this character
isn't ruined the where the roles
um the
uh diva's probably
number two
i mean i think widowmaker is pretty much number one
i am o
i like tracer
the blue one but she's a lesboy
in you can't you can't
tracers tracers alright
tracers alright
it's all about widowmaker widowmaker's ass is
absolutely ungodly alright i don't want to hear
about fucking overwatch bitches anymore
alright this is actually terrible and i feel
that
um alright
is there anything else going on here um
um these questions are all shit
um how do you
how do you deal with aging parents
leave them on the hills if they're not polite
yeah make guy from geyser
oh by the way the other oh yeah
from geyser how do you deal with aging parents
uh pray that pray that they don't call
uh put off answering them
for as long as possible and just wait for important
there is one important question in here fridgen
asks what's your favorite sandwich
uh steak bomb
and or just philly cheese steak
in general
i like i like a ham sandwich
that's just i need to eat more sandwiches
that's a sandwich huh um
if you want if you want to get my if you
want to curry my favor in a public setting
buy me a philly cheese
is a wrap a sandwich
i'll tell you what my favorite is
if it counts i'm going with a straight up
lobster roll
i love lobster rolls so much
they are the best they're always super expensive
and they're delicious i think it's
i love them but wait
but wait is it is it a sandwich
if it's on a roll that's the question
i need two slices of red
if i just take the bun
dude is cereal a sandwich
because it's sandwiched between two layers
of the bowl on each side
isn't lasagna just a stack
of pasta sandwiches
alright guys
let's
i want to answer that
pre keto
i probably would have said the ruben
although now that you mentioned the lobster roll
that's a pretty strong contender too
but i really like rubens
but now that i'm keto
lettuce wrap burgers go to fucking
i don't know
what part of a lettuce wrap burger is a sandwich
well the lettuce is the
and it's meat between things
yeah fair enough
what was the place between
two things completely wrapped
it's enclosed
let's just count in the wraps
because i haven't had that many sandwiches
tell them the place
i'm dying to know the place
but what was the place we went
after the miyazaki movie
after nine inch nails
miyazaki's classic film
oh it was called
burger stop
or some shit like that
it's just like a regular ass name
whatever anyway the gorgonzola
burger there is a great burger
get a lettuce wrap
i think it was literally called burger stop
it was not burger stop
it was called burger go
oh how silly
i don't remember what it was called
all i know is that i like italian subs a lot
they're delicious
i got an italian sausage right here
it's an italian sausage
if we're counting wraps
i would actually really like to
have a taste of all the
oh it's tasty burger
i would like to have a taste of all these burgers
wraps and sandwiches you guys mentioned
because i haven't tasted
i haven't
seen them being sold
in the uk
and it's usually like your standard BLT
in ham and
mage come down for radcon
we'll take you on the sandwich tour
if we're
next radcon's in boston though
let's get some lobster rolls
oh it's the best
mage
there are pizza places
but when i'm in lefina
i don't eat much pizza
when i'm in the uk i eat some pizza
i'm just
i'm just asking because in poland
i noticed there were a lot fewer
there were way fewer pizza places
than there are in america
in america there's lots of them
there's lots of chains but in poland
there was like one in lublin
there was like one or two places you could get a pizza
and they were kind of weird
something was just a little different
about the pizza that they made over there
i don't know
japan pizza was like a big special thing
same with the burgers
no place that wasn't mcdonald's
served a burger that just tasted
like a burger
there was a different quality
it's not like
you ran into the culture
the place i live in currently in lefina
the nearest mcdonald
is like
a over a 60 minute walk
on foot and i can be bothered
what is the
what type of food restaurant
is the most common surrounding
let me think
about lefianian
restaurants i guess
question mark
just like what is a food
what would be the main item
on the menu at the places around you
the thing that everybody gets
i have a follow up question
in the philippines everywhere sells adobo
like chicken adobo
is just like it's a staple
it's on every menu at every store
i don't go to many restaurants
that's the thing though but
oh well
ok mage i am curious
what are some chains
what are some restaurant chains
that are common around here
there's a chili pizza
never heard of it
like the pepper
like the chili pepper
i know i've got one
what other ones
boy you got me
i don't pay attention
too much because i don't go to restaurants too much
alright fair enough
there's definitely a few pizza chains
i can tell you that much
i just don't pay attention to them
i'm not asking just about pizza
the only chains i know
i can remember seeing
usually pizza chains
all mage eats his pizza
yeah that makes sense
well she also eats birds milk
as we learned
in the bonus episode
pageruns.com
let's answer the question
to find out what the fuck birds milk is
i didn't know birds produced milk
ah
well then you'll find out
we'll learn something new every day
i actually answered the question
from the very small amount
of sandwich like things that i've eaten
i really like hoisin duck wraps
but only if i add mayo to them
so there we go
hoisin duck wraps
whoa i wanna try that
that's not a thing i could find easily here
it's not too fancy but it's nice
it's just like basically duck meat
and lettuce in a wrap
that's why i add mayo
because it adds to them
swap that you
and that sounds like my kind of meat
if you know what i'm saying
do you understand the joke
i mean the serious point
that's it everybody thanks for listening this episode
you see calculations appearing on screen
mathematical formulas everywhere
okay i just got it
right as you said
thanks for listening everybody
pageruns.com
the procrastinators
one dollar get in the lounge
questions answered you know the whole fucking drill
five dollars bonus episodes
talk while eating it's a masterpiece
you're gonna want to see that shit
it is a masterpiece i made sure of it
there's that and 15 other old episodes
for a mere five dollar pledge
oh what a steal it is at this point
get in there give us money
listen to them and have a great time
follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators
we forget a notification
remember to ask us those fucking questions
and subscribe
so you get our live streams
and then also subscribe to imgames
more games
indeed
we're playing red dead redemption now
and uh
also subscribe
to twitch.tv
slash saint comics
just go to the description
and go to everybody's shit we all do shit
we're all people we all got a million things
look at all our things look at everything
spread us to your friends tell your kids
tell your wife hide your kids hide your wife
then bring them back out then tell them again
force feed everybody everything
give me money
please
there you go
i asked nicely you can't say no
thanks for being here people
we'll see you next week
go have a beautiful time
goodbye