Hello everybody and welcome to another explosive Diarrhea episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We're Diarrhea coming out of my mouth right now.
I feel like shit. I'm Tom Oliver and today I'm introducing this band of rascals with me, starting with my good boy Digibro.
Just slammed six fucking spicy octopus dumplings down the gullet and I'm fucking ready to go.
Oh god, that's gonna be real Diarrhea soon. Endless Jess is here.
I'm on the pursuit of happiness and I know everything that shines ain't always gonna be good. Everybody sing along, I'll be good.
Best of luck to you my boy. Mage is here.
How do you draw snakes? I forget.
There's like squiggly lines and then put a little like V-tongue on the end of them.
Oh no, I know a little friend. I love snakes.
Speaking of snakes, Nate is here.
Oh god, is it them snakes? Is he back with another fire track?
Speaking of them snakes, we have the poor the poor man's substitute for them snakes.
Benzane. Ray Misato, Arigato, kakakakawaii.
Wait a minute, did she say Ray and Misato as an Evangelion?
That was a substitution of my own because I don't know the actual words.
Well, it was good. Thanks. I thought I thought it through really carefully.
One minute in and I don't know what you're talking about already.
It's like an Avril Lavigne, the Hello Kitty song. You're one of the greatest artists of the 20th century.
This is real. I stayed away from that.
It came out about like 10 years ago or something, but yeah, she made a mainstream for me.
People got a little mad at her for some cultural appropriation, you know, obvious bullshit.
Nate and Ben, are you aware that Avril Lavigne did two songs for the ending of a one piece movie?
Yes. And one of them is a Nickelback cover.
What? Okay, I wasn't aware of that.
It's like it's like an acoustic folk Nickelback cover as the ending theme of a one piece movie
performed by Avril Lavigne.
Everything you just said, she was she was she was married to the Nickelback guy.
Oda did draw Avril Lavigne in one piece style because of their like buddy friendship or whatever.
That's awesome. I mean, I think she just came out with a new album.
Holy shit.
Unless I'm mistaken. I think pretty sure I heard that on the grapevine.
My whole word.
Here it is. Oh my gosh.
Look at this shit. I gotta see this. Please.
Okay. Cabin, it'll be in the show notes, obviously, or whatever.
Avril's back.
I always knew she would be.
Look at Avril Lavigne drawn by Oda.
He did this because they're because he's a fan or something.
Bizarre.
It looks good though, right? I think so.
I mean, in as much as Oda's drawings of women can look good, it looks fine.
They, well, that's silly things to say.
Ooh. One, doesn't look particularly like Avril.
Two, not Oda's best face.
Maybe it wasn't literally one. It probably was.
Yeah, it's close. It's fine. Yeah, it'll do.
I'll take it.
Thanks Oda.
I haven't watched any of the new movies.
Oh, I'll leave it.
Destroy it.
So what else is going on, people?
Who's got things on the table?
Well, hey, you know what I had, you know what it did yesterday?
Yeah.
Had fucking RFCKCon2.
Rowdyfuckers con killers.
Did you even know that was going on until I saw the live streams on my feed?
Yep.
Yep. The bunch of killers, bunch of Rowdy showed out in Boston.
We met up at Faniel Hall.
We had some IRL gang violence where they split up into teams
and they had to go around and shoot each other in real life.
I heard that someone won, that there was a winner.
How was that decided?
Okay, okay. So I came up with this game.
I actually came up with it a long time ago, but this was the first time.
It was called Endless War.
No.
Yes.
This was the first time we had the chance to do it.
Okay, so we split up into teams.
Luckily, we had four killers and four Rowdies, and so it worked out perfectly.
And basically, we defined a perimeter and we were like, okay,
I'm going to give the abbreviated version.
Basically, it's like, within the zone, you have your camera.
You have to run around and look for enemies and take pictures of them,
and then post the picture of them in a certain channel in a certain discord
we set up for it, and that's a shot and that kills them.
And basically, it's like a quick draw.
So if two people see each other, it's like, who can take a picture and post it first,
and they get the shot off first, and they win, and the other one's dead.
Fascinating.
And it was a shootout, and Connor, Connor the Rowdy, did win, but it was close.
It came down to Connor versus Shraft?
Or Sauce?
Not Sauce, but it was, yeah, but yes.
The Rowdies won by a hair, and I will kill them.
Well, that's pretty cool.
And it was a hoot.
It's a dope system.
And then we went and we live-streamed Kazi's dad's house, and that was RSCKCon,
and it took all day, and it was really fun.
Are people still traveling in for these, or is this just people who are in Boston at this point?
It was about half and half.
It really terrifies me.
You are in control of a cult, and you really should be leading into it a lot more.
Um, there was, um, Kip was there, he's from Texas, uh, I think Texas.
Fucking Texas!
Sauce Pirate was from New York.
How are they affording to fly in for these?
They've been saving up their good boy points for years at this point.
Well, they've been mining in the mines.
They've built up a bunch of slime coin, you know, before they-
Some of them still have some left over from the great slime coin market boom.
Of the pre-Negapause days, you know, that went a long way.
Okay, so what I've been doing for the last few days
is I've been, like, marathoning this podcast, called Who Are These Podcasts,
that is a podcast that reviews other podcasts, mostly to shit on them, and-
Can we get on there?
Probably, but, uh, it's- because I've been listening to it, it's, you know,
put a lot of things in my head about, like, what a podcast should or shouldn't be like.
And so I'm just, like, analyzing our podcast as we're doing it, and all I can think is,
this is the least comprehensible fucking podcast ever.
Sure.
Like, we've gone for seven and a half minutes, and nothing we've talked about is something that
anyone could possibly know what the fuck we're talking about.
Like, like, aside from, like, Avril Lavigne-
The endless war fanbase would beg to differ.
Avril Lavigne be in a one piece-
Marathoning at the mouth.
Like, I'm thinking, if you don't know anime, you don't know what we're talking about,
why it's interesting that Avril is in a one piece thing, and we even, like, we say Oda,
we're talking about the author of one piece, but we don't say that.
Who wouldn't know that?
The most-
Who in this wide world?
And then, like-
Well, I mean, as you- I mean, we are- we are the premiere anime podcast on-
It's true.
The internet, so everyone should be telling you-
I'm not- I'm not even complaining.
I'm just saying that, like, uh, it's just occurring to me.
We're doing everything wrong from a marketing perspective.
Absolutely true.
Tell me more, Digi.
I'm actually very interested, and this is a great line of inquiry,
and I'm interested to hear any thoughts you have on this subject,
because I think about this all the time.
Okay.
Um, was that it?
What- what-
Would you mean the quality of the podcast or something?
Yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Let's talk about what a- what a bizarre clusterfuck the PCP is.
The PCP is-
Sure.
It's- it's extremely bizarre, for sure, and definitely a huge clusterfuck, but, like,
at the same time, that is the only reason anyone cares, I think.
Like, it's- it's a podcast who- which only exists to serve the audience it already has.
It's a show about nothing.
Pretty much.
It's- it's a show about, like, just-
It's just us, just the people who are members,
smash together once a week to talk about whatever.
But, like, because of the fact that we- we take it for granted that the audience is,
you know, following- it's really funny, especially because, like, a lot of our audience
doesn't follow all of us, like, individually or really know anything about, like,
there are some people who listen to PCP and it's, like, they're just a fan of, say, Nate,
who listens to this and thinks of it as this podcast, Nate's On,
and then has no idea who the rest of us are.
Ah, yes, the capricious Nate heads.
Fucking Roseboys.
I just have to wonder what it even- what it sounds like we're talking about to- to anyone like that,
you know? Like, what do- do they just listen and they're like,
I have no idea what's going on?
You know, one of our- one of our longtime fans, Oblivion Fall,
of great professionalism and renown, um, he, uh, he described the other day.
This wasn't about, like, the quality or anything.
He's obviously followed all of us for the- most of us, anyway, for a long time.
But he said that, like, the PCP was his- someone said I- like, someone submitted an entrance for the,
for the theme contest and they said, like, uh, you know,
lol, I procrastinated on this.
Does that mean I get bonus points?
And then Oblivion Fall, I think, replied, said something like,
actually, I find the procrastinator's podcast, like,
the most beneficial thing for me to enhance my productivity.
Something about it, he finds very conducive to doing his work.
I don't know what that is.
I think on a recent episode, we addressed the- the irony of the fact that none of us are really major
procrastinators.
Like, well, you know, it's one of those things- it's one of those things that's like,
when you have a- when you have a astrological sign, like, I'm a cancer,
you can go searching for the ways that that actually does, you know, pin- it's the religious
mindset.
You find ways to, like, justify beliefs you already have.
I mean, we all do that about everything.
But, like, because of procrastinator, I mean, I do procrastinate on quite a bit,
so I'm like, yeah, that totally works.
I'm thinking of confirmation bias, all the ways I totally do procrastinate in a week.
But I mean, everyone procrastinates to one degree to one degree to another.
I think it's- it's a weird word, though, because, like, when you think about procrastination,
like, I put things off to the last minute, but not because I'm not doing anything.
It's like, I will find- if I know that there's a deadline, I would rather do it
right before the deadline and then cram in other shit to do before that.
And I don't really know why I operate that way, but, like- but I've never passed the deadline.
Like, I've always managed this very well.
I've never been late on these kinds of things.
So, it's funny, like, when I think of- when most people say that they procrastinate,
I think they are talking about something way worse than what I'm doing, you know?
Like, those alimony payments or, you know, whatever.
Although I have procrastinated on my taxes for a couple years, so.
Fair enough.
You know, this reminds me just of the cardinal sin that will make me hate you, listeners or fans.
If you do not put a space, when you're writing the name of the pro space,
Crastinator's podcast, I- some people actually committed this vile sin
in their submissions to the editor contest, and I'm just letting you know,
this will be a strike against you.
Oh, God.
My fucking peach, uh, uh, amiibo just fell and hit my router.
I was waiting for you to say your peach fresca.
I wish I had one of those.
But I don't.
Okay, what else is going on, people?
I'm bored.
This sucks.
Yeah, this is terrible.
Well, um-
Wait, you're like- you keep saying that, but you have nothing.
What- did you not think of anything before the show?
I've got nothing.
You're absolutely right.
Hey, let me scrape the bottom of the barrel here.
I'm off keto for, like, a day.
Was this, like, a cheat day?
I had a milkshake at RFC K-Con.
Then I had a beer and a cupcake.
Ah, I was decadent.
I'm surprised to hear that you're still doing keto because-
What's working?
I would assume that your kidney stone had something to do with it.
You know, everyone assumes that, and everyone says that.
But then I go and I look it up, and I find no data backing up that assertion.
I mean, where do you think you got it from, then?
Like-
From my kidney.
The kidney stone fairy.
Blessed him one day.
I mean, like, what generally causes kidney stones?
Like, have you done something that would have caused it?
I mean, this, okay, I've been complaining about this.
Everyone has their own, like, oh, obvi-
Of course you got a kidney stone, obviously, because you do X,
but, like, everyone's X is different.
And, like-
Sure.
So, like, what am I supposed to make of it?
Like, some people think it's obviously because-
Do everything different, man.
Some people think it's because it's obviously because of keto.
Some people think it's obviously because I drink sodas,
or because obviously because artificial sweeteners, or-
It's my bet.
Are those known to do that, though?
I don't know.
It's a perfect storm of all those Ben-Saint activities.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I kind of thought so.
I don't know.
I did some cursory googling the other day, and I didn't-
I came away with the feeling that, like,
I was less sure about any of these things, like,
oh, this definitely caused it.
I mean, you can just get them.
Some people just get them, you know?
Some people just get cancer, even if they don't smoke or whatever.
Hey, total left turn, but I actually do have something I want to talk about.
I want to quickly just mention something about keto.
I've been listening to a lot of, like, stupid reddit readings about, like,
stupid threads or whatever, and, like, the anti-MLM thread.
And I've noticed a sort of a surge in MLM.
MLM is in multi-level marketing?
Yeah.
As in the PC pyramid scheme.
Indeed.
No, that's nothing like the pyramid scheme,
even though it's called the pyramid scheme.
It's called the pyramid scheme ironically.
Give us money now.
It'll be great for marketing purposes.
True fans know it's named ironically,
and donate all their money to it.
Anyway, and they are very keen on selling you keto products now,
so that's making me suspicious of keto.
Because they're like, oh, keto coffee.
You lose weight.
What a stupid way to reason through life.
Ben, have you ever been to, have you been to a vitamin shop recently
or passed by one in your travels?
No.
God, no.
If you have, you would notice that every single one of them
have big signs on the front now that say,
keto headquarters, get all your keto shit here.
Probably due to the whole, you know, there's like, there's companies,
and I mean, there's one company called Bulletproof,
but it's not the only one.
There's a bunch.
And they just sell shit.
But like, they just sell you food that's keto.
But like, here's, you can just go to the fucking supermarket
and buy like, butter and like, meat and like, cheese.
People are dumb.
And like, yeah.
You don't, like, they'll sell you.
It's so much easier, Ben, to just go to the,
go to your vitamin shop and buy the F-bomb.
They'll sell you.
It's literally called the F-bomb.
It's this bomb-shaped supplement.
It's just, and it's all just fat.
So they call it the fatbomb.
I think it's, yeah, bomb.
They'll sell you, they'll sell you a branded version.
They'll sell you a powdered version
in a smaller container for more money.
They'll put, they'll put things on the label.
They'll talk about the branch chain amino acids,
that whatever the fuck it is,
when it's just, it's just coconut oil or whatever.
I think people just convinced themselves
that they have to do something special for it to work.
That like, it couldn't possibly be
that the stuff is just at the grocery store they always go to.
It can't be as easy as just eating bacon
and losing weight.
It's impossible.
Yeah.
And yet, it's entirely possible.
There's a great video by the needle drop
about being vegan cheap because like,
lots of people say like,
I can't go vegan because it's expensive to buy healthy food.
And it's like, no, it's not.
Vegetables and fruit are like the cheapest thing
you can get at the fucking grocery store.
Like, you can buy bananas and fucking apples
for basically nothing.
Like 25 cents a piece or something.
Right.
They're carrots.
Oh man, I've been buying so many bananas recently.
Yeah.
All of those are extremely cheap.
So it's like, just because you're going vegan
doesn't mean you have to go buy fucking veggie burgers
or some shit.
The problem with that is that like,
yeah, fruits and vegetables are cheap,
but that's not a meal.
It's just a fruit and a vegetable.
Well, sure.
Like, it doesn't feel like I'm eating something
unless I've cooked a plate with a bread and a meat set.
That's the thing is that like,
people are making the argument of like,
I can't go vegan because it's expensive.
But it's like, well, the point of veganism,
if you're doing it, is that you're trying
to make some kind of moral stance.
So it's like, you're basically saying,
I'm putting my comfort above this moral stance.
And it's like, well, at that point,
you've defeated the purpose of it.
You know, like, just eat what you want to eat.
Like, if you're not going to, if you don't care,
if you don't feel strongly enough about it to commit to this lifestyle,
you know.
I don't know if Fantano's point was this or not,
but I, with some people talking about it,
people are just dumb and super ignorant,
and they just don't know these things.
Which I think was the point of this video,
to just educate people.
People, they just think that veganism is expensive,
and they don't actually know like,
what goes into being vegan or otherwise.
I don't know that much about veganism,
but I would have meant like, you know,
like getting your, getting the protein,
getting the proteins hard, and like,
It takes some work.
You probably got to get it from like,
Just eat nuts, like bees.
Something.
Yeah.
Isn't there something like, like,
like beans are like an incomplete protein?
Like if you're, you know, like,
if you're getting like vegetable protein,
you have to eat like the right, like,
different kinds combined.
The last class I ever took to get my
computer science degree was a biology course,
and I learned actually some fascinating facts in there,
which are, when you consume anything that like,
has protein in it, like beans or meat,
or anything like that,
they, the proteins consist of a certain select set
of the amino acids that human beings use
to assemble the like, you know,
muscle and protein stuff in our own bodies.
Yeah.
And so, like, if any beans.
But animal protein is complete protein,
because it's basically the same shit.
I would think that it's more complete, yes.
Oh, I know, is I don't believe anything
Anthony Fantano says, because I don't,
Fair it out.
I don't, I can't trust a man who reviews music
for a living and doesn't give every Red Hot Chili Peppers
album a 10 out of 10.
Even the newest one?
That would be the last one.
Yeah, sure, why not?
Oh, all right.
That's all I felt when I listened to it.
I was like, yeah, okay, sure, why not?
It's 10 out of 10.
Fair enough.
All right, what do you think about this, people?
Let me drop this bomb on you.
I want to talk about the Mathematosis
notification of people's opinions.
And the large extent of that.
Yeah, that's what it is.
So, Mathematosis, so whatever.
I think Breath of the Wild came out,
I think in 2016, maybe 2017.
So it's been like two or three years or whatever.
Yeah, God, it's that long?
It's been a while, yeah.
It was on the Wii U, so, you know.
What the fuck?
The Switch hasn't been out that long, has it?
No, well, I don't know, probably two or three years by this point.
It came out in March, I think, over two years ago.
Oh my God.
So, Mathematosis, years later, comes out with his review.
And this happens with other people.
I'm just using him as the example here.
And basically, to my mind, he was shockingly positive.
And I was not expecting this and was not prepared for it.
And coincidentally, I've already been replaying Breath of the Wild
by just, I had no idea he was making this video.
I was already like halfway through.
And I was basically playing the exact way
I had played the first time and still having a lot of fun.
But all my same complaints were still there.
And here's my point, here's my point.
I'm seeing a lot of threads on like V and stuff,
where people saying like, you know, they'll point to like one review
Mathematosis did of like God of War.
And they'll be like, haha, yeah, Matt's on my side.
God of War was shit.
And it wasn't great or something like that.
And then like the Breath of the Wild one comes out
and everyone like is ignoring it because it's not in line
with the general consensus or whatever.
And I'm sure other people have been swayed by it.
I don't know.
And in the video itself, he talks a lot about like,
basically what I gleaned was that he was focused on a lot of stuff
that a lot of people enjoyed about the game
that I did not get a lot out of.
Like all the crazy mechanical stuff you can do
with the systems that are in place.
And he seems to downplay a lot of things I didn't care for
and upplay the ones that he liked more.
So I don't know.
That's what a reviewer should do.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
Like he's just stating his opinion.
It may or may not completely overlap with mine.
You know, in this case, obviously not.
Okay.
But so what's my point is my point is
Matthew Matosa seems to be a real.
What's the word?
Like a trendsetter or like a thought leader?
A thought leader.
That's the word.
And I don't know.
I guess I'm just curious because he's not even like the biggest voice,
but there's something about him that makes people
just really take him seriously.
And I guess this ties into our old discussion about like the
what's Joseph Gordon Anderson, whatever his name is.
Well, it's professionalism.
Matthew Matosa doesn't have any like huge embarrassments
or fuck ups or, you know, retardation to his name.
Does Anderson?
Nothing to piss anyone.
Yeah, Anderson released a video that people interpreted as like
firing back at his commenters.
And I guess he's like shitty on streams and he's bad at games.
So, you know, people can't have that.
So, so there's a there's a noticeable vocal section
of his comments section is now that seems to hate him.
Yeah.
But I mean, you know, it just happens.
Like there's nothing you can really do about it.
But Matthew Matosa has been like shockingly professional
his whole career.
He I mean disappears completely and then comes out with a video
and he's gone.
I mean, I want to back up here for a second
because what Nate is describing applies to every reviewer.
Like everyone gets a parody.
This isn't a Matthew Matosa specific thing.
Right.
This is just what a whole leader is.
He's a holy cow, though.
He's he's untouched.
I mean, this is something that I get like a lot of people who hate me.
They hate me because other people parrot my videos at them,
that like when I make a video, there's a subset of people who
will say like this confirms that the show was bad, you know,
and like they won't then go on and just be like, yeah, well,
not like now I believe I'm objectively right because Digi Bro said
the thing I was thinking, even though I personally will literally
say like, hey, this is just my opinion.
Everybody is no, you know, I tend to reevaluate my opinions
when Digi agrees with me.
I've really noticed that I must whenever anyone says anything,
I immediately think of why they're wrong.
Like any of you or any of my family.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, we feel it.
Oh, we feel it.
Why do I do that?
I don't know.
Strange man.
I don't feel like to play devil's advocate.
So every time we refer to you as best guy ever,
you should reevaluate that position, guys.
You should think carefully before you use such words,
which, you know, definitive.
On the subject of how everybody is stupid
and their opinions are bullshit, you
can't say anything without being responded to by fucking
simpletons.
In the last podcast, we brought up the Resident Evil 2 remake
recently.
And I was positive about it because you were at it.
I played it yesterday, by the way.
It was pretty fun.
It's really good.
Yeah, it's good.
So I said it was good in the last podcast.
And I see now a comment from someone who's like mad at me
for saying that it's good.
He's like, oh, it's just a shameless cash grab
for people who are nostalgic, like Jess.
It was like, if I wanted to be nostalgic,
I would play the original.
I wouldn't play the remake.
That makes no sense.
And then he's like, you know, outside from the visuals
and the overall quality, the game is boring.
So aside from waiting, he goes, yeah.
You're talking about the overall quality?
Yeah, this is a real comment.
Oh my god.
That's good.
That's real good.
He literally goes like, he literally goes,
the gameplay is tight.
And to the point, I appreciate that.
However, outside the visuals and overall quality,
the game is just boring.
He must mean something like the quality of just like the way
that I think what he's trying to say,
I think what he's trying to say is that the game is like
technically well made, but not interesting.
It lacks soul.
He's saying that it brings nothing new to the table,
that like it's just like the quintessential Resident Evil,
but like we just had Resident Evil 7,
which did bring a lot new to the table.
I mean, I was going to play the original Resident Evil.
And then I'm like, you know what?
Third person shooting just looks more fun.
I think I'll do that instead.
Like I'm not, I'm not trying to pick on this commentary.
I'm just, yeah, I happen to see him because like,
you know, I said something good about the game.
So of course I get blowback from someone who doesn't think
it's all that good, but I actually have a Resident Evil 2 video
coming out that is going to skew negative.
And I know when that comes out, I'm going to get the same
blowback from the other morons who think that like,
how dare you say something negative about it?
It's actually good.
That's true.
There's no winning.
On all sides of this, it's hard for me to understand
because like I just enjoy hearing people say their opinion
and justify it.
And it doesn't, it doesn't matter if I agree with,
like like Matthew Matosis' video on Breath of the Wild,
I fucking loved that video.
And I felt like he is extremely justified in feeling
the way he does about the game.
The game doesn't look like it appeals to me in any way.
Like, I don't know why lately my videos on games have been
skewing negative, like the Kingdom Hearts video.
It's like, I don't know, I think it's just like,
I feel like that's what YouTube deserves at this point
is just more of the negativity they all crave.
And well, I mean, your opinions seem reasonable.
So, you know, I'm not too surprised based on the content.
I don't ever feel like I'm being like too negative.
I always feel like I'm being fair, but people are like,
oh, this guy's bitter.
I'm not bitter about anything.
It's just, this is the kind of content you want
and this is the kind of content you deserve,
even if you don't want to admit that you want it.
Everyone knows like big takedown videos have always been
the most popular on YouTube.
And so, but yours, yours aren't big enough takedowns.
There's too much.
My videos are like five minutes long most of the time.
And usually just one point,
because I don't want to make a big video with 50 points
and take the rest of my life to make it.
You know, it's better to just, if you just want to say
one thing about a game, just say that one thing.
You don't have to make a whole fucking review analysis
to put that point in.
We always talk about this warmly,
but your video on The Hundred Knight or whatever,
The Witch and The Hundred Knight, that was,
that's like my favorite video you've made in several years,
I think, you know, not to say that the others are bad.
It's just that one stands out in my mind a lot.
It's so weird to me to see people who reject hearing
the opposite opinion, because I want to know why
people feel the opposite from me.
Like, the Gaming Brit just put out a glowing bike
comparison to anyone else, review of Kingdom Hearts 3.
Like, he loved it.
I skipped that one, so it won't influence me
while I'm still making mine.
Gaming Brit is one of the best channels on YouTube
that I've ever seen.
Yeah?
Gaming Brit's great.
He's so consistent.
He's a great channel,
and like, when I watch that video, I'm sitting there
and I'm like, this guy, he doesn't even bring up
any of the things that everyone else talked about
that they hated about Kingdom Hearts 3.
Like, he maybe like, is kind of like,
the cutscenes are kind of stupid sometimes,
but like, he just seemed to be into the game.
And like, that's great.
That should exist, even if I feel the opposite,
because obviously a lot of people feel that way.
So like, don't you want everyone's feelings
to be represented?
Like, that's the ideal.
You shouldn't be coming to one video
to be the ultimate video.
I want there to be every single possible take
represented, so I know why everyone feels differently
from each other.
Every opinion is like a tribe,
and like, you have one opinion.
You're in the tribe of people with your opinion,
and you want your tribe to dominate.
Yeah, that's very true.
I don't want my tribe to dominate.
I want to coexist.
I want diversity.
I want to quickly check.
We need more diversity in video games.
Disagree.
I need Ben to shut up.
Whoa.
Go on, go on.
Because I want to be like, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I've been wanting to interject.
We've got to talk about this.
No, we've got to get into what just went on here.
All right.
Yes, because I said, I want to interject,
and you started talking over me.
That's why I wanted you to shut up.
There's nothing more to it.
Indeed, agreed.
Talk about savage takedown.
Ben just got slapped down.
You know what, finally.
His reign of terror has been put to an end at last.
I just wanted to interject a bit earlier than I did speak up.
Like, I feel it, didn't you?
Because before the pony fandom, I never really felt like,
I never experienced people getting so upset
about other people expressing their opinions
that are different.
Because for me, personally, I love listening to opinions
about the things that I like or I hate,
even if they're different from mine.
Because for me, it's just extra content
talking about the thing that I like
or hate, I guess.
For instance, I really like Dragon Age,
and you bet you're ready.
I'm going to listen to every single review
about Dragon Age, be it good or bad,
because I want to know what they think.
Do they like it?
What do they dislike it?
And it gives me, like, I didn't really
think about it that way.
I guess that's kind of annoying.
Or like, oh, yeah, that's right.
Oh, I completely missed that thing.
Yes, I love this about the game.
You know?
It's just fun.
I don't understand.
The pony community, so the pony community
was really fucking partisan.
OK, that one, for sure, was very focused on being positive.
I don't know.
No, I'm saying partisan.
It was very, like, descent was very tribal,
and descent was very looked down on.
It was this weird, like, sort of one-of-a-kind group.
Like, it grew out of 4chan.
So there was always that, like, 4chan edgelord part of it.
But then it was also, like, this lovey-fluffy tumbler part
of it, too.
Because it was like, we're all outcasts.
We're all outcast together.
We all got to look after each other.
By not allowing descent.
There was, like, two pony fandoms.
And then there was a third that was just normal people who
no one fucking remembers.
I never met any of those.
I can't say I'm familiar.
There was only one, and it's my secret identity, me.
My secret identity, comma, me.
Hey, on the subject of, I don't know,
like, appreciating other people's opinions,
OK, I don't know about you guys.
But within my soul, I feel the growth of a villain.
I feel a villain emerging slowly over time.
This wasn't able, yeah.
Wait, when I was listening.
Wait, you've always been a villain.
What are you talking about?
Well, I aspire to be a little finger.
But I don't think I have the courage.
But, like, when I'm watching the Matthew Matosis video,
it was interesting.
Because we talked about this a bit.
And as I'm watching it, there was, like, I felt myself,
he used a lot of flowery language, right?
He used a lot of grandiose verbiage stuff.
I didn't get that.
I don't, you said that in the chat.
And I don't know what verbiage you're talking about.
Are you talking about Matthew Matosis?
Yes.
OK, OK, I want to say something.
Matthew Matosis' Breath of the Wild video
had multiple instances of him misusing words
that he really should know.
Oh, no.
Like what?
Oh, god.
Potato, potato, potato, potato, potato.
No, no, man.
OK, I'm sorry.
I can't think of any.
But, like, it must have been, like, six or seven times
for the whole video.
He, like, used the word, like, he used, like,
he would use, like, a word, like,
irregardless instead of irrespective or regard.
Like, that kind of thing.
And I was like, he doesn't, this is worse than usual.
You know.
He's getting dumber, guys.
He's getting dumber.
It was, it was, it was more free.
He doesn't usually do that.
But he did many times.
Maybe.
I wish I had a specific example on the tip of my tongue.
I noticed.
Matthew Matosis is so, yeah, go on.
I'm just saying, I never, I did neither caught that,
nor did I think there was any, like, weird words in there.
Like, I don't remember hearing anything that was out of place.
But, well, this is, here's the thing, though.
You liked the video.
I liked it.
There were things that I enjoyed watching.
In fact, I did enjoy watching it.
But, like, I had a kind of fundamental disagreement
of his point.
And here's the thing.
I think that because I just sort of disagreed
with the tact he was taking, because, like,
I made a video comparing two totally different games,
like, whatever, Hollow Knight versus Breath of the Wild.
And, like, they're very different.
But I like the style of Hollow Knight stuff more.
And, like, that kind of was, is what informed that entire,
which one I thought was better.
And, like, that still remains the case to this day.
And so, as I'm replaying the game now,
I still feel like, wow, this world, you know,
it's cool and all.
The film's pretty empty.
Whatever.
Matthew, he loved the freedom and stuff.
It's like, because we disagreed on a fundamental,
like, precept of his analysis, I felt myself
giving less charity to, like, his, like, art.
Like, whenever he makes, like, an artistic flair
in a sentence, I'm like, that's unnecessary.
Let's just catch the facts here.
I didn't notice any artistic flair in his sentences, though.
Any sentence that contains more than the basic number
of adjectives, verbs, and nouns required
to get the message across is a waste of my time.
I don't even know if I hear the individual points
or words that he's saying or making,
because, like, when I hear those videos all,
it's like a heroin trip.
I just feel like, yeah, talking about games.
I just fucking come over how he writes, like,
and the way that he, because the thing about Matthew Atosius
that I like about him above other critics
is that I feel like he really looks at everything
that the game could have been, like,
as opposed to just looking at what's there
and then saying, here's whether that was good or bad.
He looks at it and says, like, here's what could have been done
and whether that would have made it better or worse
or, like, why these choices were made, you know,
why these things all work together and stuff.
It's like he's taking a lens that goes beyond the game
into, like, just the whole possibility space
of what a game could even be.
And not enough critics are doing that.
I just love that he, I just love that he just never seems
even remotely combative about anything.
Like, he never seems to bring up what anyone else is saying.
He doesn't, like, his videos exist in a nice little warm bubble.
And I don't think he reads anyone else's shit.
Good. That's the best thing you could probably do.
That is wise, I'd say.
Yeah, he just, he feels like he just, he takes his fucking time.
He analyzes every single facet of the game.
And as you said, yeah, he really thinks about, like,
the potential of it.
Like, I don't know, when I played a game like Metal Gear Solid 5,
I kind of loved that game and come back to it
because I just don't care about the story
and I've just gotten over that, that it's total shit.
And, like, that game could have been, like, amazing
if the story was good, but it doesn't even bother me.
So I get why someone would literally give it a 0 out of 10
if they're, like, a huge Metal Gear fan.
But for somebody like me, it was, like, a 9 out of 10
just because I enjoyed playing the mission so much.
Well, that's the thing.
And that's what it looks like with Breath of the Wild,
where when that game came out,
all the people I saw praising it
were all people who like to push mechanics to the extreme.
Like, Dunkey is somebody who will find every possible thing
that you can do in that game
because he likes to experiment with a game.
I like to have a guided experience.
And, like, with Breath of the Wild in particular,
I'm afraid to play that game
because when I play Zelda, I like to try to find everything.
Like, the fun for me is in these worlds are densely crafted
in that, you know, every time I get a new item,
like, there's an immediate application for it in this place
to get this thing, to check something off the list
and be done, you know?
The idea of an endless possibility space
just doesn't appeal to me at all.
And so I wouldn't want to play it, you know?
Speaking of guided experiences and Zelda, conspiracy theory,
who else thinks that Egoraptor was paid off
to plug the bayou, the blue bayou restaurant
in his fucking Zelda Ocarina of Time video?
That's such a weird joke.
It's such a weird moment in that video
when he takes a little tangent to talk about
how much he likes the blue bayou restaurant.
And it sounds like a joke, but it's not funny at all.
It's only funny because he says it as though it's a joke.
But it's not, it's just him endorsing a restaurant.
And I hate it.
That could be a joke.
Don't remember that at all.
You've probably watched that video a lot more time ago.
He's obsessed about this.
He is.
Every day I think about the fucking,
how much I hate the blue bayou restaurant.
He's just like, it's when he's comparing the link
to the past to a theme park.
He's like, oh, welcome to Treyarch.
Try our fucking Trice Force shaped ice cream pops.
Hey, I love Disney World.
I go like six times a year.
I love the blue bayou restaurant.
They got great food.
Oh, that's a little pricey.
But you know what?
It's worth it.
Why?
That's a good joke.
Why is that a good joke?
What's funny about that?
It's a little pricey, but you know what?
It's worth it the way he says it.
It's fucking hilarious.
That's what I'm saying.
It's not a joke.
It's just he says it as though it's a joke,
which kind of makes it funny.
But it's such it's a joke.
The joke is that he says it in a funny way.
That's not a joke.
It's just a funny voice.
That's a little bit pricey.
That's a little pricey.
But you know what it's worth it?
I'll bet it's not fucking worth it.
Fuck that guy.
It's fucking human core.
Eagle Raptor is so fucking human core.
He enjoys food at restaurants.
That's disgusting.
That's gay.
The theme parks, human core.
I denounce them.
That's my two cents about that.
What were we talking about?
I don't know.
A mom and pop restaurant is human core.
A theme park is like a weird like a hamster wheel
created for us to run in by like our overlords.
I think I agreed.
But I still think that's human core.
It's like it's like manufactured human core.
What's human core?
Mage, why don't you get in your time machine
and go back to fucking August last year.
Go back to September 11th, 2001.
And I'll show you what human core looks like.
Excuse me for not caring about shit.
Oh fuck.
She says 9-11 doesn't matter.
That's the European stance.
That's fucked up.
You know human core.
Like it's for idiots.
Oh no.
You're gonna put your foot down over there Ben.
Hell yeah Tom.
High hoof.
High hoof me bro.
High hoof me in the gross disgusting audio links.
No.
Show notes.
Put that in the show notes everybody.
It's happening.
It's happening in real time right now.
So what else is going on people?
Well, I'm dying.
Yeah.
Let's talk about my cool hangover
that I am currently suffering right now.
Okay.
So yeah, I feel bad.
I was just coming in.
Just I was coming in the door as I saw
that this podcast was starting and I'm like,
I really shouldn't because I want to be dead.
But I also would like money.
So I came on, which is really my mindset every single week.
But this time it was more so
because I actually got sick.
Yeah, what if you live, you need money for that.
What series of events led you to this night of debauchery
that I'm sure follow this morning of agony?
You mean preceded.
That's right.
Right, okay.
I want you too much Matthew Matosis.
He's a lot of words.
Well, I went out partying last night with Juan,
who I talked about last week.
Indeed.
The Angels Forever thing.
And by the way, thank you everybody.
There was like a thousand dollar bump
and it's only been a couple of days.
That's great.
So that's really cool.
And holy shit.
And fucking Juan was really happy
and he loved me and people liked me.
So it worked.
People liked me now.
People think that I'm good.
That makes me a...
I fooled them.
It's nice.
You know, we have this weird little clusterfuck of a podcast
about nothing.
It's nice that something good happened
because of it for once.
Yeah.
I got to finish chewing my hangover crackle.
We are the reason the human humanity is dying.
We're the reason people are dying.
But not today.
Except Ivan.
Yeah, except Ivan.
The one person who won't die
because of this podcast.
There'll be the last man left.
I hope we won't be spared.
The last man standing.
So I went out partying with Juan
and also my friend Dylan
because it was his birthday.
So we're all...
We got to fucking bar worth of this cool bar.
We're like...
We didn't have chairs.
I mean, there was a table.
But then there was also a stand-up thing.
I was at the standing up part.
So I felt cool because I'm like,
yeah, I'm standing up at the food eating my pizza thing.
So that was cool.
And like...
So then, you know, there were drinks and stuff.
So like, I don't drink
or I don't like drinking ever.
It's bad.
I hate it.
I don't like being drunk.
I don't like after being drunk.
Feel the same way more or less.
Even though I drink sometimes.
Yeah.
But I also am really desperate for approval.
So I can't turn down a drink ever.
I can't turn down anything.
If someone says we're drinking,
I'm like, well, I'm drinking the most.
It's me.
It's good ol' energy.
I'm gonna drink.
I'm gonna be the coolest guy here
and everyone's gonna like me.
The coolest, drunkest guy.
Exactly.
Which really is synonymous.
So...
I feel you.
I was...
So I was drinking.
I did some tequila shots
with the salt on the hand.
And then I went to the place
and I got this thing called
A Man With No Name,
which is like some kind of whiskey drink.
But the ice cube was like a big round ice ball.
It looked like a ball of ice.
It was really cool.
I've always wanted one of those.
And as I was drinking it,
sort of like the poison in the alcohol
was like melting into the ice cube,
ice ball.
And it created like a ridge
around the circumference of the ice ball.
So it looked like the Death Star.
So that was really cool.
So I got another one of those
because I liked that it was a Death Star
kind of looking thing.
So then I got this dragon fruit
fucking red fruity beer drink
and that was fucking tasty.
And even after all that,
I was doing fine.
I was feeling...
You know, I was loosey-goosey.
I was making jokes.
I was being cool.
You know, I'm just walking around
like, hey, I'm just being cool.
I'm just being cool.
And you know,
everyone was telling me that I'm cool
because the podcast...
My friends, by the way,
didn't even know that I have a podcast
because I'm so ashamed
of this part of my life normally
that I haven't told anyone in my real world
anything about what I do.
I never post like shit on Facebook.
No one knows anything.
And that's how I like it.
So they didn't even know
that I had a podcast until I said,
hey, I shouted out Ivan on the thing.
So that was cool.
So they were proud of me for telling people
about the GoFundMe
and also proud of me for having a podcast
which they didn't know.
So definitely, that's nice.
It's only been going for three years.
Yeah, so I was...
Yeah.
So yeah.
So even after that,
I was feeling good.
I took some selfies in the bar.
You know, my friend had these cool geckos.
I took a picture of one.
I was like, look at this fucking gecko boy.
Oh, I want you to do a gecko, please.
Oh, it's on Instagram.
I gecko-grammed.
That's the single most interesting thing
in the last half hour.
Mage out for blood today.
Mage is the reason people are dying
because she's murdering them
with her vicious words.
So I was feeling fine
till we got back to the apartment.
But then this girl who like...
Now that's trouble right there.
Oh yeah, this girl who I call,
who I refer to all night as Facy Woman
because she had a face and she was a woman.
And like...
Typical.
Fucking typical.
Because like it was a face that I knew that I had...
Like I knew that I've met this person
probably 11 times before.
I recognized her face,
but I didn't know her name until someone said it
and like, oh, that's your name.
I've just been calling you Facy Woman this whole time.
And then that caught on
and then everyone started calling her Facy Woman.
Oh, I bet she loved that.
But uh...
Oh yeah.
But she was...
She does have a face.
It was a cool face.
She's a cool face person.
So she was like...
Like baby bouncing this jug of like potion,
this drink,
this like fucking...
This snot juice or baby slime or whatever.
Dandling it?
Yeah, on her knee.
So she was going around
and she started like pouring that
into people's...
Agape mouths,
like chickens looking up
and drowning in a rainstorm.
So, you know,
I allowed that to happen to me a few times
and that's when everything went crazy.
And you know,
when I get drunk enough,
I become God.
So I was sitting there,
I was doing the jokes,
I was saying the cool things,
I was making everybody laugh and you know.
And you know.
But of course,
sometimes I'm too funny for normal people,
I guess.
Yeah.
Because like...
You know,
because I was telling my jokes,
you know,
I might have let fly a couple of cool n-bombs.
And some wacky f-bombs, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, and some silly...
You're painting a picture here.
Yeah.
And some colorful rape jokes or something,
I don't know.
Not a lot of rape jokes,
just an appropriate amount,
I would say.
Yeah.
Whatever you think the right amount is,
it was that amount.
Yeah.
But I began to notice
like a slight shift in the room
and it's like...
It's like, guys, come on.
This isn't the internet.
You don't have to pretend to be offended by things.
It's okay to laugh at n-bombs and stuff.
But no one believes me
because the world has gone crazy.
And really,
it's not that everyone was offended,
but there was this one guy sitting next to me on the couch,
this one cuck who's f-cking...
Like, I don't know.
I said something that was too funny for him.
I said like a rape joke or something.
Yeah.
And he like,
he slapped me in the face.
No, f-cking way.
What?
Yeah.
And like...
All right, well, that's uncalled for.
It wasn't like a hard slap,
but it was hard enough to be annoying.
Yeah.
That's f-cked.
That's straight up escalating the violence.
You don't do that.
Yeah.
And I said,
whoa, what was that for?
And he just did it again.
And I'm like, okay.
What the f-ck?
What were you doing?
Why you sl-
I didn't say anything.
What are you doing?
And like,
and he did it like three or four times.
He kept like slapping.
And again, like, it wasn't like hard...
What?
Like really painful slaps,
but it was hard enough that it became
really f-cking normal.
Trying to get you to punch him in the f-cking face?
Like, what the f-ck?
Yeah, so that's what everybody does.
Everybody wants to get punched.
Everybody wants to f-ck with me.
Everywhere I go.
I don't know why,
no matter where I am,
no matter what I'm doing,
there's always one f-cking person
who just can't handle it.
One person who doesn't understand
that I'm just being cool
and has to get their undies twisted.
Because I guess I just intimidate people
with my overwhelming charisma.
So they have to find some way
to try and tear me down
to alleviate that sense of worthlessness
they feel in my shadow.
So he kept doing it a couple times
until finally I had to put some dad
in my voice and went,
Stop!
Some dad.
This party will become not fun
if you hit me one more time,
I promise.
So then he stopped,
and so that guy was gay.
Yeah.
But nah, he was alright.
We became friends, I guess.
Not really, I hope he dies, but...
I feel many ways about many things.
If you got a f-cking problem,
you say, like,
hey man, you know,
not to be a buzz kill or anything,
but I'm personally a fan, you know.
But my wife is black
and is a rape victim,
so the jokes are a little bit sore on me.
Fucking words in these situations.
I mean, even that,
I believe.
It would have been...
Like, if I made a joke,
and someone was like,
oh man, that offends me
because of, you know,
this reason or like,
hey, there's a fucking black guy
right next to you
and he feels bad
because you said that word 50 times
in one sentence,
then I would be like,
okay, I'm sorry.
Yeah, you don't go from,
you don't go from silent to
fucking slap in a guy
to silent to violent.
Silent to violent.
Chris been walked.
I just can't...
There is no words
that can come out of someone's face
that I think a slap
is an inappropriate response to ever.
Agreed.
I guess something like,
if you don't stop me now,
I will assassinate your dad
or, you know, something like that.
What if they say slap me?
I'm not gonna slap somebody
just because they told me to.
Yeah, I don't wanna go there.
I'll need some cajoling.
I'll need some cajoling
to follow through on that.
What if they say I'll pay you to slap me?
That's the cajoling I'm looking for.
It's weird to me because, like,
you can tell that nobody in the room
is really offended.
Like, most people are laughing.
Everybody's, like, having a good time,
but, like, there's this sense in people
that they have to pretend to be offended
and they just have to play along
with the idea of, like,
oh, you can't say that.
And it's like, you're not offended.
Stop pretending and don't touch me.
Well, it's not even that there's an offense
at that point.
It's that they're afraid to laugh.
Yeah.
Because, like, what's everybody else gonna think?
I can't, like, this can't be funny to me,
even though it's fucking great.
Yeah, and maybe it's also, like,
a virtue signaling thing,
of they wanna be like,
hey, just so everyone knows,
I'm not cool with this,
so, you know, like, that's a part for sure.
I don't even get what it was that I said
that set him off,
because it's not like I was just spewing
this torrent of outrageous, hateful shit.
I know how to read the room.
Everything was fine.
Yeah, yeah.
But anyways, that's just a minor aside.
That's not like a whole big thing.
We started playing games.
We started, you know,
drinking more of that baby slime out of the tap.
And, you know, we were playing Liar's Dice,
like Orlando Bloom and Pirates of the Caribbean,
part two.
Nice.
Anyways, then I started puking.
I was puking all over the fucking place,
by which I mean the toilet,
because I'm pretty, like,
I'm pretty swift when I feel a puke coming.
I can get, like,
I can weave in and out of people
and slalom my way to the bathroom.
Oh, the word slalom.
Would you say you're a man who can handle his puke?
The last time I heard that word slalom
was, like, in the phone stones cartoon.
And I never knew what it meant.
No idea.
I just know it because of the impossible
driver tutorial on PlayStation 1,
where you gotta fucking do all that shit
in the garage on the first level
and slalom your way through the fucking pillars.
That is such a weird word.
It is.
I don't think I've ever heard that word.
Slalom.
Like, no one should ever say that.
Is it not really just skiing?
Is there a slope involved?
Yeah, it's a skiing thing.
It's like an, like, you go between the flags.
I knew it was some kind of Olympic winter sport thing.
Yeah, it's just, like, weaving in and out of.
Oh, okay, okay.
You know, I know what happens to everybody.
Like, everybody knows that everybody pukes
when they drink.
But, like, you don't,
but you never want to be the guy
who's the puke-y guy at the party
while it's happening.
You want to be able to hold it in until you're alone.
No.
The next day, like, now.
Oh.
When someone starts puking,
that's when everyone's like,
oh, dear.
Oh, boy.
It signals the third act of any good party.
I mean, the best way to puke at a party
is to be like a dog who knows
he's not long for this world,
so you crawl into the porch to just dial on
so no one can see it.
You got to get out of there
before anyone knows you're puking.
Puking in silence and hopefully come back
and you're like, hey, nothing happened.
Or come back and be like,
hey, I puked, but I'm okay.
Don't worry.
Like, because I've been to a lot,
like, when me and my friends used to drink a lot.
That's not always possible.
It's not just that somebody would start puking.
It's that they would become bad.
Like, the moment when somebody gets to a point
where everyone else is worried about them,
that's when the party's dead.
Yeah.
Because it sobers you up.
Like, if you're not drunk enough to be that guy,
then you will become sober
by wanting to help that guy, you know?
Yeah.
Well, my whole thing is that just like,
I have a deep-seated need
to be the coolest guy in the room at all costs.
So, like, I will drink more than anyone.
I'll drink anything anyone gives me.
If somebody says to me, like,
I won't do something, like,
ah, you won't drink this much.
I'll be like, oh, you said the wrong thing to me, Buster.
Whoa, with the heart on it.
I don't know.
It's a Leo thing.
You know, I just got to be the guy.
I'm like, I'm really into astrology.
Also, that's my new thing.
Whoa, whoa.
What?
Not really.
Where did that come from?
Well, I was watching the Orville
and there was an episode about, like,
a planet of people who are, like,
obsessed with astrology.
And they, they, like, they do, like,
a genocide thing of people
who were born under a certain sign.
So I was watching that and I'm like,
yeah, that's a good society.
I would, that'd be cool.
I would like to get rid of all the Scorpios.
That'd be awesome.
No.
My dad's a Scorpio.
Poor bastard.
Riveting.
You would kill me.
That hurts, man.
Well, you'd thank him for it, Tom.
Are you a, are you a, are you a,
are you a Scorpion, Tom?
I am a Scorpio, yeah.
Everyone, signs, me, Aries,
fire sign, Beth sign.
I'm a cancer.
I think that's water, I think.
Leo, lion, king of the jungle, best guy.
Taurus, earth, glad it's not water.
Digi.
Do you know Digi?
Any idea?
Digi's also a Leo.
It's Leo.
Okay.
Where'd he go?
Uh, I guess he's dead?
Digi.
I was trying to find a,
I was trying to think of a way to transition out
instead of giving an answer,
but I didn't come up with anything in time.
Too late.
Crap.
Out, outplayed.
Well, what else happened then, Jay?
Go on, go on.
So, you know, I, I would be like hanging out and be like,
oh, make way, people, it's pukey time.
And I got up and I would like,
Russia, I would dart to the bathroom.
Mm-hmm.
It was definitely a dart motion,
like I would whoosh.
And I did that like two or three times,
I think, over the course of the night.
Like, and one of the times when I was in there
puking, I was like, well, I'm in here,
I might as well poop too.
So I pooped on my puke.
And that was really cool.
God damn.
All right.
Can flush more than once.
Because like, normally I would never poop
in another person's house,
but if they think I'm in there puking,
then I have, you know,
carte blanche to secretly poop
while I'm at it.
That's true.
Secretly poop.
No one will ever know.
Yeah.
So then, you know, I came out,
and then the party was starting to thin
and people were leaving.
So then it was just me and my friend.
So, you know, me and my friend
started having like emotional real talk,
and that's miserable for all parties involved.
And no one wants to do that,
but it's just a part of the party.
You have to do it at some point.
It's like a ritual for men, I guess.
Men who otherwise fucking just push
everything down all day for their whole lives.
You know, you gotta have that drunk
meeting of the minds at every party
at least once with your genuine broken.
So, I don't know.
So then that was the party,
and then I woke up in the morning
choking on my own vomit,
like fucking ACDC.
So then I fucking went.
We stopped at McDonald's in the way home,
and I got an orange juice,
and I don't know why the fuck I did that.
Because then I came home and started the podcast,
and then I immediately had to disappear
for 15 minutes to fucking vomit up orange juice,
and it was acid-y, and it hurt, and it tastes bad,
and now I'm drinking tea,
but now the tea tastes like vomit and orange juice
because it's coating the inside of my mouth,
and that's my grumbly story
about how hungover and sad I am.
Incredible. Not bad.
But I would do it all again
if somebody told me that they would like me.
In fact, there's another party tonight.
While Jesse was getting shit-faced at a party,
I, the night before, was taking three tabs of acid,
and it was pretty fucking cool.
While I was doing that,
you, the night before, did something.
What was that experience like?
It was pretty fucking sick.
Me and Zen Huxtable did a bunch of acid,
found your drugs, kids.
Listen, do drugs, though.
You can do some drugs.
Not kids, but...
No, don't do it.
As long as you're 18.
Yeah, kids don't do drugs if you're 18.
Hey, kids. Do a lot of drugs.
It's me. It's me.
You're a dad, but like your cool dad, Ben St.
letting you know that you can do some drugs if you want to.
You have my permission.
No, not alone.
Just do them in the house, where it's safe.
Or not. I don't really care.
Get on out there and get those drugs, kids.
He's the cool dad. He doesn't care.
It's all I'm doing.
That's right.
You're the good, the bad.
Don't listen to him.
See, I'm like your dad, but like really,
you know, we're more like friends than like dad, you know.
You never visit.
Like, I'm like, yeah, because I'm like too cool to visit.
Why don't you introduce me to some of your classmates?
They look pretty cute, don't I'm saying?
Hey, yeah.
I can't wait to come to your kindergarten class again
and see them. Hey, yeah.
Am I right?
High five, son.
Anyway.
Moving on from that as fast as possible.
Tell me, tell me more about the experience.
Yeah, I mean, mostly it was me and Zen Huxtable
sitting around listening to music and talking about
tautology and how everything is the same thing,
but also infinite versions of the same thing,
which is basically the conversation,
the one that you have when you're on acid.
So yeah, so that's the one that just kind of goes
around in circles.
Well, yeah, but every conversation does.
I mean, that was the nature of the conversation
was us addressing the fact that the conversation
was going in circles and and and then continuing said circle
for us for because the thing about acid is that
you can't sleep after you take it for like a long time.
Like it keeps you up, it gives you lots of energy
even after the trip is over.
So we're just kind of like standing around talking
about tautology all night long and listening to music.
But we do when we do it together.
This is the second time we've done it.
It's been sort of a cultural exchange where we just kind of
share one another's or share our music with one another,
you know, because he's mostly into like jazz and big band
and stuff like that.
And I'm more into like, you know, psychedelic rock and shit.
And there's a lot of crossover there.
So, you know, I got him into the Mars Volta.
He showed me some cool shit.
And that's basically it.
I mean, there's not nothing crazy or exciting happened
that wouldn't be over the detailed space.
2001, a space Odyssey style.
I saw I saw some cool.
I mean, yeah, I did.
I had I had some fun.
Well, because like the thing is that basically to explain
to anybody who has no idea what acid does to you at all.
And like if you've if you've seen music videos that are like,
this is what an acid trip is like, it's exactly like that.
Like it's exactly what everybody portrays it as.
But like basically how I would characterize it is that normally
your brain is in taking like ridiculous amounts of sensory data
on just everything going on.
But it it doesn't register most of it.
It puts most of it away.
It just focuses on the things that matter.
When you're on acid, it's not doing that.
It's not focusing on things that matter.
It's just taking in everything and it doesn't know what's important.
So if you were to say stare at a wall,
you will notice way more detail in that wall
than you've ever normally noticed.
But because your brain can't like,
it can't necessarily like process all of that at once.
Some of it starts to look weird and fucky
and it's all moving around.
Everything you look at is moving.
Any still image, it's moving.
Everything's moving all the time.
Because you're just like trying to keep track
of all this fucking sensory data going on.
So if you were to have no music
and just be like in a just in a room by yourself,
it would become terrifying because you you know,
you're just like seeing shit fucking happen constantly.
But like if you listen to music,
it keeps you concentrated on the music
and it sort of forces your attention onto something.
So instead of like your attention constantly shifting
and constantly like you know,
paying attention to different things,
it's like it commands you to listen to it.
And so if you listen to really dense music
with lots of shit going on,
you're going to parse every single detail in that music
and it sounds really beautiful.
So mostly we're just sitting there listening to trippy music
and when I would sit there with my eyes closed,
that's when you have the fucking mind visions.
They're like traveling the universe fucking seeing.
I kept seeing like the the like schema of my own brain
is how I would put it.
But like it was like I was seeing my my vascular system
or like the veins in my brain,
but they were all full of pastel rainbows like charging through.
Was it like that episode of Spongebob
where Plankton goes into his earhole and into his brain
and at some point Spongebob just turns his eyeballs
around in his head and looks into his own brain
and sees Plankton standing on it
with a lever controlling his movements.
I have...
Oh, you know what?
I have seen that that episode.
No, it wasn't like that.
Okay, well now I get it.
It sure was, it sure was.
I mean, if anybody wanted to like just to name a music video
that I think encapsulates it perfectly,
the video for When You Die by MGMT looks like an acid trip.
But there's tons like, I mean,
again, it's something that's portrayed in in lots of media
and granted, I wasn't like doing a shitload of acid or anything.
Like if you do a whole lot,
it can get even more out of control as I understand it.
But mostly it's just like everything you look at
is moving all the time and it's trippy and cool.
Fuck yeah, do drugs.
Hell yeah.
Well, you know, they always say,
Sam Harris, the only person I respect who's ever done a drug,
is, he always says that like, it's helpful for,
he's the guy who I first heard a reasonable argument for
that consciousness is an illusion.
And basically that, I forget,
I think it was DTM, MDMT or whatever.
He said it was very helpful for,
like it elevates you above your own,
what's it like, ego or whatever,
such that you are like, yeah.
That is what I think.
I think MDMA, which I'm pretty sure is ecstasy.
Yeah, I think that's right.
You're thinking of the wrong thing.
It's DMT that causes ego death.
DMT?
Yes.
Okay, I forget which one it was.
I don't find that.
Yeah, yeah, you combine the acronyms.
But first of all, pretty smart guy,
and then he did some drugs because he's into meditation
and it helped him be like, yeah, I don't exist.
I'm just part of the universe.
You know, there's nothing special about me.
I am the particles that are part of the universe.
That's pretty cool.
People make a big deal about like-
I don't know why I need drugs for that though,
because like I get it.
Yeah, you don't.
Like, I mean, I feel like,
I feel like you can just understand that concept and be fine.
I knew a guy in college whose name was-
I recommend doing acid because it's fun.
I knew a guy in college named Acid Paul,
who gave me the spiel about DMT and how,
oh, it's like when you die,
your brain is flooded with chemicals and whatever, you know.
He gave me the DMT spiel.
Why don't you just fucking kill me, Acid Jim?
Just do that, and then I'll experience the best high of all.
Death.
Also, you know what?
I don't fucking buy that whole,
when you die, your brain is flooded with chemicals.
How long do you have before you-
What if it gets shot in the fucking brain?
I've got what, like two seconds before I'm just out?
Is that enough time for the chemicals to flood my brain and turn me into-
I think about what the experience of having one's brain
physically damaged and destroyed would be like constantly.
I don't want to think about it, but-
I think about it all the time and freak myself out.
I think about spiders laying eggs in my brain,
and they're just, you know, dealing with-
You know, basically becoming Spider-Man is what I'm trying to say,
and you know, swinging from New York City skyscrapers.
Yeah, they laid eggs in his brain, and now he's turning them.
That's what happened, yeah.
Well, the chemicals flooded his brain,
and he's having an extended, like, flash trip.
That's actually just the moment of his death.
It's only lasted, you know-
It's stretched out like an eternity in front of him.
Yeah, but it's stretched out over, you know,
decades and decades of comic books worth of time.
Indeed, indeed.
The flash, the trip that is.
I want to watch Into the Spider-Verse again,
because it was like the coolest movie I've ever seen.
Agreed?
Good, I still haven't seen it.
Haven't seen it, don't spoil.
You should go watch it.
Hey, speaking of things I've seen, a quick-
Well, I guess this is a tangent now,
but like, I have another subject of interest to me.
But first of all, I have to ask, Tom,
I don't want to spoil anything.
It's about Devil May Cry 5, and it's just about-
There's been like some reveals of things lately,
and I don't want to like say it, if it's gonna, you know,
fuck with things, things about some characters that have been shown.
Any-
Yeah.
Am I- Are you aware of this?
The last-
Do your favorite, say it, so I don't have to.
They aired the last trailer before the game comes out on March 8th,
which is five days from now.
Yes.
I'm very excited.
Okay, and was there a character at the very end?
They showed Virgil from Devil May Cry 3 that he's back.
There, he's coming back.
So first of all, I have no idea how that even happened.
Yeah, I don't really know.
I mean, well, here's the thing.
In Devil May Cry 3, he's like sealed away in the underworld.
That's kind of what happens.
He gets trapped in Demon World, and that's how the game ends.
Spoilers.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yep.
Because you care so much about the story in this game.
The portal between Demon World and Human World had been sealed off.
I was thinking that, yeah.
Until Yusuke shows up and opens the portal, and yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then in Devil May Cry 1, which comes time-on-wise after 3,
you fight this dude called Neroangelo.
It's revealed at the end of the game that he is what remains of Virgil,
and you, you assumedly kill him at this point.
And you get the other half of the necklace, you make the sword of Sparda, it's fucking sick.
It was so cool, like back in the day,
like beating Devil May Cry 3, and then going back to the first one,
and like having this new appreciation for like, oh, that's fucking Virgil.
It was so fucking ill.
God, what a great game series.
Everyone should fucking play it.
But yeah, he's apparently somehow back in Devil May Cry 5,
looking exactly like he did in Devil May Cry 3.
Who questioned that, Tom?
What, what, Devil May Cry 4 special edition, was he like canonically in that, or was that like-
I don't think he was canonically in it.
Okay.
Because I haven't played it, but I know there is like a cutscene or something,
I think they did for DMC4 with Virgil,
applying that he was in Fortuna at some point.
Yeah, yeah.
I think there's a whole Virgil campaign in Devil May Cry.
I think you can play him in the campaign, because I know they added,
they, like the special edition, they added Virgil,
and then they made Lady and Trish, both playable characters as well.
Um, but I don't know if they have their own campaign.
I know, I know they did something for Virgil,
because everybody has a hard on for Virgil.
Indeed they do.
He's implied to have history in Fortuna, even, and like,
it has something to do with Nero, but it's not clear.
I mean, they think that he's his dad, right?
Yeah, that's like the general idea, but it's not confirmed yet.
So, they're assuming there's going to be obviously more information on that in this game,
because like the whole thing is like, they're like,
oh, Nero's devil bringer arm from four contained Yamato, which was indeed his sword.
And so, in this game, it starts with that arm, that devil bringer arm,
or getting cut off, and he gets those robot arms,
and that's like the gimmick of the game.
So, assumedly, from the very beginning, everyone assumed that Virgil would be involved in somehow,
because of the circumstances of his arm being removed and shit like that.
So, it wasn't like a super big surprise.
I think the bigger surprise of that trailer was that they showed like a flashback with Dante's
mother Eva, and like, implying that they're going to go into like the backstory of like,
how they got separated at birth, and like, what happened to fuck over,
Sparta, and how he got fucking captured and shit and imprisoned, and like Eva got killed.
So, yeah, the trailer went from, like, all the trailers have been like,
just like, this is going to be a fucking goofy, good time action game with your boys.
And then this last trailer, they drop like this emotional bomb, where it's like, no,
like, we're going to get heavy at some point, you're like, oh.
Well, you know what, that's appropriate.
I think so, this feels like they're going to wrap it up.
I highly doubt they'll ever make it.
They should.
Unless, like, this game does fucking amazingly well.
I don't think Capcom's really going to bother making another Devil May Cry.
So, this does feel like, tonally, that they're going to wrap everything up in a nice pretty bow,
and leave it be at that point.
So, well, and I guess we'll just have to see, it's coming out in what,
like, three weeks or something?
Try five days, dude.
Five fucking, it'll be out when you hear this podcast.
Oh my God.
You will be able to see our reactions live on IM Games.
If the days line up, I'm not sure at this point.
But either has happened or will be happening soon.
Okay.
Now, all that said, very interesting, and I will absolutely play it.
I've played all the other ones.
So, I'm definitely going to play it as well.
Well, except two, I skipped most or two.
Okay, whatever.
You're not alone.
Here's my, yeah, indeed.
Here's my concern.
Can we stop pretending that the characters in Devil May Cry 5 look good?
Can we just look, because look at Virgil.
Look at Virgil here.
Yes.
I put him in the show notes or whatever, the audio links.
He looks great.
He looks like an anime guy.
Okay.
We all know that's 10 out of 10.
And now look how fucking Virgil looks.
Everyone knows he's the hottest character in the whole series.
Just look at his fucking dumbass, realistic shit double chin face.
Hey, his face looks like a foot.
He looks terrible.
He looks like the guy from Third Rock from the Sun.
What's that dude's name?
Anybody know what I'm talking about?
The Joseph Gordon Levitt or like the older guy?
No, the old guy.
I don't even know where they came from.
I don't know where they came from either, and maybe they're fake.
It's this thing they do now where they model the characters after the mocap actor.
Well, that's what they do.
They literally scan, like the models of these in these games, they don't,
it's not like an artist sit down and made them from scratch, like a drawing or something.
What they do is they get an actor and they scan the face,
and they get a version of the bottle, and then they tweak it a little bit.
And it never looks good because there was no artistic direction really.
You came from real life, and real life is always ugly.
Look at Virgil's hair.
Compare Virgil's hair from Devil May Cry 3 to Devil May Cry 5.
It looks like shit in Devil May Cry 5.
It's terrible.
I haven't seen any of these screenshots.
I only watched the trailer, which doesn't show anything but his coat.
And you're like, well, that's clearly...
Yeah.
I didn't see this.
He looks very shitty.
And here's the thing.
Dante, I think Dante looks fantastic in at least this particular shot.
I think he looks dope as hell.
Now, they're still gonna have the horrible, like,
mouth-speaking realistic animation that always looks bad.
But, you know, Dante himself as a character design looks good.
God, what?
Just...
It's just like at the end of Resident Evil 7 where this guy shows up.
Just some guy shows up and they call him Chris.
Oh, it's Chris Redfield.
And you're playing it, and you're like,
like, who is this chinless gump that you are suddenly telling me is Chris Redfield?
He looks...
This man didn't punch a rock.
That's bullshed.
Like, he used to be like a cool-looking, like, attractive, beefy, like a chiseled,
fucking masculine dude.
And now he's like this chinless worm of a human.
He looks like fucking McLovin' with some, like, pubic hair on his face.
It's gross.
He looks like...
It's like a peach fuzz fuckboy.
Okay, I want to know.
I don't know this.
Why are we doing this?
Is it cheaper to do this?
If so, I've got some sympathy for it.
If they don't want to invest in, like, character design, I can...
I think it's the opposite.
I think it's more expensive.
Then don't do it.
Then don't fucking do it.
I think they're doing it for realism's sake.
And realism is the pain of video games.
Throw it in the fucking garbage, my dude.
Because they did the same thing with Metal Gear Solid 5.
They scanned it on its face.
I can't say it's anime.
Why realism?
No, that's no...
I don't...
I guess we're...
I don't know.
There's like a...
There's a sense of, like...
I think developers want the games to be...
Maybe even using realistic actors or, like, real people the way Kojima's been doing recently.
I think they just think they have to.
I think they think that they're not gonna make the profit margins that they want if they don't go all out.
Here's something.
Devil May Cry 5 is running using the Ari engine,
which they developed for Resident Evil 7.
And without knowing how that...
Because it's a proprietary engine, you know?
So by not knowing what the limitations of that proprietary software is,
like, I'm assuming they built the Resident Evil engine for Resident Evil 7,
a scary, realistic-looking game.
So all the technology in there is probably made to deliver photorealistic games.
And if they're using that engine, it's not as easy as just, like,
you know, changing the shaders and stuff to make it look more anime-y or cartoony.
Like, you have a piece of technology designed to make photorealistic graphics and probably nothing else.
Oh my god. Is that fucking guy you just posted, Jesse?
Jesus Christ versus Original Christ.
Yeah, look at this wimp!
What did they do to him?
Oh my god!
Yeah, I know.
And I know we've talked about this exact thing before, but...
That wasn't even, like, a fake reaction.
That's, like, disgusting.
Yeah, they, like...
They literally, like, I don't know.
I guess Umbrella caught him.
They put him in a lab and they sucked his T-Cown out through a straw.
That's the real T-Virus right there.
Oh my fucking god.
And you know what?
I agree with people.
Lady looks pretty good, but I'm posting...
I don't know why they're not fucking loading.
These images of Trish.
Trish has experienced the most massive attractiveness downgrade of, like,
any fictional female I've ever seen in my life.
Yeah, I don't know. I think she was pretty good in both.
Oh, okay.
She's El Goblina in the bottom one.
Okay, maybe this is a bad screen tap.
What the hell is El Goblina?
She's just a goblin.
You mean, wouldn't it be La Goblina?
Okay, fair enough. Fair enough.
That might be La Goblina.
There we go. There we go.
Okay.
People, you don't need to look at any of these screenshots if you don't want to,
but the point is, like...
I hate that we're feeling shackled.
Whatever.
Like, high-profile, like, action,
what do you call it?
Like, quote-unquote character action.
I don't know if that really applies.
Fucking Gaming Brit hates that term.
For, like, there's a lot of focus on, like, the character model,
and you want it to look like good,
and you want it to be, like, special or something,
but why in God's name would you prioritize
looking like a real person in, what, screenshots and stuff,
versus just going for an appealing art style,
an appealing character style?
It's because it's for normies, dude.
I think you're right.
Gaming has been monetized,
and ever since the 360, it's this push for, wow, this is so...
It's like the normal peep.
Video games have become that person on Facebook.
But Devil May Cry 5 is not a normie game.
It's a hardcore...
But it doesn't matter.
Like, again, the technology has to be built around certain feature sets,
and, like, this is what sells.
Like, I guarantee you couldn't make something like, you know,
Toon Link in the RE engine.
Probably doesn't have the foundation to build something like that.
I think this comes down to that whole issue
that everyone's talking about with the AAA market of
needing to constantly make more money than the previous year, where every game...
companies are shit and should be.
Yeah, and, like, it's like they could definitely make a DMC5
where they tone down these graphics.
The game would cost less to make.
And even if it did sell to fewer people,
which I don't even know if that's the case.
I don't know how much people really give a fuck
about these photorealistic graphics.
Certainly not at this level.
But, like, I think that if they toned it down,
even if it sold to less people,
it would still make a profit because it costed less to make.
But, like, I think that they need a higher just number,
like, in order to please the investors.
And I think that they have to make it this way
to show it to those investors.
Like, probably not even about, like, what they think will sell,
but when they show the game to the people that are going to greenlight it,
they have to assure them that it will have these next-gen graphics
that supposedly are necessary.
Because these people are just, like, you know, investors
who just, like, oh, the kids want, like, the better graphics, right?
So we need to give them the better graphics.
So, yeah, I'll keep funding your operation.
I think the normal people do like that, though.
You know, like I was saying, I think it's like the video games
have become the equivalent of that person on Facebook
who will just post, like, look at this really impressive drawing
this random person did.
And it's just, like, a photorealistic apple or something.
And it's like, this blows my mind how someone could do this.
It's the exact same thing.
It's like, oh, my God, graphics look so good.
Um, the most annoying thing is that, like,
I remember when I was playing Call of Duty 4 way back in the day
and, like, thinking those graphics looked really good.
And then I just had this sudden realization that, oh, uh,
all the clothes don't move, even though they're, like,
the game looks realistic and shit, like, none of the clothing,
like, folds or moves.
It's all just sculpted in place.
And from that moment on, all video games have looked horribly embarrassingly
uncanny valley-faced.
Why is it?
Because clothes don't move like they should.
Game developers and 3D modelers have seeming, to my eyes,
completely given up on clipping.
We're just over dealing with clipping.
Forget it.
We're not going to fix clipping.
I was about to say that.
Like, why in current year does any game still clip ever?
They clip excessively.
Because it's so fucking hard.
Yeah, I think it's so hard they've just said we're not going to worry about it.
Like, the problem is that, like, you get clipping issues
from what little I can understand.
Is that they're, the models in video games don't do anything.
They're literally just there to look pretty.
Like, hit calculations all done with hit boxes,
which don't conform to the geometry of the shape.
So you're always going to have issues because, like,
the model itself that you see visually has nothing to do with the collision data at all.
Right, right.
And you know, to the clipping issue, I am happy to just give up on clipping,
as long as the game plays well and is fun and snappy and good.
It's just that I'm holding them to their own standard here
of, like, visual acuity and stuff.
And so, you know, that issue has just gone completely by the wayside.
I think the problem, user end, is that people judge things
not on how good it looks all the time, but how good it looks occasionally.
Like, I think that people see a game and if a moment looks good,
they think the game looks good.
And this, I'll tie this into that JoJo thing that I got in all that
fucking heat for on Twitter, where I was shitting on JoJo for its character designs.
And, like, most people are thinking of it as, like,
but the character designs look great.
Look, I can show you a picture of the character looking great.
And I'm like, well, that's not what that means in animation terms.
It means how well does the character animate?
How good do they look moment to moment throughout the show?
You know, and so if they look like
shit in half the shots, then that's not great character design, you know?
And, you know, and even going one step beyond that, like, this is a video game.
And so, like, we're just comparing Kingdom Hearts 2 versus 3.
Sure, first of all, I think Kingdom Hearts 2 just has a better art style,
but nonetheless, Kingdom Hearts 2 character designs look way better.
And I didn't appreciate that until a Gaming Brits video where he showed footage of both.
Kyrie is so fucking hot in Kingdom Hearts 2.
Holy shit.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree.
And she's not that hot in 3 by comparison.
Everyone looks worse.
She too has become El Goblina.
I mean, La Goblina.
But yeah, there's a good meme of, fuck, it's Shion from Kingdom Hearts 3 versus Kyrie.
It's what it's like, Waifu versus La Goblina.
It's in my video.
You'll see it, everybody.
But anyway, like, Kingdom Hearts 3, just jumping.
Just jump, if you want to jump into a glide in Kingdom Hearts 3,
you have to do, like, a jump, wait till you hit the peak, jump again, wait till you hit the peak.
It feels slow.
And then you can, at the peak of your thing, it automatically gets you into a glide.
In Kingdom Hearts 2, it's like, circle, circle, square.
Bam, you're gliding instantly.
It's fast as fuck.
It's punchy.
It's great.
And it's just this fucking realism shit.
Or it's not even realism.
You can't double jump in real life.
Why can't I just do it as fast as Kingdom Hearts 2?
This sounds like the problem me and Digi were talking about in one of our first
I Am Games videos about realistic versus stylized movement mechanics in games.
And how, like, so many video games chasing realism add, like, anticipation and follow-through
to player interaction, which always slows everything down because you have to wait
for the realistic animation to play out.
Whereas most games play better with, like, sacrificing the integrity of the animation
so that it matches your input.
And a lot of these modern games don't do that.
Like, Digi was talking about, like, when you're trying to turn a character around,
they have to, like, step and rotate on their foot.
Fucking, I'm trying to play through Twilight Princess right now.
And I've literally had several deaths from, like, Link not turning correctly,
because he gets, like, stuck in his animation and will just walk off a fucking cliff.
It's like a transition between states and it's silly.
I was just thinking of, when I was watching you play The Witcher 3 the other day,
there was a moment where, like, you're walking around through all these corpses
and there was this dog that was in the area.
And I saw it just, like, glitch and spaz out and, like, change positions really quick.
And I was thinking of, like, The Last of Us, where I can't believe that in people discussing
that game, no one, well, some people have talked about it, but the fact that Ellie will just run
through areas, like, like, randomly and she'll be, like, clipping through objects and running
around and, like, disappearing and reappearing next to you.
And I'm like, how does this not take anybody out of the experience?
Like, this looks fucking terrible.
Because, Digi, it's fucking baby girl, my baby girl, my daughter.
That's all the people need.
It's like, to me, that means the game looks bad a lot of the time.
There's one video that was talking about that specific issue in The Last of Us,
and I specifically remembered them saying, like, they could have just had Ellie or your other
character wait at the beginning of the encounter, because, like, they're always in a room.
They're like, but that would just be lazy.
I'm like, but it would be so much fucking better.
And you wouldn't have known, like, they can say that, oh, it would be lazy, but that's
only because they've seen this alternative and they don't want to imagine having less.
Isn't it really lazier, though?
It seems, because it seems like you can't do anything at all.
Right, it's not lazier.
But AI is just going to do what it does and we're not going to bother trying to address this.
This person is thinking of that as reducing the amount of things in game.
Like, oh, instead of character moves, character doesn't move.
Ergo, that is less and therefore is lazy.
But they're not thinking about the fact that if it had been done that way,
they would not have questioned it.
It would not have seemed weird at all.
It would have seemed completely rational in the context of the story.
You could have even had a thing where, like, the character will wait or move based on your input.
You could call Ellie to follow you and then you'd have to make sure she doesn't get
fucking one-hitted by these guys as well.
That would be like a whole other level of gameplay.
But let's just have a run around.
I finally remembered.
There was this game.
I had a similar problem when we were talking about a game I actually played.
It was one of the, not story of seasons, what it used to be called, Harvest Moon.
Harvest Moon, I think, a story of two towns or something like that.
And what really annoyed me was this stupid horse mechanic.
I think it was in this game, I might be mistaken.
But I think it was in this game.
You got on the horse and it took a while for the horse to gain momentum.
And I would just never ride the horse because that's such a very cutesy,
simple sort of game.
And why do you add momentum to the horse?
Just hop on the horse and go.
The adding the momentum, it makes it hard.
Because it's such a sort of twitch, I need to only move one block and then stop,
two blocks and then stop.
You know, it's not like a vast exploration sort of game.
It's a very contained sort of map.
So by the time the horse moves, I already need to stop.
And it was so obnoxious and I just never used the horse.
It's just about what your priority is when you're making a game.
If your priority is realism.
Then stop making your game and throw it at the garbage.
I don't know why you would do that.
I don't know.
If there's a fucking, there's a very specific thing you want.
The blue glow I posted of Kingdom Hearts 3 and just like the sheer unbridled horror
when Mickey Mouse came on the screen and I saw what he looks like in this new graphical engine
that they've concocted out of the nightmares of children.
Yeah, yeah.
Like he looks like he looks like something killed Mickey Mouse and is now wearing his
flesh over its animatronic skull.
Like there's like his eyes are like not a part of his body.
Like it's like a weird mask.
Like the the graphics in Kingdom Hearts 3 have the graphics have become better than
the art style ever should have allowed for.
Yes.
Because now everything looks like smooth and like good and it's perfect and porcelain and creepy.
And mostly Mickey like everyone else like Goofy and Donald look okay and Sora looks fine.
I mean and you know it really it looks great.
But Mickey looks like a nightmare from hell.
I don't like how anybody looks and I don't like him.
Specifically from hell.
Everyone the whole game look okay obviously I got used to the Kingdom Hearts 2 art style.
I've been dealing with it for like 12 years now but you know everyone's so shiny.
They're so fucking shiny and you know what I got over it after a while so I'm not even that
upset about it but I do think man it's dumb is my point.
This is the Kingdom Hearts podcast every week.
No we gotta stop.
Let's go to voicemails.
We can stop.
Yeah why don't we get to the fucking voicemails.
We've been going on and on and on but it's I think I'm ready to transition.
Anyway else no anything to say.
Sure.
Yeah oh there is one little thing we have to do before we get to the voicemails.
You know it you love it and let's hear about it.
Okay here's a little remix for you guys.
Not the remix no.
I hate you.
You have to go back to the original.
This isn't how I wanted this to play out.
As you know calling each other gay is the meme way to say it.
Oh wait that's a long one shit.
Fuck the pizza party podcast.
Okay thank you thanks buddy.
So I'm so I just I'm just so you know I'm just so hashtag where's the podcast and I got so
frustrated with it yeah that I that I tweeted you know I tweeted some guy some some random guy
some guy named Nolan I don't know who he is I don't know how I found him you know I was you know
I was just like I just just shot him a tweet like where's the podcast and it was his birthday so
I threw in a happy birthday message but he was too busy celebrating the day of his birth
to tell me where's the podcast and I still haven't found it sounds like I think so I think
I think it might be a conspiracy I'm starting to get scared I think that maybe this is more than
just a subpar podcast I think that this might be an existential threat to us and all that we hold
dear and I'm mad and I'm sad and I'm and I'm depressed and I'm and I'm and I'm and I want to
pass that on to you the viewer hashtag where's the podcast well that's good Ben and luckily we've
got someone I think with a similar story here to back up what you're saying here so let's let's go
over here to a call from pizza party podcast is run by the Clinton Foundation let's see what that
might be about here we go we can only imagine pizza party podcast are they kidding us um excuse me
have you heard of Hillary Clinton yeah I've heard of pizza gate comment pizza cheese pizza
child pizza milk party spirit rituals they're rubbing it in our faces people they can't keep
getting away with this
pizza okay that's enough we can get that right there I think uh we get the idea all right well
what do we do well what do we do with this with this I guess we call up Alex Jones until we've
got a new weapon for his arsenal we broke the case we broke the case what do we do with we've
got a fucking bomb we're sitting on a landmine we've got a new attack vector that we can use
in alliance with the mainstream media to do something I don't know yeah I'm sure we can do
something I'm sure we've got a hashtag do something yeah hashtag do something somebody please hashtag
somebody please hashtag do something okay good I need to digest all this you're right well we'll
revisit this next week serious developments on the on the pizza on the pizza party pizza gate
party podcast front I'm gonna need to prey on this one okay next we got a voicemail here from
max hoving this one's real emotional so everybody please be respectful here we go
um hello members of the bcp my name is max how are you excellent I don't usually do this kind of
but I just wanted to tell you how grateful I am to you guys I recently came out of the closet
and it it's it's very empowering to see you guys just be so open about your gayness somehow I knew
he was gonna say that that's why I wanted to thank you guys have really you guys have really
me come out of my shell all right wrap it up okay and I appreciate that yeah good you got your
chuck a lot of us get out of here um um I was expecting a twist I was expecting him to have
come out of the closet as autistic or retarded or physically had been trapped I don't know if I
believe that guy's gay he needs to let me come over there and suck his dick to prove it hashtag
let digi suck uh we'll we'll get this one going we got to build steam okay next one uh this is
pcp conspiracy zero two uh there was zero one but it wasn't as good so let's hear this one
you know I've just been thinking recently yeah there's absolutely no way for me to confirm
that quote on quote Ben ben saint and quote unquote best guy ever are actually related
in any capacity I've seen no blood tests um that's true they seem to be completely opposed
politically we don't have our citizenship papers I really just don't document it and all the back
stories I've heard about the childhood you know they don't really sync up for me they don't they
don't really add up in my head I'm like hmm oh really huh you know they all sound kind of made up
sort of uh sort of fictionalized like um you know pre-planned yeah I don't know maybe it's just
me what I think that the whole the whole t-bap thing yeah get to the thing it was it was just a play
it was just a ploy like how the white stripes pretended to be siblings when they were actually
married is that true basically what I'm suggesting is that perhaps ben saint and best guy are are
actually um married married that could be it okay I don't know what's up yeah yeah that makes sense
well uh boy well now I mean I don't know can I even prove it can I even prove it to myself no
I don't think so okay well there you go that's it uh I don't know anything anymore untruth debunked
okay I have to say speaking as speaking as the person who was the best man at your wedding I think
he stole a shit I don't think there's any grounds to see it uh indeed let's move on here we got uh
giga dong mcfrank oh wait sorry mega giga dong mcfrank okay thank you I want to be culturally
respective go hey guys sorry if I sound a little weird I've been sick lately and also can't find my
blue yeti anywhere I need help because I recently met this girl and she's totally hot and she's into
me but we don't have the same interests and hobbies like she kind of likes anime I guess but what should
I do if I want to play video games with her and it turns out she sucks at them I'm 21 years old and
I am not a goddamn zoomer I hate cell phones I hate gen 4 pokemon and I fucking hate fortnite
thank you for your educated response um you don't have to have the same interests in her to have sex
with her or hang out and see if like I mean just date her and if she turns out to be boring then
break up yeah right that's fair so wait his his quest he's worried that she's gonna be too much of a
zoomer is that one I think that's definitely a valid concern I think he was saying she might
be too much of a normie for him like he likes he's into anime and video games and she's not
but like whether or not that becomes a problem will become apparent so just go for it that doesn't
work man uh anime and video games will be there forever but you know if if you if if she's the
one that got away then she won't be so uh put your childish bullshit to the side and
get some puss agreed I just no just fucking stay home forget about it if you don't get some puss
you're gonna be a puss every man has a push okay don't worry about it just be a puss ben saint
I'll I'll stand by that uh okay next up science man is calling in no doubt to educate us all
commence question how to get on the pcp voicemail
hypothesis say some weird relatable question then play the piano execution
have you ever tried to uh fuck your hamster but then your penis is too small
is that toho music no it's no game no life opening game well done well done
well yeah I mean well he proved it I don't think he's actually playing piano I think he's just
playing the song no that's probably true he had you hear that like couple of seconds he stumbled
and fumbled to get his way over to the button all right disconnect good job playing or not I don't
know definitely not it's hard to trust people I know that song very well it's definitely just the
song okay fair enough uh I will say though that though the whole uh question into piano thing
while cool is not enough to necessarily get you over the bar because there have been some that
have been skipped when there were too many of them or they just weren't interesting enough
few questions couldn't be improved with a little bit of piano I have to agree with that I have to
background music goes a long way on any of these questions yeah production values
exactly we demand professionalism uh okay now kersh keet man calling back once again go
ah I found you you thought you were safe no I didn't I only let you live the first time
this time I'm ending your life for disrespecting anime you will never see
I'm not the last thing you'll see will be me bating you up now it is time to die
ow stop baby I like anime
oh my
sorry about that dude okay why did you play that one it hurt I I know it hurts a lot but I felt
we deserved it uh but luckily we've got we're to to balance that out we're getting a call from
the god of anime is calling in next so he'll hopefully he can redeem us he'll take us to heaven
after I hope so go no what the fuck god damn it sometimes just doesn't work god damn it I'm
floating around here as a ghost Nate I need absolution here we go go there it is dear best
guy ever I the god of anime have hurt your prayers I will now grant you your one deepest desire thank god
there you go now Ben's gay as well
wow looks like both our wishes came oh we did it we did it uh high hoof high high
yes it must be nice that the man you're married to is finally willing to fuck you now
it's been a long struggle but I knew we'd get here in time um with with a little luck
and just a little bit of magic from the god of anime all right next one uh this one's called
steal we agawa uh not s t e e l s t e a l uh how ominous go
Nate yeah I just wanted to let you know that I am going to steal your style I am going to
steal your we agawa style because you're fucking retired oh and your fucking channel is dead so
I'm stealing it I'm telling you know I'm gonna fucking surpass you man I'm already a fourth of
the way there really I have a dead x minecraft youtube channel which I'm going to start back
up again rebrand it I'm not going to say what I'm doing I'm not going to fucking give it away
because I don't want anyone to fucking steal my idea but I am stealing your format and your sense
of humor just a heads up also a little bit of max mofos uh fucking door kicking in shit
from max mofo pokemon I'm gonna rip that off too okay uh just letting you know there's nothing
you could do about it because you cannot copyright a sense of humor so uh fuck you
you and uh yeah I'm gonna surpass you you know I respect this guy he's got he's got a plan yeah
me too he's got like he's got an actionable plan later I couldn't tell if he said that Nate was
retired or retired I think he said he retired pretty sure he said retired but he went on to
say that yeah I'm I'm I'm washed up I'm all done I've got nothing left to give and you know maybe
that's true you're forced into early retirement by this way uh you know I would just say I think
there are better formats than we agua I would recommend doing one of those instead because
you probably just do better but hey if it works for you I say go for it although if you call it
we add trap I will you you've been doing we are with all this time so that your enemies will think
it's a good idea and trap themselves into doing it that's true oh god I'm finally gonna pay off
all right let's I'm gonna make a I'm gonna make a bet with myself guys because uh I've been fucking
around I have to give myself an ultimatum okay by the time you hear this viewers if I have not
released the Kingdom Hearts 3 we agua I give you permission and I will not block or mute you to just
spam my twitter account endlessly at bestest guy ever spam it drive me into the fucking ground
drive me to early retirement if it's not out because it should have been out a week ago
so I have no excuses there you go uh hit me with your best shot fuck boys but it's gonna be out
so it's not even a big deal so don't worry about it um well hot damn there you go it's time for
you to be superseded by my new show be agua bitch I am giant baby
the sad part is the sad part is uh like getting one we agua done like over the span of like five
days shouldn't even be challenging in the slightest um but yet that's my major here we are and yet
here we are okay anyway forget all that shit we have one final message um this one I've been looking
forward to um it's from a man named hard poo poo go why is my poo poo hard
that's it that's the whole quest have we done it we did it boys we we you need to be drinking
more water dude you need to be consuming how is it more fiber or less fiber don't you want your
poo poo to be hard one of you you don't want it I mean not too hard for sure not like diarrhea soft
but also not like painful hard you know what's the what's the right eat some good mean lettuce
yeah exactly I mean didn't we I mean you didn't we say last episode right the pcp was the reason
people were dying of constipation but not anymore we're gonna fight maybe the show it might be
I mean nothing I mean I was saying nothing just yeah okay good good I feel good about that
um well I guess that's it uh did we do it we've done it make an episode we have made an episode
and and that's all there is to say about it I guess look at these texts I found I found uh
yeah I found the texts from last night when I was drunk that I uh sent to my significant other uh-huh
oh boy and it's just like and and there's no response until the very end so it's just like a
wall of outgoing texts and it starts with 7 15 p.m. hell yeah I'll do a good start yeah
7 20 p.m. hell yeah 7 25 p.m. hell yeah 7 35 p.m. hell yeah
dude sounds like a good night 7 40 p.m. oh fuck I'm horny 7 45 p.m. hell yeah 7 50 p.m. hell yeah
8 20 p.m. I am horny 8 25 p.m. hell yeah 9 p.m. hell yeah and then at 9 19 p.m. she finally texts back
glad you're having fun wait shit I didn't hear what was it glad you're having fun just glad you're
having fun you're having fun hell yeah oh you it's just like that time that you were what was it you
were texting me about existential death thoughts or something during radcon 3 or something I just like
I just love looking at this wall of texts and how perfectly timed it is 7 15 7 20 7 25 7 35
7 40 I think I was doing it on purpose like I think in my brain I was doing a bit
but nobody was on to it except me this one person got to witness the bit and I guess you as well
as your own most important critic and now everyone knows about it so thank god the world is aware
by the way look what mage drew in the show notes during the course of this podcast pretty spooky
pretty scary hold on where am I looking you're watching you're drawing a lot of spooky scary
shit these days yeah yeah traditional art is it's really good for a spooky art for me I guess
well that's interesting it's really fun you have such a dichotomy of style cool
it's like a slightly more anime version of like a uh scary stories to tell in the dark
kind of creature yeah you know you know what I mean I was thinking more like Todd McFarland
hmm I was thinking more like Seth McFarland and Lois I don't even work at Burger King
all right that's uh that's the end of the episode patreon.com slash the procrastinators
podcast isn't on the end of the url it's just the procrastinators god damn thank you Tom thank
god you're here for three years how do you not remember I don't know something happened recently
and I forget if that's on the okay patreon.com slash the procrastinators I guess if you trust
Tom in big quotations uh uh follow us at tbcrastinators on twitter uh and there's a
soundcloud link I think I don't know don't worry about it it's not that good anyway um all right
so that's it for the episode see you next week people bonus episode is out right now oh my god I
forgot to release it yesterday oops I better go do that right after we end have a beautiful day
don't think I haven't paid this month oh shit bye