What's up today guys? I'm not going to prolong this endeavor anymore because I'm trapped in
my father's wine cellar and listen it smells like wine down here which you would think would
be nice but after about 10 years it starts getting a little bit freaky. So I'm calling
for help. Is that Hippocrit on the other line? Hello, what is the nature of your emergency
or whatever? I'm trapped inside a wine cellar but I can record one more podcast before my
father comes in with a belt. What podcast should we record? Let's record a PCP. Okay, great.
Alright, we're going to pick people like a football coach in high school. I picked Tom
to be on the PCP. Oh fuck, I'm here on the final episode of the PCP. I'm so fucking stoked
to watch Munchy get destroyed. No, I picked Mage for the PCP. As tradition I get picked
last. Oh, it's true. It's funny because it's true. It's apt though. It's totally apt. Hey
by the way guys, wait, hold on. Head count. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 5 equals none. Wait a second,
guys. Ground quick and beat with our feet. Open up, fall into a chasm. A chasm full of
beauty. There's no, or been here. There's no need or been here. Oh, you know what that
means? You know what that means? Tom, what does that mean? Tom, what does that mean?
Tom, what does that mean? It means there's going to be no bullshit politics on this episode
of the PCP. It's literally impossible. Guys, I'm going to be real with you right now. Every
single day we record the PCP, I think myself, what topics can I bring up? There are like
one or two or three topics I think to bring up and I think myself, nah, the PCP sucks.
It's going to be political shit. I'm going to save this for RFCK. But there's no chance
of that. This PCP has no chance of being bad. I'm breaking it out. I'm breaking out the
good topics.
Oh, okay, okay.
All right, all right. Finally, a good discussion.
I have one thing to say before you get into the good topics though. As of you listening
to this audience member, Balejap Finale is out and is on the APSAdventures.site. Go watch
it, go read it. Balejap is done. I did it. It's not out for the members of the PCP to
watch and listen to and react to right now. Unfortunately, I was hoping to get it done
by now. But you will be able to see it. So links on the screen and in the description
to my thing, my big thing.
Yeah, his big dick that is whipping around on the internet.
Yeah, okay, hippo. That's like really cool though. You know, you're like, oh, jail, paper,
automation.
Can we please talk about the thing that was released on my channel that is not viewable
by the PCP members, but will be the time that the viewers are listening. And that's the
first episode of the Teen CP. Yes, that's right. The Teen CP. It's actually happened.
It was a nine man podcast that was recorded. It will be released on my channel. And truly,
it was sublime. If you lie, if you were a fan of the Charismat character that is the
Teen CP from these voicemail series, then you will just fucking just quiver and quake
and your asshole will break by the time you listen to that fucking podcast. So look forward
to that. And I look forward to that. I mean, look forward in the past backwards because
you can click on the link in the description right now. Go click on jail, babe. And like,
you know, cry because it's, you know, jail, babe. And then click on the Teen CP and cry
because it's on the heart of the Teen CP. You keep saying jail, babe. It's bail, jaype.
It's a jaype. I say, I say jail, babe, every single fucking time, literally like in text
and in conversation. Is it like a mistake? Is it a mistake or is it just like, oh, well,
you know, no. I'm on every man. Okay, guys, here's what's happening right now. As Tom
said before the podcast, but you guys didn't hear because you don't have long enough ears.
I am in Boston, Massachusetts right now. Boston, Massachusetts. Do do knock on wood. There
I did it. What was supposed to happen? Don't know. Anyway, I'm here right now. And I'm
in the vicinity of Tom in like a 25 square meter. So we're going to meet the hell up.
And I've already meeting up with Ben. Tom wasn't there because he's in a wheelchair.
He's wheelchair bound. We're going to get like an actual wheelchair for you and then
push you around the time. It's going to happen. Dude, I can't wait. I'll just be the brand
of the PCP. I'll do nothing, but I'll be king by the end. It's going to happen yesterday.
Like a week ago, by the time the viewers are hearing this, I was with Ben and Kazi and
every time we like saw someone that was incapacitated in any way, like they were stumbling or like
they were in a wheelchair. We cropped to the ground laughing up fucking awesome.
As you should. No. Well, no, we pointed and said that's Tom and then dropped the four
lines. But there's so many. This trip to Boston is a truly sentimental one because this is
the last time I will ever be in this city as a tourist. This is the last time I will
ever not live here. I don't know if I said this on the PCP. I'm sure I did, but I probably
just got in and got right out and then like, you know, I went to the building, planted the
bomb and then just ran away as fast as I could, you know, as you do. But yeah, I'm in college,
fully enrolled, fully put down everything that I need to, not even like a maybe like,
you know, like, oh, you know, probably going to happen. Like, no, really going to happen.
So you got accepted.
A guy, dude, I got accepted. I put down my down payment. I have my room. I have my room
assignments. I have fucking everything.
That's fucking legendary, dude. Congrats.
I know what it what is. Oh, I guess, September is probably when you start.
Of course. So I'm here for another week and then I'm going to be leaving. And then the next
time I set foot in these fair aisles, I shall be a resident. I shall be a legal resident.
Do you know what you should definitely do is at college in your class, you should get as many
people to join RFCK as possible.
Oh, dude. Okay.
And then and then like when you do like a live RFCK, RFCK, like, calm, you'll have like a
hundred thousands of people will be already in Boston to do it.
Oh, okay, no doubt.
There are going. Oh, no, God.
Oh, no, we were off to such a good.
All right, guys, you don't pack it at the good topics are coming back into the bag.
Sorry, guys, I'm going to have to leave now.
No, no.
Oh, he's he's he's he's deaf in himself.
Ben St. Ben St. came into the call.
And by the way, I believe in Paul, please play the sound that plays when you meet
and or if not, every no time, but anyway, just to finish that, I don't even know what the
fuck I was talking about.
But in college schemes, schemes to get people on to play in this war in college.
I really thought about it.
I am going to it basically completely shift my life around in a pretty major way and sort
of like fully dedicate myself to college or at least at the very least, that's the plan
currently. Of course.
And yeah, and I am going to go as hog while that's possibly came doing curricular and
extracurricular activities and try and do clubs and all that sort of stuff like that.
Get the most bang for my buck.
And part of that, I assume there will be some sort of, you know, video game development club.
If there's not, I'll literally just make one of my own because, you know, fucking are you joking
me? Fucking art college is not going to be able to make video games.
Yeah, yeah. Disgusting, unacceptable.
Yes, fucking moron.
Ben was talking here, but wasn't recording his audio yet because he's a moron.
But that's usually because my microphone sucks.
And also I hate you.
There he goes.
Just just kick him.
Somebody kick him.
Just get him out of here.
But by the way, I really hope that he wasn't recording thinking that we hadn't started
the show yet. And now, now no one will be able to understand why we laughed.
I really hope that was the case.
By the way, audience, um, love you.
Okay.
Anyway, back to what we were saying, uh, I am going to shill endless war so, so, so fucking
hard in whatever game development or even just to anyone that I fucking know, I'll
swear an endless war t-shirt that has a link to the discord on it.
But rest assured, I'm going to be shilling.
You're going to be the most powerful person in college because everyone else is going
to be like, uh, yeah.
I just came from my parent's house.
I'm ready to, to learn the ways of like anatomy and drawing and stuff.
And you'd be like, I'm already a seasoned game designer.
I have a video game.
I have a huge audience.
I make tons of money.
Yeah.
I'm like teaching you guys.
I'm teaching the classes now.
Dude.
Okay.
There is.
When you got accepted to college, they, there was an email sent to you saying directing
you to the Facebook group of the college being like, Hey, come on and mingle with some
of the new bingles.
And then I thought, well, I'm a bingle.
Might as well mingle.
And then I mosey dawned over and then I pose on Beauvard.
And I got into the, uh, Facebook and it was really uncomfortable and strange to actually
post on, on Facebook.
Brush assured the other zoomers there thought so as well.
And so they made a discord group and I entered a discord, a discord group for all of the
freshmen that are attending and also know what discord is, I guess.
And it was a really interesting experience to be able to, you know, like, like, like actually
like have like prolonged conversations with people from the school.
Cause obviously I'm no stranger to the school.
I've been there on multiple occasions, been all over the campus.
No, no, a lot about it.
And been to one or two social functions in there, you know, not major things, but I've
been to some, uh, some fucking hangout sessions with some of the people there.
And, uh, they were nice.
And one of the reasons I wanted to attend was that I thought that I could gel well with
the people there.
But I had not had, you know, prolonged conversations in a, in a, in a, in a discord like chat experience.
And so I was able to, the first time after receiving that blink, click that link, I said
to myself and then did so.
Uh, and entering the chat was, I think my first experience would be it was, was something
to the effect of like, wow, I like these people will be so fun to lead.
You know, like it was like, it was like walking into like a orphanage, thinking myself like,
wow, I'll be like the best like executor of commands that anyone could possibly be ever
where it's like, they were all nice people, but you could tell they were all a little
bit insecure.
So I know that I'm going to be able to use that to my advantage and get them to do like,
not like, you know, like evil things for me, but we're going to be able to like make like
cities.
Like we shall make like, in Minecraft.
Yeah.
In Minecraft.
We're going to be able to fucking achieve any goals with me at their helm.
Me as their benevolent dictator overlord.
I will be able to lead the, uh, are you going to go in like, like first day in the pizza
jumpsuit?
Yeah.
Why not?
I think that's, that's, that's a good way to establish dominance.
You know?
Oh, for sure.
Dude, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm going to wear the pizza jumpsuit because fucking, you know,
Yeah.
YOLO, bro.
YOLO.
It's, I, I, in, in the, in the initial Facebook group, there was, it was customary to make
a post like saying like, Hey guys, it's me, you know, check out me, Teehee.
And then I did so as well.
And all the photos that I sent to word, they were all from anime expo.
And there was me and my pizza, uh, my pizza onesie nearly next to a, uh, power box that
had picture of an aunt on it doing a peace sign.
Then it was me with Digi and Nate doing the Neko Neko, uh, like, like anime pause with
all the cat girl maids and those were the images.
I saw that image recently.
The one closest to you looks very disturbed.
Uh, that's going to be the entirety of my college.
How long do you think it's going to be for somebody who's going to be like, Oh my God,
Monchi, you know Digi, bro.
Um, I think it's due.
Uh, my Kazi goes to the school I'm going to and she by proxy already gets people to
be in like, you know, someone who knows Digi bro.
So, uh, it's going to be.
She's like, yeah, I know myself, you fucking idiot.
I've met Digi bro.
Oh yeah.
I forgot about that.
Worlds, worlds colliding.
Did you, were you recording last time?
Of course not.
You know what Ben?
Fuck you.
No, no, no.
Don't you start up this here.
No.
Then I have the power to kick you.
Oh, she does.
She's the she's the dude.
Do that and look like the biggest piece of shit.
Go right ahead.
I could.
I know.
Damn, please.
Above us all.
What are we taught?
What are we talking about?
What are we?
What have I missed so far?
We're talking about college.
We're talking.
We're talking about.
We're talking about how it's been.
You and Ben aren't here.
So now we are free to do as we please.
Me and Nate, you know, just confuse me and Nate.
No, you said you and Ben.
You said you and Ben, yeah, obliterated.
Same for Tex and logic.
Um college sucks.
Yeah.
Yeah, we know.
Yeah, yeah, we know. But, right, new topic, video games.
Video games suck.
This is a video game-related topic. I've been working tirelessly, like, for weeks, for months on Balejape.
I am, like, so close, as in, like, it will be out by the time you're... I mean, I already said that already.
And I've got, like, a few panels left, and it will probably be out by the end of today, even.
But I have been so fucking... I want to play a video game so hard.
Every day, I'm, like, I'm looking at my DS, even. I'm looking at my 3DS. I'm looking at my consoles.
I even bought a Nintendo 64 on a whim, just so I could have another game console.
I could look at it and be like, hey, that's old.
So you can be, like, one of those video game review men on YouTube with a wall of consoles.
Yeah, I could, I could, like, be like that.
And I look at my video games on the shelf and I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It hurts so much not being able, like, not even Minecraft, not even, like, anything. I've just been working.
I've gone insane.
That's good. That's good work.
But I want to say that during my time animating and drawing for so long, playing games is a good escape.
You can't, you can't just give up sleep because you'll just burn yourself out. That's stupid.
You can't give up entertainment entirely.
No.
So I have sort of quit, like, failed the YouTube challenge that I started in the beginning of the year.
Where now I am, like, on my off-screen, off-monitor, watching videos basically all the time because I'm always basically drawing.
So it's like, I failed, you know, it sucks. I got, like, about three months into that.
And then I just sort of gave up because it was, yeah.
I mean, if you're just, if you're just listening to them off-tab while you're working, does that really count?
Well, it definitely still counts.
It definitely still counts. It's just sort of like, it was, it was easier for me to, to rationalize it when I was animating because so much of that is, like,
you can just sort of, like, tune out the, the thing. It just needs some sort of sound.
Wait.
I listened to music for a while.
But wasn't the whole point of doing it in the first place to prevent you from procrastinating and not doing, like, productive things with your time?
It, that was the point. And, and, and that's why I sort of was okay with quitting it. I might pick it up again later.
Well, that's what I was going to say. Is it's not necessarily bad if you actually are working while you're doing it.
The trap for me is that I'll say, I'll start watching a video and work while I have it on. And then that's not what happens.
Yeah, but that's the thing. So sometimes it does, it does distract me. And I've noticed this and I'm like, yeah, this is, this is,
it's not as bad as it used to be, but it's still distracting. It's still here. And I'm still letting myself be distracted on occasion.
Are you distracted in like, you just start listening to the audio and not doing the work, or do you just tab over and start watching the video?
Well, I've been watching a lot of like T90, like streams of Age of Empires 2 competitive scene stuff.
So like, every so often, he goes, oh my God, the quick wall or whatever he says, like the terminology.
And I'm like, whoa, I want to see that thing. And I click over and look at it. You'd be like, yeah, yeah, that was, that was very exciting.
And then I go back to work. But like, um...
Is this video game lust different than normal?
Different than normal lust?
I don't know what it is. I think, I think I'm just in like a nostalgic feeling.
Like a lot of things are just reminding me of like, oh yeah, I want to play that game.
I think it's because like during Hippocrite, every time I was thinking, oh, I should play that game from my childhood,
for the reason of like making a video about it and you know, getting views and subscribers and money and stuff.
And so the prospect of playing a game would be to sit down, play it properly, take notes, do all the, you know, record the footage.
It will be a big hassle. And I did that for a while and I ended up like not caring about video games by the end of like when I stopped doing the Hippocrite stuff.
But now that I, that's never like, is not a thing anymore. I just, I can feel the lust of gaming again.
I think that's what it is.
You know, that kind of rolls into something that I've experienced the last couple of days because I've been playing nothing but like Dark Souls 1, Dark Souls 3 and Bloodborne.
I've been marathoning all of them back to back, put like 200, 300 hours into those games over the past couple of weeks.
And just yesterday, I think it came in, I ordered the Analog Mega SG, which is like a HD version of a Sega Genesis.
They like remade it. So it's not emulation. It's like real hardware that like re-engineered all the hardware and made it so it outputs to 1080p so it can work with HD TVs and like not be shit.
So I got that because I wanted to start playing Sega again because I'm making a Sega game essentially.
Exactly.
That's the one.
That's the very same.
That's the one. The only Sega. The only one that ever existed. The rest don't, aren't real.
So I wanted to get into those games again to kind of like get me inspired and like be like okay this is how these games kind of work.
This is what the visuals look like. This is like some gameplay mechanics I could learn from.
And it was interesting because I played like Bloodborne especially because that's my favorite one I've played so far.
And I just did nothing else. Like I just got up, played Bloodborne, went to bed and like for like a week. It was bad.
But with Sega games they're like so much simpler that like I'll just play them for like a half an hour.
I'm like I'm good because like they're not immersive and like soul consuming.
They're just like simple little games that like you can't get sucked into.
And it's interesting that way. So I'm like playing Sega. I'll just play it for like 20 minutes.
I'm like I'm good. I got my inspiration. I can go back and do work now.
Back in the day the games were built around the idea of you die a lot and therefore in order to see more you can pay money in the arcade and stuff.
And so they brought that to home consoles with that design philosophy.
But now a lot of it is how can we keep you staying here and you know just repeating the same tasks every day over and over again.
With like daily quests and mobile games or that sort of keeps you coming back rather than putting a quarter in the thing.
I want to quickly say. Do you guys like this whole topic reminded me of back when I had my very first Xbox.
Like I only had one Xbox but it was like the first Xbox.
And on one of the games it had like previews of other games and you could play them for free the demos.
And it was kind of like such a weird thing because it was only like that was the only time I actually had like a game that had other games on it.
That you can sort of play a little bit as demos that that's like was that a thing.
Was that like a thing. I think there were like demos like demos on console like on your console.
Oh like some some early Xbox games did do that.
Like there you buy a lot of first party Microsoft titles.
I think that they have options to play like demos of other games they had published because they were trying to get people into like the Xbox ecosystem.
I don't think PlayStation really did that much.
PlayStation had the official PlayStation magazine and every month that came with a demo disk.
So that's just like kind of a big game.
Is that PMX 2 or PSM 2 or whatever it was called.
Oh god.
PMS 2 bigger, faster, bloodier.
The reckoning.
I know in America it was OPM the official PlayStation magazine.
OPM you know they're addictive.
Yeah it was very addictive because that's where I first played Shinobi my favorite PS2 game.
I think that I'm broken.
For some reason I don't even think it's tied to like productivity or you know maturing or anything to that effect.
But I've just lost all will to play video games and it makes me feel kind of weird because it's not as though I don't want to play video games in the sense that I don't like them.
It's just that I have no like.
You're broken get a factor of reset.
You should try to enter the gungeon if you like nuclear thrown.
No that's not it.
Well I'm just saying that I'm saying that because I feel that way sometimes but then other times I will like.
Yeah everyone I'll stumble across a game and that'll engage me for a while and I'll play a lot of it.
So I'm just saying like you know I think you and I have kind of similar taste in some games.
We do.
So like that's.
Sometimes.
Yeah.
I mean I know I feel like this is this is something that I mean has happened to me probably will happen to you.
You're going through it right now is where like you used to like you know have so much free time as a younger person.
You can play a game for an entire day.
I used to play World of Warcraft a lot during the summer.
Just all the time and I would get so much XPs.
What a true unembarrassment of XPs.
Yeah.
But like after you know after I started having responsibilities and school wasn't a chore it was like a choice.
I was doing things because I wanted to learn or wanted to get better at things.
I had realized that there were certain things that I just want to work towards and the time for gaming was like a couple hours every so often and then it just sort of became like you know less and less.
Now most of the time where I play games is only when I really feel like it and that's not every day.
I mean right now it is but like yeah like I used to go every day playing at least one game at a certain amount of time and now I can go a week without like picking up a thing.
My media consumption has really just been twisted in terrible ways where it's not that I don't think video games are worth my time.
It's just that I've really been funneled into YouTube right where it's right there on my desktop so so close within reach.
I always have tabs open on a Firefox and working Google Drive or something.
Just click that little plus type.
Click that little bell to get notifications every time I upload a new video.
Get notifications and you're fucking every five seconds you're going in.
You're a fucking fool and like comment and subscribe.
Share this video with all your friends.
Share it on social media and video games and movies and all that sort of stuff that I want to watch.
But it's just even just locating movies online even if I have to torrent or you can even go to some free illegal screen site.
It's so much easier to do YouTube which is really a problem and I've limited my YouTube usage.
Funnily enough while you're getting off the YouTube challenge I'm tying it not to the point where you did where it was like you know no YouTube ever because I realized that that just would like I wouldn't be able to do that so why even.
Munchy the way you were describing feeling about video games is a way that I felt for a long time about movies like I have.
I feel like movies ever since I was born I barely ever watched movies I have no I have no desire to like seek out movies to watch I hardly even know how I would do it.
And I feel that way in spite of the fact that logically I know that there is a Netflix subscription like directly down the stairs from where I'm sitting right now that I have free access to.
But I'm just like why would I ever do that.
What's the what's my motivation.
I think I did watch Fury Road a couple weeks ago which was pretty great but I'm like OK I watched a movie for the first time in like 20 years.
I think that's good for another 20.
I know that I would like to recommend them before and then I know that you know or you know whatever I watch a YouTube video as soon as I thought wow that would be good.
And I think just in like just in concept watching art as an artist is pretty valuable to broaden your artistic.
It is.
You know Mary Weather messaged me to give me his hot take on the whole pro Jared thing the other day.
And he like sort of after we talked about that he was he recommended me a manga and I was like man I should I should you know you know I don't know you know maybe I'll check out this man.
But in particular I should just I should read more manga as you get back into reading manga.
I should consume more media that isn't dudes on YouTube talking about other media because like what the what the fuck is that.
We should we should continue watching that anime.
We should mage I've been waiting to say this.
I'm sorry I snapped at you.
I think I think I when you see the thing about kicking me I took it as sincere and I'm pretty sure it was a joke.
The thing is I did I like directly rolled out of bed and like hit and like turned on discord to get in here and I don't think I was thinking properly.
I responded inappropriate.
OK I've been waiting to say that for like 20 minutes.
I appreciate it but it's it's fine.
I thought you were just doing the meme that we did on the quick quick draw.
Yeah.
The quick draw screen.
No the quick subscribe to quick draw everybody.
No I was just legitimately grouchy because I just woke up.
Can I say that real quick just in the middle here.
People are like where's the draw cast but like if you liked the draw cast then you would fucking.
Oh sure.
Fucking yeah yeah the draw cast has mutated and and split off like a like a tumor like a brain tumor exploding out of ones.
Out of ones head cavity.
You know like they like to do like like like a numeral to.
Yeah like a to like a T. O. O. M. E. R.
Split off into its own organism and is now the channel known as quick draw and there's what like four of them out now.
Yeah.
Hell yeah like that fucking link.
It's good.
I think all of us are in Tom hasn't appeared on episode yet but you can.
No yeah no definitely.
He isn't.
He doesn't do fucking 2D art.
He's too good.
Hey guys.
Me.
My name's Tom.
Okay.
Now I don't know how viable this is but what if Tom just did like a 3D model in the time that the rest of us were doing a 2D.
Like like a super low that would show us like a super low poly obviously like I'm sure it would be really hard.
Tom question is how do you do you think it was like how viable do you think is the idea of creating a 3D model.
Of a thing in like 15 minutes.
Is that even possible.
It would depend on what you're drawing like a human character probably not because you have to like model it then you have to rig it then you have to texture it.
What what if we were like what okay hypothetical what if it was like.
Okay last episode of the quick draw we revisited the idea from the draw cast of limited color palette and it was great.
My palette was the best.
What if we were what if we were like hey.
Hey here's a color palette make any model you want and use this color palette for it in 15 minutes.
Now I don't know anything about 3D modeling so I haven't yeah.
I mean at least for me it would not be enough time like I can draw I can still do drawing and be on quick.
I know I know I know I'm just thinking like what what if like what if some fucking weirdo like Tom were to come in here and in blender or whatever and do some some out there nonsense.
Just blend something together.
We have fruit is the topic though but so been so I'm sorry but you're gonna have to leave now you've been voted out.
Yeah well.
No I'm gonna I'm gonna reply I'm gonna I'm gonna reply as though you're sincere but this time I'm gonna be sad instead of mad.
You know and on the topic of broadening horizons and seeing yes please lots of different types of art.
I've also been feeling like YouTube is like generally just sort of sludge just sort of like grimy sludge that's you know it smells.
Well it's like it's like that it's like that you wouldn't want to live there but we all do.
It's like that debut video about how YouTube is the stomach acid.
Some yeah stomach.
Yeah.
Good.
Davoo is good.
Classic.
I agree.
I've been I've been having the same.
Where's the last couple days and like I've been thinking more and more about like really wanting to make that website.
I keep talking about where it's like it's like a YouTube but you can only everyone can only upload one video a week and that's it.
I hear.
There was this one.
I want to do that.
I want that to be a real site.
There was this one thing that I watched a Digi video and in the background I think it was a let's argue and there was a bunch of like a manga volume.
Like really small low low resolution in the backgrounds floating past him.
I saw one that was like how hang on.
I think that girl looks pretty cute.
Pause.
You know cut that image out.
Search by image.
I went on a journey to try and find this manga because you know I don't read that many manga.
I read One Piece and Bleach and Naruto are both over.
Dragon Ball Z is not really a thing.
One Piece is the only manga I see.
So I was like if this is good then this will be a really funny way to have found it.
So I searched by image.
I found the cover.
It's kind of obscure.
I forgot the name of it honestly because it turns out the girl was cute and the guy is a good artist but the manga was shit.
It was boring and stupid.
What was the premise?
I just liked that journey of like discovering something just because it's sort of like difficult to do.
Like rather than getting a recommendation from someone just like hmm.
Yeah you just like you found it yourself essentially.
You're like this looks interesting.
No one told me it was interesting.
I want to know the premise now.
It was there was a girl who had like someone she loved fell from a tree and this guy was like I'm going to cut down this tree.
And she was like huh don't do that fuck you.
And then it's like a romance between those two characters.
Wait between between her and the guy who wants to cut down the tree.
It was a boy.
It was a young boy who's like fuck this tree.
I hate this tree.
And you know it's obviously going to be like a romance between the two of them.
But then some weird like angel magical stuff came up and it was just sort of like that's not really cool.
That's kind of lame.
That's sort of like bad writing.
That's like zero out of ten.
What is gamathrone.
And she doesn't want to cut down the tree because someone she loved fell out of it and died I presume.
Well it was someone fell and broke their legs and couldn't walk.
But if the tree wasn't there they would have fallen to their death sort of thing.
I don't remember.
I don't remember it very closely.
I was just sort of skimming it was like this.
I mean it was very obscure that the scan lations I saw were like so low resolution.
It was very hard to see a lot of detail.
You know when like a manga is like it's online and it's so like grainy that it's certain lines are like cut out because of the low resolution like thin lines are sort of like dots.
The old days.
The struggle.
Yeah.
So it was but the girl was a good girl.
It just I like that design.
I really do feel like it's been a disservice to me like as a person.
I feel like I'm not as edified as I should be because I am so like cut off from media traditional media.
I guess I would call even though that's not really true.
I just mean like non regurgitated non stomach acid media which is the bulk of what I listen to.
But I am fixing that and I would notice what they say conquered it in any way.
But you know when you start a new thing and you can feel in the bowels of your bowels that you know that this is a good idea and like you know stick with this and good things will happen.
I made a big change in my life.
I've downloaded an application.
I want to just say to everyone in this group and in the audience something that you need to hear because we've all heard free will doesn't exist.
So here's the true red pill.
Self control doesn't exist.
It doesn't matter if you want to do something and if you say to yourself I'm going to make a change in my life.
I'm just I'm just going to you know I'm just going to go to the gym and then you stop thinking about it.
That you nothing will ever be accomplished.
If you think to yourself I'm just going to rely on my self control.
Self control doesn't exist.
You are an animal.
You're a beast.
You need a harness to able to be able to control your rage if left to your own devices.
No matter what I don't care if you're the fucking president you will turn into a carnivorous beast if left to your own devices.
You need to create a cage that is just comfortable enough around you to not you know you know chafe but just tied up to not allow you to be the depraved monster that you know that you are.
So instead of just you know being like guys you know what this is all cool and well.
I'm going to stop watching YouTube and I'm going to get you know in on some more traditional meat.
I'm going to play some games.
I'm going to watch some movies that will not happen because why would I I haven't changed anything about my life.
I've not changed the system under which I operate and if the system isn't changed.
Why would I expect a different outcome when I execute the program that is my life change that fucking code and what code am I changing.
I've downloaded a program called cold turkey and it's an app blocker that literally forbids me from opening YouTube and will not allow me to.
I hear you all clicking to fucking go Google.
It will not allow me to watch YouTube videos or various other things such as discord.
I have scheduled blocks under which like from like sleeping time literally it locks me out of my computer.
This is hardcore shit I'm dealing with right now.
I've seen that I was looking for similar things because I wanted to block discord for the first like 19 hours of the day.
So that I only jump on at the end to just like talk when I'm tired with friends and stuff.
But that fucking turkey thing you got to pay for it and as soon as money was involved.
I was like oh shit.
You recommended me another like timer app.
God what was it called.
The thing about like tracking how yeah.
Toggle.
You don't have to pay for that.
Yeah you fucking do.
I went to the website and it wasn't free.
No you don't.
The mobile app is free right now.
That's the one that's like you can like put in how much time you spend on things right.
Yeah.
I'm using it for free.
You're just a freak.
You're a freak.
I'm not.
No I'm normal.
I'm normal.
No.
You're a freak.
There's one thing about toggle.
Like section here.
I'm sure you can get a pro version.
Yeah you can get a premium thing.
Like enterprise is custom pricing premium and starter.
None of them are free.
I don't fucking understand.
Maybe it's only free on the mobile app.
No I have it on desktop.
You're used to freak dude.
Playing simple.
It knows it knows it and it won't let you download it.
Yeah.
All right.
I guess I wouldn't either if I were toggle.
One thing about toggle.
I tried.
I got daily own toggle the day you mentioned those.
Yes.
I was pretty good like 22 23 days in a row.
I remember 55 days dude.
So you know I've been doing that that prompts me at the when I turn on my phone like how
was your day.
It's like oh yeah.
It was good.
It's been good most days sometimes it's rare.
But toggle.
I tried for like a week and then I stopped using it because a lot of the time you know
you press a button it starts a timer you press the button again and that is like a chunk
of time that you have logged while you're doing something.
So when I would draw I would press the button draw and then when I feel like a needed breaker
press the button again and then at the end of the day I can see how many hours I'm spending
on certain things.
That's good.
It's just when I get distracted by certain things it's I don't remember because I'm being
distracted I don't remember to press the button and then the data started to become
all over the place like hours of hours of like oh I wasn't animating for those extra
hours.
I think I was doing something else.
Ah shit.
I said.
And then I just sort of fell out of using it because it's it's it's too it's it's sort
of I can't really get gleaned too much from it.
The only thing that it's good for really is the idea that there is a timing thing going
on during work so that you're less likely to be distracted sort of like having a boss
over you like tapping his wrist like you better get this certain amount of hours in like
the only the only real benefit is the side benefit the main benefit doesn't work.
I get it.
I disagree and I think that the problem that you're putting forward is actually a feature
and one thing that I quite like about it I think there's so many minor transition costs
when you do what I do draw for a little bit make a few lines go back to YouTube click
on YouTube video watch for a couple seconds then go back to drawing the switching back
and forth between those apps obviously the clicking time is nothing but your brain just
focusing in on the drawing like oh fuck what was it doing our coding like oh fuck where
was I what was I doing milliseconds right but those add up and I think that just I mean
they are distractions YouTube videos and you know whatever podcast anything else that could
theoretically be in that position is a distraction and therefore detrimental to you being as
productive as you possibly could be.
So yeah you're right the data will be skewed so don't do it unhealthy behavior it's try
it's an active disincentive to do something that is bad and that I don't think is a good
thing so my click on that timer I think myself okay I know what I have to do I'm going to
work for whatever in many hours that I think is appropriate and I won't do anything else
because one thing that goes hand in hand with the cold turkey thing which is a you know I
can schedule out blocks is that I have clear working times and I have clear you know leisure
times and so I think myself okay I'm gonna be working for this long I'm gonna you know
start a timer I'm going to work and I'm not gonna be distracted because I know I will have
time to goof off soon so why be distracted now just get my work done I do it I clock
out and it's fucking primo dude it's fucking projudo wrap that shit in mozzarella and
eat that literally delicious it's fucking basil straight up straight up basil bro straight
up basil on a t-shirt cook on spain hey it's funny cuz like cuz like you know most people
like go to work and have a real job and it does that automatically you have work time
and relax time but we have to like do that ourselves I I don't know guys like for me
I have to have something in the background to work I can't work without the noise so hold on
yeah there are podcasts and music I think are well worth my time this isn't like a time to close
myself off in a cave like you know I have to be fully dedicated my work no brainpower can be
allocated there are many podcasts which are not two dudes talking about fucking nothing that I think
are extremely beneficial to my being to my core that I think honorically edify me and I think
it's important and fun for me listen to and there are tons of audiobooks I can listen to and just
tons and tons of music how often do I listen to music fucking never besides when I'm working how much
do I love music quite a bit so it really it's not that I'm I'm trying it's it's again it's I'm
making a cage for myself that is not chafe it merely restrains myself and makes me more disciplined
okay it's fantastic for me that's not what I was saying okay okay I'm just saying like I need the
noise to work like I can what I do is I find a playlist of something I don't particularly care
about but just interested just enough to sort of like tune in every now and then but it's not
something important or worthy that I have to pay attention properly for instance I've been so you
guys know though the people who like read out reddit posts and stuff like yeah yeah our whoosh or
our slash that happened so I I just find one of them and they upload like daily I go to play all
the videos and I just like have that playlist going in the background and I don't have to switch
between the videos is just constant noise and I don't particularly need to like I just I take in a
little bit just enough to get the context and and I'm drawing and I'm focusing on my drawing for the
most part I just I get I get just enough of that noise to keep me going and from getting irritated
because I get irritated when there's no noise and I can't focus on my work and then I just end up
browsing for forever trying to find something to listen to because I just cannot work on other days
if I if I find like find that like a really good song that's like really catchy or something like
that and I just put that song on loop for fucking five hours that one song on loop and while I'm
drawing because it just gives me that inspiration to draw and keep going and I just I have to and
like if I if I switch to a different song it changes the mood because you know different songs
different moods different feelings behind it but I need that one specific song so I have that song
on loop and that's how I work and I cannot work without the noise yeah I you know I think I feel
like if there's like a podcast that is truly edifying like super important and you really love
listening to it that would be way more of a distraction than something like a game grumps
playlist that you've heard like eight times already yeah exactly like something to know to dull the
brain like what was that thing that Japanese thing the bamboo that goes up and down with the
water feature oh yeah like the sound of running water is supposed to be calming and it's just
supposed to create like noise I think it's calming because it's just sort of you know a background
stuff like noise to to fill in so that you're not like noticing small sounds and thinking about what
they could be or you're not noticing your own bodily movement sounds it's just sort of like your
ears get to turn off while this noise plays well so you can focus more on the things that you're
looking at I don't disagree that white noise is valuable nor do I think that people shouldn't use
it and mage if you feel like you are not distracted by YouTube videos well that's fine I do that and
that's why I'm working to solve yeah yeah it has to be certain kind of content because if it's
something I'm generally interested in and want to listen to yeah I'm gonna get distracted by you
because I want to focus on that but if it's something I can just sort of like it's not important
it's kind of like trash but at the same time I'm vaguely interested it's just like ha ha it's a
funny sort of story but it's not mandatory for me to listen to it's not something important then I
can just have it in the background and not really see my brain works really weird where that there
are certain tasks I can do with background noise like if I'm drawing I'll usually have music or
something on in the background just to kind of keep part of my brain occupied while I'm doing this
but if I'm reading anything if I'm writing anything or if I'm or if anytime something gets really
difficult like if I'm doing like coding stuff for my game whatever and like I've run into a problem
all that has to immediately be turned off I need a hundred percent of my brain on this topic yeah
can't if I'm absorb any of it if I'm writing dialogue or sketching and coming up with poses I
can't listen to anything if I'm inking I can listen to something because it's a little more
mindless if I'm if I'm yeah if I am editing a video or something that requires more a lot more
focus I probably have to turn it on especially if I'm editing a video you have to listen to audio
them but yeah I need to turn that shit off but let's talk about let's talk about Twitter
hippo okay hippo I see here's my ego I see this red man comic I got into some internet drama
recently I said some guy was dumb I didn't need to say it but I said it anyway I guess I'm the
dumb one is this about me weeks ago I have like a stockpile of red man oh I say it's not okay I
read that I was ready to fight no I wouldn't I don't necessarily think you getting into Twitter
arguments is a bad thing I think it's kind of funny yeah and you clearly enjoy some of it yeah I do
but it you know I say generally arguing is exhausting and you get a little tired after a
while I mean like with the Mahler thing the other day like I got a little tired of answering to
like these fucking randos but I felt like obligated to explain myself when I thought they said
something that was like oh I can actually see how you might have a misinterpret I don't know
they're all mostly just fucking dumb idiots who were just like Mahler's smart and you're stupid
for you're not agreeing with him why do you think he's wrong haha you're the one who just thinks
he's wrong with no explanation like ah god damn it so that was terrible I don't know people
been criticizing me people say they hate my tweets they hate my Twitter people on follow me
because because I have opinions and because I don't just post something sarcastic with like a I
don't know a fucking shitty photo edit because that's what people want on Twitter I guess I don't
like that I like getting mad at people when they're stupid and I'm not gonna apologize for that
constructive conversation to be fair say what Tom Twitter can be difficult to have like a
constructive conversation yeah if there were no I could have made a much better explanation of
what my point was if well no one would read it to it longer I could have made a much more clear
explanation of what I was arguing about if yeah without the character limit but I mean you know
that's just the nature of it I think the I think the character limit is one aspect of it I feel
like a lot of it is just um reading everything in order is impossible like I heard that you were
having a thing with Mahler and I know what Mahler is so I was like oh I wonder if this is interesting
I couldn't follow any of it I tried like click through and through to understand what so wait who's
who's the where where does it go yeah to understand what I was talking about you would have had to
kind of follow the like the thread of the of the of his conversation with Lindsay Ellis like back a
couple posts to like see what he had been saying it's like that that's the sort of stuff that causes
people to come into half of one aspect of the conversation yeah see something out of context
essentially and react to it on its own and then it's like a like a high like a like a Richard
hive of scum and villainy and misinterpretations and like you know just people easily getting angry
at stuff um which is why it seems like a stupid place to do it but I don't know that's why you should
it's surprising me to shitpost it's it's surprising to me how little twitter not being my life at
hall has affected me I would think since I use it so often that I would there would be like a big
like gaping twitter a hole in my heart but it's been pretty quickly eaten up by youtube and just
work in general or just other things and so I haven't been on twitter in like probably literal months
literally I only have the quick draw twitter as my set login for every device because I use it so
little it's the only thing that I need to use it for and so I have no idea what this debate is like
who mawler is and what is even happening in it uh but I know that I don't want to know there's just
a well I'm gonna I'm just I'm gonna educate you anyway mawler is just a fucking intellectual
jackass that's all you need to know that's oh I hate you know he's an anti intellectual he made
he made like a like a eight part I don't remember the number of parts but like uh it totalled like
19 hours uh video series deconstructing hbomber guy's defense of dark souls 2 in excruciating
detail and I watched that because it was like he has a pretty good voice he talks in depth about
everything so it's like well he talks in he talks in depth in the sense that he like he specifically
points out every tiny thing that's why he makes like four hour long videos criticizing two hour
long movies yeah it's it's essentially like a reaction video but he reacts to every sentence
and every word I know that guy I'm yeah yeah oh my god every every single guy on youtube yeah
that that's the guy no wait hold on actually I just okay I I know who mawler is not by name but
because my friend showed me him a couple weeks ago and and and he said it like like he put on
mawler on his fucking ps4 on the tv and he said just watch a little bit of this and and and uh and
tell me what uh what the k like like what this is so I put on for like two minutes and I couldn't
like understand like what the point was yeah and then I clicked for me but there is no point
he's recapping the movie see frame by frame yeah yeah isn't that what like my little pony
people used to do I mean yeah the reaction community whatever whatever you would call it
like the idea of taking a video it's I think it's spawned like a near around the brony fandom
but the idea of like reacting to a video by usually youtube video by just like pausing what
they were saying saying well that's stupid continuing the video and then pausing against like
huh well that's also stupid you're pretty stupid huh and they would do that and get like into big
dramas disputes and it's just it's really good for drama it's really good for views yeah and people
started doing it about movies and games and all sorts of really just cranks that algorithm
um I mean I don't even necessarily hate it all the time because it's not it's not like everybody
who does that is immediately wrong about what this is that in and of itself very is not like
offensively it sounds like the everything wrong with uh sort of series that people are a little
bit yeah a little bit like that basically it's it's it's everything wrong with someone said this on
twitter and I agree it's like Mahler is basically everything wrong with if instead of each sin taking
like five seconds he talked about each one for like 12 minutes uh and there's no ding and there's no
ding oh but the dings though oh god I love that dings are so funny how how will how will I know
there is a mistake roll credits roll credits um god awful awful do you guys we we all hate
cinema sins right that's not a hot take right okay oh no that's not a hot take at all there's like
there's a whole community around videos about why cinema sins is not good and they're all I love
those videos I love that I watched a few um yeah there's there's one in particular by the guy who
does the everything wrong with everything wrong with well yeah he was his his one his breakdown
is really good um well so I don't know the thing I don't like about Mahler is like that he makes
those videos that's kind of dumb but the really bad thing is I mean you guys know that he claims
that his his criticism is objective like he said he literally says that and he says that everyone
else's is unobjective subjective and he thinks that the way to be objective in your criticism
is just to not read any subtext into anything and only point out objectively true things like plot
holes yeah this is a little strange the thing is though I don't I don't I don't know what quote
that like that information comes from he said it a bunch of times I swear well I mean I don't yeah
I mean sure I'm sure he has it's just sort of like there's a lot of a lot of uh yeah what would you
call it anger I guess about like um certain internet people for being having stupid ideas about stuff
yeah um it it just comes from a place of like lack of charity I can't think of charity
what like maybe he's you know he said that right yeah pretty dumb multiple times in multiple
contexts okay I'm not saying he didn't say that I'm not saying he doesn't believe it okay I'm just saying
why is that even a bad thing he's just a guy doing a stuff what hold on why is it a bad thing I mean
like hundreds of thousands of people watch his videos and agree with them but how is that so bad
because he's wrong do you know no not to me a lot of people can be wrong without even knowing it
all right here's my hot take here's my searing hot take uh people can be wrong some of the time and
write some of the time and people can be right some of the time and wrong some of the time when
people are wrong is it not is it not acceptable I'm not defending him I I just I'm just using that as
a branching of point for that that hot take because I feel like yeah it's you say one wrong thing and
then everything else you said is but it's not but it's not just someone said a wrong thing it's
someone says someone repeatedly says a wrong thing and hundreds of thousand people say yeah I think
that too is that not a problem I mean depends on what they're talking about is it just movies and
stuff uh basically yeah I mean it's it has a potential to be like if they're taking his word
as gospel so if he starts saying something more malicious uh like kill all the cats in the world
and it was like yeah fuck yeah you know then that's the problem I mean yeah yeah objective objectively
you know cats are bad we have to destroy cats oh you know objectively that's true and objectively
I agree no stop you know that that would be bad but it's like I think this movie sucks and everyone's
like yeah that movie sucks just like that's not good it's not it's not just that a movie sucks it's
a whole way of thinking that is like bizarre and and and like just misguided yeah I mean like you're
free to argue with these people if you think they're wrong that's you know that's what he does yeah
yeah you're so I'm not I'm not against uh you arguing with the people it's just like it's a
more matter of who cares when I see someone who when I see people that just have like bad logic
and are just arguing it's I'm sorry it happened unlike a totally like what happened fucked up
logical basis I want I want to be like hey let me point out why this is bad what well there's
just some like movie guy right the thing is the thing is as long as you're bitching about movies I
don't really care I mean he doesn't he doesn't really get into politics I mean I'm pretty sure
he's sympathetic to like the whole like anti SJW thing but that's not I mean in some of his reviews
like in the in the Captain Marvel it kind of I don't know you can kind of feel it in the way he
talks about certain things but he's not like explicitly being like no let me take this bit
to talk about why Trump isn't as bad as everyone says he is he's not doing like that or anything
uh I all right I feel like the general idea that a certain you know large people a large
number of people are thinking in a damaging way is it's sort of I don't know I think I'd rather
like look at it from like an observational perspective rather than thinking oh no these this
guy is um you know making all these people think this different way I feel like it's
all these people resonate with this way of thinking yeah and I just like I wonder why that
like I don't think this guy is contributing to anything in particular I feel like a lot of people
maybe watch cinema sins and then they think I'm gonna grow up and now I'm 12 and now I will
watch maula because it's the same thing but a little more edgy I guess I have no opinion on
this topic specifically as defined just now but I have something that's very adjacent to it I don't
want to switch off just yet respectful but but I will say that I don't know what I was gonna say
never mind fuck you okay take that out take take take what I just said don't take it out
don't take anything out leave it all in reverb it echo echo it and reverb it like munchies
and making a grandiose speech the rule like oh wow I have like to try and put music in the
background I like I like I like having an editor he he he can do all the things we can be like hey
hey hey hey editor hello did you say did you guys see maybe you didn't on twitter
oblivion falls uh video of him asking asking rebel taxi wears the podcast yes it was fucking
great yeah I didn't watch all of it because I assumed the crowd wouldn't get it and it would
be very awkward yeah I mean well that's kind of the point like of course they're not gonna know
what he's talking about and I'm like are they just having fun with the memeing or or like
where the pcp fans because there were a lot of people who seem to have yeah laughed there there
were there were a surprising number of people who's acted as though they like knew the context
yeah I was I was that was the part of a surprised about I thought you just kind of
get was gonna get weird stairs sitting back down but there were some people like high five and I'm
like yeah dude that's what I that's what I would have assumed too but no there were people that
were like yeah where is the podcast bro uh if if you were at that thing and you heard oblivion
falls say that comment below and say yes I'm both a rebel taxi congo and a pcp fan it's at uh
momo con I think how do you justify being both at the same time where's the loyal oblivion fall was
on um I'm not sure what the panel was but I was talking to him last night and he said he was on uh
he was on some panel at I assume momo con I'm pretty that's the one that's going on right now
right and uh I know yeah he's I remember what I was gonna say I was gonna say that you I don't
think there's anything wrong with like fighting for what you believe in the sense that you know
Ben you want to debate about you know this guy being wrong I agree with you yeah it's pretty
shit point pretty shit brain and you should probably take it to the toilet yeah but uh aside
from that which is fucking boring and who cares the real shit is uh what you said the beginning
hippo of people are just like really fucking like down like no charity there's no like you know
you fucking you you someone says something kind of wrong fucking obliterated gone forever now and
the problem is that now like what like what do you mean like oh kids these days people these days
are so ready I know I mean after making a bad after making a mistake it seems like when when
people make a bad point they become a bad person and I think it should like we should focus on
talking about ideas not people like if you have a bad idea shit on the bad idea all you want well
but don't hold the person you said I would I would have demonize everything I would have I would
have done that I'm just talking in like a general okay but let me just use my example is I would
have done that except that the people who jumped in to uh disagree with me didn't at least for a
while until I pointed it out like they weren't jumping in to be like here's why I think Molly's
argument was a good one or here's why I think this idea is a good one it was like they were jumping
in to be like look at this idiot who disagrees with Mahler and that was like end of thought I mean
you're always going to have fucking yeah like that you know that's just I'm sure we have sheeple
who would do that too it's just it's inevitable maybe I do it's it's the essentially a smug enemy
face they posted I don't even know if it comes from like someone literally responded was basically
just a pepe and like basically nothing else and I was like uh I love point taken
me and you've been we're talking about this sort of yesterday talking about like winning debates
I feel like that sort of like no charity stems from that sort of thing where it's like you want to
be right right you know you want to show that you are smart and deserving of an apple uh and so you
own it up are trying to be like dude so wait you're saying this like that's pretty unrealistic
and then and then and then and then they go ding roll credits and uh you get zinged on
fucking twitter and uh so you want to retaliate and say that they are a monster or a retard well
I feel like an apple can I get an apple please yeah I don't yeah yeah yeah hot hot take I don't
particularly like apples they're okay some of them are okay an apple and some some some are better
than others but in general apples are a pretty mediocre tear they're like a sea tear fruit like
secret tip for whenever you get into that situation if you ever say something that people have an
issue with and someone responds like angrily trying to like catch you in a gotcha moment you just have
to lean into it like because the the way that I tend to do these things and it seems to work like
90 of the time if someone like comes at you and is trying to be like trying to catch you in a loop
just respond very uh uh like genuinely like someone's like man that's fucking retarded you're an
idiot blah blah I'd be like okay uh how so like tell me and I'll just like you just start like a
normal friendly conversation like they're here like they're here to fight and you respond with like
well let's talk about it yeah and that 90 of the time it just turns into a normal discussion at
that point yeah because they're being listened to not challenged and then you can come to a
mutual understanding and then it just totally avoids the whole problem and if they're there to
argue in bad faith like they'll lose steam because like suddenly they can't do what they what they
wanted to do yeah I was a big fan of of digi's um everyone I forget what it was called did you
bro verse everybody digi bro versus everybody because it it sort of shone a light on that sort of
you know comment that people would leave they'd say hey fuck you you suck and then when he's like
well why do I suck and they're like well you know uh they just they wouldn't have anything really
specific they maybe would have like one thing like you said um you said this thing and like uh
and they would just look stupid and it was great I've actually had like a few a few comments I don't
remember who has PCP comments or just my on my videos like when people like said something mean
about me and I responded and they like immediately took it back and I'm like it's okay it's just I
think people sometimes forget that there's another person behind the screen and it's like so so they
just a lot yeah and so you just have to remind them sometimes it's it's not like hey I'm here
it's not like um anyone is like better than anyone else with regards to this because I feel
a little angry at certain faceless commenters when they make me upset and I like I don't respond
but I'm seething yeah but really they're just a person like if I knew them if I could see them
my way of doing I would like to be I would like to give them the benefit of the doubt
most of the time is what I think yeah my way of doing online discourse usually boils down to
when I have to respond to the way I just mentioned and then if I'm like on the other side like if I
feel like I want to like score a point on somebody instead of like going in very aggressively I try
and just like genuinely ask a question and give them an opportunity to restate the answer because
like when I make an assumption like that what I try and do is be like okay what they're saying to me
sounds retarded so instead of going in and being like you're retarded I'm like I want to give them
another chance to restate it to be like like basically asking for clarification because maybe
I like to try and assume I'm interpreting it wrong so I'll give yeah I try and like comment
sometimes or like respond to a tweet be like and give them a chance to rephrase it to make
sure I'm understanding it correctly and then try and usually ask a question from that to kind of
get to the nitty gritty of whatever the issue is I don't know I just I'm always more interested in
having a legitimate conversation even with people who blatantly disagree with me because I think
that's just not just more valuable but you'll get to a better answer I mean yeah it's it's very
gratifying when somebody who was giving you shit and then you actually do that because I don't
often do it sometimes I mean I don't get that much shit because I don't do that much stuff but
when it has happened and I do approach them like asking why and get the clarification it makes me
feel better to know that they don't actually they're not actually out to get me that much it was just
a little thing it's like well you know what that's just a fundamental disagreement you push back
you're both gonna leave mad but if you actually kind of like engage in a conversation you can
leave satisfied and that's way better for both parties
if only you could do things fucking swell and things fucking rosy cheeks and
again I feel like the idea of winning a debate is so
vile and disgusting well I feel like it's almost like a perversion of the idea the platonic ideal
of a debate explanation point debate obviously it's fun to put on your fucking war paint and you
know go out with your fellow labels to attack some other shithead labels and make them feel bad for
being labels and and then you know you can retire and it'll be a fun time for everyone involved
except your ruining culture and also I hate you and you're just breeding with just a truly like
fucking there's nothing in the world I hate more than just fucking circle jerking tribalism
where it's you know you go into a debate for the sole purpose of of going and like chuckling
into your friends being like man fuck this guy dude I'm gonna fucking tag on my twitter and say
something mean dude well in this well all right in this uh in this attention economy that we got
gone right like the purpose of the debate like from a practicals perspective you're right the
platonic ideal of a debate is that two people enter with opposing of views and and logic to
back it up and they argue their points one person leaves and they argue their points and in the end
we like we reveal the truth right we all we all like collectively arrive at truth through like
arguing different points but but the but the practical not even truth but just you know agree
over and saying to both of the arguments and maybe you could decide but but but the practical
reality is that the reason people are engaging in debates in platforms like youtube and politics
and stuff is not for that reason it's because doing so gets you attention and brings attention to
your viewpoint and generally speaking you're not going to convince anyone of well like you're not
going to convince anyone of your point if they already disagree with you well you're here you're
here to introduce people that maybe don't know haven't heard your side of the debate you're here to
like let them hear it for the first time this is why it's like you know you put up a you put up a
oh like evolution versus creationism right oh teach the controversy let's have a debate
your no no that's a bad example it's not a bad example but better example flat earth you put up
like like here's why i think the earth is flat here's why i think the earth is round you put
them both up there and they debate the winner in this scenario is the flat earth there because
if people are debating this idea as though it's like two sides of the same coin it's platforming
the idea as though it's like on equal footing with the round earth's idea and now like even
though 90 percent of people 99 percent of people are gonna hear them be like well this guy's obviously
crazy there's gonna be a few people who maybe have never heard the idea before maybe they're like oh
this is interesting maybe they're convinced by some of his logic maybe they get on board that's
that's that's what it's for it's to reach that new audience you disagree well wait wait hold on
what do you disagree with exactly i'm just i literally don't know i just i just i i still
think like even stupid ideas should be debated because like we don't know what's stupid like like
in this situation yeah like flat earth sounds pretty stupid and i i really don't think they're right
but like who gets to decide what's stupid and what's wrong okay okay let me let me take like an
individualist look at this hypothetical scenario you are say you're a guy you're a scientist maybe
you're like a famous scientist or something or you're a little bit famous you're a little bit
known you're respected you have the opportunity someone is like hey i believe that the earth is flat
let me debate you in like a broad sense i guess it would be wrong like to say like this guy is not
allowed to say that like the earth is flat he is allowed to say the earth is flat but if i'm this
scientist and some guy challenges me to the bit this debate i would net i would never say yeah
let's have this debate because i don't want to dignify that position with respect it's not worth
and it honestly makes me look it makes me look bad to engage with that idea
thing though here's the the other side of that coin because like ben your your point of saying like
by giving this these certain topics a platform that legitimizes them the flip side of that is that
if you're someone in a position of authority who should be easily able to dismiss a ridiculous
claim like this and you refuse to do so on the grounds that you don't want to give it a platform
you're also giving everybody who might be on the fence about it like well the scientists can't
defend it maybe that just makes them look more legitimate like they don't have a way to defend
it so so like both of them like no matter what happens you're gonna lose ground to stupid people
because they're just stupid people everywhere i don't think i don't think that's necessarily true
in every case i think when it comes to certain topics where like the person is easily reachable
and it would be like if they don't respond it's pretty obvious that they are deliberately
not responding then there's that aspect of it but if it's like you know you don't uh some scientist
has a paper written and you know a youtube commenter says hey scientist like you or like a twitter guy
it's like uh debate me like him ignoring that twitter user isn't necessarily going to give
that guy a lot of clout but if he writes a paper and he asks the guy to you know or peer review it
or like to to you know think about what this says read it please and then he still dismisses it on
the face of what's on the title then it's different then it's like you're you're you're deliberately
halting this potential thing and that's bad and that's seen as bad i wanted to say like like you
don't have to debate absolutely everyone who comes your way with a stupid idea it's it's not your
job so to speak to do that however like if you are trying to be an authority about
certain knowledge you should be able to also defend your position against legit like rivals you know
lately the people so people would understand your position as well because like not like you're not
born with the knowledge of science and that the earth is round you learn it from other people
and if some people are a bit skeptical about it i think it's like if you're a scientist who
you know believes and wants people to believe it you should be able to at least make a video in
responses like be like hey this is why earth is round this is the science behind it you know
well this reminds me of like people like evolution or a creationist being like science class should
teach the controversy right like like they're like oh well they're not gonna they're not gonna
teach they're teaching evolution in schools that's terrible okay how about this teach that some people
believe in evolution other people believe in creation and the answer yeah and the answer to
that is no because one of those is science and should be taught in science class and the other
isn't the other is yeah like the yeah the difference is because one can be scientifically
observed whereas the other not so i am on the side that can't be observed scientifically so i don't
know if you're if you're the scientist and someone's coming you and trying to argue the earth is flat
but like they're i mean their arguments are not i mean they might be like sort of dressed up in a
scientific way but like i don't know i wouldn't i wouldn't do it unless someone had like maybe
someone had like a really compelling argument that like was convincing people was like pretty like
scientific if someone's just got like a bunch of pseudoscientific nonsense that they're going
around arguing and i don't know i don't think it's worth debating it like if there's nothing to if
there's nothing to debate i guess what i'm saying is there needs to be some like meat to the argument
to make it like worth you know having the debate in the first place and i just don't think there is
any meat to like a flatter if this is a argument something sort of like pick on someone your own
size uh like the debate means more if the disparity between the people debating is very large you
know uh you know fucking i don't know Neil deGrasse Tyson arguing with uh me uh with munchie wears
tiny hats like two youtubers with very different subcats like um that would be like whoa you know
like you obviously the the the lesser viewed party would get a lot of views you know in whatever
context that is not not necessarily on social media could be just clout or like on the news or
whatever it is it's basically just if you're the smaller guy you'll get more you know so like i agree
with with ben on that that you shouldn't necessarily give people anybody um you know uh a platform
just to share to share the platform with you if you're so much bigger but if there's a guy who is
like um become on the level of a Neil deGrasse Tyson in in so much that he has uh a lot of people
backing him and he's kind of you know he can't ignore that then a debate is warranted and i think
you should like i don't know it when the when the sizes are about the same size it's fair enough
you should recognize that if you've got an audience if you've got an audience and you agree to a debate
with someone of an opposing viewpoint like you should basically do that with the understanding
that like no matter what happens you're doing them a big favor even even if you like quote
unquote win the debate you've done them a huge favor just by having it in the first place and do
and do you want to do that i think i think it's just choose your battles wisely sort of a sure sure
sure yeah any good advice talk about a very nice topic colors okay let's talk about colors let's
talk about sonic colors hold on hold on i just want to quickly because before the podcast started
and you weren't there i wanted to say i wanted to rant a little bit about colors okay yesterday
when i went to bed around uh who knows when i i i had this thought just like what's up with people
having favorite colors says the person who is devoted you know i i think i know what you mean
but go on yeah it's just it's just so odd i mean i can understand sort of like people having a
favorite flavor or something like that because it's a it's a way to sort of um it's kind of beneficial
to you especially like if you if you can tell if the food is properly cooked and whatnot or whatever
or like if you'd need a little bit of salt and you like taste is different but like um then like
you see colors and like there's like no reason to like one color over the other but people do
and for me personally just owning something in purple like gives like a plus 20 points to happiness
as opposed to as opposed to owning something exactly the same but not purple and i don't
understand why but i i would argue that that is the same as flavor and taste um because it's i mean
you know aside from like the i love the taste of raw meat that will kill me like that's bad
but like you know people have lots of favorite flavors you don't just eat one thing and i feel like
you know your colors can you know you have a multiple favorite colors
looking at the same color your whole life will get tiring i think uh even for you purple things
give you happiness because a lot of things are not purple and you see them all the time
and and it makes it a special thing to have a purple thing unless your room is entirely purple
which would be funny if if is the case in my mind it is slowly increasing the amount of purple in
in my room and my life uh oh i recently ordered like like two little um what do you call it like
no no devies no covers no cheats uh what's what's the blankets there we go that's the word uh two
blankets because like it was like literally five a.m and i thought like we need we need like a blanket
to like throw over our a sofa because the the one just like literally has holes in it that we currently
have so i ordered two one for myself and one for the sofa but what both of them were kind of too
small for the sofa and now i'm stuck with two purple blankets and i'm really happy because
they're both of them are so soft um i think i i talked about one of them in the last podcast
yes yes i still have it i'm so happy and it's like i wouldn't be as happy if it wasn't purple i think
i would still be happy because it's soft and comfortable but like it's also purple and with
butterflies and i like butterflies and i'm just so happy i i i would be right unlikely that this could
be uh explored scientifically but do you think that if you had like contact lenses in that made
everything purple forever uh that you would eventually get bored of seeing purple no
are you sure i am i am i am certain that's my final answer be sure but i don't know i haven't
been tired like purple i've had the obsession with purple like started started small but i have
this obsession with purple since i was 14 or so so it's been over a decade since i started liking
purple the and and it's the amount of me liking purple has only increased over time so i feel like
it's gonna grow until it consumes me so do you think it's part of an identity thing like the
fact that people know you're the purple person is like adding to it uh i don't know and i didn't start
exactly as purple honestly if you think about it because the original version of mage was
mostly black and white was only slightly purple eyes and she slowly grew purple over time
and now she everything is turning purple uh no i i don't know no it's just it just makes me happy
it's just a nice color uh speaking about you should listen to deep purple about colors i don't like
though like i have a i have a small personal grudge against the color green like it's not in
in its own fault it's a good color but the thing is like i was born in may and it's like the color
of may is green like oh what's your what's your lucky color why is the color of may green i because
like i i don't know someone decided and it's like wait hold on i don't know if that's true well look
up like birthstone alithuanian thing no no like uh if you look up birthstones they're color green
like what was your lucky color is like may if you burn me it's green the birthstone of may is emerald
that's true yeah you know my birthstone is diamond best one april bam obliterated oh fun uh i've got
moonstone pearl and alexandrite oh why do you have several all my favorite steven universe characters
moonstone is fucking sick pearls are like really good in dark cloud uh gem for weapon
enhancement and alexandrite is a fucking steven universe i'm sorry why do some why do
some ones get several ones why why is may stuck with green i'm so i'm so unhappy it's probably just
because people got confused and couldn't remember what the real one was or what the old one was and
they made up a new one and then people mixed up the two mage are you green is that what you're
saying right now no you're not green i'm not green i i i i think green hashtag free green mage
in in a like like like there was some kind of dimensional swap took place where like
our world's mage was green but like an alternate reality mage was purple and like some kind of
she fell through the the the green line the escalator yes she fell down she fell under the
under the escalator into the green light and swapped with her purple alternate self or something
okay i'm i'm on like birthstone color bernadette this this this is a lot of fucking colors i'm
i'm trying to find june color right but it's got black blue brown clear green pink purple
red and white okay one of these one of these has to be no but what may has like aqua black
blue brown clear green so it's like that there's a lot that i got i gotta figure this out i gotta
figure out what my color is colors for april yellow red and colorless colorless
all right how cool is that isn't your fucking because because of diamond that's so cool that's
my favorite i love that experience of what the worst and best color is here's some literally
objective colorless that's why i draw in black and white april april babies yeah all the trades
also doesn't connect lines when when drawing yeah that's also an april thing i think i see
that here on wikipedia yellow red and green i'm not looking christmas here is the objective
worst color everyone should agree with me here yellow because that's gotta be fucking
bright and saturated look good you ever seen a fucking dull yellow is just dull yellow is
not even yellow anymore it's just brown i mean all right i can just say that you say that but
i think the reason yellow is so bad is because computer monitors cannot show really yellow
what and to darken a yellow is impossible to make look good like if you have yellow paint
oh there's so many lovely things that can happen that what do you but on a computer monitor like
if you if you go to like to photoshop you can't get a good yellow what are you what are you talking
about dude there's a v source video this yellow thumbnail says this is not yellow and is it because
your display displays in red and green red red blue green yeah i know i i don't it wasn't it
wasn't just i don't understand that it was interesting it's still you like it looks yellow
it doesn't not look yellow i don't know yeah but if you look at certain things in
realality realality they are more colorful no it does i see in a yellow flower and i'm like
a sniff sniff it looks the same on a green i don't care i don't see that yellow looks bad
i'm just saying that it's not as versatile as other colors yeah that's true yeah but you're
saying you're saying that from the perspective of a digital artist who draws i am i am saying that
because i'm me hippo did you forget ring ring knock knock well i think the problem here is just
that yellow is a more narrowly defined like maybe in another culture there wouldn't be a word for
brown and yellow would encompass even dark yellow which includes brown all of you are insane you know
shut up lock you all you know you know that like i mean you know that like other cultures don't have
the same color words like no i know that's not what i'm saying yellow doesn't equal brown you can get
dark like like gross ass yellow that doesn't brown no hold on opening up manga studio right now
i will obliterate you with facts and logic right now you're saying you're literally what are you
talking about okay i'm literally you're literally this is this is literally the second yellow controversy
in the pc i'm drawing i'm drawing a big swatch of yellow right here right now and then i'm putting
and i'm putting would be such a peaceful topic and i'm putting it down not i'm putting the the
darkness i'm sliding the down the darkness that are halfway and i'm drawing and it's like an
olive green that's why we can't have nice things it's like olive color it's no longer yellow
okay uh i have a question okay correct me if i'm wrong but like in japanese didn't like the
color blue and green used to have like the same word for it i'm not sure but maybe what's what's
japan okay i have heard i've heard that uh the ancient greeks did not have a word for blue
which is why that uh in the odyssey homer describes the sky as being like burnished bronze
because there is no word for blue for him to use to describe it and people didn't use to have purple
either so that's why a lot of flowers are called like use the word blue in their titles despite
being purple i'm angry like violets are blue yes lel literally violet
yeah i'm looking i'm looking at yellow i have like a perfectly saturated yellow here and i like if i
slide the slider down even a little bit it very quickly turns into like an what i would describe
as more like a puse or olive color it's it's still just looks to me as though it is a dark yellow
description wrong it's definitely wrong wrong yeah wrong no you know what you know but i think
you like to be a bad person because you just said i love to be like a bad person i love being a bad
man to my friend hey by the way guys i don't know if you guys know this but like episodes don't have
to go on for like three hours in case you didn't we could we could do voicemails literally right
right i've nearly finished i've nearly finished my color uh quiz i'm nearly there it's not the
voicemails i don't really i don't fucking care about this and fucking you know what yellow love you
love you boy well i mean we can't we can't move on to voicemails if we're done taught if there's
nothing else to live we want to talk about yeah yeah you know okay i just want to say because
nate wasn't here i did the voice yellows again for the second time in a row and i just want to say
that this was like possibly the worst voicemail batch we've ever had hey did you get one did you
get one from terezi yes i did okay just checking i want to say just quick quick
disclaimer about i still about the colors i i i think green is a neat color i just don't like
it being attributed to me that's all i nobody does that though myself because we're talking about this
like people like people like you know the whole may thing is is okay it upsets me i've well i've
never heard of it so well i i i grew up like see i grew up with like a girly magazines were just like
oh what's your horoscope you're your your sign you're your lucky color your lucky number stuff
like that and it's always green in between in between like going out on like marauding like
raiding campaigns in like the bombed out wasteland of lithuania and like like like you know plundering
you know plundering uh like ancient ruins and stuff and like beating people with baseball
bats you were reading like teen girl magazines that were telling you about your birthstone how
to incorporate it into your wardrobe to be fair i only read one magazine it was like it wasn't
even a magazine it was like the the the way the wings no no not the wings the witch the witch comics
the only reason i brought the yellow thing is because i wanted everyone to be like ha ha yeah
me too much yeah i also know the difficulties of picking correct shades of yellow this is
the worst topic ever i want to kill myself uh it's blue i'm blue god so i'm gonna start out like
worst to bet so there we got like i don't know maybe like 20 voicemails we're down to six uh and
like maybe a half of these are even slightly good so uh we're going to we're going to start with uh
my personal favorite and i feel like one that uh sums up the sort of general quality here
and then navigate over to our slave real quick whip them real quick yep yeah here we go make sure
you turn up your uh your speakers really high for this because it's extremely quiet
fuck been sane
all right that was it cool wait what wait i missed it oh oh oh you want to play again yeah yeah
no no no problem hippo yeah i'm happy to play this all i'm happy to play this all day
fuck been sane thanks uh hey hey important no important no i said peace i used the i used
the color word puce before i looked it up i'm wrong turns out puce is like a dark red or purple
brown i thought it was like a nasty i get fucked yeah because it sounds like puke wait wait wait
i think i was thinking of chartreuse i was thinking of chartreuse so sorry everybody
go back and correct me next next next next we have a uh a voicemail from the embodiment of
the pcp voicemail we have him himself calling into the show oh god hey guys it's me a pcp voicemail
here i just wanted to leave a message for all those commenters out there cutting themselves
because the pcp doesn't read their comments uh just use me instead at least one of them is
gonna have to listen to you and you know voicemails are to be honest just the cooler way to go right
you really want to be a part of a youtube comment section no yeah i agree we provided you we provided
you that we don't use that we don't know who's that that's my roommate pcp comment section
i'm really sorry man i didn't think you heard that it is his roommate the pcp comment
said it if i thought you were in earshot we stop crumpling maybe i think no it's like the typing
of a okay there's no reason to bring my mother into this and what the slur is really the could you
really spell him right see see comment this goes on for like an hour so i'm gonna disconnect right
here but uh in case you fucking that hosts are too unruly and you literally couldn't understand
uh this this is the pcp voicemail he called in but his roommate the pcp youtube comments uh came
in started typing in a came that he was speaking it seems like comment section is a real asshole
but fortunately we've given you an out so you don't have to you don't have to be like him you've
got the speak pipe right at your disposal link in the description i we did the meme that we
don't read the comments came from uh because i do it's not really a meme it's just sort of like
an implicated you know implicitly people don't assume that the youtube creators are human beings
that we were saying that we thought the comments were bad because the people assumed we didn't read
them even though we do we've talked for the last like two episodes about how contrary to popular
belief we actually do most of us do read the comments here's the thing we read the comments but
none of them are good enough to warrant responses yeah i respond if one if one makes me mad enough
i respond so uh that's how you get how you trick me uh that now we're gonna see like a hundred like
hey ben hey ben fuck yeah and i'll and i'll spend an entire day responding to all of them if you
address me specifically i'll probably respond i don't just mean refer to me like like say my name
in the comment i mean like if you're speaking to me i will speak back most of the time speaking you
shall be spoken to here's also another one that i'm gonna cut off prematurely uh actually you know
what nah i'm just gonna let it go for the entire time who cares oh this is the wrong one oh whatever
this is a special announcement from rid of my ass batman oh my god this batman is a brony and
will be appearing at brony con 2019 in bolton more maryland we'll be there if anyone would like to
split the hotel cost grab a bite to eat or just hang out directly mess it yeah hang out direct messes
at rid of my ass bat one all over case that's rid of my ass bat one all over case
as for the members of the procrastiners how can i get a hold of you so we can meet up at brony con
well because you're like 75 percent of the reason i'm going we're thank you very much goodbye well
the other 25 percent is probably we'll probably like tweet or something about like where we are
or so i don't know like where you can find us i don't know we would say come to our panel but
those bastards won't give us one they totally snubbed us they totally fucking sometimes i
i was like hey the horseshoes crew is coming back can we get a fucking thing and then they
can you get a fucking denied and i said yes i can you just did it let me let me let me i'm
throwing something out here see if you fucking agree uh find out when the reviewing is whatever
panel they inevitably are gonna have at brony con have a meetup at a restaurant and pull a bunch
people out of the convention at the same time i think why don't we just show up to that and
like be rowdy in the crowd oh rowdy in the oh my god oh my god clip that clip or somebody clip
i mean or i mean dab in the crowd uh yeah okay okay yeah wow great okay these are really great
so far so far we've had someone say fuck been saint and i really don't even remember the rest
they've entered one ear and out the other well good because i i don't want to hear you just go
through each one and recount them i don't want to hear you make a maller a maller a maller video
about all these voicemail we've missed the first shot what impossible did they make a move yet
i kept in gaylord no i think they're deciding right now all right
splints three six
they will miss luckily my battleships are in the five five c five
jesus christ they're god us you bastards this won't be the last you'll hear of me retaliate
i kept in gaylord where to see two god damn us i kept in gaylord well uh uno uh did we ever like
actually get the the the battlefield set no i don't know whether the weather hit
no it hit us oh god we're link we're sinking oh wow what a fucking shame okay i want to i want to
i want to i want to i want to say i want to say uh well done i want to i want to i want to i want to
i want to i want to use a i want to use a three let's use a three somewhere please someone
what do you mean wait what do you mean use a three i want to i want a three something
i don't know what you're talking about five by five grid we're playing battleship with this guy
a three yeah exactly eight no no no no no what we need to we need to attack a i need to attack
adjacent to where we just hit because his ship nah dude nah no you don't know how to play real
you a three you just throw a strategy right into the world we're gonna die we're all gonna
fucking sink at sea and it's all because you didn't listen to me there's not enough space for strategy
too many battlefield commanders spoil the war both of you to assume that i don't want to die this is
this is a nightmare this is uh then then i should i should too many komodo spoiled i i know i know
i know mage you want to die it's fine no you're not you're not taking me down with you i don't
care i will i'll tie you up and force you to live no never we we've got a voicemail that i was that i
was uh uh deemed in anticipation about uh last night late at night saying uh i was uh messaged
by the person who recorded saying to make sure to play on the podcast and i said okay yes and so i
am doing it now this is the one i think it is hey quick before they realize i don't have a browser
type hctps colon slash discord.gg slash lowercase n lowercase t uppercase s uppercase r uppercase
x lowercase e lowercase x type nr quick quick quick quick and let's rowdy thrash thrash thrash thrash
thrash thrash no no okay all right he do that except at the end it's not a lowercase k it's
not a lowercase x is lowercase k so do that but typical rowdy this is a typical rowdy just
why the fuck haven't you guys bought a fucking url yet for this thing what do you notice the discord
invite don't worry yeah don't worry about you can buy a url that just reconnects to any url you
have rfck.com's bought by some fucking chinese company no no no you get rfck.slime you could
probably do that no there's no slime check wait is there there's a link there's a link to the discord
on the slimecorp website right yes okay well just go you go to slimecorp.net yeah go to slimecorp.net
and you can uh you can find your way there all right here's the last one hi it's terezi pyro
so i was hanging out with discord yeah and my discord baby risco wants to get bottom surgery
he really wanted me to ask this the dating bottom surgery give you a second virginity
what's up with that okay so so in case you're not trans aware like how i was i was trans unaware
bottom surgery is is you know when you change your genital to the other one so oh i thought it was
just like getting a bigger butt yeah i thought that too that's that's ryan agents first as well
okay okay so the question is the answer is clearly yes yeah yeah you think you think so yeah i agree
i agree i well i'm gonna disagree with a caveat i don't think that changing okay if you have a dick
and you're and you've fucked with your dick and you're not a virgin and you get even you change
your dick into a vagina and then it's like oh am i now a virgin again no but what i think is that
what i think has happened is that you have previously lost your dick virginity but you
have a new virginity to lose oh yeah you have you have you have a different it's a you've
lost you've still lost your old virginity you've still lost that but you there is a separate
virginity that you may that you lose independently plus virginity yeah well well like it's like
erica moan said on strip search like you have multiple virginities like you can lose your
butt virginity that's a separate thing you're you're you're very various different kinds of
virginities ah so many what a cornucopia you can collect them all your sneeze virginity yeah the
first the first time you do a big sneeze that's you're losing your sneeze virginity and big sneeze
and so on and so on in that order uh i really i thought that you know we were when we were talking
about this um we were talking about how i terezi and what is the terezi risk i don't know it doesn't
matter it really sucks for you that risk is trans though no it doesn't um well she'll have a vagina
soon changes nothing so it's fine um the the uh man i think nate would probably have more to say
about this i think he would probably argue and play devil's advocate in response to this question
nate would probably say oh i hate old people do me too uh damn okay well this this episode
fucking god kill me all right why why are you so why are you so stupid you are munchie you're being
a down in this episode what's going on he's growing up guys he's becoming an adult let's talk let's
talk about how you feeling munchie let's talk about your feelings what's going on with you
hey let's have a little moment with dr us yeah you know what okay i'm i'm leaned on our chair
guys everyone hates us everyone thinks that we're fucking boomers and that we're lame and that we're
fucking no we're not cool anymore everyone comments everyone leaves comments saying that we're
fucking jaded that we're nihilists and i'm not a nihilist i just hate everything because everyone
hates me yeah i thought you were just i thought you were just mad because you're locked in the
wine cell you're about to get whipped by your dad i mean that's fine i guess and you know i would i would
welcome that at this point exactly hmm everyone's like oh fucking the political talk you know what
fuck it i'm happy because i uh the the game engine i'm using construct three they're adding
javascript coding it's not going to be a baby game engine anymore i can learn how to do real
code and put it in my game that already exists without having to rebuild it so that happened
this week and i'm fucking stoked about it there good good vibes positive energy yet i'm i'm feeling
good because this wasn't a lot of stuff done and i'm doing a lot of stuff that i've never done
before and learning new things is always very nice yeah like i don't know why you're upset
the the the youtube comments are small beans everybody here is doing cool things we didn't
have nate on how cool is that huh what a wonderful day this is we we are participating something
magical and rare as a unicorn a podcast without me i know he's he's he's everywhere take a picture
he's everywhere take a deep breath enjoy the the uh the sensation because it's gonna be a long time
before you get it again i feel like i almost feel like we need to stretch this out because like
we without we didn't have nate or digi so there was no like long stuff to like argue about
and i feel like that's i feel like that's a win for them and i don't want them to have it no it's
a win for us because i don't want to give it to them argue about everything hey guys that you know
that abortion in israel first palestine like that whole drama with pro jared you know that i agree
with everyone in that me too man me too you guys want to talk about pro jared some more it's like
my favorite thing this is like fucking fox not that fox news this is like we're all we're all
creative people here don't you think the real deal with all of us getting an extra hour oh wait
i have you know i have something i want to say um oh no um this hopefully when you're listening to
this i've decided i'm pulling the trigger vapors three is almost done so when you listen to this
episode one i'm gonna do this in like a lead up to releasing actual vapors three what what
yeah i know right one of the one of the vaporettes from one of the vaporettes from um um the book
from the kickstarter last it's going up on my website under the vapors it'll be like the
latest page of the vapors it will be up live right now it'll be the two-page vaporette
drawn by emily ree who you should follow who's a great artist who does a comic called anarchy
dreamers and you should follow her on twitter at ree underscore emily she is the guest artist
wait yeah this is fucking bullshit what do you mean why is my vaporette not on your website
you why don't i get to be on st commis dot com there's a couple and i'm gonna release them one
at a time ah so there so there you go you'll you'll be there this is the worst day of my life
munchie munchie you gotta cut ben some slack his website has to be updated manually so he's gonna
start with the two-page one that takes the least amount of work so you can make sure he gets it
done by the time there's there's two there's two two page ones and there's your like 11 page one
um okay so so this episode is just like saint comics saint comics saint comics dot com no this
week i'll release this week i'll really re i'll release emily's next week i'll release lauren
colt's the week after that i will the week after that i will release yours and the week after that
vapors three out so one month from today it's god damn i know right uh that's and that's what's
happened too long it's been so fucking long i don't don't listen i'll cry if we start talking
about how long it's been and you nobody wants to see that what's not saying that is a bad thing
okay you know what guys we don't talk about shit that we actually care about we only talk about
shit that's like oh you know we can say that like you know i guess that's like a thing that we can
say let's talk about shit that we actually is that it's actually like matters and that is actually
important in any way that pertains to us specifically and our personalities or our careers as a
internet career because we never do that we're talking about like oh you know on twitter like
someone was like bad and like i don't like bad people you know when people are like stupid uh
yeah i do too i also know that ben that's important to me you don't you don't you don't talk you
let's talk about your fucking comic because you've been on a tear lately you've been fucking
actually making pages but no one knows about it because they're hidden behind the fucking
howl hall the fucking fortress yeah that is your patreon yeah yeah um uh well yeah i mean i think
i've talked about this before i mean i did that because it's like well my patrons should have
some sort of privileged access to the content right so it's like well i'll just until the
comics done i'll just put them on patreon only which is like i mean before that it's not like i
was releasing them one at a time i just wasn't releasing them anywhere until i had the whole
thing done and released it all at once um but i don't know you were saying that like i should
just fucking release them one at a time and maybe yeah there there's so many people that like want
to be ben saint fans but just have no concept that you are actually doing work as far as like a
lot of people concerned you are doing nothing as far as a lot of people are concerned yeah i
feel like this exact conversation already i think i think so too this exact conversation yeah i'm
pretty sure i'm sure you brought this up okay whatever i mean my i mean my hope is that like
when it all comes out at once people will be like oh he was working on something this whole time my
preconceptions have been shattered i'm gonna go to patreon.com slash ben saint and show my appreciation
before but ben didn't agree with me so he has to agree with me this time i'm just i think that time
and this time i'm just equivocating because i don't know what's real and i don't know what's
true and i don't know what the right thing to do is everyone press one of ben should just release
his fucking comics normally well like a normal person yeah okay well everyone's gonna say yes
normally as in like one chapter per week no no like you know he releases pages like he's done
with them and they on his website or maybe like it's like you know you get them like a day before
as a patron or something you know what i think i think that is generally a bad idea with the format
of ben's comics because uh certain things read better when they're all in one chapter you know one
page that may not have dialogue on it like the last one it just like i mean i don't know how it feels
for the patrons who who get to see it yeah um as it comes out the same problem little bit by little
bit but i don't know whether that would really it like is it worth people thinking that ben does work
to have them have like a kind of worse experience reading it it's not a worse experience because
they're able to get it sooner and be able to have it more in their mind it's definitely not
optimal as reading it in the backlog it's definitely a worse experience to read something
one page at a time that's a continuous this is why this is this is why i did it in the first place
and didn't and just and didn't release one at a time and waited until it was all done i've run to
this problem myself because i'm working on this on the game right now and like i have i there's
nothing to release now that the game's out and have to work on an entire fucking video game like
am i gonna release every level at a time like over the course of like a year and that's completely
different i mean you could you could do that i could but let me finish yeah because i've had
this problem like even when i was doing comics like three years ago i was having a problem
like i've tried wanted to release big things because like it was a story and told a story and
like the the answer unfortunately is just make more shit yeah the way that's that's always the
real answer the way to do it would be work on the big vapor's comics and then like every like one or
two weeks release like a four-pan a little like gangstrip with the characters to get people to
care about the characters for the big release i've been thinking about that running two comics
like that's really the way to do it and it just you know it just takes more work but like you
just kind of have to nut up and make it happen i've been thinking about that like what if i did
not exactly like the red man thing but what if i just did like sort of like a like a like not much
like in the way of new drawing just like the static character just like a little bit of like
dialogue just like a little like dialogue short comic snippet thing um get my i don't know writing
juices flowing a little bit uh or something you do like a sprite comic with the vapor so you just
have sprites you can like reuse all the time um boy yeah and just like wait wait what if i put them
just do garfield but with what if i put them right like i have like an isometric view of
like their room and i made little like little like sprites of them and i just move them around the
room right it's it's and i made homestuck and i just what if i made homestuck that's kind of
that's kind of cool it is cool i think i gotta go very soon but i just want to say
it to remind people bail jpeg is out it's finished it's my comic my thing my cool thing that i made
and it's really good and it's finished and it's so good and go look at it and as cool as that is
the zumi demo is even cooler and that's out it's getting updated it's on new grounds check it out
well i'm gonna make two games how about that oh well hit me up i'm gonna make two zumi games i'm
just gonna copy paste your game and then color change well yeah well the champion the champion
visual novel rpg experience has been on stcomics.com for about a hundred years now did you ever put
the the champion game on new grounds i have not uh i'm a little not i'm a little unsure i mean you
know i don't know how the new grounds works i don't know what kind of file for i know i haven't
looked into it at all but it's something i kind of want to help you out if you want to do it it's
fucking not hard at all okay i'll i'll look into it and if i need help i'll i'll DM you and be like
what the fuck what the fuck is this yeah i just add a lot of i have a lot of people who play the
game on new grounds so it like it's a good site for that wait wait i mean i made the game in
game maker is that fine you should be you can can you do html5 export from game maker uh yes
because that's the format that it's on the web on my website it you just you just upload a zip
file that's it you're that should that actually i might be able to do that like right now maybe i
don't know yeah it's it's already left we gotta go oh no patreon.com slash the procrastinators
give us your fucking money five dollars get you access to 25 bonus episodes we're recording another
one very soon and it'll be up and then you can hear new shenanigans do we want to oh yeah i think
we've already talked about what the previous bonus episode was that i missed because of my kidney
stone um it was uh quizzes yes that's the newest bonus episode we take a bunch of crazy personality
quizzes other weird quizzes that reveal way too much about our personal lives not me i wasn't on
this one i'm talking like i was because i wish i was i wish i was too it was a good time worth the
listen worth your money help us worth a mere pittance a mere pittance of five dollars it's
it's it's nothing it basically won't even miss it when it's gone but the experience you gain you'll
never forget you can but you can buy a latte at starbucks or you could buy like 40 hours of bonus
pcp content hmm yeah what a head scratcher that one is yeah so do that uh follow us on twitter
for at tpcrastinators and uh if you want to listen to this in audio form i do still upload the
podcast to itunes spotify it's on spotify it's on google play and itunes it goes into it there in
audio form and uh yeah on on on my podcast app that i use every single day uh i have subscribed
to the pcp just because it's really crazy just see the pcp next to like a real podcast yeah imagine
that can you munchie we are a real podcast what i know dude people listen to this oh no
no where's the podcast spinning in his great where's the podcast it's on itunes and youtube
and that other what's the other one where else is it google play google play yeah so check it out
and unlike certain podcasts we can answer that question yeah yeah seriously get get on whatever
the pcp is boomershit click on the teen cp that's better bye bye thanks for listening
i am an asshole i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it