Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast
post-Bronicon edition. Welcome back, everybody.
Last week you had the non-Bronicon. Today you have pure distilled.
Those fucking nerds, those non-Bronicon embarrassing.
Sorry about that, everyone. The nightmare is over.
Yep, you're welcome. Ben Saint is back.
The glorious Ben and Nate combo is finally back.
Everyone was dying for it once again. Everyone was complaining.
Where's Ben and Nate? Our favorite duo.
Where's Ben and Nate? I need to know what they thought about Bernie Sanders' appearance on the Joe Rogan podcast.
We've got to know. We've got to know.
Through the past weekend and week, we have been putting our hooves up over and over and over again.
Just completely thrashing around, just dancing our hearts out about Bronicon.
Now that's over. That was the last Bronicon we will ever experience.
Can we please put our hooves not up, but over our heart and pray?
Can we get some forward slash right parentheses in the chat, please?
Can we please get those flooding the chat? I would really appreciate that.
Munchy, Ben, Gib, Jesse, the whole crew's here, plus me.
All the people who went to Bronicon.
Yes, literally all of us, and no one who did go.
Was this intentional? Did we do this on purpose?
Not really.
Well, all right then.
Yeah, obviously.
Well, it was a glorious time.
I want to say it.
As we told everyone who went to Bronicon, this was not what was destined to be.
Because there was another person who was supposed to be here, and that we cried and cried about not being here.
And Tom, Tom was going to be at Bronicon, and it was going to be incredible.
He has more friends at Bronicon than us.
No, no, he was going to be in Illuminati's Secret Spirit cooking parties, and it was going to be great.
It was going to be a great time. But his back is just so fucked up that he couldn't even make it.
It's literally like a nightmare, and I'm scared for him.
Well, who knows, man. I hope he is better or whatever.
His back or his legs, or I'm not 100% clear on that.
I did the last PCP. I'm sure he discussed that at some, I don't know how much he said, I didn't listen to it.
I have not listened to the last one yet.
And also Digi didn't come, because he has a wicked heart.
For all the sympathy we have toward Digi.
Let's talk about Digi's wicked heart for a second.
All the sympathy we have for Tom.
It turns into rage at Digi.
His cynical, evil heart, and not going to be with friends.
I just want to say, to even push this even further, because you may think,
Oh, well, you know, Tom might have been fucked up, but like, you know, he's a poor boy too.
Nate specifically was like offering to help pay for his flight to get to Bronicon.
We did look into arrangements somewhat to see what could be done.
Even if that was paid for, Tom said he still couldn't go. It's just pure pain.
Let me tell you, I don't remember who it was, Nate or Munchy.
One of you suggested that like, well, what if you come and we just carted you around in a wheelchair?
What if we push you around in a wheelchair?
Unironically, it was like, dude, I will be the wheelchair push guy.
That's my excuse not to talk to anyone.
I don't have to do anything. I have the excuse.
And they're like, no, I got to fucking push a thing. I got to do it.
No, sorry, guys, I can't fucking do this. I'm out.
Yeah, sorry, responsibilities. Oh, I'd love to, but I have to push this wheelchair.
Yeah, yeah, that was good. You know, it was gonna, Tom's wheelchair was going to be my, the talk of the town.
No, Tom's wheelchair was going to be the guitar to my give and take at a party, if you know what I'm saying.
You know what I'm saying?
I do, I do.
But it didn't, but it wasn't to be. So fuck you, Tom.
You couldn't, you couldn't do that. You couldn't do me this one thing and give me that out.
You couldn't even help Ben in this one aspect of life. Truly a useless man.
You couldn't even help Ben cheat out of social situations scenarios. You couldn't even help Ben cheat at life.
That's right.
You know, every, every opportunity that was ripped away from Tom tragically is an opportunity that Digi squandered willingly.
Yeah, yeah.
Deliberately, maliciously.
We tried again to come maliciously.
I know he had just been to Otacon the weekend before. I know that's true.
But he had what, four days to rest up? Plenty of time. Plenty of time.
I mean, I came to bring him to Bronycon from camp.
I will defend him until the day I die.
Nothing to do with Otacon. He had been saying forever that no guys, that sounds dumb.
That's dumb. Why would I want to go to Bronycon?
Bronycon.
This is that thing I think permeates this group to some degree that is this deep rooted shame about having been a pony boy at one time.
I never identified as a Brony, but I have zero shame about being a pony boy back in the day.
Who has shame?
Literally, who has shame?
No, no, it's just Digi that has shame.
Yeah, I think it's, I really think it's just Digi.
Okay, maybe it is. Maybe it is.
Maybe, I don't think Tom. Do you think Tom, do you think Tom has the shame?
I think Tom's got that Brony shame.
I don't. I don't. No, not really.
Do you think, do you think Mage?
You know, Mage maybe a little bit. Maybe a little bit.
I don't think, I don't know if Mage has the Brony shame. She's definitely got Brony rage from like people messaging her, asking her like, hey, I love how you draw a pony.
She's frustrated about that.
I think Mage is the very normal, maybe kind of like artist cycle thing.
Mage is a little different from us.
She's mad that she's been typecast.
Yeah, yeah, that's true. And like she kind of has moved on artistically and I think feels a little annoyed.
She's still associated with that fairly strongly.
So I think she has some annoyance at that.
But I mean, she could, she can tell you all about it, I'm sure.
Okay, let's look at this from Digi's perspective.
You know, he, of course, you know, he has no reason to go to BronyCon other than to meet us.
Well, none of us had a reason to go.
Why do you think I fucking went, motherfucker?
I listened to the podcast he was on and he did say that the reason it was like he wanted to see us, but like, like Radcon is like not too far off in the distance.
It was just about to say, yeah, yeah.
Well, we don't know that, nobody's planned Radcon at all.
Nobody has planned it.
We do not have a plan.
The desire is there to do it like kind of soon.
Yeah, the desire.
I suppose, I suppose.
This sounds like a rationalization maybe.
I imagine that he wouldn't would rather think like, oh, well, I'll wait for that as opposed to do something which I don't want to do, but just have the frosting of my friends that they're also sprinkled on top of.
Like, I think all of the BronyCon things he would hate, which I did as well, even though I thought it was funny.
Ironically, I wasn't able to have fun with you guys.
The only times I felt joy at BronyCon that were not in spite of BronyCon were anytime that a song from Friendship is Witchcraft came on.
And then I was like, I'm unironically back into it.
I remember.
I remember why I gave a shit.
And then the song would end.
I'd be like, this is the fucking worst.
This is a fucking nightmare.
I mean, you had a couple like, like, like, like depressant, like on the floor, Ben St hates BronyCon moments.
I did.
Yeah, I did.
No, I, but yeah, let's talk about those.
There were quite a few of those, of the famous Ben St tantrums.
All of that convention floor.
They were not tantrums.
Let's talk about, let's talk about my depressive episodes at BronyCon.
Sure.
You had low lows and low highs at BronyCon.
And first of all, the whole thing is underscored by this, this Twitter thread that you're doing of you, you know, here I go to BronyCon.
Here I am meeting my friends at BronyCon side.
The thing about that, that was, that was ironically ironic.
Indeed.
You know what I mean?
That was like double ironic.
So it was like half sincere.
It was like, it was like, I genuinely feel dread and terror and dismay at the thought that I have to go do this, even though I think I will probably have a good time.
And I was like, how can I monetize it?
So I put it on Twitter and made $0.
Could have logged, I suppose, perhaps.
I don't know.
I could have logged.
Is that a way to get money?
Maybe.
I don't know.
What even is, what even is money?
No one knows.
I almost feel a little bit stupid going to BronyCon.
Like I feel a little bit like I've made the decision.
No.
No, really?
Because, why money?
Because it's the hottest take of a year.
At first, I thought it was going to be like a mix of like, oh, you know, I'm going to BronyCon.
I'll be with my friends.
That will be the main source of passion and joy.
But also, like, you know, like, I will sort of like go to a panel or two and just be like, haha, isn't this silly?
Or also even just go around to the vendor store and buy anything.
I couldn't get one iota of joy from like real pony shit.
No panel.
I'm done.
No panel was any good.
No.
I mean, the Lauren Faust one was like kind of good.
But it was also kind of depressing because she was, she was like talking a little bit about like, all right.
Here's the one like, the one interesting thing about that panel was that she was talking about her like plans.
Wow, you guys really fucked this up, huh?
Like the plans for the main six and all that.
And season one, she was doing the thing.
It's like she didn't know whether there's going to be a season three.
So for season two, she just sort of treaded water and she didn't like introduce the plot elements that she wanted.
To expand on in case the show didn't continue.
And then they got rid of her.
So like that was her biggest regret that she didn't start like her pony story.
And hearing her talk about that was just like, that was like, oh, so like it, it's, you know, really sad.
I mean, I already knew it was really sad, but like she sounded really sad.
And it's something.
We're all in this panel together and like there were like several moments of like across the board.
Everyone there had their own like sad moment.
They had their own like Lily of the Valley moment, if you will.
No.
So like even, even Lauren Faust was the demon to another.
So like Bonnie Zachary, a person who first made Malapony.
Like one of like, I had heard this before.
One of the like thousand.
Wait, like made it back in like the fucking six season?
Yeah.
She was, she was there.
Yeah, she was there.
Wow.
How old is she?
She's like 70.
Like 80.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Okay.
Well, okay.
Whatever.
Lauren Faust, like one of like the, the, the funny, the funny sound bites that she always
says is that, you know, when, when she was brought into Hasbro and someone showed her
like a, like a Malapony movie and they're like, Hey, what do you think about this?
And she's like, wow, this was really bad.
I can do it better.
Basically.
And then she repeat that story.
And like Bonnie like was there and like, like squint and cringe a little bit.
Wait, what did she say about the movie?
They, Lauren Faust said that the movie was really bad.
Did she watch it?
That the old show was shit and terrible.
Yeah.
Oh God.
How uncomfortable.
No, no.
Okay.
No, Ben, it gets worse.
Smash cut to later.
We did a review of that like first ever special Malapony.
Later.
I don't know if that was the first one ever, but there is a point where, where Lauren Faust
is like, like describing like an old show that she wanted to pitch to a network, but
she didn't really get the pitch together.
Was it Galaxy Girls?
No, it wasn't that.
Okay.
So she was doing that.
And she was like, you know what?
You should make that into like a book, like like a pop-up book.
That would be a really interesting thing to have in a book.
And then Lauren Faust or so, or I think the moderator was like, you should, like you do
should work together.
That'd be really cool.
And then Bonnie was like, oh no.
Lauren's a way better artist than I am and she's a way better writer than I am.
So I wouldn't have anything to add.
No.
Get fucked, get fucked, you old bitch.
Get fucked, you old bitch.
Die, boomer.
Die.
Literally like listening to an episode of Quick Draw.
It was so sad.
Everything was sad.
Everything was terrible.
Everyone looked like they had like waste of their lives and they had.
At the end of the panel, they brought a coffin in and they got Bonnie to climb in and they
carried her.
A pink coffin with pony tassels.
Yeah, with like a Puget Pies key mark on it.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
They gave her a noose and it was like that gif where you're looking through the noose
and you see the anime girls, but it was my little pony.
Okay, it was very clear that nobody gets out of this fandom without a lingering depression
that will last a lifetime from it.
Even the creators.
It's just, okay, think about it.
How much suffering has Lauren Foust inflicted upon the world?
Like how much like net total suffering has she personally caused?
Literally worse than Hitler.
Yeah.
You know what?
Like I don't even think that's that incomparable.
You know, at least Hitler's victims were dead afterwards.
Yeah.
They're going to live with this trauma.
It's a literal nightmare.
So that was the only panel that was even slightly positive.
Interesting.
The rest of them weren't even funny.
Ironically, the rest of them were just straight up like a fucking nightmare.
Well, no, no, there was the, uh, the, uh, the costume runway panel.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, with the Fluttershy.
You want to talk about it?
Big, evil Fluttershy.
That was all right.
I guess.
Talk about the Fluttershy.
Floated off to a cosmic realm beyond the scope of mortal comprehension.
Like the actual winners of that contest.
I mean, whatever.
They were like, kind of okay.
I guess who cares.
Some, some, some, some competent costuming work going on there.
The moment when like you Jesse burst into laughter like as loud as you possibly could.
I was like, oh my God.
Like we were sitting in the back so nobody could hear, but it was like really loud.
And I was like, oh my God, this, this Fluttershy's killed Jesse.
Yeah.
It was like eight feet tall.
Well, well, like we had like a group of like a bunch of like fans and like lesser YouTubers,
like hanging around us and stuff.
And so like there was people around, you know, like laughing at my jokes and shit because
they thought I was cool.
So I was like, so when the, when the costume panel started, you know, I had this, I had
this bottle of Wild Irish Rose that I had bought that morning at the liquor store across
from my hotel room.
So I, you know, I immediately, I started drinking as the panel started and it was just
enough to get me like perfect drunk.
And so I was like cracking jokes.
I was like doing running commentary, like making like quips about everyone who came out and
all the costumes and all the, all the, all the little, you know, the glad handing hangers
on around me.
There was like a let's play jokes and stuff.
Yeah.
It's like a let's play, but like real life.
Like is there a word for that?
I don't know.
So I was feeling pretty confident.
It's called comedy.
It's called improv.
I was feeling pretty self assured in my place in the universe.
I was like, nothing can possibly rock my perceptions of the world.
I know exactly who and where I am.
So, um, so right at like, right at peak drunk, this costume comes out and it's like, I guess
you would describe it as furry, but that's not doing it justice.
It was like, it was like a fursuit times 11.
It, it was this lumbering monstrosity, this behemoth from beneath the death.
Like a mecca.
It was like, it was like its own, like personal robot.
It was just rise, like face the thing that should not be.
It's just like lumbered out on, you can hear the earthquake with each lumbering step of
this man standing 10 feet tall, like Paul Bunyan, but even stronger.
Um, and it's just, it's like a, it had like, it was a, it had like hooves, like no hands,
like flat hands.
And it was, and like its head was like 10 times bigger than its body.
And its head was kind of like, like rolling around on its shoulders and stuff, like a fucking
silenail monster.
And it was like, it was like Aldrich of the Deep from Dark Souls 3 that swelled to such
size that it lost shape and became like a formless mass.
But it was supposed to be Fluttershy.
It was so ill fitting that it was just like, every part of it was just like loose and like
moving around like a, like a Jacob Slatter abomination.
And it's fucking 10 feet tall and it lumbered out on stage and I'm at peak drunk and I
just see it and something happened in my body.
Like my soul came out through my eyeballs.
It was like, you ever see that music video where the girl in the pool and at the end
she sees the Eldritch thing and her eyeballs explode.
It was that.
I think it's called fantasy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it was the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life.
I can't explain why any more than I just did.
Why it was the greatest thing I have ever or will ever see.
But it captivated me.
It got inside my brain.
It drove me to the brink of madness.
I am its thrall.
I became this Eldritch creature's thrall for all time.
I will serve big evil Fluttershy until my dying day.
I will, I will work to, to, you know, create, to, to ripple out its machinations throughout
my society and the world.
I will work to achieve the perfect apocalyptic setting for his glorious return.
I just, I just started laughing harder than I've ever laughed in my life.
And like, I got dizzy.
Like my vision was actually blurring.
And I thought I was having a stroke or something.
There's like a red vinerette, like around your like field of view.
Yeah.
And you're taking like.
Remember that horrible Dark Souls 2 effect when you enter a boss room and like the weird
red pulse appears on the edge of the screen.
It was exactly like that.
Yeah.
And I almost died and I think maybe I did die.
And what is before you now is not the original me, but a superior version created from the
trauma and chaos that was birthed by this monstrosity.
And after like, and then like as soon as it was there, it was gone.
Like you didn't see it again for the rest of the panel.
At the end of the panel, like all the costumes were there at the side and they were like
giving up the awards and stuff, but you didn't see big evil Fluttershy.
Big evil Fluttershy.
It seems impossible considering the size.
Yeah.
It just went off stage and disappeared and it was never seen again.
But after the panel, when you guys all went off some direction, I had like a spider sense.
You know, it had planted its seed in my brain.
So now I can always sense it's present.
So I knew where to go.
So I was like a rat in a maze that was cloned from another rat that had already completed
the maze.
Exactly where to go to find big evil Fluttershy.
And I ended up alone in an elevator with big evil Fluttershy.
And at first, you know, I dare not speak out of turn amongst my Lord.
I dare not bother it.
But after the elevator ride, I couldn't hold back my excitement anymore and I flagged it
down and I'm like big evil Fluttershy.
Big evil Fluttershy.
It's me, your favorite thrall, endless chess, global icon and national treasure.
Here to do your bidding.
And I saw it without its head on without its head.
And what was what was under the head?
I will never say I will never speak the true identity of big evil Fluttershy.
It's better left the imagination.
But it was glorious.
And I'm like big evil Fluttershy.
Can you please for my familia at home?
Can you can you put on?
Can you once more don the big evil Fluttershy head and take a picture with me?
And it graciously accepted my humble request and I did get a selfie with big evil Fluttershy.
And it was the peak of my life.
The greatest moment.
Oblivion, get that in there.
We got to get all these.
But by the way, while the like the rankings were finishing up, they were like announcing
a third place in the costume contest.
It was some whatever crazy Luna Celestia fusion thing.
Second place was, I don't know, some like Pinkie Pie thing.
And as like as they're like, okay, and the winner of the cut, we're all chanting big evil Fluttershy.
Big evil Fluttershy.
It was not.
It was some other idiot.
But you know, Jesse, while that was happening, while you were making your whips and quips,
Michelle leaned over to me, you know, my girlfriend at this time and said to me, Jesse is really funny.
And at that moment, two things happened.
My IQ plummeted to zero.
And my rage surged to levels never before seen by man.
And I knew you had to die.
There was no way I could let you live after she said this to me.
But I thought I would leave you until you were in a vulnerable position.
But alas, you did not let your guard down.
So watch your fucking back.
The picture of my Lord Big Evil Fluttershy.
Ha ha, get cut.
Green garden.
That was a great time.
Where the girls in the pool is so apt for this entire thing.
Since all is just funneled into this convenience area, like like housed the slaughterhouse,
ready to fucking finger each other and get our tongues up all up inside some brony mouth and ass at the Brony Conhorgy.
And we go inside and we just slowly look around as we see the people around us.
And we realize there will be no fingering or tongue and ass here.
In fact, there will be nothing but your eyes firmly planted at the ground
as you do the virgin walk up and down the escalators.
Try not to notice the people around you who will surely rip out your eyes
and pull out your intestine if you were to look at them the wrong way.
It was literally a nightmare.
As long as you equip the sacred red badge of do not approach me,
you have an impervious bubble that no one can penetrate.
I didn't feel like Brony Con was like a nightmare.
I mean, yes, it's full of freaks and autists and fat, crazy people who don't know how to dress.
For sure.
Or how to bathe.
Or to talk.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like it's on the surface.
On the surface, it's a nightmare.
But there's something about it.
I mean, I had just come to Brony Con from retard camp.
So I had been like...
I forgot.
I had been like taking care of disabled people.
So I was in the zone at the time.
And just seeing all these people is just like, yeah, it's normal.
Yeah, they're just people.
They're just people.
Oh, no.
So it was like, this was like a desensitized to it?
Yeah, a little bit.
It's just like I wasn't like blown away by how freaky people were.
It was just sort of like, yeah, ponies are cool.
Everyone's having fun.
This is great.
I really love the atmosphere.
I love the atmosphere of just like acceptance and like blind like love.
Alright, bro.
Yeah.
It was really stupid and I liked it.
Okay, listen.
No, I was funny.
Yeah, I had a great time for the record the whole weekend.
No, of course, sure.
I want to illustrate the kind of people that we were there because it wasn't just like
they were like kind of weird.
Okay, for instance, the first night while I'm getting my badges, there's a person behind
us.
There's two people actually who I never turned around to look at because I knew if I were
to look at them, there would be something wrong.
Like just something bad would happen.
Maybe not even to me, but on the other side of the world, there would be like a terrorist
attack in China.
So I could only hear their voices and you know, separate from them, you know, many rose
back in the giant long line that was a registration for the badges.
There was a guy playing saxophone, you know, trying to like, like alleviate some of the
stress of being in line, you know, trying to be a fun kind of kooky guy playing megalovania
and other such songs, maybe smashed mouth a little bit in there, trying to have some
fun, spread some joy.
He was the meister for the entire line.
And these people, just like whenever a note would be produced from the saxophone, would
like violently shudder and like actually like exhale and be like, ah, this shouldn't be
loud.
Like if it were up to me, like this wouldn't be loud in society.
They would cover their ears.
They would groan and they would have much disgusted look on their faces.
And like, like rock back and forth that they were hit with like a psychic wave, like a
blast to the shock and blast to the forehead of the temple.
Like from this dude, like making music, like it wasn't bad.
Like they, they had like a quote unquote like sound sensitivity trigger, which I have no
idea what that even means.
And I don't even believe it's true for these individuals specifically.
Like they were just constantly just acting like everyone around them was being so annoying
and so uncouth and improper in line registration for bronicon.
Did you see this person at any other time?
Like, did you see them later?
No, never.
This was the only experience I had with them.
Maybe they couldn't, maybe they couldn't hack it and they just didn't show up the next
day.
Dude, okay.
They were complaining the entire time about like fun things that were happening.
And then when they weren't complaining to one another, they were like, the only thing
that's getting me through this is how good my nails look.
Dude, look how good my nails look.
Oh my God, your toes look so good, bro.
What?
You know, literally not to be mean to these people, but you would simply think if someone
is like some trauma related to sound sensitivity, a con does not seem like the right place for
them to go, right?
Yeah, just wear earmuffs.
Like sorry, bro, if you are at a con and you don't like con things.
Yeah, it's kind of a strange choice.
It's just like so like incapable of nearly existing.
Like just subsistence is like too hard for people at bronicon.
Yeah.
Like being more subsistence is way too hard.
Boy, that's a big mood.
No, you can't say, you can't turn into Twitter like this, but you can't say things like that.
I honestly said lit yesterday.
It made me sad.
I got the better of me.
Well, you know, being around so many weak people, I think like elevated my powers because
all weekend, like you said, Nate, because I'm so funny, according to Michelle.
Yeah, it's like all weekend, I could feel that my chakras were perfectly aligned and
my powers were at their peak.
I was at my most in my most powerful form.
And I think it's because like every every time that like it would have dipped, something
happened that like rejuvenated me and like pushed more power into me, absorbing more
souls like Shang Tsung.
It was like, you know, it was like seeing Lauren Faust and then seeing Big Evil Fluttershy
and like because I knew it was the last one and it was a big deal.
And it's probably the last time that we're going to see some of these people.
And the last time we're going to have a chance to like be at the big Brony Khan party.
It like I was like willing myself to be in a good mood, like the best possible mood the
whole time because like going to the convention, I didn't.
I was like so angry the whole week leading up to it.
Like, I don't want to go.
I don't want to travel.
That's exactly my yeah.
And like right up to like right up to where I got to the convention.
I was just like steaming, fuming mad.
But then I like walked in the doors and I'm like, OK, it's business time.
It's time to be like a professional.
It's time to be everyone's hero.
It's time to be global icon and national treasure.
The horse, you fucking king and shake everybody's hand and kiss everybody's baby and have
adventures and have stories to tell and fucking lose my fucking mind and go crazy and have fun.
And I will.
Yeah.
I will myself to be like the perfect being.
And thanks to the powers of all these like mystical totems that I kept running into like
Faust and Big Evil Fluttershy, I was able to accomplish that herculean feat of being cool.
It's so disgusting being the coolest guy at Brony Khan.
We've had literally the opposite reaction because the entire like month's proceeding.
I was like, dude, Brony Khan.
Well, I can't wait to fucking get crime through Brony Khan orgy and then hang out with all
my friends and I'm going to meet like a whole mob of 60 people there.
And then I just like get in.
I like become autistic.
There was something about me that like made me like want to like blend into the crowd.
Like it made me regress to when I was 13 at the last Brony Khan or like, you know, whenever
it made me like just like being in that conventions there, being in that mindset, being in my
literal little space that is my little pony conventions.
I just receded back into the recesses in my mind and I just became the same person I was.
So I just became autistic and awkward the entire time and I just became like one of the masses.
Like I was receded into like the mob collective of Brony Khan the entire time, just wasting away.
You know, at the end I was like, it's too loud here.
Oh God, if we're up to me, this wouldn't be allowed.
At the end, after the convention was over, that's when like all the suppressed race
and hate started flooding back like all at once.
Because like it's not like there were no annoying things that happened during the weekend.
But it's that like every annoying thing that happened, I didn't notice because I was willing
myself not to and I was pushing it all down.
And like the second that I like woke up the day after the convention, it was like the valve
had turned and it all came pouring back.
All the fucking first of all, all the physical pain and sickness and age that I've been suppressing
when I was like reliving my glory days and my youth at the convention.
And secondly, all the pent up rage from the whole ordeal.
And like, like I woke up the day after the after the convention.
I woke up like in the middle of the night and couldn't get back to sleep.
And I felt it.
I felt that I had a fucking sore throat.
And I'm like, oh my, like just instantly pure rage at having a sore throat because there's
nothing more heinous on this earth.
And I'm just thinking, oh my God, which one of you fucking mutants shook my hand and had
a fucking disease?
And now I'm going to be living with this for a fucking month.
Just like just hating all things.
And then I fucking went to the airport and I got on a plane and there was a child behind
me, just the whole flight home going, where we going, mommy, where we going, mommy, mommy,
where we going, where we going.
Oh, you want a minge?
Yeah, just like right in my ear, like a dentist drill.
And I'm just like, I almost went through the gate home at the airport in handcuffs because
I was about to chuck that fucking infant out the window, that nine year old or whatever
infant.
I almost committed a murder on the plane.
And then I got home and I've just been sick and mad and fucking sad the whole time because
I'm not at RooneyCon anymore.
I'm not at my post con mortal agony because I'm not in my element anymore.
The one place that I'm an important person and everyone thinks I'm cool.
You know, it's almost like some people like work better when dealing with actual human
beings one on one as opposed to on Twitter or social media.
It's almost like that.
It's a more natural, like better way to deal with the world to do it in person.
What's this gobbledygook you're trying to dispense with?
I know.
It's hard to imagine.
Anyway, time to go sit and tweet to Bernie and ask him for his cockpicks.
The theme of mine, Bernie Kahn, was one of positive character development.
Because the last time I went, I mean, I am still like a shy person, but back then I was
like, I'm crying right now, guys.
What are you going to do about it?
Are you going to change my diet before me?
You know, it's really funny.
It was the first time traveling alone, first time in America, first time meeting all of
you.
Because you only went once before, right?
Yeah.
And also first time having to say, oh, hi, you like my work?
Cool.
Right.
And so every experience I had that wasn't as a complete embarrassment felt like a victory
to me.
So I guess that's why my spirits were so high the whole time.
There were multiple moments where I did something that I wouldn't have done last time, like when
I saw the Susie from Delta Rune cosplayer and I was like, I'm going to go compliment her.
Because last time-
Oh, that was a perfect comparison to the previous one.
The very distinct moment where I think, I don't remember who of us saw.
The last Bernie Kahn, there was a cool Raven cosplayer and she looked really good and none
of us went over to say, hey, that's really cool.
And we just looked at her from afar.
I mean, she knows it's really cool.
Whatever.
I know.
But this time I felt like I should do the thing that's more difficult and I went over
and complimented her and I got a picture.
And that was cool and I felt really cool about it.
Way to go.
And I felt comfortable walking around the artist alleys by myself instead of like staying
with a group cos it's fine.
I can meet people.
I can find people.
I have a phone that works in America now.
I don't have to be worried about like not being able to call anyone.
So, yeah, like everything was great.
I- Oh, and here's my big thing.
APSAdventures.site, my webcomic website thing.
I had a punk the plush with me.
Rest in peace, the Kickstarter for that.
But it doesn't matter.
I had the plush and I had a bunch of leaflets that I had made previously and there was like
25 to 50 of them.
And I tried my best to hand them out to as many cool people as possible.
I think I have a list here of like notable ones.
Lauren Faust, I stood in line to get a signature but I said, I fuck the signature.
Could you have this and you become a fan of me please?
So that was cool.
Hell yeah.
I saw Emma Larson scurrying around acting like blending in because he looks like one of them.
Dude, as the con ended, he was like the first guy out the door.
We saw him like sprinting off away out of BrodyCon forever in the back of your mirror.
I saw him slinking around and I walked up to him and say, hey, did you have this?
And he's like, yeah, sure.
So I don't know whether he's going to read that but I gave it to him.
I found SaberSpark and handed it to him.
I love Compossible a lot, famous KP.
Thank you, KP.
Riddle My Ass Batman showed up.
I gave one to him.
Of course.
Oh man, we saw so many capers with Riddle My Ass Batman.
We riddled so many asses.
Past analysis, British Ninja.
Dr. Wolfe, I gave one to.
Kazy said something about my conversation with Dr. Wolfe.
She was watching and Dr. Wolfe sort of leers over you with condescending eyes
and like a more Santa word if you're sitting on his knees saying I won.
He has the eyes of a predator.
He's like a skinner.
Like a wolf, dare I say.
Dr. Wolfe, all I want for Christmas is for you to review my web comic.
And he's like, ah, okay, I'll get around to that.
Ah, okay.
He lied.
APS Adventures?
I've heard the name, but beyond that.
Oh, the Ice Cold Water Man.
He was selling Ice Cold Water.
I gave him my leaflet and he didn't get it at first, but I stood there explaining it.
It's like it's a comic.
Like you can go, you can read it and it's like, are you selling anything on there?
Yeah, sure.
It's like, okay, I'll give it a look.
So, you know, he's got it.
As long as you're selling something.
As long as you're like, you know, I was advertising.
He didn't understand advertising if there wasn't selling.
It was like, what are you selling?
Ice Cold Water Man was involved with perhaps the emotional highlight of the entire arc.
Oh yeah, we will get to that.
I mean, I did give one to Miss Anthropony as well.
And Chad, AKA like the meme Chad guy.
Yeah, Cosplay Chad, whose name was Nate, by the way.
His name was Nate.
That was a really cool guy.
There was lots of really cool guys.
The only other person I have written down here is Ephraim.
Even though like, he's not any more significant than the other people that I gave the leaflet to.
He's just like, the most prominent that I could think of.
Yeah.
And yeah, I gave the leaflet to a bunch of IRCK people and some friends of some other pony-reviewed people.
It was just like, yeah, I am advertising.
Lauren Faust is now a biggest fan of Bailjap.
Please go read it.
She's drawing fan art right now.
Speaking of RFCK people, let's talk about Slimehouse.
Oh well, I want to talk about Slimehouse on the RFCK that will be recorded.
But we can mention a brief here.
Well, I'm not going to mention everyone because there was a lot of people and I'll forget someone, I'm sure.
But there was a house of like 12 or 13 people just came along in case you don't know.
They were just RFCK people.
13, like Organization 13?
Yeah, it was.
Oh my gosh, fuck yes.
And they were not pony people.
Like one of them had like ever seen My Little Pony before.
They were just there for basically an RFCK con at Brony.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure T-Fab has probably seen My Little Pony once or twice.
Good man.
Yeah.
It was so much, I was so glad.
Dude, it was the best part of the con.
They made it so much more fun.
It was the best part of the con.
Yeah, by far.
I mean, we had a literal gang around us like the entire time we were at BronyCon.
It was fucking sick.
They were awesome.
We could easily dominate any group with our like-
Dr. Wolf should have tried fucking with us and see what happened.
And Levy Jevy gave me a bunch of communist pins.
He brought like a big box of like old like pins from like communist states and he just
was like, yeah, just take as many as you want.
It took like five.
It was awesome.
That's sick.
It was so great because the people at Slimehouse are like OG RFCK people and like they know
what's up and so it was great being able to talk to them.
It was great being able to like, there was one point I forget what I was doing.
The Gen-1ers.
They were like all Gen-1ers.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like walking around.
I was trying to do something specifically.
I might have been looking for Miss Anthropony or I might have been doing something else.
But the point is I didn't want to talk to anyone.
And so there was some dude that was like, hey, Munchy, is that you?
And I was like, yep.
And I just kept on walking at one point.
Come on, dude.
You got to say hi or something.
No, no.
I said like, yo, hey, and then I kept on walking.
But the point is, is that like that was like, you know, that's the PCP had experience.
But like the RFCK had experience where like I like real, they say slime once and then
I'm all up in them and we just hang out all the entire time.
And it's great.
It's a great time.
And they were great to hang out with.
And after the con on last day at the pier, well, me, Hippo and Ben and Cassie were all
waiting for our Greyhound bus.
We're just hanging out in the Baltimore Harbor and it was great.
It was a great time.
Oh yeah.
Well that last night just like chilling on the harbor was the best.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah, it was red.
That was nice.
Too bad we left a little bit before that, me and Michelle.
Yeah.
But you know, just on this subject, there was just a whole bunch of people who came to
BronyCon specifically to like see us.
Yeah.
There were many people who fit that description.
Oh, there was people who watched my stream, Juicy Shack Meet.
Oh, Russell was there.
Russell was there.
Russell himself in all his ghostly glory.
If anyone watches my stream, Juicy Shack Meet and his fiance who he proposed to live on
my stream or at least was updating as he did it.
That was there.
Those two were there.
It was great.
I can't remember everybody, but that was, this is just why Munchy's idea of going to
BronyCon, like I don't care about the ponies, I'm totally over it, but just have a unifying
place where people can meet, which is kind of what the point of a con is in general.
Honestly, the main thing for me is that it really has my gears were and thinking about
some sort of like PCP meetup specifically for like all, it's not just for PCP heads,
but everyone in the extended PCP universe getting together in one place would sure be
a dope thing without the distraction of outside forces like BronyCon or whatever.
I am a little sad that it was the last one and there's not going to be another chance
to go to it and see all those people again.
Just go to Trotcon, dude.
Trotcon's in October.
Yeah, you're right.
What is that?
Made up country, like fucking Baselvania or some shit.
Yeah, Maryland.
I'm sick of hearing about all these fake conventions and fake quarters of the world.
Oh, shout outs to Tarbuck Transom, the belt man.
Oh, okay.
Let me tell that story real quick.
I got that belt right here.
I'm looking at it right now.
It's fucking sick.
Okay.
All right.
Listen up, lads.
I've got the story pulled up right in front of me.
So let me just tell you real quick.
So me and Michelle both, just a preliminary thing.
We both cosplayed like most of the days.
And so Michelle cosplayed as keg standard Phantom Horm and he made it to BronyCon.
One Brony Curious was there live as a Rule 63 gender swap version.
Way to go, Michelle.
Tom lives on through you.
Rest is soul.
And so I was there.
I don't know.
I did like a keg standard thing, whatever.
But okay, the biggest thing was I was there in an eight slime corp executive suit.
Yes.
I did like Katana.
My Sheen Eye.
It was glorious.
And he made those paper pins for everyone.
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
I made a bunch.
I made myself slime corp pins to hand out.
One of which I gifted to Miss Anthropony, of course.
Indeed.
As a show of good faith.
It was wonderful.
And okay.
So I'm wearing my fucking suit.
I'm going out there looking like a million bucks oblivion.
I'm going to need you to add some visuals for this.
But I look down like halfway through the day, whatever, I stand up, I unbutton my shirt
to walk around or something.
I notice I'm not wearing a fucking belt.
I can't believe my standard issue slime corp belt is nowhere to be found.
And I'm looking, frankly, strictly unprofessional.
And it makes me want to kill myself.
It's a nightmare.
When all of a sudden, he had already happened to walk up to me, one mysterious man with
a large suitcase.
I don't know what he's doing.
He said, hey, nice to meet you.
Hey, I like your stuff.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's up, man?
I stand there.
I say, oh my God, I forgot my belt.
He says, would you like me to make you one?
This man, this man was a humble belt Smith.
This was not a setup.
This was not a scheme.
This was not a ruse.
I literally realized I didn't have a belt.
He says, I literally will make you a belt on the spot right here.
And by the way, I don't know if people remember this specifically, but this was on a holy ground
because we were in the area, like on the first and possibly the second brony cons were like,
I mean, to me, this is holy ground where we all like hung out the whole time.
There was this balcony.
It was, it was at that sacred spot, the chair, the chair place.
That's right.
The chair place where you can overlook like the, the main entrance, everybody comes in
and stuff.
It was on this, this hallowed ground where this event took place.
Oh, and by the way, Michelle was unconscious from drinking too much on the floor for this
entire episode and missed the entire thing, but was right next to me.
Hilarious.
Oblivion, edit that in.
She'll love it.
Um, so the point was right there in front of me, he opens a suitcase, he pulls out his
wares and his tinctures and his potions and his lashes and immediately goes to work measuring
and like measuring my waist to know how much he needs and fucking folding the fabric.
And he has this wooden contraption where Tarbuck Transom, of course, is his name.
And what he does is there's a link in the show notes to the whole Twitter thread.
Go buy this.
This man's fucking wares.
He's a magic man.
His shtick is he weaves first of all, he's like a handyman of the stars.
But what he does is he uses this wooden contraption and the idea is he makes like like cloth and
belts and necklaces and stuff in the style that a pony would be able to from my little
pony.
This is like the conceit.
Now I don't know if this work because he definitely needed fingers to do this, but it's close
enough.
This wooden L shape that he like hangs the belt off of and like weaves it towards him
like a fucking like a like Don Flamengo puppeting the entire population of Dressrosa from one
piece.
And basically he just weaves a belt in front of me like like like Charlotte's Web and
gives them it's perfectly black matches my suit perfectly.
I put it on and my honor is restored.
Slime Corp is no longer disgraced on this day.
He saved Slime Corp.
He saved our profits.
There's no greater prize to be saved in this world.
So thank you Tarbuck Transom and people unironically go click the link to the Twitter thread I
made about this.
Just listen to this one little phrase about how I'm describing it as he's weaving this
belt.
Okay, here's here's from the Twitter thread.
And I say with my puny monkey brain, I struggled to comprehend the IRL birth of a new universe
I was witnessing.
Alas, I could only gaze, slack-jawed, and pray that God would forgive this man who dared
create such wonders in defiance of his law.
This was me witnessing the belt being woven before my eyes.
Scroll down.
I have links to like his his fucking cards and stuff.
If you want a holy relic of a belt or a necklace or like a wristband or whatever, look up Tarbuck
Transom.
He's your man.
He's a god.
He's a saint.
He also gave me and Munchie a po-nut pins.
And if you don't know what that is, a po-nut is a horse butthole.
Oh my god.
It's funny.
Oh, that's what those were.
He asked me.
Oh, Tarbuck, you were such a pure man until this very moment.
He shows, he takes out a satchel, right?
He takes out a small satchel containing who knows what.
And he says like, I don't know.
And he just says like, I'm like, oh, what's, I made some joke about, I don't remember what
I said was in the sack.
And he's like, actually, it's full of horse buttholes.
And I'm like, all right.
And so he takes them out and he's like, here you go.
And he's little, these little pins, little buttons, horse buttholes, a mother and daughter,
a twilight sparkle.
Yeah, you got Twilight Velvet, mom.
And Twilight Velvet.
And he gives us each one.
And I'm like, all right, sick, and I wore it for the rest of the con.
And also, the first day, like first thing that happens before we saw Chris Chan, oh yeah,
we all saw Chris Chan.
We met Chris Chan.
We took pictures with the lady herself.
And Christine, fuck, wait, where's my Chris Chan still?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We were talking about Tarbuck and the pussy thing.
Yes, okay.
So he, oh, the button, no, first thing that happened before that even happened, like right
through the door, someone puts a sticker on Munchie's back that says, I love ponut.
Yeah, I don't know who did this, I don't know how it happened.
But instead of a heart for love, it's a ponut.
It's a bottle.
Oh, of course.
Like, so you take it off and I take that shit and I slap it on the back of my phone and
it's still there.
That's like my eye, my eye, my eye ponut, ponut sticker is going to be with me for a
long, long time.
You know, a sales spiked for our boy Tarbuck.
When I started telling the story, but they've plummeted back down to zero.
No, no, no, don't worry, don't worry.
He was a hero to me as well.
Because see, like I came to like, in the vendors hall, I was at this place and they had prints
and I'm like, oh, I want that prints.
And the guy at the vendor's thing was like, oh, okay, here's a ticket, come back in a
half hour.
So I'll print it off for you and I'm like, wait a minute, you're telling me I got a,
I was just about to be out of this hall.
I got to come back now in a half hour.
Every other, every other booth has prints at the ready.
You didn't warn me that I'd have to wait for your ass.
So I'm, I'm steaming mad.
I'm steaming mad.
So then I come back there a half an hour and he still hasn't finished my print.
I'm like, how long does it take to print off a picture of a flutter shy, you son of
a bitch?
I'm fucking, I'm furious.
I'm so mad.
I'm going to lose my fucking shit.
But luckily Tarbuck happens to also be at that same booth and he's like, you know what?
This is bullshit.
I'm going to get you your print right now.
And he like rushes off to the printing machines and he just does it himself in like two minutes.
And I'm like, what a hero.
And also I left my energy drink there and he kept it for me.
He didn't pee or poop or spit in it or anything.
As far as you know, speaking of leaving energy drinks, Munchy, I left my fucking berry quake
in your bag.
It's still in there.
You better fucking guard that thing.
And also he got me a belt as well.
I like, I just saw him.
I ran into him another time and he was wearing a belt and it was like a red and gold like
Lannister colors custom belt with like the Lannister symbol belt buckle and it looked
really cool.
And I just like absent mind like, like, Hey man, that's a cool belt.
And he's like, you wanted it.
And I'm like, what?
And he just took it off and gave it to me.
And so now I have a cool belt around his ankles and waddled off.
Truly the element of generosity.
Oh, it's so true.
It's so true.
He really was.
We should literally do, you know what, Tarbuck?
We should like, we should like partner with him to make like PCP brand belts, like the
PCP belt.
Oh my.
We can go for him.
That's a fascinating idea.
It's a swell idea there.
Yeah.
It's made.
Hey, let's talk real quick about the, the live action gang warfare that took place.
Okay.
There were some highlights of that, of that exchange, specifically me when I fucking
killed you, Ethan.
Yeah.
You think I'm going to let this go?
No.
I fucking took a picture of you and you're dead.
I was literally solid snake.
I was, okay.
There was a gang warfare going on between the killers and the rowdies, obviously.
And it was photo.
What would you call it?
Picture tag or photo tag or something?
I mean, you have to shoot the other player with a camera, but it's based on picture
tag or something.
You post a picture, you post it in the discord chat and whoever does it first, then you're
dead.
It's an elimination challenge.
That's right.
So, okay.
Cassey won.
Yay.
Great for you, Cassey.
You piece of shit.
But better than that, more interesting.
Who got the picture of you like bolting?
That was Cassey.
That was okay.
That's what I'm getting to.
So I kill Ethan.
I'm literally the sneakiest man.
I'm gonna just paint the picture real quick.
This is going on for like an hour.
I am hardcore camping in the dealer's room.
It was great.
I'm standing at this one great little corner where I can see a bunch of access points to
the fucking dealer's room.
And I've got my eyes peeled.
The problem is, I don't know any of these fucking unpopular, no-name fucking rowdies.
Who the fuck even are you people?
Develop a YouTube presence already, if that would be really convenient.
Also real quick.
All the rowdies didn't like post their pictures in that chat the way like all the killers
did.
That seemed fucked up.
What are you talking about?
All the killers right before we started posted pictures.
Why didn't the rowdies do that?
Because we had all sized up each other right before it started.
You weren't there at the beginning and you weren't listening to the rules.
Which would have come handy specifically for you because you would have been able to get
a lot of revives because you wouldn't have been yourself.
That's definitely true.
I would have run.
There was a whole section of the stream where we like take, like we like look at each other
to know what each other looks like.
Okay, well then why did all the killers specifically go out of their way to post their pictures?
Because a bunch of new people got recruited and they had to post their pictures as soon
as they were recruited.
Exactly.
Okay, fine.
But point is, so I was just camping and whatever, everyone's dying, I'm watching in the chat
as people are dropping, left, right and center, Ethan, I see him coming around the corner.
He's in hardcore maximum gamer mode.
He is crouching, he is stalking, he is hiding behind things, he's got his peepers popped,
he's in every direction simultaneously.
But that fool, he dips into the bathroom and I knew, I knew this was my chansu.
So I just go, I go to the corner, around the corner as the door leads out back into the
dealer's hall and I camp there in darkness praying, he doesn't look around the corner,
he doesn't, as we say in the biz, check his six as he leaves the bathroom and he did not
that fool and I get endless pictures of him leaving like a dunce.
So that's how you do it in the big leagues, lads.
Okay, but then I see people being like, oh, I gotta, Steve is like, I gotta get into the
dealer's hall.
How am I supposed to get into the dealer's hall?
I'm camping there waiting to stop any fucking piece of shit rowdy who tries to get into the
dealer's hall.
And as I turn my back for one split fucking second, Kazi literally cheating, having revived
already, oh quote, following the rules, yeah, whatever, suck my dick.
She comes back and she says, I see her and my phone is down, I'm looking away for one
half a split fucking second, I see her, eyes go wide with awe that she may have the chance
to capture the rarest of beasts, me, Nate Bestman, and her phone goes up faster than
mine can, so I know my only option is to sprint out of there and pray some of these colossal
land whales will block the line of sight so I don't get captured.
But alas, despite my incredible speed, oblivion put this on screen, it just wasn't enough
and she got me and you know what, good kill, good kill, Kazi.
That's a great picture nonetheless.
The image of forgetting you is so incredible because you are just mid-sprint, you are, it's
like a gazelle, Gavilan is a man.
Let me post it in the fucking thing, there it is, there.
The caption is simply, that feel when.
That feel when?
And you know, people are going and they're posting all kinds of things, that feel when
someone mentions yang gang, I think a frame posted that, I don't know, that feel when
someone criticizes capitalism, you know, he's there, the boy is there.
Oh, this is me and my keg standard cosplay incident.
Oh my god, this is so incredible.
Look at my foot is off the ground, I'm clearly pivoting on my left foot, my muscles rippling
as I'm speeding up, it's like, you ever see that, that animatrix-
It's like a real statue.
It is, it is, you ever see that animatrix thing of like that black rile like racer
guy, that Olympic runner, and like his muscles are rippling, yeah, literally me, literally
me escaping the matrix.
I think if you look closely at this picture, you can see me physically moving, breaking
free of the confines of this picture.
You can see the lines of code around you as you're picking through the machines.
But it wasn't enough in a Titanfell that day, the Ratties took the victory.
They did, they did.
It was a resounding victory.
Please just analyze with me.
All three real life gang violence is Ratties have won.
All four slime fest, Ratties have won.
Is there a single victory the killers can point to in any regard?
Yeah, the moral victory every single time, every single time.
We are morally undefeated.
No, no, actually, because Ballard, who got me, I didn't, like this guy was wearing like
a pink and purple, green, like Hawaiian shirt.
I didn't know him, and I didn't know whether he was a killer or a rowdy, but I took a picture
of him and I was uploading it.
And he hadn't seen me.
And I asked him, you know, are you a rowdy?
Because I can't actually tell, I'll stop your picture upload if you're a rowdy.
And he's like, yeah, he wasn't a rowdy, he was a killer, so he clearly didn't win the
moral victory on that.
Hey, lying is within the rules.
Lying is absolutely fair game in this gang warfare lifestyle.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's the moral victory to me.
I want to have a call out post.
According to the RFCK people who knew this was happening for literal months, they couldn't
follow the simple rules of wearing your gang colors, and it made me genuinely feel like
purple.
I didn't fucking know this was happening.
It made me so mad that like no one paid attention to that rule, and I hate them all.
So you're welcome for being so bad at everything.
That's fair.
Um, that was, that was like one of the highlights of the con before that me and Ben put up all
these flyers that I had made for Slam Corp and they were super cool and they were there
until the end of the con.
They were there until the end of the con.
It was great.
Dude, post some of those pictures.
A couple of them got taken down, but a few of them, like most of them stayed around and
like we're still there at the very end.
Yeah, I found a couple.
It was like finding, it was like finding Easter eggs.
Yeah.
It was cool.
Someone joined the server, at least one person actually joined the server because of them.
That's dope.
We did it.
We did it boys.
Um, it was awesome.
Yeah, dude, sick.
What else did they just say?
I mean, what else do we do?
I mean, there's like, there's like a ton of little stories in a ton.
There's tons, yeah.
It was one of those things where it's like you should have been there.
I mean, all of the joys aren't, you know, necessarily antidote so there are certainly
more.
I mean, there are thousands that we could tell, but like most of the fun was just being
there with everyone, you know, being with all of our fans and all of our friends, just
hanging out around BronyCon.
It was great.
If I had to give one prescription, if I think there's one thing to take away from this,
it's that look, I understand not everybody had the money to like fly to BronyCon and
not everybody.
Like we didn't promise we'd do anything really.
Like there was no guarantee.
I'd simply like whenever there's opportunities, try to take them because, you know, like,
oh, like we were saying, like Ben and Jesse and stuff, you know, they weren't looking
forward to seem like a pain, but you know, even the pain and even the financial struggle
of like trying to scrounge up money to afford stuff like this.
I'm not saying be responsible with your money, but like if you can do it, you know, the pain
of going there and like the exhaustion is temporary, but the memories, the memories last
a lifetime.
Yes.
So try, you know.
This is definitely what I was thinking.
I was, I was like putting off making the decision about whether or not to go.
I had made like a half decision like, oh, it's expensive to fly.
I'm just, I'm, you know, whatever, I'll meet you at Radcon.
But I kept thinking like, am I going to like enjoy these memories more or less than a couple
hundred pounds?
Yeah.
Like really?
Like money can be made back.
I can't do this again, especially since it's the last Bronycon and I do have some pony
things I want to do as in like meet Lauren Faust the first time.
Indeed.
So like, uh, I think it was definitely worth spending the money now and having fun.
Yeah.
It was, I got what I wanted out of it, which was a ton of really hilarious stories and
exactly adventures, even, even like the little like just side missions and were hilarious
and cool.
Finding the random, like the setup game machine and playing the Wolverine game on NES, the
LG, the LGN game was in Spanish for some reason and Wolverine's going around.
He has no claws in that game.
He just jumps around.
He's like multicolored pipes and fights like star men from earthbound and collects hamburgers
for health.
And at the end of every level, saber tooth shows up and starts ranting at you in Spanish.
He would do that.
It was dope.
All the times when we walked to McDonald's and it was so fucking humid and hot, we walked
to McDonald's and Ben got like 1200 quarter pounders.
No, this is, this is, this is, this is the hack.
This is the hack.
You go to McDonald's, $3 for two McDoubles.
That's sick.
That's $6 for four McDoubles.
You throw the buns away, $6 for eight, eight patties.
It's pretty good.
Well, I was with you until you said throw the buns away.
You monster.
Throw the buns.
I know, I know.
You want the buns.
Poison.
It'll be, we will die.
The thing about the, you know, this makes me, I think about this a lot, but it's like,
you know, a while ago, I'm not saying it's on the same level, not exactly equivalent,
but like years ago, I decided I don't want like, for example, like a romantic, long
dist relationship.
If that's what like a relationship required, like for me, it would not be worth it.
So like I, a long distance relationship, like some people are happy to do it.
That's fine for them.
I decided I don't want it.
No one's happy to do it.
They're all lying.
Yeah.
Nobody wants to.
It's not the ideal, obviously.
Some people think it's worth it.
Hey, that's, that's fine.
That's for them.
But like, I really think like one of the main reasons why is cause like, I just think there's
something kind of essential about being around other people who you care about physically
and kind of like, I think that these sorts of things, honestly, for us, like as a friend
group, as the PCP, I think it's kind of really important that we too get together to kind
of like, when once we're together, like everyone, when they're in real life facing each other,
no one's like as mean as they can be online or like snarky.
So it kind of just helps like refresh any negativity.
I don't know.
Like there's been a little bit of bile between me and Ben lately.
I don't know about you, Ben, but I felt like totally cleansed and I was just so happy to
see you and hang out with you.
I was just like, what are we even arguing about?
What does it matter?
Especially the, with this group in particular, because with this like friend group, the, the
fact that we're like a podcast and a business is so toxic and poisonous and horrible.
It can be.
Yeah.
Like online, across vast distances, like it's just a business and every part of it sucks
and I hate it every day.
I want to kill myself.
So like with you guys in particular, seeing you in person is vital and I totally agree.
I totally agree.
And that's why it reminds me of the actual friendship in the way that this doesn't.
Yeah, for sure.
For sure.
Hell yeah.
We're like, like there was one night when we got back from Slimehouse, me, Kazzie,
hippo, me and Ben saying, that's the ticket.
Oh, what, Mr. Pepperjack hot dog.
Yeah.
The whole time.
We ate hot dogs with Pepperjack.
We got back.
And, and, and McDoubles without the buns.
We got back from Slimehouse and it was really late and we were going to go to bed, but
we just stayed up talking about the con, just talking, just cracking jokes and talking about
Lion King one and a half in Tumba.
And it was sweet.
We were talking about Tumba.
Yeah.
In Tumba.
Hey, Tumba.
You know, that's why I went to a fucking pillow fight, I think as well.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, yeah.
We had a pillow fight.
Yeah, we had a pillow fight.
And these guys were doing that every night.
I was out wandering the streets of Baltimore fucking homeless as shit every single night
of the convention.
God, Baltimore is so fucking scary.
I got offered drugs like eight times.
It's pretty, pretty spooky.
It's pretty spooky.
I said at one point, as there was a literal trash tornado blowing through the street.
We experienced that.
Yeah.
This fucking city makes Detroit look like the emerald city of Oz.
Got my pink hair complimented a couple of times though, so that's pretty good.
Fair.
Fuck yeah, worth it.
Oh, there's this.
There's this image.
You can see my fucking, you can see my trance and belt too.
That's true.
You can see my gut hanging out.
Oh, yeah.
We recreated the thing with new friends and old.
What a wholesome experience.
And then we dumped him into the bay immediately afterwards.
Fucking Limies.
As pointed out by another Twitter user, Queen, please look at Ben and analyze the way that
he's holding that pillow.
I'm far on the edge.
Look at his hand.
Where am I supposed to get left?
Ben, is that a literal hover hand when we're trying to be holding up a man in the air?
My other hand?
What am I supposed to be like grabbing his wrist?
Possibly?
Yes.
I don't know.
My other hand is on his shoulder.
My right hand is just like, what's the point of pushing on his arm?
He's trying to give a thumbs up.
I don't want to fuck around with that.
You don't come between a man and his thumbs up.
Let me see.
What else have we got here?
Speaking of hover hands, let's talk about a real cool guy who would never stoop so
low as to use the hover hands.
Check out this sweet picture of me and Lauren Foust.
Yes.
Wait, where?
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Incredible.
My hand right around her waist like she's my fucking prom date.
I don't give a fuck.
I do not hover hand ever and I never will.
You can't make me.
It's a mistake.
Yeah.
It's great.
What a beautiful image.
Lauren, she's looking great.
She's keeping it tight.
Nothing but salutes for her.
You know what I'm saying?
Hell yeah.
What's she up to now?
At moments after which, she was like, hey, dude, who is that guy with you?
Dude, APS Adventures?
Dude, would you know where I can get the document?
What's that?
Oh, by the way, by the way, just in reference to our previous friendship time discussion,
I think this is the image for me that sums it all up, the bed snubbing time.
Oh yes.
Yeah, that's Ben Pepperjack in hand.
Ben, shoes on foot one day.
Now, I don't know if everybody saw, but the socket continues.
Let me fucking repost this here.
Fucking, you know, briefly, in the continued sorties of Shoe Gate, I was briefly able to
reclaim them, and I feel that the moral victory is eternally mine, but one day, you know.
That's correct.
I was going to say that, you know, like in this foot image.
This foot image was great because it gave birth to the two dualities of man, you know,
the Nate souls and the Munchie steppers, which will be in internal conflict to the heat
of the universe.
Very true.
Yeah, I kind of regret keeping my socks on, honestly.
That's the right thing to do.
I feel left out in the foot fetish community.
It's the Christian thing to do.
Oh, you know what?
While we're just saying nice things in general, I believe Ben Craigman, it was Hargadine.
Hargadine gave me this wonderful United Federation of Planets.
That's right.
Incredible.
And I wasn't supposed to tell you that it was her, but I did.
In defiance of your plan.
This is like my favorite.
As a liar and a cheat.
This thing is so sick.
I love it so much.
It was such a nice thing.
It's pretty cool.
Thank you so much.
It's absolutely beautiful.
Thank you.
Oh, can we talk just a little bit about the TF2 analysis anarchy panel and the chanting
and the adoration.
This huge crowd of people have for the worst thing I've ever seen.
We went to the table in the vendor's hall.
Okay, I don't know why this exists, but they had a fucking table dedicated to selling analysis anarchy merch.
Where's my tune critic?
It's in June, guys.
Damn it.
It was my tune critic.
Phantom Horn was not represented.
He has been erased from history.
He has, as is tune critic, tragically.
Tragically.
Related to that, I just want to say that they gave analysis anarchy, like a huge panel.
Everyone showed up to it.
They had their whole booths.
Bum, fuck, nobody has had panels.
We tried to apply for a panel and they wouldn't even respond to us.
They didn't say, no, sorry, you could do it.
They wouldn't even say that they did nothing.
The fucking guys were hosting the how to be a furry panel who literally had no idea what they were doing and said so immediately.
They got a panel somehow.
The fucking brony drama panel, which was just a bunch of complete nobodies reenacting a discord call where everyone had a shit mic and they didn't know how to speak.
It was about that level of quality.
Well, real quick, I missed the...
Oh my god, I totally lost my train of thought.
What were we just talking about before that thing?
Do you have to analysis anarchy in a panel?
I was going to ask, for the era, this is the last time we'll discuss it.
I feel like we just fucked up.
The thing was, I didn't sign on to confirm I was going to BronyCon until like two, maybe three months ago and you had already tried to get a panel.
Did you never came? Tom intended to. I don't think he was involved.
How did that go and who was involved with it?
There's two things.
Because, frankly, Munchie, you were never particularly well-known.
If it was just me, Munchie, who wants a panel.
No, no, no.
It wasn't like, hey, it's me, Munchie Shatsky, can I have a panel?
It was me on the Procrastinator channel explaining who the horseshoe crew was and that we were the horseshoe crew and saying, can the horseshoe crew get a panel?
That was my explicit words.
And I mentioned everyone who would maybe come.
That didn't get a panel, but the Brony drama got a panel.
What the fuck was that?
It was embarrassing.
It was not only the horseshoe crew. I also applied separately for a pony cast panel before that.
There's no reason the pony cast shouldn't have gotten in.
Yeah, it's a pony show that was kind of up to date and they did get back to me.
They just said, sorry, we're fully booked.
Wasn't it just too late?
No, I did it as soon as it was open for submitting panels.
Well, that is very surprising.
They must have just made an editorial decision that they wanted pony...
Maybe they just really wanted like the most active people, even if they're like terrible discord called drama horse.
I don't know.
I was looking for FNGR's panel the whole time and I couldn't find a man.
I wanted to get up to date on the drama.
Well, dude, okay.
Well, speaking of FNGR, we're going to repeat this entire story on the RCK.
But I want to say it here because it is legendary.
It is fucking incredible.
The saga of us trying to find the same.
Yes, we need to hear it.
So I want to say, in case you aren't aware, and you should be aware, because if you aren't then you're a fake fan.
Me and Ben, on Ryfurgers Cop Killers, on our famous Frog Fractions episode, called out Mini a Pony YouTuber.
And in response, Miss Anthropony, a person who I don't even think we mentioned by name.
I think we just mentioned like his friends and he got upset and he made a vlog about us.
In fact, he's probably listening to this right now.
And he made a very funny video that me and Bo thought was very funny in response to us.
And we thought, haha, wow, silly.
And in this video, he states that he will kick Ben in the dick at Ryfurg.
That was a threat made against Ben.
And since then, we had already cooled off and mellowed down and we had already talked to him and everything was fine.
But still, that idea of kicking Ben in the dick at Ryfurg was such a persistent idea in the back of our minds that we knew we had to meet him and get this to be real in any capacity.
And so we were trying to hunt Dan Mapp, and the first time that we saw him, we were right up next to him.
Me, Nate, and a whole bunch of people, like Jesse was there, Hippo, Kaz, I think everyone was there besides Ben.
We're in a big group full of like 40 fucking people all just walking down the street in the middle of like Baltimore.
And we saw him walking up to us. We said, hey, Mapp, he walks past us like he was walking up to us. He's past us now.
Miss Anthropony, Miss Anthropony keeps walking, goes across the street.
Miss Anthropony, it's us, it's the PCP, it's Hippo, it's Jesse.
Like, turns around, gives us a limp thumbs up, walks away.
A limp thumbs up with his infinity gauntlet. Yeah, on the whole convention.
Incredible.
We tried to talk to him and he wouldn't pay attention to us. So now we think, okay, something's fucking up. There's something going on right now.
He is probably terrified of us. He probably thinks-
There's a literal gang with Munchie, a literal gang of rowdies and killers right there.
Yeah, with these rowdies and killers behind us, all these people wearing gang colors just wade to fucking pop.
They're just waiting for the go ahead to tear him limb from limb from you, Munchie.
Yeah, can't blame him.
And so, we tried to find what we couldn't find. And then last day, we did it-
I guess there was nothing fucking to do at Bornecombe. There's not a goddamn panel we want to see. There was nothing.
So we want to see him more than anything else.
So we dedicate the entire other day to us trying to find him.
If Frim and Ethan stake out the entire Vanillers Hall, we check his Twitter update and we look at his last tweet to find out where he is.
Okay, it was Miss Lauren Frost. Okay, we saw him go in here.
Okay, all right, block this interest, block this interest, but we'll be able to get him.
We're gonna do a fanning, sweeping motion trying to get him out of the Vanillers Hall and trying to get a picture of him. Can't do it.
And so, we're, like, dejected, trying to find Miss Anthorhomne, but he's, like, a skittish gazelle trying to escape our lion's claws at every moment.
Like, he knows that, like, the hunt is afoot and he will not let us stomp down on his chest.
And so, we're dejected, walking around, going to panels.
And then we meet a Mr. British Ninja.
And Mr. British Ninja is the person who replaced Hippo on TF2 Nessus Anarchy as the Red Spot.
And so, we start talking to him.
And we're just, like, like, you know, hey, how's it going? What's going on? You know, what's up, bro?
And then we mention that we're trying to get Miss Anthorhomne. He's, like, oh, you want Miss Anthorhomne?
Why don't I just call him?
And then we have a guy on the inside. We have a guy on, like, in the TF2 Nessus Anarchy.
We have him in the analysis pony YouTuber sphere.
We're gonna be able to get to a contact in Lure and literally trap and deceive Miss Anthorhomne into allowing us to take a picture with him.
Quick aside on that. He showed us his Skype chats with Miss Anthorhomne,
which was just a long string of Miss Anthorhomne saying, hi, hi, hi, hi, hey, hello, hey, are you there?
Hi, which was really funny.
Sick.
I didn't see that part.
And then, by the way, British Ninja was like, yeah, he seemed good.
Yeah. And so, we get him to call, and so there's a meeting arranged after closing the ceremonies.
This is like the very, very, very tail end of the con.
It literally just ended. Brony Cotton was ending right at that moment.
This is immediately the aftermath of the closing ceremonies when everyone was pouring out the doors.
And we all knew there was no other, he had to be in there. There was no option. He was there.
And so we get a meeting. At first, we're gonna try and, like, literally, we've set up, like, like, centuries to spot him.
Yeah. But eventually, we're like, no, no, no, let's stream on this.
Let's just wait outside, you know, British Ninja will tell us when he's coming.
And so we wait outside the doors. Brony Cotton literally ends, like, the bell rings, and the students shuffle out of school.
And then, like, one of the first guys, Miss Anthropon, with his Thanos glove, and then we all, like, surround him in a circle.
Yes, yes.
Every, every appearance he made. Yeah.
Yeah, okay. That thought.
That really added a lot of texture to the whole experience.
It sure did.
So we surround him, and, like, Miss Anthropon gets, like, scared for a moment, and starts to, like, wobble at our feet.
Like, I'm so sorry for what I said to you, but I'm so sorry.
He did seem genuinely afraid when we appeared before him.
I mean, we all surrounded him and just went, nightmare, nightmare, nightmare, nightmare.
So that was an odd choice, but...
And then Ben, like, the benevolent deity he is, says, rise, peon, and then smile upon him, gently.
And then he rise with tears in his eyes. I think I remember that.
He paddled back and said, you're among friends to me.
I'm impressed.
And then the rollercoaster of emotion with Miss Anthropon, it was, like, went from, like, pure, like, terror,
like, I can only assume at, like, the literal death he thought he was about to experience.
Like, most likely.
Actual terror from a little, like, like the daggers of the Furies that were about to go inside of him,
went from just joy to seeing us, and we got so many pictures with him, and it was great,
and we recreated, you know, the kicking each other into the dick.
Look, I told him, I told him, like, hey man, you know, there's one, like,
I've been looking forward to this moment, and I just, the thing that I want more than anything is,
can we please get a picture of each other kicking one another in the dick?
And he was super happy with it.
He went like, yes, and it was, yeah, there was a literal crowd cheering for this moment.
The crowd literally went wild.
We cannot express how hyped it was.
It was a crowd of, it was a crowd of all of us, you know, all of our people,
but because Bronnico was ending, everyone was coming out.
There was just, like, loads of people around who were also cheering,
because, like, it's the thing that's happening.
Yeah, this was the emotional climax of BronyCon, bar none.
And we can't describe how joyful it is that we finally found Miss Anthropon,
that we're doing this iconic moment, that he's happy, that everyone's happy,
all of our friends and allies there, you know, all the people that we met,
all of our fans and friends, and all the people, the new people we met there,
like, like, past analysis was there.
I just said, it was all coming to a close, this was the end of BronyCon.
And then, something that I cannot believe happened.
We need to do some backstory here.
At every BronyCon, there has been one figure that's pre-leaded all of the conversation
between the upper and lower societies of BronyCon.
This person has single-handedly funded and, you know, armed the BronyCon masses.
I'm talking about, of course, about,
Ice Cold Water, one dollar guy.
Ice Cold Water, one dollar.
So there was a dude, shirtless, selling water at every single BronyCon.
He became a national icon, a treasure, if you will.
He went beyond the legend.
He's an urban superhero, a static shocker, Luke Cage.
Indeed, indeed.
Literally.
And so this guy, who's an icon of BronyCon,
that completely embolifies all that BronyCon stands for, all of its ideals and virtues.
He, just out of the blue, comes up to us.
He just, like, runs right into the center of the big, like, circle of people
that are, like, cheering and, like, clapping and stuff, and just, like, hooting and hollering.
We have a picture that someone was down to picture, right?
I don't know.
And so this spirit of BronyCon past, present, and future, gulp, comes into us.
And we get a picture of Miss Anthropony with the Ice Cold Water $1 guy.
And it is just the encapsulation of all of that period of culture and history.
This, like, closing chapter, all of, like, all that Miss Anthropony represents,
like, all the analysis of Milo Pony YouTubers, all of the cesspool and stuff like that,
but just that sort of, like, simple naivete and, like, simple, just, like, joy
that they experience for the show just rubs off on you.
The Ice Cold Water $1, the institution of Baltimore, Maryland, you know,
the hustling and the streets and the grime and that sort of, like, cess.
Just all accumulates into one giant glob of just, I can't even describe it.
It was so serene.
It was just completely disgraceful.
Transcendent.
This was, could not be written.
Yeah, it's could not be written.
Life is stranger than fiction.
It was incredible.
It was literally amazing.
It was definitely the high note.
It was a magical thing.
Where's the picture of that shit?
It was the site of...
Ice Cold Water Guy.
Brody Count was a weekend of...
And then Miss Anthropony immediately called his mom and told her about it.
I wouldn't blame him.
It was a weekend of great moments.
And he wanted to know who had, like, pictures,
if anyone had been filming when he had initially come out,
because he wanted to, like, show his mom the video.
Aw.
I know some people were.
At least parts.
Let me tell you my greatest defeat in life.
The site of my greatest failure.
It was when it was at that end part when Ice Cold Water Guy was there.
First, like, Miss Anthropony came up to me and started, like...
Oh.
He started apologizing to me like,
hey, for everything I've ever said to you.
I deeply apologize.
I'm like, what the fuck did you ever say to me?
I don't fucking even know who you are, man.
So, like...
So, and then Miss Anthropony starts talking to me about Kingdom Hearts and stuff.
And I'm like, okay, I was talking to this guy about Kingdom Hearts.
But while that happens, you know, Ice Cold Water Man stuff is happening.
He's coming and he's taking pictures with everyone and stuff.
And he goes to take a picture with Kazzy.
And he's like, who is a phone?
Who is a camera?
So I take out my phone to take a picture.
And I take a picture of Ice Cold Water Man and Kazzy.
And my phone is on, like, 1%.
It's about to die.
And he goes, hey, hey, man.
Let me put my number in your phone so that you can send me that picture.
So I'm like, I'm freaking out like, oh my god.
This is my chance to have a real life superhero in my contacts for life.
I'm literally going to be friends with Ice Cold Water Man.
And he had just got done telling Ben all about how, like, if someone messes with his friends,
he'll kill that person.
I asked him.
I said, I was like, excuse me, sir, Mr. Ice Cold Water Man.
I have to ask because I know I'm a big fan of your work.
And I just need to know would you consider yourself a rowdy or a killer?
And then he goes on this long...
And he goes like a weird, like, tire rage.
Long tangent about how, like, you know, he's like, you know, a peaceful person,
but he'll defend someone if he has to, you know?
And I'm like, OK, OK.
But would you say rowdy or killer?
And then he just does it again, basically.
That's a tough choice.
You know what I realized?
I should have been like, OK, OK, that's fine.
Do you like pink or purple better?
That's just sort of how I finished it.
But I forgot.
He didn't give an answer, so whatever.
I mean, he definitely thought you were asking, have you murdered anyone?
He's the killer thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know.
I look obviously, obviously.
I just was hoping.
I just wanted him to say something.
I just wanted an answer.
But I will never know.
He's friend to Juvie, killer, even the lowly stay deads.
He's a filth.
You're saying he's a filthy sentress is what you're saying.
Perhaps.
Perhaps so.
So, so Jesse.
I'm safe forever because this is protection.
This is my chance to have my own personal superhero in my context forever.
But my phone is on like 1% battery life.
It's about to die.
The Santa Pony is like right here in my ear talking about Kingdom Hearts.
And I'm like, I'm trying to find my contacts on my phone, which I've never fucking used
ever.
Fucking so like I can't even find the phone.
Then I can't find the contacts.
I can't find like where to make a new contact.
And I'm freaking out because my phone's dying.
The Santa Pony is going off about Kingdom Hearts.
And I'm like, where is it?
Where is it?
I can't find it.
And then my phone dies.
And I miss my chance.
And then fucking Ice Cold Water Man chews me out.
Like it's my fault.
Like I'm incompetent or something like, oh man, you don't even know how to even find
it.
And then I'm like, listen here, Ice Cold Water Man.
You son of a bitch.
You know, and it just figures.
You know, all weekend everyone's coming up to me and shaking my hand and taking pictures.
Everyone gets to meet their fucking hero, their idol, Endless Jazz.
But when it comes time for me to meet my hero, you know, everything has to go wrong.
I got no phone battery.
It's fucking dying.
I can't find my contacts.
The Santa Pony's talking off, fucking tangled.
Shit!
I'm just freaking out.
I'm having a panic attack.
I totally empathize.
Because before that, we had met up with Sarancia and talked about me being on Christeries and
stuff.
And like she had been like, you know, here I'll send you a text like, like add me to
your phone.
And I also realized that I have no idea how to use the contacts menu in my phone.
And I'm trying to fucking figure out how to add her.
And I'm, well, at least, at least I struggled with that.
Like in privacy.
Like she wasn't around to see me be like, oh, wait, wait a second.
Wait a second.
Where's the button?
It was like out of the open.
There was like spotlights on me, like under the heat of the sun.
There was a huge crowd.
Everyone looking.
Everyone disappointed in me.
I schooled Water Man cutting a fucking promo on how incompetent I am.
Such shame.
Like separately, Ben says to you, dude, you choked.
And then later, if I was there, I say, dude, you choked.
Like separately, independently of one another.
Well, you know, meeting heroes and villains alike, you know.
As we said before, I did meet Chris Chan.
We all met Chris Chan.
That was great.
Really, really nice.
Really nice in person.
Happy to take photos.
Interestingly, you know, Chris became such kind of just a staple.
There were many times where Chris was just sitting, you know, alone in a chair.
Just, you know, absorbing the atmosphere.
Chris was just around.
Just like.
Yeah.
We chatted behind her in like a bunch of panels.
Like right.
But it's like just rubbing elbows with Christine Weston Chandler in the flesh.
No doubt.
I never, I never came across her.
Really?
That's crazy.
I would have given her one of my leaflets.
That's too bad.
Five or six times, yeah.
I bet Chris would have been into your shit.
Maybe.
Don't say that.
Oh, but you know what, while I'm just posting these, also got a picture with the only Pegasister,
one Jenny Nicholson, who I quite like.
I'm a fan of.
Yeah.
I think she sucks.
Nah, she's garbage.
I found her as well.
Let me tell you this.
Let me tell you my Jenny story.
We're walking to the, we're walking to the brownie.
Who Ben and I have worked with on brief bits before and pony stuff.
She was, she did lend her voice to TBAP a couple of times.
On occasion.
Yep.
I was walking to, yes.
I was walking to, we were walking to the brownie drama panel and it was in like the other
building.
We had to go across the skybridge and she, she was like, it was like with two other people.
She just walks out from a hallway and I'm like, oh, it's Jenny Nicholson.
I don't really want to talk to Jenny Nicholson, but, but I do, I am confused and I am unsure
whether this is the way to the skybridge where you ask her like, hey, is that the skybridge
over there?
And she's like, yeah, we go through there to get to the Hilton.
Oh man.
And I keep walking and then fucking Nate is like, wait a minute, that was Jenny Nicholson
and like run back.
I run back.
And I got this picture.
I got this picture with her right after that.
I got to talk to Jenny Nicholson.
Ben is so much cooler than me though.
He doesn't give a shit.
That's so dope.
Jenny Nicholson is guilty of the worst crime that a person can be guilty of and that is
being more famous than they deserve.
I can't think of anything that deserves a more scorn and derision.
Fair enough.
I don't know.
I think she deserves it.
She's, she's done some good.
That's the fucking dumbest thing ever.
No, I said to her.
She made, she's like Friendship is Witchcraft.
She made, she made Friendship is Witchcraft and then she spent the next seven years sitting
on a bed.
Hey, look, look.
I like that.
That's funny.
That gypsy bard song from Friendship is Witchcraft is the instrumental basis for one of my classic
songs, Crystal Ball.
Yeah.
You know who wrote, you know, you know who wrote that?
Griffin Miller wrote that.
That is true.
Oh, shit.
I don't give a fuck.
But I also had an encounter with Jenny Nicholson after you guys had left because every, every
time you guys left to go back to your like nice comfy, like affluent white people hotel
room, I had to hang around the convention center all night like a, like Oliver and company
in his cardboard box in the rain.
Let me listen.
It's hard being, it's hard being an affluent white person.
That bed was so soft.
It had such terrible lumbar support that no, this is act gen, genuinely genuine.
I wasn't paying the entire convention because the bed was too soft and it made my back hurt
and I can't fucking handle like it's awful.
It's awful.
It would honestly like kind of ruin like the first two days for me.
Yes.
It sucked that bad.
And this, and this was when I had my fucking depressive episodes like sit on the floor
with my head in my hands.
Like, oh God.
That's not fun.
Having your pillow fights.
That was late.
Sleeping on the rocks and the streets next door.
This picture that this picture give just posted of like Munchie, Ben and Kazi and glowing with
pink light.
They must be at the routing rough house right now.
Wait, wait, where?
Hold on.
Look at it.
It's in the chat thing right there.
This is the New York layover.
Oh, that's, yeah, that's the, oh yeah, yeah, when we were on the, man, I look so grumpy.
When we were on the ride home, we still, we had like a three hour layover in New York
and then we just fucking walked around Times Square.
Oh, that's New York.
Yeah, that's cool.
That's cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was New York, New York at like 3.30 in the morning when like everything was closed
except for in McDonald's.
Okay, that's great.
But Jesse was in the middle of the southern.
Yeah.
So what were you saying?
Sure.
We had pizza.
We went to the rate.
You and Jenny had pizza?
Yeah.
Wait, that's KP.
Why did you and Jenny, why did you and Jenny have pizza?
Are you sure you don't mean KP?
Cause that's KP.
I was with both of them that night.
Oh, okay.
So that's cool.
Cause like the first night or one of the first days, I don't even know.
It's like such a blur.
It was like a 10 months we were there or something.
Like the first night you guys all went off to your hotel room and I'm like, I'm going
to fucking wander around here for a little bit.
So like as soon as you guys left, I ran into KP and we hung out and then the next day.
Oh, but behold, Jesse's KP TF2 sticker from analysis anarchy hanging off his land.
Incredible.
Well, I had to buy it because like, like to me having KP merchandise is the funniest
thing in the world.
It's fascinating.
It's so like skewed towards young people, like little kids.
Like I've never made it through a KP video ever.
And you know, like I like for the longest time, I didn't get it.
Like one of the first Brony cons is when I actually hung out with her for the first
time and I saw like all of her fans come up and all the fans coming up to her were
like actual little girls.
So like, okay.
They are not an impressive bunch.
Yeah.
So I'm like, okay, I get it.
I get what you're.
So like it's, her kind of it is just so like for kids that I find it hilarious.
To proclaim myself an undying fan of KP and to to buy her merchandise and have her sign
it and stuff.
It's hilarious and cool.
So yes, I did buy a cool KP sticker, which then I heard from her is not even like an
official KP product.
She didn't get any money for it.
It was all the TF2 guys.
So I got ripped off.
Thank God.
Yeah.
Which I think I went to charity.
I heard.
So that's nice.
If that's true.
Fuck.
Now I have to be okay with it.
But then, but then I ran into her again the next night when she was coming out of her
panel and she came up to me and she's like, Hey, it's you.
It's my favorite fucking guy.
What's up?
Let's go to the fucking rave and and fucking I'm like rave.
That sounds horrible, but okay.
Yeah.
So I went down and we met up with Daniel Nicholson and we were eating pizza and shit.
And he went to the rave and it was it was a fucking rave.
That's for sure.
And it was fucking incidentally Jesse played our dad and Jenny played our mom.
So dad and mom were united at last.
That is true.
I'm not completely certain that she knows who I am.
Like I've hung out with her before.
I've talked to her.
She's never addressed me by name.
I don't know if she knows Jenny or KP.
Jenny Nicholson.
Jenny.
They meet a lot of people.
I don't know.
No, KP definitely knows who I am.
Yeah.
But we should get we should get we should get Griffin Nilla on the PCP.
Is he isn't he like really popular?
You know, I've heard conflicting reports about this, but I've heard that Jenny was really
horrible to him.
I mean, I'd be interested.
And I want and I want that to be true to validate my preconceptions.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
The atmosphere coming out of the rave.
I think you guys should have been there because it was really something else.
It was like the real climax of the convention because people were coming out of that rave.
It was like three in the morning and everyone was just losing their minds in like the front
hall.
Like security was like trying to like, okay, it's time for everyone to leave for the night.
Get the fuck out of here.
And like nobody was listening.
Everyone was just like thrashing in the front lobby, like singing pony songs.
And I like I had a moment where I like I found the the perch by the fountain and I like sat
up and I perched there and I sat like Indian style, like in the horseshoe finale video
and I watched my fucking people come out in droves from the rave hall and just like filter
through the lobby and like singing and like this joy celebration.
I just had this moment where I'm like, yeah, this is pretty fucking cool.
You just like this moment of like, no one's ever going to get this like you had to be here.
It's like actually kind of a cool special fandom, even though it's weird and awful, but it's
actually it's like, yeah, and I was like, I was just watching over my people like a like
a like a lonely God and it was fucking cool.
That's interesting.
And then I went out and I and I walked like a mile to the hotel where the people said that
they had a room for me and they lied and I couldn't get in and they were all asleep.
And so then I fucking was homeless all night and I was fucking wandering around Baltimore
for like miles and miles, real folk blues on multiple evenings.
I had the real Baltimore experience because I came to the city the same way I come into
every city, which is not planning for anything.
I refused to plan for anything.
I refused to book a hotel in advance.
It's life is more interesting that way.
So probably so every single night after everyone was gone and it was time to like sleep for
the night, I had to like find a hotel myself walking around the city.
There were no hotels open anywhere near the city.
I had to like the first night I had to walk like two miles into the depths of the city
into like the real ghetto, like horrifying scary place to find like this crap ass hotel
that was way overpriced.
Yeah.
And I did that a couple nights.
But on the night after the rave, even that hotel was also booked and I couldn't find anywhere
and I was wandering on the city for hours and it was like, it was like four in the morning
and I just gave up.
I was like around the convention center.
I'm just like, whatever, the sun's going to come up in a couple hours.
I'll just like lay down here on the concrete by the convention center and fucking sleep.
You're not alone.
You're not alone doing that.
I'm not alone.
There was a person sleeping on every street corner in Baltimore, mostly like, you know,
actual homeless people.
Well, I am actually.
Yeah.
I was, but it's never mind.
Never mind.
I'm just one of them, I guess.
It really is the truth.
So I'm just laying there on the con.
I'm like, I'm looking at my phone like this.
Is there anyone who might have a place for me to stay?
And I see that Ben's online and I look at it and I think to myself, I would rather die
than ask Ben for help.
So I put my phone down.
Good thinking.
Right choice.
So I get comfortable there on the concrete.
And then one hero, one, one noble superhero from my Patreon discord, which everyone can
get in for $5 on my Patreon.
There's my plug.
And so this fucking hero from my Patreon discord came by the name of Tabby Nickel.
And he's like, I have a room because there was like a group of people from my discord
who had gotten a hotel room.
But the guy who paid for it, Bryce, could not make it to the convention.
He had plain trouble and he was really bummed out about it and it sucks.
But there was a vacancy in the room and Tabby Nickel's like, hey, I got this fucking room
so I went in and I went and I slept next to a man for like one hour and he saved my life.
Well, that's nice.
Yeah.
We did it.
I would have liked to have gone to that raid, but rave.
Yeah, me too.
That's something I've never done before.
We had an Airbnb that was like 20, 25 minutes away from the place.
Like I was, you guys were saying before, just like at Radcon 3, a lot of the most amazing
times, and even when we were at like Anime Expo with me, Digi and Munchy, a lot of the
best times were just like at night when everyone's just chilling and relaxing.
So like if we could have been there, probably would have been pretty dope, but like it was
already full and we wanted our own space anyway.
Yeah, it was definitely a raid.
I'm not like a dancer.
I'm not a, I'm not a reveler.
I'm more of like a, I'm more of like an arms cross standing.
They're just observing the other freaks and mutants having fun.
That's my fun.
My fun is observing.
So like I will not dance at a rave.
You cannot make me.
If you try to make me, I'll kill you.
But at the end of it, when the guy came out and he played the discord song, even though
it wasn't the discord song, it was like a 2019 remix, which wasn't as good, but nobody
seemed to mind.
So he came out and he played the song.
Everyone's going crazy.
And KP, who for the most part was also an observer.
She hands me like her discord plushie and she's like, here, here's the discord plushie.
Wave it around and dance.
And I'm like, you fucking goddamn bitch.
So I have this.
So now I have this plushie and I have to like wave it over my head.
Like I'm part of this and I'm not.
I'm an observer.
I'm mad about it.
Yeah, you're better.
So I have to figure out like some kind of movement for my fucking body to perform.
So I came up.
I invented this insane autistic.
I guess you would call it a dance.
But if anyone, if it was caught on film, I would delete all of my channels and disappear.
It was like.
It was like part robot and also part teahawk from Street Fighter two.
You know how he has his elbows out and he's walking towards you.
Like ready to do like a flying eagle dive.
It was it was a teahawk robot and also like with discord plush.
And I just like, I'm like, okay, I have to keep doing this until the fucking song's over.
Jesus.
And it was, I mean, it was cool.
I guess it's the point.
And then the song was over and I got the fuck out of there.
You know, there's one other person I wanted to mention who was it?
Brad Khan.
I mean fucking Brony Khan that I did not meet, but I would have liked to if I'd known.
And that was ContraPoints.
ContraPoints actually showed up to Brony Khan.
Yeah, she showed up.
She showed up for like one day.
Yeah.
And was around.
If I'd seen her, I would have liked to say hello.
I saw a picture of her and Jenny.
And beyond that, beyond that.
I heard about it later.
Oh wait, you met her?
You saw her?
No, no, I just said I heard about it later and I saw a picture of her and Jenny.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, ContraPoints said on Twitter, what was this?
This was like a week ago or something.
Said, wow, Twitter shamed me hard for going to Brony Khan.
The stigma is real.
And thanks.
Thanks for being on our side, ContraPoints.
Thanks for being an ally, ContraPoints.
Finally, an ally I care about.
Well, that's it.
All right, guys.
Check out this week before we wrap up.
Sure.
This is from the day after the convention.
I was still in Baltimore for a day, so I was wandering around and I decided to go visit
the grave of Edgar Allen Poe.
Oh, shit.
And take a sip for my homie.
So fucking way.
They're in my KP shirt.
Sit in some fucking vodka.
It was fucking dope.
Wow.
This is exactly what he intended for society to become.
Yeah.
This is what he died for.
Sick.
That's incredible.
This is post-modern all right.
Dude, I hope there's like, you know how there's like the Beatle Burners which is like
a really tech Beatle song to make them like my little pony.
There should be like an edit of like the Raven, but it's just about the bat pony.
Oh, or changelings.
Edgar Allen Pie.
Yeah.
What's that?
Edgar Allen Pie.
Oh, it's cutie fucking Pinkie Pie, but it's Edgar Allen Poe.
That's good.
Well, hey, I don't know if you guys want to talk more about Bronicon.
I've got one.
Yeah.
I don't have anything about Bronicon.
I do want to mention my travel home because it was a slightly unusual.
So me, Munchie, Kezi and Ben, because my round trip flight that I had booked going there,
the flight back was like at 6am on the fourth day and I didn't want that.
So I just skipped that flight and instead I had a flight booked for the end of the fourth
day or something.
Or maybe the fifth.
In Boston.
So I went back to Boston.
We had a layover in New York.
That was cool.
New York stinks.
Lol.
I hate it.
No, it was sick.
It just kind of sucked because it was 3.30 in the morning.
No, I mean like literally it stinks.
Oh, no, that's true.
That's absolutely true.
Yeah.
Okay.
Point taken.
But anyway, I missed check-in at my flight when we went there.
I didn't realize for a-
Because we had hot pot.
Yeah, the hot pot was lovely.
I really want to have that again.
But yeah, I didn't realize for check-in for international flights, you have to be there
an hour early.
And I would have like checked in earlier on my phone, but it wasn't working.
So I was just thinking, I'll check in at the airport.
And it didn't work.
And I got, you know, rebooked on a different flight and it took a really long time.
It was really stressful and I didn't like it.
We thought you were going to have to end up staying until the next day or something.
I thought so as well.
It seemed dire.
Yeah.
They gave me a flight and it was in three hours after the thought, when I was supposed
to leave.
So I was fine.
You know, I can wait in the airport for three hours.
I had some friendlies ice cream.
It was okay.
It was just alright.
You got them for big chocolate.
Dude, did you get the green goblin?
Or did you get the fucking clown head?
I didn't know what to get.
I just got some chocolate ice cream.
I don't know.
Alright, alright.
It's basically a friendlies experience.
Nah.
It's not very friendly.
It's not very friendly of me.
Love you James.
I was waiting in the, I got to my gate on the TV.
There's a TV there and it's showing like the number of people who haven't like properly
checked in.
And because they rebooked my flight, I had like a special boarding pass.
But it wasn't like a, like I wasn't technically on the flight.
Like it said a seat like request on the piece of paper.
So I went up to the lady and say, what does this mean?
And she says, oh, you're not on the flight yet.
Once everyone's boarded, then we'll see if there's space.
I'm like, oh, you know, this is going to be like a really stressful wait.
And then I'm going to be told, fuck you.
And I'm going to have to call Munchie and like mess up his plans, his and Kazi's plans
for like flying the next day or whatever.
Or I guess I could have stayed with Ben, but I don't know.
Anyway, I was there.
I was there like just watching the long line of people enter the plane.
There was like three people left.
My name was still on this TV as like on standby and the number of names that hadn't been
checked in, they were like passenger names.
They were being like checked off as the people walked in and they had the number of seats
on the plane.
I am.
I'm Gibbentake.
MLP famous.
Give me a seat.
God damn it.
Lauren Faust loves me.
I have a video with like a hundred thousand views.
Not bad.
About fapping to horses.
I don't know if it was that one.
Anyway, they had the number of seats on the plane.
They had 168 and it was filling up and it got to 166 and I was like, what do I do?
I don't know.
I'm just sort of like pathetically standing there like being sad and a cold sweat.
Yeah.
And the lady, she was not impressed by the fact that I had like a seat request.
I think she was just like, fuck this guy, mischeck in or whatever.
But finally she says, you can go in.
I go in and I have seat 6A, which is a very like low number.
Seems good.
I walk into the plane and I'm in like the beginning of the plane.
I'm in the part where it's like the first class business class seats where you have
lots of leg room with a fancy chair and a TV and I sit down at 6A and I'm like, whoa.
I'm like, whoa.
And I'm in business class.
It was really strange.
Something I'd never experienced before.
I got to see all the things.
I was frantically doing like an awful Casey Neistat review of everything.
I barely filmed anything.
I was just too excited.
So was the experience, does anyone know how much more business class is?
My question is, is it worth it?
Should I just buy them from now on?
Well, all right.
For me, I mean, it was just comfortable.
It's just like everything that sucks about being on a plane, i.e. you can't go to sleep
and you can't lie down.
That's solved.
So instantly it's great.
Also the service is a lot better.
They don't look at you funny if you don't know what to say like they do in the regular plane.
They're very calm and nice and they give you complimentary orange juice for takeoff.
I'm like, what if this spills?
What am I supposed to do?
I've got to chug it.
Yeah, like champagne or orange juice?
Like orange juice, I guess.
What's that thing, orange juice and champagne in the morning?
Mamosa.
Mamosa, that's the one.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I had like a steak dinner before that had like a soup.
What?
I saw that.
I'm retarded now.
Why did you make me stupid?
What is wrong with you?
I do not know.
And there's like a button on the chair thing.
There's like an Egyptian hieroglyph with buttons on it.
And with arrows.
And there's the stripper button.
I didn't know what it did and I pressed it and I was just covered in beautiful naked women.
It was really like a blow job.
Oh, did you even really see that one?
Oh, the shit.
I missed that button.
Were you on the Jeffrey Epstein flight, dude?
Oh, I hope so.
Yes.
Fuck yeah.
That flight has a sharp down return.
Were you Indonesian's flight of 337 and you got lost in the middle of the Pacific Ocean?
Just like Jeffrey Epstein is right now.
It was a body double.
He's a billionaire.
You can afford that.
Anyway, I had a fun meal.
I watched Nancy Drew again because I just felt like it.
You watched her again?
Because I like that movie.
And then I started to watch another one like about this teen singer.
But then I was like, you know what?
I'm tired.
Let's get my face mask and my ear plugs from this complimentary toiletries suit.
A little case.
I pressed the button to go into sleep mode on my chair and it turned into a bed.
And I had a duvet and a pillow and I just went to sleep.
And before I knew it, I was there.
The whole flight was gone because I didn't wake up.
I was actually soundly asleep.
It was unbelievable.
I'd never experienced something like that.
One day I got a jolly story.
It's me, your father.
How was your trip?
Oh, well, you know, I just was talking to, you know, creator of my little pony, Lauren
Faust, about some projects that I'm working on, you know, see if she wanted to get involved
in a way.
And then I flew back to my business class, see, you know, in my airplane.
And also I drank caviar and I kicked orphans.
Also, I'm fucking stupid.
Wah, wah, wah.
I'm pissing my pants right now.
Change me, change me, dad.
No.
No, he's in my representation.
But basically, the moral of the story is miss your flight.
Miss your flight and good karma.
Miss your flight, change your life.
Yeah.
And like, I think because I was so positive, that was good karma.
That was like, I believe in karma now only when it suits me.
Oh my God, you know, had the worst karma at the entire fucking time?
You talk about how Ben was just so unbelievably mean to that one waiter when we were getting
the flat bread.
No, you're wrong.
Oh no, they accidentally charged me full price.
He would have lowered it, Ben.
You just have to remain calm and ask politely.
Okay, that, look, I talked to that, maybe it wasn't the same waiter.
That place like overcharged like everyone.
I was not the only person that they, look, I think they're, I honestly think they were
doing it on purpose and just like not applying the discount.
Maybe.
Okay.
And I didn't yell at the guy.
I just said like, hey, my order is wrong.
You charged me wrong.
Fix it.
Look, that may be true, but it's also a fact.
What do you mean that may be true?
That's the whole crux, the argument.
No, no, it is because Ben, how do you explain how everyone around the table turn you and
said like, whoa, Ben, relax?
I don't know because you're all fucking weird.
Oh, is that what it is?
Because you're all fucking weird ones.
Yeah, you're all fucking weird losers.
I think that it's strange to complain to the waiter when he charged you the wrong amount
for your meal.
The facts are, you could in a polite, reasonable, calm way say the exact same thing and get
the problem solved without being mad at the waiter who probably didn't do anything wrong
in the purpose.
It was just funny because there was no build up to the rage.
It was immediate.
Yeah.
Okay, it's kind of funny.
It's a meme.
You guys are overstating it.
There was not rage.
I just like said it.
I didn't yell.
I just said.
It was very funny.
Hey, you got my order wrong.
Fix it.
You did kind of like slam the paper down at the end and like cross your arms at the guy
and look at him pointedly.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay.
I wasn't like yelling at him.
I was yelling, but there was there was there was vim and vigor in the vocal tones.
Yeah, I was really.
Yeah, I was annoyed.
Yeah.
I was annoyed that they didn't charge me.
Right.
You did kind of talk and talking.
You did kind of talk into the other kind of flip the table over and punched a dishwasher
on the way out.
Yeah, I guess, but they charged, they literally charged me double what my order was supposed
to cost.
I talked to other slime guys and they told me like, yeah, the same thing happened to me.
I thought it was an odd choice to whisper to the general manager as we walked out.
I don't want to see him again when I come back.
I mean, you know, fair enough.
Ben, we just need to address your also burning hatred for weight staff in that class of people.
Weight staff.
You just hate them.
I was extra annoyed because the meal that I had ordered was shit.
It was a terrible order.
Well, okay.
I mean, I was pissed about that.
Fair enough.
Dude, over on the main justice side of the table, we were living it up.
We were eating disgusting.
We were eating like whiskers from walruses.
Yeah.
Yeah, we had the barbecue.
We had the classic barbecue.
Not only us, like us and like all the slime guys.
Frankly, the PCP boys were weak.
They were not united in getting the flatbread.
But like all the slime guys got the flatbread.
I am like thinking about it now.
I am salivating thinking of the mozzarella flatbread that I got.
That was good too.
The margarita pizza or whatever.
No.
Okay.
Actually, we can't end this because we need to talk about the saga of trying this to
come true.
This was another like prevalent saga and I need to say this because it was me who was
trying to organize it.
So we all walk into Burning Con knowing one thing.
Listen, Digi Bro, the greatest YouTuber ever loves the Kona Grill barbecue chicken flatbread.
He talks about it day in and day out.
He did an entire video dedicated to him discussing the ups and downs about this beautiful piece
of food that brought him to tears at one point.
We were there when he discovered his love for it.
Yeah.
So it's a magical almost holy, almost like ambrosia, like a modern day representation
of ambrosia given pizza form at Kona Grill.
I mean, knew we had to go there.
By the way, just the background of this, Kona Grill's are closing.
The company is bankrupt and they're like mass closing stores.
Just like BrodyCon.
It's just a miracle that this one was still opening.
It all comes full circle.
Yeah.
Dude.
Okay.
All right.
So we all immediately, we gather that barbecue can flatbread.
Of course.
Like we can't go here and not get it.
So like the first day, we are in a giant, giant group full of RCK people, you know, PCP
people, you know, all the fans and friends, everyone wants a barbecue can flatbread.
And so I'm like, okay, we obviously just like can't like walk in because, you know, it's
right next to the con, like literally like two feet away, like right next door.
Everyone's going there all the time.
We got to make a reservation.
And so I call up this person, I and I say to the person, hey, listen, we've got a big
party here.
30 people.
Can I make a reservation?
They say, yes, no problem.
For on the third, you can come back.
We're going to be able to get you 30 people.
No problem.
What's your email?
I give them munchy wears tiny hats.
And then they say like, Hey, by the way, if you want to like, if you want to have the
full menu since there's going to be 30 people, it's going to be extra because, you know,
we're going to have to make a whole bunch of stuff.
Can you just like tell me like what you're going to order so we know we have enough for
all of you?
And then I'm like, yes, all 30 of us will be ordering the barbecue chicken flatbread.
And she says, okay, we'll get more, we'll get extra barbecue chicken for you.
So I'm like, okay, cool.
That went great.
Actually, you know, look, I'm coming back.
Okay, we got a reservation.
That's, that's great.
You know, cool.
30 people are barbecue chicken flatbread.
It's all in the bag.
Smash cut to the third.
And I'm like, okay, let me just check in, you know, let me, let me just see, you know,
what's going on.
Like, you know, let me just say like, Hey, we're coming over.
Make sure, you know, they didn't forget about us.
We call the manager is put on the phone, can't speak English, like as like a very, very,
very big, which I can't even like understand what they're saying really.
And so I'm like, Hey, reservation for 30 tonight.
And they're like, no, no, no, no, no, no, you made a reservation request.
You made a request for a reservation.
You didn't actually make the reservation.
And so we're going to need to get a $15 from every single person involved in order to make
a reservation.
Otherwise, we can't help you.
We can't even get you a table like, like, I was like, can we just get like a smaller
group and like, no, no, no, no, like, you like, you just have to like a complete, that's
$450 for the layman by the way, doing the quick maths.
Yeah.
Insanity.
Um, literal insanity.
And so I like, I'm just do check it because that was the whole point.
Like we were talking about like all the time, like barbecuing flatbread.
That's the thing we're going to do.
We're going to get this.
We're going to make this happen, bro.
And then I made the reservation.
Everything was fine.
And I just wanted to check in just to say hi.
And they said, no, everything's ruined and we're going to gouge you for fucking, we're
going to fucking extort you for this barbecuing flatbread.
You want to cry?
You want to, you want to follow in your father?
Did you bros footstep?
You want to eat barbecuing flatbread?
Give us money.
Suck our fucking cock.
Right.
God damn now.
I'm just not gay enough.
And so, and so what ends up happening is that like I scurry around all the PCP people just
like, you know, the core group and like, okay, don't tell me what we like got to get a reservation.
So I make a reservation for just us, for just the people.
We all walk in and apparently it's like a sweatshop.
There's like, we walk in and like half of the restaurant is EMT.
We could have easily fit 30 people in there and we ask, Hey, why is this entire section
of the restaurant, like this entire fucking room not being used and they're like, we like,
we even working like all day, there have been no shift changes.
We there's like six people on the entire staff.
We are like being worked to the bone like it like help us were dying.
We're being like the Indiana Jones to children being whipped by our corner girl overlords.
And and and then they purposely and spitefully try and charge been $35 for his two years.
And I just draw my righteous very down.
So true.
This, you know, you know what you did when you became he'll never, he'll never work.
I mean, who?
Yeah, when any and Jones gets corrupt, like mind break, dozen into hating all children
and love slavery, he'll never work in this town again.
Just a beautiful Ben moment because he just like, like the waiter was just like asking
around the table, like, how was everybody's meal?
And it was like, great, good, lovely, fantastic.
I didn't like it.
You charged me too much.
I didn't say I didn't like it, even though I really didn't.
But anyway, it was all fine.
All this time has people got to come in.
They got to like shuffle in like one by one.
They all had like that could be split up.
It wasn't like a unified thing.
Like we all wanted to.
But you know, it's fine.
Most of the people who really wanted to were able to come and kind of go real.
The barbecued chicken flatbread, my rating.
8.5 out of 10.
It was really good.
I give it an A.
It didn't make me cry, but it lived up to the hype.
It lived up to the hype.
It was really good.
It was acceptable.
I had a bite.
I'd give it a 7.
It's pretty good.
But it's a little too strong.
It was a restaurant with food in it.
Yeah, that's that's my that's my appraisal.
Jesse, I can't get over your food.
Like the entire time I was I was like talking about, too.
Like, I was like continuously looking over like I was like gas.
I was like, oh, everybody was getting on the like the meme train
of the barbecue chicken flatbread.
But I'm an adult.
So I was like, fuck that.
I want I want like a sushi thing.
Like, yeah.
So I got some kind of like sushi crab lobster fucking every undersea creature
at once, like rolled into like this alien pot, like from the movie Aliens.
And it was awesome.
Put them in your mouth and they fucking like explode in your mouth
and all the little meats and the little critters come out
and all the little sea spiders run down your chin
and start to study about the table.
When fucking Munchie said he's never had sushi, I was like, what?
Nani? That is that is honestly shocking.
That's crazy, dog.
And you're from California.
Cuck Sushi Central, as I understand it.
But well, that is, of course, true.
I mean, I mean, I mean, in what?
I'm not going to go to a Japanese restaurant.
What about for? Well, you get both.
Just try it once. It's good. I'm telling you, it's good shit.
I don't. I don't.
My name is Ben.
And please, that's for me as such now on question me ever.
OK, so people confused us for a long time.
People confused us all the time.
People like refer to me. I got called Ben multiple times.
Yeah. Yeah, same.
I don't know what the one time. OK, I'm dressed.
I think I'm I don't remember.
I think I was like Slime Corp.
Nate or whatever. So whatever it's me.
I'm wearing communist glasses, part of the N8 suit or whatever.
So like, OK, pretty recognizable.
I'm standing next to Michelle dressed as phantom horn.
Oh, no, no, I was keg. I was keg.
So whatever. I have my keg glass on and my normal purple glasses.
Michelle's next to me as phantom horn.
Someone walks by points to Michelle as as phantom horn says,
hey, it's Ben Saint and then keeps going
and doesn't even acknowledge my presence.
First of all, I'm keg standard.
You look if you recognize phantom phantom, you should know.
And I'm like me and this is Michelle, not actually Ben.
I could I could understand.
I could understand someone knowing who phantom horn is
and not knowing keg standard.
But if you know that phantom horn is Ben Saint, then you must know.
The implications are mind boggling here.
Although, OK, do the possibility do you remember?
Do you remember that that girl who like was talking to Michelle?
She came up to Michelle and asked her about her phantom horn cosplay
and was talking about it.
Oh, yeah, he was in like, she knew that he was like in the first episode
of an Al-Zaki and stuff.
And she's asking like, oh, yeah, who was that guy?
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know anything.
And I'm standing right there, just kind of like looking between the two
and like, should I say something?
And finally, I did.
Finally, I was like, oh, yeah, by that was me, by the way.
Yeah, I was phantom horn.
And she was like, oh, OK, I just walked away.
Singles, you bought a point of totally
inconsequential curiosity for her.
I think I may have been like as give and take, recognized by more people,
which is funny. Yeah, I think it feels like T-Bap was more popular.
Well, T-Bap, I don't know.
I feel like I feel like phantom horn was a pretty iconic, well-known design.
I don't think it was very phantom horn.
I think phantom horn reached a bit.
Yeah, beyond beyond.
He had a little bit of reach beyond just people that watch T-Bap.
Like I heard about it.
It's a great design. It's a great design.
Well, I mean, he was also in analysis.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
I think even I think even beyond that, people knew about, oh, yeah,
that that one OC with the toilet paper roll, which for the record,
keg standard, me was offered the role of demo man.
I turned them down because I read the script.
That is what happened.
People forget this, but it's true.
I deserve all the praise.
Thank you very much.
People don't forget.
Nobody cares. Yeah, you might be right.
You might be right.
Hey, OK, so moving on to Bronicon, I have one outside story of something
that happened to me yesterday that I would love to tell everybody.
It's a bit of a saga, but I think when it's done, you will agree.
This is this might even rival
Bronicon in its sheer ferocity of energy.
OK, so so so Jesse, have you been to King's Island before?
You've probably been there, right?
No, where is it?
No, OK, it's an Ohio, Ohio.
Design Park. That's like Nate.
Wait, I just want to say real quick.
This is so bizarre, serendipitous,
because I also went to a seer fair owned amusement park.
OK, so I was there yesterday.
But yeah, timeline is pretty close.
So so the thing was we had gone.
Me and Michelle, just like at the beginning of summer,
we're like, hey, we haven't been to like a water park thing.
Let's go to King's Island,
which is like a water park slash amusement park.
And like we paid like exorbitant prices for the tickets.
They try to get you to do like student discounts or mill.
Like they really try to do discounts.
I'm like, I don't know any of this.
I'm just paying the full price.
And they were like shocked that someone is like actually paying full price.
But whatever, I did it.
But the thing was, if you buy the crazy, the ticket,
they're like seventy five dollars per person for one day.
I know it's it's insane.
But here's the thing, when you do that,
you actually get a second day just free.
You can just come back and it's so basically that like halves the price.
Now, you're not actually like making your money back.
You're going to spend more at the park,
but like it feels good.
And so I did it.
So me and Michelle went yesterday, August 10th, 2019.
So the park is great.
Me and Michelle spent most of our so last time we were there,
Michelle and I, like the first thing we did was go on like a wooden coaster
that we were told was not that big a deal.
Oh, right. I've told this before,
but was actually horrific for her and deeply traumatizing
because she is not good at these things.
So she was traumatized.
So we spent most of the time yesterday doing like baby coasters and baby rides.
There were a lot of fun, had a good time.
OK, but but as the day went on,
the looming mountain that is Diamondback.
Diamondback is the fastest roller coaster.
I think in like the like the Midwest,
it's like it's like a million feet tall.
It goes like 80 out 80 miles per hour or something.
And like it loomed over me as a challenge to my masculinity as like I
when I was young, I did like the Superman ride is Six Flags, New England.
I did all those crazy rides, but I'm like, I'm like spooked.
This is the final boss of King's Island and I don't know.
I'm going to do other stuff.
So as the day goes on, I start to do the more serious rides.
And then as we get close to the end of the day, I'm thinking like, oh,
maybe I'll do like the Banshee.
It's like the second fastest one.
I'll do this thing called the monster.
These are other kind of more serious rides.
But like, no, I've got like an hour and a half until the park closes.
It's like eight thirty.
And I'm like, Michelle, now's the time.
I'm going to be a real man.
I have to get in line for Diamondback and oblivion.
Please edit in some footage of what it looks like to ride Diamondback
and just the sheer scale of this thing.
It's fucking insane.
And I was legitimately terrified, but I get in line at like some like eight
forty five, an hour and 15 minutes or so before the park closes and the saga begins.
So so time is ticking and I'm waiting and waiting and waiting.
I told Michelle it probably be like 45 minutes, but 45 minutes passes.
I'm like not even halfway there.
And it's getting closer and closer to the closure.
People are in line way behind me.
And I'm like, there's no chance they're getting in.
Why are they even waiting in line?
I don't even know if I'm going to make it.
But hey, whatever, I'm just I'm just praying that I get there so I can actually
overcome this obstacle that's been there.
Because like the first time I went, I was too scared to even try.
This is my second time.
I don't even know if I'll live in Ohio like this time next year, like summer next year.
If I'll ever get another chance, this is my last opportunity to do so.
So the pressure is building.
I give Michelle my phone and my wallet and I get whatever I get in line.
I'm waiting. OK, so here we go.
So I'm starting to get nervous as we're getting closer and closer up to the line.
And and, you know, the duration of the wait starts to introduce fears into the mind,
you know, little little demons, little demons start to creep in.
And I'm like, I'm just watching other people go line after line of people
doing this insane, like vertical drop.
You guys, I've got to get a fucking picture of this thing.
It is so fucking.
I'm watching it right now.
Link that to the other guy so they can see too.
It's fucking insane, this fucking ride.
And so I'm thinking to myself, do I really want to do this?
What if I just get on there and I'm just panicking and crying
and pissing myself and shitting and I'm legitimately too scared?
So my my heart is wavering in a big way.
OK, all of a sudden, like the Virgin fucking Mary,
a kindly mother of like two people up in the line starts chatting with other people.
And I just hear her over say that, like, like this is like a 50 year old mother
with her child, and they've both done this before and they're like,
oh, yeah, she's like, oh, you know, it's a little scary on the ride up.
But like after that, it's like such a smooth ride, like because it's metal.
And sure, it's fast, but you can really you can endure.
It's no big deal.
And like hearing those words, this encouragement from this from literally
I mean, that's her and her son, presumably Jesus Christ himself.
It just it fills me.
It fills me with confidence.
I'm like, this mom did this.
No problem. I am a boy.
I am a man. I can do this.
And so I feel I am at peace.
I feel reassured and serene.
I'm committed.
So, you know, the lines go on for a long time.
We're getting close.
We get to like the stairs.
The final approach.
It is five fifty seven.
So sorry, nine fifty seven.
We've got three minutes until the things close.
Everyone's starting to get spooked that we're not going to have enough time.
And I'm getting spooked, too.
And meanwhile, so of course, Ben, I'm sure you'll appreciate this.
The fucking like gold speed pass people are just waltzing right by all of us
waiting in line. Those capitalists, did you?
Did you know that one percent of the theme park visitors ride?
Ninety nine percent of the.
Oh, it's it's it's unconscionable.
It's fucked up.
And OK, so me and Michelle, because we knew that this was an issue,
we just we went and asked like, hey, guys, we're just curious,
like we might get speedbasses.
This is early in the day.
Should we get them? How much should they be?
And they were like, they're between seventy five and ninety dollars up hop
for one day, the fucking speed pass.
Can I was my mind exploded into a thousand pieces when I heard that.
It was fucking insanity.
So obviously we didn't fucking do it.
But so so I'm in line.
These fucking speed pass fat cats are just waltzing right by.
And I'm like, you know what?
Capitalism, it had a good run.
It's time to end.
We need equal opportunity for equal people.
This is fucked up to the core that they're just waltzing by.
But as we're good, did you did you seize the means?
We you know, I tried.
I initiated my plan to start writing my manifesto right then and there
to be published probably tomorrow revolution.
OK, but but as we were getting there, now I notice.
So we're like on the stairs.
Just me, Michelle was waiting for me the whole time as I'm climbing the stairs.
I see that actually I'm getting to a point where the speed pass people are
actually only being allowed like four or five at a time.
And actually the main line is actually going faster, even though there's a lot
less speed, people like, sure, the speed people get on like faster overall,
but they still have to wait until their line clears before they're allowed to go.
And the general admission, people like me, we're getting on like there's like,
you know, like 20 of us getting on paride and it's making pretty good time.
So like I said, it was nine, nine fifty seven, the clock is ticking.
We're going, but we're actually getting a pretty close, you know,
we're getting pretty close to being in line.
It's like nine fifty eight, nine fifty nine.
And then finally that, that, that humble child, that, that school, uh,
fuck school child on summer break, getting his summer job.
He looks at me with the patience of, of Buddha himself and gives me the slow
nod and ushers me into the golden realm of this ride.
So I'm stepping like a fucking pimp onto my row 10.
I believe it was a fucking diamond back.
I'm next to, I'm next to some guy.
I don't know.
We sit down.
We chat, we're bantering and as we're getting, it is pitch black.
It is 10 p.m.
You know, there were a couple that went after us, but this is among the very
last rides that go on down and back, but that's not all because at 10 p.m.
every night at Kings Island, a fireworks show begins and right as we are sitting
in the seats about to go, the, it is fucking stroke at 10, the fireworks
begin to go off in the distance and we're, we're just, we're in awe.
We're like, this is, this is, I cannot believe you're talking about the fucking
gold saucer fucking date night.
That's exactly it.
I had Tifa next to me.
She was sucking my dick and squeezing those titties.
It was an incredible experience.
And so as we're climbing up this, this terrifying mountain that I'm
experienced utter panic at the, at the prospect of going down, but I have the
Virgin Mary's words in my mind, keeping me calm and at peace as literally the
fireworks are going off directly above our heads, like a little bit to the left
past the fucking Eiffel Tower that's at Kings Island.
We're filled with the spirit of America.
And as we go over the peak towards the plummeting distance down below, I'm
filled with the courage.
And so I sing out, I know that it was due to only because capitalism, I didn't
get a gold pass.
It was the system works perfectly.
It is operating as intended.
I'm experiencing the fireworks.
I'm experiencing a love of my people and my country.
We were the most diverse group of people on the planet.
We were all brothers in this enterprise.
We go over the peak and I literally in real life, breakout, looking at the fucking
fireworks and the rocket red glare, the bombs bursting in air, gave proof through
the night that our flag was still there.
The crowd, everyone on the right is cheering with it.
They join in the song.
This happens in real life.
We're all singing the national fucking anthem.
We go crashing down.
No fucking way.
We go over the first hill.
We're singing our fucking hearts out.
We're saluting the flag over the second hill.
Okay.
The thing about it's 10 p.m.
There's no lights.
We are in pure darkness.
We're going down over the second hill, but we feel the spirit of George
Washington filling our hearts as we're going down.
It's darkness, but the fireworks, the bombs bursting in air are illuminating
the ground below and we feel safe and it fills us with the courage to handle it.
And we're writing it out.
We're going down and we keep singing the song.
Oh, say does that star spangled banner yet wave 80 miles an hour tear streaming
from my eyes, from the, from the wind or the land of the free and the home of the brave.
We come to a stop.
We ease into the final, the final resting place.
And I just shout to myself, this one's for you, George Washington.
And they burst into applause.
The guy next to me, Dennis or Derek, whoever he was, he's my new best friend.
He turns to me and he says, that was the most patriotic thing I've experienced
as long as I can remember.
A child in front of me turns around and says to me, quote, nice singing.
It was the most, it was the most heroic experience I've ever had.
We're, we're, we're cruising in.
I'm getting off.
I see Michelle waving to me, having experience.
She was thinking to herself, oh, I wonder if Nate's on that last one.
I hope he makes it.
I was, I was in heaven with George Washington, with America.
We, we saluted the flag.
We joined in brotherhood.
I've never felt more at one with my people of America as I did that day.
Thank you, capitalism.
Thank you, George Washington.
And thank you, America.
God bless us.
Everyone and scene.
And that's, that's the story of me.
I made it.
I made it onto Diamondback and I love America more than I ever have before.
Take that, Karl Marx.
That's a real story.
It's a real story.
That, that was, that was beautiful.
I'm crying right now.
I thought I really saw it.
That was a journey.
I fucking shredded my throat on that ride and now.
And maybe it's time for those voicemails.
What do you say?
Let's go on a high note.
Yeah, yeah, let's do it.
I got the one right here.
Oh, by the way, about the Diamondback thing, I, the thing was,
I kind of feel a little bit guilty, like I didn't fully experience all the terror.
I think I almost had like an unfair buff of patriotism and courage
because I don't remember the ride that well.
I kind of blacked out with love.
Everyone knows, everyone knows courage is cheating.
I kind of agree.
OK, OK, that said, let's go to the fucking voicemails here.
Let me hit play.
This one is from saying goodbye to a goat.
OK, go.
So Quentin Tarantino's new movie came out.
It's pretty dope.
In the past, Tarantino has famously said that he would retire
after he directs 10 films.
And since he considers Kill Bill volumes one and two to be one film,
that makes this his ninth movie, meaning he has one more and will then retire.
As artists, how do you feel about this approach to art,
setting a limit for yourself so that your career doesn't dwindle on
and you lose your creative spark or ability later in life?
You think it's a good idea?
I think it's bullshit.
I mean, I think it's bullshit.
Yeah, it's a weird idea.
Yeah, if you if you have like a good idea that you want to make later,
why would you be like, oh, but I made 10 already.
It's one thing if he's not going to stick to it.
Come on, if they were like, oh, I've made 10 movies and now I'm burnt out
and I feel shitty and I don't want to make stuff.
That would be I don't understand that.
But to say from the beginning, you know, I only got 10 ideas.
And then after that, fuck it, fuck it.
Who gives a shit?
It's like, what the fuck are you talking about, man?
You know, on its face, it sounds like a preposterous idea,
but let's let's give the idea it's due because I think it's kind of interesting.
Jesse, I'm sure you remember there's a famous Star Trek, the next generation episode
where I think I've talked about a bunch of times where like there's this there's
this dude who's like in charge of some important science thing or whatever.
And like he meets Diana Troy's slut mother who's dope.
And they they like he hits his 60th birthday or something.
And like his people come around and they're like, well, this is what we do.
On your 60th birthday, we literally celebrate your achievements.
And then you commit suicide because like this is the time limit.
We give our people to like achieve things in their life before they we kill
them, like they kill themselves in honorably, so they don't be a burden.
Double that other movie.
The new movie Midsummer is also that.
Oh, oh, is it about that, too?
Yeah, dude. Oh, did you see Midsummer?
Oh, did you see it?
Did you see that?
Dude, it was so good.
Scary spooky bullshit, baby.
Dude, yeah, dude, I love that.
It's a horror movie every single day.
I was a sunshine the whole time.
Yeah, that's dope.
Yeah.
Dude, OK, my alarm is the scene from my god, I got to see that every single day.
It's like a half week or more or else I'll be stuck up every morning.
Oh, my God, I'm a burning bear.
I'm a burning bear.
Let me out.
Well, OK, OK, so so obviously I'm not actually in favor of that idea.
But like the idea is, I mean, I'm sure Quentin thinks that in a couple of ways
that like he doesn't want his legacy to be tarnished, probably by like the
shittier things he might get older and loses them and vigor and shit.
But like you just got to I mean, definitely like some people only have
so many like creative sparks in them before they're dead.
Like like an artist that makes albums
past their peak just because money fucking David is like it's on.
It's not ideal.
Well, David Bowie was just very little David Bowie is kind of an exception
to, you know, many of these things that David Bowie is the ideal.
I guess it makes sense when you look at like Quentin Tarantino himself
specifically as like a guy who just like makes the movies he watched growing up
because you can kind of see like, OK, well, he made his crime movie
and he made his David Caradine Kung Fu movie and he made his horror movie
and he made his Western.
So I could see how like he just wanted to make his version of the movies he liked.
And now that he's run out of those genres, that makes sense, I guess.
Yeah, I've changed my own mind.
I think it's cool.
You know, basically, if somebody wanted to do that,
I can't really find a way to like object to it.
I wouldn't do it because it seems silly.
Like I would take more of the approach of limiting.
It just seems like why would you like I think I mean, at the beginning,
like it's just like if you have nothing else to say,
they don't say just for the sake of it.
But like it seems weird to me to just like say that like, oh, I will.
Well, he is also talking about doing a Star Trek movie
and how that wouldn't count towards the 10.
So so like I can see how like maybe I think director still right,
but not like both on one movie or something is his point.
Well, yeah, I'm sure he do things, you know, to fucking fill his time
and be somewhat creatively fulfilled in other ways.
I don't know.
I mean, also, it's it's just sort of like a pretty cool marketing idea
to like this is my final film.
So you better go see it.
He calls one like the hateful eight.
It's the eighth movie.
He's really he's really sticking to that theme with his like numbered movies,
at least a little bit, the fucking once upon a time in Hollywood.
It's not called like nine boys in Hollywood.
X nine boys.
I mean, it's us.
Damn, that is us.
OK, well, there you go, Quentin, do your thing.
Let's go on to the next Quentin himself left that voice.
Was that a good idea?
No, no, no, no, Quentin, you have no more lollipops.
Let's listen to our boy, Dang Energy, Dang Energy calling in.
OK, go. Hello, PCP.
You might have heard of bang energy, which reverses retardation.
Well, let me tell you, energy drink called Dang Energy.
You know what it does?
It gives you retardation and I've been drinking by the gallant.
My IQ is like the city New Orleans below sea level.
Well, I just cannot shit, even says on the side of be aware, you may shit.
And man, the best thing this energy drink has done to me
is make me appreciate my little pony.
I just can't get enough of it, man.
Dang Energy, get retarded.
Get retarded.
Is it on Amazon?
We're kind of by it. I need it now.
I mean, I will just say to this guy that he seems dare I say almost a fake fan
because this is just literally just like this just is exactly what
the fuck energy is maybe as a competitor.
It's not all any like, oh, yeah, like you thought of it being like it makes you retarded.
Yeah, wow. OK, yeah, that's really funny, dude.
Smash cut to the entirety of New
Los Angeles City, OK, I know Milwaukee being being forced upon.
Fuck energy just day and day out for like months preceding this.
Come on, bro. Come on.
Pretty fucking crazy, pretty voice jail.
If you ask me, I just thought the marketing team for Dang can afford
the rights to the hit retard anthem.
Let's get retarded and let's get retarded.
I mean, it really writes itself. It really writes itself.
I mean, I mean, does does does does Dang Energy even steal your soul
and make your soul into slavery by the devil?
I don't think it does.
Yeah, come on, dang.
OK, let's go on.
We've got one from a comfortable.
Sama, comfortable, Sama. Go.
Hey, fellas.
Yo, have any of you guys been to a movie alone?
If so, please tell me about it.
Once the movie was over.
When you stood up to leave, did the women of the crowd laugh
and help you with their snacks and sodas?
I'm a fight with no social connections, but I want to see
millennia mattress and I want to see these Djibouti movies that are coming to theaters.
But to be honest, what's wrong with this person?
I'm not with you.
It's just I'm a little anxious.
Wait, what's happening here?
You said he's he's anxious about the idea that if he goes to the theater by himself,
people will notice. Yeah, yeah.
And laugh at him.
Nobody will give a shit.
Yeah, I'm laughing right now.
I achieved that fucking mode of like, I'm finally old enough.
I can go to the theater by myself now.
And I saw Spider-Man Far From Home by myself in the fancy theater
with the big chairs that recline and it was dope.
That's that fucking scene where Mysterio is doing the fucking messing with Peter's mind.
Fucking Kino.
Oh, was that good? Was that good?
I was thinking about actually didn't like it that much,
except for that scene with Mysterio, which was great.
I like Jake Gyllenhaal.
All of these all of these zoomer Spider-Man movies
are just not hitting the right spot for me to be perfectly honest.
Yeah, I feel you.
All these people with anxiety who don't really the house need to understand
that only you think about you.
No one else is like looking at you and being like, oh, what's that?
Dude, it doesn't have any friends, huh? That's sure strange.
Everyone's just like, oh, it's a weird thing.
It was great, but it was it was it was not my taxes.
Now fair. That's understandable.
I'm not I'm not going to tell you just don't care.
But I will say no one does care.
So, you know, let let that fuel you with with power.
Nobody cares. You're fine. You're fine.
Yeah. Yeah.
No one no one cares about you or what you're doing at the movie theater.
This is a silly question.
Please kill yourself.
You know, I'll give you I'll give you some courage on this.
I don't do this a lot, but like I will go to the movies
and generally I'll take Michelle or whatever.
But like I am both happy and willing
and honestly eager to go to the movies by myself.
I don't even want to go with people.
I only do it because like I might as well take someone along for the ride
who might want to see it.
I would love to go alone and just not talk to anyone.
The movie is great.
And I do recommend it.
If you can't afford to go to Bronycon, go to the movie theater
and you can't go to Bronycon ever again.
So go to the movie theater instead.
It's better.
Midsummer was so good.
I think about that scene when when Christian is a high off his ass
and then this dude like writes in his face and he says why would you do that?
I think about that every single day.
Did you see the previous one by the director of Pereditary?
That one is also great.
No, I haven't seen it.
I haven't seen the thing that I did a video, but it was a patron thing
because I forgot to release it.
It was for the scary spooky bullshit thing.
And it was like the last one that I forgot to ever make public.
So I have to wait till this October to show it.
But I think the world's first heli movie.
Like, you know, you know, there's scary spooky bullshit.
Some of it's scary and some of it's spooky and it's all bullshit.
Some of it's scary, spooky bullshit.
But the next level, the next category is heli.
You don't want to see a heli movie.
You don't want to do 70s drugs and then strap yourself in for a heli movie.
It's too intense.
You'll fucking you'll have night terrors in real life in real time.
And it's a great experience, but it's an experience you never want
because it is hell. It's cool.
So that was how it is.
I don't think that Midsummer was quite as heli as hereditary, but it was great.
It was as good, but not as if that makes sense.
What's the general premise of hereditary?
Just the they're kind of like the same movie.
They're kind of like companion pieces.
They're both about a cult doing a stupid ritual.
They believe in retarded gods and demons and they have stupid customs.
The first movie is like
like anything like the whole plot is a spoiler.
So you can't say anything about it.
It's basically like a movie about someone being sacrificed by a cult
from the perspective of the person, like from the perspective of the sacrificial lamb.
It's how I saw it described, and it's really scary.
And it's just like horrible things happening to this family.
And there's it's just bleak and horrifying.
And it's awesome.
And I'm watching both now.
And Midsummer is like a companion piece to where like it's also about a cult.
But this one is during the daytime.
And it's kind of it's got like a real like a like a 70s wicker man atmosphere to it.
And it's just the bees.
Yeah, like she goes there.
She's got this like horrible fear and anxiety about death
because her sister committed suicide and her parents are killed in it, too.
And she's like all messed up and she goes there.
But these like crazy like Swedes just like pumper full of like magic mushrooms.
And they start like they have these like ridiculous rituals
and people are jumping off cliffs to like kill themselves because they're too old.
And and it just it just gets crazier and crazier until at the end.
It's like the most completely fucking but fucking insane shit you've ever seen.
And it's cool and it's disturbing and it's rad, dude.
Yeah, it's so good.
The end the end of the year.
I saw this review that really earned me.
There's this channel that I found when the Game of Thrones finale was happening
and everyone was shitting on it.
I found a channel who was also shitting on it.
It was pretty cool called the the the critical drinker or something.
I think that's it.
He's like this like Scottish guy and this thing is that he's drunk
and he just complains and like when he was complaining about Game of Thrones,
it was cool and I was all on board.
But like the more you watch of his videos,
the more you realize that he's one of those who like sees every movie
through the lens of like this is SJW propaganda.
Oh, it's another SJW movie and all these fuck it's all feminism.
I can't stand it.
And it's just like shut up, you fucking idiot.
It's just like like I agree with you, but shut the fuck up.
It always makes me sad when I hear people like that,
who might not do something like say, enjoy the awesome,
wonderful experience that was watching Steven Universe or something.
It was his midsummer review that was really irking me because he just like
he only saw it through the lens of like, and of course,
the main character who's a female is right about everything.
And her boyfriend, her boyfriend has to, of course, be a stupid asshole
because he's a man and it's like, oh my, that's not the point of the movie.
And it's like like he was like and the part the part at the beginning
where the parents die and the sister dies, ultimately had no impact
on the story or the themes.
And it's like, are you fucking retarded?
You actually say that, what the fuck?
It gave her like this anxiety about death.
The movie is about death.
It's not about feminism.
You're just choosing to see it through these fucking insane
anti-SJW culture warrior goggles and you're missing the whole fucking point of it.
That's one of the reasons.
YouTubers, stop it.
I watched Red Letter Medias.
I watched Red Letter Medias review of this.
And that's one of the reasons I like them so much.
I feel so confident that they are not political and it's like fantastic.
Great. Just tell me what happened.
Is it good? Great.
That's what I want to know.
OK, well, sick.
Let's move on to our next fucking voicemail.
This is from Loll Pussies Put Here Eating With Spoons.
I don't like that.
Go.
If you get ice cream in cups and not drinks, you're literally pussy, bro.
I don't like this.
Liked for the burp in the middle.
Wait, what?
What? OK.
Yeah, I agree. Let's play it again.
Let's play that again.
I'll turn up. No. Oh, you heard it.
OK, never mind.
I think he's just saying if you don't use your pussy, that's true.
Hard to agree. Hard to agree.
It's the wrong.
It's the wrong way to do it.
It's the coward's way out.
I. I don't want to see that person in here again.
Voice jail. Voice jail.
You know what?
You know what? He doesn't he doesn't deserve it.
But yeah, voice.
All right, let's just one and done.
Let's just one doesn't deserve it.
But let's do it.
One and done, buddy.
Loll Pussies Put Here Eating With Spoons.
There you go.
Straight to jail.
Let me post that.
OK. Yes. Yes.
Oh, my God.
Let us get more liberal with our ban hammer and our jail key.
We'll throw the whole.
This is what Roque Pierre felt like.
He was like, oh, yeah, we'll kill the king.
Oh, I can just kill anyone now.
They just went around doing it.
It's great. OK, we got one from.
Let me see. This is idea man slash woman or creator man slash woman.
OK, go.
Hey, PCP, so.
So with a unique group like yours, I'm wondering,
you guys as creators, do you guys have more trouble
with coming up with an idea for something?
Or do you guys have more trouble
actually doing the work of the creating?
Definitely doing the work.
Yeah, definitely.
Some of you not to name the names and they didn't seem to be lacking
in the making things department.
Shut up, dude.
OK, I'd be the answer.
I have I have a huge backlist of projects.
So yes, obviously, look, my problem right now is it's hard to make weekly
videos and still carve out time.
But I'm fixing it, God damn it.
Give me time. It's been one month.
Give me a break.
I'm easing into a new job.
Fuck you.
My thing is that like the ideas are come easy and they never end.
And it's yeah, like so.
But my problem is that massive backlog of stuff
and this becomes overwhelming to start on anything like I'll have an idea.
And I'll just be like, well, I better just forget about that,
because like I have other ones.
And like, yeah, that hurts me so much.
Yeah, and I don't have I don't have like writer's block ever so much
as I have like the block of like, oh, my God, what's the point?
I don't want people paying attention to me.
I don't want to fucking upload a video.
I fucking hate all of this so much.
Like, I feel like that 99% of every day.
So that's my thing.
Like, I have the ideas.
I just don't want to be seen easy.
I like really enjoy like working like actually just like making something happen.
But I hate like having to come up with ideas for like what to do.
I hate having the initial just like, oh, God, OK, so what's going to happen?
Like here, like what's going to happen at this aspect?
I don't know.
But like once I have like, you know what I'm doing, then it's like really like fun.
Well, that's I mean, that's that's the work.
That's doing the work.
Like having the idea is one thing that's like like actually flushing it out
and like figuring out the details is part of the work.
Yeah, like, like, like, like right now I'm drawing comics.
And it's like, yes, I came up with the idea.
I know exactly what's going to happen.
But like the literal like panel layout and the smaller things,
like I don't have that in my in my head.
I have some panels that are like the big ones, but like getting to from,
you know, all of the stuff getting to doing all of the smaller parts.
They're still creative, but there is like a lot of work in there.
Yeah. And it's just it's it's just it's like I'd rather just be doing the end.
I'd rather be doing the cool.
I feel you on that.
But like I'll I say this this I know I said this before, but like
honestly, the place I am that is the happiest that, unfortunately, tragically,
I'm not really in right now.
The place I'm happiest is when I'm working on a project that I think
that I at least initially think was good and I'm, you know, was excited to be
working on it. I just love being trapped in basically the prison of working on
that project and not having to worry about other things.
Like that's like when I'm working on like a big smash video when I was like,
that's why like my six month periods of like making those big videos,
the best anime ever is or whatever, I love being there because like every day
I know exactly what I have to do next.
I know the purpose I have.
It's it's honestly freeing to have that kind of restriction on what I can do.
It makes me not have to worry about when you get on when you get on a roll,
even the working part can be the fun part.
It's just like the general.
Yeah, totally.
It's just for me, the general anxiety of uploading a fucking thing.
And it's just like increases every year and it never gets any less.
So now it's like everything is your second guessing everything.
Like, oh, my God, someone's going to take this out of context and someone's
going to weaponize this against me and someone's going to fucking not get
this joke and someone's going to take this too seriously.
And it's like, what's the point?
Just make everything Patrick on exclusive, which I do.
Patreon.com slash endless jazz.
Become a patron and give me money.
It's cool.
That's that's fair.
That's fair.
I feel that it feels so good to have a clear, like very specific
goal thing you're working on.
Like right now I'm working on a what?
Undertale to the air.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm working on a sequel to like the ARG
that I talked about previous on the PCP for more endless war stuff.
And it's just great.
It's just great coming up with stuff and like, oh, dude, I can do this
and it'll be really neat and epic.
And then I write a bunch of stuff like, wow, I'm doing it and it's great.
It's the only thing the thing that I like I said, I love being in that space.
But the one thing that haunts me fairly frequently, it's not even that
like I write down every good idea I have, basically, I write down and I have
documents and I have like things relatively organized.
So it's unlikely I'll like lose track of them.
But specifically in that process, the thing is there are periods where I get
an idea and I'm really excited about it.
And I know that if I worked on it right then and there, I could make something
really cool.
The problem is, even if I write down all my thoughts, if I get back to that
project in like six months, it's just that that fire oftentimes will go out.
And then it's like, oh, like, even if I make this, like, am I even that excited
about it?
Like, is it it's the exact same ideas?
I've simply lost the passion for it.
And that's that can happen.
Sometimes it's the opposite.
And sometimes I'll write half of a script and stop giving a shit about it.
And then I'll find it again, six months later, having forgotten it and be like,
oh, that's cool.
And I'll just absentmindedly start adding to it.
And then I'll finish it randomly six months later.
Like, hey, you know, it's like once once you kind of bring the project back
to life, like when you work and like you're actively working on it and like
changing something.
Oh, I can add this here and like you're editing it, which, you know, I do
that fairly frequently.
Yeah, that is a pretty gratifying process.
If you're losing the passion, like halfway through a project, you can just
take a break and come back to it.
And sometimes that works.
Sometimes it gets lost forever.
That's very true.
You know, I like I have like everything I've ever written for like the last eight
years, like every lyric, every song, every like video idea, every script,
like everything like fucking like terabytes of like written stuff is all
on this one laptop that I've used forever.
And none of it is backed up anywhere.
It's not in the cloud.
It's only on this laptop.
So I live my life in a constant state of fear and anxiety that something will
happen to my laptop, because my entire life is on there.
I feel like you almost kind of want that to happen.
I think I do kind of do and it almost because you can back those up to
like Google Drive or something.
But it's really it's hard and weird because it's on like this.
It's on this old MacBook from 2014 and everything is written on this
program called notes or something.
And it's not like any other like document that you can't export the files
anywhere, they export in this weird file type that like only works on a Mac.
Can you not like copy paste?
I have to I have to highlight everything manually and copy paste it to
like Google Drive if I want to do it, which I've started doing.
I've started doing it.
It's like a forever.
What? Yeah.
Wait, what did you say?
Like highlight, Command A or like Control A is like highlight everything.
My God, I've never heard of such a command.
Is that true? Is that a joke?
Uh, what if I just click and click on a text thing and you press Control A?
No.
All right.
Yes.
Well, that's Troll A selects everything in a page.
Well, that's OK.
That makes it command A.
But yeah, that will be easy.
I almost I almost had a tragedy the other day because I was in bed and I was
I was looking at my laptop and stuff and I see like the biggest
brownest, hairiest, strongest spider I've ever seen.
Literally on my laptop, like very near to touching me and like instinctively.
I'm like, ah, and I just and I chucked my laptop across the entire
fucking like landed upside down and it like caught just right on like a plastic
bin so that it didn't smash and it was like it was a stroke of luck.
It was a miracle that it didn't get destroyed because I chucked it full
fury across the room before the spirit of George Washington wants you to make
those videos.
He wants you to create those those things.
But by the way, I just want to say an unrelated to all this.
I just want to say that it just dawned on me that like I haven't posted
anything on Twitter besides like bronicon updates in like literal months.
I have not posted anything on YouTube in literal months.
Probably like everyone like has no idea what I'm doing.
So I'm just going to say again for the thousandth time,
dude, I'm in RFCK get in there.
If you're ever wondering what happened to that guy, come in there.
Go there.
Fair enough.
Don't you stream like what's your live streams on your main your channel there?
No, no, no, it's on RFCK.
Those are on Twitch. OK, OK, that's cool.
Yeah, it's all in ours.
I'm I'm all in on that.
That's what I'm doing now.
So if you're ever wondering, that's that's it guys.
Come on over. OK, we've got one last voicemail.
This is from Make Rebel Pickles.
Great again. OK, great. Go.
The last episode of the PCP was great.
They talked about t-shirts for two whole hours and I was in trance by every fucking
minute of it. So I was thinking why is this boring business talk interesting?
The obvious answer is because they care about it.
They care about making money.
They care about their business.
They care about their artistic process.
And that's what I really want out of a discussion topic.
I don't want to see this good idea.
No, I want you guys to fucking care about what you're talking about.
Don't just say something because you gave a good topic.
Say it was you like it.
Say it was you mean it.
Problem I have been talking about politics is was he's the only one who cares about
politics.
OK, OK, politics.
But every time they talk about it, he says, I'm not a professional.
I haven't researched this.
True. Nate did research during fucking log in.
He should fuck research the fuck out of green log in.
So he could be an authority on it.
So Nate, why are you talking about politics when you can talk about green
log in instead of what you care about?
Talk about your art.
Talk about their artistic process.
Make the PCP Rebel Pixels again.
OK.
Yeah, I mean, fair, fair comment, fair comment.
Can't can do that.
You know what, actually, this was almost kind of entirely
like one kind of like topic dedicated PCP.
You know, we've been talking about tossing back and forth.
The idea of like doing like a topic episode.
And I just think that like trying it out couldn't hurt,
even if it doesn't not the whole episode.
We tried it out for like a year and a half.
Well, we tried for several years.
Wait, stop, stop.
Everyone is like, oh, God, like,
poppics are banned now when, like, at the very beginning,
we went back to topicals.
It's always like, hey, the reason why we don't like to talk about this is
sometimes a lot of the time, the topics aren't anything that we care about.
That's the specific problem.
And if there ever was a topic where we wanted to talk about something
exclusively, then we should do that, and that makes sense.
True. This was like established at the very beginning.
Like this isn't like a controversial, like, oh, we have to either do.
Either. I totally agree.
I don't disagree.
I mean, today's episode was a topic.
It was right. And obviously we all did.
I think what will generally make it better for people is to just be more
mindful of, like, rotating the cast of characters on the show.
Because, like, the last week, it was all just Digi and Majin Tom,
which is a unique cast of characters for the podcast.
And everyone in the comments seemed pretty positive about it.
True. Maybe it's just separating Nate and Ben forever on the podcast.
Maybe that's what needs to be done.
Well, I think we've because everyone's just complaining about the pot.
By the way, in the in the hotel room,
I got to witness firsthand the loudest and most furious communism debate
I've ever heard from this.
Yeah, that was between Nate was going to let him finish.
Yeah, it was Ben and Michelle.
That's true.
And it was like it was like the PCP were a physical location
and I was inside of it with Noah and you can't leave.
Except that.
Yeah, I had to run away, though.
We just left the room.
Well, that's the night.
You're all cowards.
Thing about the thing about that was that, yeah, we were like literally
shouting at each other and then like, but then like at the end,
it was just like it was just over and it was fine.
Yeah. I don't know.
It was like even even when even when we even when we were shouting,
like I didn't feel like bad, like I felt like a little annoyed,
but I didn't feel like I wouldn't consider this person shouting.
And like there was there was no cool down either.
It went from it went from loud shouting to just in the debates over at the end.
That's true.
There was some form of conciliation that was like they agreed that like
something was bad or something.
And then it was like, yeah, OK, we're good.
It was like she if I remember she was like,
what are you what are you going to do?
Just like storm rich people's houses and take their shit.
And I was like, no, I just think we should tax them.
And she was like, oh, OK, I agree.
Yeah, yeah.
That was the end of the end of the debate.
OK, you know, for the record, I just wonder about this sometimes.
Sometimes I no one's ever said this, but I always wonder if people think
that in some way, Michelle, who, you know, basically seems to agree
with me on a lot of these things, like is like my agents are like acting
on my behalf, but I just want to be clear.
That's absolutely not true.
We I mean, sure, we talk about these things,
but she's not like an indoctrinated mind person.
And we disagree on quite a bit.
So I don't know if anybody ever thought that I just want to be clear.
That's not the case.
Michelle's a fucking name.
Yeah, I mean, if Nate had around the worst.
I I like I giggle with glee laying back in my my soft bed, thinking
about how I've slurred if I'd made about how it's like the worst thing
that you would you did.
Achieve slurring the term Nate had.
That's true. That's true.
Possibly because I didn't push back against it at all.
And also and also invented the term.
That's true. Yeah, that's true.
Well, rest in peace, Nate heads.
That's going to do it for another episode of the procrastinators podcast.
The party's just the end.
Yeah, that's that. That's the last one.
Oh, thank thank God.
How long was this one? This is what are we at?
Two and a half hours.
Good. So this is a meaty one.
Patreon.com.
Rack on four today.
Let's see, guys, the air.
That's that's that's next on the agenda for sure.
We didn't even get to talk about how I destroyed my basement floor.
Do you want to talk about the real quick, save it for next time?
Or I'd be happy to feel like you want to talk about that next time,
Munchie? Yeah, yeah, talk about an RFC.
Let's see about RFC.
I'll talk about just fucking fair enough.
Follow us on RFC K.
Oh, RFC K is on YouTube now.
I've I've I've moved.
Well, I haven't as of you hearing this.
Yeah, yeah, I moved all the streams.
I'm uploading all the streams onto the ratty fuckers cop killers YouTube channel
because I know some people just don't in don't won't go to Twitch.
So if you're on YouTube
and you want to see all that, there's like 40,000 hours of a ratty fuckers.
Well, now that my boy ninja is not on Twitch,
why would I dane to go there?
It doesn't have the stamp of approval.
So, you know, he was sucking up all the traffic.
So like, it's got to go somewhere.
And why why would it go anywhere but ratty fuckers?
Are you guys going to stream there or just like re upload the the streams there?
You know, I was I was I was thinking about maybe we could do
I mean, it's possible to dual stream.
It's possible to dual stream to Twitch and YouTube at the same time.
Oh, that'd probably be good.
I don't know exactly how to do it, but I know it's possible.
Well, we can think about it.
Yeah, OK, in any case, my body is all sore from yesterday, Ben.
I'm still like I'm like writhing in pain right now.
Why are you sore? That's what I wanted.
Oh, because Munchy came over and worked out yesterday. Oh, sick.
That's dope. Munchy and Munchy and, you know,
Cassie's been coming over and this time she brought Munchy and we all fucking
lifted and I'll just yeah, the floor of my basement is destroyed as a result
of this other lifting exercise or yes.
Yes, that's right.
How interesting.
Turn to literal gravel. Oh, my God.
That's a story for another time.
Yeah, yeah, there you go.
OK, patreon.com slash the procrastiners, one dollar,
Patreon lounge, five dollars.
I believe all twenty nine of the bonus episodes I think we're up to now.
So it's a fucking steal.
They're pretty good.
Fill your life with more podcasts.
And that's it. Pledge one.
Big podcast, five dollars.
T.P.
Crastinators on Twitter for updates.
It's a good place to be.
And I don't know, I think we retweeted.
I don't know if we reach to a bunch of Bernie Kahn stuff.
I should, though. I should on the PCP Twitter.
Anyway, that's it, everybody.
See you next time.
Have a good week.
Wonderful time.
And I like you.
Bye.
Who's your who's a.
Hey.
Oh, die.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?