Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever. Oh, who else is here? We got, yeah. Wait, is that, is the best guy
ever? Don't you mean, don't you mean my favorite cryptocurrency miner, Brad Garlinghouse? I'm
sorry. The mask has slipped. My name is Brad Garlinghouse. I am the CEO of Ripple Cryptocurrency.
I've been fooling you all this anime bullshit, all this video game bullshit. It's been a
fucking ruse to pull you into my scheme, to profit to like 1% of my vast capital gains.
Finally, you've decided to contribute something to society.
It all began 29 years ago when I snuck it to Ben Saint's Mother's Womb, who I knew would be a
ripe candidate for manipulation and emotional destruction later on. This is a long con I've
been running here. And as you can see, the fruits are ripe and abundant. Bravo, sir.
We got, yeah, you can hear the grass, Tom Oliver, Gibb and take, you know these guys.
And New York Times bestselling author DigiBro, creator of Road to Radcon 4, with Chapter
2, hopefully coming soon, but that's on you guys.
Road to Radcon 4 asterisk, assuming you'd give us lots of money.
But if you do give us lots of money, you will see the thrilling continuation of the series
in which we introduce our main antagonist. Who could it be? Who could be the biggest
obstacle to making Radcon 4 happen? I think there's a distinct possibility that this is
not on the procrastinators channel and most of the people watching this have no idea what
the hell is happening. It's very possible that this is on my channel, in which case,
hello, my subscribers. This is the procrastinators podcast. It's been going on for like four
fucking five years. How long have we been doing this shit?
Like three, four, five years. Like three, four, five, two, one.
A lot of years. Whenever Undertale came out.
Eight, eight, 12, you know, what is this number?
We've been doing this podcast since Undertale came out.
That's true. The best thing to happen to the internet
since Undertale, the procrastinators podcast. That should be our tagline.
And the reason that it might be on my channel is that Brad Garlinghouse, the evil crypto
mastermind, has taken over the PCP channel. So in order to prevent...
And other channels as well. Many channels. He has an empire now.
In order to prevent Radcon 4 from becoming Bradcon 4, as per his evil plan, we must
continue the story. So give us money on Kickstarter.
And also thanks everybody who already, because this Kickstarter has already funded almost
all the original stretch goals.
Let's just quickly take a look at that. We've got, so last time there were 308 total backers.
As of the whole time, there's already 156 backers and it's, we're 22 days ago.
You said there were 308. And now there's 156?
I'm saying that on Radcon 3 there were.
Oh yes, of course.
So with 156 backers, we're already at $10,573. So we, Radcon 4 is happening. We've met our
first and second stretch goals. So there will be a Tiki Bar and the OVA will be made.
The important note in all that data you just spouted was that with half the number of people,
we have achieved more money.
Correct. That's correct.
So really the important question is where the fuck are the rest of you guys? You goddamn
placards.
There's another 150 of you out there, 152, just waiting to give us money.
That is the 152 people who unsubscribed because of the politics discussion.
Damn, we are the 152 who would not give to Radcon 4. The proud.
Yeah. Well, I mean, if you guys want, now that we've established that, so hey, go give
it to Radcon 4. It's still happening. Don't worry about all this other bullshit. That's
going to happen no matter what.
I have a question for Ben before we continue about this topic.
Oh, God.
Ben, is this, find your phone.
No comment. Did I find my phone? No, it's gone.
Shit. I lost my phone for a while, but I ended up finding it.
So is this the crypto fascists I keep hearing about? They're just going around shilling
cryptocurrency, stealing people's channels.
I mean, he's crypto because he's mining Bitcoin and he's fascist because he's a bad man.
That's what I thought. I'm with you now.
I take back everything. You're right.
I think this literally counts. Yeah. Even I think this counts, right? It's certainly
fascist to steal somebody's channel without permission, right?
You know, I think that's a little bit loose use of the word fascist.
Like annexing another country, Garland House here has annexed our channels without our
permission.
I mean, that's true. That is true.
Fascism just means I don't like it. So, yeah.
That's probably the most honest definition of fascism I've heard.
And I definitely do not care for what I'm seeing here today.
According to Wikipedia, fascism is a form of far right authoritarian ultranationalism
characterized by dictatorial power, forcible suppression of opposition and strong regimentation
of society and of the economy.
That sounds like my boy, Brad.
Sounds exactly like what's happening.
I can't believe it. I can't believe it. He was hiding in plain sight all along.
It's the crypto punks versus the crypto fascists, the ultimate battle.
That's right.
My only question is, will Brad continue to mine once the sun goes down?
Yeah.
Like, how long will this continue?
I wish I had answers.
That'll be the final insult, where we're just going to have to bring out the big guns.
There's only so much injustice we can take.
The second the sun goes down, I'm tweeting about this man.
This man is still mining at its night.
Listen, Brad, as one night miner to another, don't do it, man.
Consequences, man.
I suffer the consequences.
I want better for you, Brad.
Well, you got a...
Known fascist sympathizer, Ben St. looking out.
You got to respect the hustle, though.
You got to hand it to him.
I do.
Where don't mine at night came from?
The pony version of the Minecraft parody of the Ken Perry song.
That became a meme at Radcon 3.
Yeah, that's correct.
Ben got his ass kicked for mining at night during Radcon 3.
God, it's such a rich tapestry.
This is what we should do on every episode.
Imagine if you're just the normal...
You're just the normal Digi Bro subscriber, bombing into this video, not knowing what to expect.
And already, with this many layers deep into PCP lore, they're gone.
They're just gone.
Well, this is why you need to watch Radcon 4 when it comes out,
and donate to it to make it happen, so you can understand it.
If you're not aware, you should watch the Radcon 3 playlist,
and all your answers will be revealed.
When are we going to do PCPU lecture PCP?
I think eventually.
That's actually a really good idea.
We're going to start from the beginning and go through the whole history.
Give it a couple more read.
Is that going to be a stretch?
We did the RFCK one at RFConK, and we allowed audience participation.
We could do the same thing with PCP.
We could have us, the audience, raise our hands.
Hey, don't you remember that one time that this really stupid thing happened?
Imagine if we had a meetup, and the meetup was for the PCP lecture on the PCP.
We've long had this idea, at least I have,
of doing a public, more actual con where people can come and attend,
even if it's public or something, I don't know.
But then, with a gathering of people, we do that lecture.
That was the RFCK lecture, basically.
Well, we'll steal their idea.
Which was great, by the way, and is coming soon.
Stealing their ideas, as if it was easy.
I hope it comes out before the Kickstarter ends,
so people will be tricked into giving more money.
I also hope that.
Connor, Ethan, get on it.
I hope that by some magical fucking circumstance,
that the Stealing Your Dad episodes from Rancon 3
also come out before Rancon 4 happened.
Someone suggested making that a stretch goal for this Kickstarter.
They're almost all done!
Munchie said that two of them are complete, one of them is almost done.
He just wants all three of them to be done before he releases them,
and he literally just doesn't care enough to...
What a fool.
He simply doesn't...
See, that means that it's up to you people to create pressure.
No, they did! They created...
I don't know if you know this,
people from my Discord formed a Discord
specifically to Badger Munchie about this.
And they did so. They ran a whole campaign,
and he literally said what I just told you,
and has still not done anything.
Well, that's not enough pressure, obviously.
He just doesn't care.
He needs to feel the sting.
He needs to feel the pain of not releasing the...
What can we do to Munchie?
He's too powerful.
I don't know.
He's got nothing to lose.
I guess you're right.
I think the people have to, from that Discord,
raid RFCK,
try to destroy his hometown.
That's the only way that will get us attention.
I mean, RFCK and Stealing Your Dads,
I like to think they exist in the same universe,
at different timelines.
So I see no canonical conflict
between a bunch of Stealing Your Dad heads
bomb in from the dystopian post-slime future
to say, fuck you.
Do it.
Maybe the unborn disaster was right.
See, the most unfortunate thing about it to me...
Yeah, it's time like shenanigans now.
Like, while there may be extant episodes
of Stealing Your Dads,
they were merely podcasts.
The only episodes that are, like, good
are the ones that have not come out yet.
So I don't know if there are Stealing Your Dad heads
the way that there would be if the show was out.
I mean, probably.
Probably.
When are we gonna get the man and the boy?
Oh, boy.
Oh, yeah.
When are we gonna get GRPJ, Kingdom Hearts 2?
Oh, no.
We're all gonna call that right now.
That's right.
I'm not me.
I'm such a good boy.
I did all my projects.
You did.
I mean, you got T-Bap Resurrection out.
I got Ten Paces in Drawout.
I did it all.
That's true.
I'm thorough.
Everything PCP related I've gotten done.
It's only my personal projects that are taking a little while.
They're gonna take a little while longer now.
That was your father's idea.
Nobody ever...
Yeah.
Let me break it down for people, just the story of what's going on.
Here's your little public service announcement.
The following channels have been hacked.
It definitely seems like it's my fault.
And I'll tell everybody why in a minute.
But these are the channels.
My main best guy ever, which is currently renamed Brad Garlinghouse and is streaming
some cryptocurrency stream that I have no control over.
The name of the video is RippleXRP Goes To The Moon Explosion Emoji.
New cryptocurrency partnership and bullish news.
3,000 people are watching this.
Redcon5, Crypto's On The Moon.
Why don't I pull these kind of numbers when I stream?
Either on my channel or on my fucking Twitch.
God damn it.
I'd be a partner right now, Brad.
Maybe a lot of them are fake viewers, though.
That was my thought.
I mean, I think people are watching for the drama.
They're like, this is wrong.
This is fucked up, which I totally understand.
I mean, this guy's gotta be botting as well, right?
No doubt.
It's not, by the way, we're gonna laugh.
Brad Garlinghouse, really funny.
It is not actually Brad Garlinghouse, just to be absolutely clear.
Brad Garlinghouse is the CEO of some company.
This is an important man.
It's like Elon Musk of crypto.
It's not actually him.
I've been looking into it and he's a very rich man who owns this Ripple company,
which basically just moves money of various types around.
Anything that can be used as currency, basically.
It is a way of trading that internationally.
Apparently, they're under a huge lawsuit,
and he's in trouble for skirting the law.
That's why he's trying to pull a couple of side hustles,
like capitalizing a couple of YouTube channels here and there,
just grab them while you can.
It seems to be common in the crypto world for things like,
for hackers to take people's channels,
livestream under names that are famous in the crypto world,
such as this one.
But the actual people who took your channel,
you can tell us about.
Yeah, please do.
Well, okay.
You know, I'll tell you.
So there's a couple interesting things that happened over the last couple of days,
so I've been talking of two.
So, okay, this seems to have happened on around the 22nd or the 23rd,
I think on the 23rd.
So just so everybody knows, I'm already in contact.
Oh, by the way, all the channels, just so you know,
all the channels that are not us.
It is Best Guy Ever, Bestie Boy, Best Guy Ever livestreams,
The Procrastinators, The Poddycast, T-Bap, and CanTent.
All of those have been hijacked.
Yesterday, I went through T-Bap,
and I ripped every video that I could,
just in case the worst happened.
I could not get all of them.
Some of them I could not rip because they contained music.
They were maybe like a dozen of those.
Oh, Ben, you gotta use, you can get them.
You just gotta use a multitude of YouTube rip sites.
I recommend switching between Clip Converter and several others.
I use Clip Converter to get the ones that I did manage.
What you gotta do is you have to use VLC.
You can download YouTube videos with VLC.
Oh, no shit.
It works 100% of the time.
I need to remember to do that from now on.
I got Phantom Reviews. I could not get Keg Reviews.
Keg Reviews putting your hoof down was copyright claim.
That needs to be preserved for all time. It has to be saved.
It's a beloved video by me, if no one else.
Okay, so those are all the channels.
Here's what happened, everybody.
What happened was, I recently have been looking,
a lot of people were like, oh my God, Nate,
did you not two-factor authenticate your channels?
Lol, did you use the same password?
No, this is not the issue.
What happened was, by the way, we have checked,
there have been no suspicious logins from China or Russia.
I don't know if you saw my screenshot.
On T-Bap, there was a suspicious login account from Russia
on January 1st.
January 1st?
Yeah, I screenshoted it.
Okay, I believe you. That must have just been before this.
That must have been just an unrelated, I guess,
separate hack thing.
Because here's what happened.
I've been talking...
I've been so lucrative.
I'm just saying, maybe potentially,
I do use a VPN.
I don't think I've ever set myself to Russia.
Maybe I said to Russia and logged in.
I don't think so, but I don't know, whatever.
I was getting...
Recently, I'm doing one last
Weagawa
before I wrap up Weagawa's for now
and are focusing on the bigger content,
as I've told a bunch of times.
For that, I was like, okay,
it would be really funny and also cool
and thematically appropriate
to finally get one ad on the last
Weagawa for now.
I more aggressively was looking through
all the messages I get
to see what ads are going to be.
And I will still be talking to.
But one of them...
I should have known, man. I should have known.
But here's what happened. There was just like
one of those emails was like, hey, do you want to do this thing?
We'll pay you to, like,
promote this software. And so what I said was like,
there was a link to a website
and let me actually go get the name of this.
Because this is, I mean, at the very least other people
can avoid this. Nobody clicked this link
that you're about to leave the name of.
No one clicked on this link from this company.
And here's the fascinating thing. This website
is extremely professional looking.
And this is why I was tricked.
It's supposed to be like a cloud software
like, what's that thing where you're
streaming gameplay between things?
This is like the general pitch they had.
Their website looks really good.
And the whole thing was in English, the email.
But I noticed that it seemed to be from,
it was like Russian text or something.
So I was a little bit, okay, I don't know what this is about.
So they just say like, hey,
download this software. So I mentioned this one time
and I'm like, okay guys, I'm open to this
if it's good. Can you like, tell me what
you need me to do if I'm going to do this?
They respond and they say,
download this software, show it off in a video
and like, we'll pay you for it.
So I'm like, okay, I will go
see what this is about. So I'm looking
into it and I, this is,
I go to the website, everything's fine. I'm just like,
okay, I mean, I'm not going to agree
to do this yet until I know
what I'm getting myself into. But what I will
do is just download the software
and like, see what it is. Cause that
should be fine, right? And what I believe
happened is that I download
the thing, I install it and
nothing seemed
to happen on my computer. I was like, this is
weird. I don't know what happened.
Nothing changed. But then
several days later,
every YouTube account that like
I just am logged into
generally speaking, all the
accounts on there had disappeared
from my Google accounts and
they, so they seem to have been like moved
to other people's Google accounts.
So what I think happened is that there's
some bot in here that uses either
like your Google, like your cookies
cache or maybe like the fact that I'm
currently logged in because there were no
suspicious logins from anywhere else. It probably
was done from like my machine
that it just went in there. It like
hijacked the fucking
links to all these accounts and
this is something you can do on Google. You can
just move your account to like another
Google account on your YouTube channel.
So I think that was done
by at least some kind of intelligence
because it wasn't done to my
vast number of just like small little throwaway
YouTube accounts I make for various purposes, like test
uploads and stuff. It was only
like the big ones that are regularly used
and have some value. So clearly
even though like BGE live streams probably
has less than a thousand subs, right?
It's got like 1500, but I do upload
like twice a week and it gets
you know, like 500 views
per video. So that's not zero.
So I guess they thought that was above their
threshold for whatever reason.
But yeah, that's
pretty much the full story of like what I know
and so I'll just tell everybody that I
have contacted Google
for all of these
things, for all these different accounts.
I've got like separate tickets running for each
different account and like I seem
to be in contact with humans for all of them
and apparently they are working
to sort it out. And from what I've heard
this isn't confirmed, it takes
like people have reported that when this has happened
because this is a fairly common thing, it happened
to Pogo apparently, famous music
guy on YouTube and a bunch of other people
that like it takes around
two weeks before things get resolved
typically speaking. So you might
not see any of these channels active for another
two weeks. Hopefully after that they're back.
That's what I know.
I seem to see the only thing that's
really bad right now is that they're
actively streaming on my personal
YouTube channel and best guy ever.
And you know, some people
are unsubscribing and you know that's too bad.
I hope no one's being tricked into buying fucking crypto.
I highly doubt it.
I don't even understand how, like
who the fuck would fall for this shit? Like how does this even
work? How does this racket even
there was somebody in my discord theorizing
that like maybe they literally
just do this to like smear the name
of Brad
Garlinghouse or whatever.
But I don't know. I feel like just some
Whoever it is though, what gives me a little
bit of happiness is that like knowing the
MO, if these people want to
they could tank and delete everything
or just fuck up everything on all
these channels if they so chose.
But it seems like the MO is just
to use them for whatever reach they have
and generally speaking they seem
to come back. And there seems to be a pretty
healthy like reversal process
when you get your shit back. Like if videos
are deleted within a certain time frame
YouTube can restore them. So even if
like someone was telling me that like hey Nate
seems like the number of videos on your channel is dropping
that's ominous.
I didn't look into it, but even if that's
true, hopefully they'll be able to be revived
if not, I know a bunch of people are downloading videos
and including me, I've got most of the important
ones stored, so
we'll see. I guess we'll just see in time.
Most of the important ones. That's
not good enough.
I need all of them.
I don't have literally all of them, it's true
but I have all of like, I have every best
anime ever, best game ever and like all the
viagra was I think from the last several years.
So I should
have pretty much everything. We'll see.
We'll see. So obviously it's not good
I can tell people don't be too worried
if you're concerned. I'm generally pretty optimistic.
They changed your channel banner.
They changed the banner?
They changed the icon now?
They replaced my little icon face.
I still see you. I still see your face.
I refreshed it and I see
Brad on here, but I don't know.
Also all the affected channels have
strings of Russian
text in the about page that seem to be
like passages from
Fight Club and or the Bible
or something. Just like edgy
posts about
like in the night we do
dangerous things and in the morning
we only regret. No, I mean once she searched
them and they were from Fight Club, like literally.
It's just quotes from Fight Club.
Maybe they know I'm a big fan of Fight Club.
He's tossing your bone here.
You'd appreciate it.
Anarchy in the UK, bro.
Let's fuck them up.
Well, that's the status.
Hopefully things will be fixed soon.
I don't know. I don't know.
That's it. That's all I got.
Oh, boy. Well,
if you don't want Radcon to become
Bradcon, then you've got to
donate to the Kickstarter.
Our lawyers advise us
that donating to Radcon for it will in no way
save Radcon from becoming
Bradcon.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe some people will think
considering there is a Kickstarter with a good
amount of money attached to her right now,
I don't know if people might think, like, is this some sort of
fucking publicity stuff? This is odd timing.
I mean, there's no doubt about that.
I mean, it was definitely,
I was pretty upset just this morning
because I scheduled my video to come out at
12. So, and of course
it came out alongside this. It's not that
it's not that I'm
mad that it's sold my
Thunder. It's that it's funnier than my fucking
video. That's what makes me mad.
That is unfortunate. The Brad Garlinghouse
name is funnier than
this story that I think is hilarious.
I am seeing a lot of Brad Garlinghouse
comments on the
Digibro light novel. Sorry, dude.
You just got to lean into it.
It's given you the path forward. That's right.
We can capitalize on this.
Brad Garlinghouse is
definitely going to be
in the Royal Rumble at Radcon.
He's clearly the main villain.
There's no doubt about it.
So, you know, pledge if you want to see
that. I mean, we're probably going to
definitely going to be doing it already.
Indeed.
What's going to happen to the party cast?
I'm restarting my phone.
Our ship is going to get sunk.
Our ship is currently sinking. We're bailing out
the water. Hippo and BGE Boy
are currently bailing things as fast
as they can. Hopefully we stay afloat.
I mean, there is a possibility
that some or all of these channels
don't come back. But, like, even if that
happens, we're just going to make new ones
and, like, re-upload as much as we can
and just keep going. I mean,
I don't know. Hopefully that won't be too bad.
I mean, the thing that sucks
not so much, like, if that's
the case, you know, if, like, you can't get them
back, the worst thing
is not that we can't have them back,
but they still have them.
That, I mean, yeah. They still have
your channel, like,
anything that links to your channel will now
link to Brad Garlinghouse.
I have some fear that, like,
I mean, just considering the legality,
it seems to me that this, I don't know this for sure,
but it seems to me the most likely thing is that
this was done, like, via, like, my personal
longings, that, like, Google
will be like, sorry, Nate, like, sure,
you can prove you're you, but, like, this
was done on your account. We can't
prove you didn't do this. We don't have the
authority to just give them back. I mean, if they were to say that,
that would be the most fucking, like, pretending
to be ignorant thing I've ever heard, like...
I mean, I'd hope so. I would hope so.
Well, even if it's from your account, it's not
like you can't take
it back if it was, like, a mistake, like,
oh, I accidentally did this. Can you please
undo this? Like, Google can't say no.
I guess you're right. That's just stupid.
I'm just thinking, like, what about respecting the
rights of, in this case, like, they're a criminal
clearly, but, like, the other person...
Well, hold on. If you, if they believe
the claim that you
accidentally moved it to this other thing,
how would it be... like, that would mean
that this is, like, two different... this is
one person, basically. How would it be
disrespecting that channel's rights?
Like, either way, you're the original...
Or what if?
Your account is linked to the channel.
The hypothetical I fear slightly
is, like, what if I had under the table
made an agreement to, like, sell my account
to these people, which I totally didn't
do, to sell my account to Brad Garlinghouse
stuff's
wallet full of money that I did,
in fact, do the thing I'm saying with. What if
I had sold it to them, and they're like,
well, I mean, you know, that's your business
if your account got... we don't have the authority
to just take it from other people.
But it seems unlikely, I know.
I'm just thinking about how my...
One of my friends, one time,
sold a World of Warcraft
account to somebody for $400,
and
that person then used it to,
like,
like, just farm gold or whatever, like,
he turned it into a bot, and
got caught by Blizzard, and they returned
the account to my friend.
Like, he just got to keep the money,
so, you know, sometimes things go...
Well, how an extra good.
Dude,
when you get the channel back, it's going to come
with so much cryptocurrency.
That would be...
That, I've looked at my World of Warcraft account,
actually. A bot stole it,
and then when I got back,
I just had so much vast wealth
in the game. I was a god.
They just helped me out.
You know, thinking back on it now,
actually, that is fucking hilarious.
Fuck yeah. But, uh, thinking back,
I remember my League of Legends account,
I think this is one of the main reasons
I stopped playing. Oh, no, I think I didn't play
for a long time. In that lapse,
like, I noticed that I couldn't get back in.
It seemed like it had been stolen, or something had
happened with it, and I could... Yeah, I definitely
had been stolen. I couldn't get into it.
And I, like, there was some... I had some average,
ooh, maybe I'll, like, try to get in and, like,
help my friends, but then I was like, oh wait, it's League of Legends.
I'm not gonna put in the effort to get back in there
just to, you know, lose more money and stuff.
Uh, so, thank you, hackers.
You saved me on the one hand, you hurt me on the other.
All in all, that's what I call balance.
That's balance.
By the way, um, I'm getting
the name of the company. Okay, got it.
So, this is the email I got.
It's just, it's this company, Vantex.
V-O-N-T-E-X.
That's the one who messaged me. Guys,
in my recommendation, I would not accept a deal
from Vantex Promo.
Uh, if you get an email from them,
they're, uh, they're, I don't mean to
disperse, disperse, disperse the good name
of the Vantex corporation.
But, uh, whatever. Yes, you do.
But they are, they are literally the real crypto fashists.
I mean, maybe it's like a Brad Garlinghouse thing
where, like, they're just using a different name
to fuck with people. I mean, I don't know.
I mean, probably not. And the other thing is,
I try, one of the things I did early on,
before I installed the software, was I was just like,
Google these guys and, like, see what they are.
It's like, what the product is. Like, there was, like,
zero results on the internet for Vantex,
like, what, why.
So I should have known.
You should have done that.
I was thinking myself, I'm being such a
big brain ethical boy right now.
Like, I am absolutely not going to agree to just
take these people's money until I know it's like
a product and I'm willing to use it, blah, blah, blah.
But I will just try out the software.
That couldn't hurt, right?
Little did you know.
Little did I know.
Yep, that's correct.
That's correct.
More like soft skull.
You got on you there.
As opposed to what?
You know, like a soft spot on your skull,
cause you're like a baby.
Oh, well, yeah, but it sounded like you were saying
soft skull, like that was a play on something I'd said
previously. Yeah, the software.
Oh, right.
Yeah, see.
Got it. Well, yeah, I have a small brain
both confirmed to this point.
Very soft.
Very smooth.
Very, very smooth. No wrinkles here.
So my computer is definitely still
compromised and very likely still
has this operating. So I'm
spending the vast majority of time
unplugged from the internet on that machine
because I need to wipe it.
As Tom advised, I need to just completely
destroy the computer and rebuild it
software from the ground up, which I will do.
But I'm in the middle
of editing something and I am terrified
of rebooting it
and not being able to like make all the weird
connections. You know how if people use Vegas
like you pull files from all over your computer,
I've got things like a download folder and like
like an editing folder and
the reason I don't have that problem is that
anything I'm working on, I keep
exclusively on the desktop
and it's a great motivator
because I hate having
shit on my desktop. So I will
literally edit the video just to get the
fucking shit off my desktop. But what happens
when your editing project is six months long
though, just by virtue of the price?
That has happened and it's miserable.
It fucking sucks. There's too much shit on
my desktop. Well I mean
so I'm hoping to have that video done
the one I'm working on soon and it'll be ready
to go. This much discussed Nate's working
on a video for the end of the month or whatever.
I mean there's been some derailings
even before this Radcon 4 really took
up a good chunk of time. But like
I might have it ready real quick
I just won't have a place to upload it
until I have the channel back
and I'm just gonna give it a couple weeks
to see if the channel returns at all
before I make best guy ever
Redux or whatever the fuck
thing I have to do to keep moving. Second
best guy ever. Secondest
best guy in the world will be
the second channel. I'm looking forward to it.
Well if you need to, I can temporarily host it
on my channel too.
Have everybody shit.
I did that with
one of Jesse's videos once. There was
a Ground Zero's
vlog he did that's on After Dark.
It never got re-uploaded anywhere else. It's just
on After Dark.
Yeah it must have been years ago I forgot
about that.
So in other
news, today
I got
television
for the first time in years.
Television. Why? What's that?
Did you watch Big Bang Theory Use Me?
Because I found out
that these days
good old
satellite but
cable? No not cable.
Antenna.
Antenna TV.
Well there ain't no bunny ears no more.
The technology has come a long way.
And so
I just like 25 bucks on Amazon
bought this big flat
thing that you put in your window and I've got
50 channels. So why the fuck do I ever need cable?
It's pretty sick.
I'm just saying.
It's funny to me to think
like
TV kept advancing
and getting crazier and it's like cable
and now you need a thousand million channels
and now you need all this extra shit
and then the internet came along
and I was like I don't need cable. What the fuck
would I need it for? Well the answer to that
is the Olympics
or
just like CNN
that occasionally throw
something on
PBS front line documentaries
which are not live streamed or shown anywhere
for some reason.
No the dem debates are all live streamed.
I haven't seen them live streamed.
They're on CNN. I'm sure they're around.
What about the replays though?
They don't have any replays for people like me
who don't watch them live right?
No. Just watch your favorite
alt-right commenters review of the
how do you think I'm informed nowadays?
That is
unironically the better way to watch it
because I mean they cut out the filler
so I mean you know it's
there's a bunch of
there's a bunch of people who just live stream
they're like live reacting
to the debate while it's happening so
that could be better. That sounds definitely
better. The debates are fucking miserable.
They're boring. It's shit. They're terrible.
They're fucking I mean what are they
on like five or six? I'm just saying like I'm
sure they're all been consistent with the shit.
There's like five now.
I think the last one was the final one before
the caucuses started. On average
one thing happens in three hours
and you'll hear about it.
Yeah.
You'll hear. The only story
from the last one was the thing with
Warren and Sandy and it was all over Twitter.
Literally all that fucking
happened. It was so boring and terrible.
That's true. I mean we know their positions now it's about
whatever fucking clash is happening.
Well hey speaking of TV do you have
a cartoon network on there?
The one thing I kind of want to watch
sometimes is like Toonami
slash Adult Swim. I'm like oh that'd be fun
to just turn on. It would have been nice to have
but I think that's on cable.
We get some kind of food channels.
I literally just hooked this up like right before
we started the podcast so I have not
explored it at all.
I just bought a TV for the bedroom
and an antenna.
I remember trying to watch Rick and
Morty like when we were
at the time we did the
60 minutes or whatever
and it's so fucking weird on the Adult Swim
website. They're like streaming
here. Click here to watch the new Rick and Morty
episode and then they're like dot dot dot
if you have Hulu
or fucking blah blah blah.
It's like why would you just lead with
I need Hulu to watch it or whatever
they want you to be like well I guess I'll just get
fucking cable right now.
I guess you got me.
There must be people dumb enough to do that otherwise
we'll be doing that.
If I really need to watch you know Rick and Morty
right then and there on there
every time they put up these weird
Roblox Mike I'm just saying on the high seas
fuck you.
I'm a thousand percent
more into piracy than
anything else.
I didn't really miss TV
at all
and I still really don't
but it's like the idea that
if I really have nothing
to do there is a room I can go into
and just put something on
and it will put flashing lights and information
in front of me without me having to decide
what to put on. Yes.
Because I spend a lot of time
like YouTube
unfortunately not enough fucking
shit comes out.
I'm always star for more YouTube content
and I'll sit there like
maybe May just cooked dinner
we've got all this beautiful food laid out
in front of me on this TV tray
for 15 minutes trying to find something
to watch while I eat because there's nothing
on YouTube.
So in situations like that
it might be nice to just
I mean granted I put the TV in the bedroom
but...
I do like sometimes
putting on like the BBC news channel
when I'm just like
waking up making breakfast or something.
Black Hawk news channel.
I just love seeing that on screen
like a huge
but anyway
but like
they just do the news and it's so boring
and so like in the background
occasionally I hear about like oh something's happening
I'm like oh cool I'm just drinking my coffee
and waking up
it's a nice little like noise box I guess.
It is aesthetically pleasing
to kind of be passively informed about
what's going on in the world even if you know
mainstream news maybe they got some issues
I mean I'm passively informed of what's going on
in the news every day anyways because I watch
YouTube and I trust that more than
any of the other news outlets but
I guess the revelation
I would say is simply that
cable is obviously
not worth paying for
because you have to pay for it every month
but an antenna is just $25
and you have those channels forever
so
why not?
That's all I have to say on the matter.
I've got some news
I know what it is
and I'm a big fan.
It's the Lord of Ghosts comic
Chapter 2 is out.
I haven't read it yet but
you're way short to do it
because it's way better than the Vapors has ever
or will ever be.
Shit.
That pony fucking comic about slime
Garbagio
put it in the trash where it belongs
it's all about the new hot joke.
It's readable on
gibbentake.site
I'm really proud
of what I've been
doing.
I have to ask
that one shot of the clock tower
that was homestucked
you didn't actually draw that whole thing did you?
I copy pasted a few places
but yeah I kind of drew the whole thing.
Oh wow.
It was weird.
I was drawing it.
It's traced so it's not like
disclosure.
But like
it was sort of discovering that
I guess I just like the act of drawing
because this is really inefficient
and not even that useful.
It's like a big like wow moment
but it's also kind of pointless
and you wouldn't need to do that really
and I did it anyway and it took a long time
but I just liked it.
I loved that little moment where you flash between
like that and then the next panel
of the like almost chibi-fied
like big eye of the tower
and it's a different moment and incidentally
the whole comic is probably the most attractive
looking thing you've ever drawn
up to this point and I've absolutely
like it feels like a huge
jump in your skill.
I don't know if I thought that about chapter one
but with chapter two I really stopped
and felt it out and really
really enjoyed reading it.
I gotta read it.
Can I understand this comic
if I don't know anything about it?
Yes Digi, yes you can.
Yeah, I've
written the entire thing to
be its own adventure and you don't need to know
anything about R.C.K.
There is like a little bit of backstory
to catch you up on the basics
of Endless War but the Lord of Ghosts
himself travels to a different place
and is doing other adventures.
Digi, you will love
the literal embodiment of clusterfuck
that is the Lord of Ghosts.
If just one look at his
misshapen freakish body and you'll be like
this is me, this is me
if I was a little monster.
He's pretty relatable.
What did you think of my artwork
for the Road to Radcon 4?
I was frankly way into it.
It was great, it was kind of exactly
what I hoped for from a Digi
and frankly it seemed like
I'm feeling some experimentations.
You're trying some new things it feels like.
Yeah, new things like dropping piss on my face.
Yes, yes.
It was wonderful.
Hippo, what you got to do?
Okay, I know you've made
you made, or sorry
look pass this on
to Gun Girl because I know
Gun Girl is a zinester
and is the author of the best selling
zine and one of the best selling zines
in New Los Angeles City, the Gamer and the Bear.
Yes.
So you know about zines.
I have been converting
I have been converting slime and punishment
into in-game
zine form
and the first seven issues
of slime and punishment are available
in Endless War as zines
that you can purchase with slime
if that's your pleasure.
I'm going to get around to finishing it up soon.
Everything should be a zine.
Why don't we have
a PCP zine already?
Like a real life...
A real zine.
I've been planning to make my own zine
for a while
but I would have to be the only
contributor to it
and it just wouldn't be as cool
as if we had it.
I'm into the idea. I would actually love
to contribute to a zine
but how would we distribute it?
Wait, I've got an idea
and it's maybe Twitter, but
do you remember that website that we had a guy
in his free time working on
which was absolutely beautiful
and was like 95% done
just because I was busy and I never get back to him.
I forget his name right now.
But that could be a pretty good vehicle.
Click on the sign for the latest...
A zine,
what would it consist of?
Is it a news magazine or is it just comics?
The one I want to make
is called
Cluster Punk
and it would be
all kinds of shit
but the number one article
I want to write for it is my Cluster Punk
fashion show article
or the current line
just photos of me wearing
cool outfits basically
but I don't know yet
I just have always wanted
to make a magazine
so
my plan was just to fund it through
the same way Ben did his comic.
To me, the spirit of a zine
is you go to
your fucking mom's office
to print it out on 8x11
you fold it in half, you staple it
you put boxes of them
in stores or on city corners
or whatever
If I made a zine, that's how I would do it
It's funny you say that Ben
that is what I was planning to do
back in 2012
I had this one I did called
the Virginia Beach Hermit Society
that was incomplete
but the plan was to just print them out
and leave them at Barnes & Noble
but the thing about that is
it won't work and nobody will give a shit
so I'd rather just do it
to a means by which people will actually want one
Makes sense
I like the idea
of all of us collaborating
parts to a zine
some of us doing art
Imagine if Jesse wrote articles
it would be incredible
He could literally write anything
and it would be publishable
but organization
and all that
has always been an issue
especially when there's no money involved
We need the money first
then our effort will follow
We can worry about that later
we got Radcon 4 to worry about right now
but maybe we can discuss the possibilities
with zine at Radcon 4
If we reach 20k guys
we will start talking about a zine stretch
to let 30k so let's get it going
I wonder how far
we could push one kickstarter
just by adding new stretch goals onto it
It depends on how good
if it's something that is really good
and pertains to a large audience
a documentary on
the fucking Shanghai 7
the most dangerous samurai bunch
I don't fucking know
at some point it would be like
why not make just another kickstarter
for that other thing
No
Why do that
when you can do this
capitalize off the hype
20k is going to take
some doing I think
While we're on the subject
we're putting the stretch goal on this one
I don't think it's impossible
Obviously the math isn't going to work out this perfectly
but we're at over 10k
and we're at half of the previous donators
Do a little math
if they all donate, surely
that will bring us up to
5th of what we've made so far
is from two people
That is correct
Our $2,000 donors
We did have $1,000 last time
so you really have to subtract $1,000
from that to get parity from last time
That's true
We need to find more exchange students
I know
We gotta pull them in, we gotta have a better outreach program
We gotta reach out to the inner city
My thinking is
the people that made it
succeed instantly
are a lot of the people that donated
last time
A lot of the people that are really invested
knew about it immediately, donated immediately
So I think that we will probably get more
If we didn't do anything else
we would probably get more donors
than the first time
but probably the remainder of them
would be smaller donors than we've had
thus far
So I think that
we'll need to have more donors
because we'll need to reach new donors
to actually double the number
of donate
even if we do hit the
$380
Reaching out to Digi's audience with the book
is a good gesture
I hope so
I gotta talk about it at the end
of any other videos we do too
Just gotta campaign for it
My reaction is that it's ready to go
I haven't tweeted about the Kickstarter at all
I've been meaning to
I'll do my part
I'm doing my part
Good
I'm extremely curious about
what will happen when the end of the month
comes around and people get their paychecks
as well as
there's always spikes
in the last few days when people are like
I wanna push to the next goal
The final push is
I know for a fact that some of the most excited people
are waiting for payday
because they want the higher tiers
I mean
you can donate
and then up your pledge later
That's true, nothing against that
You can
if you have 10 to chip in now
and you do that and then you get paid
and you're like hmm, money in my pocket
Better throw it at the PCP
You can go in and up your pledge
and choose a new tier and everything
When I gotta go update the whole
stretch goal section with the new
Digiteers and stuff
That's it anyway
How long is the PCP
a light novel gonna be?
It depends
I kept the first chapter short
just because it's free
It's easily digestible
and it's a nice start
of the journey
The second chapter
will have to be considerably longer
Just think of it this way
Every chapter will be multiplying
the number of characters
The sheer amount of time it takes
to even have one interaction
will naturally lengthen the chapters
by way of how many characters are involved
I wanna be written about
so get that to the
when am I coming in
like the last one or near the last one
I think you're the third
Next is Ben and I
Weird number
Not to spoil too much
but the idea is
generally that the first three chapters
each introduce two
people and then the last two chapters
will be the
you know, the actual
attempt to get our
shit together
Right
Epic journey
I kind of like
I was out with Munchie
yesterday and
he was just sort of offhandedly mentioned
that we were talking about new stretch goals
and so I'd come home and I
just find this whole
light novel
scheme just kind of like fully formed
and already in action
and I'm just like well, okay
I guess that's happening too
That's what happens when you're off the grid
I suppose
Yeah, out with no phone
God's barely even being alive at that point
Man, I'm not sure
I might not be able to stream without my phone
because my twitch account is like
after authenticated
You should just like
contact them and like try to tell them
that's gotta be a thing that happens
You should
take a little go to get in there
I bet they can help you out somehow
I think there's ways to
simulate
phone apps on your desktop
but I'm not sure that would work
for twitch authentication
Yeah, I don't know
I'll figure it out tonight I guess
Losing your phone fucking
sucks ass
It sure does
I bet it was Brad
Fucking Brad
When I saw
that the accounts had been hacked
my first thought was somebody found my phone
and got into the PCP account through it
Everybody thought
the death of the PCP
was gonna be like our content
going downhill
or all of us fighting each other and hating each other
but no, it's just losing access to all our fucking channel
No, it's just just Russian hackers
All in one fells
it's just like I'm just logged in
to these accounts
I mean you don't think that just being just logged in
is going to put you in danger
It seems like it's a pretty sophisticated
program
This was definitely very sophisticated
Never download anything
Don't download more RAM guys
Do not do it
It's not good
By the way, Ben, I forgot
Right in front of me, I have your package with your precious vape juice
that I need to check out
I know we've got a lot on our minds lately
but frankly I'm disgusted
Tell you what
I crave the juice
I will check if the mail is closed
If it is open, I will go immediately after we're done recording
If not, I'll do it tomorrow
I crave the Flav
Indeed
I understand
This is because of
weird draconian
laws put in place
about certain kinds
Have I explained this already?
I don't want to be redundant
I think in general
These are vape juices that they will no longer
sell in Massachusetts
I had to order them to send them to you
so you could send them to me
because vendors are
handcuffed
On YouTube, I'm pretty sure
in several places I've seen ads
and I think I was just listening so I wasn't watching
but I've heard that
they're trying to get kids addicted to flavored vape
You wouldn't buy a flavored cigarette, would you?
Say no to vape
It's untested and dangerous
Who wouldn't buy a flavored cigarette?
What the fuck are they talking about?
Something like that
Some of the people that came to
RFCKCon, like Smoke and or Vape
and elsewhere too
They talked to a bunch of people that are like
I was vaping but now I can't get them
so I'm smoking again
What the fuck?
Congratulations
It's almost like this was
the tobacco industry's plan the whole time
It's almost like
100%
It really makes you think
Surely the tobacco company would have
got in, tried to
worm and drizzle that way into this new thing
That's what I've heard
Well they probably want to destroy the old
Do own a lot of the vaping companies though
They must know
But they're going after Jewel
almost exclusively, right?
Isn't Jewel the one suffering the most from this?
I mean it's the biggest company so I would assume
They're just trying to get their biggest competition out of the way
And then
They don't care
They're making money from cigarettes anyways
They'll probably get into the market
as soon as Jewel is obliterated
Once they can buy it out
At least in the American market
I know they're putting all these regulations so the vapes
are in the same category and you can't do them
But cigarettes
They're falling off a cliff in terms of usage
nationwide as I understand it
This vaping was like hey
What if smoking didn't have to be a miserable
experience that you just got your nicotine
And then the rest was just
mediocre
Just a cool cloud
I enjoy smoking cigarettes a lot more than vaping
Well
You don't need any individual experience
It's not exactly the same
They have a slightly different appeal
That being said, when I had
access to vape
I completely quit smoking
After I hadn't smoked for a while
I was like, cigarettes disgusting
Gross
Are you still of that opinion?
No, I'm back on the analogs
And I hate it
You see what you've done vapes?
Thanks Charlie Baker
I don't know, like Marlboro NXT's
or Camel Crush or whatever
Type 2 Magnum Extra Large
Just like a few
I'm not like
Never been like a pack a day smoker or anything
But I wanted to end
Just call our mother
Tell her you're stepping into your fucking grave Ben
Just tell her with your own two words
It's a filthy habit
Especially for a star athlete
That's true, no doubt about it
How are you ever going to hit your 600 pound squat like this Ben?
How? Tell me how
It's not going to happen
The dreams
600 pound
It's doable
That's a reasonable goal
Reasonable
I personally
Spotted a guy in high school
Who was squatting 500 pounds
Was he going parallel?
I can't remember
I was too aroused by his wriggling muscles
I was distracted
If he went full parallel
That would be an impressive squat
I mean he looked like the kind of man
I want to look like
So honestly that's the only reason I work out
A high school boy
That's right
For the record I was younger than him at the time
To be clear about
What's going on here
So there I was 28 years old
Squatting teens
Spotting them at the gym
Just my usual haunt
If they're doing a cool 500
I mean
They're clearly able to consent
They know something
Nate aren't you
Are you 30 yet?
I'm 29 still
I'm creeping up there
I'm going to be dead
It's depressing
It's very depressing
Dab dab dab
There's just no hope for this world
I've basically given up on
Technology progressing
To me being immortal
It's fine we're all going to die really soon
The coronavirus is going to kill us all
Thanks China
I guess that's true
I started hearing about this coronavirus
Is that okay?
Are we good?
Short answer no
Long answer if you find out that it has
Arrived in your city
Don't go outside
That's what they said about
The flu
The chicken flu
The bird flu
It never amounts to anything
And everyone gets all excited
That's not true
Sometimes it amounts to something
It amounts to some amount of death
Ebola was bullshit
Ebola killed like 7 people
Coronavirus has so far
Killed at least 60 people
We know there to be
Hundreds of thousands of people infected
Most Chinese cities are locked down
It has come to America
It is spreading through Texas
It's in France, it's in Orange County
It's been identified somewhere in Virginia
With only one case
The place we're all going to
Excellent
Not that survival rate though
Thousands infected 60 dead
That's pretty good
That's not the survival rate
The infection lays dormant
In you for weeks on end
It's suspected that there are hundreds
Of thousands of people carrying it
Who don't know about it yet
Potentially in the air
It is very easy to get
And very hard to notice
If you have it
I'm asymptomatic
And if it's on simp
There are some light parts to this though
You can be immune to it
It mostly kills older people
People with weakened immune systems
We're finally getting rid of the boomers
Ben and Tom are vulnerable
Ben and Tom are going down
It's got to take out the boomers before the election
Go coronavirus
This is the final bid against Bernie
This is their last ditch attempt
The BNC is at the core of this guy
This is going to propel Bernie into office
Because only the young voters will be left
I guess that's true
Won't he be dead though?
I was thinking won't like all of the candidates
For the Democrats be dead
Yang just wins by default
Tulsi Gabbard is finally going to get her chance
Tulsi V. Yang
Tulsi V. Yang is all that's going to be left
Thank god, what a fucking future that would be
It's just going to be Pete, Pete Buttigieg
Oh right, that's right Pete
Who's going to vote for PM?
I'm just saying if Pete Buttigieg does the floss dance
At one debate he's got my vote
I'm glad Yang's polling above Pete
I mean it's not a huge accomplishment
It's a fucking joke
I certainly like Yang more
He seems more like a solid dude
Did you guys see how the other day
When there was that completely natural
Vote for Bernie hashtag
That was going around
That the next morning there was a
Obviously very planted and fake
I'm voting for Pete hashtag
If you were to click on it
Most of them were
I'm not hashtag voting for Pete
Because he's clearly a CIA plant
Like that's like
He's going to take our weed guys
I saw hashtag
Hot girls for Bernie
That's a powerful one
I'm all for Mommy Tulsi though
I'm all in on
Tulsi's too hot, she can't be president
She is too hot, it's weird
It's not right
Don't you want to be able to say
You jacked off to the president
Did you see the Stefan Mullen you tweet about Tulsi
He did it again
Did he do the eggs thing?
He did the egg thing
He's like, she's 38
Second marriage, no kids
Hope she thinks about having kids soon
Imagine how fun it would be to grow up in Hawaii
Times running out, ambition alone
Won't keep you company in old age
Oh, I mean
As always Stefan
Spot on analysis
But perhaps not the right
Timer plays
No, no this is it
He generated
A lot of buzz with the last one
So he's at it again
I totally believe that he did it
Knowing the kind of reception he gets
He knows what response the Taylor Swift one got
Yeah, no doubt
He's not stupid
I don't need
Okay, I put in some stats into
Likeability
As a normal person
He's like, I'm cashed and I don't need that anymore
Are you trying to say that calling
Taylor Swift a dead egger is an unlikable move
Cause that sounds fucking hilarious
Dead egger
To some, to the feeble minded
Yeah
He's a mad lad, there's no doubt about it
I think he's overreacting
Oh my god
I mean, you can't make an awit without a few dead eggs
Rewind that and play it back again
That was too good
If that's not the title of this episode
I don't know
Holy shit
Fuck
No, you can't title it, I don't want it to be spoiled
You know, that's a good point
So I got on Twitter today
This morning
And I see
Kobe Bryant died in a helicopter crash
That's a funny meme
That's real though
It did happen
I thought it was a meme because
Didn't LeBron just beat
His career score record
Like yesterday
I don't know bro
Basketball
I feel like yesterday I just happened to see
A trending hashtag
Because LeBron had just surpassed Kobe
In terms of overall career scoring
And then the next day Kobe explodes
I mean, does anyone know
What happened
Maybe someone intentionally
Murdered them, maybe he
Was this
I have no idea but like
As I pointed out in the chat
Somebody predicted this
Eight years ago
In a tweet that had shit tons of retweets and likes already
So I assume that
Maybe he's just a man who took a lot of helicopters
And people just thought this was going to happen eventually
I have no idea
I was saying
If this happened to Bill Burr, I would have understood it
Because he historically is
He flies helicopters, he loves helicopters
And Kobe is an enthusiast or used a much
But clearly
He is rich, no doubt about that
His daughter was in it too
Oh my god, are you fucking kidding me
No, yeah, him and his daughter were on the helicopter
Jeez, that's Christ
To me
That rules out the suicide
Because I don't think the man would kill his daughter
I'm just saying
Did he crash his own helicopter
Because he was so fucking mad about his American being beaten
Wait, wait, wait
He's so mad, like the specific emotion
Is he seething with the raid
I'll show you LeBron
He's on twitter
He sees the hashtag trending with his right
He's like darn it, just like veers into the ground
I believe towards despair
I don't think so
Probably not
I don't know who was flying it, I don't know anything
I don't think he was personally piloting it
I knew nothing about Kobe other than
He was a good basketball player
He had a good smile, seemed like a good chap
Rest in peace, bro
I'm just a little embarrassed
Because I saw a tweet from Misanthropony
Of all people who was just like
Boy, sure is sad that Kobe Bryant died
In the helicopter crash, I thought it was a joke
About his record being beaten, I'm like
Classic
Classic map, classic irreverence
Yeah, so he gave that a like
Turns out
I mean, to be fair
I probably would have assumed that as well
If I hadn't seen it from a news source
Like when it came on right
Boy LeBron
You really got egg on your face now
Should have held off
beating that record
For shame
Have you no sense of decency, sir
Rest in peace
Rest in power, Kobe
That's all I got
I don't know anything else about Kobe
I guess fortunately for myself
Since I don't have to feel sad
Fair
I want to talk a little bit
About San Gatsunolain
The shogi boy anime
Because I've been watching the second season
And it's beautiful and great
And
I have
In conjunction with my brother
HGB guy
Who you can find on YouTube and he makes weird videos
Go check him out lol
He does a lot of woodworking stuff
And builds chairs now
He literally lets chairs
And
He is like
He has the tools and the manpower
I think what we're doing together
I've told him about this anime
We're both watching it
And we're gonna make our own shogi board
So that we can click
The pieces on the little thing
Do you have any desire to actually learn
How to play or just to click the pieces down?
I think
It's gonna be like a solid
3 hours of clicking the pieces
But then we might learn
I actually learned how to play shogi
When I was a young man
It's really not that much more complicated
Than normal chess
Except that like
I played chess for 2 years
It's not like go at all
Go is the insanely complicated one
This is
But shogi is like
Shogi is more like chess
Shogi does have more
I think shogi does have like a multitude
More like possibilities
Than chess though
The pieces can evolve like in checkers kind of
So that's a big factor
I tried to learn it in high school
I printed out like a set on paper
And cut out pieces
Good to know that shogi is stealing
Both of you
Obviously need to watch
Since you actually know anything about shogi
I know a little bit
Show ever
I kind of wanted to watch
I read much of the akagi manga
Which is obviously about gambling mahjong
I do not understand the rules of mahjong
One fucking bit
And I had no idea
And I think it actually did hurt my enjoyment
Because they're trying to be like
Oh, he's got like a shitty hand
And they're like misleading you for when it's revealed
He actually turned it into a really good hand with these moves
But because I don't understand the difference between the two
I'm like fine
So they make it very clear
Through
Like visual aid and
You know mind narration
Of certain characters
To make it like
Very easy to follow along
I have no idea what's going on most of the time
Mostly because shogi
Looks at a glance impossible
To understand because they're all like
Japanese characters on the things
Right, if you don't know that, sure
So like even if I'm learning a little bit
In the brief moments where they show the board
From top down view
And you're supposed to
You know if you know shogi
You might be able to see what's going to happen
They spell it out
So nothing like goes over my head
And I can follow along fine
It's just so fucking
Good of a show in general
It's not like
I would compare it a little bit to
I mean my anime
And manga like knowledge
Is lacking but
I shield 21, Nate
It has that same sort of
It's one of my faves and bends as well I think
Just in terms of like making a
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
In terms of making a show about a sport
Really good
No the racist part was my favorite part Ben
But yeah
I remember that
It's pretty good racism as racism
It's not like the same sort
Biological essentialism Ben
It's not the same sort of
It's just black people's muscles
Can never be great athletes
Sorry again please
It's not exactly the same sort of
Show in any like
Train montage thing but like
I don't know
Is it racist to say another race
Is better than yours
Well I mean
It depends really what you mean by the word better
In that context cause I mean
Is it racist to say
I think I believe Inuits are better
At surviving in cold temperatures
Is that right I mean maybe
By some definitions
The thing about I Shield 21 is that
It's like the moral
Is not like like the white guy
Is mad that like the black guy was
Like a better athlete than him but the moral
He learns to get over that though
It kinda comes down to like
It's not like oh well you know
You just gotta you know everyone
Everyone has a great chef
A great chef can come from anywhere
It's uh oh black people are actually just
Better athletes
I mean look it's true
Look at the NBA bro
I mean there's been
People who have said things like that
Throughout history you know
Like Hitler
Sure
I mean the message at the end is like
Despite the natural
Genetic advantage that at least Panther has
That yes is heavily associated with black
People's muscles in those words
It's like Sena
Sena is gonna just try hard
Sena has his own
It's a similar
Sort of
Thing where like sometimes
You'll never reach the top but you gotta keep going
It's just also happens to be about race
And that's what makes it weird
It's pretty weird
I like that part in Song God's No Lion
Where they were like despite being
Really high intellect east Asians
With those damn Askenaji Jews
With their higher percentage of IQ
We just can't compete against them damn it
So close
What are Askenaji Jews
Ashkenazi
I actually don't know exactly what the difference is
But they're the ones that everyone says are
Smart
I just know it from people saying that
That's all I know, I couldn't tell you
You guys know Sean, he's a bread tube guy
He didn't really
Fuck off, Sean's great
He's really good, he did a video
Fuck you, he did a video about
The bell curve
The book, the bell curve, you know that one
The one that's like
You know intelligence is heritable
And it just goes into how
Right
It's not just
People being like oh you can't say that
Like that's unacceptable
Science, you can't
The book, no the book like set out
With a deliberate agenda to push a certain narrative
It doesn't
In a weird way
That isn't like
Scientifically rigorous
It's a good video
If you say so
I've heard arguments to the contrary
From people like Sam Harris
He said that it was pretty well sourced
And good, I could be wrong
Sam Harris keeps bad company
And I don't trust him
Don't actually know anything about Sam Harris
But whatever
For his religious stuff
And his
Not determinist
But like self control
Self determination
Yeah, versus determinism
Free will, sorry free will was the word I was looking for
Free will aka that thing that's not real
Exactly
Exactly correct
But it seems like it is so it's almost as good
About something that's no lying
I was going to say that like
I was surprised to hear from Digi's
Video recently about like the best anime of the last decade
That was his number one which was you know pretty cool
And I really want to check it out
I watched episode one
And loved the animation and I remember
Vividly my favorite scene was when he like
Comes home to that family
And everything goes from dark to like warm and fuzzy
And so
That's like
All the girls are so fluffy and glowing
That aspect of the show
I think is one of its most like divisive
Elements because there are some people
Who they don't like the
The tone shifts
Like the way that it goes from like so extreme
That is the point
That's literally the point
I love that shit because it's the way that he
You know he's like completely in his own head
Just like all these dark dots
Swirling and it's like the super dark color palette
And then he enters that house and it's like
You know it's like he literally can't
Be the person you would normally be
That's like having a conversation on twitter
And then meeting up
With your friend in real life
Oh my god yeah it's exactly like that
It's literally like when I get up the internet
And do anything else
I love how much the show
Is
It's about his growth
In ways that like
A normal
Thing about a guy who's good at
Ex sport or whatever
It usually isn't about
He's a
Prodigy or like a middle schooler
Like a professional
And
My first thought is like
Okay so this is gonna be about him
Meeting like shogi players
And then beating them and then training
And beating them and one after the other
But it's so much not really about that at all
It's all about him
And all of the stuff
That surrounds shogi in his life
Yeah
Nate did you ever watch honey and clover
No I just saw a little bit of it here and there
It's the same author so it's very similar
It does look similar
Update on the brad situation
Brad Garlinghouse has been streaming
For three hours
He is up to 3.4k
Live viewers
That can't be right
It was definitely up before 12 when I woke up
Maybe he started
He did
It got taken down and restarted at one point
Brad just killed it
The adsense after this all comes back
Hopefully
I would assume not because adsense
Is tied to your google account
So probably the adsense for this will go to
Whatever
Google account the channel is tied to
Anything done during this time
I would estimate so like all of my videos
That are still getting views here and there
Probably I'll go into his account
If it's just like one month's worth of pay
That ain't gonna break the bank
A couple of adsense money
Brad Garlinghouse is a spine
As we go on
I hope
Obviously it's fucked up
Please give it back Brad
Come on now
We're all gentlemen here
We're both businessmen Brad
You and I we can work something out
As I pull back
The trigger on my revolver
Directly at the back of his head
Just log into the account
Transfer it on over
Peacefully
Shall we go to voicemails
I'm ready
It's already been over an hour
That was a fast hour
We had a lot to talk about today
Time goes by fast
And despite everything bad going on right now
It is kind of fun to talk about
Oh there was one thing I was gonna say
Which was just like
I am so excited to play the victim card
I cannot wait to get out there
Mix it up
We have some victim status to cash in on
Oh boy
You just brought up something that I do think is
Kind of an interesting topic
Something I don't understand
About people on the internet
Is everybody takes themselves
So fucking seriously
And their opinions so seriously
And I really
I have to feel like if you are
Capable of taking all this stuff so seriously
You must not realize how bad things
Really are
Did you be fucking you just kill yourself
Like if I took
If everything that
Happened that I found out about
That was terrible like affected me
To the extent that it should
I would just be dead in an afternoon
Like there's so much
Fuck shit on this planet earth
And I just spend all day thinking about it
And the only way to get through it
Is to just make it funny for yourself
I mean we've talked about this before
How like I don't understand
How people can say like oh you can't joke about that
It's like well then how am I supposed to deal with it
But like I seriously think those people
Must just not realize like
How bad things really are
I mean there's one like
There's one operation going on there
Which is like in your life
You selectively can decide
What it is you choose to spend your time
Thinking about and dwelling on
And you could be like a mother Teresa
And choose to dedicate your whole life
To like individual suffering
Like getting down to the
Made in Australia style from Demon Souls
And taking all the filth of the entire world
On your shows to like try to help
I mean what I'm saying is like
Cause I feel like I do go out of my way
To find out like what bad is happening
And it's not that I don't care
It's that like acting serious about it
Will kill you
Like the stress, the depression
The just like the thinking
Like just thinking about it
It's like fuck it's like
I don't make jokes about it
I don't know how you could deal with it
If you literally were like paying attention to it
Like just thinking about what's going on right now
It's like we you know
Are in conflict in the Middle East
Still there's missiles
Going around even I think today
Like Iraq or some
There was missiles landing
By our bases in Iraq or whatever
Who by the way had like a
Million man protest to try to get us out of their country
Which of course we're ignoring
Reporting on
You've got the coronavirus
You've got the Epstein scandal
Still going on
No one knows where Gisela and Maxwell is
Still like I mean it's just like there's so much stuff
I and again
Like if you don't joke about it
I really don't think that
Anybody who knows how much is going wrong
Could survive taking it
As seriously as the way people take the few things
They do care about on Twitter
Here's my hypothesis
I think it's these people do know the world
Is fucked up so they choose to ignore it
And just try and delve into media and stuff
And so when small little infractions
Happen in the media that's their escapism
They blow a gasket because they have no
That's probably true
To deal with conflict
That's true on all sides
The people I see who act like babies
About that kind of content
Are the people who seem to have the least perspective
On like how fucked things are
So I think you might be on to something there
I think these people are sheltering themselves
And so they don't even realize
How bad it really is
And they're complaining about shit that doesn't matter
Like I mean considering like the
Hacks and stuff going on right now
I mean for me I think I'm a pretty
I'm a pretty open-eyed guy
I mean in general I know I've got my own perspective
And all that stuff I'm not thinking about the wars
Going on every second of the day and all that stuff
But like when it comes to something like this
I try to just gather all the information
And I'm like okay
The worst case scenario
The worst case scenario here
Is that like these channels are gone forever
I'm like okay if that happens
You know it's not like everybody who is interested in my work
Is gone from the world
You know I'll rebuild and like hey
I'm not gonna lie I think about things like
Historically I remember to this day
Like moments when like Dr. Wolf's channel got taken down
He came back and like doubled a sum count in a day
I mean hey there's probably some kind of silver lining
I didn't know that happened to Dr. Wolf
I mean that was like early days
I think about that as an example
Like Mumki Jones when his channel got taken down
They come back and obviously later on
Things got worse for him but early on
He did experience some stuff like this
So like in the grand scheme of things
Like in my overall arc of life
Of just trying to survive doing YouTube
Like is this a setback?
Sure
But will I be able to one like make it funny
And possibly you know
Entertain people with a funny story that happened
Probably, probably
To just sit around and be upset
I got all that out of the way
Like when I first noticed but now I'm over it
Remember when Mumki's channel got taken down
And he went around talking about how his life was over
And got addicted to drugs and started cheating on his girlfriend
And now his channel is up to 150,000 subscribers again
What a fucking pussy
You know that's a pretty good example
You know whatever you say about Mumki it's all fine
But I mean when we all saw that we were like
I mean yeah Mumki this is really bad
That's true but like this seems
Too dramatic a reaction
Masterson built him a website
Like what the fuck I would be
I would love to have a website built by Dick Masterson
I mean you know I suppose I could say
Like what position am I in to judge someone
Who's lost their website
Except that at this very moment
He has lost multiple YouTube channels
And shit
So I don't know
Not even just yours but collaborative products
No like all of yours too
Whoops sorry guys
And thank God you guys are all
So far
But Nate the thing is we're actually having a secret meeting
Once it's over to vote on kicking you
Sorry
Obviously we're just waiting until Radcon
When we have you in person
Let me just say alright that makes sense
You should wait until after Radcon
Until the money gets paid out cause right now
It's all going to my bank
So like you're just gonna want to wait until
Don't say that Brad's always listening
He'll go for that next
Ah shit
There it all goes guys
There goes the kick started too
At least it seems like
Think about this though
Like this thing was on your computer
It could have affected more than your YouTube channel
That's what I said
That's why I said to reformat immediately
Yeah and I'm going to reformat
I would have done it already
I don't want to have to redo months
Of work so
I'm currently using other machines
Just gonna redo years of savings when his bank account's emptied
I mean maybe
I'm changing my passwords I'm doing all the stuff I should do
But
It seems like the one
Consider the fact these guys approach me
Through an email they're like hey
You're a known YouTuber we want you to sponsor this video
Seems like their main target was
YouTube and obviously they could have put other stuff in there
But like you know it seems like
That's the only thing I've noticed any effectiveness with
The only thing that like
Really could have been targeted the way they did it so
Overall I'm not too worried about the rest of my life
I don't want to be destroyed or anything
So I guess we'll see
Just the important part
Just kind of like the main livelihood
Thrust I mean that you know
I'll survive
It's almost
A little bit relieving that the stream
Went up because we at least know what their goal was
Up until that point
There were days of just like well
All the accounts have been stolen we don't know why
Or for what fucking purpose
That's true and considering like I said
Before like the stories that people have gotten
Their accounts back after like maybe two weeks or so
I mean it's already been you know
Three four days hopefully
You know we're already well into that timetable
I don't know I guess we'll see
It's reassuring that you're talking to a human
Yeah fine
Like you start with a bot
You get a ticket created and then they put you through via email
To what appears to be an actual human
Alright well it's 444
So in the name of Jay-Z let's listen to voicemails
Yeah sounds good
Alright so okay so again fucking
The damn bot is broken so we gotta listen to him
By clicking on them but if you want to leave voicemails
Go to the speak pipe link down below
Which miraculously is still
Active and people can submit voicemails to
Even though we haven't paid and we're way beyond
The total capacity
I can't explain it and neither can anyone else
But we're gonna listen to him here so leave your voicemails
There
Alright first one is from cringe
You guys have it pulled out?
Yeah are we good?
Oh you got it
Oh okay on the count of three
Let's all click on cringe here we go
One, two, three
Hey PCP all this radcon 4
Creative hype has me
Wanting to try and put myself out there
In the form of video game streaming
Thing is I'm an introverted motherfucker
And last night on my very first
Ever stream within an hour
I had 200 of my facebook
More me friends watching my stream
Hopping in chat
Now the thing is
I am a total cringe lord
I don't know how to deal with this many people
And I was just wondering how all of you do it
Gib what's your advice
You seem more the introverted type like myself
How do you put yourself out there
For the internet people
I'd really like to try and get myself out there
And make a hobby out of this if nothing else
No monetary goals in mind
Any input would be highly valued
Thanks for your time guys
What the fuck introvert has 200 facebook friends
If you're getting 200 viewers
That's like
You're like the top 1% of twitch
Yeah that's staggering
I am games rarely broke 100
Viewers in its entire existence
On youtube I was able to get
Significantly more streams than I
Or viewers than I did on there
Maybe facebook is also way better
Was he streaming on facebook?
Yeah I think so
Speaking personally
I have 79 friends on facebook
So literally not enough for this to happen
He was asking you
I clicked the thing but it took a while to load
So I was out of sync
So I may have missed
What was his question exactly
He said he's a cringe lord
And he's introverted
But he did a stream yesterday
Got 200 viewers on facebook it seems
But he feels I guess nervous about it
Cause he got more people than he expected
He was asking for advice
I don't know how to make a hobby out of it
If you have like a big chat
You can kinda just ignore the chat
I mean not completely
But you can kinda just let the chat interact with itself
For like long stretches
For significant stretches
You don't have to worry too much about it
I mean in terms of like being introverted
And putting yourself out there anyway
It's just a matter of
Doing it a lot of times
I mean if you listen to like
Early episodes of the pcp
I am like a
Even more meek than now
I'm still like not the loudest person
But like in general
I've improved a lot
In terms of being able to speak
Not just on podcasts
But like in conversations
So yeah just do a lot of streams I guess
It's interesting that he chose
The word introvert
Cause like I would consider myself an introvert
I don't think of streaming
As talking to people
It's just talking to myself in front of people
That might be why
It's easier for me
The abstraction of the fact that
It's just names that I don't know who they are
Makes it not feel like
I don't feel like I'm public speaking
Yeah maybe he knows all these people
That would definitely be a different feeling
I mean yeah I would not want to stream
To what he said
Quote normie friends on Facebook
First of all get rid of these fucking normie friends
What the hell
I mean if they're
If you don't like them
If they are donating get them the fuck out of there
Yeah this is a pay to play community
Here on my Facebook guys
Gotta turn those players into payers
Oh no
Well
Wail is over
You clearly like doing it
Here's just a plan you can use
I would say the more you do it the more comfortable you'll be
So that's fine
Like a little bit of make a plan for yourself
Like know what you're gonna do
How long you're gonna do it you can
Post ahead of time if you want people to know
Then like it's a known quantity
You start and stop at a time
There's no pressure on you to do more
And you can just relax
Interact with the chat as much as you please
And just get the experience under your belt
And you'll be fine
If there's too many people watching you're already doing something right
I think the most important thing is that
You just started it's not gonna be amazing
That being super entertaining
Is part of the process
Practice is gonna make you much better at speaking
You're gonna get a feel for not only
How you like interacting on stream
But what your audience responds to it's a give and take
Between like the viewers and you
And you'll just kind of like
Become more comfortable with it
I just think the best thing to do is just keep pushing onward
I mean Kobe Bryant
Wasn't a great helicopter pilot in his first day
Oh
Shit
Too soon dude
I'm sorry Kobe
He's dunking in heaven
Alright let's go to the next one
Even I feel bad about that one
I haven't even absorbed that fact
It's so weird that I actually haven't in my life
It is very strange it feels like a family guy
Skate more than like a real
Some people joke to cope
Alright let's go to the next one
This is a camel quandary
Is our next voicemail
Alright on the count of three
Here we go one two three
Hey PCP I'm gonna try and keep
This short and sweet
As I'm sure you're well aware
Camels are quite adept at dispensing
Bile great distances
They spit as a self defense mechanism
What kind of on command for their amusement
If you were to have a camel
Genetically modified to dispense
Any liquid in this manner
You so desire what liquid
Would that be and why
For the purposes of this exercise
Camel must be all green
And the liquid selection
Will not affect the camel's well being
Let's say you chose something like lava
The camel could then spit the lava
And it would not
Catch on fire from the inside
Curious to know your thoughts on this
Coconut milk
Anything keto is fine
Come
No doubt
Camels already do that
I guess I'd take huel
Just squirt huel everywhere
I don't want to catch fucking camel spit
We all go straight to like liquid
We want to consume from its mouth
How can we use this camel to nourish ourselves
It just saves money dude
It just saves money
My choice is of course weed
That's not a liquid
It can be a liquid
The oil, the vapable oil
I was trying to remember
The word, the oil was the word
I was looking for
Start hurting camels, you just run around with buckets
Trying to catch spit
I was going to say stevia
Cause that's just expensive
Stevia
That's also a salad, isn't it
You can get it liquid
Okay, okay
Just pop open one of my fucking seltzers
I want it to be a little sweeter
I've got it, water
They've already got their own water
Like if I'm on the desert in a camel's spit
And water, that's great
Aren't they already spitting water?
It's spit though
You can't drink that
If it was like pure clean drinking water
Pure clean drinking water isn't bad
We should get
In Dungeons and Dragons
There are a bunch of different dragon types
Everyone has a different type of breath weapon
These are probably like their younger cousins
Speaking of Dungeons and Dragons
I made a tweet a few days ago saying
I was like getting into critical role
Like hardcore cause I am, I'm addicted
And a bunch of people have responded
To that tweet saying do D&D at Radcon 4
Make it a stretch go we pay for it
Dude, oh yeah, oh I talked about this
I thought we should play the Chuck Tingle
Pen and paper RPG
Oh my god
A live stream of a D&D
Session is a pretty good idea
I mean that's what critical role is
It doesn't even need it
We could like make it with good production
Every now and then I have this idea
Man we should do like a PCP D&D game
Or something and I absolutely think we should do it
I'm not as interested
In doing D&D as
So you guys don't know about this
But Don Jolly, my friend
Has a role playing game that he made
Called Gorefest
That's really fucking cool
And there's a video of him doing a live Gorefest session
They actually got a venue in New York City
To play a live Gorefest
And it's basically a game
That is meant to emulate
Like 80's action movies
But it's very streamlined
It's way less
Rule intensive
The way it plays
Is how we would want to play D&D
So I think we should look into doing
Gorefest
It definitely does not have to be
D&D specifically
Like nobody cares
In general though
Okay
It's a good idea
Is there like a GM for Gorefest as well?
Yeah you need a GM
I was talking
My friends IRL
Are big into tabletop games
And my friend was telling me
He told me about the chuck tingle
The tingle verse pen and paper game
Which sounds pretty funny
There's also one, this is an official thing
There is a Wendy's
Yes there is
And you gain bonuses in combat
By eating Wendy's menu items
You do
Like literally in real life doing that?
Yes, in real life
So we should definitely get on that
I really hope there's a Wendy's near Radcon
I'm gonna link you guys
The video of the live Gorefest
It was about the mission to kill Jeffrey Epstein
For assassins
Had to compete
Regardless of whether I want
To play this game
That does sound good
You gain bonus XP if you can recover the flight logs
Alright
Let's go to our next voicemail already
We got a bunch
Number 3 is just fan meetup please
Are you ready to click?
Yeah
I'm ready
On the count of 3
Yes
Hello PCP
A couple episodes ago there was mention
Of a possible fan meetup during Radcon 4
And I was wondering
If you guys were still having that idea
To fit that into the busy
Radcon 4 schedule
I know you guys already have so many
Backer
Rewards
But I'm sure there are so many people
Who would love to meet you
I personally would have to buy a plane ticket
To a place to stay
But I would do that in a heartbeat
If it meant that I got to meet my favorite content creators
So I'm wondering if that was
The idea you guys were having
Thank you
There you go
We were talking about it
In the discord group
Our discord
I think it's a good idea
It is a good idea
I didn't weigh in at the time but I like the idea
I had reservations mostly because
Of potential
Problems with
I don't know
People flying out and finding a place to say
And then the weather
We don't have a venue and it's
It's lame
I saw that conversation
And Munchie was talking
I basically agree with Munchie 100%
If we just
Say a time and a place
It's up to them to figure it out
Let me just say
There was talk
For Munchie of
Letting everyone into the house
I don't think we should have the meetup
At the house
As long as we don't do that
That's against our house rules
We couldn't do that anyway
I have an actual point I can make
Against that
We all really like that idea
We would definitely put some big asterisk
Go at your own risk
We cannot promise a good time
We can promise that
I guess around the grand scheme of things
Every child is born with
Only a guarantee of suffering and nothing else
We also cannot promise that people
Will even enjoy the content from Radcon
For
At least they know from our
History what our content
Whereas if they were actually at Radcon
They know what a bunch of disgusting degenerate losers
Who don't do anything cool we all are
And how we selectively pick
And falsely represent our real lives
I do think the idea of a fan meetup
Is a good idea
Where Radcon For is taking place
In Virginia
I don't think it will be
That fun of a place to have a meetup
But
I do think it would be a good idea
After
Whenever the next Radcon time rolls around
To do what you guys were saying earlier
And literally do a convention
Like get an actual space
I think we can do both
I don't think being in Virginia beach
Is like a problem
Like any place we wanted to do it
Would present its own
Logistical challenges and I mean this is when
The most of us are going to be in one place at one time
It seems like a natural time to do it
I'm just saying
A meetup at Radcon For
Will be
Potentially pretty cool
And most likely expensive
For whoever needs to get there
What do you guys think we would do
At this Radcon
I had one thought
Meet us at the park
Literally
I just thought it might be fun
For example to have a volleyball game
Or something like that
That was literally what I thought would be fun
It's just an excuse to hang out
With people
And maybe get some cool footage for Victor
Here's an idea
That might work
Which would be if we did it
So where Radcon
Is actually happening
Is not technically in Virginia beach
It's in Norfolk
But Virginia beach
The actual ocean front
Is a gigantic huge commercial
Tourist beach
That is just a line of about 200 hotels
So
And the hotel on the very end of that
Is fairly cheap
So if everybody was going to stay there
And we did it at the actual beach
Which means we come to them
That would be good
There's literally volleyball nets
They're already set up
That sounds great
I love the ocean
We marched down the beach in a giant mob
And we protest legalized
PCP
You stole
The rfckcon slime protest idea
I will say
For slime
But we can do it again
The ocean front is crawling with cops
So I would be a little bit
Not trying to draw too much attention to ourselves
Did I mention that
The slime protest
The cops actually rolled up
And stared at us
And left
In the first week
That Pokemon Go came out
Everyone was hanging around at UC
The Cincinnati University
Everybody was there
The cops rolled up
And just kept on going
There was an unbelievably large amount of people
In this one little entrance
Where there was like four polka stops
Directly next to each other
Understandably so
The cops are good boys
If we did it at the ocean front
It would be reasonable
Because even if people weren't just coming to see us
It's a tourist location
There's automatically things
I will say though
Have money if you're going to do this
This girl right here
I'll take care of myself
I want to hang out
If they know going
With their eyes open
That's cool
We don't really have to do
Or provide much of anything else
Beside we will be there
That's the main thing
The only thing I'm worried about
If it rained that day
If someone goes wrong
We'll just go inside
And let people know where we're at
Or something
We'll probably do something like that
As long as we're at the ocean front
There will be plenty of places we can bus
It's a place that is designed
To host large numbers of tourists
The Virginia Beach beach
Is it okay to film
I assume it would be
With Victor's camera and everything
I filmed music videos there
If you want to see the spot I'm talking about
Watch the sad boy
It's all filmed at the ocean front
Because we could make
A lot of footage from that
Be part of the OVA
Because that stretch goal is reached
That's exactly what I was thinking
Where would we film those things
Synergy
Be an extra in the OVA
But don't come if you have money problems
If you're interested
We're not responsible for anything
Should this be a stretch goal
I don't know
I think we should do it
We're already pretty
Kitted out on stretch goals
My fear is
That people who would donate more
Will instead buy plane tickets
Maybe we'll be like backers only
I think it should be a sad thing
Nothing's going to stop people
Nothing could stop them from just showing up
It's true
We will work this out later
We'll keep you posted on
What the fuck's the deal people
We'll get back to you
Let's go to our next voicemail
Which is I'll Die
On getting a Hewlett sponsorship
Ready to click everybody
Good to go
Count of three
Nate, if you're really serious about
Getting this Hewlett sponsorship
Then you need to do one vital thing first
And that stops giving you free advertising
You always talk about
How you love the product
And you think it's great
And that they need to give you a sponsorship
But why would they start paying you
To do something that you are already doing
You're already an advocate for the company
That would just be a loss for them
And would make your message seem a little less trustworthy
Because now you're getting paid to say it
So by this logic
You should express
No positive feelings about a product
Until you're sponsored
I think that's probably true
For monetary gain
There's some credibility to that
But I do think that if
Your audience sees how much you hype
Fuel and then they actually
Did something for you
The audience would respect that
That's true
I know for a fact
Many people have gotten into Hewlett
Due to my love of the product
I literally did free promo
For fucking Kona Grill BBQ sandwiches
And they eventually sent me
Two $25 gift cards to Kona Grill
Which I have not been able to use
Because they shut down
Almost all the Kona Grill
It was that that put them over the edge
That cut into their profit margins
They were like
We're gambling it all on these
Two $25 gift cards
Also the nearest one
To me is in Baltimore
The one that we've been to so
Maybe one day
But fucking if
Okay, so perhaps I will
Tamp down on the Hewlett
Praise and up my attempts
To actually reach someone at the company
Until something gives one way or another
Alright, next one
Next one is simply called
I Hate Teenagers
Teenagers, it says
I might have misspelled that
Let's call them Teenagers
Alright, the count of three, here we go
One, two, three
My wife for her job
Works with teenagers
And so that means
Far more often than I would like in my life
That I have to be around teenagers
And I fucking hate them
It sounds miserable
As a bunch of guys in their late 20s
Or early 30s
Who are constantly surrounded by annoying
Teenagers in their fan base
How the fuck do y'all do it
How do I spend more than 15 minutes
Around these awkward fucks
Trying to blow my brains out
It helps that we're
Interfacing with them through the internet
Where you don't have to deal with this much of it
I think we might have to cancel that meetup guys
I mean a lot of the people at RFKanK
Were like late teens
Like probably
A good third of them were under 20
Or something
And you know what, it wasn't that cringe
It wasn't very cringe
Obviously there are plenty of teenagers
Munchy was a teenage
Was like 12 when we fucking first met him
Yeah, something like that
Teenagers who like
I think there are certain teenagers who just like
And I mean everybody says this
But they get it in their head
That they just know everything already
When you interact with those people
And they're like
I think there are some teenagers
Who, yeah, they're smart
And you can have a conversation with them
But they kind of expect
That they will not know
As much about the world as you do
As an older person
And when you talk to a teenager who doesn't seem
To think that that would be the case
It's so frustrating
It's like how can you not understand
How little perspective you have
Because you're a fucking in school
Like it's, being in school
Is totally different from living life
Outside of school
You learn so much just from
Like the first second
You're not in that controlled environment
That your perspective is radically different
And so the moment you have
You're responsible for paying your own bills
And like maintaining your own place of residence
And getting all your own food
Like I feel like I became an adult
The second that was my responsibility
And not until that point
Which was at like age like 24
Or 25 or something
Pretty much when I moved out on my own
Well, really it was when my parents moved out
Of my house
I think humans are kind of like beasts of burden
And by applying a burden to them
They actually rise to the challenge
And grow and evolve as beings
And that this is kind of a helpful
State of being for the species to be in
To some degree
I just solved the case
I just cracked it wide open
By the way, I was going to say about teenagers
The other thing about that is
We always say that Munchie was an outstanding teenager
And still is
He's 18 or 19 now
So still a teenager
But Munchie, as long as I've known him
Has been way ahead of the curb
In terms of like other people his age
I mean his intellect is astounding
It is substantial
And even if it's not like raw
I don't know if it's like an IQ or whatever
It's his initiative is like the real X factor
Like responsibility
We're talking about a guy who figured out how to
Not need to attend high school
So I don't know what the magic he pulled
But he clearly knew way the fuck
More than I did when I was his age
Just take for example
Our discussion about having a meetup
At Radcon 4
For example, that girl who called
I don't know how old she is, maybe she's in her 20s
Maybe she's 30s, I don't fucking know
But it could easily see her being a teenager
Along with lots of other people who might want to show up
And also take the people at RFC K-Con
Or RFK-Con, whatever
All those people are pretty young, a lot of them fly in
But what did it actually take them
To that point, they didn't just wake up
And let mommy and daddy do everything
They had to be involved in a community
Actively participate
Find out about events, arrange to be there
At a time and date and make all this happen themselves
Only the ones that were capable of that
Actually made it
It's making it to the end of the fucking Naruto
Chunin exam, if you survive to the end point
You have needed out the week
In high school I would not have been
Equal to the task of
Scheduling my own trip
And paying for my own plane to get no fuck
We were babies
I'm thinking about all the times I went to convention
It wasn't until pretty much when I was forced
To drive Ben and DeVue to Atlanta
Because Victor flaked
That was the first time I ever did
Any kind of major travel
Where I was in charge
I had to make any decisions at all
And even then it was just to drive
But from that
That experience opened my world considerably
I traveled the whole country after that
I was scared to drive
I mean you hated driving up to that point
Or sometime around there
It's not scared of me anymore
Because I just do it every day
One of the things that makes me less
Worried about who should I be
To even get here
Means you have a baseline level of competence
And it's like these people are going to be
At least kind of decent
Hopefully they have a baseline level of competence
A lot of the teenagers
Or involved have already crossed
At least a few of these thresholds
If we do end up having a meet up at Radcon
And you are a teenager just know
That we probably will at some point
Want to go into the bars
That litter the shoreline
Of Virginia Beach
And you will not be able to follow
You can go into the bar
You just can't order any drinks
I mean they're not going to ID you at the door or anything
I mean some places they don't let you to go
Most of them are restaurant bars
You're in a tourist area
They expect you to go with family
That's fair
For the guy's call though
His question was like
My wife works with kids
She's probably a teacher or something
Those kids had to cross zero hurdles
To be involved in your life
That's the problem here
There's no skill floor
No
It goes all the way down
So
I would just say just minimize contact
That's all I would do
Divorce is your only option
Consider
You know I would say
Just try to find the ones that are at least
Kind of decent
It's me or the children
Repeat after me
Me or them
Next voice
This one's simply called where
And let's click on it
One, two, three
Where is the Tarantino podcast
I wanted
I mean the Tarantino cast
Whatever
Nate you promised that there will be more episodes
Than one
We'll record the next one
If you don't want to
Watch the next one
And I'll be like a backer
Behind the scenes content
Like we did for
Pulp Fiction
And then we'll do a podcast
There we go
That's a great idea
On a somewhat similar
I think it would be cool
If I made my
Long awaited debut on the Poe D
Cast at Radcon
I'll finally catch up at one piece
That would be great
We'd love to have you
So where are you now
Oh god
Did you make it to Big Mom yet
Yeah I'm on
So you're in the realm of things that have been covered
On the Poe D
They've met up with Jinbae again
I think I'm maybe like a hundred chapters to go
Before I'm
That's not bad
Wow it only just occurred to me
A potty cast has been going for like three years
Hasn't it
Long fucking time on the potty cast
Yup
It's a good time
Well Ben we would love that
Fuck it for one piece
Who knows
Maybe five more years until the series ends
I guess we'll see
That sounds like a great idea
I think like three years ago
Or so Oda said
In five years
He might have said five or seven
The arcs are getting longer
I'm not just imagining that
The arcs are definitely getting longer
Dressrosa was the longest of all time
Wano was already I believe
Among the longest ever
So they're even longer than Skypea
Dude Skypea is
Pretty long but compared to like
Dressrosa it's like nothing
Looking back on it
And Dressrosa was like the worst arc too
Which is
Dressrosa isn't even bad all the way
Anyway let's go to the next one
I'm really excited for this one guys
So you thought that Steel on my channel was bad
Well I've got even more bad news for me
Here's Nate Bestman
This one's really gonna stain my reputation
But let's give it a listen
On the count of three
One, two, three
Listen buddy, only problem with that
It was just too long
Damn
That's the long
And short of it ladies and gentlemen
Alright let's go to the next one
Okay let's follow this up
With a powerful voicemail
From Homeless Ben
He left three
And I kept the two that got me to chuckle
So let's hear that
Okay first Homeless Ben
Saga begins on the count of three
One, two, three
And a pot to piss in while you're at it
A pot to piss in and a sink to shit it
If there's anything left over sure
These are the truly the two basic needs
On like Maslow's hierarchy
Those are the two lowest level ones
Please guys help him
Alright next Homeless Ben
It's technically part three but it's our next one
Alright on the count of three
One, two, three
Hey guys drunk Homeless Ben here again
Today I asked my brother
Nate for help but it was all a trick
As soon as he let me in his house
I took a shit in his sink too
That'll choke capitalism
The plan is going smoothly
Did he say the one more
Did he say the plan is going smoothly
That's right Ben
This is a narrative
I'm thinking that might not be the real Ben
Cause I don't think he would have left Nate's house without those fucking
Wait Ben already has the shoes
God damn it I fuck it all up
Let me tell you Ben
Those boots I got this Christmas
When we were together I saw you
I and my boots Ben
I didn't even want my boots
I have boots
Mom and dad were just dead set on buying us all boots
Even though I told them I do not need boots
Mom messaged me
And she was like Nate you want some boots
I was like I would love some boots
These are cool and so she got them
She was like oh how about Ben
I'm like I don't know what shoes he has
But like if you want to get him boots
Mom's fucking up this operation again
She's going to become redundant in the system
She wouldn't make the cut
She wouldn't meet the skill floor
To make it to Radcon 4
We should make a stretch to help our mom
Make it to Radcon 4
Pay for a chauffeur
Alright next one
Pancakes
Another Ben St. Yikes
I don't know exactly what that means
You typed it
Yeah but like there were colons
In suspicious places that like
Changed the meaning of the following words
You know how it is
One, two, three
Hey PCP
You won't believe it but I got myself into another little
Pickle here
So I was listening to the new PCP episode
Ironically of course
When I heard something coming from the trunk
I opened it up and it was the girl
And she said hey
It's really hard to breathe back here
Leave the trunk open
And I said what do you think I'm stupid or something
So I shoved her back in
And closed the trunk
And then shot it a couple times you know letting some air
Wrong story short
I just got back from taking a 6 feet hole
And I was wondering you know
If I should go to the funeral
Because I just met her
And I don't think I'm socially obligated to go
And it'd be total cringe
I have a met her parent right now
But
I look pretty cute from what I can tell from her phone
So what am I supposed to do
Oh and before I forget
I did find a wallet
It has Yang 2020 on it
With a Yang scratch down replaced with Bernie
So would you send it to my P.O. box
Send it to my P.O. box
Please, please return that kind sir
Right it was a saga
Grabbed a girl that's right thanks Pancakes
With update
No comment
Well I mean I guess he wanted advice
Go to the funeral and fuck the sister
Yeah that's yes
Do it on top of the open casket body
A guilty man would never show up
To his own victims funeral
So you'll be in the clear
That's true
That's so true
Get ready for a wacky situation where you two
The sister are making out over the dead body
Over the casket and then you're like oh no someone's coming
So you jump inside grab her
Close the casket on top of the two of you
And you get buried alive
And wacky hijinks ensue
Pretty wacky
The sax plays the whole time
That's right
The sister requested to be buried
With a little mini speaker that played the acuity sax
Oh like the two of them
As the casket being carried
They're both like horsed out
They're like burst out of the bottom and they start running around
As like they're chasing them
When they see this they're like oh hey now
Cut that out they shove the legs back in
They put it in the coffin in the whole new barriers
Yeah the happy ending
They're just like oh you're not getting away this time
We've had too many this week
Alright anyway let's go on to our next one
This is the number one
Hewle again on Hewle version
3.0 we've got a review coming in
Let's hear what the Hewle world is like today
On the count of three
One, two, three
Alright enough
Primary retardation aside
Hewle 3.0
My current review
After drinking some
Right now
Pretty solid
It's much smoother
I think the taste is also better
It's worth boys it's worth
Well there you go
Until I have a chance to taste it
If it's solid then how is he drinking it
Wait
It's powder god damn it
They have bars too though maybe he got the bars
He's got to mean
Like he said like the textures better
He's got to mean he's got to mean
I was doing a joke
I was rolling with the joke but then Nate
Took it totally seriously and it ruined everything
I just didn't understand I apologize
Get out of here Brad
He clearly stipulated no memes
No jokes, no japs on this voicemail
Hewle version 3 seems to be worth it
I have two bags of Hewle 3.0
You do?
I haven't had any
Cause I'm on keto and they're not keto at all
Why the fuck did you buy them
If you're on keto then god damn it
Because literally
Like five days after
I ordered them we decided hey
Let's do this whole beach themed rad con 4
And I'm like well now I have to get hashtag not fat
So I have to go on keto again
Oh okay now's a good time to check in
This will be I think this will come out at the end of the month
So me, Ben and Tom made a little
Wager or well I mean we just made
An agreement that we would work out
Have you guys been on point
I have not
I'm down 12 pounds
12 pounds down so far
Wait since New Year's
Yes that's pretty good
That's fantastic we started a little bit before
No rckkcon completely threw me off
I did lose the weight that I gained over the holidays
But then rckcon hit
Okay well hey as long as
Fucked it all
Alright well stay strong
Brother I will say that
I floundered
For the beginning of the month
It is true
And so I would say I'm
Probably like about the same weight
I might be up or down like one pound
But I'm roughly equivalent
My goal was just to work out three times a week was my goal
I failed that for the beginning of the month
I am doing better
In this latter half of the month
My goal was to set a trend
I'll make another deal
Let's do it again
I'm going to Hawaii
In like fucking 10 days or so
For my little actual vacation
With Michelle and her family
And I'm gonna be gross
And ugly and fat
And everyone's gonna laugh
But hopefully I'll like lose it
By living to island lifestyle
Is it nice in Hawaii
What could possibly be worse
It's nice in Hawaii
It's not as bad as last year
Yes it's perfect all the time
I haven't even thought about
Getting beach body ready
For the fucking thing
I don't even know what I'm supposed to do
Is there like a guide
For skinny boys
Aren't you just naturally beach body ready
You're just like slim
I'm slim but I'm not like
I'm like a skeleton sometimes
You gotta eat lots of protein
There's one important factor
That's being beach body ready
And it is so overlooked by gentlemen
Of our persuasion
And it is being tan
You gotta have
You don't want to walk out there
Like you're a fucking comp sign major
I'm not gonna get it
How the fuck am I gonna get a tan
Before much
I'll tell you how Gib
You do it the way that I do it
Oh wait you're in London
You got like clouds and shit
I'm gonna be the pale beauty
I'm gonna be the one
The beautiful geisha
Or like the Scottish Highlands person
They got white skin
I'm white I can do that
I'm just gonna be so hashtag
Not fat by rad con
That no one's gonna even notice
A ghost
I'll be rocking my usual hardcore
Farmers tan that I have from driving
All the time
That sounds good
I mean like a month prior
I will have spent like 10 days in Hawaii
So that tan that I will acquire
Will probably last at least a little bit
Until when I get back
So hopefully I'll be able to coast off that
For that time
Alright let's hear about fucking this Brad Garling house fan
Okay alright so Brad Garling's house
Is number one fan
And let's hear what he has to say
Alright in the count of three here we go
Next voicemail you ready
Number 12 Brad Garlington house
Fan Garling house
You know what I'm talking about
Oh I hear you loud and clear
But do you give I'm not hearing confirmation
Oh sorry I give you
Okay okay alright in the count of three
Here we go one two three
So I've got a question for Brad
So like how's Ripple gonna
Like turn out like
Is this crypto gonna be
A thing I should worry about or
Like I don't know much
About the crypto man
Should I just should I use your code
Should I not
I don't know about this Ripple stuff
Okay
Like fuck dawg
You started making anime then you revealed
Your names actually Brad like what the fuck
Brad
It was an orthodox business move
On my part but let me tell you guys
Hashtag Ripple
Hashtag XRP
Hashtag cryptocurrency
I mean you're definitely gonna want to like sell
And give me full access to your bank account
By clicking the link in my currently active stream
The only way to mine
Cripple is at night
Like you there's no way to do it
During the day so like you'd have to
Sell your soul in multiple ways
The only currency to be mined at night
Uh yeah it's like
It's like when you evolve an EV at night
With max friendship it turns into an Umbreon
Just when you mine crypto at night it turns into
Cripple or Ripple
Close enough I like Cripple
Alright let's do our last voicemail
Boys from the man himself
Me, Brad Garlinghouse
Is calling in CEO of Ripple
Let's hear what I have to say
On the count of three one two three
Poor little Nate
Swinging his pickaxe at the dead of night
You thought that you could mine cryptocurrency
While everyone else was asleep
Well too bad
I have assumed direct control
Hacking was easy
All I had to do was swing my silk touch
Pickaxe at the screen and your channel
Popped off right into my pocket
Now I will reap the rewards
Of all the cryptocurrency your subscribers
Can provide
This is what you get Nate
This is what you get for mining at night
This is going to be directly quoted in chapter two
Brad Garlinghouse voice grail
You know voice grail
I don't know
If we put him in the voice grail he might steal all those too
Yeah we can't give him access to the voice grail
As well
But he earned it though
This is a maritime and voice jail
Let him take the souls of the lowly bunch
In voice jail
If he earns his way into the voice jail
And he fair and square steals all of them
Hacks all of their accounts
Takes all of their ad rev I think he deserves it
What if we make Brad Garlinghouse the guard
Of voice jail
He can't be trusted
He can steal all the security footage
So all the people in voice jail can
Mysteriously kill themselves
We should put him in the voice chain
Oh yeah
The voice block chain
It can't be stolen
That's blockchain technology right there
Yeah whatever that is
There you go that's where you are Brad
Welcome to the team thanks for your contribution
Alright that's it
We are going to go to the website
Link to the description
Leave us your voice mails
Shoutouts to Brad for acting fast
Cause we just saw this morning
He's been playing this for months
Yeah I'm sure you're right
What else we got
Gibb and take.site
Read the lord of ghosts comic
And belljape and everything else
Belljape and lord of ghosts are the best ones though
Radcon4 kickstarter bruh
Radcon4 kickstarter help fund
We have tons more stretch goals
They're just gonna keep going forever
You want that calendar boys and girls
Come on help us get the calendar
You can up your pledge at any time
So if you see something new and shiny
You're just like I gotta have that
It's never too late
You can always up your pledge
Maybe we should go in
Maybe you pledged that
That's what I just finished
No you said you can pledge it
I said you can up your pledge at any time
Okay well don't
You cut out
It's discord's fault
Hey go to patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators
And podcast that is
Link down below and give us $5 for all the bonus episodes
When you hear this there should be a new bonus episode
Wait a minute
Our channel is down
We'll make it available somewhere
It'll be somewhere
We can definitely link it on the patreon
Nothing but the channels
Only the channels are affected
The kickstarter, the patreon
Well that's fine
Correct everything else is fine
So that's all good
Of course now $1 you're in the patreon discord
But as much as you like we appreciate the support
Follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators
You will probably want to follow that
If you want any updates on this particular saga
Because we will surely retweet or tweet from there
Any updates on channel statuses
So follow that or I'll
Primarily be tweeting from mine
Remember when I learn more updates
I'm not going to like between every second
Of every detail but when there is meaningful things
To let people know, I will let them know
But you can expect, I don't know
From the time you hear this, probably like a week
Could be a reasonable time to expect before anything changes
So you know
Keep your expectations in check
And keep your ear to the ground for more
I guess that's it everybody
And of course there's more voicemails
Kickstarter, check out Lord of Ghost, etc etc
And we will see you next week
Save us
By the way
If we do not have the video up
This might be on Digi's channel
Could be somewhere else, I don't know
We'll try to get the channel back as soon as possible
But obviously as soon as the PCP is back up
Everything will be re-uploaded there
And we will continue as normal
So here's hoping that happens fast
Alright see you then everybody
Bye
Thank you