Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We are back again to talk about cool things that we like because we have the ability to
do so.
I am the best guy ever, and I'm joined today by Hippocrit.
Yes, I got alcohol today.
Good job.
We've got Lethal Aurora Mage.
I did not get any water, I'm sad.
Seen Agua.
I think that was Italian.
Anyway, Mumkey Jones.
I already have to pee.
I still need a bigger hard drive for my PS4.
That's my most pressing concern right now.
We all had liquid things, and you had a PS4 thing, you broke it.
It's turning my brain to liquid distress, knowing I only have 80 gigs left on my hard
drive.
It's a problem.
So our topic for today is, as it's the end of the year, we're going to talk about all
the celebrities who died in Toy Shots.
No, we're not doing that.
We're not doing that.
They deserved it.
Those alt-right fucks.
No, we're going to talk about what we're looking forward to in 2017, and our goals.
I'm thinking about specific goals.
I got plans for 2017.
I'm going to make that year my bitch, and it's going to be good.
But before we get into that, just one little piece of news from the 2016 year I would like
to announce that we have officially brought into the fold of the procrastinators, Monkey
Jones is now an official PCP TPC guy round of applause.
Yay!
I did it.
I was autistic enough.
Yeah, you did.
Just barely.
Yo.
I hope one day I can reach the levels of autism that the rest of you aspire to.
Well, you've got a couple of children's cartoons to make your way through before you get to
that point.
That's true.
So who's got some resolutions that they want to shoot out?
Not fucking resolutions.
I'm talking about goals.
Resolutions are for the queers.
That's true.
I'm talking about action plans.
You know?
Action drafts.
That's what I'm all about.
Action draft.
He's my coach.
He's my life coach, actually.
Well.
And he's keeping me on track.
I have a couple plans.
A couple different plans.
Sure.
Let's hear them.
Obviously, there's Radcon, which is going to be fun, and there's going to be-
One week, baby.
One week.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I should probably tell somebody that I'm leaving this day.
That's true.
Me, too.
Nobody knows.
Well, yeah, there's Radcon.
Nobody knows what it's like to go to Radcon.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Except for all of us.
Except for us.
I think you're all antagonizing me.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Paige, we love you.
You got so much help, Paige.
You're not going either.
We'll have Radcon.
Oh, true.
London at some point.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
If we could get another Kickstarter thing going on, to fly us out to London like the
K-On! Girls, and we can go on a fucking tour, how fucking ill would that be?
That would be so cool.
I mean, did you-
I feel like you could probably pull it off.
He made this happen, which is beyond what I expected.
Yeah, man.
Clearly, his fans are as gullible as they are rich.
Yeah, fuck you guys.
Okay, anyway.
I'm sorry, Gib.
Let's hear your shit.
But for personal stuff, I have-
I made a tweet that I wanted to get a bunch of things started.
I want to start, you know, I don't expect to finish all these things, but I expect to
at least manage to start writing a novel, developing a game, making an album, and something
else, making a comic.
I don't know.
Please tell me it's a rock opera.
I want to start all those things, and that is-
Okay.
That is my overall goal is to begin them all.
What were you saying, Momkey?
I said, please tell me it's a rock opera that you want to make.
It is probably going to be a rock album, because that's the music I like.
There could be an opera in that.
Rock opera is the best genre.
Comedy rock's good, too.
Because I can't really do serious singing, so that'll be-
We're just living in a generation immersed in irony all the time.
I can't be serious anymore.
It's real hard.
It's real bad.
We've lost the ability to be sincere.
That's our coping mechanism for the bullshit that we have to put up with.
None of it's real.
None of it matters.
Let's just-
We're all going to die someday.
Yeah, we're all going to die.
They used to go out and kill their enemies, but our only resource now is to just sink
into irony and just-
Our only resource now is memes.
Yeah, that's what we've got left.
These are the weapons our fathers gifted to us.
The only thing we're killing is our future as a goddamn millennia.
Oh, such depression.
Here we come, 2017.
Such edgy depressness.
Hey, Bo, do you have any goals for your YouTube channel?
Yes, I want to get to a point while I'm thinking of doing all these other things.
I want to-
Obviously, I want to finish the Rayman video, and I want to do Ratchet and Clank 2 review.
But I have a goal that I don't know whether I'll actually get there by the end of 2016,
but I'll be working towards it the whole year, is just making it so that I always have a
video coming up the next week.
So whether it's a miniscule review or a big review or a GRPJ, I want something to be coming
out the week, you know, before, you know, just scheduled a bunch of shit so that I never
have to be like, oh shit, I got to make something in two days or else I'm fucked.
Backlog dream goal, that's it.
Now, do you see that as- I mean, I don't mean to be critical about it.
Do you see that as like a dream goal, or is this something that you have a plan to achieve?
Well, I say it's a dream goal, but it is a plan.
I'm going to work towards doing that.
That's why I say it's a plan for the next year.
My dream goal is to be rich and have no problems at all.
But, you know, I can't do that next year.
That'll be like 2019.
Well, that's- 2019 is really weird to say.
I don't like it.
2019?
Just think a few years ago, 2017 was weird to say.
I don't know, 2017 sort of rolls over.
2019 sounds like you're counting down.
It was going to be fun to say 2020 though.
Yes, I'll be looking forward to that.
Oh man, everyone's going to be seeing real clearly that.
No, I knew somebody would say that.
I made a tweet about how everybody is going to be saying,
I have 2020 vision or some sort of joke like that.
Oh yeah, that's the one.
I've got 2020 vision for when we get that fucking racist massages
Trump out of office, if you know what I'm saying.
But like, no, the joke was like,
people every single day in 2020 will be saying,
like if someone asks them,
hey, when do we do the thing or what's happening tomorrow?
They say, gee, guys, I don't have 2020 vision.
They ask me if what's happening right now?
Gee, it's stupid and it's going to happen.
I'm probably going to have to get glasses in the next couple of weeks.
I need to get my eyes checked, so I can't wait for that to happen.
And then I'm just like, no, I don't have 2020 vision.
Look at my fucking face.
Fuck you.
Get that joke out of here.
It's racist.
You know, I need new glasses too.
Ever since Radcon won, actually at Radcon,
I like dropped my glasses that I wear occasionally
and I broke like a half of them.
And then sometime later, the other half broke.
So now I've just, I've been wearing taped glasses on both side.
I'm wearing them right now.
They just, they look like a fucking idiot.
And also, you guys probably don't know this.
I only learned this as I was experiencing it.
If you wear glasses, they probably have little rubber things
on the parts that go up over your ear.
If those fell off, as they have on both sides of my head now,
like there's nothing to hold the glasses kind of to your head.
And every time you move, they fly off your fucking face.
I'm wearing the most ghetto glasses of all time.
Okay, I don't need to get into a whole big thing about my glasses.
I need new ones.
My glasses.
Give, I had one more question about your plan.
And it was that I noticed that you said you wanted to start those various projects.
I was wondering if you had any kind of timeframe for when you were going to finish them.
Because I really don't enjoy having multiple projects running at once.
And what if that would be a challenge?
Starting them, you know what they say, like, it's easy to talk about,
you know, talk a big game, but never do anything.
If I have the projects begun, I can always say,
well, I tried, you know, and I want to have at least like a first draft
of a terrible story by the end of the year.
You know, nothing that I could put out,
maybe like half the story done.
You know, just get up to like DigiBro level writing
and you'll be pretty, you know, that's not acceptable,
but it's getting there, you're getting there.
Yeah.
And for the comic, I don't know, maybe draw a couple pages.
I don't really expect to do the comic, actually.
Comics are hard.
Oh, yes.
I was thinking that'd be like the one you're most likely to do.
Yeah, how hard could it be if Ben Seed does it?
Well, if I made the art deliberately not very intensive,
I guess I could do a comic.
It's just that drawing a square and then putting something in it
is always really annoying to me.
I don't know how big to draw the square.
I don't know what shape it should be.
So I would rather just draw everything in the same size square,
but then that doesn't look good on a page.
It's like, how do you, how do you do it?
I should just do a home stock.
This is my life hack to you for when I was doing comics.
You draw all the art and then you put it in panels afterwards.
That's interesting.
That's how I did all my comic pages like back in the day.
What program did you use to draw?
Um.
MS Paint.
That's the best program.
I used to draw it on it all the time and that's no joke.
But before I had internet.
That's how you get pro.
That's true.
But seriously, what program did you use?
Um, I was using Art Rage and Manga Studio.
I kind of jumped back and forth between both.
Art Rage.
I know it's so cringy, but it's good.
It's awesome.
I'm not cringing.
I'm loving it.
I want to get that shit.
Gib, did you have any other shit to say about your plans?
Or can we move on to someone who's actually interesting?
Whoa!
Got him!
We're all just going to talk about it.
We're just going to grind through all this shit and get all that stuff done.
We're just going to sit here jerking it all through 2017.
That'd be good.
I hope so.
I mean, let's get to my goals.
Jerking it.
That's my plan.
It's not even a goal.
I accomplished that with flying colors throughout 2016.
Yeah.
Just one color, though.
Just one flying color.
All the colors of the rainbow at once.
Oh, no.
I mean, with me, there's a little bit of red in there as well, you know, so it's, uh...
I'm sorry, Mage.
Help.
Why are you sorry?
I'll be your doctor.
Why are you sorry to me specifically?
I don't know.
Because he's a fucking beside who thinks you're a weak woman.
What are you saying?
You're saying you're a weak woman, Tom.
You're a bad person.
I mean, yeah, I am a bad person.
It's fine.
Oh, no.
Tom is a good person.
Oh, God.
We're off the fucking rails.
What's...
Gabe, I'm sorry.
Were you done?
Was there anything else?
If I was going to say something, I forgot it, so forget it.
Okay.
You can bring it up later anyway.
Gabe, I think your resolution should be to tell Nate and myself when we cut you off
to just shut the fuck up when we do the show.
That's a good goal.
That is a good goal.
Shut up, Nate.
Thank you.
You asshole.
There we go.
Oh, it's only 2016.
It doesn't count.
That's true.
You can't do it yet.
Just get in practice.
It's fine.
How about you, Tom?
What are your goals for 2017?
I have a few, I guess.
So I want to start writing my book.
I've already started writing some stuff for it.
Good.
I'm hopefully going to put the first part out in the next three or four days, I think.
Wow.
All right.
How long is it going to be?
Well, it's combined.
I think it's just under 20,000 words because there's a prologue and then the first part.
It's pretty fucking good.
I dropped both of those at the same time.
And then I want to do another part every two months.
So like six releases throughout next year, that's kind of the goal for that.
That's how Moby Dick was written.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it was like every fucking month he would release another 5,000 words or whatever the
hell.
Same shit with...
It was a little different, but fucking Christmas, fucking Charles Dickens, whatever the fuck.
Christmas story.
Christmas Carol?
No, not like...
Yeah, damn.
A Christmas Carol, yeah.
He was paid by the word.
What a champ.
He is a champ.
I'm sorry.
So what else?
That's exciting.
I'm looking forward to that.
Yeah, so that'll hopefully start in a few days.
I'm going to update the website to go with it.
I'm going to try and get more healthy, because my eating habits this year have been atrocious.
Like, there's a very normie goal, but I mean...
What's wrong with that?
Have you been not eating or just eating?
I mean, I'm so poor.
It's like, I could try and buy good food, but you know, Doritos are five for five dollars
right now, so that's just my life.
Play a bag of rice, dog.
Big ol' bag of rice.
Yeah, I've actually started doing intermittent fasting.
Why didn't you go full weave and make rice balls?
I mean, I could.
Jelly filled doughnuts.
Yeah.
I mean, I got...
I'm just going to eat nothing but jelly doughnuts all next year.
Dude, why are you doing intermittent fasting?
You're already a skinny boy.
What's the deal?
Well, it's because usually I have this bad habit of I'll eat like one or two meals,
and then like right before bed, I'll just engorge on more stuff because I'm bored.
So I'm kind of like trying to force myself not to do that,
because that's like the worst time to eat stuff.
And it's definitely like...
Hey, you know, I actually...
I was reading about that.
It's that there's...
Let's just say at best there's inconclusive evidence that eating right before sleeping
actually contributes to, you know, like fat gain or anything.
I feel like...
I'm just saying...
My personal experience and looking at my scale tells me that there's definitely some sort
of at least personal biological correlation.
All right, fair enough.
It makes kind of sense though, especially like if what you eat before bed is something
like sweet and sugary and stuff, and that's really bad.
Okay, we're talking about how like we feel that our bodies are doing it as opposed to
the statistics.
I'm just saying let's...
Well, statistically, if you only eat eight hours a day and you're fasting for 16, your
body goes into ketosis longer and burns your fat reserves, and that's my mindset behind
doing intermittent fasting.
Okay, okay.
So you eat within an eight hour window, and then 16 hours, eight hours being awake, and
then eight hours while asleep.
Ideally, your body's not eating anything, and it's just burning your reserves.
That's the idea behind that.
Yeah, okay, all right.
I also read that you're supposed to eat sweets before the actual dinner, because sweets are
easily stored in the body and they become fat, but if you eat them first, they're going
to be used up, the energy, and your body can just digest the food at its normal pace.
So my mom's wrong this whole time, and you are supposed to have dessert first.
Yeah, but the thing is, I think the reason people would say like, oh, you have to have
dessert last is so that little kids wouldn't ruin their appetite, because yeah, you should
eat the sweets first, but if you have nothing but sweets, that's also not good, you know?
And when you're growing up, you might want to eat a lot of sweets, and then you don't
feel like actually having the nice healthy dinner afterwards.
So they're making sure that you eat the normal good food first before you eat any sweets.
True, sir.
Kids are very stupid.
That's true.
Then again, so am I, because I'm still a man-child.
Okay, so beyond your dieting goals, what else you got?
I might finally quit YouTube.
Who knows?
That's definitely in the cards.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Why would you do that?
Because I hate YouTube.
It's like, it's a painful process.
I'm not going to start making things.
I might just like start blogging and just say, fuck YouTube, it's dumb, because I don't make
any Patreon money anymore like you guys do.
I make very little, but I found the most money that I've made online has been this month,
and this is a bad month, but through Amazon affiliate links, I've made more money this
month through that, then working my job, then Patreon, anything.
Wow, that's pretty good.
Yeah, it's pretty ridiculous.
I mean, it's the holiday season, so I guess that's probably why.
Oh, true, true.
There's tablet things.
You sure you're not going to keep doing those, at least?
Well, I would, but nobody sends and responds to my emails anymore, so I can't get any.
Otherwise I'd still be doing them, but I keep, like there's two good ones that came out the
last like couple months.
I've been emailing both companies since October to be like, hey, gimme, and they're just like,
we're not responding to you, but they're not responding to anybody.
Nobody has any of these new tablets, so I get comments every day.
See, that's interesting.
Review this one, and nobody can, because nobody will give them away anymore.
It's like, well, now you got to buy them, and I'm just like, no, I don't.
I'm just not going to do it, so no one will buy them.
You fools.
I don't know.
I've been doing a lot of research on actual blogging, and apparently people can still
make money doing that, and that's kind of cool, and that takes less effort.
I think YouTube is a clusterfuck anyways.
It's like turning into this not bad environment, but there's just a lot of bullshit going on
with YouTube right now in general that I'm not a huge fan of.
You ain't wrong about that.
I did a couple videos the last couple weeks talking about, like,
how YouTube's a clusterfuck, and then how YouTube alternatives that people are talking
about aren't going to work, and then the third one's going to be like the social network
that fixes it all, and I still haven't finished all the prep for it, but that'll hopefully
be going up in a couple days.
I might still just use YouTube for vlogs and supplemental content to boost the actual
blog, like do little videos here and there, but I can definitely, I can do more with
writing anyways, so I'm better at writing than anything else.
Maybe you could make live streams of videos.
You're self-typing the blog posts.
Let's do a Let's Type.
It's so good.
That's a great idea.
Let's blog.
Yeah.
Watch me sit here.
So some major changes are coming for Tom Oliver, potentially.
Potentially.
I mean, it's kind of like one of those things I'm probably going to play with a bit and
see if it works, because if it's a dead end and I can't get anything out of there, then
I'm like, ah, fuck it.
I'm also possibly starting a new YouTube project, though, that I think would only work on YouTube,
because it's going to be another kind of review project.
I've mentioned it to you guys a little bit late to the party.
Late to the boy.
Oh, yeah.
Which sounded like a great idea, and we all liked it.
I mean, you know, if it makes sense economically, of course.
I mean, it seems like it wouldn't be too much of a burden to do, so I might try and shoot
for doing that for next year.
The reason I haven't started it yet is because my friend Ashley, she was going to do all the
editing because, like, fuck editing.
Oh, wow.
Okay, cool.
But then we were talking, and she's like, well, maybe I could do more than editing because
I kind of want to be in that.
I'm like, well, I don't know what you're like on camera, so we have to practice that and
see if we can get a good dynamic going.
And she hasn't gotten back to me on that.
That sounds like she just wants to be a YouTuber, but she doesn't have the confidence yet.
I don't really know.
She's trying to suck you off, dude, and not in the good way.
She's trying to lead you.
Oh, my God, did not intend to come out that way.
Dude, watch out.
That girl's trying to suck you off.
Get the fuck out of there.
I think I'll stay right here.
I'm sorry.
No.
I don't really know.
I mean, so depending on how that all goes, because we've been talking about, like, possibly
like, moving in and getting in place with her and our other mutual friends.
That's kind of why that conversation started.
But that might be delayed because I have to move out by August because that's something
big is going to change some of 2017 is I'm going to be losing my house.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
That's a change.
Yeah.
So I'm going to try and find a place to live.
So that's something I'm going to start working towards probably in the next week or so,
like, trying to get another second job so I can save up money to get out of here.
Oh, man.
Such a real person tongue.
It fucking sucks, dude.
Being a real person, it makes you want to die.
Yeah, but I mean, yeah, but it just makes me feel like such a sheltered little baby boy
when I'm like, oh, yeah, I can just live with my parents for a couple of years.
It's fine.
I mean, I've already done that.
I've been here since like 2012.
So I've paid my dues.
I'm just an older man.
So like I'm coming up on 30 and it's like, maybe it's time to stop being a little bitch
and be a real man and maybe I don't know if I can do it.
We're going to try and we'll see what happens.
That's another reason why I might have to just stop doing YouTube because like if I'm
like busting my ass like 60 hours a week and like possibly moving to like a shitty apartment
and it's like, oh, check out my awesome studio in the crack house down in, you know, wherever
the fuck I end up.
So I don't know.
It's going to be things are going to get super fucking different for me personally this year
or next year, depending on how you want to look at it, depending on when you're listening to this.
You have like a couple hours left of me saying this year.
Yeah, maybe did you will get it up instantly?
We'll say.
Sounded like he was busy with other shit tonight.
That's true.
He's busy getting drunk.
It's New Year's Eve.
Oh, did you have problems getting it up?
Here it is, folks.
I do have some bad news, everybody.
Oh, monkey's dead.
I just looked it up and I think I was wrong about Moby Dick being serialized.
Oh, no.
It's been bothering me for about 10 minutes now.
Well, isn't it like a super old book?
How would they?
How would that function?
It's from like 1851, I think.
Yeah.
And I thought King Critic got exposed for a hack today, but it turns out Monkey Jones.
That was pretty good.
I didn't know what you're talking about.
Check out Monkey Jones, too.
Some hot guys.
Okay.
Well, Tom, we are all excited and slightly concerned to see how things work out.
I'll let you know how I'm doing for my hardcore boss.
I'm sure we'll be in touch.
If all else.
Yeah.
Guys, go help Tom out, patreon.com.
Yeah, we'll make sure the money gets around, you know.
Mage, why don't you tell us what your plans are for the coming year?
You're a mysterious entity and the procrastinators.
No one knows.
Yeah.
Not even you.
Yeah, exactly.
I was just about to say that.
I'm living in a constant limbo.
I don't know what happened in the past.
I don't know what's going to happen in the future.
What am I doing now?
What is this?
Well, how do you not know what happens in the past?
She doesn't read the newspapers.
I forget.
I have such a bad memory.
I'm not just trying to be cute here.
I really do have really poor memory.
Oh, you can't help it, Mage.
You just can't help it.
Now can you?
Shadam.
Got him.
Anyway, I am going to try and fix up my health and stuff.
I've had a big scare recently with my health.
It was terrible.
I'm going to test.
I'm going to still have a stomach ultrasound soon.
That's called being pregnant.
No.
No, no, no.
Stomach.
It's a natural process, Mage.
It's in the stomach.
Yeah, when you're pregnant, the baby's in your tummy.
Stomach and tummy are two different things.
No, it's in your tummy.
My mommy told me so.
Stomach ultrasound.
Are you calling mom key a liar?
Guys, no.
You're on thin ice, Mage.
Be careful.
Don't even joke about it.
I don't want any kids.
That's like the worst joke I've ever had.
If you weren't slinging that thing around town, Mage, you wouldn't need to worry about it so much.
What, does she have like a three-foot clit or something?
Oh, God, why?
That's a mystery for the ages.
Guys, you're all gross.
You're all bad.
This is why I was apologizing earlier.
This is my PCP.
I'm kicking you all out.
Goodbye.
All right.
It's time for the Mage cast.
Okay, Mage.
But seriously, yeah, I'm going to fix my health up.
I was going to go to like some sort of health camp or whatever my mom was talking about it.
Me going there.
Health camp.
Yeah, health camp.
I'm going to starve myself for 10 days.
Starve yourself?
Is it a fat camp?
Are you going to fat camp?
No, no, no.
Okay.
All right.
To get stuff in order and stuff.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
So I'll be needing to save up some months.
My mom said she would cover some of it, but she can't anymore because she has to have laser
eye surgery for both eyes.
Oh, wow.
Best news to find out on Christmas.
She's going to have laser eyes?
Yes.
She's getting them installed, dude.
Yeah.
My mom is going to be the best.
Very important.
Yeah.
Did you say you're going to starve yourself?
No, I'm not going to starve myself.
I'm going to go to this.
Constantly interrupting you.
Yes, exactly.
No, I just need questions for clarification.
That's what she said.
Well, I'm going to go to this camp and they're going to like strictly regulate what I'm eating
and what I'm doing with myself for the 10 days and whatever it's like.
I'm just saying it sounds like fat camp.
That's all I'm saying.
That's all I'm saying, guys.
Yeah.
I was going to say if you need to starve yourself, you can do it for free by going to Tom Oliver's
house.
I'll have you know that my pantry is packed to the brim with choice ramen, all right?
I've got all kinds of flavors.
Whatever you want.
I'll hook you up.
All the cardboard you can eat will be available.
I can eat that for Tom, guys.
I do too.
Patreon.com slash Ben St.
But yeah, I need to say up for whatever that camp thing, whatever it is.
My mom told me about it and like they all speak in Russian, so I have to go with her
because I don't speak a look of Russian.
Sometimes.
Does the name of this contain the word gulag at all?
You know, just wondering.
No, no.
It's actually in Latvia, but they all speak Russian because I don't know.
They probably speak Latvian too, but my mom can speak Russian, so there we go.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah.
I would have spoken Russian too, but then at a young age, I decided to not.
So I don't speak Russian.
Oh, really?
You made a choice not to?
Yeah, well, yeah.
In school, you could have chosen like a third language.
The first one was Lithuanian.
Third language?
Yeah, first is Lithuanian, second was English, both mandatory, and then you had a choice.
What's the first one?
Lithuanian.
Lithuanian dog.
She's from Lithuania.
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Eastern Europe.
It's a European country.
Can you speak that language for me right now?
Oh, my dick is rock hard.
Yeah, dog.
Oh my god.
But yeah.
I legitimately forget sometimes that languages besides English and Japanese exist.
That's how much fucking disgusting we buy them.
Yeah, we had a choice between Russian, French, and German, and I already spoke a little bit
of German, so I went with German.
That's cool.
How's your German then?
Is it good?
It was decent back when I used it, but now it's probably rusty.
I probably understand a lot more than I can speak.
I couldn't hold a conversation honestly, but I can understand a lot more than I can speak.
That's cool.
Both languages, English and German, I was taught by cartoons.
Oh, so you said, so you said, where did you learn English again?
You've told me before.
Cartoons, Cartoon Network.
I'm just wondering if there's a specific one that stands out to you as a particularly
potential.
I was just watching cartoons in general on Cartoon Network all day, every day.
Well, not all day, but yeah.
Like a real American.
That's the laboratory, stuff like that.
Yeah.
Mage, I'm curious as to how you're going to make that money.
Because you don't, I mean, you occasionally make a, put an image on your deviant art that
I've seen, but I don't know really how you make money.
I haven't, yeah, I haven't been making money, per se.
I don't have a Patreon.
I haven't been concerned myself with making money, but I guess.
Welcome to European culture, everyone.
Not concerned about making money.
The state gives you everything.
Here's your health care.
Here's your food.
It's fine.
Here's a live in Muslim refugee.
Hey, hey, hey everybody.
I'm here.
I'm here too.
Hello.
Is the podcast on?
Yes.
I hope you're recording this shit.
I am recording this shit.
I was going to poke you because I saw you playing Pokemon.
It's like, how do you play Pokemon while we're here podcasting?
I forgot.
I forgot the podcast was starting.
Some nice fellow challenged me to a battle on the showdown.
How'd you do?
I defeated.
I crushed him.
Thank God.
I was real lucky.
I got Diggers B.
Ben's what?
That's the first guy.
I saw his dance and I swept half his team.
And then he told me that he loved my work and it really made my 2017.
Oh yeah.
Ben's won for 20 now.
All right.
We're working our way back up.
Yeah.
But I'm sorry.
Mage was telling us about her lifestyle, degenerate as it may be, but it is hers.
Okay.
But yeah, for 2017, I kind of really liked doing that little animation I did.
So I might actually put up more.
I have more fun spending several days drawing an animation that I do sitting down for an
hour and recording myself play Undertale.
As weird as that sounds.
Yeah.
It is.
It does seem a little more lucrative.
It's kind of amazing.
Actually, I have no idea.
Lucrative.
But it gets a lot of views.
I mean, you're Undertale videos.
I was going to say Undertale videos are big.
They are not small.
You guys mean her animations.
Of course.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
All those.
Yeah.
No, I meant the Let's Play.
I haven't finished that one.
Yeah, the Let's Plays.
Yeah.
But yeah.
I just want to kind of do more.
They haven't gotten that many views.
As an American capitalist pig, I would advise you to drop the Let's Play.
Focus on animations of that kind.
The only thing is I want to finish that Let's Play at the same time.
I have more fun drawing stuff than I do.
Oh, God.
Please draw, Mage.
Please draw.
Fuck the Let's Play.
Nobody cares.
It's so true.
I'll consider it.
I kind of feel bad dropping it, like after, you know, just like procrastinating for half
a year and be like, hey, guys, I'm back and then one episode later.
Okay, guys, I'm quitting this Let's Play.
Just like, hey, guys, I'm back.
Die and have game over.
Just like, I guess the game's over.
Yeah.
There you go.
Sorry if my audio is, I'm using a new microphone and I just noticed that I'm clipping the fuck
out of my sandwich.
So sorry about that.
I'll try and adjust it.
Just don't shout and I think you'll be good.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's okay.
We've got Tom's audio, so we've got a bare minimum that we're still well above for the
rest of us.
As long as Whistler doesn't try to use hypnosis, Ben shouldn't be screaming.
Whistler, you know, scholars will debate.
Scholars will debate until the end of time whether Whistler really, whether Whistler just
made a mistake or whether he was an inside job, whether he was, whether he was, whether
he was your inside man.
But you know what?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter whether it was intentional or not, you know, we can't, we can't stand
for that kind of thing.
Incompetence is even worse sometimes.
Do you think Whistler may be what, like he was, he was doing his hypnosis, but the fact
that it failed was because he was too busy whistling and waking him up.
I mean, I hope so.
Or he's a Whistler blower.
My, my friend, he's a whistleblower.
My friend Crack, my friend Crack drew a picture of Whistler getting ready for the firing squad.
He's got a bandana around his eyes.
Oh my God.
That shit.
I will go, yeah, he sent it to me on Patreon.
I will go and tweet it later.
Put that in the next episode at the end.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I am hungry for guest art.
I have had to do my own guest art a couple times.
I'm just thinking of the way Polyworld looks and he's got like the eye bumps that come out.
Would his eyes not have like an individual bow around each one?
Well, that's not how Crack chose to depict it.
Give us the big questions.
All right, Mage, was there anything else you wanted to add about, I'm curious if there's, yeah, please, go ahead.
Yeah, I kind of wanted to wrap it up.
Yeah, I think I'm going to do animations on my channel.
I'm thinking about maybe actually starting a Patreon.
I'm not too sure about that.
Do a dog.
It seems very fiddly and then I'll have to do extra stuff and I'm not really reliable.
You don't have to.
Dude, my Patreon has no rewards at all and I still make a pretty decent amount.
Most people do, but you don't have to.
Most people are suckers and they're chumps and I hate them.
Well, I mean, it's going to be their own choice.
It's not like I'm going to pressure them to do Patreon stuff, whatever.
Of course, otherwise they'd be right.
Yeah, I'll say about that.
I've been debating on whether or not to have Patreon for a while now, so I might do that.
Dude, we're the biggest pro-patreon people in the world here.
I don't see any reason to not do a Patreon ever.
It always seems like a good idea.
I mean, Christian Weston Chandler just started his successful Patreon.
And it's a rousing success.
$250,000 and he'll make you a 15 minute YouTube video.
About anything you want.
Yeah, anything you want.
Man, that's a bargain.
Okay.
I'm sorry, mate.
We are interrupting.
One last thing.
No, it's fine.
I might start doing commissions.
I'm still iffy about that because I'm not.
Like, I used to do pony commissions and ponies are really fun and kind of easy to draw.
But I want to, you know, start including like humans and stuff.
And I have big troubles with like anatomy of humans and I'm just like,
maybe I'll start off with Chibi's first and see how that goes.
So I might open up commissions soon.
I've been saying that for a while now, but I am legit thinking about it for serious
because I do need the months.
Weren't you doing some commissions earlier this year or like a month ago or so?
Yeah, I did some sort of private requests.
We kind of came about and I was like, well, I don't want to, you know, open up commissions
and have like a bunch of people commission me then I'll be overworked and I won't get
them done because I had to go for Christmas to my family and stuff.
So I did a few private ones that people asked me.
And yeah, and it turned out well.
And that's what kind of inspired me to maybe start actual commissions like public commissions.
Well, hey, if you do it, let us know and we'll shout it out.
I have never done like a round of commissions before.
I don't really like working on commissions, but I don't know.
It's practice in a way and hey, some way to earn months.
Yeah, yeah.
Who needs money when you live in Europe?
Am I right?
I do.
I do it for enough money, but frankly, I would feel uncomfortable asking for the amount of
money that would make me feel like that would make me feel like it was worth the pain and
suffering of doing someone's commission.
Yeah, I was doing commissions like a couple of months ago, but I was like thinking of
the pricing.
I'm like, no one's going to buy these.
Like I'm not going to like bother drawing your shitty OC for less than like $50 baseline.
Yeah.
And I mean, you know, people are so goddamn entitled on the internet.
They think artists should just draw them shit for free.
Dang it.
Well, it's just fucking lines on a paper, dude.
I have a system that I'm kind of happy with.
It's a little, I guess, you know, we achieve it at the same time.
I think it's good enough.
I charge by the hour and so the effort put in depends on how many hours, you know, you
commission me for.
So if it's a very detailed design and you commission me only for an hour, don't be
surprised if it's just like base colors at best.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
Well, the problem I would see with that is that I think a lot of customers probably wouldn't
know what to expect from, say, an hour's work.
Yeah, I do like previews, you know, you know, examples of what it would look like after
an hour or two hours or whatever.
I don't charge for the sketching process, though, because the sketching can take anywhere
between like 15 minutes to like an hour or so.
Because sometimes, you know, I don't get it right and then I have to redraw all the sketch
all over again.
So I don't feel like it's fair to charge for it because it'll double the price for some
of the commissions.
But other than that, the sketching is work.
On the other hand, though, it doubles the price.
Yeah.
By the same token.
Well, I don't want to rob people of their money.
I want to be fair.
Oh, but then we're coming at this from completely different angles, and if that's the case.
Mages, sketching is work.
Why is it not worth paying for the sketch part of the process?
Mages, let me tell you how cheap I am.
If I ever start doing commissions, I'm making very sure I'm going to have a whole document,
like a terms and services agreement you have to do.
Yeah.
And it's going to have a revision clause in there that you get two free revision.
After that, I charge you $3 a complaint.
A revision's clause is important.
Okay, guys, Ridley, I think of it this way.
I could make a butt load off of Nate if he ever commissioned me.
That's true.
That's how I do a lot of revisions.
He's like an addict.
He just keeps putting money into the machine, hoping that his commission will come out good this time.
When I worked with CeCe on my banner, she still tells tall tales about how many revisions
I had her to on that shit.
Was that like 100?
No, but it was a lot.
It was a lot.
I mean, even one is too many.
We were in a group chat while you were doing that, and she just kept being like,
what the fuck?
This is crazy.
And we were all just like, made some mad man.
For me, I just kind of like send them a preview of the sketch for the pose and stuff,
and they okay me, then I finish the drawing, and I send it over the finished drawing after they pay me.
And I'm not going to change anything about the pose or whatever,
but if they want some adjustments with the colors, I can still do that.
If you're not happy with the pose, tell me at the sketch stage or else you're too little too late.
Yeah, okay.
Well, we don't have to get too bogged down in the details of Mage's hypothetical commissions that don't even exist right now.
Sorry, man.
Sorry you don't care about art, man.
Sorry you're just not an artist mindset, man.
We get the idea.
Who have we heard from already?
Tom and Gibb, and now Mage.
Okay.
His name's Hippo, by the way.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mage, do you have anything else you want to add?
Have a good year, everyone.
Yay.
All right.
Now, Mumki, how about you, my friend?
What are your plans for 2017?
Well, much like Hippo and Tom, I'm an aspiring writer,
but the only difference is that two years ago I wrote my book.
So my plan for 2017 is to actually release it.
I thought you were saying delete it.
That's probably the better plan, to be honest.
I've been working on this deletion for years.
I'm very proud of it, and I finally have a copy of it that I think I can release,
so I'm waiting for the first copy to come in the mail so I can make sure it's okay.
Are you going to do a dramatic reading of it?
Oh, yeah.
I was thinking about it, but it's really long, and I mean, if I did...
Maybe the first chapter.
Just to get people interested.
Yeah, I might do that for the...
What is the total work count of your book?
It's not bad.
The word count?
Yes.
I think it's like right around 100,000.
Substantial.
I mean, give me a work of comparable length.
Are we talking like Deathly Hallows' length?
Or are we talking Animorph's length?
I don't fucking know.
Okay.
It's 21 chapters of a great story about a school shooting, and I love it.
How are you going to release it?
There's a website where you can self-publish called lulu.com that I actually recommend.
It's pretty good.
Oolulilia released Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters through Lulu.
Oh, yeah.
You're a good company, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's going to be there.
And if you're interested in hearing Munky's take on a school shooting, check out my YouTube
channel, and I'll post links there.
I thought it was going to be like the story of Elliot Roger, but from the perspective of
the gun or the knife.
That'd be interesting.
The book was heavily influenced by the Elliot Roger case, so...
Imagine.
As far as YouTube goals are concerned, I guess I just want to double my subs next year.
If I end the year with 30,000 subs, I'd be pretty happy.
And that's about it.
God, you have so many.
And you really gained a lot.
You really gained a lot recently.
I was just curious.
What was the spike from now at like 15,000 or so?
What were you before you started the surge?
I don't know if I'm on a surge right now.
I think I'd get like 30 subs a day.
Okay.
Well, when the Be Got to H.K.I. video went big, how many were you at at that point?
Zero.
Oh.
I went from zero to about 5,000 in about a day.
Wow.
And then that channel got deleted like a week later.
Oh, really?
So I lost most of those subs.
Oh, good.
But then luckily, the video went viral again, and I got a bunch of subs back.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
That's unusual.
That video was on the front page of Reddit three times.
Whoa.
Damn.
I'm waiting for the fourth.
If he got to H.K.I.
He's a big one, you know.
Which I actually have not seen.
Wait, no, no.
That's the one about the girl who wants to have sex with a million dudes or something?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have seen that one.
Actually, I have not.
The anime or the review?
No, the review.
I don't watch anime.
Oh.
I'm not a fucking anime.
So, yeah, those are Mumke's goals.
Go check out youtube.com slash Mumke Jones.
Go check him out.
All right, cool.
He's pretty good.
Well, I mean, yeah.
He's pretty good at Pokemon, I've heard.
Yeah.
He just gets lucky every time.
Yeah, how do you like my Metagross I got, Ben?
First, it's a fucking, it's a Beldom.
It's a Metang and it will be a Metang in our next battle.
So don't go counting your chicken for the hatch.
First of all, why would I bring it to the battle if it's not a Metagross yet?
Hmm.
That's solid.
Yeah.
Solid quest.
Well, I mean, it's still pretty good.
It's still like 420 base stats.
Fair.
420, I hear you on that, brother.
I hear you there.
Yeah, high five.
High five.
Listen to Ben, not a nerd saying, talking about Pokemon stats.
Yeah, 420, 420 plays it with my brothers.
Ben, tell us more about your plans for 2017.
Mumke, I assume that was everything you've done.
Yeah, I'm a boring person.
Okay.
Agreed.
Ben.
YouTube goals in term, I guess maybe it'd be nice to hit 10,000.
That'd be cool.
I hadn't really thought about how I'm going to do that.
But my real goals for this year, I guess, I mean, I thought the champion would be done
a month or two ago.
So definitely going to finish that.
Going to finish this Nuzlocke and then probably not do one for a while.
Oh, Vapers 3, definitely going to do that.
That shouldn't take the whole year.
Are the rumors true that this one's about Magda?
That's right.
It is.
Oh, shit.
I know.
The people cried out for it and I delivered.
One more of that hot poof in my life.
So, yeah, finish champion, do Vapers 3, and then do a lot more.
I want to draw more comics and when I get a chance to take a break from Nuzlocke, I'm
sure I will be able to draw more than I had been previously.
And I guess I would probably like to release some kind of book, you know, like some kind
of collection or maybe just paper, you know, soft cover, trade paperback copies of Vapers
or Champion or whatever.
Yeah, that's a good plan.
So, I guess those would be my goals for 2017.
Oh, and also just make more money because I'm on a crash course with bankruptcy and
something needs to change.
What's your time frame?
Is that going to be within 2017?
Possibly.
We'll probably know by the end of the year.
Worst case scenario, yes.
Okay, how exciting.
Oh, yeah.
I've got one more question.
You've been making a couple like little analysis type of videos on your channel.
Oh, that's right.
Plans to do more of those because I like them.
Yeah.
I guess in terms of YouTube, I'm not saying I'll never do another Nuzlocke again, but
not for a while.
And so, if I guess once that's over, I will probably go back to posting like speed draws,
possibly art vlogs, and yeah, maybe a couple more of those little analytical, I don't know
if I'd call them in now.
Yeah, I guess they're in now.
Yeah, they're in there.
They're analytical rants.
They're just my thoughts.
I just thought, thought dump, fucking vlog, you know, I just talked about shit.
I really like those.
And I thought that for the final product, the effort, the effort put into quality of final
product ratio was really good on those.
And that ratio is something that I'm pursuing intensely these days.
And yeah, like, I mean, the first one was like, I just sat down and talked for half
an hour.
I spent maybe like, I don't know, two or three hours editing to turn like the film footage
into the repeating like looping clips because I like, I like that inspired by Digi's decompression
chamber.
I decided to do that.
And also, because that, that was an easy way to get by the YouTube restrictions because
they, Davoo and Digi kept telling me, Ben, don't go over 10 second clips.
And I was like, well, I don't want to find like, it's like a 20 minute video.
That means I'd have to find like, like a hundred clips.
I don't know.
I can't do math.
I need to find so many clips to fill that up.
Fuck that.
I was like, what if I found one clip and just looped it over and over again?
And it was great.
It was brilliant.
I'm a genius.
So anyway, I really liked how those came out.
And yes, I will do more of those.
And I guess that will probably be a big part of my YouTube shit going forward.
Or I hope so.
I hope they can find success because that one, the one about the Ghibli, the one about
only yesterday performed reasonably well actually, better than I expected it to.
How many, how many views does that have, man?
The Space Funeral 1 did okay.
It's like, is that like 3,000?
That's pretty good for a channel of like 2,000 subs.
Oh, or wait, wait, let me, let me double check.
It got, it got, yeah, just under 3,000.
Yeah, that's cool.
Yeah.
So it reached outside my sub base, which is, I mean, what more can you ask for?
To true.
That's the goal.
So yeah, that's my plans.
Some more YouTube stuff, lots more comics, maybe doing some actual printing and trade
paperback publishing and, you know, try and get that going.
Since that, since that was the goal.
Ever since I started drawing comics, that was the goal.
Like all my pages are formatted for book form and stuff.
They're not really formatted for the internet because I always wanted to sell them and to
sell physical copies.
It would be pretty cool to buy a Vapor's Trilogy book.
I know, man.
It would be, it would be pretty, that's the dream, right?
You know, I feel like, I feel like there's a lot of people that are more focused on that
than me.
Like I never really, I don't know.
Some people don't feel like they're legit until they have a physical form, a physical
book and like I don't feel that way, but still it is, it would be cool.
That feels somewhat of a hangover from the days when books were all there was.
Yeah.
But now there's, you know.
Totally.
The tangibility definitely kind of like, oh yeah.
It appeals to us as material beings.
It just makes it feel more significant.
There are, you know, there are people that would buy a comic book that would not read
a comic on the internet.
You know, like there's people that you can reach that way that you wouldn't reach on
the internet.
So like, you know, it's another thing, another region to expand into that would be neat.
And I would really, I would really like to get like picked up by a company, picked up
by a publisher and published, but if that doesn't happen, then I will just fucking bootstrap
and do it myself because that's what I've done my whole life and I'm going to keep doing
it for as long as necessary.
I'd like to get picked up by a big burly man who can protect me in his arms.
That's my goal for 2013.
Sure.
Like out of the act of one moon.
Get Machamp.
Oh yeah, Machamp.
That's right.
My favorite guy.
His warm embrace.
Well, that's cool.
Anything else?
Is that everything?
No.
Wait.
Yes.
Alright.
Patreon.com.
Of course.
Okay.
So everybody's gone.
So I guess.
All the important people gone.
Okay.
We can go home.
We can end the podcast now.
Thanks for coming everybody.
Goodbye.
Wait.
There are more people here.
Well, there's me.
I haven't gone.
I don't know.
I've made my stuff pretty clear in like my now second to last video.
I gotta tell you, I'm so thrilled to have managed to get that last, you know, edit
manga video out before the end of the year.
That was one of my goals.
Thank God I did it.
Yeah.
It took way too long anyway, but still might as well get it done.
Best manga ever, Lucifer and the Biscuit Hammer is, you know, it's really different
from your other stuff.
And yet I feel like it makes sense in the grand scheme of the best guy ever and what
and the values that your channel represents.
I agree.
Yeah.
I think it does work as, as like, like you're the best guy ever and every video you make
on anything has to be the best version of a review or a true thing of that thing ever.
Whatever it is, whatever it is, it's the best one that I know that like you've been wrestling
with the idea of like trying to find a way to increase your output of production, but
I feel like at this point that it almost spits in the face of the channel's like established
personality at this point, that like your production value is like so key to just like
your identity at this point.
And I think it's, it's something that YouTube is severely lacking.
I feel like you're, I think what you should probably be focusing on isn't like, how do
I make things faster, but how do I get people to partner their shekels in a more significant
fashion to, to fund my slow production.
I have, I have to disagree.
I really think that I really think there are areas where fat could be trimmed from the
production pipeline without sacrificing too much quality.
I think, I think that's a fair argument, but I don't, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying if you can trim the fat and make the same quality done faster, I agree, but
I don't think that the production values should drop down in the name of quicker output.
You know, I agree with that.
I agree.
And I think what it comes down to is sort of the way in which I release things like,
you know, making one 45 minute video about a thing and releasing it once every six months
is just like, you don't have to do it that way and it's not optimal.
So you know, there are other ways to get to the same end goal than doing it in that way.
So I mean, yeah, that's relevant.
Like these, these are a lot of the things I've been thinking about, about the way in
which I produce content.
Because you know, I like everything I've done, but I am really trying to think I'm very serious
at this point, since I've met all my obligations to making my stuff viable as a way to survive
on YouTube.
And people are already quite generous on Patreon with me, considering how much I've released.
It's, it's, it's very, it's very much appreciated.
But I do still need a bunch more if I want to be able to live solely on it.
So, you know, but you know, so that, that's where I'm at.
My goal is to in 2017, leave my job and do YouTube full time and you know, whatever capacity
is appropriate.
And a lot of that involves changing my content a little bit, you know, somewhat, and a lot
of it also involves working with the procrastinators.
Because I really see a bright future with, with the procrastinators and specifically projects
like the plebe and the weeb and other things that we haven't, that haven't even been, you
know, concocted yet.
But there are all kinds of things we could do.
And I really, I really use red letter media as an example of, of how you can make that
work.
Frankly, I don't know how those guys can afford to survive.
It doesn't seem like their channel is quite big enough to support, you know, I don't know
how many people are involved in that production, like six people, maybe some of them have jobs
they do on the side.
They're, you know, like they have that.
I don't know.
But that's fairly new, you know.
They have a Patreon.
Even before Patreon, they were selling merchandise and they were, they were selling films and
stuff.
So I'm assuming they're making a decent amount of money through merchandising.
Those guys make a lot of money.
Even on ad revenue.
I've bought two of their shirts over, over Christmas vacation.
And finally, I'm so glad I got a, I got a VHS repair shop t-shirt and I love it.
I love it.
That's what we need to do.
We got to, we got to merchandise the PCP.
You know, for real though, that's, that's, that's definitely true.
Right now the PCP makes zero money.
What's that made?
I can make some draws for like maybe shirt designs or something.
That'd be cool.
Yeah.
I really think in 2017, this is something that we should do.
Uh, it just, just kind of building up the organizational infrastructure here.
I mean, it'd be nice, really the, the show plebe and the weeb is sort of a PCP project,
but we would just release it on Digi's channel.
I mean, it's, you know, he did the thing for the most part, but since PCP is too small
and it wouldn't be paid attention to it, it's, it's released on that.
But like in the future, you know, this is the place where things like that would be
for the most part.
So, you know, I, I don't know, I don't have all the thoughts worked out yet, but I think
about it.
I think if we want the PCP channel to be like Reddler to Meteor, we would need to have like
a, like a star show, like Mr. Plinkett to go on there.
And I don't know whether anyone would be up for not putting it on their own channel
and instead putting it on the PCP, which is why it's kind of weird that.
Well, it would have to grow, you know, I looked it up and their Patreon is at $16,000 per
month.
Well, that's pretty good.
There we go.
It's pretty good.
Yeah.
That's split between, you know, like how many people I'm gonna say six, but I don't
know.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe some of the guys are part-time and it's just like Mike and Jay and Rich, I guess.
I don't know.
I think Rich is a construction worker.
What?
He just showed up.
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh God.
Does he build things?
Yeah.
Like he just does this like part-time.
He does build.
Instruction work.
Man, that's, that's, I want to say that's crazy.
That union dog, that union.
Wait.
Oh God.
I just remembered the most important goal for 2017.
Yeah.
Just touch more boobs.
Oh.
I don't even get into that shit.
What?
Who said that?
I don't know.
I didn't hear it, but it made me mad.
I just said I hope you kill yourself.
Oh wow.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
I just, yes.
I crave the, I crave the touch of a woman, the scent of a woman.
And I must have it.
I must hunt one down.
By any means.
Ladies get out there and date him.
Ladies go on and date him.
But she smells good.
Smells like a woman.
You know.
That's a good smell.
Then that's what I'm looking for.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah.
Mm.
Yep.
That's all I have to say about that.
Great.
Let's, let's please move on.
Okay.
I don't know.
I'm just thinking if I have anything else to say.
I need money.
Everyone give me money on Patreon.
Yeah.
Faster videos will come.
I need it most.
I just want to say that I do think legitimately my transition from being able to do YouTube
barely any time to do it at the end of the day after I work all fucking day to being
able to do it all the time would be a big transformation and we all know best guy ever
is the best content.
We all know it.
It's a fact.
You can't deny it.
So please people do yourselves in the world of favor by, by giving, giving me money so
I can, so I can make more of it.
How much do you need to do it full time?
My, my goal is a month.
This would be a massive pay cut from what I make now.
But if I made around $750 per video on my Patreon, I think that would be a starting like
livable wage.
I could build on that.
How are you people using such a little money?
Based on how many videos per month?
Based on two.
That's based on two videos.
Well, I'll raise you one, Nate.
I, I could do, I could work full time for $600 a month, I think.
But you already do.
I think I could swing it.
You do for $0 a month already.
So, so who, so who's delivering the better value on your dollar here, patrons?
Do we have any fan questions this week?
Oh yeah.
That's, that's good.
We certainly do.
Let's go to the Twitter.
I need to have like a private discussion with both of you and how you can live on such
a little money.
I need to learn these secrets.
My overhead is like nothing.
It's not.
I mean, no, talk to Ben.
I, I live on a salary, so I'm, I'm okay.
You know, don't.
Ben moves.
My, my, I, I pay, I pay rent at, at Digi's house and I fucking eat leftovers and that's
my whole life.
Shit.
Yeah.
Ben's a master of, uh.
I need to move in with Digi then, clearly.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
Don't, don't muscle in on my leftovers.
I eat nothing but ramen right now.
I eat those for the Pokemon battles.
Oh shit.
That's true.
Okay.
So we're, we're moving on.
Last time.
Yeah.
Munch, uh, uh, monkey was wondering where Ben found those leftovers.
Now you have your answer.
Um, so, okay.
So it's time to move into the non-gay section of the thing where we, uh, answer questions.
We, we always tweet and when we start recording generally on Saturdays, uh, at the procrastinators,
uh, Twitter at TP Crastinators, uh, that we're recording to ask us questions that we will
answer at the end of the show.
So, uh, let me see, I put that out and I'm going to find some fucking questions in here.
I should mention right now that we're all recording this on New Year's Eve, so none
of us went to a party.
Yeah, I know.
None of us had any friends.
No.
Pretend it's not that night.
Pretend that we're cool.
I'll be, I'll be drinking maybe.
Yeah.
I'll be trying.
I guess I'll be trying.
That's how shit my life is.
I'm tipsy right now.
Yeah.
I have no friends and I'm home alone.
Here, uh, okay.
Here's one.
I mean, I don't know if anyone even has an answer for this, but we can kind of chew on
it while I look for more.
Uh, anyone have a best creator non-PCP of 2016?
Who's, who's somebody who's made some of that impress you this year?
Yeah.
Why did we need that, that special caveat?
Of course I wasn't going to pick a fucking PCP member.
Well, because obviously everyone would just say me.
They would say me if they knew.
So, exempting me.
That's true.
Well, the Ben Saints and the Nates of the World might, but I don't know about the rest
of us.
That's right.
Um, some of it.
Okay.
What happened in 2016 in terms of YouTube videos?
Uh, the Fine Bros launched their really successful network.
Yes.
Ben, Ben, Ben.
Got him.
That's pretty good.
Uh, my answer is the Fine Boy.
H3, H3 stopped being funny.
Jon Tron stopped being funny.
H3 is okay.
H3, H3 is the same as he has always been.
Okay, so he was never funny.
He's got more money than he had.
Yeah.
A lot more.
Um, everyone sucks this year.
Uh, Maddox destroyed his personal and professional reputation.
Oh no.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, Dick, Dick Show is just a commercial for Dick and how cool he can be.
And it's the 50 second.
Is that a good thing or a bad thing though?
It's a 50 second tie as Patreon.
He can't stand it.
Okay.
I don't, I don't watch it, but I can't stand it.
Oh, I love the Dick Show.
It's great.
Yeah.
I don't want to give it a chance.
I don't want to give it a chance to win me over.
I can't, I can't think of a single one 2016.
I mean, 2016 is a whole year.
So that's a long time.
I'm trying to remember anything I even gave a fuck about.
Did any video games, did any video games come out this year?
Doom 2016 kicked fucking ass.
Yeah.
Wasn't Dark Souls 3 this year too?
It was.
Oh wait, wait.
Oh wait.
One minute ago.
It's, it's, can I be in this video by a HGB guy?
Let me link it.
I don't know what it's going to be, but it's, it's my brother in a horse mask.
I'm giving, I'm giving artist of the year to HGB guy for sure.
That's my Amungus.
Yeah.
The fucking Champ of Amungus.
He gets, he gets it.
Everyone go onto YouTube, go to HGB guy.
Let's put a fucking link in the description to the artist of the year.
The HGB guy is your brother.
Yeah.
That's right.
I feel like I've seen that person fave some of my tweets and I had no idea.
For introducing, for introducing the character of Cunt Corona.
You know, he's going to be big.
He's going to be big.
I'm really excited for what he's going to do this year.
Oh, I want to say I did, I took great strides this year because I finally got a YouTube URL.
My YouTube URL is now, is now C slash Ben St. Comics and I'm so fucking proud of myself.
Hey, hey, try entering that URL sometime without the C because it just works sometimes.
I don't know.
It's a little mysterious.
Yeah.
Give it a try.
Whenever I post a link that's like going to be a text, I just get rid of the C and it's fine.
It just sort of figures it out that hypocrite means hypocrite user.
Okay.
Here's, here's a substantive question.
Oh, I forgot to say who that was.
I'll go back to it in a minute, but at kin, kin.
Okay.
It's kin KKUK at that guy says, are you planning on doing any other PCP races anytime soon?
And the answer is yes.
Yes.
We are thinking about what to do.
We don't know what they're going to be yet.
Race war.
Race forever, forever to decide on the, on the Pokemon race.
I said we should do Spyro one first person to get 10 dragons wins.
I don't do over that audience.
That's not a bad.
I like that kind of goal.
I think that's not bad at some point.
I feel.
Yes.
I think that Mega Man or Mega Man X, but like a specific challenge.
Let's just do them all at the same time.
Each one of us picks our own game, makes up our own goal, and then we all race toward
the end.
I'm just telling you, I want a speed run gotten home in that case.
That's a 20 second completion time.
Oh, by the way, I just want to say before the best creator, non-PCB of 2016, that was
at the out sin.
So thanks.
Thanks buddy for that question.
HGB guy.
Yes.
It was him.
Okay.
So here's, here's one more and we get this is going to be the last one, I guess.
Anyone have by at John Attenbury.
What is the top PCP meme of 2016?
So Radcon 2 was this year.
I mean, Radcon 1 was this year.
So there was quite a few.
Oh man.
There was a lot.
It would have to be.
I like, I like handboys.
I think I got to go with handboys.
Oh yeah.
It's definitely.
Handboys.
Yep.
That's it.
That's the answer.
I also, I also enjoy, it's not really a PCB exclusive meme.
Well actually, there's half of the people here that weren't at the first Radcon and don't
know handboys.
Yeah.
I have no context.
What I enjoyed the most simply because it related to something I was present for was
the resurrection of Double Batman and introduction of Triple Joker.
Double Batman, Double Batman.
Yeah.
Expansion into the Triple Joker as well.
Only a Triple Joker can kill the Double Batman.
That is a solid pick.
That is proven in the, in the.
Solid match.
You know, my favorite meme was the wrestling show that we did.
The wrestling.
That was great.
Everything that happened in that thing was great.
Everything about it was just solid, solid gold.
It was.
Man, I can't wait to do another one at Radcon 2 in one week.
Actually, oh my God, it's so, it's so soon.
It's not weird.
It's like five days from now.
That is fucking weird.
Well, I don't know if this counts as a meme, but the, the hunger, the hunger games, the
hunger games battles that the hippo has been popularized.
He's popularized them a couple of times this year and I really like it.
We did the Pokemon ones to pick Pokemon teams.
And then we did the hippo.
You just did the one with the PCP.
That was great.
It was great.
It just so happened to be perfect.
Especially with you.
Yes.
And the KKK and Vincent.
Me and the KKK and Vincent and Davoo and, and I was like stealing from, from, from Brunswick
when he's asleep.
I think I'm just going to let all of the KKK in the back.
Yeah.
When his back was turned, he's too powerful.
That's, uh, and then at the very end, uh, when, uh, Colt came back from beyond the grave
to execute Jesse.
Yeah.
Glorious, glorious.
Okay.
I think we're done for now.
No more questions.
But there are so many questions.
Uh, well, I mean, we can't fucking do this all day.
How long have we been recording for?
Wait, wait, wait.
An hour and 10 minutes.
We've got like 10 minutes, 10 minutes until, uh, New Year's for England.
Yeah.
Oh, should we just hang out for 10 minutes until it's New Year's time?
I think we should.
We could do, we could do a few more questions.
Okay, tell you what.
We'll do some more questions.
Especially the question I won.
Oh, okay.
Go for it.
And then until 5.5, will, will you read it?
Uh, will I read it?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm looking.
Uh, one sec.
I don't, I know.
Is this just on the Twitter?
I mean, I'm looking at it.
I don't.
Oh, here it is.
Okay.
Let's see.
Oh shit.
Okay.
This is a good question.
Uh, like you said, at Ninto 55, if the entire PCP were to move to one country, which would
you guys want, excluding the USA, UK, and Japan for obvious reasons, I might, I want
to go to Japan dog.
I want to go be a Gaijin, uh, live in the neat life, but can't do it.
So.
Estonia.
No, guys, guys.
Oh, let's, let's just go to Lithuania.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Like, guys, Lithuania has like the best, fastest, unlimited interwebs.
It's, it's.
Oh, that's all I needed to hear.
It's great.
Like, like it doesn't, at least the internet I'm with, like it doesn't have any monthly
limits and it doesn't have like a stupid limit on it for like to download at like 16
megabytes for whatever.
It's, what's the, uh, what's the lolliporn situation?
Allowed?
Not allowed?
I, I haven't looked into it, Nate.
Oh, you've looked into it.
Don't lie to me.
You, you shame me, Nate.
You shame me.
I'm just looking out for your best interest, Ben.
I'm trying to protect you.
No, stop.
Get out of here.
Don't, don't.
Any other contenders here?
Yeah.
The internet's great.
The food is great.
It's, it's a good.
It's a good country.
Like if you guys, guys, like the best part is if you get paid for it, it's a good country.
The best part is if you get paid by like Patreon, whatever, by like foreign money and
just spend it in Lithuania, everything would be super cheap to you in Lithuania.
Yes.
That's true.
You're making a solid argument right now, man.
And if you say, if when you're coming in, if you say that you're a war refugee, they
just like give you a hot wife to rape.
So, you know, looking, that sounds pretty good.
Nate, what the fuck, man?
That's, that's right.
That's what I hear.
I appreciate it.
All right.
We're, we're in Eastern Europe, not Western.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
My bad.
We can go to Germany and that'll be fine.
Actually, the refugees escaped from Lithuania to go to Germany from what I've heard.
Yeah.
But let's not go into that.
But yeah.
I was going to say, oh yeah, yeah.
It's super cheap.
I probably could.
If I moved to Lithuania, I probably could live on what I make on Patreon right now.
And then I'd never have to draw another comic in my life.
Thank God.
Yes.
I do want to say that I think Nigeria might be a good place because there's this, there's
this prince who's been emailing me for a while.
And it sounds like there's some good land deals that are just available to me.
If I were to, you know, go down there.
Wireless LAN.
Yeah.
He's going to give me a budget on my, on my land.
Well, hey guys.
I mean, it, it's technically, in some respects, it is part of the United States, but it is
also kind of an extra dimensional location.
So I'm voting for the city of Quickville.
Oh, that's a good one.
The city of Quickville, it is a cool place with an average amount of cool places to chill
at.
That's true.
I mean, they've got McDonald's.
They've got the mall.
Great places for a date.
McDonald's.
Quickville mall.
The mayor is a benevolent dictator.
That's true.
He polices our thoughts for our own well-being.
So I appreciate that.
Yeah.
Nobody's gay.
They've cured gayness in Quickville.
And, and asexuality too.
So there you go.
Thank God.
I, I won't go there.
No thanks.
You might be obliterated if you set foot mage.
So watch out.
Disintegrate.
I think we should all move to LazyTown.
Oh, man.
It's like a paradise.
It is a paradise.
I am pretty lazy.
And we could join Rot and Robbie's team and help them out, catching that sport of flop
faggot.
I mean, Robbie Rotten, you fucking...
Oh, what did I say?
What did I say?
You said Rot and Robbie.
Oh, it's the same shit.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on, dude.
Wrong way around.
And we're, we're the biggest, uh, uh, anime analysis of LazyTown guys there is.
So you gotta, we gotta reputation to maintain.
That's true.
I was analyzing it in my head every moment I see it.
Um, okay.
We need a new question.
This is, this, this one's dying.
Um.
We'll go on, man.
Let's see.
I'm just sitting here.
I'm just sitting here vaping, vaping my life away.
Okay.
Here's, here's one, uh, uh, by, uh, at unwe on me.
Uh, how mad.
So we're looking for a one to 10.
Will Ben be when mumky beats him again?
So, you know, what's...
I can answer that.
I can answer that question.
Only you can, Ben.
It's, it's, it's an, it's an exponential increase every time.
So like the first time I was upset.
The second time I was 10 times as upset.
Right.
So next time.
I detected that.
Yeah.
So next time.
115 times.
I will be, it'll be a hundred times.
And, um, that'll be, that'll be, I think, that'll be approaching the limit of what a
human being, uh, can survive.
Yeah.
If I can sleep up here, Ben.
It's like mob cycle.
Sure, mumky.
Exactly.
To get your expectations at a fair level.
Sure.
I need to assure you beyond a reasonable doubt that you will never beat me in that game.
I fucking promise you.
Okay.
And that's all I have to say.
Expectations managed.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm excited to do it.
Oh shit, Ben.
We, we got a battle.
I battled mumky already.
Uh, yeah.
I am, I, I'm, I'm a little behind.
Oh, and I want to battle mumky too.
We'll do that.
Guys, like, battle on the, like, the page where, uh.
We go, it, it's, it's, I don't know.
You gotta add each of his friend codes.
Oh, you mean, like, are they actually giving me?
You add friend codes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Not on Smogon.
Yeah, okay.
Although you can't, or not Smogon, showdown, although you can do it there too.
Okay, here's one, here's one.
Um, guys, by at Sefixer, it's S-E-P-H-Y-X-E-R.
So fuck you, dude.
Sefixer.
Um, what kind of project would you like to do if you had all the time, skills, money,
and motivation, et cetera, to do it?
I would make exactly the same kind of content.
I might make an anime myself, but other than that, I'd probably just make the same kind
of shit I like doing already.
If I had a limited whatever, I would like to recreate Homestuck, but starring me and the
PCP, I'd actually have a good ending.
Which you did start, which you did start.
Oh man.
Sorry, I just realized what I would do.
I would make a game the one I've always wanted to make.
What kind of game?
Kind of a tale too.
No.
Hippo, I did tell you about it when we met up before Pokemon Go a little bit.
Remember?
It's kind of like Pokemon, but not.
Actually, I'd probably make a game too.
There's a game I did that's burning in the back of my mind for a better part of five
years.
Oh really?
I would probably do that.
That's cool.
Well, mostly I would do the same things I'm doing now.
I would draw comics, but I would outsource some of the work.
I would outsource backgrounds and things that take up a lot of time and that I don't feel
nabbed that much.
I would pay someone to do background art and stuff.
That's cool.
I would probably make games.
I would start dabbling in mechanically minimal lists, narrative, short game projects is something
that I've kind of wanted to do.
So you'd make artsy faggots shit and off to worry about the money because you're already
rich.
No.
He's trying to get around saying yes, but we all do.
What I'm saying is that I'm not saying that I would make super artsy shit.
I'm saying that the games I would make would be small and not.
I wouldn't make sprawling RPGs or platforms.
Are we talking like Tower of Heaven here and that kind of shit?
I don't have a dream game project that I make.
I just did something I'd like to dabble in.
That's all I'm saying.
All right.
That's cool.
I want to mention, in my version of Homestuck, since I'm the main character I'm replacing
John, John Vriska, it's going to be canon.
It's going to be the entire, as soon as she ends the story, it's going to be the whole
thing.
But you said John Vriska is going to be canon?
Oh, because it's you now.
Okay.
I got you.
It's going to be the whole thing.
It's going to be just 300 million thousand pages of me and Vriska just kissing the concert.
I'd read that for a dollar.
Now this is how I know you guys are all gay because when this guy said what kind of project
you want to do, you immediately thought art project, when there are far more important
projects to get done.
Let me tell you what I would do.
Yeah, but I don't care about the truth.
Let me tell you what I would fucking do if I had all the time, money, and resources
to do it, which are already available.
Star Trekking.
I would work.
We need a warp drive, guys.
We need a warp drive because right now this planet is a ticking time bomb and humanity's
existence is at stake.
We've only got, who knows, millions of years, thousands of years, 10 years.
I don't know.
We work on our space program.
We need to colonize other planets.
We need to fucking get out there under the stars because I don't want humanity to die
like a punk on one tiny ass planet.
We need a warp drive.
That's the number one thing we need.
Nate, I hear what you're saying, but I think the right answer is to build Trump's wall.
Once we solve the immigrant crisis, the warp drives are going to fall from the fucking sky.
God will then understand that we've done his bidding and will just give it to us because
that's-
We need to nuke all of Europe and then we'll probably be safe.
Sorry, mate.
You've got to be sacrificed for the greater good.
Yeah.
I'll also get-
Not if I sacrifice you first.
Right, you know.
Is England also, Gabe, you'd know this, is England building a wall between itself and
Europe as well?
It already has a wall.
It's like the fucking-
It's called the ocean, isn't it?
It's the ocean.
They're an island.
Yeah, but that's not impressive.
No, they need to cave in that tunnel.
Yeah, that's right.
There's an undersea tunnel, right?
I don't think so.
The channel, dog.
The channel tunnel thing.
Yeah, there is.
No, you're right.
You're right.
Back me up.
Yeah.
He's gone.
Do you live in the channel, Gabe?
Is that where you are right now?
What happened?
There's a tube, right?
There's a tube between France and England.
He's asking if the tunnel exists between England and France.
Yes, there's a train that goes called the Eurostar.
I've gone on it a couple times.
In fact, I've gone on it like eight years ago.
Nailed the little boy.
Hey, we're two minutes to midnight.
Okay, thank God, because I'm just filling time here, folks.
We're filling time.
Can we squeeze in one more question?
I wasn't joking when I said I had to pee at the very beginning.
We probably can.
How do you deal?
Okay, by at I Like Serial 421, how do you deal with creative dry spells
when you have people constantly wanting new content?
I don't know.
I ignore them.
You get depressed and you curl up and you turn on the shower.
I don't have that problem because my projects take so long
that I never lose ideas.
You're saying the shower until you die.
I don't give a fuck about people wanting new content.
The one that wants the content to be done more than anyone else is me.
It's only me that I'm a coward.
Maybe he means to best succeed, feed the algorithm or any of that shit.
Well, there's two options.
You either just do it anyway or you do something else instead.
Okay, we're getting close here.
Usually what I do is I distract myself by making a give and take video.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
If you got something you want to do, you either do it anyway or you do something else.
Who's watching the bombs?
I'm getting rid of Europe right now.
What's our time?
We got seconds?
23.
I don't have seconds.
Let me see.
We're like one minute away.
No, it's midnight for me.
You guys are in the same time zone?
Yeah.
They should be.
They're in England, dog.
Wait, is it?
Wait.
In England it is.
Here we go.
For me, it's a few seconds behind, all right?
Count it down.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We did it.
Hippo, how many celebrities are dead in 2017?
100 million.
Oh, thank God.
I'm hoping more die this year.
All right.
That's it.
Thanks for that.
Man, that was great timing.
So we're ready to wrap it up.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Thanks, everybody, for asking questions.
Make sure you tweet us.
If you got, this was a different one.
This wasn't a topic that we took from anybody.
Actually, some people did say talk about 2017.
But tweet us at tpcrastinators throughout the week with ideas for
things that we'd talk about next week's show.
And also, when we record every week, we put out a tweet that says,
ask us questions.
You know, we responded this fucking tweet with questions and we'll
answer them as we did right here.
So if you want to do that shit, go to the Twitter at tpcrastinators.
Send us shit.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
And we'll see you next week.
Bye-bye.
Happy news.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money.
I'm supposed to be creating funny.
Think that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius.
That's what they came for.
Instead, I'm tweeting, hashtag repeating.
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah, it's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life, being a genius.