Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the favorite
show that's on the internet.
I'm the best guy ever, and I'm joined by Hippocrit, Mumkey Jones, and the Munchman
himself, Mr. Munchyshatsky.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I have a story about all the sex toys I received during my monkey mail bag thing where I made
the great decision to open up a peel box and let my loving, adoring fans send me, you know,
fan mail, books, games, but no, they sent me like fucking tanga eggs and dildos and shit,
naturally, but I made a rule with myself that whatever I get in this funky mail bag I will
keep and use as props in future videos just so like people can see them and be like, oh
yeah, I remember when I got that, that's funny, so I'm at a point where my bedroom closet,
I'm still living with my parents, is full of sex eggs and dildos and adult diapers and
all this weird kinky shit and like, of course my parents don't watch the videos or know
anything about it, so they just like, one day I just suddenly have all this weird shit in
my closet and like, you know, mom, it's for the monkey shit, you don't need to understand,
don't even question it, but then I was doing the Vietnamese crystal nuzlocke and I reached
a point, I think at the seventh gym where the game froze and I couldn't continue so I had
to quit the series, but then I had a fan on Snapchat named Julian who said, hey, I'll
play a new file and I'll catch you back up to where you were and I'll redo everything
and I said, oh yeah, that'd be great, thank you so much and he says, all I want for payment
is for you to send me one of those tanga eggs in the mail.
So I was like, okay, there we go.
So you did it.
And Julian saved the let's play.
What a hero, what a hero.
I don't know why he wanted it.
Oh, I can't imagine why.
What a weird request.
Just fucking order your own, why did you want one of mine?
He wants it with your taint on it, you know, with your corruption, that's what he wants.
So that's my story.
There you go, Julian, nobody knew that, but now that's out there.
Congrats.
Well, I only have need for one toy and that is Lego.
And when I'm in the mood, when I'm in the mood, I make for myself a little penis prism out of Lego.
Right.
I just, I just just build it and keep adding bricks until it's completely crushed.
And then, you know, I attack people with it.
It's not a joke.
I'm not, I don't actually do that.
Oh, I have this fetish where I get off on accidentally stepping on a Lego and hurting
my foot really bad.
I like that.
It's very specific.
It makes me cum every time.
Yeah.
Hey, speaking of that, I don't get that.
I do not get that.
I've stood in Lego boxes.
Oh, come on.
They're hurting like a motherfucker, dude.
They don't hurt more than nails.
People make them out like, oh my God, it's the worst.
If you get about a nail, if you step on it, it usually isn't sticking out.
They don't hurt more than nails.
Guys, look at all the ways I can hurt myself more than a Lego.
What's the big deal?
Just watch me.
I mean, it's not like lighting your face on fire.
All right.
I get that it's funny to over exaggerate something to be like, oh, it's funny how
much I'm scared of spiders or I hate Lego or, you know, how much I'm willing to
kill myself, you know, stuff like that.
You wouldn't actually do it.
You wouldn't actually go that far.
You say you do and it's funny.
But I've never, ever hurt myself standing on a Lego except when I was like three.
Like I can stand on Legos right now.
And it's fine.
It happens to people when they're like eight.
Yeah.
It traumatizes them from a young age and that's why it has that stigma.
I just don't like the idea that it's cool to be an adult and saying, oh man, I still
step on Legos and I'm still getting hurt and I'm still a pansy about it.
It hurts, dude.
It doesn't hurt.
It really does hurt that bad.
Yeah, it does.
It does not.
Okay.
Your thing is you're a weirdo British hobbit man with hobbit feet.
So you can take this kind of punishments.
It only weighs like 90 pounds.
Yeah.
I used to eat Legos all the time so they don't scare me anymore.
That's fair.
I don't like this podcast at all.
I want to run away.
I want to run away and I want to delete my audio.
I don't like it.
I don't like what's been going on.
Incidentally, here's a question about that.
When is the, okay, it's by at Levy Jevy says, when is the PCB going to cross over with
the Inseparable Social Media podcast?
Never.
Never have, we hate those guys.
Don't ever fucking ever say that again.
Yeah.
That's off the table.
Don't even, all right, new question.
I'm trying to think of anything I can say that'd be funny, but nothing is coming to
mind.
Terry Dactyl says, what species has more value?
Mimes or clowns?
You fucking know, baby.
It's fucking clowns.
Mimes have actual superpowers though.
Yeah.
And mimes have never made shitty rap songs.
My favorite mime is, my favorite mime is Pee Pee the Frog.
Pee Pee is very nice.
He's a funny Mimee, yes.
Le Epic Mime, XD.
Here's what we have to know.
Mr. Mime, Marxist influenced moon enemy.
Mime.
Yeah.
He's fucking communist from space.
Can't trust him.
Clowns, homegrown, homegrown, American, Land of the Free, American First, Nationalist Party,
German Workers' Party, taking back the state, giving the tower back to the people, taking
over the government, annexing the places where they did that.
Poland, yeah.
You know what?
Munchie, Munchie, listen up.
I need you to answer this seriously.
Who wins in a fight?
Well, 45, Mr. Mime are three ICP juggalos.
Who wins?
Who can use thunderbolt?
Who can use thunderbolt in those two groups?
Juggalos are poison type, probably.
They're both poison and dark type.
So they normally would be, but they'll have a dark voice, so they'll lean.
Because they go to the dark carnival, because they live in the darkest world.
They live in it.
They live with the dark carnival.
They're going to know about all the miracles and the magic of the fucking world through
the dark carnival.
The dark carnival is your inspiration to witness that without explanation.
Just take a look at this fine creation and enjoy a band with appreciation.
Ghosts, ghosts, the midnight ghosts, mysteries of the world, magic at the most.
I'm fucking gay.
I'm a juggal.
Mr. Mime is a fucking communist.
He's a Soviet black state puppet regime set up by Stalin to be a tank of egg salesman
for his personal use.
It's not real, okay?
Snap out of it.
We're breaking the social conditioning.
Breaking the globalist.
Mr. Mime is a globalist.
Get him out.
Oh, yeah?
Well, guess what, Munchy?
Mr. Mime can use reflex.
All that shit just went right back to you.
Shit, fuck.
Yeah, you're right.
Shit.
You didn't see that coming.
You can't beat Mr. Mime.
He's too good in the OU, dude.
What about the insane Mime posse?
That would be our sign language.
Yeah.
Completely silent raps.
It's a rap group for deaf people.
Just, just, yeah.
They're lesser known.
They're lesser known, yeah.
Wait, how are they for deaf people?
Because they only do sign language because they're Mimes.
Well, you know what you can do?
Oh, right, deaf people.
I confuse that with blind.
Like, I just imagine like blind people would listen to Mime rap.
Because they don't know.
Okay, what do you think about this?
Okay, this is my idea for music for deaf people.
We sort of encase them in a full, like, rubber suit, right?
Okay, so their whole body is, like, surrounded by this.
And then, like, that surface is the speaker.
And you know, like, because people, you know, music is like sound waves in the air.
And then you blast the beats into that surrounding film on their whole body.
And you crack their bones.
And they can experience the music.
Break the music.
And then you buy, like, a pack of mechanical pencil from CVS.
Right.
You pick up the eraser.
Then you pour out the little, like, individual, like, mechanical pencil, like, parts.
Then you put the leg in down your lemon pipe.
And then you push in there so small.
Then it can fit right in.
And then it gets to the point where it has a little bit of resistance to what breaks.
And now there's a ton of layers, like, five or so pieces of mechanical pencil lead
inside your lemon pipe.
And you squeeze it around.
And that's what you have to live with for the rest of your life.
Is that it?
Is that it, Nate?
Yeah, God, I guess that's it.
That's one way to think about it.
The BotFlyz will use the lead in their Minecraft expeditions.
Yes.
Have any of you guys ever been to, like, a real musical production, like, an off-Broadway
show or something?
Yeah.
I've been to a real Broadway show.
What's they're dealing with?
They always have somebody off to the side of the stage doing sign language.
Like, who is that for?
Stage directions.
No.
No, no, it's for the audience.
It's for the audience.
Yeah, but, like, why would you go to a musical if you're deaf?
Because you can't watch the show if you're reading the sign language and you can't hear
the music.
So what's the point?
It's the same with, like, I guess, subtitles and anime, I guess.
Yeah, like, you know, you kind of have to look away briefly.
But in this case, you literally can only watch the sign language person.
You can't watch the people on the stage dancing.
You can't hear the music.
I don't know why you would go to that show if it's $300 a ticket.
Sometimes you just want to go out on the town, you know?
You want to, even if you're deaf, you want to look pretty.
You want to go out with all your fam.
Some people are, like, partially deaf.
Like, they can't understand things, but it's sort of muffled.
So they can still hear, like, beats and shit.
There's a lot to enjoy about the experience in addition to hearing it, I guess, so...
May I just want to be the presence of other wizards, you know?
That's right. That's right.
Okay, well, I guess that's their choice, but it sounds retarded to me.
Off the record, off the record.
This is terrible.
Can we have this be the bonus episode instead?
I don't want this to actually come out.
What's wrong with it?
This is perfectly fine.
I'm very embarrassed that this has happened.
I'm really sorry, everybody.
Dude, we'll edit it out.
We'll cut this part out, too.
No.
No, cut this part in. Double it.
Double it right now.
Like, overlay it.
Like, echo and reverb it.
Yeah, crunchy.
Crunchy, you should edit the episode.
I do.
Okay, here's a question that I've been thinking about, sort of, for a while.
So, at Ice Killer 159, what a badass, with that sick escavalier icon that I love so dearly,
says, what are each of you guys' Myers Briggs type?
And the reason I bring that up is because I think this is retarded, and I hate those,
and I don't know why people like them.
My Myers Briggs type is.
Oh, God.
Isis.
Yeah!
I was going to say, I was going to say ICPC.
That's my, uh...
Introverted Socialist, uh...
E-Bills.
Islamist.
Sexham.
Inferior.
Stupid.
Oh, that's what they're called.
Those losers.
I would classify myself as a supreme nihilist, deep-cover Republican.
Deep-cover as in, like, you're deep in the blue pill trenches?
Possible deep-cover Republican.
I don't know yet.
Okay.
We're going to pull back some layers.
Does anyone here have any sort of defense of why I should give a shit about these Myers Briggs
types?
Tell me why they aren't just masturbatory things.
We can be like, I'm a this.
Oh, my God, you're a that.
I don't think anyone here cares about them.
It's literally the same shit as fucking...
It's the same shit as fucking astrological science.
They mean nothing.
They're fucking retarded.
I don't give a shit about them.
Oh, like Star Science?
They're fun.
They're kind of fun.
Star Science.
Yeah, so that's the reason.
So the question is, do I like fun?
No, I hate fun.
But it's not fun.
It's so like they can feel superior.
Like, oh, you think you're cool.
I have the same personality type as BBC Sherlock.
Look how fucking cool and smart I am.
Oh, yeah.
You're like, yeah, you're so cool.
I have fucking Hitler's DNA and Gandhi's DNA.
Fuck that bitch.
Yeah, I think it's bullshit and those tumblr fucks who like that shit need to fuck up.
But that's a weird thing.
I am an ENFP bitch.
Is that a real?
Is that real?
Yeah, I tested it when I was in like kindergarten.
Well, you're extroverted?
Somebody in the PCPS and extroverted personality.
Yeah.
Imagine that.
Much should be the one.
Okay, but here the thing about this that creeps me out is that it's like some like it seems
like a lot of smart people get into this.
And like they, I don't know, like people really care about this.
So like, is there something I'm missing?
No, they're actually not smart people.
They think they're proving that they're smart by doing this.
Yeah, I think I think what it is like, like with the star sign stuff, the star sign stuff,
there's not enough different variables that go into that.
It's just when you were born and people are like initially like, oh, well, that doesn't
mean anything.
But when it's like, oh, I took a test and now, now I have a thing that I can attribute
to a celebrity that like, like now I'm like that guy, you know, it's, it's more legitimate
in their eyes.
And I guess they like it.
I mean, I didn't know it.
Yeah, I didn't know IQ score aren't the people who are probably that smart.
Yeah, I didn't know that it was even like not real.
I just did it once and I was like, well, and then I forgot it like a week later.
So yeah.
Well, it's interesting you bring up IQ because a lot of people think that IQ is like a totally
bullshit thing that doesn't actually have any impact on life.
But it is pretty well proven that IQ does have a direct correlation to like life success.
Like it's not all the time, but it does, it doesn't matter.
I'm saying the type of people who actually care about it and talk about it.
Yeah.
I think about IQ so little because I'm the smartest you see that makes sense to me.
That makes sense to me.
I don't even know what a high IQ is.
Is it 50?
Is it two?
Here's why Malcolm on Malcolm in the middle is a great character because he is so cool
because he's fucking black and you want to be like him because you just love black people
so much.
Yes.
As having an IQ of 160.
But instead of going around telling people his IQ, he proves that he's smart by being
a fucking smart person.
Yeah.
Malcolm's great.
Uh, monkey.
Cut this little bin.
Cut this part out of the gas.
We should both, you should talk about Malcolm from the Malcolm in the middle and I should
talk about Malcolm.
Malcolm's at the same time.
Go.
Timmy Turner went into each other's worlds.
That was very attractive.
I don't remember that ever.
Maybe it's just never had a childhood.
Oh boo boo boo.
Oh yeah well have you played Jimmy Neutron
Attack of the Tonkeys on PS2.
He becomes the nihilist trying to make the millennials feel bad.
The best video game ever.
Is that true?
I'm serious.
Fucking Jimmy Neutron Attack of the Tonkeys on PS2
is actually my favorite PS2 game.
I've never talked about it because I'm saving
like a 20 hour like analysis.
Would that constantly be better than Shadow the Hedgehog?
I just don't know.
It's marginally worse.
What about Will Ville off the rails?
That's pretty good.
You ever play that one?
We carnival dude?
We carnival?
That's the height of an artistic American spirit.
That was for PS3 you idiot.
What are we doing?
What is this?
Nate's going to find another question.
I sure am.
You're not the bossamino.
I've been scrolling for some.
And I'm a baby.
This is what I was saying.
When I was said I'm truly embarrassed
and I'm really sorry.
I was the one who made the piece of it.
This is the best.
Okay.
All right.
Here's another one.
My extreme distaste is part of why it's the best.
That's probably true.
Okay.
Here's a question.
Here we go.
IkloneIKLone asks, what's the best console of all time?
And why is it the GameCube?
The PS2.
I said PS2 before you said GameCube.
Bitch.
I win.
That's true.
I think I would go with the original Nintendo DS.
Actually.
I would go with the Nintendo DS.
Why?
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, that's right.
Why is the original?
The original original broke instantly.
Okay.
Well, to be fair, I guess my favorite was the, you know, like the slightly smaller one
that came out with.
The DS Lite.
Yeah, the DS Lite.
Exactly.
The DS Lite.
It's that one because it had.
You could play Pokemon Platinum.
Oh, man.
I can't.
Diamond, dude.
Diamond.
No.
Okay.
I've gotten like the most joy out of my DS than I did.
Yeah, there it is.
There's the one.
You liar.
You're a fake gamer because it's a Game Boy.
A Game Boy.
I tricked you.
I just seemed to like to make sure that you knew that they was a girl.
Oh, shit.
I know that's a Game Boy.
I've heard that jingle more times than I've heard my own voice.
Yeah, I got goofed.
Well, I felt tricked out of the way.
Oh, wait, because the DS starts up with that.
Yeah, that's the one.
Okay.
See, I'm a real gamer girl.
Anyway, the DS I played in my bed.
My favorite way to play video games is sitting up with a bunch of pillows behind me reclining
in my bed all tucked in and cozy with my fucking console in my head.
And I figured out how to hack my DS so I had literally every game for free on the entire
console.
I'm a genius.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, nobody didn't do that.
I had.
Well, you did too?
Okay.
Well, anyway.
My brother was a hacker genius and he got the R4 thing and he gave me like every single
video game.
I played all Professor Layton's, all the Phoenix Wright games, all the Mario Kart DS, fucking
everything.
The DS, the DS for real, has like the greatest game library of all time.
I would say, yes.
You know, there's like a couple of okay games.
I hear this is Final Fantasy games okay, but it's shit compared to...
There's Club Penguin on that one, that console.
There's Club Penguin.
There's Club Penguin games.
There you go.
Club Penguin Jump Ultimate Stars, all the Layton games.
I think something really good about the DS was when like your parents would drag you
to the high school football game and you don't want to watch it.
So you go into the...
You could chat with people on the fucking pic-toe chat.
Oh my fucking god.
Yes.
And you just harass people because they can't prove who you are and you just talk shit
and make everybody mad.
Who else had the DS long before?
They actually had a game for it or I had like, I think I had Mario 64 and I would spend
way more time pic-toe chatting with people on that thing.
And you play that game when you draw like the top half of a picture and then the next person
could draw the bottom half and it would look like they're all one picture.
You know, I've never really experienced DS with strangers or people because bringing
like a DS to school wasn't something people did enough to be a cool thing.
So, you know, I'd never experienced that sort of element of it.
We have to go back.
We have to bring all our DSs and just go to a room and then just...
Yes.
Radcon 3, bro.
Radcon 3, the pic-toe chat experience.
Let's do it.
Radcon 3DS.
Yes.
By the way, my most tragic experience while playing any video game ever in my entire
life was thus.
I went into GameStop.
I bought a copy.
I already had.
I already fucking had a copy of Kirby Superstar Ultra.
I just bought another one because who gives a fuck?
Oh my God.
So, I bought another one, pre-owned, and then I 100%ed all three files two times over the
course of one day and then brought it back at the end of the night to return and get my
money back.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Is that even possible in that kind of timeline?
Oh, it's possible, mate.
It's possible.
It's more than possible.
Holy shit.
Fucking juggalo.
Guys, press one in the comments if we should do a Kirby race in the PCP.
Press one.
It might be cheap in the comments if you want to see us cheap over the game race.
Hippo is not invited.
I would rather do that because we can do that quickly.
I'm goat.
I'm a new character.
Hey.
Oh, this is a good question.
I'm nervous.
This is good because it's at Jenny's Makudomaru, our old friend, asked, guys, just got a PS4
and I have Dark Souls 3.
What should I name a character?
So, I'm going to respond to this one.
What should we name their character?
Undertale of 589.
I mean, 587.
How about...
Naming characters is not difficult for other people.
It's difficult for other people.
I don't know.
Give.
Give me something.
You're a pun man.
I don't know what to base the pun on.
I don't know who this person is.
I don't know how they play.
I don't know what they like.
Dark Souls.
How about Black Guy?
Okay.
Black Guy.
I'm responding with Black Guy.
Classic character name.
Capital A, U, M, A, K, U, A.
Amua Kua.
That's you, bitch.
That's a Ua.
Okay.
I'm going to put Black Guy or Amua Kua.
There we go.
There.
Responded.
You type that to them?
Of course.
I just responded to them.
Now you all listen to the podcast.
You follow.
That's true.
We lost that whole view because of you, Nate.
God damn it.
Nah, I got to watch.
They know.
How about...
Okay.
Here we go.
Is there anything...
I want to get someone.
I want to do someone.
Okay.
Hey, dude.
Go for it.
Okay.
From an untitled abridged...
What would you do?
Lock up the Jews.
Just kidding.
I would never do that to my brother.
Wait.
I'm actually really tolerant and I love all Jewish people.
The one thing that I would do...
Yeah, don't lock up men.
...was lock up all the neo-nazis.
Yeah.
Actually, I would never do that because I'm actually an extreme racist and...
I'm really not happy about it.
So the thing that I actually would do is I would just take some antidepressants.
Please.
Please let me...
Was the question, what would you do?
Yeah, I think it was what would you do.
That's a good question.
Good question.
Wait, who asked that?
I think you said that.
I would continue to be on the podcast right now, I guess.
That's good.
You bring the whole...
Just filling them out on the disc.
He's got a real sound board situation going on.
He's probably surrounded by various different materials and substances that he crank a lot of moments notice.
Yeah, he's the Folly Effect's king.
In my blue pills.
There you go.
I don't even know how he achieves these sounds, but I...
Amuakua...
He broke!
He literally broke!
Did you break Amuakua?
Yeah!
Oh, no.
His Dark Souls 3 player is ruined.
God, this question is shit.
Bobby, I'm going to call it at BobKevin101.
Your question fucking sucks.
Best waifus and or favorite video games?
Dude, what the fuck kind of question is that?
I'm bored as shit.
Never come to my house.
Riska and Homestuck.
Is the joke both that we've done those episodes and that you've made videos on those subjects this month, Nate?
Yeah, something along those lines.
Bobby, you're a basic bitch.
Sometimes people just don't know anything in the ACO tweet.
I'm just kidding around, dude.
I'm just kidding.
What was the question?
It was best waifus and or favorite video games.
Why and or?
Why is that an and or sort of situation?
I don't know.
You can only like one.
You can only...
You like video games or anime waifu people?
I think you guys might have done this one last week, but...
Did you guys do what is your least favorite creation that you've made?
The universe.
I don't fucking remember.
I'm going to answer it now anyway, though.
My least favorite creation I've made, honestly...
And that's from Geifi McGee.
Oh, cool.
I would have to go with and I...
It's kind of silly, but I honestly cannot even really look at my Undertale video anymore.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I agree.
I completely agree.
It's because like...
I don't know, like there's a lot of reasons why, but it's...
At the time, I was like...
It feels too much like a game theory.
Well, I don't actually think it's that much like...
I think it's much better than the game theory.
But like...
Okay, so it's obvious that I put way too much effort into it.
So when I look at it now, all I see is like wasted time that I achieved...
And like, what did I get out of it?
You know, like 30,000 views on a video that...
Yeah.
In my opinion, is without a doubt like the most...
It has the most to say about Undertale of any video I've seen, but like...
At what cost, you know?
Yeah, it's unfortunate because like Undertale was like so...
Overdone by everyone, but nobody did it like properly.
And so when you come along and say all these things...
By the time you got it out, like the basic idea of what you were saying had already been said in various other places.
Just not in a cool enough way.
But it felt like really old and very flashy for no reason.
It's unfortunate.
It's honestly kind of why I don't really have as many warm feelings about Undertale anymore,
even though it is a objectively fantastic game.
I'm just sour about the whole thing and it comes me out.
It's my own fault.
Except for Sam's.
A few weeks ago, me and Ben were watching I Love Impossible a lot as we do all the time.
And I remarked how it's literally best game ever Undertale.
All of our videos are literally best game ever Undertale.
How do you figure, sports fan?
You are I Love Impossible a lot.
There's just shit constantly.
Okay, I see what you're saying.
I worked way too hard to try to make like everything that happened really cool and flashy and poppy.
Don't do it kids, don't put it on the road.
I Love Impossible a lot.
You.
Same person.
Thank you KP.
A while ago, probably almost, it's probably over a year ago,
there was a lot of subreddit drama going on at the great A under A subreddit.
Oh really?
And I didn't like his videos in the first place so I thought,
okay, I'm gonna take advantage of this drama before anybody else.
And I'll make an anime review of great A under A baby.
Oh, I'm gonna put him in his place and make him look like an idiot.
And the video's dumb and gay and whatever, nobody cares.
I don't know if I saw that one.
That's okay, don't watch it.
I was trying to catch up to speed on the monkey anime reviews because this is what I first found out about you.
And I get to that and it's sort of like weird and not like anything else.
And I also talked very, very slow.
In my old videos, I do talk pretty slow and people always complain about it.
But in that one, it was like I was trying to talk to a group of retarded people,
which I guess would be the great A under A fan base.
So it kind of fits.
I don't actually remember what was in that video that was so bad about it.
It was just like, he doesn't like these band people.
He was on a stream talking about how a 14 year old girl in his moderation of his subreddit was like a whore
and was like saying mean stuff about her and stuff.
Yeah, but what was your video about it?
What did you do?
I was just pointing it out and that's it.
But that's just a theory.
A great A under A theory.
This is good, I like this.
Gabe, what do you hate about yourself?
Wow, what a question.
I guess sometimes I say things without actually understanding whether or not I actually agree with myself.
I just feel like I need to say something.
So sometimes in podcasts, this is like a specific moment.
But I think earlier in the podcast when I was talking about something, I forget.
I think I know what you mean.
Yeah, it was fame.
I just had a visceral reaction about fame probably being bad
and I don't really want to be recognized on the street.
And sometimes I regret certain things I say and I don't like that I can't take it back.
I can't take it back, but it's now recorded and it's part of a thing.
And there's various moments in podcasts and stuff I just don't like what I say and I'm like,
oh wait, you're trying too hard or you're silly, then you're not supposed to.
It's a bad time.
I fucking...
I know what you mean.
You can always state a retraction.
I think that's something not enough people do.
People never like to admit when they were wrong or when they changed their opinion
and they'll just hold on to stupid ideas for no reason.
No, no, no.
I mean, I would retract it, but I need to think about it before.
I know whether I actually disagree with it now.
I just know that you're all against me and I'm like, oh, maybe I'm stupid.
Maybe I'm being an idiot.
It's okay to have an unpopular opinion.
Well, no, I mean, I think I know what Gibbs is getting at.
Because once you say something, even if you set it off the cuff and you didn't really mean it,
once you put it out there in any form, people just latch onto that
and even if you make a correction, people are resistant to change the impression that they've already formed.
So yeah, that should happen since it's annoying.
I think about that too.
Yeah, I mean, I've always been scared of podcasts.
I do them because they're a challenge to...
I mean, they're not really a challenge anymore.
I can just hop on and say, oh, fucking, I'm here.
But they used to be like, oh, no, oh, no the whole time in my head
and everything was like, I was tensing up and I was sweating and I was shaking.
Like, no, I can't, I'm not saying anything.
I gotta be saying something.
Any podcast I've been in, I feel like I haven't been like...
I mean, no, that's not true.
See, I'm doing a thing where I say something that's not even real.
Not even actually what I think.
I'll just shut up.
That's the thing where it happens, the thing that you're talking about.
Isn't there a word for that?
Gay?
Yeah, I think that's the one.
Yeah, yeah.
God damn it.
Ash Rock Relab asks...
Is there any type of you guys that you're super into and it's so weird
you don't even bother recommending it to other people?
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck was that question?
I didn't even understand that.
Is there anything...
It's so weird that you like it, but you don't want to recommend it.
Well, it depends who I'm recommending it to.
Weird things are inherently good to me.
If you show me something that's weird, I will like it.
No questions asked.
I want to feel slime.
I want to feel sludge.
And I want to feel most of all ooze.
Well, what if I just watched the new Taylor Swift music video and I'm like,
you know who'd be into this shit?
I'm Munchy.
My buddy Munchy would love it.
I love Taylor Swift.
She used to go on beat and I love my beat bros.
I love Debbie the Frog.
Dude.
The Taylor Swift Taylor.
That's a good one.
I love you, Hillary.
You're my favorite.
But yeah.
I know with her.
I mean, I like a lot of vaguely weird things.
Sometimes I post them in here where I feel like in the PCP chat that is,
when I feel like people in the chat would understand it.
It's usually just YouTube poop things that sometimes there's one that's like,
can be appreciated despite not really being into YouTube poop.
Because I don't think any of us, aside from me, are really into that sort of
YouTube stuff.
So, I don't know.
That's generally what I don't recommend, even though I love it.
It's just, it's one of those things that's like, you know, if you like it,
then we can have a conversation.
You tell your suggestions.
Yeah.
You tell your recommendations to like the audience you're talking to.
So like, I don't know, I wouldn't come on here and recommend the same things
to watch that I recommend to you guys.
It just depends.
Yeah.
I've found a lot of people, especially in these online communities,
have a predisposition about all reality TV and assume that it's all shit.
So, even though Survivor and Big Brother are two of my favorite shows,
I never want to recommend them because people would just write that off
as being something that they think it is.
So, I just gave up a long time ago.
You know what I'm just realizing is that people, you know,
normal people generally just recommend things because they like them
and not really thinking about who they're recommending it to.
They just want people to like things.
Whereas us, like we do like reviews or we talk about media a lot.
So, the idea of like recommending something on like a platform is different
from just saying something to a friend.
Yeah.
Like you're talking to an audience that, you know, like it's not worth your time
to talk about something that they may not already be into
if you know what they're like.
I'm with you, dude.
George, where are we?
We're in Undertale, Homer.
Undertale, what's that?
Skeletons and monsters?
Love and shit, you know?
Like sands and papyrus.
Oh, shit.
We got to get the fuck out of here, bro.
Okay, here's a question.
This is just a fun one.
Hey, we've got our red pills and we've got our blue pills, but what's your pill?
So, let's decide a PCP official pill that we can, you know, distribute.
Oh, a pill for the mascot.
What pill is he?
For that guy?
I mean, he's kind of gray.
Gray pill?
That's already taken, isn't it?
Plus that sounds shitty as fuck.
What about mage-pilled?
We could all get mage-pilled.
I'd like to get mage-pilled, but that's a specific, you know.
What is involved in being mage-pilled?
You know, just like a nice, you know, nice soft-spoken guy who likes to talk about anime in video games, you know.
Unless you play MMOs with your friends on the internet.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
And you're a really tall girl.
It's a pretty wholesome pill.
Germ pill.
I'm just going to round some off here.
Germ pill, antidepressant pill.
Empire pill, saturation pill.
Crushed blacks and whites pill.
High saturation pill.
Wait, wait, wait.
Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff pill.
Sabrage pill and that.
Sabrage.
What about pill-pilled?
Pill-pilled.
I think, I mean, our conversation right now is pretty pill-pilled.
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know the pill thing.
The red and the blue makes enough sense, but what the fuck is all those other ones?
We agree.
The green one is if you're fucking blissed so hard, you're going to fucking turn over and die.
There's a whole big image, like, of a hundred different types of pills, a billion different types of pills, and I'm like,
I don't have time to read all this pill knowledge.
I don't want to get it wrong, though.
Guys, I've got a good question.
Wait, you don't.
It's not good.
No, I'm super into the expanded pill lore, and you guys are always just on the mainstream bullshit.
No, me too.
Me too, dude.
You guys are just so pill-pilled.
I just kind of hate it.
I know, I know.
All right, boys.
He's got to get that expanded.
Yeah, go, go, go, go.
Since we've got, you know, an even number, ten people in the PCP right now, sort of.
We don't need to go into it.
Right.
We may not have left the chat today, only to come back probably tomorrow.
If you had to ship all the PCP members with each other with no repeats and no one left out, who would be with who?
Who is that from?
That's from KZSNIP.
She's getting a lot of questions today.
I can already tell, there's going to be a lot of demand for Gibb in this situation.
No.
Fighting is going to be a lot.
We don't get to pick who you want.
I think the canon ship is me and Jesse, because people have drawn us together before.
Yeah.
See, people are going to write that.
On a ship.
On a ship in the pony cast.
Yeah.
God damn it.
Me and Gibb were on a ship before anybody.
We've been on the poddy cast for over a fucking year.
Everyone hates the poddy cast.
It's just arbitrary.
No.
Shut up.
Fuck you.
Now, would I be with Ben or with Digi?
I would say, I would automatically put Jesse and Digi.
Jesse and Digi, I would put together.
That just seems like, that just seems like.
Guys, they were the original.
They were your little sister.
They were the original, I mean, I know Tom and Digi were actually the original.
But Digi is so invested in like his Digi friendship that-
Wait.
I feel like Digi and Monkey would be a good ship.
I'm going to say Digi is invested in his Jesse friendship.
That's what he is all about.
Wait, guys, we can't just focus on love.
We need all the quadrants.
Oh no.
So so so.
So Monk would definitely be in Kismis.
Kismis with Ben.
No doubt.
Yes.
What a colleague yeah, I'd probably go with that. It's cuz it's like a love-hate thing. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's fits. It's cute
How about Ben?
Yeah
Gibbon would be like more rails with fucking Jesse. I would think probably
Yeah, they're not that bad as a medicine. They're on their super pirate ship or whatever. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
The first ones to ever be on the ship. Yeah, and then Tom and Digi would go together cuz they're like the old boys
Um, yeah, they haven't fucked in a long time though. Yeah, I don't know whether
He's like he's so ethereal he needs to become like corporeal again, you know
We have like Nate
I should probably be with mage, but then again mage is like asexual so oh, you know what you know
The perfect pairing mage and Tom because mage is asexual and Tom is bisexual. So he's gay that works
I could be gay so that'd be like perfect that works out. Wait, so who is Nate with the munchie? Who's left?
If you're not actually bisexual, I'm sorry, I didn't mean that nice. Yes. Yeah, he's okay. Good cut that out
Just because he's vegetarian
I'm just like, you know, I'm a man and I have needs and you will satisfy those needs
You much we both the only women can be fat we know we know this yeah
I think Nate should wear a pearl costume and then fuck Steven universe. That's a good idea
Yeah
Oh Peter, okay, so that's everybody
There you go. That's official. Yeah, that's pretty good. Oh
Dear, here's another one the KZ again KZ snap
KZ is the fucking VIP with decent questions about it's because these are like specific and they're fun to answer
So here we go at KZ snap says, uh, would you ever get a tattoo? And if so, what would it be?
I bet you guys have all thought about that. Yeah chakras and all of my chakras
64 points
And he do you of course use the you know the ancient Hindu was the manji, you know the the swastika would be on all chakra points
I've always been a very anti tattoo
But I think I would get one as a joke if I lost some crazy bed and I had to get like digibro's face on my ass or something
But otherwise I'm not just planning on it. Yeah. Yeah, that's just a fun story
I would I would get an emoji movie ad on the tip of my penis
So that yes, yes, that's great so that every vagina will go by the oh, you know for the movie dudes for the movie
The the the water splash one probably
That's a good one
You know, I'm pretty spiritual so I would get a star of David on one nipple and a swastika on the other
Yeah, I have actually thought about this and for many years now everyone's gonna think I'm a fucking sellout piece of shit
But I've wanted to get the the joe star star on like my my upper left back
But I've wanted that for like 15 years. Okay, so it's like I first read Jojo
I'm not one of these fucking anime new joys. I hate people who like the things I like only I'm allowed to like it
You guys are Joe Joe reference. Oh
God, I'll probably never do it though
It's literally it's become so normie that I probably just won't ever do it because they don't like you know
What I've never really thought about having like an actual tattoo like I'm thinking well
It's kind of painful and it's permanent like I'm probably gonna regret it
But as a joke as a as a hilarious joke and as long as it's on my back
So I don't have to look at it all the time
I would put like a like a like a like a as if I was married to brisker like a like a weird love thing
Yeah, or maybe just a symbol something like really retired in her now and hilarious
But by the way brisker shit will never die. She's real forever. She's real forever
But by the way that that just just to increase my indie credentials
It I wanted that tattoo after I read part six of Jojo
And it was after Joleen did her epic fight with guard Westwood during the survivor battle
That was the most maybe want to do it and find the entire fucking. Yes. Thank you
It is the best fight in the entire series. God somebody gets it
And and it's
Every single panel
Yeah, sorry what I've got a topic for discussion
Okay, go on go on this one comes to us from mum key underscore Jones who wants to know
Was Nate the best guy ever justified in stealing a picture of some bitch dressed up and she's like fat and ugly
Oh this one, huh? I think we should talk about it, and we haven't talked about it. You know, that's totally fine with that
Okay, well, let me give you the backstory real quick. So in my
video about how
Communist glasses are not fucking orange for me a mouthful. I I used a cosplayers photo and full disclosure
What I did was I just googled like female coming to cosplayer like I had actually used this image before in my
Gurren login review. So, you know the criticism would be equally valid that I used it there as well and to my
Discredit I did not credit anybody who was in it, which I I agree was and worse like not not like
Was rude I guess like I don't think I actually need to have any responsibility to do that if I had to give credit
To every single Google image I put in my videos the whole description would be nothing, but that shit, okay?
Well, here's the thing
I think that it is possible like we say that like but the argument you're kind of making and I think about this myself
Because I do this a lot too is like that's really just us being lazy whether or not we're actually allowed to do it
That's just a saying like it would be too much work. So obviously I'm allowed to do it
I don't know if that's actually true, you know
Well, I don't think Google you don't own it anymore. I don't think that's accurate
I think I think I think I think I think what it is is it's it's not illegal, but it's just it's it's a nice
It's a nice gesture to link to something. Well, okay using it
Let's separate is though that if you're using a lot of images
You're not gonna go through nobody's gonna go through the the the rigmarole of
Getting links to all the specific different sources, but that that's completely insane
But that's like saying that like if you do like many crimes like they all become less important cuz like you've
Let me separate this into two things, okay
We can I think we can deal with one immediately then we can just talk about the second
I don't want to confuse the two so there's the legal issue and then like the moral issue
So legally what I did was 100% fair use. Yeah, absolutely
Nothing wrong with just using someone's image because all I was doing was commenting on it
I wasn't like saying it was mine. This is just me describing a picture 100% totally fine
Yeah, there is the like the more moral issue like is it good to do that?
Especially considering I didn't give by the way by the way give I have amended
So I have added links to those things in the description because I agree, okay
You know, I did think like okay
It was this person specifically commented like hey not cool
You should you know at least let people know who I am and I agree if someone goes out of their way to say like
Hey, let me do this it would it would be merely spiked to be like no
I'm not gonna fucking do that and I am not a spiteful person. I don't want to do that
So now has she acknowledged this because she she like suck her goons onto your video to like attack it and down
You know post comments like she was being a huge cunt about it. What she wants. I actually disagree
I actually people were saying that she was being quite rude
I don't really think that that's the case like she in her comments. She complained like
You know, hey, you didn't give me credit not cool
Way to just use my picture, you know without my permission and and also like it said like especially in like in this kind of light
Like because I was insulting her for not having like the perfect glasses color
So let me say first of all, I don't it's fine. Your customs customs fine. Don't worry about it. I thought it was ugly
Well
I think she could have done a lot better
We all could do we could all do a lot better
Well, okay, I have I have okay some some
Viewpoint on this cuz sometimes I'm too lazy
And I don't want to play a whole game to get a specific clip right in in a video game review or anything like that
you know and
When I do that I download the video and then since the video has the name of like the YouTube link
You know that the YouTube title later
I can just copy paste and find the link and then put that in the description and I generally do that sometimes
I forget sometimes I'm just like it's like nobody's gonna notice like I'm but if it's like
Like for the Kingdom Hearts grpj. I didn't play that game. I didn't record that game for all the grpgs
I don't record the footage because that's too much. That's too big
So I go around and I you know
I find people who have played through the whole game and I get certain things from the videos and I linked to them and
I make sure to say I stole this content from these people just so that nobody's accusing me of being like
It's subtle about it like I'm saying I took you say that in the video or in the description in the description
I said content a game footage stolen from and a bunch of links
So okay, I feel that I don't feel the need to do that all the time
But when it's like a lot, you know when it's something that could potentially be noticed
I mean what I feel I feel like it's it's just customary to just if you have an easy way to put the link in there
You may as well. There's nothing really wrong
What if somebody went to gibbo Gibbon gaming and they write use some of your footage for review?
Would you care personally? I wouldn't give a shit. I couldn't care less of a shit about that at all
It means if somebody went to
Took something out of one of my streams
If I was notified of it if somebody somehow noticed that it was my play through and they put it on their video
And I went to look at it. I I guess it would depend on how much well, let's use like I like on a baseline
Let's just say it's just a clip from one of my streams
They're not using the audio. They just need footage of the game that they're yeah, yeah
Then I wouldn't give a shit, but I feel like gives it yeah
But I I mean what I feel like doesn't necessarily but guys
I'd rather have no altercations happen if somebody's gonna get mad
I'd rather than never get mad or not have a reason to get mad if there's a link to the thing in the description
So what what you guys are talking about is just people's feelings, right? Like that's what's in consideration
Yeah, that thing that I never care about right
Well, you know, I I mean I have thought about this
You know, I did some reflecting on this issue and I thought about like what if someone
Use one of my videos like you know put a fucking weaponized thickness clip or something into their videos
Like what if they did that and they didn't credit me and you know like it's just the joke like it's not like they're saying
It's theirs, but in the exact same sort of situation they put a clip of mine
You know, it's totally fair use legally. There's no problem with it, but like I think I would really like a link there
I think I would sort of be be miffed if there wasn't a link to to me. I yeah, I think well
I think with that
I would agree that I would be miffed as well
But it's also kind of already become a meme and it's like you ever hear
Okay, okay, you try to copyright memes that just means be something being a meme does not
Invalidate like ownership of of like the image it simply does not it doesn't do that immediately
And I'm not saying I like own the intellectual rights to this phrase or anything. I'm talking about you know, like yeah
Yeah, I know I know but I wouldn't I wouldn't blame somebody for having heard a meme that I originated and not
Going to figure out where it comes from like if somebody did that I wouldn't be mad
I wouldn't care because I understand that if it's out there and it's all over the place
Right can't really do anything. Okay. I'm with you on that if someone like stumbles upon it and uses it on that basis
Absolutely because like I do I mean I do that all the time
I tons of the images I get in fact most the ones I use my videos are stuff that I've collected from 4chan over the
Years that I don't give any source for and I couldn't even if I wanted to I've just found them and I've saved them
And I just throw them up there. So I mean maybe that is morally not
Flawless, you know, I would like to give credit to every single person who has made these things over the years
But you know, you just got it. You just got to think a bit of like like what's what's realistic?
Realistically, you know, nobody's really gonna give too much of a shit if
somebody's like if
Somebody I took a video game clip from finds it and they notice it they might say hey, could you link to my thing?
Like that's the least that's the most that could happen
It's not really gonna be a big deal, but I put the link there anyway
Just just because like it's unnecessary, but I feel like you know, why not it doesn't take it
It takes like a minute to do that
So like realistically what what sort of effort do you would you expect people to go to to link to something?
If it's if it's just something in a Google search, you would have you know, you click on it
You can get the image right there. You don't need to go to the source of the image on DeviantArt, right?
It's it's a it's a bit more effort. It's I don't expect people to do that. I don't do that
Okay, but you know, I'm totally with you on that
But I would say if that person were to come to you and say like hey, dude
I notice you use my video or my my image or whatever, you know, that's cool. Not the biggest deal
Maybe I wouldn't I don't know whatever it doesn't matter how I feel
But would you give me credit? I'd really like credit if you don't like do that
Well, that's like, okay
I'm just saying like it's easy to like not worry about it like whatever
I'll just use the image who gives a fuck but to then ignore someone who comes to you and like request it
I'm not saying that makes you like a monster. I'm just saying like that's not cool. It's not a cool thing to do
Oh, yeah, obviously like if somebody went out of their way to tell me I would yeah, of course
Because then they've given their link to to me
You know their name like I can easily find it
Like if I have to go if they expect me to go searching for it
Because if I if I don't remember where I got it from then I might not do it
I don't think but I mean if there were any legal issues. I don't remember or it's too much work
Those are not actual legal defenses. So I'm just saying if this were a little thing
We've decided that the legal stuff is like it's mostly fair use basically all the time
So what's the moral standpoint Nate? We all know that it's legal
But why do you kind of have a shaky moral standing on it? Well, you say it's shaky, but I think I've been pretty clear
It's that no, I mean, why do you think it's not morals when I'm asking? Oh, well really
It's because I've consulted how I think I would feel about it
And I think if someone used my work without crediting it. I would not like it and I would want the credit
So somebody took a snapshot of one of your videos because this was you didn't steal her cosplay
You used a photo of the cosplay so if somebody steals your well
That's different than if somebody takes a screen cap of your clip and uses it
I don't think that's that bad
Well, I mean you got to put the full context in because the the whole picture was like you could tell this had been photoshopped
So like someone had worked on this image after a picture had been taken and so there's the cosplayer involved as well as the photographer
And I'm assuming that's the person who also like did the photo editing because you could see like the background had
been darkened to make this person like pop out more
You know like that's work and in a perfect world. Yeah, I think everyone who does any work on something like that should should get credit
And get so if the person who designed the character came to her and said hey, can you delete that?
That's my character. Please don't cosplay is that you think she would delete it? She's a well
Well, but again, I'm not saying anyone should ever have to delete it because I think this is totally
It's just an issue of you know, is it a cool thing to do or not?
And I think if the character designer for Kamina came out and was like hey, dude
You're using my shit without crediting me. You got to credit me
I I would say that yeah, like she should credit just be like by the way this character was designed by whoever on wherever
They're not
It just to ignore like the imagine if fucking I don't know
Imagine if Elliot came up to you and was just like monkey, you know by the way, dude
I'd appreciate if you would just put links to my videos for all the clips you use and just like imagine imagine looking at
I'm saying no like no, I'm not gonna do that like you can do it
I mean in person you would say it online and I can just ignore the email and move on
Well, yes, you can if you came in person you'd probably have a gun and then of course I would do what I think I think I think what this is
Is that it's it's the fact that somebody got upset about it and right?
It's a deviant art thing because like I get my images from Google. I don't usually pick fan art
I usually go for like official art because it's less hassle as it's more recognized see I use a ton of fan art personally and get it
all from 4chan
Yeah, so if you use an artwork, let's say I drew an image of something
Or I took a picture on Instagram or something and I find it in a video by someone else
I would be like, oh, okay. This person knows me. That's my first thought. Mm-hmm, or they they found my image somehow
I wouldn't immediately be annoyed that they hadn't linked to what I had made because
Well, actually, I don't know cuz yeah, you might right by trade. Yeah
Okay, but you know I generally generally generally I I wouldn't care so much
Unless it was like a they were just stealing a huge amount of something I've made I I have a position on this and it's it's
It's exactly where I was before just I don't know with all that other shit
It's that I'm going to continue doing exactly what I've been doing up to this point of using the images
I've collected and not really worrying too much about giving proper credit to people
But if anyone requests it, I will certainly add it if they are like, hey dude use my thing
Appreciate credit. I'll be happy to put it and I won't go like out of my way to not put credit if I can easily do it
But it's just it's kind of excessive. I mean, I was in this position when I made my quarry in the house review
I I needed a thumbnail
So I just googled quarry in the house HD picture and that took the first thing I found
But it turns out that was the thumbnail for somebody else who made a similar quarry in the house review
And he sent me a message on YouTube said hey, monkey. I love the video, but I made that thumbnail
Can you switch it? And I was like, yeah, yeah, okay sure thing buddy. So I switch the thumbnail
So yeah, I guess I see where you're coming from. Mm-hmm, but I didn't have to and that's the point
Yeah, you didn't have to legally have to great great review by mother's base. I love that card now. Yeah
Actually mine. I think mine came out before his did so fucking great mother's basement video
Speaking of mother's basement mother's basement asks, why do you kill me?
Yeah
Here's a real question
Jeron I guess I've been thinking about this at Gergerad asks
a PCP guys, why
Why don't you tell us the topic of the episode when you asked for questions? I don't know
I don't know dude. Is that something we should do?
I think no, no, no, no, it's it's something we shouldn't do because if
Say if it wasn't like a stupid episode like this
Yeah, we would have been talking about that topic the whole time and then questions would be something else if they ask questions about it
And it's just like well, we already talked about that. We're already talked about that
We're already brought up different. I agree. That's okay. That's a good answer. There you go, Jergerad
Yeah, okay. Let's say here's a here's a shitty last question
At dr. Sand shrew I like a good name asks pancakes or waffles
Okay, when I was a little boy, I used to be super into waffles
I was like a super like like like well like
Champions like like yeah, I was like a waffle nationalist
I wouldn't like have any pancakes bullshit. I used to always eat them
I would I used to always eat chicken and waffles. That was that was that was what I ate
That was the only wall dude. Are you like African-american or something Lamau come on now
Oh
Okay, um, but yeah, but then later fucking delicious
Munchie laughing a Nate's joke was funnier than Nate's joke. Of course. It was my jokes are shit
Then I discovered something amazing
Pancakes with
Wow grand reveal even though it's the only other option. Yeah, yeah, yeah pancakes
And I was like what I ate next will make your dick blow off
If I eat the pancakes and sit the waffles then I will have a different taste than the waffles
But see munchie I especially like I especially like how you specifically said
Pancakes with just butter because a lot of people will drown their pancakes and syrup all the time
But I I'm in agreement that I think that just pancakes and butter is kind of better
It's kind of like the most delicious thing in the world
Here's the best thing you'll ever eat in your life
Yeah, you get two frozen egg waffles that were probably in there like eight months ago
Right you fry those fuckers up in the toaster
Then you put peanut butter on them you make a little sandwich then you douse it in syrup and then you eat that
That's way better than any pancake
Sounds like a glory hole, but like better
Then let's know in the chat what topic are we doing? He's listening better. We're not doing any topic. What do you mean?
This is laziness. We covered laziness thoroughly. They're only guys guys. Okay, fucking
This episode clickbait
Yes, I think it might be clickbait. No
Pancakes the only time I've eaten pancakes was only time
Well, yeah, they don't have it's not it's not a thing
Pancakes pancakes for breakfast is not at all a thing
We don't eat pancakes. It's just not a thing. Do you waffles literally fucking treason? What about what what are waffles?
They're building waffles for a reason cuz they're from Europe and all Europe is the exact same
Uh
Waffle all right. I think is it just like a grid pancake? Yeah, it's like we're crispy. It's crispy. Yes thicker and crispier
Yeah, I've never really had a waffle either. What I have had like put I have had like potato waffles
Which are waffle shaped potatoes and they I love those okay?
I
Know it's that's what I associated waffles was because that with because that's the only thing I'd ever had that was called a
Waffle is of a little potato thing and I was always confused when when people in America would talk about having waffles
I'm like, wait a minute. That's not a waffle. That's not that's not it. That's not what it is
Anyway, the only time I had pancakes was at rad con 2
During one one of the times we went to breakfast and we had them. I was like, huh? Yeah, I get I get I get it
Was the time. Oh man, that's nuts. I had no idea. That was your first time having pancakes
I think it might have not been the exact first time
But it's the first time I had like an American pancake with syrup on it. I've never had never had syrup on
I don't know guys. We've we've we've we've we've we're running kind of long here. You know, we've been going for a while
Shall we get to the topic?
Yeah, no, I was gonna do that, but I'm glad you did because laziness is like
You know, it's
You know, I get it. Whatever like laziness is like I do it
But you know, like I know I shouldn't but you know, like whatever, you know, like sometimes sometimes they're just sort of I
Can't think of the word. I mean you should do a series. Yeah, okay, okay, man. Do it
No, it was a joke. Oh, hey
It's a joke. I was too lazy to find the word
If we in the episode maybe Nate can record the fucking audio for my Pokemon tournament that hippos in that's true
Dude, I was up till fucking 6 a.m. making my fucking me a man for a piece of shit. All right. Easy. I said I get it to you this weekend
Oh, yeah, I'm lazy. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Fucking day for my god. I'm the lazy one
I've been working eight hours a day. God damn it. I'm gonna fucking job
Everybody hates fucking Nate. Fuck you people
I like that mug. Anyway, did you get it yet to come in the mail?
It's not here yet, but I'm gonna drink out of it when I get it
But a fucking the lazy, right? Here's a here's the thing about lazy
No, no, here's the thing about lazy. Okay, it's the name of a song by deep purple. It's fucking great
Go listen to that. Oh, yeah, it's like
No, no, that's the that's the kinks I think
That's the kinks. Oh, is that the song that goes are you a real villain?
Yeah
In laziness this is going down when she takes a piss
Deep purple is the name of a bird. Fuck you Nate
Me a mouth of us really great. Oh, yeah
All right, okay. Well, we got our mandatory piss in let's uh, let's let's
I
Praise it praise Keck praise
Judas fuck my dick and fuck my ass. Bye everybody. Bye
Wait, I was about to say something
We're done. No, no, no, no that I want that the podcast to end exactly when I said that
Unless munchies doing something like having sex with his cat
Oh
Okay, that's done fade in the intro fuck Ben. I'm stopping recording
I
Don't want to do