I want to bless that guy. That's son of all things.
Son of all things. Son of all things.
Son of all things.
Aw, welcome to the Pro Crastinators podcast. Where are the reason people are dying?
Hello, I'm the Pro Crastinators. That's true.
That's the phrase we use every time.
Every single time we say that. And every single time it gets funny.
It gets truer I'm opening up my speak pipe so that when we get to that part of the show we will have
Which is now let's go straight to voicemail honestly, we probably should
Know I have you I do I do have a few things to talk about this time. I have I was I was unprepared
I didn't think to like write down notes this time. I did at least one
I have I have three notes today. I I have three notes
Usually these stretch out for a long time
Well, we want to lead off
with something yeah, okay, so I
Have been playing and only a little bit because it's very new and I haven't really had a chance to use it yet
And have you heard of Pikmin bloom?
Is that the new Pikmin it is a Pikmin Pokemon go clone
Made by the made by Niantic and it is I saw it involves
Walking around Google's street map view, but with Pikmin involved instead of Pokemon and it's it's really cool
Actually, because it's it's not about
Going and finding rare Pokemon although there are Pikmin that are rare and all that they got a cell
bullshit like
things that they have they're all like coin store and all that but
The draw is not about like going and exploring and spinning Pokestops and gyms and stuff. It's just walking because it counts your steps
It's a step counting game
so it just encourages you to go on walks to make flowers bloom and
Pikmin and you just have a bunch of Pikmin following you around on the map. I did see some people talking about it on Twitter I
Mean I have not played Pokemon go in a long time because of my shitty phone
Which I definitely should have switched to the new phone that crack gave me by now. I just haven't done it
Phone yeah crackers gave me if he had a bunch of phones
He said that and he just was like here. This one's this one will work better than yours. He's gave me one
Why I have not switched yet
So I don't know if it's true, but it probably is
Yes, it's it's cool because it's like
You don't have to actively actively play it. It's basically
The egg hatching, you know bunch of steps in a Pokemon go you hatch eggs by walking large amounts of distance
You don't have to have your phone open and an active so you can it uses like the Google fit like step counter
So you have to download Google fit it'll count your steps when the phone is just you know on standby and
Then you open it up after you've had like a walk in the park or you're just going around to a place
You know what just going anywhere and then you say oh look at all the new like nectar
I got and then your Pikmin you can feed them near the flowers bloom
And you just have a bunch of Pikmin and you they use like the Nintendo me
You know avatar this link to your Nintendo account or you don't have to link it, but I did
And it's your it's your me. It's your me. So it's much more customizable than Pokemon go, which sucks
To be to be frank does suck the customization sucks
You can have one haircut hair style. That's it stupid, but the me's are looks like me
It's it's really me for real and
and on the cutest thing is
You can use these petals that you get from your Pikmin and
You like activate them and then flowers start blooming where you walk and the point of that is to
Lay flowers so that you can look at where you've been but also everybody in the game sees the same flowers
so if
You've left a trail of flowers people can see that trail
If they're in the same area, it's just sort of like slowly the world is being
covered in flowers and nice things and you do that to like make larger
Like flowers bloom in place of like poker stops
There's like these big buds and the more flowers that are grown around it the more they grow and then like items can fall off of them
And your Pikmin can just pick them up and bring them to you and it's really like casual you just sort of
You see cute things happen every so often and you just need to go for a walk
It's not not an intensive annoying min maxi game like Pokemon is sometimes
And I like it. I like just you don't really need to do anything and it's cute
I love a game where I don't have to do anything all you need to do is go outside and that's a good thing
Even though it is a good thing. That is a good. It's it's getting old. It's getting a little bit cold for going outside
Gonna take my I can take my air conditioner out of my window. I keep telling myself. It's fine
And I don't have to move it. No, I'm sure it's not leaking cold air or anything, but it's it's it is it is
I have a
I still don't go I'll go out a little bit more often these days
I still don't go out enough. I don't go on like walks anymore. I guess I probably should I should I need to as well
Yeah, it's just one of those like oh, but I like being fat and lazy. That's way funner. That's true. That's true
Speaking of being fat and lazy
My lifts are come my lifts are coming along. I'm strong now
I'm my lower back is sore. I my dead my last deadlift
I think I pushed it a little far my my form was bad and I was like no
So I went I went down five pounds and I deadlifted again the other day and my form was good
I was like yes success, but my lower back is really sore. I think it's sore in the good way
I think it's sore like it was a good workout and not like my bones have incurred some damage my my
connective tissues
Don't worry about that the more you break the bones the stronger they become they grow back stronger. They grow back stronger
Yes, that's right. That's right
Thankfully, thankfully, yes
Just hit your head against a fucking brick wall and then you'll be you'll have like a shield your brain
Brain damage and your brain will grow back stronger the second time
Not smarter just stronger
Mass not definitely not smarter. Yes, it will be tougher
It will be scar tissue to resist a second attack. It won't be able to think though
Man, I saw a I saw like a gif or I saw a video of
neurons on like a Petri dish
It was like a microscope
footage of
Neuron, I mean the caption said it was neurons attempting to make connections and the neurons were like
They were literally like like swirling around like moving around and like extending their little cell
Arms and like reaching out like trying to grab each other
And I was like rose but cool
It felt and I mean it it felt like the way it feels when you're trying to think of
Something that you forgot and you're like trying to reach like oh, what was it? What was it?
Uh, it's and it's like it's little cell arms like reaching like shooting out like trying to
Grab each other and make connections between each other. I was like they stretched before I was like I was like yep
That's what it's like. That's how it is in there
It was pretty it's kind of gross a little horrifying like most things are
Hmm, I don't like to imagine my brain filled with tiny little squirming arms. No
I like to imagine my brain as a corridor with doors in it and you go in the door and it's like hey, I remember that
No false I
Shit shit. Oh fuck that was gonna make me
Say something, but what was it? Oh, no help and neurons you saw
Brains fired when you saw something
Memories. Oh, no, I can't remember
I literally have to squeeze out my nasty little cell arms and grab more of them
Come on neurons a glomerate
Think think
Think think about what you're trying to do to me
That's the if you watched a Sonichu lecture, too
You know that that is the official theme
Anthem of quickville is think by Aretha Franklin. Oh
She she wrote that song after looking after looking in a microscope and seeing some neurons squirming around and thinking yeah
That is what it's like. I want to write a song about it
Uh
Think think about how you're just a collection of neurons. I
Was watching I thought love was real but actually oh, it's just a chemical reaction bitch
rick and mortade
speaking of
There was a I was I was catching up on the anamorphic time podcast. I'm a few episodes behind
but I watched one and
Think it was Tyler of Nate and Tyler. I think it was Tyler that said something about like
The human the human body is like it's like so much of it is actually just bacteria
Like we're basically just a scaffolding for bacteria to live in
I know that's true in the in the intestines kind of yeah, probably not in the whole body
Equally, I don't think that's true in the brain
fortunately
Yeah, and the gut probably
There oh, um
This is interesting
Viewer a viewer of the show a watcher of the show named Bob Disgaea was on a
Was on an episode of anamorphic time and I think is going I think it's the next episode that's coming out soon
I think
and
apparently he
He he he messaged me on discord and he told me about it
And he said that he peppered in a bunch of like PCP memes and references or something and I just thought that was pretty funny
It's um, it's a weird epic. It is epic. I can't wait for that episode is not out yet
But I think it's coming. I got a catch-up on the show so I can be
Contemporary when it what even is a PCP meme. I'm trying like well, I know I know he drops at least one
patreon.com slash
It's a great PCP me I
He didn't specify. He's just kind of a vaguely alluded to that he made a bunch of like
He he made some references and I don't know what they were but I'm curious. Um, I
I um
The the wait shit. Oh god, I'm reaching again my neurons
What what's happening to me today
Um
He it was again, it was about mine is a petri dish
Wait, it was it was about
It's it was literally on this subject. It was about bob disgaea
It was about anamorphon time
Oh, um, I don't know if this is a coincidence or not, but
The anamorphon time guys have a guy
They have a guy who I think hooks them up with like interesting animal facts. I think that's what this guy's job is
He sends them like the the most interesting like weird animal trivia for them to discuss and
That guy's name that guy is a guy who I knew he used to be
In my old discord not on the current iteration of my discord
But in the previous iteration from a few years ago
That guy's name is divine soup can
And like I was listening to anamorphon time and they're like, yeah our gay our guy divine soup can and I'm just like
I think I was like what?
I think I recognize that name. Yeah
Wacky what I guess I guess it's a coincidence that it's just a guy who
Used to be around
And now he's over there people on the internet. Yeah exist after I stopped looking at them. I wish they would not
Actually
As a matter of fact
Speaking of well, I was gonna say speaking of whatever you were speaking about but it's got nothing to do with that
um
Picross right?
I love Picross. It is my my go-to
brain game
time waster
And I've been playing the steam game of Picross
And I've been slowly completing every single
Puzzle that they have and I'm now up to like the very last one which is 40 by 40
Which is a very big grid
And there's they're like the the method of like figuring it out works every time
So I don't really need to think that much. I just need to count
From left to right up to down
Filling in the squares and it's taking over my life
I feel like after I completed this entire steam game of Picross
Pages and pages and pages of puzzles
I'll be like well now what do I have to buy another steam game?
Do I have to buy more do I have to
There can never be a pick. You must you must complete you must consume
You must consume more content is what you must do at that point. Oh, I don't uh, it's it's too much
It's it's like yesterday
I I was I had red letter media huff in the bag in in the background and you know
At the point where you're like rewatching half in the bag because you've already rewatched all of the best of the worst
That you've been doing too much youtube
Yeah, and I'm like real listening to that. I'm just doing Picross all day and I was like, oh wait
There was a day here and I it's gone
I've been I should stop but it's just so
Like you click on the boxes and you make a picture
My most my most recent iteration of that youtube phenomenon is that I've been
You know, I I like a bunch of to sneakers videos
But I haven't played most of the games. He's talking about well
I've I'm I'm down bad for youtube content to the extent that I've I've was listening to his uh
Yakuza videos even though I don't play yakuza and I don't know what he's talking about
But I got to listen to something
uh
It sucks. I can't help I can't help
feeling
Like I've got to do something about this
But when I get when I sit down, I'm like, uh, you know what?
I feel like just having some random crap in the background
Yeah and doing Picross again, you know
You know what I actually rediscovered something that I this is not the first time I figured this out
But I remembered that actually I kind of work better
with music on um
It okay, it has to be like
It has to be the right kind of music. It has to be like energetic music
I have to it has to I have to be vibing with it
and then I can really like
Help me stay focused on the task at hand and I I've been putting on some some
Some tunes uh this week while I was working while I was cranking out uh phantoms revenge assets
And I think it probably helped me focus better on that
Um, but the thing about that is that there's very little music that like I like and that like I
I'm excited to listen to and that I
Vibe with in that way
Um, and I so I'm like
I'll like pick a song and I'm like, yeah, this song's good
And I'll listen to it on loop for a while and then I'll get bored of it and I'll be like well
Fuck now what there's
There's nothing else
Um
Yeah, there's a fine line for me with with music
Between being hype and being like, yeah, I love this and being too hype that I
I take my hands of my keyboard and mouse and I start like miming the drums
And just really my head around I kind of help. I love miming drums. That's funny. That never that never happens to me
I get too into it. I it's
Just musician things, you know
I guess so I guess so
Um, interesting to like vulfpeck is like it's so fucking good, but I can't
Work to it. No, that happens to me if if I'm if a if a video essay or some video youtube video is on
And I get too interested in it. I'll like start looking at it instead of my work
With music. I'm never like, oh, I gotta like
I gotta like pay attention to this. I gotta drop what I'm doing and pay attention. Yeah, I mean, that's why
Half in the bag and and best of the worst is good because it's just sort of like
Some noise. I've seen these videos before and occasionally rich heavens laugh is so loud and I'm like, oh, yeah
I'm no
There they are
But I should be doing work to that and I'm not I'm just playing pick-russ again like a fucking rube
Although at the moment
like
Well, I said last week I'm working on secret project stuff
and I
I'm still sort of doing that, but I'm sort of like
Going back to my computer at the end of working on that
secret project
And doing the the red letter media. I mean, you can't I mean, you can't work on it like 24 hours a day
No, no, yeah
So while I'm working on it, it's not really the sort of thing I could do with uh sound
Yeah, like in distractions, but whatever
With with that I can I can um, I can draw
I can draw with music
Yeah, I can't like do I can't like
I can't really program with music and I definitely can't program with like
a like talky youtube video
um
Drawing I can do a bit by sort of uh reflex or a bit by sort of like
I don't really have to think about it too. I can just kind of do it by feel. I don't have to concentrate on it that much
um
Um, well, I mean it depends what it is
I mean sketching out like a blocking out a page of a comic
Is more intensive than line art. Yes
You're just filling in the things and making each line look good with other lines. You don't really need to think about
the entire
Feeling of the page because you figured that out already with the sketch. I was oh, man
it felt
amazing I had a
I had a euphoric moment
A few euphoric moments this week actually is when I was working. I was working on
I was working on actually shit. It might have been last week. It's sort of blending together
Um, but I was I was working on fans of revenge. I was drawing some assets and I I don't want to say
It's be too specific for spoiler reasons, but I had to
draw spray because the butler did I had to draw a
face I had to draw a face
that was
screaming screaming with rage and I
was so I like
I I sketched it and then I like moved it to the my little like
Sprite template and then I like sprighted over it and I like I added the details and the whole time I'm drawing this face
I had music on
I was vibing with it and I'm drawing this this this rage face and I'm
And I was making the face. I'm like, I'm twisting up my own face and rage is going like
Like making the sound did I talk about this last week?
I think you did talk about because I remember I remember screaming into the microphone last week
I just it felt so good
It felt so fucking good
Being enraged
Uh, okay. Sorry. Sorry to bring that up again. Uh, listen, we've done
3000 episodes of the pcp
Uh, it's I guess it's it's okay to recycle material, but it's not okay to recycle material from last from last week
So I have to I have to be careful about that sort of thing
um, yeah, I mean
For me, it's a little difficult because like the secret project
Secret I don't want to reveal it yet, but I'm thinking in the back of my head
Well, if it has been revealed I could there's so much I could talk about so much content
I can make and put in this podcast we're doing
Yeah, it's like hard because like aside from that and playing video games and learning about pikmin
There's not really much I've been doing
How do I fill a podcast with oh, I've been working
I've been working on something working. You'll know beats beats working
Yeah, yeah, I mean I I have to wonder at some point like does anyone care what the secret is
Would I already know what it is?
You do but like like the people like would it is the is the hype building or is there no point to me keeping a secret about it?
I'm not sure. I think
I think that um
Probably some people listening are curious what the secret is probably most people will only be the most hype when it's
Revealed all of a sudden, right?
I feel like I feel like the real the real win of being secret to a certain extent it might build hype
Well, okay, it would build hype if you were like it's a secret
It's a secret but but I'll release it like at a specific date
And then you would hype up like this is the date that I'm going to drop the secret and maybe you
Drop a few like very tiny breadcrumbs
If you do that would maybe build hype in the moment
It's probably only building a bit of interest
But it will be the moment when you release
And all of a sudden you're like here's this fully finished thing that I never even talked about before
That will be everyone will be like what?
It is one of those like
Because I imagine like
I'll put it out on the pcp
Not everybody listens to the pcp that's in the like pcp fan circle
So I have to go to discourse and tell people individually. Hey. Hey, look at this. Look at this
And even then there'll be people who slip through the cracks and be like months and months later be like, oh my god
Give I had no idea you were doing this. I was like, yeah, well
Follow me on twitter. Are you idiot?
I'll you don't talk about it. Oh, well, well once you put it out. Yeah once I'm not gonna not tweet on twitter
It's gonna be gonna say it in every possible way I can
I wonder what my reach is if you could if you could quantify that
Yeah
How many people could I notify about a thing I'm doing?
I believe yeah your your reach
I believe the term for that would be your reach. Yes
My neurons how far can my neurons reach other neurons from other people?
um
So, yeah, I get phantoms revenge is like no longer a secret project. It was for a while. Um
Oh my god, I'm just I'm thinking
Man, I started working on it in December
And then I I released the demo in april
And now it's november
God I'm like
God
I that that feels terrible. What even happened this year? I don't know
Oh my god, I don't think anything happened. I think I was sick most of this year. That feels terrible and I
I I hope I I feel like okay. My gut says the answer is no
But I don't know if I can trust my gut on this one. I hope that it's wrong
My gut feeling is no and the question is like was it worth the time?
Does did the time justify itself?
Uh in in working on it. I hope so
Uh, I guess we'll see
Oh wait, I know what happened
I made the lord of good for yeah, well for me the lord of ghost kickstarter
Clarissa gunsmoke and then from january the secret project was started
You did do Clarissa gunsmoke this that was this year, right earlier?
Yeah, there was a few there was a few weeks months ago. It was fully released and I you know august
How long ago was august what the fuck well, it's november
That would have been three and a half months ago. No, it was longer ago than that, right?
There's no way the no Clarissa gunsmoke initially with the streams was last year, but I released it recently. Oh, yeah. Okay. Okay. That's
Yeah, yeah
Um, but I
Okay, the thing about secret projects though that I want to say is phantom's revenge is no longer a secret project
But I have recently started another secret project, but it's not no. No, it's not what you think
I'm not going to say what it is. It's not a thing that I have revenge dlc
It's not something
It's not something like phantom's revenge where i'm going to be working on it for a long time. It's just a little
It's just a little uh thing
I can't even I can't even starting a band. I can't even hint at what it is without giving it away
I hope this will not be too long before I can announce it. Um, it is just a little thing
Like I cook in under the hood in the background. It will hopefully be ready
It probably it will hopefully be ready in not too long and I will not actually have to do a lot of like work on it myself
I won't
Give any more details than that what it is. But when it's ready, I'll let people know and I think everyone will
Have a good chuckle about it. I think it will be very amusing
Uh for everyone and that's all I'm gonna say about it
I see I have an idea what it might be, but I won't say anything. Okay. Yes, please. Please. Please don't please don't say anything
If you have an idea. Yeah, um, but it's
It's a little
It's gonna be funny. It's gonna be really funny
Okay, that's all I gotta say about that
Um
All right, uh, let me complain for a second. You already know this kid, but I just got a complaint about my headphones. Um
Yes, so for a long time. I've had this my headphones have been shit
And uh, they just sometimes like the the battery they're wireless the battery dies on them all the time
The signal sometimes just fails recently on the last like five or six episodes of the pcp
I've had a thing where my
Signal will get choppy and I'll have like difficulty
It'll be a little choppy
and
The only way I can fix it is by turning my head a little bit to the left
Just sitting where I am and just turn my head a little bit left
And then it it it works better for some reason
um
the
Today I plug in my I had unplugged my headphones because I had been using my usb ports for other things
So I plug the dongle back in and I sit down to record and
There's almost no signal. I can just it's so choppy that it's just a little occasional
And um the I'm like okay
And I try turning my head and it again I can turn my head and when I turn my head to this one particular angle
Oh, I can kind of hear
But I'm like I can't just sit with my head at a single angle
It's so bad that I'm not just going to sit here frozen in place with my head at this one angle
Like a radio aerial just like oh, oh, I gotta tilt my head or I can't hear
So I had to get my these other headphones out
My dad gave me a pair of headphones a while ago
And I busted them out today and I've plugged them in and they're working pretty well
I don't they're not as comfy. I don't know. They're they're the kind that like go over your ears, which I sort of don't like as much
Um, but whatever they're fine
They're fine except that the cord these are not wireless. I think they have a bluetooth connection, but I have not enabled it
but um
The the the headphone jack cord that they came with is so short. It's like two feet long. I can't move my head
Oh god. Oh, I know. Oh god. I unplugged it. I unplugged it
Wait, I'm plugging it back. I moved I jerked my head to make a point
Um, can you hear hello? Are you there? Okay? I can hear you. Okay. Wait
Say say something
Okay, no, all right. I thought maybe I was hearing it through bluetooth, but um
Okay, say something again something few. All right, uh, cool. So anyway, that's my
I was gonna say gotta get a longer cord, but actually I should probably just try and enable bluetooth
I guess that would probably be good. I never liked wireless headphones
I mean, I know the appeal the the utility of such a thing
Very obviously great. You can move your head around, but I've got these um
I've had these I think I have to take them off to see the logo hang on
Yeah, Sennheiser
Sennheiser headphones that are like used
They were recommended by my university as like good for doing audio work
So I got those and they've got a really long cable
I can walk all the way around the room wearing them and they're comfortable
And I've had them forever
And it's just a wired connection. It's just so much more reliable
When I even even with my wireless headphones, I would often
Use them with a wire because they would need to have them plugged into a wall socket
You know because they'd be out of battery anyway. So like half the time it it didn't even matter that they were wireless
Yeah, it doesn't yeah, it doesn't matter to me that much
Whether they're wireless or not
Um, just this short wire is very annoying. I can't
I mean at least I can change the angle of my head. I just can't move my head more than like two feet away from my
computer tower, uh lull
Um
Hey, you know what I was you know what I was uh doing I did a little bit the last like day or two
Just because you mentioned it on the last episode that I went and I I watched some
I watched some some british, uh, uh
Some british financial youtubers talk about credit cards
Uh, oh
Yes, I learned a little bit. I sort of I was a bit disappointed to learn
What I had already felt might be the case
Which is that um the rewards you can get from british credit cards are just not very good
No, they never looked very interesting. There's one there's one guy I watched called sasha yansen
And his basically he said that like
Yeah, like like cashback rewards cards in the uk
Almost don't exist like they used to kind of exist
But now they they've been like just in the last like a year or two. They've been like drastically reduced
I think because due to covet he said it's that seemed to have something to do with it
But he recommended he recommended there's like one left that kind of is good
That he recommended and they were um the amex the amex platinum cashback
And the amex platinum cashback every day are two like similar
Cards that do give a a note a substantial reward. They have a certain like they have a sign-up bonus and they have a percentage cashback
uh bonus so if you were still
interested that was
Uh what he recommended amex platinum cashback cashback cashback every day the difference is like the every day one is no fee
But it like has like a slightly lower reward basically, so it's like if you're gonna spend over like 10 000
Over like 5 000 pounds in a certain period
The the regular one is better, but if you're gonna spend less than that the every day is better
Something like that
um
That was that that was the what I learned that was basically the gist of what I learned
Uh from do you have a link to that video so I can listen to him say it. I um, yeah, I think there were
Sasha Jansen baron cohen
Wait Sasha Jansen
Yeah, there were there were two there was one where he just kind of
Okay, I think I think this was the video. There's one where he goes over like
Okay, I I think he probably mentions the the amex platinum
Every day cashback in this one right here. Uh, I'll put it in the
Sorry, I'm taken forever to do this. I'll put it in general here
Does he does he mention amazon classic tesco foundation zopa aqua advanced capital one classic
Oh, no, these are um
These are no these are like beginner ones
There's a different video where he recommends the the amex platinum one
shit
No, I gotta find it
I have to find elias are cut out the awkward silences
Uh, okay. He definitely does mention the amex platinum cashback in this one
I think this is it
There might have been one or two other ones, but uh, yeah, anyway
Okay, that thumbnail is funny. Even though I use that as the currency denominator
Symbol it's funny seeing it being like oh make pound pound pound. Oh, yeah
Instead of dollar dollar dollar. Yeah, I'm so used to seeing dollars used. Yeah, just as like, you know, you're right. I noticed that too
Those crazy Brits in there crazy crazy gbps
I love I've always loved writing the little pound sign not like that. I do like a squiggly one
Yeah, with like it's the loop at the bottom. Yeah, the loop way loop at the top and the bottom
Yeah, I like it too. Um
I like I like I like treble clefs and I like ampersands
And I like um the pound sign
The the gbp pound sign not the hashtag. Yeah, is there a name for that or is it just the pound sign?
Yeah, it can't well if it's called the pound sign then it shares its name
Hold on
Sim, okay symbol
This is fun fact challenge. Oh, we're looking up first symbol for gbp
Uh
Okay, well, it's well, it's called the pound sterling
No, it is it's just called the pound sign
pound sign the pound sign is the symbol for the pound sterling
Okay origin symbol derived from the uppercase latin letter l
Representing Libra pondo
Also pondo pound, okay
same
Basic unit of weight so it was always a unit of weight same same origin as the lb for like pounds as in the weight measurement
Wait, no
Is is that that's lb not lp
Oh interesting lb toss
That the pound it was always a weight became an english unit of weight and in england became defined as the tower pound
Equivalent to 350 grams of sterling silver
So it's based on silver the literal weight of silver is why it's called the pound
Interesting. I I feel like I knew that I feel like
I'd never looked at this before I kind of just assumed that like it had to be a pound of something right
And I mean it's called a pound sterling so like of course it's silver
What else
I was
Wait, you there?
Yeah, I'm here. Okay. Um, you miss me
Yeah, um
Big big Joel made a thread on twitter the other day where he talked he mentioned he talked about inflation
And how like inflation is kind of good actually
Because like if if a currency inflates
I don't care about his fetishes
Ah
It devalued it devalues it literally like helps the bottom
Like percentage because it devalues the assets of the people that have a lot of money
And it devalues the debt of people that owe money
Like it's like in when inflation it's literally like good for poor people when inflation happens as long as it doesn't like go out of control
Hyperinflation the economy's broken
um
And he mentioned he mentioned the gold
I forget that he mentioned this and I had heard of it before but it wasn't something I knew a lot about he mentioned that like
the switch like from the
From the I think from like the the gold standard to the silver standard or something was like a big
Like proletarian movement. It was like a working class movement to switch from the gold standard and like
Doing that like somehow
Caused like a mass wealth transfer
basically
It was it was the idea was like
That also was sort of like devaluing currency
But it was like there was a big like there was like a labor push
For like the the adoption of like the silver standard
And it was and like the goal there was like yeah devalue the currency
because it represents in effect a
mass wealth transfer from the top to the bottom
Uh and inflation kind of does that which is sort of interesting
I guess that makes sense if you've got like a large amount of money and it goes down by a percent
The richest people will lose more
It's it's it's true person. It's it. Yeah, it does make sense and it's and it's just true people get
People get hung up on like oh inflation. Oh my my money is worthless and like
Yeah
true
Your your money is worth less
sort of but like
If every if yeah, if everybody's money is collectively worth less
Then the cost of goods
must
increase across the board
Right well like like it your money is is worthless, but people who have more money
It's worth even less and so it's sort of normalizing
Yes
So in in terms of like where you stand on like the hierarchy you have actually moved up because the people above you have been hurt worse than you
Uh based a little bit based a little bit base
um
Yeah
Economy am I right?
um
No, you're wrong. Oh, oh the the reason why okay, um
Long long time viewer someone who I someone whose name I remembered but I had not heard from or seen post in a long long time
on twitter reverse spectrum
Uh, he added me with a video that he thought I would be interested in and he was absolutely right. This was amazing
um, this was a video
about the infinite money machine is what it was called wait the the um
What was the channel called infinite?
money
machine
This was okay. The the channel was called patrick boil
Uh
This video is very funny. He delivers it in like a very dry sort of sarcastic way and it's it's really funny
It's a good video here. I'll link the video. Um
The the point of the video is a story about a guy who
Basically he basically scammed his credit card company, but it's like legal
He just exploited a loophole were in
He had a card that gave him 5 cash back on at grocery stores. So he would go to grocery stores
Buy visa gift cards
Use the visa gift cards to buy money orders
Transfer the money orders into as deposits into his bank account
And then use the balance in his bank account to pay the
The the credit card that he had used to buy the visa gift cards
And you know all the the fees in that transaction
Were less than the 5 cash back that he was getting from doing it
And so he was just getting free money every single time he did it and he just did it for a year
And he made like 300 thousand dollars
and
Yeah, and the funny and the funny part is they couldn't even tax him
They couldn't even tax him on the income because it's not income. It's discounts
He he generated 300 thousand dollars in free money and it wasn't even income
It was 300 thousand dollars in discounts of money that he never had in the first place
um
Just just awesome just awesome and um, I guess that doesn't work anymore. It's um, okay
It might work in some cases. It's basically just a question of like how soon will the bank catch you doing it
If the bank, I mean the bank can terminate your account for any reason if they catch you generating hundreds of thousands of dollars
They can just terminate your account if they want to so it's basically just like how
How can you fly under also?
Yeah, it's how long can you fly under the radar doing it?
And also I think that kind of across the board like rewards and cash back have just kind of gone down
Uh in term because of like the economic, you know recession and stuff
Um, so that's a bit so it's a bit harder to do. It's definitely harder for a multitude of reasons
But I think I don't know I was considering how I could maybe pull off a limited version of it
um
like, uh, I don't know I have um
I could buy like instacart gift instacart gift cards
I can buy them online. I don't even have to go to a store
If I could flip them
For even a small even a for like a relatively small
A fee I could do that with the I have I don't have unlimited
5% like this guy had but I have I have like 5 cash back on groceries up to like an annual limit of like
You know $10,000 or whatever
So if I could like do that much I could be generating, you know
A few hundred maybe a thousand dollars
I mean optimally if I if I could do it with no loss, which I probably can't
Um, but it really makes you think
Gets your noggin joggin
Uh, there's something
So appealing to me there's something so appealing to me about like
About cheating the system
About like just living on like not
What's really appealing to me about stuff like this is that it's like if this is how you make your money
You're not working for anyone. You don't have an employer
Nobody is extracting your your surplus value
You're just taking it from people with more than you
And I just think that's so cool. It's noble. It's noble in my in my opinion. I would call myself a hero actually
Oh
Yeah
Um, so anyway good good good video that one. Oh, he has another one about like the beanie baby
He had one about it was it's sort of about crypto, but it's more just generally about like
Bubbles and like, you know in like
Investing frenzies collecting frenzies in general. He talks about like
Just collectible assets or so-called treasure assets in general and how
Like yeah, sometimes they increase in value, but they're usually like they're lossier than like traditional assets
They're more subject to risk
They're more subject to like market whims. They don't generally outperform
Uh, sometimes they do but they in general they don't outperform the market
Uh, so they're just kind of stupid
Uh
God, I don't know crypto is bad
Uh, he compared he compared the nfts to like the beanie baby
craze, which I think is probably definitely true
God
Yeah, if if only they the nfts were as cute as beanie babies
I know right they could they could at least they could at least be cute if they do nothing else
Um, it ironically would make it like harder to hate if they were like cute
I don't know animal animal crossing-esque like little things. It's like oh look at others the fact that they're ugly. It's just like
Honestly, it's it makes it so easy
Honestly, I'm glad
Honestly, yeah, I'm glad that they're ugly like I'm glad that they look like shit
If they looked good, I feel like fewer people would hate them, which would be bad
So like I'm glad that they look bad. I'm thankful
I would hate to live in a world where like they're good and people like them
I
I guess the only other thing I have on my list of things to mention is that I've been reading a book
Could you believe it?
No
It's called uh, it's called the general by c.s. Forester
Oh, that's a good song. Do you know that song?
I I don't I have seen the others and I have discovered that this fight is not worth fighting
I like that song. Anyway continue
Yeah, the general first published in 1936 is kind of about uh, a general in
his his life and times
During before and then during the world war one
Where he's like doing stuff. It's just really nicely written
And it's good and it's a little tiny little
ancient little
book
But the best thing about it
The best thing about it that I found is that I have this leather bookmark
And I love having a leather bookmark in my hands
Well, my other hands I'm reading the book because something about I've had this for like
More than a decade. I've used it for various books
It's a bookmark that doesn't degrade easily. I think about other leather bookmarks from like, I don't know
Like uh, you go to a fucking place or zoo and they have like the generic station area a zoo
Yeah, when you when you try to think of a gen a generic place the first thing that comes to mind, you know
Like a zoo places that are like locations that are cool for kids and they have places that give like
Yeah, yeah gift shops and memorabilia and stuff. Sure. Yeah
They they they have their their things relating to the place they and then they have the generic stationery
Oh, it's a pencil with the name of the place you're at
pencil sharpener
Whatever
There's like a lot of these leather bookmarks. It's hard to say bookmark
um
And they're so fun to have because you hold them and there's they they give a little bit
They're kind of tough, but over time you sort of wear it in
Mmm, and it's it's a really good. It's a really good
fidgety thing that doesn't break easily
And it's you know, it's just
It's a tactile
That's why I like reading real books is only because of the bookmark is so fucking fun to hold in my hand while I'm reading
Yeah, I can't get into kindle because it's like, uh, I'm looking at a screen
I I've heard that screens are bad
Even though it's not really powerful screens are bad
But like, um, and if it's on my computer or an audiobook, I'm like, ah, but I if I'm listening to a podcast
Audiobook, I got to be doing something else and I I can't pay attention to it
But reading a physical book works because of the bookmark
Everybody should have a leather bookmark and they will read like a hundred thousand times more
That is my and it's my pitch for bookmarks
leather
It's a hard sell
The general itself is is a very nicely written book
But it is very old and there are a few times where the hard rn word is used. I've seen
What is it about?
Well, it's about a general in his exploits to like
Go through the ranks and it's like it's a character book. It's not really like so it's a war. It's about this one guy
There's a novel. Yes. Okay. Okay. I think there are some
Characters that are real generals or real like army officials that were integral to the war and he interacts with them
and
and it's like, uh, he's kind of
Autistic this guy. He's all very prim and proper, but he hates social interactions and he just talks in very normal
Not normal, but like very direct
emotionless ways
and he gets he has like he
he meets a
the the daughter of a
duchess
and she is like described to be sort of horse-faced and ugly
and like not not particularly
you know
Fancy and stuff for her station. She you know, she knows how to dress and all that but it's like
She is unremarkable and he's kind of socially awkward and they really loved each other and they got on so well
and it's like
You know, she she as a as a daughter of a duke and duchess
Doesn't really she's quite sheltered. She doesn't know what a real man is like
Um, she doesn't know what it's like to have like sex that's like good and he's kind of bad at it
But because she doesn't have a frame of reference
She's okay with all that and it's it's kind of funny. It's kind of funny how
this guy
I don't know it's it's hard to explain the the appeal of this character in this book
um
The general go read it. Just it's it's my book report. Who who's it by?
A c.s. Forrester as I said, oh, sorry. I'm stupid lull
He's a he's a guy who who wrote something or other. What did he write?
He wrote something or other. I don't I don't know. I don't know books. I I just like sphabas or something
Something something hornblower
Observer, I don't know if I can know I'm reading the back like I have it right in front of me, but yeah
The general it's it's like
I think the thing I like it's Herbert Curzon is the name of the guy character
Yeah, the thing I like about him is that he's kind of autistic
and
Very relatable to me in a funny way in funny ways like he's so old fashioned
But like his his his thought process is like described in such a way that I'm like, yeah, you know what?
Parties do suck. I do like not want to go to them
True and he's and he's all like he's really into
making his army his his battalion is his
Squad I'm not sure what you call it that he's in charge of
um
By the time the first world war is going and he's in the trenches
and he's like um
he's really into
like be he's he's got a
A way with like making sure everything runs well for the purposes of being better than other people
And people respect his like strictness and is no nonsense stuff
And he's not like he doesn't have a good personality which makes him perfect for like running a tight ship
and it's just sort of
I don't know it's it's weirdly cute. I find him weirdly cute as an old-fashioned timey general
Hmm
I'm reading the I'm trying not to I'm reading a bit of the
story framework on on wikipedia
That seems I've never read I've never read anything by c.s. Forrester
I just had it on my shelf and it's like, oh, this is old. Maybe it's good, you know old good
new bat so
True and it turns out to be true. That's what I did with um when I lived with those guys in um california for a while
I just like one of the girls had a bunch of old books on her shelf and I just grabbed old books and read them
That's when I read um the plague by camu
and I read uh
The stranger also by camu just read a lot of camu. Wait is stranger by camu?
I don't yes. Yes, it is. Yes, it is. Um, she must have been a camu fan
um
Neat, um
Oh god, there's a there's a loud
The helicopter outside my window, but the way there were there were people talking
There were people talking like right outside my window when I first uh logged on but they they quickly
Stopped so good good for them. I appreciate that a lot
Good for them. I have only one more note about things I did this week
And it was something that I got really excited about almost as excited as I got about drawing that angry face
last week
Um, it was about it was about water
It was about I was really hyped for different kinds of waters that I could acquire
I was um
I went on
I went on instacart and I'm like I'm almost out of sparkling water
It's time for me to shop around for more and I went on
I went to uh, hana fords. I looked I looked up the menu at hana fords
I looked what they have what what they have on offer in terms of sparkling water versus seltzer water
I looked at uh, aldi. I found I found new offerings at aldi that I had not seen before
um
I have I have learned
I have I now have a big shelf full of all different kinds of
sparkling waters sparkling water beverages and seltzer waters
Uh, as well as just water beverages neither sparkling nor seltzers. Um
God, I'm I'm truly rich in spirit
um the the
I have learned that many places sell things that are called sparkling waters
But they have artificial sweeteners and like flavorings in them
Making them basically just soda
But with like a sort of health conscious branding
To them, but I like them a lot. I love them. They're my favorite. I think I think there was like a tom scott video
explaining why disani isn't sold in the uk
Hmm because like uh coca-cola
Owns disani and disani is like an amer- it's it's seen as an american thing to have mineral water where the minerals are added
um
like artificially
And so like this kind of like uh, it was a huge backlash
against disani once that was found out and
because of a
TV show only fools and horses an episode where there was a scam
It was a comedy skit show and what's oh, okay, okay
and uh, there was an episode where there was like a scam with like
Sewage water being sold as special something or other and that was like in the public consciousness when that scandal happened
Or it became a scandal because of that and then they couldn't sell that water because nobody trusted it
So and and so mineral water is like you can't put the things in afterwards
You can't add things to water has to be just water. What the fuck?
Wait, okay. So the problem with disani is that they add minerals to it
Yeah, they they they have a treatment plant where and that's and that's bad
I I think chemically there's no difference at all. It should be fine
In fact, it is as far as I understand disani any water where you just
Mineral water like from the scottish highlands or whatever I guess bottled and then sold and it's like
Oh, it's actually from there or it's actually it's like got rid of like
Crud and soil and you know bad things they filter things out
But they don't add like chemicals in
Because of the public perception of that being a bad thing even though it's probably fine
So that's just how water is in the uk. That's why I have never seen or like rather
Um, but we have different brands for water bottles in the uk that I've never seen in america or like the other way around
And I didn't never have seen disani before I went to america. It was always avian or volvo or like stuff like that
Highland spring
I think
I think that's the difference between
sparkling water
And seltzer. Uh, wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on. Uh
Okay
I think that like if if they artificially
carbonate it
Then it is seltzer
If it's like naturally carbonated
Uh, then it's naturally carbonated. Yeah. Yeah, like certain. Okay
It seems
Silly and I kind of feel like there's no way they actually do this
Like they actually go to like a naturally occurring like carbonated water spring and like obtain
Natural sparkling water from the spring like there's no way that they do that
But like supposedly that's the difference between seltzer and sparkling in practice
I have I am finding that the difference is that sometimes they will they will just add a bunch of shit
Add a bunch of like flavorings and sweeteners and shit to spark to sparkling water
And make it basically soda
Uh, but not always and then they don't do that
Then it's just
I think the difference is that the carbonation is artificial and versus natural
um
and
Minerals man. Minerals are just a whole other whole other ballgame
uh
That's that's
Really so like
Is that is that a it's a is it just a weird uk thing that they're like you can't add the minerals
You gotta you gotta find the night the minerals got to come from the earth or I don't want them
Yeah, I essentially I mean, okay
I think it's it was it was more just like
A scandal happened
And then from then public perception was like, oh, it has to be like real otherwise. It's it. Yeah, it's being natural from
You know a water source or a high up in the mountains or or just wherever but like you can't add chemicals into water
We won't buy it and so that's just sort of continued
I don't know whether it's changed, but from what I remember from this tom scott video, which wasn't that long ago
Uh, it's still like that
I'm reading some article here
Spring water is according to fda. This is american definition
A spring a spring water is according to fda derived from an underground
Formation from which water flows naturally to the surface of the earth at an identified location called a spring
It can be a man-made borehole, but there are other regulations associated with that if it's a man-made spring
Uh mineral water also comes from an underground source
But it differs from spring water because mineral water contains a quote
constant level and relative proportions of minerals and trace elements at the point of emergence from the source
What
So mineral water is just spring water, but it's like it has a certain amount. It has like the right amount
of nutrients in it or minerals, I guess
artesian water refers to
Water that comes from a tapped aquifer artesian actually refers to the natural geological process of pressure that causes water
From an aquifer, which is a layer of permeable rock and soil that can store water to rise to the surface and form a well
Oh, no artesian. Oh, not artisanal. It's not artisanal water
It's artesian water, which is not referred to like craftsmanship. Okay. I know what an aquifer is because I play dwarf fortress
So no need to explain that to me
Uh my my recipes dot com
Um fuck
So reading gov dot uk about so much rigmarole. What is what is this considered?
Mineral water and the definitions of stuff. I think it's mostly like a branding thing
Like you can sell water where you add stuff in but you can't call it mineral water or something
Because it would be insane
I guess tap water is technically mineral water. I'm not even sure actually
Okay, this is just a list of all the natural mineral waters recognized in the uk
And how to apply for recognition. Okay. Well, whatever. It's not information
It's just a list
I don't know how to read this that that definition that I just read seemed to specify the to be mineral water
It has to it has to have the minerals
When it leaves the ground
Yes
So I guess us has that as well. I don't know. So disaney
is um
Okay, dis disaney is not mineral water. It is
Purified and mineral enhanced water
Yes, that's the distinction. Okay. I see I see it may have been it may I may be reading too much into the video
Because he may have said like it's the reason disaney doesn't get sold
Because there was a an association with treated water being gross
or something
This reminds me there was a not illegal. There was a video recently from folding ideas
Where he talks. I think it's a a british like celebrity chef. I forget the chef's name. Oh jamey oliver. Yeah
Did you see that the chicken nuggets video? I I yeah, I have seen I never really thought about it before
But it makes a lot of sense that he's probably like a bit of a
upper class
the
Yeah, the
the thing about like oh
The chicken what's wrong. What's wrong with the nuggets is that they are unclean
They are made of the unclean part of the chicken the dirty chicken meat
Not the good not the good clean chicken meat the filthy haram chicken meat
um
Yeah, what do you there's that one line dan says where he's like, you know, if if your criteria
For eating of food is that it has to look nice at every stage of production like that's a you problem
That's not really a mark against the food that like at some point in the production like something looked gross about it
Right. Yeah, jamey oliver has been around. I've seen him a lot as like a uk like
guy of of food
relevance note
and and like he's he's definitely been like
prominent in the way he talks about
Uh, I'm just trying to protect the kids because they're eating all this gross
Fatty crap and it's bad
And everyone's like, oh, yes. Yeah, it makes sense
Never really thought about him like that before but it does make sense to think of like he's just
He's health conscious
But like kind of in a stupid way
Yeah
I mean, is it like in the video how he's like
He's sort of trying to contend that the nuggets are unhealthy, but it's not like
It's not really argued
that way
It's argued in a sort of like wishy-washy
aesthetic
Yeah, kind of I mean, I guess this is dirty sort of way dirty for just reasons
Yeah, just for reasons. I
I think it it resonated with a lot of people
For some reason at the time when he was like he was hot shit. He was he was the the the young
crazy new
Chef kid on the block and he's coming out with all these recipes and he goes he goes like bing bong bash
Bosh
Pan like that and I was like, wow cool. Yeah. Wow. Look at this guy. Look at this guy go. He's so quick. Sure
I haven't really seen anything that he does though aside from saying that nuggets suck
I mean, do you I guess do you watch cooking programs? I I don't really I
Well, you know, my parents watch the Great British menu, which is like super high and
Chefs from all corners of the UK
Great Britain Northern Ireland Wales all that Scotland and they have like one from each district
one from each sort of area north of England
Midlands or whatever
And they compete to make a banquet meal
For like a big event somewhere every every year or so
And that's that's a good one
I like because they're like top of the line like Michelin star chefs
From and they're really good at what they do. So it's very interesting seeing them
make like insane
Meals to a brief of like a theme
That's quite fun. And then there's the Great British Bake Off, which is
Well, I've heard of that one baking. Yeah, that that's a big one
Because it's it's you know, that's fun. I don't really watch like much
Myself I'm just sort of catch it when it's on it's like. Oh, yeah. Look at that. Look at that fish
Look and like chop those onions real quick. They know what they're doing
And I think I have seen a bit of Gordon Ramsay
Yelling at people. Oh, sure
Who who has because that that that's always fun, I guess
Uh
What would we how do we get on this topic? Uh, you were talking about sparkling water. Oh, and how the like food
right how
The the the dasani is unclean because it's the minerals do not come from the earth
Uh, I just remembered this. Do you want to I mean, have you been following the uh, the the kyle rittenhouse stuff?
I've been seeing a lot of kyle rittenhouse stuff on twitter
I will not have too much to say about it
I didn't follow it when it's when it first came out as a like a big news thing and I still haven't really followed it
like the just I get
Is that he killed some people
and the court is determining whether
You know how the
What should happen next is he gonna get punished and thrown in jail for murder or is it self-defense?
And that's the big question. I guess he he uh, it seems okay
People say he was defending himself and in the moment. Yeah, he definitely was being
aggressed upon
The the the question in my mind is like
Was he was he aggressing simply by being there and I really think he was
I really think that the fact that he went to this place
Open carrying, you know brandishing his weapon at the protesters was like
made him a a what's what's the like, you know
Basically constituted an active threat and I feel like the the protesters were
Defending themselves by trying to you know disarm him
um
and I think you know
that's my opinion and uh
I am it's very it's been very sad and disheartening seeing
Lots of people lots and lots of people
Even people who you might have thought would know better
Uh be like watch the try watching the trial and be like oh, yeah, I guess I guess it was self-defense after all
Oh, yeah, I'm pro. I'm pro written house now
Uh, it's seem seems like
In my I mean in my corner of the internet
Obviously everyone thinks he's you know, he's guilty seems like the broader
Internet is is turning pro written house, uh, which is is just very sad
Uh
I don't
Maybe it's just doomer talk, but it seems like even the the people that I follow
I follow a few people who are lawyers who have said like
He's getting off. He's got he's getting a full acquittal
Which is very sad, um and makes me upset
um
But I mean in my head like I just assumptions I make from bits and bobs. I see is that oh well, he's white so
like uh
Him brandishing like an automatic weapon
Uh is like
It's gonna be looked at less harshly by the general public
Uh, then if it were a black person and for that reason I just assume maybe he you know
But like I can't really assume that until I've looked more into it
So I'm just uh, whatever
Maybe it sucks. Maybe it sucks. What's happening, but I'm stupid and I haven't been interested enough to look
I have been
honestly, I
You know, I've seen some of the
Judge being like weird and and bad
And I've seen a lot of the lawyers being like doomer about it being like this is fucked. He's getting a full acquittal and like
I don't know. Yeah
I can't I can't affect the outcome
And like who knows how things will shake out
Why why I'm
I feel like I know what's going on. I've kind of just been like I don't sort of don't want to read anything else about it until it's over
and maybe then I'll
I'll be curious what the verdict is
Why why worry about it until then? I mean, I guess if I really wanted to
Take that logic all the way like why worry about it even afterwards like it doesn't directly affect me. Why worry about anything?
Um
Why even care at all? Why not simply touch grass?
Uh, which I mean, I guess I guess that's true
I don't know. I don't know. I have no conclusion
The thing the thing is that I've heard is well, it's like
The the details are iffy
Like it's not like there's like it's not like a police shooting
Where they had a body cam and it's so obvious that the policeman has done wrong or like it was filmed
But yet and yet still
The police are getting off
You know with a tap on the wrist
Um
So like from what like the information involved in what happened is is confusing
And so it could go either way like it could actually be
Like I don't know it really I think I think bringing a bringing a gun to a protest
Really betrays like what you intend to do at the protest. Yeah, why bring a such a large gun?
Yeah
He was he was he was he was there to he was there with a gun to protect
Property other other people's property
with deadly force
And some and some people online think like that's okay and that's good and people should be allowed to do that and should do it more
Which is pretty fucked up
He
I don't know I don't know what else to say about it. Uh, he it's from a moral perspective like
Stopping a window getting smashed by killing someone
Is not equivalent in any way. There's there's no in mind. There's no question that that's that's what he was that that's what it was about for him
Um, he maybe is an intimidation thing. They're like, I don't know sure you have live ammunition. You uh, yeah, whatever
Yeah, um, he
The I've seen the have you seen this judge
The the judge really seems
The judge really seems like a piece of shit. The judge really seems he really seems biased in favor of the defense
And he really seems like he doesn't know what he's talking about and like there was a part where
He just seems weird and like he just rambles about shit for at times
And there were there's a part where like I didn't see this part
I just heard about it, but I guess the prosecution
Was like trying to show him something on a screen
And it was a digital, you know photograph
Or or video screenshot or whatever and they they're they're zooming in right they're just zooming into the image
And the judge doesn't understand what zooming in is and he thinks that they're like digitally altering the image by zooming in on it
And they had to like I guess he asked like extremely old
He's he's not like he's he looks like he's maybe like late sixties
So he's pretty he's pretty old. He's not like ancient
He's quite old
Yeah, but like he
I guess they had to like consult an expert witness about like weather
Zooming in on a photograph counts as like altering
The data but like it doesn't he just seems like he doesn't like
Want to hear
He seems biased is what I'm saying and also incompetent. So
You know
Who knows who knows?
um
It's a lot of like it's a lot of like I can imagine, you know, I can imagine
that there'd be some
larger
Like um attempt to get kyle out of
easy
By like, you know, like familial connections or stuff like that. Um, I could you could imagine a lot. I just
Personally don't know too much about what's going on. So it's hard to say. Oh, yeah, it's all a big bunch of bullshit
I'm not in yeah, so whatever
I'll just say that I think it's dumb to bring a gun
to a place like that
And then not expect anything bad to happen if he gets if he gets an unequittle
the messages
White people
Go out to protest with a gun
shoot protesters
The system supports you
Um
Yeah, I don't know it's bad. Um
I have no more notes. I'm out of notes. I'm out of topics of discussion
Uh, do you got anything else or should you want to go on to voicemails?
Uh
No, I don't think so
Uh, let's go. Let's go. Do you have um
Oh, yeah, I'll get whatever whatever whatever it's called open
Speak pipe speak pipe comm slash pcb voicemails
If you want to send us a voicemail, baby
Um, all right, let me just get these downloaded here
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, I'm collecting I'm collecting these voicemails like nfts. I'm right click saving
All right, uh, you ready? Yep. Okay. The first one is called it's venom and
Oh, somebody messed somebody asked me like did I get to play this
voicemail last week they sent it like right as we were finishing recording last week
Shit was it oblivion fall fuck? I don't remember somebody was like wanted us to play this one last week
But I didn't lol. Anyway, uh, it's venom three two one go
By the proletariat
Bummer
Does it make a different broadcast that would that was growing everything
Okay
So, yeah, this was um because later that that day last sunday when we recorded last episode I did go on the drawcast
later with um
It was sitel teleperte
Was it oblivion oblivion fall? I think yeah, it was like a regular is a host
Yeah, I think it was I think was it just the four of I think it was the four of us. Yeah, we did a um, we did a comics jam
which you know
I you know the pcp
Invented the drawcast and I introduced the pcp two comics jams. So it's basically I basically own this property
It all came from me
We did a did you mention that on the show? Yes, I did a little bit
Um, uh, yeah how I introduced I think it was at
Brony con. I think at one of the brony cons. I got everyone to draw a comics jam
Sitting around in the hallway. Well, hang on. I remember munchy talking about someone
Telling him about it and him telling you about it or was it the other way? No
No, it had to be the other way around because I learned about it from one of my fellow
Camp counselors at astro camp
I definitely did not learn about it from munchy
Okay, so you probably told munchy. Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I must have
um
That was funny. We did a yeah, those were we did some pretty funny comics in that one. Uh, there was a
There's a there's a keg standard in phantom horn comic in there, too, which is very good and I like it a lot
Uh, so I got I got teleparted to draw keg in phantom
Uh
Uh, yeah, that was that will be out in a few weeks. I think over on the drawcast
Channel, so go to the drawcast channel
There's a bunch of the content on there and eventually do you know when the the telephone?
One is coming out or people still working on their drawings for that one
Doing the drawings and then they're gonna come back around and ask us to like have like a bit where we
um
Like commentate with them over our section of the drawing like sped up. Yeah
um, yeah
So it'll be still a while before that's finished. Okay. Well, I guess I'll just uh
Wait for that then
That's delicious. Mmm. Lemon seltzer water
Not not sparkling water not flavored not sweet and just regular just a touch a hint
A hint of lemon flavor
God, I love I love deals
I love
I love the taste of a deal. I do this is this is the taste of a deal
I'm looking at I'm looking at the the instacartman and I'm going through and they've got you know
They got cans they got lacroix that that's costs like
Fucking $18 a can boo. Then they got like off-brand lacroix. That's can it's also cans in a box
You know, that's less not good enough lacroix
Then they have
They have what's they have like the uh, the leader the leader bottles
The leader bottles of the various different flavored sparkling waters or like the uh, the six-pack cases of like the smaller bottles
You want to get it bottled you want to get off-brand?
And then it's it's like pay it's like sense
It's like it's like pennies literal pennies for me to drink drink like a king all the flavors
All the flavors of the of the world of of of deepest darkest Peru
deepest africa and the the the the mango the tangy mangoes of the of the of the
Of the the amazon rainforest uh all brought to the
To my palette um from places unknown all for all for pennies on the dollar
anyway
I'm just thinking of like a like a blue steel
keg of lacroix
Blue steel
Why would it be blue like like I don't know just sort of like painted blue like a steel keg
Like a wooden casket of lacroix
um
Lacroix is fine and all it's just that it's name brand so it it costs more and who
It's the same it's the same fucking product
um
Next voicemail is red five rainbow three two one go
Hey, wait, do you think trixie can like copyright strike you?
For selling the road to radcon books
I'm no wait. No, that's a real life one is dm dmca
No, because she abandoned it because I mean she she did write them
You're making a profit off of it. She wrote it for and she like
It was it was it was it was specifically a kickstarter
It was specifically a kickstarter
Uh reward that we promised she promised to deliver it for
Radcon and then didn't so like I I mean, yeah, no, absolutely not
She didn't finish it ben wrote the final chapter
So it's not entirely
but I don't know
I feel like
Imagine imagine if she tried imagine how
Imagine how fucking imagine how fucking stupid she would look. No, nothing would happen
No, it's it would be impossible
um lamal
um
Next voicemail good good question good good question fair fair fair question
But the answer is no
Next voicemail is called your first voicemail recording always sucks three two one go
Ben look we love you, but your defense of investing in bitcoin without mining bitcoin
The other episode was off-based and someone needs to fucking tell you that
Just because you don't actually mind the cryptocurrency itself
Doesn't mean that you're you're not doing harm because you still do harm by giving it legitimacy by giving them money
If nobody invested in bitcoin, it's value. That's a terrible argument and it would just be that's really stupid
tossing the same
million couple million dollars back and forth with each other
Just because we exist in
Society doesn't mean that we need to participate in the worst aspects of it
Just because I exist in society doesn't mean I must go on to become a police officer
Just because I exist in society doesn't mean that I must go on to become a landlord
You like listen just because we exist inside doesn't mean that we have to do yeah, I got it all the bad things that society
Listen you also work to make society better. I
You know it's true. If that's what i'm criticizing about you right now
If only if only nobody just had invested in bitcoin then cryptocurrency wouldn't be a thing if only people didn't buy
NFTs then NFTs wouldn't be a thing like yeah
Obviously I said I said this last week like
Okay, some dag zaggles DM'd me on twitter with what I think was meant to be a technical explanation for why
Crypto transactions are the same as mining and his and he said something about like air dropped coins
And I gotta be honest. I didn't understand what he was telling me dag zaggles if you're listening. I am sorry about that
I don't get it, but maybe you're right. Maybe maybe on a technical level. It is the same in which case
It is what it is
um this argument that like oh you're giving it legitimacy
Is I just don't care. I'm sorry. I said this last week
I don't like bitcoin. I don't like cryptocurrency. I don't like I don't like lots of things. I don't like banks
But I still have my money in a bank
um
the
if if I thought
If I thought if I really thought if I knew for a fact that bitcoin was gonna like double in price tomorrow
I'm sorry. I would buy bitcoin. I would put all my money into bitcoin
Would would that be
Giving it legitimacy. I don't know maybe a little bit. Maybe some insignificant. It's it's too late
It's too late for me to do anything to like actually stop it
But like if it was going to explode tomorrow, I'm sorry. Yeah, I would get it because like
I want my money to double like that that
I guess it's selfish, but like I don't think me not getting it
Would have like a significant impact
I just want I want resources. I need to accrue resources
every person needs to accrue resources in order to thrive and uh
I'm I got I'm sorry. I gotta look out for number one
Yeah, I get the argument, but it's like
It's not that you should strive to engage with things that you don't like but like
It is a kind of a like at a certain point
Everything you do is bad because it's all tied up in
The economy which is tied up in
other things that like
Disenfranchise people or enslave people in other parts of the world. It's like it's hard to not
Yeah
participate
And when you don't
Participate in a small section of it as an individual
Not much changes at all if anything ever
It is not
It's not it's not really the the the the the onus doesn't really on the individual
to set an example
That can change
I don't know the world
If you have a lot of reach then yeah, you got more onus on you to do that
I have I guess we have some it's just so small that it's like
It's I don't know I have never I have never claimed that like my
My own personal not owning bitcoin is like a moral
stance the the reason that I don't own any
Actually, I have a little bit that I had to pull out of Kucoin
But like whatever
The reason that I don't own a significant amount of bitcoin is right now is because
I believe that it is
A bubble that is going to pop at some point and I don't want to be left
Holding the bag if I I'm sorry if I didn't think that
I would buy bitcoin if I thought it was going to go up to a if I was really convinced it was going to 100k
I'd buy it
I'm sorry. I'm I'm sorry
um
I don't think it's going to or or maybe it might but I also think it's going to crash and I just I'm like
I'm looking at it and I'm thinking like
At some point. I think it's going to pop. It's going to crash and I just I just don't want
If if I invest even if it goes even if it goes up a little bit from now
Maybe I could make some money if I invested right now at some point though
There's going to be losses and I think it's probably best avoided
Just so that I don't
And yeah end up holding the bag. I don't know. I might the issue. I could be right or it could be wrong
I guess the issue of that argument really is like
It's it's adjacent to like you live in society like you criticize society like you get you live in it in the same way
He referenced that it could be
Well, yeah, but like and it's yeah, it's it's it's saying
um
you should
like
show us
How you would live outside of a society or like how you would live in a better society
Instead of living in the one you're in now
right, uh
No, maybe it's not entirely
like
The same I'm trying to think of how to put this because like he said
um
Just because you live in a society doesn't mean you have to do anything
He said just because you live in a society doesn't mean you have to participate in the worst parts of it
Right, I mean true
I don't have I don't have by doing it. We're not saying we have
We're not saying anyone should or how to I don't know. I feel like it's just it's
it's putting the pressure on an individual rather than
Like like like the the point of pointing it out and saying hey, you're doing a bad thing
is
It just hurts individuals more than it like changes the world
If you know what I mean like people just feel bad about what they're doing
But the system is still structured in a way that it's hard to not do it. Yeah
And then I don't know
I guess I don't find too much of an issue with him complaining about you or I doing
stuff like that
Yeah, I don't find it helpful either
um
I mean, I guess I
appreciate anyone who is like
I mean if you're if you're sitting there and you're like
Hmm bitcoin is definitely going to the moon
But I will abstain from buying it because I think that it would be morally wrong
Like I would I would uh, I would come I would commend you on your on your principled
Actions I would say that's a pretty impressive like moral sacrifice you
Are making or think you are making
I wouldn't
If I still like chicken nuggets and even though the meat industry sucks
I I don't know consider there's so many things I could be doing to like to make statements and stands about like how things are bad
And I will only do the good things
And it's I don't know it's too hard
Consider that consider this viewer say that if you threw all your money in bitcoin right now
And then a week like and then it was going to blow up and you were going to make $10,000
You were going to get $10,000 from bitcoin right if you did that
By not by not doing it. You are basically throwing away $10,000. So are you willing to just personally
throw away
10,000 of your of your dollar of your potential dollars to you know, not
inflict whatever
You know environmental damage would be done
By you know that amount of bitcoin transactions. I don't know exactly how much
that is
Unless unless I saw evidence that like it was
Really like doing like more than $10,000 worth of harm to the world. I probably would still do it
It's hard to quantify. Yeah, and it's it really would only it's like a lot of things if everybody
Had that attitude then there's the solution. I wouldn't sacrifice that would be there unless I knew everybody stopped using
Cryptocurrency and then everything's great. But of course
How do you influence everybody?
You don't you don't do that
By telling each person individually because you know, a lot of them are not going to
Agree and then the people who do agree
Not all of them are in like a good
Like the the best situation to change up their habits not necessarily just with crypto but with anything that like
Like like, you know eating meat or or doing this or that
Every it's it's not everybody's in the right position. Some people are and even then they might get lazy
it's it's
I feel
A waste of energy to go after individuals
To to you know to wipe your finger at them
and say
You're doing a bad thing
by giving legitimacy
yourself you only
I think there's but at the same time, I don't know what they could do instead that would
Reach more people because that's hard. Anyway, so it is I guess continue to I guess I can't I can't blame I can't blame anymore
I can't blame them. Yeah, I can't I can't
um
Next next voicemail is called caramella boy
three two one
Hey, pcp
I was in for a shitty day at work
But then something magical happened then said check out this stupid caramel dancing video by yannis Ali
And so I went and did that
And it was just a magical 40 minute trip. I was smiling the whole time. It was like I was in middle school again
When he said balsamic vinegar, I had like the biggest pog in front of my computer screen because I was like, oh my god
That's the joke from lucky star. It all makes sense now
and it was just
Exactly what I needed to make my day better
um, thank you so much ben for
Recommending such an amazing video and even though he's probably not going to hear this. Thank you so so much yannis Ali
That was an amazing video. You are a true god
Thank you pcp once again
caramella
The yannis Ali video is great yannis Ali has made a bunch of good videos. I think that's probably his best
Uh, it was definitely the most I've seen he did ones on like letters
and they're
Like I think that's the same guy right like like talking about the letter e or something
Maybe his numbers. Oh, yeah, he did he's done a bunch of videos about letters
He did a bunch of videos they seem like intellectual like oh, I guess I need to be a letter nerd
He has really appreciate this a bit, but he has moved more into um, he has moved more into, um,
Like more media stuff and more like youtube friendly stuff recently
Which is fine. His old his old stuff is pretty interesting, but it's very like
Who are you who are you gonna talk to you about like oh, I learned some interesting facts about the letter c today
Yeah, um
Yeah, uh next next voicemail is called who?
three two one go
Hey, I wanted to ask you guys the who would win where why of radcon
I'll start with the who on this week
Who do you guys think is going to show up if you do another radcon?
and also
Who are you going to name it after?
surely you can't keep it named radcon we could after trixie's dead name especially after trixie is kind of
Not friends with the show or the group. I don't I don't care about any maybe you keep it radcon's a cool name
Yes, but yeah, who do you think will show up and will you change the name?
if we did it
A name change maybe maybe if we wanted to I don't know to
possibly because like um
Being obviously I don't think a lot of the people
Who who used to come would want to come?
for various different reasons
Man she doesn't want to be on the internet anymore
uh
Trixie obviously is just gone and we don't like her so she's not invited
Tom would would would show up. I maybe Nate would show up probably if there was like it was nicely organized
and
potentially Jesse
But like as a stretch
I think if it was a big enough deal and we asked
He may show up at some point, but I I don't know. I have no idea what he feels about the state of the pcp at the moment
Wait, I'm being I'm being rude on twitter again. Oh god dang it
Okay, good. Um my um, I have spewed. I have spewed my bile
on twitter
And uh, I will probably continue to do so
um
Anyway, the next voicemail is called
addressing only the maddest niggas
Uh, okay three two one go
Few absolute maniacs who are really listening to the pcp from the start
Uh, could maybe just all of the kindness of your high
um compile
A list of all the times they talk about homestuck
Uh, or Andrew hersey
They send it to me
Or just, you know, put it on the comments. I would appreciate it very much
What does he really want for that info did you understand did you understand the question? What was the question?
Yeah, he was he's saying to
addressing like mad people in the pcp audience
If you could get all of the instances of the progress and they just talking about homestuck or Andrew
Hussie and then telling him in the comments all of them
I we talk about that's so many times over the entire
Like of the podcast so that's a lot of
timestamps
I don't know what they plan to do with it
Uh, I don't by the way, this this this is the guy that i'm pretty sure called into the anamorphon time
Podcast that one time this this is the voice that i'm almost positive
Called into the chris grinds episode of that. Uh, so if you've if you've heard that episode of anamorphon time
Let me know if you think it's the same guy. I'm pretty sure it's the same guy
um
Next voicemail is called boris j 3 2 1 go
Ben do you realize a lot of pcp viewers also listen to the dick show?
Uh, I'm sure some of them do
I feel like uh, what am I supposed to do about it the vast majority of those who
Enjoy the dick show probably don't enjoy the pcp, but maybe they do
Except when politics comes up. I don't know. I'm sure I'm sure there's some crossover. I mean, you know a lot of people who
Listen to the pcp were digi fans and digi shielded the the dick show a lot. So like yeah
I don't know man. What whatever
I don't agree. I don't like the dick show, but like
What's to be done?
uh
Next voicemail is a tweet. Um, here i'll i'll post the tweet in the
Server
Oh, is it um coming up? Why is it not a typo?
Uh, sorry the link doesn't work. Sorry, buddy. Let me try again. Um
Next next voicemail is called fuck Ralph
Three two one go. Huh? What you there?
That's good. Okay. Okay. Three two one go
So we don't have any friends. So I just decided to like ramble into the void
Aka like your ears
I just watched the Ralph the movie maker video about linkara and
I don't know about linkara. I don't know if he's like
Bad person or like cringe or base because I'm not the fucking nerd
But like that video that might as well be
like the
Ralph's embodiment of
Trixie going on that podcast and basically just projecting all over floors
Because this smug little asshole like he made four. I think four movies that all fucking suck
He charged like 20
30 dollars for them on blu-ray
Yeah, like funding for them and they fucking sucked ass and he has the audacity
To to mock like another person
for acting
badly
Like he acts any better that fucking rat face little fuck. I hope he's fucking
Wait, so you're talking about Ethan Ralph, right?
No, he's talking about Ralph the movie maker. Oh, he charged
So he charged 40 dollars for a shitty DVD of of what?
Of well movies he's made I guess
Oh
And yet and yet he courtesizes linkara's movie. I think
The hypocrisy I I don't feel like that's that's fine. Did linkara make a movie?
I guess
Well, I mean if this guy thinks that Ralph the movie maker made worse movies than linkara
Then I mean that's a pretty strong claim. Well, I mean, I don't know. I mean, I haven't seen linkara's movies
I kind of assume they're not good
Linkara is a bit of a cringe individual, but you know, they they make the type of
Things that their audience enjoys if this guy is saying that like
Linkara gave better value for money unlike the like he gave he gave it at a more reasonable price
and all that
I mean, I'm fair enough. I feel like this guy thinks that linkara gave a better product
Yeah, I I don't know. I think well, he says he doesn't know about linkara
So he's coming at it from like Ralph the movie maker makes bad movies and yet
criticizes them
Which I think is
It's I don't find that to be a problem if somebody makes a bad movie
I mean, I'd like red letter media and space cop was terrible
It was not a good movie and yet they they think they can talk about movies
Hmm. Yeah
I mean, you don't necessarily have to be you don't necessarily have to be a great movie a great filmmaker to criticize movie
You don't whatever they always say you don't have to be a great chef to like, you know, know if food tastes good or whatever
Uh, yeah, I mean
I don't know too much about Ralph the movie maker if two people make you good videos
So if two and biased, I guess
I've seen a couple Ralph the movie maker videos and I guess they're fine
Um, if two people each make a shitty movie and then they each point to each other's shitty movie and they're like that movie sucks
I guess they're both right
Yeah, they can both be right
Uh
Yeah
I don't know
Seems like linkara doesn't really
Criticize people a lot seems like linkara takes it personally
When like other internet people like say his stuff is bad and he like doesn't really do that he like
Gets pissy and like complains about other people who are like too critical seems to be
His thing but so which is which is okay. I mean it seems like he he doesn't dish it
Because he can't take it which is fair enough. Honestly, it's valid. It's perfectly valid
um
Okay
Yeah, I don't know. I haven't seen any of these movies. So I don't fucking know
um
Next voicemail is called ppr
pcp public radio
three two one go
From member station wflg. I'm sydney norman with your weekly roundup
This week's story the trial for kyle written house continued with an explosive day on wednesday as written house took the stand for cross examination
Written house began crying during his testimony describing how he improperly used a weapon
He intentionally brought with him to a volatile situation and the community is not a part of
This prompted judge bruce schroeder to admonish prosecuting attorney thomas binger for asking written house questions
Judge schroeder then called a recess and told written house to use quote bruce's big brave boy
And that written house earned an extra hour tv time that night
It wasn't long after the court had returned from recess that judge schroeder threatened to hold binger in contempt for referring to the individuals
Their in-house shot has people
Bitcoin up 4 3 i'm up 2 xrp up 2 this is bpr
Another another beautiful day in the neighborhood
Yeah, yeah, this is what i'm talking about
That was that was half factual and the part that wasn't factual was just was just extrapolating from the existing facts of the case
Uh, that's pretty much how it how it is
uh
bummer
Okay, next voicemail is called it's true
3 2 1 go
Shred it
Shred it what
Shred it raped my dog
What is that what they're saying? I think he's saying shredded raped my dog
Oh, yeah, I guess that they might be saying that
Uh, I guess it's true because they put four exclamation points. Yeah, that's what
That's what convinced me
Um next one is called
Okay, there's no voicemail. It's just called. Why is the header of the pcp website so
enormous
And the answer like that
I don't think that's true. The answer is that it's just like a default template and that's how big the template's header was
Uh
Yeah, we have a picture of a cactus
We have a picture of a succulent on our website because by the way
Okay, we got to change the the the description of the episodes because apparently the the episode descriptions still link to the like the um
the mp3
Like google drive folder, which is no longer updated if you want the episode mp3 is you got to go to the website now
The episode mp3s are all available on the website. That is where we upload them now. So we should change the description
Change there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
um
Okay, that's uh, that's that uh, next
Uh, one is called good morning
three two one go
I love you guys so much you guys. Uh, thanks, man
For years, I love you guys. We've been podcasting for years. My my my buddies
My part of social buddies. I love you. I hope you're a blessing a blessed Sunday
um happiness
health to your families
and to yourselves
um
Ben, I would like to know your thoughts on infinitely just in in the fossil walls
I know you comment about them before the podcast. I remember that and I know it's it's a comic, but I
I don't remember
The details or what you actually think about the the book and the fossil was I have the book in my hands right now
Um, kisses. I love you guys
The um, I have only I haven't read that much David Foster walls. I've read infinite jest and I've read um
One or two of his articles
Or his short stories rather like I read um
I think it's called like
A very fun thing. I'll never do again the one where he goes on the cruise ship
Uh, that one's kind of good
It's cool. I guess
um infinite jest
Oh, I've seen I've seen the movie
based on uh
Is it called um portraits of hideous men?
I haven't read that story, but I've I've I've seen the movie based on it and I
Thought it was all right
The infinite jest book is really long
It's probably too long
It it drags it points it took me like a whole year to read it
uh the the like
The thing with like the footnotes and like the huge indexes at the end is very it's pretty annoying actually like having to flip
Having to keep two bookmarks and like flip back and forth through
The whole book is very irritating. It doesn't I don't like it, but it is what it is
Uh, but like there's scenes from the book that I remember
Years later that I that I have retained and I found
Interesting, so I guess
I guess it was worth reading because it left me with
impressions
So would I recommend it?
Yeah, uh
What what else can I say it's uh it had interesting ideas in it even if it was pretty bloated
Oh, okay, uh next next voicemail is called ben saint
I don't know how to
I don't know how to speak french
three two one go
My accent is brazilian. You guys have uh, ben you have come down my accent one or two times. It's it's brazilian. I'm from brazil
I I thought it was south american, so I was in the right ballpark
um
Next
This reminds me in a in a mental game of telephone. I just played as my neurons were reaching out and touching each other and wriggling around
Uh, that reminds me that one of my roommates is brazilian
Which reminds me of one of my other roommates who I have never even barely talked to
Who I heard this week listening to tim pool
in the fucking kitchen
And tim pool was going on some unhinged, uh, kyle riddenhouse shit
And I just want to say
It makes me really mad and I hate that guy
Uh, that's all
I have to say about that. Oh
Oh, the the thing the title of that
Translates to I will eat your ass
If you come as sick. Oh
Yeah, that sounds
Oh, that must be portuguese then portuguese. Yes. Yeah, well
Because actually
Which is basically just which is basically just a mix of french and spanish as far as as far as I'm concerned
And I don't care to learn
Any more about it that might prove that wrong
Uh, it's spanish adjacent literally. I mean, yeah next one is an imjer link
Okay, I like this one roll video
I'm Trixie. This is a Trixie Trixie's crunchy roll video getting 10k views. Oh man
I like that they use the uh
The the toothless thumbnail
Yeah, Trixie's a crunchy roll video did did pretty good like for modern day Trixie, which is to say that it cracked 10k views
Whoo
Yeah, wow
Um
That was her that was her big sir her her big her
Her big shot the big the big move there is like mining old digi
Stuff for like new
Takes about it referencing and uh
And uh remixing and regurgitating. It's sort of worked a little bit
Um good for her I guess
The next one is uh, oh man, this is doing numbers
Next one is called nnn week three
three two one go
We're going on two weeks now and I gotta admit I did struggle a bit this week
I was on twitter checking out the latest benzane tweet when I saw a natweet on my timeline
Saying he was about to start streaming on twitch
My mouse hovered over the link for an uncomfortable amount of time before I worked up the courage to do something
That would have seemed impossible years ago
I unfollowed nate anyone who takes no nate november seriously should probably do the same
Unfollow and unsubscribe from nate
Stay strong no nate nation if and as always no nate. Yes watch if you if you are playing with fire
If you're still following nate if if you are serious about no nate november if you're serious about no nate november I would have to agree
Being subscribed and following is is definitely yeah playing with fire
There's uh, there's no there's no question there. Hey man, stay strong
You know, I know it's rough. It's tough out there for a no nater
um
But uh, we're in we're all in this together
Uh, we here we have committed to a no nate during november
Lifestyle here. We are we are an eight free zone
Uh for november and uh, perhaps ever, uh, we will see
Next voicemail and this is the last voicemail
Mercifully is called giraffe titty
three two one go
Shut up then. Just shut shut it shut up
Okay, okay. Sorry
Well, I guess I will because the podcast is over so
Yeah, was this in reference to my first sona?
Uh, oh, yeah, I did I your giraffe sona I
Do I don't think I mean I don't think so
What would be the connection there?
The giraffe has titties
I would have thought
Okay, it would be about that. But maybe yeah, I would I would have thought so too
But it's just a guy telling me to shut up
So, well, I don't know man
I don't get it. I don't get it
Duh
I guess one thing I didn't mention is those little
Hands drawn oh like mouse drawn commissions. I did
I've stopped doing them because I don't like having responsibilities of any kind. Um, yeah, absolutely pretty cool
People like those these cute little little things go to twitter.com find my twitter. It's the best one. It's the only good one
Yeah, find it find it somewhere in there. Just find it. Just not gonna tell you where
It's the needle in a haystack, but when I'm gonna let leave it up to you to find it
So that when you do you'll have more satisfaction
You'll get you really get a get that dope of me and you go. Yes. I get it
I love uh games that have exploration and what better way to exemplify that love
Than to just tell you to look for it idiot. I have um
I haven't played noida in like a while. I think I just I've
I've basically quit noida
Well, honestly good. I played way too much of it played way too much of that fucking game
But it's probably it's probably good that I'm that I haven't played it in a while. It's it's good. Um, it's good. I'm free. I'm free
um
uh
I guess that's it. Uh, is there any anything else you want to talk about before we wrap up?
Go to patreon.com slash gibbentake if you want to know about my secret project. That's true. I reveal it
I have it. Oh, I haven't listened to it yet next month. I haven't listened to it yet
But uh, I'm gonna I'm gonna because I want to hear that I'll I'll be I'll get into a lot more specifics next month because uh
When I first made that like oh, this is what I'm working on
It was the beginning
Or like at the end of last month and I hadn't yet
Got a lot of work done but now
Now that it's fresh in my mind and I've been working on it the last few weeks
Um, there's more to say so the end of this month. Hmm. Yeah, you should patron and then I will explain a lot more
I'll get into the details
Uh, um
I will plug
Anamorphon time again. Maybe by the time this comes out the episode with bob dis guy I will be on and I will be eagerly awaiting
hearing them say patreon.com slash ben saint
And who knows how many other wacky things?
Uh over there
Funny stuff
um, that's it
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Get our bonus episodes hear that juicy drama learn some fun facts
Find out what to do if somebody calls you a gay wizard
Uh
I guess that's it
Good on speakpipe.com. Oh, right. Uh, if you want to send a voicemail
Uh, the link in the description
Naturally, naturally
All right, that's that's the episode. Um, see you next week everybody. Good night
God speed and
Peace get fucked. Oh that no, no, no