I won't bless that guy. That son of a-
That son of a-
Son of a-
Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Crastinators, ah, I thought you wanted me to do that.
The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The Pro Crastinators Podcast, I'm Ben Saint.
The Pro, ah, Crastinators Podcast.
Ben St. and Gibb and Tate are here after a one week hiatus.
Was there a week hiatus?
Well, there was a week between the last time we recorded and.
Oh, I see.
The usual week, one week hiatus.
This is zero second hiatus.
We weren't we weren't gone.
Well, we were recording.
We're just on schedule.
Well, we're recording a day late because you were traveling or something.
I was sleepy is that's the truth.
That's the whole that's the whole thing.
No, that's all there is to it.
I was coming home from camp and so we could record the normal time.
Was it and it was going to be a later recording.
But then I was like, was it the gunnery?
It wasn't a gunnery.
That's a summer camp.
It was just we have a Christmas camp as well.
A Christmas camp, which we just call Christmas camp.
It's just like in December get a, you know, everyone has a good old Christmas fun.
There's some activities and a Christmas dinner on the last day.
It's really just a stay for a night thing in like cabin somewhere.
Yeah.
OK, OK, like a family thing.
I know the it's the scout group.
Oh, yeah.
That I volunteer at.
So it's the same like general scout sort of stuff.
Yeah, help out with the other mentally disabled children.
And I make sure that they don't, you know, do anything fucking stupid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Definitely, definitely.
I make sure they have a lovely time, but it was very fucking tiring
because there was a there was a kid who is very hyper
and needs constant supervision.
So I needed to do a lot of that.
And by the time I got back, I was like, fuck, I don't want to do a fucking podcast.
No, no.
OK, that makes that makes sense.
OK, I see. Yeah, I didn't know what you were up to.
I just knew you had come back from somewhere.
Yeah, cool, cool, cool.
Oh, I finished your lecture.
I actually got to the end.
Yeah, how well, I mean, I hope you had a good time.
Hope you enjoyed learning about.
Yeah, stuff.
My favorite thing is is the connections from previous characters,
like the fact that, you know, everything's so connected.
Even though the generally the law is
or the story of each game is you're a little guy
and you've got to stop a certain number of similar guys that have different powers.
Yeah, go get them.
And like, that's every single game, but the story and the law is like
it keeps expanding on itself.
Yeah, I do like how like it goes from like there are humans
and they build robots and then there's the whole thing with the reploids
and then the carbons at the end.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, the what would happen if what would happen
if robots became so smart?
The the thing the thing about the carbons is that
because they were made like first.
So it's really it's really kind of tenuous to draw the connection.
You can kind of see it if you if you take a step back and look at the whole thing,
you can kind of see that they were doing something.
I hear people talk about the end of ZX Advent and be like, oh, well,
yeah, I think, you know, maybe.
Oh, all those like human body parts and the immortal reploid DNA
that he says he's got like somewhere in a vault somewhere.
Like maybe he used those to like build the first prototype
and throw units, which became the carbons.
And it's like, yeah, yeah, maybe.
Yeah, it's possibly.
But like, you know, who really knows?
Because like, yeah, the legends is like XXX DX.
Legends is way, way, way more than 9000 the year, 9999.
It could be. It could be.
But. Yeah, it was all.
But it was also made like before it was made before zero.
It was made before into creates started like zero and ZX.
So basically, Capcom told them like, yeah, OK, here's Mega Man X.
This is the the canon.
And then here's legends.
And we've decided that legends takes place in the future.
And we didn't think about it any further than that.
So just go wild.
And they were like into creates just kind of had to be like,
well, how can we how can we?
How can we establish some connections between these two things?
And they they did an admirable job.
And I think people are probably onto something with that thing
about like Thomas Thomas's threat at the end of ZX Advent
being related to the prototype and through a unit project.
That seems like it makes a lot of sense, but it is ultimately speculation.
Yeah, that's just I wish we got ZXC wish we got wish we got Legends three.
Yeah, hearing from Twitch last week about the the the the the fall of Inafune
was really it's really depressing.
It's even it just gets more depressing the more I learn about it.
Yeah, I I mean.
I like what is Mega Man currently?
What is a Mega Man?
A mega pile of secret, a mega pile of mega lore.
A pile of scrap serotonium.
Like he he was fired or I forget.
But like basically fired from Capcom.
Yeah, for his for his for his cheeky monkey behavior
of of of of getting games made that are successful.
And they didn't like that.
But now what is the IP of Mega Man doing?
Has there been a game since he left or yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sitting on it.
Well, yes.
After he left, which I think was in around was it around like 2008,
2010, something like that?
Because that was when all the projects started getting canceled.
Yeah, there was.
I think after he left, they they did Mega Man not
well, nine and 10 and 11 have all come out in like not recently.
But like, I think those are all post in a Fune.
At least 11 is post in a Fune, for sure.
OK.
That has.
Has it been 12 years since Mega Man 10?
What the fuck?
I remember Mega Man like being talked about on YouTube early on,
because like everyone likes Mega Man.
I never heard about it before.
I saw lots of like videos that YouTube music.
You'd never you'd never heard about it?
Never heard.
Well, maybe I'd seen him in like a gaming magazine,
but I didn't have an NES or any of that.
Oh, yeah. OK. Yeah.
I was I was growing up in the time where like Ray Man was the hot shit
and Tomb Raider was all over the place.
That's I mean, I had.
I had I had a like computer.
I had like a PC demo disc that had a bunch of game demos on them.
And I had a demo for Ray Man, I think the first Ray Man.
And it ran really badly on that computer.
So I thought Ray Man's.
Oh, yeah. Sucked ass because it was like at like 15 frames per second.
The PC port of Ray Man.
I don't know if it was a bad port, but I remember trying to play that
on a really shitty laptop and it just wasn't very good.
It was OK.
But, you know, I tried to play it and I played it a bit
and it was quite hard and the frame rate was bad.
And I think I don't know if I ever beat the demo or if I just gave up on it.
I think there were other games that I liked more.
But yeah, I remember Mega Man 10 or 9.
What was the newest like the old it was it was newly made,
but looks like an NES game. That was well, that was 9 and 10.
Yeah. So I remember that those coming out and being everyone being like,
oh, my God, they're doing it. Yeah.
But it's old fashioned.
I'm like, who's Mega Man?
And they said, shut the fuck up, get out of here, get out the fuck out of our forum.
You idiot. Mm hmm.
They were right. They were right to say it.
Or wait, no, eight. Eight was the one.
Eight was in. Eight was in 97 or 96.
Oh, my God. And then nine was in nine was the first retro one
or the first recent retro one in 2008, 14 years ago.
So not that recent.
And then 10 was in, I think it was in 2010.
And then they didn't do it for like literally 10 years.
These yeah, 10 was in 2010 and 11.
No, 11 was in 2018.
They went eight years without a new Mega Man game.
And then they went and they've gone another
they've gone another four or five years since then or four.
Oh, yeah, four years.
But apparently there is and I heard this in my discord.
Apparently there is internal documents talking about something
that is internally referred to by something called,
and I hope I remember this correctly.
I think it was called like Mega Man, Tensai.
And that's not an official name.
It's just an internal name for something.
But apparently whatever it is has the biggest budget
of any Mega Man game ever made.
So something is being worked on, which is very.
Omega Man, it's a new Mega Man.
And he's going to be Omega and Oh, zero.
I'm thinking of another thing for zero equivalent.
Well, you know, I mean, there is Omega.
Oh, I didn't know.
You will you fail the let you.
This is a test that you failed.
You got to watch the lecture again.
Do you? Yeah.
When, when, you know, when Dr.
Vile, when Dr.
Vile, you know, stole zero's body and turned it into Omega
as part of the Alpezo project, Project Alpezo.
I forgot he called it Omega.
Was that? Wait, what was the what was the zero
that was like a empty shell like it was just the body
and the soul was somewhere else?
Yes, that's Omega. That's Omega.
It's it's not it's not empty.
It has like a soul, but it's just evil.
It might be like zero's original personality,
or it might just be like a different entity.
So it's unclear.
OK.
But yeah, that's Omega law instead.
It's it's got to be I feel like it's got to be either
Mega Man 11 or sorry, Mega Man 12 or Mega Man X nine.
Why would Mega Man 12?
It's such a huge budget, though.
Well, it would be an NES style.
Well, it wouldn't because I mean, you know,
Mega Man 11 is not in the NES.
Oh, Mega Man 11 is like.
They they they might have you not see Mega Man 11.
No, it's like it's 3D.
It's kind of got a new it's pretty modern looking.
I assumed all the new classic Mega Man entries were throwbacks.
No, nine and 10 were.
But 11 was they sort of modernized it.
And, you know, if you don't know,
just like I think we said this on the show,
like a month ago, Mega Man 11 became the best selling Mega Man ever
for basically the series entire history.
Mega Man two was the best selling Mega Man ever.
No other entry ever eclipsed it.
And then 11 just did, which is like a huge deal.
So it doesn't it doesn't I mean, from a business perspective,
it's not that shocking if they're like, well, we got to do another one.
And I think it's got to be it's just got to be 12, right?
Like it's got to be 12 or maybe X nine.
Because like, yeah, you know, the market has shown that the demand is there.
Yeah, I wonder because like all the
like not spin-offs, but like new parts of the the franchise,
the X, the zero ZX legends, they're like
they're more lore heavy than the classic one,
which is just sort of a monster of the week kind of, you know,
while he's back at it again, beat him up pretty much.
More like like, you know, Fune would not be needed
for a classic Mega Man.
I mean, as much not that they necessarily need him at all.
But like, yeah, I think they wanted to follow on like the story that he'd written.
Oh, yeah. You know, there were there's making an X game would be difficult
without any input from him.
I mean, I don't know if into creates is still working for Capcom,
but like if they could get if they could get into creates to just do
to do whatever game they're doing next,
I feel like that's that's going to work just fine,
because they made a bunch of really good a bunch of really good Mega Man games.
And yeah, I don't I mean, they made I think they made nine and 10 and 11
without Inafune, I think so.
Yeah, that's it's doable.
That's doable.
Well, I mean, I'm hoping that whenever whatever that big project
is that's being worked on internally, it'd be cool if it comes out
and it would be even cooler if it gives my video a big algorithm boost.
And everyone's like, oh, my God, X nine is here.
I can't believe it.
We can revisit my favorite character, Axel.
Finally, we can return we can return to a trans what we can once again
step into Axel's shoes and a trans our enemies.
Yes, finally, there should be
a new character called Falsetto.
And she's a she's a she's a woman.
Falsetto feels.
That's like a base counterpart base and Falsetto base should come back.
Base I don't know.
Base should come.
Genuinely, base should have been in Mega Man 11.
And I don't know why he wasn't in it.
He wasn't even in deals.
It's actually kind of fucked up that base is nowhere in Mega Man 11.
You get Proto Man, get base, you get Quint, you get zero.
You get everyone who isn't Mega Man likes all of the shadow of the Hedgehog
characters, put them all together in one game.
Oh, and Proto Man and Proto Man was not in 11 either.
This is so fucked up.
What were they thinking?
Games, games, trash, games, trash, trash, trash.
Um, yeah, if I play a Mega Man game, I will probably.
Well, I don't know, would you say I should start with zero because
they're a that's a good, like self-contained series.
That's the impression I got.
They are good.
They're really hard.
They're some of the hardest games in the whole series.
If I'm being if I'm being frank with you.
Dang.
Yeah, I think I think it's generally agreed that those are like.
Some of the some of the classic ones might be equally hard, just basically out
of like poor balancing, the zero games are like hard on purpose.
I'll be I'll be frank.
I used I use save states.
I use quite a bit in my in my revisit of the series because I just didn't want
to replay levels over and over again to get that.
Truly the most valid way to play games that suck if you don't.
Absolutely, absolutely.
Games, I already beat the level.
I beat the level.
Get out of my get off my case.
The the it's so weird.
OK, Mega Man Zero has this scoring system that gives you a rank.
I don't know if we mentioned this in the lecture, but it's really funny.
It has a scoring system that gives you a rank and it gives you a code name
based on a combination of your rank and on like certain metrics.
Like if you kill lots of enemies, it gives you you get one code name.
If you heavily favor one weapon or another weapon, it gives you a different
code name and they can give you some really funny ones like like a wounded
edge boy or or or stuff like that.
But it also like punishes you for like playing the game.
Like if you use cyber elves, it's it's really hard.
It's really hard to like get cyber elves.
You have to feed them crystals and they're very expensive and they don't do that much.
Like they're pretty minor buffs, except for the really expensive ones.
So but if you use cyber elves, it like hurts your rank.
And it's the game just like don't you don't use the mechanic that we've made
gave you to make the game easier.
And in and in zero two, it's really annoying because, OK,
zero two actually has a sort of Mega Man
ask like you gain the enemy's weapon when you kill the the boss.
Like there are a bunch of like alternate attack modes that zero can unlock.
But you only unlock them if you beat the level with an A rank or better,
like an A or S rank.
And your rank is cumulative.
So if you like start out doing bad, like if you get a C rank on the first
on the first level, if you or if you get ranked badly on the first level,
like even if you do better on the next level, because rank is cumulative,
you still won't get the level because it'll average your your ranks out.
And it'll be like, oh, well, you did an A rank on this level,
but because you had C before it averages out to a B.
So sorry, you don't get the enemy weapon.
So you go the whole game with a shitty rank
and you don't get get any of the alternate fire or like special weapons at all.
And the game sucks.
Game is fucking asked and it's dog.
Can you not can you not go back?
Is there no and you can't go back?
No, you can't go back.
You you can return back to the level,
but it doesn't give you like a new like rank because it's not like a mission
because like there's no boss at the end.
It's just you just walk around the level and like find items if you want to.
Oh, so that's the sort of game where like.
Like if you're doing badly, you just die and game over.
I mean, it's perfectly it's perfectly none of the alternate
like fire modes or the alternate attack modes are like game breaking
or like that much better than the regular one.
So it's not like it cripples you and makes the game really hard.
If you don't get them, it's just lame that.
It's just lame that you don't get them unless you meet this
like very specific and somewhat arbitrary thing.
You should just fucking get them for beating the bosses.
I'm sorry.
But it's it's it's perfectly it's perfectly doable to beat the game
without that stuff, but they are they are helpful.
Sometimes. Yeah, see ranking and scores.
I usually I'm like, yeah, whatever, I'm going to get a low score.
I'm going to get a low.
Oh, yeah, because I suck.
No, yeah, but but if I when I was doing when I was doing
actually important, I did not give a shit.
I did not give a shit about the rank, which was fine, except in zero,
two, which for some reason, gates like these fun little things
behind your stupid rank.
You're not allowed to have fun unless you have pain first.
You're not allowed to have fun.
You're not allowed to have fun unless you're a supreme edge man.
No wounded edge boys allowed.
Only supreme edge men can answer the secret clubhouse.
Uh.
And then three is the perfect video game.
And then four is almost as good, except it's really weird
and they give you a stupid special weapon that sucks.
But the game is like, no, it insists that it's good, even though it's bad.
OK, I'm I'm I'm realizing now that like your lecture on the lore of Megman
has almost nothing to do with the enjoyment found in the game.
Although you did talk me into playing legends at some point.
So I will try that.
Oh, you definitely sound fun.
You definitely should. You definitely should play legends.
I did. Yeah, I didn't really. Yeah.
I mean, as the as the title says, yeah, it's about it's lore.
It's lore focused.
Didn't really talk about the mechanics of the game, except to complain
about Axel's a trans and how it doesn't do anything.
There's no point.
There's no freaking point, man.
Does Axel have a little buddy called Grease?
Unfortunately, no.
Also, it's spelled AXL.
It's not spelled AXEL.
Because he's too cool. He's too cool for vowels.
He's actually not the game.
The game doesn't treat him like he's super cool.
The game mostly treats him like he's a a spunky brat.
So, I don't know, whatever.
Well, uh, well, hey, hell, yeah, glad you watched that.
You know, who else watched that?
Hundreds of thousands of people, two hundred and fifty,
a quarter million other people.
It just it just last night, it hit a quarter million
and it has officially it has surpassed
Kokoro Wish and Sonichu 102 and become my third most viewed video
passed after, you know, Sonichu 101 and Tales Get Strolled.
So. Good job.
It's great. It's amazing. Yeah, thank you.
I wonder if it will.
I wonder if it will eventually surpass Tales Get Strolled.
Maybe. Maybe if it gets a big.
It could. I mean, I'll go boost at some point.
I've seen people who are just like excited to see a long video.
So I feel like people would more likely click on an eight hour
big obsessive video game thing.
You know, I was looking at my metrics and I saw,
you know, how it shows you like views per.
You can see that you can see how many views it's gotten per hour
for the last 48 hours. Yeah.
Well, I was looking at that and I noticed that like a lot on several times,
there's like a spike in views around like seven PM, eight PM.
And I and I wonder if that's like, oh, this is these are the people
that like use these videos to go to sleep.
That's great. It might be.
It might be.
I don't have I might have said this already, but I don't get it.
I don't really get I can't I can't use videos of someone talking to go to sleep.
It doesn't work for me.
But people say that they do that.
So, you know, I think that might be those people.
Sometimes when I'm in bed and I've got my phone,
I'll be clicking on YouTube videos, not necessarily looking for something
to make me fall asleep, but I end up being sleepy.
And then I'm like, oh, shit.
I wasn't paying attention to any of the last like minute.
I should turn this off.
And that's how I know when I should go to bed.
But go to sleep, actually, you know, I said in the video,
like leave a comment and I'll try to answer questions.
But there's like so many comments
that I mentioned that like the video's comment ratio is really high.
Like it's it's it's my most common.
It quickly became my it's my second most commented video.
And it's it's it's definitely going to get more comments
eventually than the than the Son of Chew lecture.
Like people just can't stop commenting on this thing,
which is which is probably doing a lot for it algorithmically, which is nice.
So I I've tried to answer like some I've responded to some.
But like.
They just keep coming and they don't stop coming, you know.
Do you have metrics for how long the average
like view like watch time is?
Yeah, where do people leave if they leave?
I assume most people like the majority would stay for the whole thing.
But just in chunks, I think it's actually.
It's actually, I think.
I think people actually like tend to click off it pretty fast.
Like I think I think the I think like I think the watch time drops off
like really fast, like at the beginning, which is a bit.
Sounds bad, but I mean, I think I think it's it's mostly because you you
lead with the talk of lectures and the PCP and hey, guys, well, you know, well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, look, I'll show I'll show you the graph.
Oh, shit, insider info.
Oh, these are you can post it on screen if you want.
You can we can we can public this private insider info if you want.
It's fine.
Where is it? Here we go.
Yeah, as as you can see, there is a big I mean, every video is like this to some extent.
There is a big drop off right at the very beginning.
You know, it quickly it quickly falls to like 20 percent or so.
And then it actually recovers a little bit.
And I'm pretty sure that's people taking my recommendation and clicking
the like skip ahead to where the actual game discussion starts.
You know.
So there's like a 40 percent drop off of all people.
I did.
So do you know how if those people leave very quickly, if they're counted as views?
Or is that information?
I think they are.
I think they are because I know that views are separate from unique viewers
because I know that the video has around 100,000 unique viewers.
So.
Yeah, I think I think that one account
revisiting the same video multiple times does count as multiple views.
I I think I would imagine so.
Yeah, pretty pretty sure.
Well, let's let me let me show you.
OK, here's the similar metric for the Kokoro wish lecture.
Just to give a side by side comparison.
I know I've definitely done that thing where I'm like scrolling through
videos and like I click on something thinking, yeah, this might be interesting.
And as soon as it's finished loading, I'm like, actually, I don't want to and I leave.
I'm pretty sure that doesn't count as a view because it's like half a second.
But who knows?
I'm I'm looking at that.
OK, the stupid stupid discord is taking a second to process this image.
But looking at the Mega Man graph, I'm not sure what those like big spikes at the end are.
I, well, I'm curious about that as well.
But I did notice there's a bit where it could be that the people's favorite games
they want you to talk about and they click on that time code.
Who would that be?
Yeah, let me because I saw there was a part near the end half
where it's like most rewatched place, you know, the little bumpy line
that sometimes videos have where it's like, oh, this is the place
this is the place that people always click on to go see again.
It was near the end.
It could be the similar place six.
Let's see. The first bike is at 603.
Thirty one. OK.
So that's a little that's that first spike is around.
Or just or slightly after.
Mega Man zero fourth.
It's in the Mega Man zero four section. OK.
And then the second big spike is at 63311.
And that is at what am I talking about then?
Six thirty three.
That's just before I start talking about Mega Man X seven.
But it's not at the exact like time codes.
It's not the exact time when like you can click the little chapter starter
and it starts the chapter there.
So I'm not really sure.
Maybe they manually click on the time code area.
Like on the bar, an average, an average of people clicking around
the also spike.
Also, I have not looked at the.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, the the view like the viewer retention graph on the timeline is like,
yeah, it's big spikes like like huge spikes comparatively around.
Yeah, the trend, the end of Mega Man zero four and the start of Mega Man X seven.
OK. Or no, no, no, they love that they love it.
They want it, whatever it is.
It's no, it's it's X eight.
It's the start of X eight.
Why? It's not even at the very.
It's just kind of like towards the beginning slash middle part of X eight.
That's that's the the the money zone.
That's the the hotspot.
You know what they you know what the people want now.
It's the part where I'm talking about like rockets and the and the the orbital elevator.
Huh.
Weird, crazy.
Crazy.
Anyway, anyway, to the graph, yeah.
Like, look at this, the Kokura wish, like the Mega Man lecture.
OK, now on the one hand, like the numbers are stretched out.
So it might be a bit deceptive and you might it might be like.
OK, like, yeah, they both kind of drop off really quick at the beginning,
but the the the Mega Man drops off much faster.
But actually, it's like kind of eight times slower than that
because the video is so much longer.
But yeah, the Kokura wish like quickly drops to about 33 percent.
And then there's that little kind of dip around the halfway mark.
And you know what that is?
What? That's the the part where I show the the little video,
like the game that she made, the little two zero and adventure game with the music.
How people skip through that?
I think I think people skip through that.
What was it called?
I'm pretty Halcyon.
Halcyon days. No, no.
What was wrong?
The pink girl, fuck, I'm blanking on what the pink girl's name is.
You know, the one spinel. No.
But she's got that name that means purple.
J.D.R. Pink Girl YouTube.
Help me. No, I mean, Google, help me.
Simply go to your own video.
No, I don't.
How?
No, what's the name?
I don't want.
All right, to give up.
Got to watch your own lecture.
I can't give the covid brain, the covid brain fog has come back.
No, this is the Mega Man thing.
You've you've filled it with Mega Man knowledge now.
Some other knowledge is gone.
Heliotrope, pastel defender heliotrope.
That's the one. Oh, you.
I know the name. I just haven't met the man.
Well, you were.
Yeah, you did.
Maybe you haven't rewatched that video because you were there.
And I haven't rewatched the video.
It's been a long time.
It's the pink hair.
With the comic either.
This the superhero girl.
That's like the puppet that the guy put the the glowing orb in.
Oh, yeah, the sex doll that became his daughter.
Based anyway.
Yeah, that's the there's there's a musical when it's not musical,
but there's a part where I play a like video sort of like
video game bit in the middle to show it off.
And yeah, people click through that.
And then, yeah, versus on this one,
it like immediately drops to like 20 percent or even down to 15 percent.
And then it recovers up to like 30 ish.
What's that first little spike in the Mega Man?
Oh, you mean not the one at the very beginning,
but like kind of a third in? Yeah, yeah.
And is that where you start talking about X or something?
Yeah, analytics tab.
That's at two hours and twenty two minutes.
So that is.
No, that's some that's in between when I'm talking about Mega Man X
and Mega Man to the power fighters.
No, sorry, Mega Man seven.
But between Mega Man seven and Mega Man to the power fighters.
Yeah, I don't know why there's a spike there.
It's very strange.
Oh, speaking of why, it's not really much to say,
but like Mega Man knowledge has made me like, oh,
I remember when Game Grumps played Mega Man seven,
that was like the first game they played and I go back.
And it's like, oh, I remember this. This was good.
Why is this not a thing anymore? Dang it.
Mega Man's happening and they're just chilling out and joking.
Were they playing Mega Man seven, you said? Was that the one?
Yeah, it's like got the guy with the big chin robot.
Guts, man, all thing.
Not Guts, man, the the guy who sells stuff.
Oh, auto. Yeah, I recognize him in the lecture
when you play to demand. It's like, wait, I know that guy.
That's from Game Grumps.
That's the guy in the Game Grumps play through.
There's, oh, you know, it's like,
oh, Protoman told you to burn the trees in the forest.
And there was that whole bit.
They did seven asses is from that game.
Do you remember seven asses?
Do you ever watch?
Wait, you watch Game Grumps at the time?
I I've definitely heard seven asses before.
Yeah, it was it was a moment in the Mega Man seven that I didn't
realize at the time, but I'd since realized that
like John was playing and Aaron was looking up
which tree to burn to get a specific item.
Yes.
But they didn't want to say they were like looking at a walkthrough.
So John said, how much ass do you think Mega Man gets?
And Aaron says seven.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, seven asses.
And it's the seventh tree, I guess.
I might have watched that video because I definitely remember that
or I might have seen it in a clip compilation or something.
But OK, the thing about auto and I'm hazyly remembering this,
I might get some details wrong.
But I think it's in Mega Man.
I think it's it might be in the one with cutscenes or it might be in.
No, it's in it's I think it's in one of the X games.
It might be an X for there's like an anime cutscene
and you can see auto in one of the cutscenes.
And it's and it's like auto is like cannon in in X.
But only in a cutscene and it's and it's like an Easter egg.
But he's there.
And it's a little wacky.
Hang on.
More like auto erotic
asphyxiation, am I right?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Very good.
He just chokes you.
And that's what that's that's how that's the game.
Oh, no, no, no, he has.
Auto has a small cameo in Volt Catfish's introduction scene
in the PlayStation Sega Saturn PC and Mega Man X collection versions of Mega Man X3.
Oh, it's in like a re-release.
It's in like an additional cut an additional cutscene
attitude to a re-release of X3.
He's like he's like sitting in the background.
He's like sitting in like a in like a Japanese style house,
like sitting on the tatami mats, watching TV or something.
And then Volt Catfish like swoops out in front and goes like,
die, Volt Catfish, die.
OK, that's debatably canon.
The fact that it's a remake makes me mistrustful.
Remake, more like P make.
I I urinate on this game.
I love when my video gets views and I love money and power.
I love clout.
This is just what Dr. Wiley would say.
Yeah, well.
What of it?
Maybe he had some maybe he would maybe he had some points after all.
But what would you say would say?
I love Dr. Wiley.
There's some things I love about Dr. Wiley.
He made some good points.
You know, he was just looking out for his for his robots.
You know, he made some mistakes, but haven't we all?
You know, I'm just thinking of like of like a YouTube version of Mega Man,
where like Dr. Light is a YouTuber and Dr. Wiley re re uploads the video,
but he changes it, changes it to make it evil.
I'm thinking about I'm thinking about a future because like we're getting on
towards 20 X DX already.
I'm thinking about a future where like Dr.
Light and Dr. Wiley are like guests on the Joe Rogan podcast,
like arguing about like whether I don't know,
like whether the double gear system is like the future of robotics or something.
You're thinking of using two gears.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What we don't like is like, you know, the the human, you know, a police human,
the robot police, the robots, the police are using now are too dangerous.
They they kill indiscriminately.
You know, we've got to we've got to build robots that can that can make
moral judgment.
We've got to advance AI to the point that they can they have human intelligence.
They can make moral judgment or something.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, Dr. Wiley, let me go back to you.
Let me go back to where you were saying you.
You're saying you want to add a second gear.
You're talking. You're saying you had two gears, though.
That blows my mind that I've seen one gear.
One gear I've seen before this little this little what do you call
the the Boston Dynamics dog?
There's a really I know that was a really weak Joe Rogan impression.
I'm sorry. I'm not that familiar with the man's work.
He just sort of is a big guy.
And he mumbles, isn't that the truth?
I yeah, there's not really like anything that distinct about the way he talks.
It's it's mostly his mic quality.
It's like the radio voice, like the the ASMR deep guy.
And he's just sort of like, wow, wow.
Yeah.
Oh, this is it.
Yeah, that's really that's really important.
That sounds like it sounds like your team is doing really important work.
Hey, you guys ever try DMZ?
You got you guys ever take mushrooms?
I don't know. That's my best.
That's my best. That's my best impression.
Dr. Light would make the little Boston Dynamics robot to like,
oh, it's stack books on shelves.
Isn't he a good boy?
Isn't he a good dog?
Mm hmm. Yeah, pretty good dog.
And then Dr.
Wiley would make it pee on and take a shit all over the floor.
I've added we've added poop and pee technology
to bring to bring humans and robots closer to get closer than ever.
Uh, Dr.
Master Thomas at the end of Mega Man ZX
ZX Advent, hmm, Master Mikhail, you know, we've since the equality laws,
humans and robots, you know, we for equality, humans no longer poop and pee.
But what do you think we did with all that poop and pee, huh?
What do you think?
Do you think we just knew we were going to use it for something?
We're going to use all that poop and pee.
It didn't just go away.
We saved it. We saved it.
It's the future, Master Mikhail.
Oh, no, what do you think we did with all the poop and pee?
We've condensed it into a new material that we can use to make new robots.
Robots made of poop and pee.
We call them.
We call we would use to build who build Elysium.
This is the future.
Uh, uh.
Diarrhea.
Lol. OK.
Hey, Lois. Diarrhea.
Hey, Wiley. What? Diarrhea.
Mega Man has infinite possibilities.
And this is what we choose.
That's why his name is X. That's why his name is X.
He doesn't have a code number.
He doesn't have a Wiley number.
He has the variable X because he can be anything.
Give. Do you understand?
Do you understand?
Could there not be a Mega Man Y?
I.
I guess, you know, there's a there's a in like the toy line.
There is a, you know, you know how in Kingdom Hearts, right?
There's there's there's key like the key blade.
Some key blade.
Some some say Kai, but the meaning is the same.
Yeah.
And, you know, well, there's there's a there's like a dark evil X called
called Kai. Mega Man Ki.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, some say key, but the meaning is the same.
Mega Man Eeks.
What's his? He has a slightly more long name than that.
Magnificent man.
He's like a dark copy of X and he's like gold and black.
Metal X.
Wait a minute. OK, there's also.
Oh, God, fucking damn it.
In the cards in in like the in the Mega Man in the Rockman X Mega Mission
like card series, there's one called how the fuck do you pronounce this?
OK, all right.
So X, his name in Japanese is pronounced X, right?
Like it's just the Japaneseization of the pronunciation of the letters X.
Well, this guy is called what the fuck?
This guy is called Iksu and it's spelled like this.
It's spelled like this.
Eeks.
So this guy is from the card and he's an evil doppelganger of X,
right? And then there's OK.
Well, I you could read that as nine because of the Roman numeral.
I think that would be going against the wishes of the of the Greek.
And then there's this guy who is from the toy series.
And this guy, OK, in spite of the way his name is spelled,
his name is just pronounced Kai.
It's not pronounced X, Kai or key, Kai.
It's just Kai.
But you spell it like that as though you're meant to say it twice.
Kai, Kai.
And this guy is he's not a doppelganger.
He's a prototype copy.
He's a prototype copy of the original game.
So he maybe he's related to copy X.
From the other more fucking Mega Man
and then there are Pokemon like so many of these guys.
No, there's not a thousand.
There's not a thousand different Mavericks or Reploids.
I'm going to have to say probably not.
I mean, I guess there are lots of like generic background.
Reploids.
So like all of the ones, all of the ones in the lecture
is just the ones in the video games.
But then there's the I guess a card game and like the comics.
And yeah, most of those are most of those are repeats, though.
Most characters and Mavericks like reoccur in the different,
you know, cards and games and stuff.
Each each each version has like a few new
dudes, a few new a few new dudes.
And I guess they're all I guess they were all the sub bosses.
Like, you know, there's like the the block Golem.
I wonder if you added up like all the different.
I mean, if you added up all the different enemies,
there probably are more robots in Mega Man than there are Pokemon
because each Pokemon is like a little bit more robustly fleshed out
than a rank and file enemy in the Mega Man series.
Like a little propeller with eyes from Mega Man.
Yeah, two or just a little met.
You know what a met is?
I don't even a metropolitan.
I don't even mention Mets.
Mets, Mets are the little guys in the classic Mega Man,
the little like black guys under the hard hat.
Oh, the little yeah, I like those guys.
Yeah, and they come in different like varieties sometimes.
They're just they're just little Mega Man goombas.
They're sometimes called Metals or Metars or Mets.
I think I think in English, they're usually just called Mets is what we've settled on.
And they're even in zero because there are cyber elves
that can transform regular enemies into Mets.
Just just because, just as a little cameo.
Hey, damn, there's so many things.
So many things to say.
Twitch was talking to Twitch a little bit in the server in the guest server.
And he said like, you know, he could just he could go on all day about Mega Man.
And like, there really is like there really is just no end of like facts
you could bring up and be like, did you know that in this one game,
some fucked up shit happens?
And you say, yes, of course, every game is like that.
I just I just assumed it is pretty cool.
Like just just the sheer quantity of little stories and characters and stuff.
Yeah, I like I like a really robust universe.
Yeah, it is pretty robust.
It's it's pretty robust and.
But it's just it's just it's it's it's a little annoying that like
I get I'm getting a lot of comments that are sort of specifically doing
the thing that I like didn't do, which is being like, oh, well, actually,
you know, this is the like X is the explanation for something in the games.
And it'll be like some fact that's like from the the manga or from like a cartoon
or from like a book or something.
And I'm like, kind of I kind of tried.
I mean, the mangas are specifically the mangas and the cartoons are specifically
an alternate canon.
The books, generally, I would say, probably are like legitimate canon.
Although they are mostly like.
Kind of after the fact is sort of a lot of it is retcon stuff, which is fine.
But like manga stuff is like doesn't it basically doesn't
count unless it's like something that's very strongly hinted at in the game.
And it's like reasonable to be like, this is probably what the game was trying to say.
And even then you kind of have to you kind of have to debate it.
I got a pee quick.
OK, back. OK.
I'm back.
Wahoo. Wow, we've been going for almost an hour.
Wow, that flew by.
I want to talk a little bit about something I mentioned last time briefly.
Yeah, the idea of going hibernating because it's cold and I just want to sleep.
I tried it out.
Well, I didn't really try it out.
It was just sort of.
Well, it the the idea is.
I'm done with like friendship ended with toil.
Now sleep is my best friend.
I just want to sleep for the whole rest of the year.
Makes sense.
I've realized that it's a little.
Like difficult to feel good at the same time.
Like it's nice to indulge a bit,
but like I feel bad that I'm not doing the things I did.
Got all this Clarissa stuff to still do.
Yeah.
So I'm going to I'm going to change my approach.
Hibernation nation is still happening,
but it's it's not so much that I'm going to stay in bed,
but I'm going to turn everything into a bed.
I'm going to extremely comfort my lived experience.
I'm going to wear blankets everywhere.
I'm going to I'm going to move my bed
and I'm going to get all my plushies and blankets and pillows
and put a big old like crash pile in the middle of the floor.
I'm just that's I feel like I need that.
I need to be able to just crawl into that
and then crawl out of it without too much trouble.
And it's different from going to sleep
because you can't really sleep on that, but it's nice and comfy.
I'm going to try and make it comfy
like the default state while I can do work at the computer and elsewhere.
I I think it's a worthy endeavor and I wish you great great success in it.
Yeah, it's just so cold.
You wake up and it's you don't yet.
How do you consider getting?
Have you considered getting a space heater?
Space is too big.
Just get a little space here, put it in your room.
That's what I do.
My room is I mean, sometimes it gets a little chilly.
I mean, all I really need is a blanket and I'm fine.
It's there's something to be said for a blanket
that's cozier than just a heater.
Yeah. I don't know.
I feel like it depends on the degree of chilliness we're talking about here.
I feel like it's it's like.
My my my wishes are to feel comfy all the time,
but I will only feel happy if I'm also getting some stuff done.
So I just need to be comfy while I'm working
and making my room more comfy is a good way to do that.
All right.
I understand.
Wait, I had to bite off my pinky fingernail.
You understand?
No, I do not.
Oh, well, sometimes you just got to do it.
I looked at my nails and they're they're fucked up.
But why it's not it's nothing.
It's it's a head nail polish on.
But they're starting to chip.
And so it looks like my nails are like cracked, but they're they're all right.
I got a call.
I could go to the dentist.
I've been saying for years now that I need to go to the dentist.
You know what I decided?
You know what I decided I'm going to do?
I had a genius idea.
One of the reasons I've been putting off going to the dentist
because I was like, I don't know how to sort out insurance
because like I don't have a like big boy real job.
So I don't have like employer provided dental insurance.
So I'm like, well, should I get some kind of private insurance?
And I looked into it and every private insurance company seems like they don't do shit.
They seem like garbage.
And I'm like, OK, well, I don't know what to do then.
But I realized, you know, I can probably just do.
I could probably just call the dentist and ask them
what insurance should I get that will cover, you know, routine procedures
like cleaning and maybe like cavity filling because they.
We're on the same team.
We both want the same thing.
We want an insurance company to give them money.
I could probably just call them and they'll just tell me, oh, yeah, get this,
get this, it'll cover all that stuff.
Have you done that yet? Have you done that yet?
Not yet. But it was just a couple of days ago.
I was like, I could just ask them.
I haven't done it yet, but I'm going to do that.
I hope that works because that that should be an easy way to do it.
I feel like I feel like it's I've I've arrived at a reasonable conclusion.
I feel like they'll want to help me with that so that I can pay them.
My teeth look like shit.
My teeth look terrible. I hate them.
They're like so dingy or too yet they're yellow.
In my they're yellow than they used to be.
And I hope to get some pain.
I hope that if I get them clean, they will look better.
I hope that if I get them clean, they will look better
like I remember them looking and not all dingy and crappy.
I hope it's a temporary state of affairs.
But I'm actually scared.
I'm actually scared they'll go to the dentist and they'll clean my teeth
and I'll look at them and I'll be like, oh, they still look bad.
My life is over.
So I should just not go to the dentist to avoid that.
Yeah, avoid all possible bad things.
Never leave your house, never do anything.
Yeah, foolproof, can't fail.
I think I mentioned in the PCP chat.
That I had a I had a battle of wills with my old landlord this week.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you said something about that.
Yeah.
Can I can I give you the quick version of what's gone on with that?
Yeah. OK, it's it's.
Uh, I knew this lady was not trustworthy.
Everyone else that lived in the building that I talked to said,
you're not going to your deposit back.
She's going to try and like scam you out of your deposit.
She's going to make up some fake shit.
You're not going to get your deposit back.
And I'm like, well, well, that sucks.
So I deliberately did not pay my last two months of rent.
Oh, three months, actually.
Well, because, I mean, I had already paid last month when I moved in
and she had a security deposit.
So I was two months behind on rent, but she had the deposit.
So it was really only one month behind, sort of.
So that was a couple of months ago I moved out and.
Kind of just to be a dick.
I knew that I was two months delinquent on rent,
but I kept texting her and being like, no, I didn't do it a bunch.
I did a couple of times I texted her, like, where's my deposit?
No, you're going to give me back my deposit.
And then this week she messages me back to be like.
There was some shoes.
I was going to send me a bill or so she was like, I'll send you.
I'll send you a statement.
And I think she had my zip code wrong or something.
So like, I didn't get the statement so that we had to figure that out.
But anyway, uh, cutting to the chase, she says, like, you're behind on rent.
You owe me a lot of money.
And then she sends me a bill for.
Like more than two months, two months rent.
She sends me a bill for like $1,600.
And it's like, you owe me two months rent.
No, mine, two months rent minus the deposit.
So she did include the fact that she has my deposit and that went towards rent.
So that was good.
But then she also included like, like a hundred and something dollars for a
cleaning bill, um, something else, $250 for damages to the window, which means,
okay, when I moved in, there were like some metal bars across the window and I
couldn't put an AC unit in.
So I asked this, I literally asked the like super or whatever, the supervisor,
I asked him, can you get these bars off?
And he was like, sure.
And he took the bars off so I could put my AC unit in.
So I didn't even do that.
The fucking property manager did that.
So that's outrageous.
And then the final straw was like, I think it was like $500.
She wanted like $500 in late fees for the payment being late.
And yeah.
And that's like, that's, that's most of a month's rent.
And here's the thing.
I have, I have read the law.
I have read Massachusetts tenant law in Massachusetts.
Landlords can charge a late fee and it is not technically capped how much they can
charge, but they cannot charge a late fee until rent is more than a month late,
which to be fair, this latest month is one, one month's rent is, but she was
charging for two months because she was including both of the months that I didn't
pay, but one of those was covered by the deposit.
So it really doesn't make any sense to charge a late fee for that month.
And then on the other one, okay, the lease stipulates that there will be a late
fee after a week, which is illegal.
That's not what the law says you're allowed to do.
And then it says there will be an additional late fee after a month and
the after a month late fee that it stipulates is $250, which is outrageously high.
But even that outrageously high amount is for the entire house.
Like it's for everybody living in the house, not just for me.
One guy, one of five guys living in one room.
So the fact that she tried to charge me that amount like twice for two, for
two different months is like completely ridiculous.
So I have to do this.
So basically I go into attack mode, right?
I go into like rabid dog, you know, backed into a corner, you know, a mode.
And I, and I'm just, and I just get, and I just like lawyer up.
I'm like, I'm going to call lawyers.
Like I'm going to take you to court over this.
Like we're going to, we're like, fuck you.
And she's like, I'll sue you for this.
I'll, I'll sue you if you don't pay.
What do you mean you're not going to pay?
You're a bad person.
I'm going to sue you for discriminating against me for being Indian.
She said that she said you're discriminating against me for being Indian.
There's a long text thing and she got really defensive.
I know, I know in my heart.
And I told this to her, you don't want me to go to, you don't
want to take me to court because your lease is illegal.
You've broken the law a bunch of times.
You, I have, I have text messages of you requesting late fees when they are not legal.
I have text messages of me requesting you to give me a copy of the lease.
And you did not give it to me.
You refuse to give it to me, even though I asked you for it.
That's illegal, you know, you will, you do not, you do not want to go through
what you will go through if this goes to court.
I probably could just simply pay her nothing.
I probably could just not give her anything and there would be nothing she
would be willing to do about it.
And I told her that and she got really mad.
She said, I'm disrespectful, said I'm discriminating against her for being Indian.
And I, and I said, no, I didn't even respond to that because it doesn't
even merit a response.
But anyway, the long story short of it, the ultimate conclusion is that,
yeah, I bullied her into, I'll pay the rent that I owe minus the deposit,
which she already has.
And I, and I even agree, I'll pay the $100 cleaning fee and like another
like $100 late fee or something.
So I expected not to get my deposit back at all, but in the end, I am getting
it mostly back minus like $200 for the clean, the cleaning fee is honestly
kind of fair because yeah, the place was kind of a dump when we all moved out.
So I'm not even mad about that one.
Uh, the late fees, the late fees, a little bullshit, but like whatever.
I talked to her down from $1,600 to like $900.
So like, I don't care.
Uh, so that's what happened.
This woman is a demon.
She's a vampire.
Uh, I might, I just, after I send her the bill, I might take my, like the, I might
try to like report her to some bureau or something because she's definitely
like a scammer slumlord who is like breaking the law.
And she definitely does this to all her tenants.
She definitely bullies them all into giving her ridiculous late fees.
And I'm sure most of them do not have the financial security that I have, that
they can like play this stupid game of chicken that like if they lose, they,
they might go to court and they might, you know, have to, she said like, oh,
I'll sue you for double, you know, I'll see you and the courts will make you
pay me $3,000.
They'll make you pay me double in the end.
Don't, don't do this.
And I was like, no, you're lying.
I know that won't happen.
Die.
Wow.
That sounds, I mean, I'd, I'd be fucking scared.
I, I mean, it was, it, it, it was, it was, I was a little scared because like,
what if she, like, I, I know that she won't actually take me to court.
I'm confident she doesn't actually want to do that.
But I was afraid that she might take the bill and send it to a collections
agency and I was afraid of that because if it went to a collections agency,
then it might be report, even whether it's like, I didn't think the bill is
legitimate, but like, I was wondering, like, even though the bill is legitimate
and all these fees are just made up, can she just send that number off to a,
a, a collections agency and have them like, and then they report it to a
credit bureau and then my credit takes, that's like the worst thing that can
happen to your credit score.
And I have an immaculate credit score and I would be so mad.
If like, I lost my incredible credit score because this, because this
devil just made up a bunch of fake fees and told a credit bureau that I owe,
that I owe her that money and they just believed her.
That would make me so mad.
So that's what I was really upset, really scared about was that happening.
I knew that I would win in court because I had like, I had records of her
like breaking the law and stuff, violating like 10, 10 agreements.
So I wasn't that scared about that.
I was afraid that she would try to go through with it, even, even like,
without knowing that she would definitely lose.
But in doing so would like, would like harm me on her way down, basically.
Yeah, you don't want to ever try to get justice because you'll go broke.
You'll get banged out.
I'm sure, and I'm sure that when she does this most of the time, people
do not want to risk that.
And they're just like, yeah, because, because the other guy that lived there,
he like, he just didn't get his deposit back.
Like he, he, he moved out and she just kept his deposit.
And I'm sure she said like, oh, yeah, late fees.
Oh, yeah, cleaning fees.
Oh, yeah, there was damage to the room.
Yeah, we are there.
I'm keeping your, I got to keep your deposit.
And like, she's just a thief.
She's just a thief and a criminal and she should be in prison, in my opinion.
Um, I don't know.
It's almost like you may as well trash the place.
You may as well, you may as well do as many, break as many rules as you want
because it's not going to make a difference.
Yeah, definitely, definitely.
Good.
I think that happened to me.
I mean, when I was at uni or as in a shared house, but nobody was really
willing to do like the, the bins.
And I was, we were all lazy, I guess, but like the bins did pile up.
There was rubbish everywhere.
So I understand that he took my deposit.
Um, but he also was a scary old man.
And I don't think he liked me or anyone.
I didn't think he liked human beings because it was, it was a university area.
So like, he's probably tired of those darned kids.
And he had a point because we didn't clean up anything.
Who wouldn't be tired of those darned kids?
Yeah.
Um, my, there's a, there's a, there's a fucking situation in my house right now
is that there's no toilet paper anywhere.
And like, I bought a huge box, like a huge case of toilet paper.
I bought like, you know, 20, like 24 or 36 rolls or something a while ago.
I just bought it and I let everyone use it, whatever.
And it got used up.
And now it's been like a week where there's like barely any toilet paper.
And I'm just, and I'm just kind of waiting for someone else to get some.
And nobody else is getting any.
They're just, they're just sitting around with their poopy butts.
I don't know what they're doing.
They don't know what they're doing.
Like, are they all just, everyone just have their own in their room that they
are like courting for themselves?
Possibly.
I remember I did that because I didn't like buying stuff for these people.
I mean, I would have it in my room.
I just, I just bought a bunch.
I'm, you know what?
I feel, I feel like I've kind of like an idiot because like I did it once and
nobody thanked me for it.
And now, nobody else is stepping up to do it.
So, yeah, I guess I'm kind of a rube.
I guess I'm the fool if I do.
But like, I kind of just want to probably, I'll probably just do it again.
It's hate, it's hate that everyone's got there.
Everyone's got their own secret toilet paper in their own, whatever.
It's fucking idiots.
Some, grow up.
Just grow up.
I'll do it.
I don't care.
Be like 25 bucks and give a shit.
Annoying, though.
It's just, it's just the, it's just the principle.
It's just the principle that really, okay.
Everyone else is happy.
It's, it's a, what is it?
You know that meme?
It's like a political cartoon.
It's like a guy standing on a podium and it's like, who wants, who wants to
stay hydrated and everyone like raises their hand and is like, now who wants to
actually drink water and like nobody raises their hand you don't talk about?
I haven't seen that, but I get it.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, yeah.
Who wants to wipe their, who wants to wipe their ass?
Everyone.
Yeah.
Who wants to buy toilet paper?
Nobody.
It's really just one of those, like if you don't communicate with the house,
everybody is going to hope that every, like every other person does the things
that need to be done.
Yeah.
Well, somebody's, somebody's got to do, obviously somebody.
All right.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it one more time.
I'll buy a big case of it one more time.
And then when that runs out, I'll put a message in the group chat and be like,
Hey guys, I bought toilet paper for the house like twice now.
Could somebody else do it?
Could somebody else just do it, please?
Um, that's, that's my plan.
Good plan.
Yeah.
Let them feel guilt.
At least, at least they will be in pain.
Slight name and shame, name and shame.
That's the, that's the move.
Yes.
Um, there's also rats in my house.
Maybe they were using the toilet paper.
Yeah.
The last place had mice, which was gross.
This place, uh, apparently this is a new problem that was not a problem before.
Like other people have lived here for years and this has never happened before.
But there are like rats in the kitchen now and everyone is freaked out about it.
And there was a, there was a kerfuffle, there was a, no, there's a new landlord kerfuffle
because, and I didn't do this, but one of the other people here called the landlord.
And I guess, and I guess threatened the landlord with like, we're going to
withhold rent until the rat problem is done.
And apparently that didn't go so well.
Uh, but like he, they said like, okay, it's being handled.
They've got pest control guys on it.
Pest control guys are coming and they are checking on the house and they are
leaving traps and they are leaving poison and they are doing whatever they do to get
a house pest free.
So like, okay, cool.
Uh, glad it's being handled.
So we did not withhold rent this month.
I really hope it doesn't come to that.
I really do not want to get into a thing about it.
However, the rat situation is untenable.
It is unacceptable.
There are rats in the kitchen.
Like, that's disgusting.
That's vile.
Yeah.
Is it like rat poop?
Just on the floor sometimes?
I have not seen any rat poop.
I have seen the rats like eating out of the garbage.
Yikes.
Yeah.
So I mean, you know, we're all pretty upset about that.
Did you see summoning salt called me a nerd?
Uh, oh, I did.
Lol.
You you messaged or like added them on Twitter.
I said get owned with your with your video being top of search results for
Mega Man or something.
Yes.
When you searched and this was not not signed into my account, but when you
searched, uh, what was it when you searched Mega Man on YouTube, the first
result was my video, the second result was like a music video called the song of
a song called Mega Man by somebody called take a on a channel called the
shooters and I don't know.
I've never heard of that, but whatever it is, it's got 25 million views.
And then the third result was the summoning salt Mega Man to speed running
video.
So I told summoning salt to get owned and he responded and he said get owned.
Uh, by, he had a little image.
The image was him.
Girl, I'll just, I'll just post the image because it was kind of funny.
Ellie's are showed on screen right now.
Oh, I see.
He typed in nerdy, got you top of the list.
Top, top of the list, top of the list.
Hey, you know what?
That's, that's clout.
He, he ratio, I feel, I feel, I think it should be illegal to ratio someone when
you have more followers than them.
What did it, my, my, my tweet at him got like a, got like three or 400 and his
has a 1300, his reply has 1300 likes.
I don't know.
He's got a hundred.
He's got a hundred thousand followers though.
I think that, I think that spiritually I ratioed him actually.
The moral victory.
I think I would, I would call, I would definitely call this a moral victory
100% for sure.
Yeah.
Ah, base, base, base.
Um, damn.
Try to think of a.
Yeah, I can't think of anything off the top of my head.
You want to go to voicemails?
How long have you been going for?
It's just been an hour.
Oh, like it's a little early.
An hour, 20 minutes.
It's not that.
Um.
I don't know.
Uh, what are you thinking about for Christmas?
Um, I asked my mom, she asked what I want for Christmas.
And I, I said, I would like an immersion blender.
I would maybe like one of those magic bullet blenders.
I would maybe like a rice cooker.
But apparently there already is a rice cooker in this house.
It's just like the parts are like.
Not together.
I might have to like find the parts just like Z just like X in Mega Man X two.
I might have to like fight the fight the X hunters to collect the different parts
of the rice cooker and then put it all together.
Uh, oh, shit.
Wait, um, one piece.
Oh, fuck, I didn't read this week.
Oh, you got to read it.
There's a new chapter.
We got to do our corner.
I guess, I guess we could read it right now.
We could do the same thing as last time, but you're the one reading it.
Yeah, sure.
Let's let's do it.
I completely spaced on one piece.
Um, I should have reminded you.
I did see it and I was like, I should tell Ben in case, but I forgot.
You, it would have, uh, it would have helped, but no matter.
Okay.
Chapter 1068, a genius's dream.
An emotion.
Jerma 66 is an emotionless voyage.
These two once belonged in an organization called Mads.
Oh, uh, skip to this time code posted on the screen to get plus one piece.
We should make a time code for that.
Okay.
So, so I really, by the way, I realized that, um, the, the past, the pacifistas
with the dark skin and the wings, the luminarian, the luminarian pacifistas
are the seraphim.
Yeah.
Okay.
I didn't put that together last time, but I understand.
See, I don't want to say anything that you haven't read yet.
So I'm waiting for you to like, yeah, make comments.
I'm, I'm waiting until there's like something.
That I can come in and like, definitely comment on.
Wait a minute.
The grand line.
He pawpawed someone.
Who, who did he pawpaw?
Himself.
Like he's gone.
All of, all of those parts that were falling off of him and then he, he popped himself away.
Oh, that's him.
It's his, his robot guts coming out.
Yeah, they were repairing him or they were like trying to like undo the, the, uh, what
do you call it, like the pacifist station or whatever they would, you would say.
Oh, that's what they were doing.
The, the Revolutionary Army were doing that.
Okay.
That, that's, that's, um, presumably, I can't remember if they say it out right, but
like when they went to marriage water to save him, I think that was part of, there's
one of their objectives is to find and rescue Kuma so that they could undo the damage and
maybe get him back to his old self.
Okay.
I want to create a kind of world with science, a world where energy is widespread all over
the world free of charge.
Yeah.
Communism.
Yes.
Based, based the resources that produce energy are fought over in many countries.
Which when becomes the seed for war, you can feel energy here over there and everywhere
else, even though the world is full of it, they can convert it to visible power, a large
fuse of war.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
He wants to give everybody what they need so they don't need to fight anymore.
Ever, everybody, everybody has free energy.
God damn.
Sounds like I'm really interested.
Hmm.
I think a person that can make everyone happy is good.
I'm not interested in being a hero, though.
Okay.
Dynamic power source was able to power this ancient robot soldier.
So he's looking into whatever powered this ancient technology.
Okay.
Yeah, this is Mega Man Legends right now.
And this is, they found ancient something or other.
Oh, they found, oh, it's a refractor.
Okay.
Thank you for putting it in terms that I can understand.
So it's like a quantum refractor.
Okay.
No, gotcha.
I stepped too deep into the forbidden story.
I will be eliminated by the world government.
Just like what they did to Ohara.
That's not good.
CPO are those who only act under orders of celestial dragons, but it's CPO.
It's not CP9.
They are at the top of Cypherpole.
Oh, well, that must mean they're really powerful if the number went up.
Well, number went down.
It's CP0.
Oh, right, right, right.
It's so, so wacky that they don't even have it listed.
Everyone thinks it stops at CP9, except now everyone knows.
Except now everyone knows because it's no longer a mystery to the reader.
Chaka, CP0 is on the island.
OK, OK.
The CPO, I guess, is apparently here to kill
Vegapunk because he knows too much about the void century.
That makes sense.
Sentomaru, wait, who's Sentomaru?
If you remember here, right, he appeared at
Shabaodi with the original Pesifista
and he was like in charge of them.
So I guess we're learning now that he's like a Vegapunk.
Like guy, like he's on this island.
I definitely recognize him.
I remember there was information about like his,
like being the grandson of somebody important or the son of someone.
Let me check.
Oh, he's the captain of the Marine Science Unit.
He calls Kizaru uncle, but that might not be
that might be a like a friendly thing rather than an actual family thing.
He might be calling him like Osan or something.
Is that the word for like an ojiki?
Ojiki.
Yakuza family, father, boss, yeah, it could be that.
But he's a Marine boy and he's a Vegapunk.
Marine science officer person who can control the Pesifista for some reason,
maybe just that they've been programmed to accept his orders.
Roku gun is the finger gun, right?
It's when they shoot the little.
Uh, I can't remember.
I remember Shoku gun.
It looks like he's.
Kick it out of the face or something.
It looks like he's exactly what he's doing.
He's jumped and his legs are like his knees bent and he's got his.
Yeah, he's probably doing the finger thing or like just punching really hard.
OK, all right.
So CP CP CP zero.
The kill Vegapunk.
Damn.
The thing I got from this chapter mostly is that Vegapunk has his like,
oh, this is my dream and, you know,
those straw hat pirates don't have an old man on the crew yet.
Maybe this is like a new crew member or at least it's certainly going to be temporary.
OK, certainly going to be temporary ill on the crew for like a while after this, possibly.
You know what?
I think I didn't even think about it, but like.
Yeah, that would be awesome.
That's so awesome.
Vegapunk rules.
Vegapunk so good.
So cool.
I hope I hope it's a good design.
You know, if we're if we're having like stupid new new team members.
Yeah, yeah, Vegapunk.
Yeah, please.
Yeah, it's it's because we've not known enough about Vegapunks like once
and like why he's working with the world government.
And it's, you know, last few chapters is like, oh, it's because
in order to pursue science, you need a lot of funds and you need a lot of,
you know, freedom to work.
Yeah. And so the world government can provide that for him.
And that's the only reason.
But he's getting close to some secrets that he shouldn't.
And so just so happens as the straw hats arrive.
That he needs to get out of there and he's going to be killed otherwise.
So like it's perfect time for him to stop being working with the world
government, stop being a pirate.
Yeah.
Certainly going to be like even he's already in outlaw, I guess.
Yeah, he's currently in, I mean, CP zero is like.
Implied to be super secret so that even the Marines don't know about them.
So like this is like an assassination attempt.
Yeah, he's not like publicly an enemy.
He's not publicly an enemy, but like, I don't know what will happen.
They are taking out.
It will be pretty cool if he gets a wanted poster after whatever's happening here.
And then he's like, oh, cool.
You want to join the crew or more likely, I think he's going to join the Revolutionary Army.
Because if Kuma is going to drop in, obviously, Jewelry Bonnie,
his daughter, they're going to have a thing.
There's also things that can happen.
I'm excited to see what's what's going on.
So there's like obviously, immediately, the two strongest guys
seeing each other, Luffy and Luchi, are they going to have a rematch right there?
Like how the fuck is that going to go?
So Kuma, he's still like, you know, a mindless robot.
Like the Revolutionary Army basically like kidnapped him against his will
to try and like undo the conditioning or the program or whatever.
I think it's it's not been made totally clear whether he has.
Like no sentience, he might just not be able to move.
Like he might not be like too far gone or anything.
But yeah, it seems like because there was that part where he
in during the time skip, protected the Straw Hats, protected Sunigo,
the ship from being attacked for like those full two years.
And then he left, which seems like somebody programmed him to do that.
Because otherwise he's completely controlled by the the world government and the Marines.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Yeah, Frankie or someone just sees him and he's just sitting there and then he stands up
and he leaves, doesn't say a word.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
That's really weird that that happened.
Hmm.
It's probably going to be very sad if he if he arrives.
I don't know why he's going there.
But like if he's been like called somehow.
You think he's going to Egghead?
I mean, it seems the most logical place.
Yeah.
Like he got some sort of notification and he's like zapping himself over there.
And then maybe jewelry Bonnie will see her dad.
But he won't be able to say anything.
He'll still be like an automaton, maybe.
Yeah.
I I mean, I just I just don't know.
Just don't know what's going on with him.
I mean, I guess who was it that said that he was an asshole?
Was it was it?
Fuck, what's Shark Man's name?
I'm forgetting.
Jin Bay.
This Jin Jin Bay was the one that said like he was like a tyrant.
He was like a douchebag king.
But now he's like now he's a row.
He's been reprogrammed for the Marines.
But also he seems to like secretly be working on behalf of the Straw Hats.
And more like the Revolutionary Army.
Yeah.
Which so like maybe from Dragon somehow or Vega Punk.
Some deep code inside him that allows him to to do good still.
Yeah, we're going to learn a lot more about all that for sure.
Yeah.
I mean, hype.
I like I like I think Kuma is pretty cool.
I'm interested.
I'm really yeah.
This these revelations these Vega Punk revelations are pretty pretty cool.
Pretty pretty exciting.
Pretty like what's what's his what's his role going to be.
Yeah, he might I could see him joining the Revolutionary Army for sure.
So fucking base fucking epic.
It's awesome.
I notice in this that one panel where the the the seraphim that they were returning.
Bear looks like Kuma.
Yeah.
They called it B Bear or S Bear or something.
S Bear.
Like seraphim bear because yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do notice that he is shaded is to have darker skin.
So you were correct.
I think sometimes sometimes he is.
It's kind of inconsistent panel to panel.
Which one are you looking at?
We'll look at this one.
He's he's not he's not shaded here.
I think he is.
Oh no, he kind of is a little bit.
I see.
I see it's it's faint, but it's probably like a bad scan.
A bad scan.
Yeah, because like it's not pure white like it would be if it was just, you know,
unshaded.
I feel like there's a half tone in there.
Oh wait.
This is like because you see his hair is like white and it's lighter.
OK, this is we're doing we're doing phrenology on this on this Kuma clone.
Well, this is his hands here look like they might be shaded.
I'm trying to find one that's clearer because OK.
Well, the point being the the the similarities to King having the black wings
and the white hair and the darker skin.
He does have the white hair for sure.
Oh, that one.
I didn't notice that one.
Yeah, that's just this one.
He just not looked at all all it's going to take all I need is one panel where it's like
very clearly like they definitely like made a visible like shading to differentiate his color.
All you need is one example and I'll be like, OK, I'm sold.
I don't need whoa.
Sorry, I sneezed.
Did it sound loud?
Yeah, it did.
But like muffled distance.
I muffled it with the with the blanket.
I think it's probably the case that he looks like a lumarian.
But I feel like I feel like none of these panels show it very well.
But I'll wait.
We'll wait and see.
Yeah, so like I think I said last time last time we talked to one piece that like
I don't feel like Egg Island is going to be particularly long.
Definitely not as long as one or not sort of feels.
I mean, we just got here like three chapters ago.
Yeah.
And the battle is on.
Yeah, already like Luchi and Luffy are there.
Fighting is happening.
And I don't believe anything else is going to come up other than Kuma.
I feel like this is going to be like a short confrontation followed by maybe Kuma arrives
to save the straw hats and blast them away somewhere because Bonnie is with them.
Yeah, it doesn't feel like they're setting up like a big sort of like sprawling backstory
that all culminates in a big like battle like like they did with, you know,
a Wano or anything like that.
Yeah, although I am curious.
I wonder if like the different.
Do you think there's anything more to like the backstories of the different
uh, uh, vagabunk pieces that is like or or just not he just made them.
I mean, I think the like the the it's a lot of it's been explained by him saying
this island has some ancient technologies and I derived a lot of my science stuff from what we
found and that's just sort of like that's how he's so smart and has so many good technologies.
Hmm.
Also, my brain is this giant building and it's gathering information.
That's also helpful.
Because what's interesting here that the their ship, the ship zero
fucking ship was eaten by the the the sea beasts, sea beast guys.
Is that is that what happened to the ship?
Yeah, because Luchi said, I know we won't be able to like
as soon as we attack our ship will be destroyed.
So we got to get on that quick.
And so they they abandoned their ship so that they can get in.
Did the ship get destroyed?
Yeah, there's a thing with like the what are they?
What's the word?
Not real, not manmade sea.
Artificial.
No, artificial.
Natural.
Artificial sea beasts.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
They ate it.
And then I see them like looming around the ship.
There's a panel later where it's it's shown.
Okay.
That they're doing that.
I believe you.
I believe it.
Well, just take a little screen grab.
Yeah, it's it's what's his face?
You're speaking of Mega Man.
Some of these guys do look like Mega Man enemies.
Oh, yeah, these these little robot little robot eyes.
There's two.
There's two robot dudes among the.
The Vegapunk people.
Just some of them look like robot.
No, there's three.
Well, there's three if you count Daft Punk.
There's Daft Punk and then there's two like the little like clanky like oval men.
Yeah, they're definitely Mega Man people.
Definitely.
Definitely Mega Man.
Actually, I mean, Daft Punk does look sort of like the Valiant enemies from X4 vials like soldiers.
So, you know, I guess they're all Mega Man, actually, when you really when you really think about it.
You have to wonder about it.
I have to wonder how strong like Luchi and Kaku have become since water seven and all that.
Yeah, because they're the top level guys.
This is the level of guys that were at Wano with their funny masks playing like Othello or whatever.
At Wano?
Yeah, there was the two really tall guys holding masks on their face and then the shorter guy
with just sort of goggles and they were like in a room.
What?
And they were like, hmm, the insurgents have like 3000 strong, but Kaido's army has like 16,000.
But they're turning the tide of battle.
That's those guys.
They were like commentating what was happening.
Wait, who?
Who were they?
I mean, I remember that scene.
I remember that scene.
I don't remember who was saying it.
It was, I mean, I don't know their names, but they're like sheepie zero as well.
And they interfered with Kaido's battle.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Okay, wait, I didn't realize those guys were CP.
Yeah, that's their hair on special business, but it just so happens.
Oh, you're right.
All that shit was happening.
Yes, yes, yes.
I remember now.
Okay, okay.
So these guys, yeah.
They're the same level.
So like, they're definitely going to be strong.
Did we see those guys fight?
There was a part when shit was going down that they had to go and intervene.
So like one of them died, I'm pretty sure.
Oh, shit.
They fought, they fought X-Drake.
I guess somewhere.
Yeah, yeah.
There was a few confrontation.
I can't remember exactly who fought.
X-Drake and Killer?
X-Drake and Apu, I think.
Yeah, Killer was there.
They were like forced to team up.
Killer was fighting against them.
Or no, Killer was fighting against Kid.
Why would Killer fight against Kid?
No, he was fighting against, not Dracula Mihawk, the straw guy, the voodoo doll guy.
Yes, Basil Hawkins.
Basil Hawkins, yes, yes, yes.
So many fucking characters that you track up.
There was like a hundred fucking fights in 1-0.
It's unbelievable.
But yeah, those guys were very strong and they only really,
like if they were completely let loose, they would have done some massive damage.
I think there was like that part where the big ghost, the flame ghost was traveling down and
it blocked off those guys from fighting Usopp or something.
Oh, the big like goopy flame thing that was burrowing down through the castle.
Yeah, and it was going down.
It was going to blow up the big explosives at the bottom.
I didn't even remember how that was stopped.
Do you remember how that was stopped?
No, I don't.
Yamato was running to catch it, but what did she do in the end?
I don't remember.
Wait, I think he threw all the bombs down into the floor and then they exploded.
But like in the middle of the sky, instead of it, I can't remember exactly.
Like it dropped out the bottom of the city and it blew up in the air.
Yeah, something like that.
That sounds...
There was like seven different ticking clocks.
There was so many fucking...
If this happens, everyone dies and if this happens, everyone dies.
But then if this happens, everyone dies and the island falls
and kills everyone below it as well.
So we want the first option where everyone dies.
We don't want the second one because there's other even worse things happen as well.
It's not just that everything was going to explode and fall out of the sky.
The island will fall out of the sky, so Momo had to make clouds.
We're talking about the difference between a sky lagoon and a space station Eurasia,
a space colony Eurasia here.
Oh, yeah.
It's tomato tomorrow.
There's difference of scale.
But then also there was a fire and everything was burning and everyone was going to burn to death.
Yeah.
And then everyone was going to drown because it was too late.
And it was going to blow up the weapons stash in the bottom of the floating castle.
Yeah, there was like so many different possible ways that everybody could die.
And then if Luffy dies, Kaida would come down and kill everyone as well.
Right.
Yeah.
It's so fucked.
And then it all happened as well.
It was honestly really difficult.
I don't even remember half of these things.
Oh, yeah, that did happen, didn't it?
Like, oh my god.
Yeah, I kind of imagined reading it all in one go because week by week it was like,
holy shit, so much happens in one chapter and then whole other sets of things happen in the next.
I did.
It might have hurt my reading comprehension a bit to binge it, but it's okay.
I got the gist.
But yeah, this is not setting up to be anywhere near as long just purely because of the amount
of characters.
Like, there's three CP0 and Luchi and Kaku are probably pretty strong.
Stussy was that whole cake.
I don't remember if she did anything combat wise.
The girl?
Is it the silk girl?
No, no, no.
That's Khalifa.
Stussy or Stussy was like, Sussie is better.
Stussy was like-
Wait, is that the one in the chicken mask?
Yeah, she's wearing a funny mask.
I don't know why.
Oh, I guess she's part of CP0 the whole time.
Like, she was like-
I don't remember if she does like it all to be perfectly-
She was at the wedding between Pudding and Sanji as an invited guest because she's
a very important person for various reasons I can't remember.
But while she was there, she secretly was being undercover agent for the world government.
She's CP0.
She has knowledge and she let the world government know what happened.
Because you know Captain Morgan, not Captain Morgan.
Fuckin' Morgan the Big Bird.
There could be a Captain.
Oh yeah, the news guy, the news bird.
Yeah, Morgan the news bird was there and he spread-
I love Morgan the news bird.
Yes, he's so good.
He's like a dastardly devil, Big Bird from-
He's a dastardly devil.
He's like a freedom of speech guy, but in a good way.
He's like an actual freedom of speech guy.
Yes, and he spread the news in a way that he wanted it to be spread about Whole Cake.
And that led, I think, to Luffy being branded one of the new Yonko, like the five emperors.
He was one of them now.
I was like, I'm not sure about that, said everyone.
Isn't his name literally like News Morgan?
Yeah, Big News Morgan.
People just call him Big News.
Should have called him like Big Scoop.
I like Big News Morgan.
Not Big News is good.
But yeah, he was there.
He spun it the way he did on the newspaper.
But Stussy, Stussy, they're not a saying.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay, Lucci's got a chicken sitting on his shoulder.
Is that Stussy?
No, no, that's the pigeon.
Do you not remember?
He had a pigeon the whole time back in water seven.
That's just a pet pigeon that he has?
Yes.
He, if you remember, when he was introduced, he was like, didn't say anything.
But the pigeon sort of spoke for him.
And that was his gimmick.
And you didn't know how strong he was until he revealed himself to be a member of CP9.
And then he started talking and he was evil.
I do not remember that at all.
Do you remember they worked for, like, they were undercover.
They worked him and Kaku and Khalifa.
Do they work for Tom?
Or no, not Tom.
They work for Icebar or Iceberg for Galila Company, the shipwrights.
With fucking Pauly.
And I think that's it.
There was some other guys.
Yes, I do remember that.
Don't remember the pigeon, but okay.
Yeah, the pigeon was there as his, like, I speak through my pigeon thing.
I don't know why, but like, I guess the pigeon is strong as well,
because he's got his own fucking tie and hat.
He would have to be.
I don't see, oh wait, no, I see Stussy.
I think in this panel with the kuma facing away, I think I see her like silhouette.
Yeah, she has a few speaking bits, like when Kaku tries to jump
and then there's the force field, she's got the chicken mask on.
But like, what's her power?
What's her deal?
I don't know, but she revealed herself to be a secret government agent
instead of whoever else she was at the whole cake wedding.
When shit went down, she sort of snuck away and she had that bomb.
I think her briefcase had the bomb in it and the bomb went off.
Or maybe someone else had the bomb.
She's the one in like the fluffy feather mask.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, what was that bomb?
Wait, there was a bomb?
You're talking about Sanji's wedding?
Yeah, Sanji's wedding.
Do you remember, I forget exactly what I think the briefcase was given to somebody
by fucking the Fishman Island people.
They gave it as a reward or a gift, but it's a bomb.
Oh my God, it's just like bullet train.
This is the plot of bullet train.
What even the fuck was that bomb?
I can't remember, but I think she was there when that happened.
I forget.
Yeah, I vaguely remember a briefcase with a bomb in it.
Maybe, I guess.
Because the big fucking cake, like mountain, the whole cake,
the wedding was being at the top of, that got exploded and it fell down.
Yes.
And it was frosting everywhere.
That feels true.
Agent of CPG, in her cover as an Emperor of the Underworld, that's right.
She was an underworld person, does shady deals in the similar vein, I guess, to Doflamingo.
She's just sort of part of the underbelly.
And so she was invited to this wedding.
Good for her.
And good for her, girl boss.
And she is, yeah.
All right.
Epithet Queen of the Pleasure District.
Oh, she's like a...
On a whole case?
Yeah, that's what she was called.
Or that's what her alias is.
It could be that she is both that and a member of CP Zero.
Oh, okay.
But that implies that she's like a super rich brothel owner or something.
She owns every brothel in the world.
Good for her, girl boss.
Hell yes.
Hell yeah.
Okay, it's good to review all this stuff because I feel like I've forgotten more than half of it.
More than half of everything that's happened.
There's always...
I mean, it was always a thing in the podcast as well.
Nate had a lot of stuff memorized, more than me.
Really?
And whenever I got something wrong, he would say, no, don't you remember?
You fool.
700 chapters ago, there was this said.
I think it's because he keeps up with discussions on chapters.
He probably reads discussion on 4chan.
Or somewhere else, maybe.
Where people pool their knowledge and reference things.
I'm like, I don't really care about all that stuff.
Just like Vegapunk's giant brain in the egghead loft.
Yes.
Vegapunk's egghead brain knows what the will of D means.
Vegapunk's egghead brain could tell you what Stussy's devil fruit power is.
He's been paying attention.
Well, I could read the wiki.
What's her power?
Infiltration skills.
It's not a devil.
She's so fucking sneaky.
She can tiptoe like no one's business.
I mean, I guess if she's CP, she's probably a zoan.
But you never know.
Doesn't seem to have any.
Might have just not been revealed yet.
Cypherpole doesn't necessarily have animals.
I think that was just like a CP9 specific thing.
BlueKnow was also CP and he did not have zoan.
Get a door fruit.
He had the doa fruit, yeah.
The doa doa fruit, but he had like long bullhorn hairstyle.
He looked like he was obviously going to have a bull zoan, but then he just didn't.
Everyone else had a zoan.
And if you remember Califa, she had the soap thing.
Yes, yes, the soap.
She made a big like woollen sheep coat of like soap.
And then she put her arms around in like a C shape to look like lamb horns.
And she did like a pose and she was like a sheep.
And like Nami was like, cut that shit out.
That's stupid.
Oh, yeah.
So like all of them can be an animal.
They're all like sort of an animal.
Especially the ones that literally are.
Some of them are literally just are and the ones that aren't sort of pretend.
Yeah, I love that moment.
That was such a good one.
Yeah, you're feeling me with fond memories of a time when I was surprised and delighted.
It's always a good thing.
Yeah.
So what else happened in the chapter?
Yeah, just they arrived.
CP9 has made their landing and.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
This is what I was going to.
This is what I was going to say.
There's three members.
It's going to be hard to stop calling them CP9.
Yeah, CP0.
There's three members here.
Presumably they're all very strong.
Luchi is probably the strongest.
Yeah.
But they're up against the entirety of the Straw Hat crew, which is very strong.
Like cumulatively.
They beat him.
Like individually.
They beat him once.
And like obviously Luchi is a lot stronger.
Luchi is probably a lot stronger as well.
But like what chance does CP0 really have to do anything here?
Luchi couldn't fight the whole crew.
He couldn't fight the whole crew, I don't think.
And he certainly couldn't fight the whole crew plus every Seraphim.
Every Seraphim and all these Vegapunk people who I assume have like crazy powers.
So like what are they going to do?
Kuma is going to appear.
It might be that Kuma turns the tide.
And if he's working for CP0, he'll like do something real bad.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like what even what even could happen?
That's what we're going to find out the next chapter one piece.
Okay, CP's goal, they're just on an assassination mission, right?
They're just like assassinate Vegapunk.
That seems to be their goal.
Yeah, I suppose it'll be like get Vegapunk out of here.
Because he's like a little, he's an old man.
He's not physically strong.
He's just got a funny brain double fruit and a lot of tech.
So if they get him, then he's gut.
Yeah, he's also got like, I guess he, I guess he, did we really,
did we know that he was just like projecting a hologram this whole time?
I think we didn't.
No, we didn't.
Oh, okay.
I don't think so.
Maybe somebody else was projecting a hologram.
Someone, someone was projecting a hologram.
I think what it was is like we see him half stuck in something and he said,
oh no, the teleport didn't work again.
So it's presumed that he teleported his physical body.
Or it could be that he just has the ability to teleport around his island.
So like he's just doing another teleport and that was his physical body.
That's how he teleports.
Maybe, yeah, maybe.
I wonder, would be pretty interesting to see him fight like what,
what abilities does he have?
Like, or has the, I assume he has made devices for himself.
He's probably got some devices, some gadgets, some gizmos.
I, I think there's no, there's no doubt, no doubt about the gadgets and gizmos.
Damn, I wish there was more.
Looking forward to continuing this journey.
You there?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just, I'm trying to see like this last image.
What's her face?
What's her name?
Monster Atlas.
It's Atlas, the big girl.
The big one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought that was one of those, I thought that was one of those giant,
I thought that was one of those giant kids from,
where were the giant kids?
From punk hazard, the, the experiments that Caesar clown was doing on those
children because Big Mom wanted to make a race of giants for her family.
That's the one, that's the one.
Yes.
But I guess she's not, unless maybe she is.
No, she's just, she's just big.
She might just be big.
Are they, are they all robots?
I would assume they're all like entirely artificial.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe not.
I know, I've no reason to believe either way.
I just assume that they're completely robotic.
Yeah, I guess that's probably a, like, since they're all seemed, they're all a set.
So probably they're all the same type of thing and some of them are definitely robots.
So probably all of them are robots.
Oh my God.
Like Mega Man.
They're so mega.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean, that makes sense.
Is Vegapunk a wily or a light?
Vegapunk, more like Megapunk.
What, what?
Megapunk.
Sanji kind of has like,
we've been seeing Sanji in a second.
He was with, who was he with?
I forget.
I guess we haven't seen much of him.
I don't think he was even in this chapter at all.
Yeah.
No, he's, he's with one of the groups.
I don't think it, yeah, the two on the ship are Zoro and Brooke.
Right.
They, they haven't done anything.
They've just been chilling.
And then.
But they probably have definitely heard the explosion.
So we might be thinking.
Here with Vegapunk is Luffy and Chopper and Jinbei and Nami?
Is Nami here?
Yeah.
No, Bonnie.
Okay.
So Sanji and Nami and Robin and Frankie are somewhere else?
And Usopp.
Yeah.
What are they doing?
They went up into the place and they were looking around.
Oh, um, what's, Kali, no, the girl, the girl Vegapunk is taking them to go and look at like
the Seraphim chambers or up to see the punk, the punk archives?
Something.
Yes.
Yeah.
They, they met up with, with Daft Punk and he started saying things.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
They're, they're with Daft Punk.
They're in the control tower.
And also the evil girl.
Seeing, seeing everything.
Also, is that a, is that a joke like Vegapunk, Daft Punk?
Is that like, is that a joke?
Is that on purpose?
I mean, I feel like Daft Punk is famous enough and that design is like similar enough that it was
probably true, like, yes, like a reference.
Like he, he looks like Daft Punk on purpose, right?
That's not, that's not a coincidence.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Everyone loves Daft Punk robot designs.
Okay.
Just check it.
It would be cool if there was like a Mega Man reference in this, in this whole thing,
you know, like an explicit one.
I, I mean, I would be, I would be, I would soy face.
I would soy face.
Uh, you know, a couple people have said that like
Mega, people have definitely said that Mega Man is just a ripoff of Astro Boy.
And I've don't, I have never read Astro Boy.
So like, I'm sure that to a certain extent that, that's definitely true.
But like,
I, I would think a lot of, a lot of the trappings.
Yeah.
A lot of the trappings of the design, like Astro Boy is a young boy.
There's, there's scientists that have like lost a child and turned a, made a robot son.
Yeah.
I forget like how the law, like I haven't read all of Astro Boy.
I mostly know Astro Boy law from the GBA game Omega Factor, which is like the best GBA game ever.
Really?
Uh, well, as a game, it's fine.
But like the, the, it really tugs on your heartstrings.
The story is really good.
Oh, wow.
And it's, it's because that draws from every Tezuka work ever, every character from his
entire library of stuff.
And they just make a unique story building with, with all those building blocks.
And Astro Boy does deal a lot with the sentient of robots, humans versus robots.
Yeah.
And like, and power dynamics and, uh, like who should live?
Who should be like the tough questions.
So it's, and then there's this cute little boy,
this cute little boy with an R, a gun on his arm.
Yeah.
It's a space.
Does, does Astro Boy have a gun on his arm?
He, his arm turns into a gun.
Oh, okay.
So yeah, just like, just like Mega Man.
Yeah.
Cool.
Uh, oh no, I wasted my time.
I wasted my time.
I experienced the derivative work of media.
No.
Gringe.
I love Astro Boy so much.
I should read everything.
I'm sorry.
I've read like a couple books.
They made, they made a, they made a GBA game that's just like a mishmash,
melange of all of like Tezuka's classic manga characters.
Yeah.
That sounds amazing.
This, it is great.
You should play Omega Factor.
I think, I'm intrigued.
I think you would enjoy it.
Although I mean, I'm not, I haven't really read,
I haven't really read much Tezuka, to be honest.
I don't, I don't know anything.
I didn't know anything about any Tezuka before I played that game.
But like, it's, it's good.
There's like Blackjack, the, the surgeon.
And there's fucking Kimba.
That was Tezuka.
Kimba's in there.
Well, it's like cartoon all stars to the rescue.
Yeah.
But, but good.
But good.
It's, it's really good.
People cry.
I cry at the end of that game.
That's the, that's the sort of,
that's what they call good story writing.
That's what you call, that's what you call epic.
I don't know.
I have to pee.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Not to change the subject or anything.
Although going into the bathroom and seeing no toilet paper
just reminded me about my new housemates.
And it reminded, and I was reminded.
But the other day, one of them mentioned that he was like
thinking about starting a podcast.
And I was like, oh no.
You haven't told them, I assume.
No.
I was like, I can't let this guy know.
I can't fucking let this guy know.
I told one guy that I was working on a YouTube video.
Which you were.
Which I was.
Yeah.
That was a cup like a little while ago.
He asked me like what I do.
And I said, oh, you know, post stuff on the internet.
I've worked on YouTube.
Oh, I'm just posting.
I'm just posting.
Some people are just born posters.
But I didn't mention a podcast.
And this guy, he just offhandedly, he just saw I had a microphone.
And he asked me like what I use it for.
And I said, oh, you know, I record stuff with friends on, you know, sometimes.
And he was like, oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, there's something about, I don't remember what he said.
He said something about, he says something about he had a friend who like
was starting a podcast.
And he was like, maybe I should start a pocket.
And I was like, ah, no.
Imagine if it all converged like you're all in your separate rooms,
making podcasts at the same time.
We become a post.
We're a post-in house.
We're a post-in family.
We post in this house.
In this house, we post.
And if you're not posting, then you don't live here anymore.
Yeah, damn.
Podcasting sure is cringe.
Long.
Continues podcasting.
Here we go.
He's, he said on his podcast, he said with his latte, with his soy latte,
he's paid $8 for his Starbucks soy latte, but he won't pay $8 for his blue checkmark.
I haven't seen anyone with a blue checkmark in a long time.
I guess I don't see them that much anyway, but.
I see them, I see them around sometimes.
And it's always, it's always cringe.
Honestly, the worst is when I see someone that makes a post that I agree with and I check
and they've got a blue checkmark and I'm like, oh God.
Did they have that before the paid thing though?
No, there's no way to know.
No, there is a way to know.
You can, you can, if you hover over the checkmark on their profile,
it'll tell you whether they have it because they're notable or if they just bought it.
So you can see.
And whenever it's someone that bought it, I'm just like, well,
I might agree with your opinion on this particular issue.
But like, I'm not, you're, you're DNI.
You do not interact.
You're, you're dead, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, we can't be friends.
That's just how, that's the way the news goes.
That's the way the big news goes.
Big news, Morgan.
What a, what a dude.
Yes.
Want to see more of him.
I'm sure we will.
He's, he's, he's the news.
That's the way the news goes, as he says.
His famous catchphrase.
All right.
Well, what do you think?
Voice mail time?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, let's do it.
I'm looking at and I'm seeing that the first voicemail of the week is called.
Wow.
You see it?
Yep.
Do you see it?
Okay.
Well, let's, let's hope that my internet is better this week than last week.
Lol.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, by the time I was, I'm sending these, it's a hundred thousand.
Good job.
You did it.
Oh.
High five.
Yeah.
Did you, did you high five me?
This was sent a week ago.
Yeah.
The video made a hundred K in just under a week.
And now at the two, it had, it was like, it was at like 200 and like 30 something K
at the two week mark.
So thanks, thanks.
You know, it's very refreshing.
I have had a couple people finding, find me through the Mega Man lecture
and they, and they don't know what the PCP is.
They don't know about Sonichu.
They don't know any of the horrors.
They're free.
Yes.
Their minds are clean and pure.
They don't know about Digi Bro.
They don't know about my little pony.
Imagine being someone like that.
It's so refreshing.
I can't, I can't.
I have to live through them.
The next one is called clicking a pen.
Three, two, one, go.
So I just saw that Mega Man video.
True.
And at the 12 minute marker.
So you say, hang on, I'm thirsty.
And that was pretty funny.
Thanks.
That made me laugh, made me laugh really hard for like a minute.
Thank you very much.
I liked when I said I'm thirsty.
Anyways, that's not the point.
I was just going to say, I like the video, but when's the Mega Man battle network
one coming out?
Probably will do one.
I probably will do that at some point.
It'll be a good companion piece.
Yeah, I think I might have said this, but I think I do want to do it.
I should do it and I want to do it.
I don't want to do it right away.
I feel like I've had enough Mega Man for the moment.
For the Mega Moment.
For the Mega, for the Mega Moment.
I kind of don't want to like play more video games right now.
I'm going to do something else.
I just released, I just released a damn
Patron's Q&A podcast where I talk about
what I'm going to do for the next lecture and other stuff.
So, um, actually some of it might be a repeat of what I talked about here on last week,
but don't think about that.
Don't, don't worry about that.
Next one is called It's a Good Idea.
I stand by it.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, Ben, your Mega Man lecture is finally out
and I think it is time for you to move on to your next, uh, large project.
And I think I've got a great idea for you.
Here's my pitch.
Here's my pitch for the next months long arc of the, uh, the life of Ben St.
I know, I know.
Here we go.
My big idea is you should fuck Jenny Nicholson.
Hmm.
Think about it.
Make a video.
Make a video out of it.
That's an idea.
You know, maybe there's something, you know, you know, it sounds crazy, but I mean,
it just might work.
You, she can make a video about it.
You could both make content out of that.
I could make a video about it.
She could make a video about it.
We could review it.
Hey, Jenny Nicholson, what are you doing in my review of sex with you?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'll put it on the maybe list.
Now that's content.
Oh, dude, I gotta kick out of that.
X1 is called right now.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, now make your brand in your catchphrase whenever you finish a sentence.
Say, huh, maybe I should make a lecture about that.
Everyone will love it.
Your fan base will triplicate.
Triplicate.
My fan base will triplicate.
It's like a Japanese, one of those anime character, like they end a sentence with a
nyon or a nyodon or something, or they end it with a pya.
But for me, it's maybe I should make a lecture about that.
I could roll off the tongue pretty well.
I'll workshop it.
Motivate, and I end every sentence with a till day, till day lecture.
What do you think?
Till day?
Yeah, you know, till day, the squiggly line.
I always pronounce it tilde.
Oh, whatever.
Stupid, stupid.
Never mind.
It's just like tilde swinton.
Yeah, yeah, that's how you spell it.
It's no, it's not.
No.
Yeah, it's like, no, it's like e.
It's an e.
It's till day.
It's tilde swinton.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I see.
Mm, swinton, I end my sentences with...
What was that?
Well, okay.
Next one is called, we'll see.
There's congrats on the video ban, congrats on 69k ban, congrats on 100k ban, congrats on 169
ban, congrats on 200k ban.
Haven't hit 269 yet, so I look forward to that.
Congratulations.
Next one is, is lecture better than video essay?
Question mark, three, two, one, go.
Yo, so I'm listening to episode 337 right now, where Ben is like talking about all the topics for
potential lectures.
And I feel like, yeah, some of these aren't great lecture topics, but I think some of them
would just be nice and short concise, like regular ass YouTube video essays, I don't know.
If there's something that Ben just doesn't want to do, I would like to know.
I think I said something similar in the, my Patreon post where I talked about this, like,
yeah, some of those things, yeah, would not make for a great lecture.
Like, I think in particular I said the one about phantom horn, like, discussing phantom
horn as a character, like, that's not lecture worthy.
I could make a video about it.
I don't know, to be perfectly honest, I'm very out of practice at, like, writing essays,
but I think it's something that I would like to pick up and try doing again.
So maybe I would just try and, like, write a video essay about something like that, that I
want to talk about, but that I don't have, like, a lecture on.
The lecture format, for me, is a bit of a, it's sort of a bit of a, it's sort of a bit of a, like,
I don't know, it's kind of a way to, like, get content out of, like, speaking off the cuff
in, like, a structured way, but that I don't have to, like, prescript and read off of a script about.
I always feel like my, my voice is so weird and stupid when I'm speaking off a script,
compared to, like, speaking off the cuff, it's just sort of like I'm saying something,
and I say it in the way I normally talk, so it's like, it's flows.
When I write a script, I'm not really writing the way I would speak unless I try to.
I, I feel that as well.
I feel like, yeah, like, my writing voice is different from my speaking voice,
and I guess I don't, like, I don't really do scripted content, and wait a minute.
I feel like, am I getting deja vu? Was I talking earlier this episode about, like, how, like,
did I, did I say something earlier this episode about, like, oh, but if I did
that, if I did something, like, would, like, would people still accept me or something?
Am I crazy? Do I have a nightmare? Do I have a waking nightmare?
What you're talking about?
I don't know. I feel, I feel a sense of deja vu, like, I said this already, but anyway,
what I'm trying to say is that, uh, uh, yeah, I feel like I wonder, like,
would I, would, would it be annoying? Would I, would I sound annoying? Like, either my,
my writing voice as in, like, the way that I structure my senses is stuff when I write,
or my delivery, reading on a script. When I, when I hear myself reading off of a script,
it feels awkward and stilted to me, and I wonder if others feel the same way about it, or is it
just that it feels weird to me because I'm not used to hearing myself talk like that?
Um, it could just be you. I mean, I feel that way about my script-speaking voice, and you know
what my videos sound like. I assume you remember, like, hypocrite videos don't sound like how I speak
or whatever. A little, a little different. There's a little difference. It's like,
I mean, I sometimes- The cadence is a little bit, yeah. A little bit different, yeah.
But you don't think it's like terrible. You just think it's different.
Yeah. I think that probably other people would not think that it sounds as weird as I think it
sounds when I hear myself speaking like that. To me, it sounds unnatural, but also like reading,
reading scripted content is like, that's like most of what people say on, well, that's not true,
because in video, in the video essay genre, like, that's the standard for video essays,
and like, nobody thinks it's weird. So, I don't know. I feel like I should try it. I feel like I
should try, like, yeah, write an essay, read it as a video essay, because I never really did that.
I did the closest thing I did were the rambles and the Winnie the Pooh videos, but those were not
scripted. Those were like, yeah, I was reading off of notes. I was sort of speaking off the cuff,
going off of notes that I wrote. I should at some point try to write a script and deliver it
in script and just see if it sucks or not. Yeah. There's no, like, correct way to do it.
It just whatever ends up being good. Like, I feel like I, unfortunately, I'm not good at
remembering things and keeping on track. So, if I go off the cuff, I need to do a lot of editing
afterwards to make it flow good, but I sound better and more fun when I'm off the cuff,
and I can do more funny bits in between points. I think, yeah, I think that, like,
the Mega Man lecture, the way that I delivered it off the cuff, but then I, like, cutting it down
into, like, only, like, the parts where I'm, like, speaking animatedly, and I'm, like,
no pauses, no, like, um, um, um. I really think that that captures a lot of, like,
energy. I really think that makes it a pretty engaging watch. So, I think it worked well.
And that's the same thing. I mean, they did the same thing in the ones that I said,
in the, the, the, the carry can read video and the Mike's Mike video. That's exactly what they
did in those. And I think it worked similarly. So, I think it's a good formula. It's not the only
formula. And I might try, yeah, for some of those other topics, maybe if I want to make that Phantom
Horn video, I might make it as a more traditional YouTube video essay. Yeah. That's a good question,
though. Good question.
As a quick, a quick aside, what do you think of long video essays, you know, just sort of a long
video essay that has, like, a lengthy, like, musical intro where it tries to be super epic,
and there are, like, titles and stuff? Because I don't like those. I want-
Are there?
I, I, I feel like you can have, like, a flashy video essay documentary or whatever.
But I want to get to the point immediately. I don't like it when there's, like, this implied,
like, reverence for a video I haven't even seen on, and I don't even know if it's good yet.
Can you get, I can think of one or two examples. I mean, the, well, the only thing that jumps
from, some of the action button reviews kind of have that a little bit.
There, there's, it was just sort of, like, I felt very strongly about it when I saw people on
Twitter talking about this specific video. I can't remember what it was about. And they said,
oh, it's so good. It's such a really good video. And I click on it and I'm like, okay,
lay it on me. And it's just sort of, like, slow and, like, epic. And they're not saying anything
yet. And I'm like, okay, this is the big intro for your, like, three hour long video.
You don't remember what the video was?
I didn't watch it because it was like, I was annoyed by the intro and I left.
Do you remember what it was called or who made it or what channel it was on?
No, it was just sort of a passing encounter with, you know, one of those types of videos. I'm like,
I understand that if you know what the video is about and you care about,
like, if you are making it, you know that it's going to be epic. But like,
I don't know that. I'm just some random person. I see it and I'm like, I get bored immediately.
Action button is the only example I can think of like that, to be honest.
All you really need is a good immediate thing, like summoning salt.
And they're not all like that.
Summoning salts, like video essays about speedrunning. I do, I mean, the formula is pretty
done for me at this point. I don't really care about speedrun world record,
like recaps. They're pretty cool still. But the way he structures the videos has always been good
is that he gets you like he gets the big point off immediately. Then there's the music and then
he goes into like the big the intro. Well, like it's a little bit beginning.
I'm not complaining. It's a little bit like high school essay, the way that he structures them.
Like it's not a problem. It's fine. You know, if it don't if it work, if it ain't broke, don't fix it.
But it's a little bit like, since the dawn of time, mankind has wondered how fast can you beat
Mario 64? Today, we will explore the answer. Music plays okay, and then we're in. Like that's the
intro paragraph. Yeah, like it's like it's fine. It's serviceable. I wouldn't say he's like the
best one of it. It's just the first one that comes to my head is like somebody who gives you the
initial what is this video about immediately and then has its intro and then the explanation follows.
I mean, the first few times, I was like, oh, cool. I don't know anything about speed running,
and it's so handy that there is a video that's going to teach me about it. Because like that's
it's hard to at the time he was like blowing up kind of wasn't like a big community around
speedrun, archiving and talking about at least not I mean, it's it's gotten bigger. It's gotten
bigger, like because of him. I mean, maybe maybe it would have anyway. But yeah. Yeah,
there may be were people already doing it, but I just never saw them.
No, he definitely was that like at the forefront of the like, Hey, what if I made videos explaining
speed running? And it's like, it's good content. It's a good formula. It's the kind of video
that like, I can if they make more of them, like I'll watch them because like it's good stuff to
just put on to like, sort of pay attention to the reason I say the formula has gotten old for me
or I'm done with it is just I think a lot of the same tropes are used in the way of telling the
story. Like you've got this character, this gamer who's doing these things. And then suddenly,
somebody found like, this was how the low the record got. But then you discover this gift
that saved a minute. And then people did it. And then there was this new runner and it's like
and then that same guy from before also did it. And then another challenger came. It's pretty
simple, like the beats of the story, regardless of the game, regardless of anything, the whole point
is that it gets the patterns, the patterns, the patterns emerge. Yeah, the pattern, you start
to see the code behind the matrix a little bit, I get you. And so I'm more interested in games
that I care about and know about than just, I don't know, Mario Kart Wii.
I okay, I know that you haven't seen these, but man, I got a little annoyed.
Because I made, I made some pretty mild criticism of Tim Rogers action button on Twitter yesterday.
And not everyone, you know, some people disagreed with me and that's fine. A couple of people got
really mad and like, were really like angry and defensive and accusatory towards me
for like really, really gentle criticism that I made. Like, basically, I literally just said
that one of his videos was better than a different one of his video. Yeah, I saw the tweet. How mad
were they? I don't, well, one guy saying so much. One guy told me I should die mad. And then he said
that I was accusing Tim of faking a disability, which I was not. People, people said, some people
said I was just projecting. Some people said I was a hypocrite because, yeah.
I don't know. I didn't like it. I really didn't like that attitude. I said that in my, I just said,
I said that the, I didn't like, I didn't really like, I mean, I like the Bokunopiko, not Bokunopiko,
the book, sorry, the Bokunonatsuyasumi video. I enjoyed it. I thought that the vacation
diversion was a bit longer than it needed to be. I kind of don't like, I sort of, I sort of have
the same criticism of the Tokimeki, I like the Tokimeki Memorial video. It feels more unique.
It feels more original. It feels to me like the Bokunonatsuyasumi video was sort of kind of trying
to do the same thing again. And I'm like, okay, this doesn't feel as unique. This doesn't feel
special the second time. And then the, I don't know. That's it. That's it. I like the first one
better because I feel like it was, it's the original version. And like, I don't know, man, I'm sorry.
I don't even know where I was going with that. I like those videos. They're good.
I'm deeply suspicious of Tim as a person, but like whatever, that's neither here nor there.
Why are you suspicious? I don't know. I don't like how self aggrandizing, he's self aggrandizing,
but it's in like a stealth way that I feel like, I'm, I feel like I'm going crazy because I feel
like I'm the only one that notices it. It feels like everyone thinks that Tim is like a very like
self deprecating, self effacing, humble guy. And I think that's like a trick that people are
falling for. Like, I think he's humble bragging, but he's doing it in a very like,
he's doing it in a very effective way that people are genuinely falling for it. And that makes me
uneasy. I haven't watched any of his stuff, but the only impression I've gotten of him
through people talking about how cool his videos are is that there's a lot of parasocial stuff going
on. And maybe his videos are good, but they love him when they talk about him.
Yeah. I mean, I would have agreed with that before, but like now seeing, seeing like,
you know, this was just a couple of people, but seeing like a couple people get genuinely outraged
with me over my mild take. It's like these, I don't know. I don't know. I really, all right,
I feel, I feel this way about Tokimeki Memorial and the Boku no Naziasmi videos.
Both of them lean a little too hard into they basically are about Tim. They are more about
Tim than they are about the video, the game. And that's not a sin. That's not a crime. However,
I don't like it. It reminds me. I don't know. I don't, I don't like when I get that feeling
about a video, I feel dirty. And Tokimeki Memorial and Boku no Naziasmi both give me
that feeling a little bit. Like the point here is for Tim to talk about himself. And that makes
me like gives me a yucky feeling. And then I don't know. I think he talks about himself in a way
that evokes pity while at the same time aggrandizes and mythologizes himself. And
I don't know. Yeah, it feels almost calculate, it feels calculated to evoke
a certain level of devotion of like protectiveness and parasocial devotion. And I feel like that's
what I witnessed yesterday from a couple of these people. And it has, it reinforced,
it reinforced a sort of a sort of creeping sense, a sort of vague feeling that I had about him
has been validated somewhat a bit. Right? Yeah, I mean, maybe, I feel like, I mean,
the reason I said parasocial was mostly because I didn't know what the appeal was. And nobody would
tell me. They would just say they're so good. They're so good at these videos. I'm like,
but like, why though? Well, I mean, he talks, I mean, he is an interesting guy. And he does
have interesting stories about his life. And like he's he worked in the gaming industry. And he has
genuinely interesting anecdotes to tell about like workplace conversations he had with like
Sony executives and like things that like, you know, people you've heard of like Suda,
like told him in person, supposedly, he, you know, has a lot of insight into the gaming industry.
He has a lot of opinions and he's met people you've heard of like American Johnson.
And he ties a lot of his talk about the game into like stuff about his childhood and like
growing up and like how his school, his, you know, how like one of his older classmates was
Subway Jared. I think his older brother was like friends with Subway Jared for a little while.
Uh, somebody burned down his high school gymnasium when he was like a high schooler. And that's a
whole thing. And he ties that the news hysteria around that he taught uses that to segue into
talking about like the news reporting on video game violence. So you know, he gives a lot of he
gives a lot of very, he gives a lot of very insightful analysis of the game and insight
into the industry and the people in it and the culture around it. And you know, that's all great.
Okay. And then the Tokimaki, the Tokimaki Memorial one and the Boku no Natsuyasumi one
are very much where he sort of take talks about the game in a way that he sort of opines about
like his childhood, his, his, his experience growing up, his experience with like, you know,
anime and gaming and culture and all that stuff and gets really emotional at times. And like, you
know, I, I enjoy it. I enjoyed those videos. They're good. And I just said that like, and I
just said that one, I just like the, I just like the first, I just like the first time he did it
better, you know, I got the sense that because the Tokimaki Memorial one was the one that got big,
and it was, that's the one that I found first. And it's the one that got the most views. And
it's the one that kind of blew up the channel a bit. I feel like, I feel like he tried to do it
again. He once again, he took a, like a social simulator game and he waxes very, waxes philosophical
about it. He gets nostalgic for his childhood. He goes on a whole, he goes on, goes to visit his
old school and he talks about like teachers he knew when he was a kid and stuff. And you know,
that's fine. I just kind of feel like he did it, he already did it a little bit.
Okay. That's my, that's my, that's my action button rant.
Action butt on. Yeah, more like action butt is how I would summarize my opinion.
Yeah, he seems all right, I guess. He's fine. He's fine. I don't, I don't, I don't begrudge him.
I don't begrudge him any of this. I get it. It just sort of, I guess I'm like averse to
parasocial, like, like getting to know a person. I know it's not unique to him, but like that seems
to be when, when people talk about him, that seems to be a lot of the appeal is that he talks
about himself and he's interesting. And I'm like, I don't want another parasocial person. I don't
want, I don't want that. I don't want to care about another like e-famous person anymore.
I get that. I get that. He is interesting, but also I, he does lean into the,
it's kind of every YouTuber, to a certain extent every, the point of every YouTuber is to talk
about, is actually to talk about myself. I'm here ostensibly to discuss a topic, but really the
point is that I want to talk about myself and make you love me. And Tim is very much that.
It's not like Tim is like egregious. It's just, it's just that I don't go in wanting
like to know people. I care about videos and if they're good, I'll eventually get to know them
anyway. I understand. I feel you. I feel you. I mean, I do think they're good videos. At the end,
at the end of the day, I have to concede they're entertaining.
What's your, what do you think is his best video? I'll watch that.
I would probably say, I guess I would probably say the Tokimeki Memorial one.
Okay. I mean, the Boku no Natsuyasumi one is good.
You've got to watch the Boku no Pika one.
I mean, I mean, the other ones, those two are more about, are even more about him than the others.
I mean, he talks about himself in every video, like that's a given. Those ones are like especially
like that in the ones like about Pac-Man, the Pac-Man one and the Doom one, I would say like
focus more on the game, the culture around the game and stuff. Yes, it's not like I dislike
YouTube's talking about themselves. I don't know. I feel like that's kind of why I stopped watching
ContraPoints and why I stopped watching Philosophy Tube is because I felt like
it felt a little, it made me a little sick that like, these channels have kind of become about
the person that's making them. A little bit. Not really about philosophy.
I mean, Philosophy Tube had recently a good video about the NHS and how fucked it is with
regards to treating trans women or trans people in general, which was very relevant to me. So,
that was a good one. Sure. Yeah, very personal. ContraPoints hasn't made a video in a while.
No, but her last one. What did she do? I didn't remember. The last one was the one about
Void, the drug, the stuff that you drip into the water. Yeah. And like it was fine. I didn't hate it,
but I was like, this is just a video about how you're struggling with addiction and like,
best of luck. It's a short film. Best of luck with that, but...
It was a nice short film about herself, and that's okay. I guess I'm just not interested in those.
Okay. Yeah, I think we're on the same page. Right. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I have this.
This is something that I feel about many content creators on the web.
I guess it's sort of a thing that I feel about celebrity in general,
is that it's evil. Is that it's evil and bad, and anyone who engages in it in any way should be
cast into the lake of fire. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, at the end of the day, if the videos are
good, if the reason they're known, like the stuff they make is good, regardless of like
parasocial stuff. I guess I don't mind. I guess I don't mind being wrapped up in it.
Well, let me... If it works for me. Let me... What did he do? He did the Cyberpunk 2027 one. That one's
like... That one's really big. It's... That one's like... That one's too big. That one's too big.