I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, that's the start of the episode. Go!
Hello everybody and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the only show where topics go to die.
Excellent start, excellent start.
Guests, keep it going, keep it going.
Hi, I'm a guest, holy shit, I never paint. I paint.
That's true.
Also, I have with me, right next to me, Asha A.M. Hello.
She also paints.
Never paint and Asha A.M.
Yes, yes, I have seen both of your art on Twitter and elsewhere.
You two are, I've seen your usernames around for years and years at this point.
We met at Dating Sim back in the day, many eons ago.
Right.
Back before things got weird.
You both, I'm sorry, did you say the Dating Sim was before it got weird?
No, shit got weird.
I met the world, I met like the pandemic started, I think, wait, did it?
Yeah, the pandemic started, S.
Yeah, it was pre, that was pre-pandemic.
Yeah, it was.
It released in the first week.
Because it was pre-radcon.
Yeah, it was pre-radcon four.
Actually, yeah.
Because radcon four caused the pandemic.
Yeah, yes, we all know.
As, you know, if you've read, you know, anyone who's, wait, did I, did I publish, anyone
who's purchased Road to Radcon has read the backstory and knows that coronavirus came from,
that cold corona was transformed in a horrific accident involving super aids, ISIS, and other
things that I can't remember at the moment.
I think there was a Lovecraft squid involved.
We guess that all along, we didn't even have to read it.
That was clear.
We knew it deep in our hearts.
Some twists, yeah.
But yeah, you, right, I forgot, you both wrote for the, well, you did art.
I did art hero.
You both did art.
I did art and writing.
You did art as well.
And more or less directed.
You became the director.
Well, co-director, I guess, together with Chip Weisman.
Yeah, to keep everything together for these grueling 18 months of production.
Yeah, it's funny that I've enjoyed the game and it's like, wow, this cool thing just suddenly
appeared.
I never really asked anyone involved what the process was like.
I've heard that it was a bit of a nightmare because, of course, it would be such a large
project and so many things going on.
Yeah.
But what's the story, huh?
I mean, this is an interview now.
Oh, cool.
I guess.
We did have an interview thing on the PCP channel like two years ago with Nathan.
Oh my God, I forgot.
I'm so embarrassed.
No, it's all right.
I remember, I'm sure I've forgotten some bits of it, but I remember listening to it.
I don't know.
Yeah, if you want to say anything about that.
Yeah, I mean, I think it just started in the game launch.
I guess we'll link in the description.
Link in the description to the dating sim for anyone that hasn't played it.
And also, we can link to that interview.
If you want to recapture the aesthetic and the feeling of the PCP from like three to
like six years ago, play that game.
It's a time capsule.
It will never be relevant again.
It was only relevant at like one specific time in history.
Yeah.
You know, okay, have I mentioned on the podcast before that I conscripted several of you,
the PCP dating sim guys to write the dojin.
Have I mentioned that?
I'm pretty sure you have mentioned it.
Have I made that?
You might have.
Okay, that's true.
That's true.
Yeah, it's you.
I asked you guys, since you guys did such a great job making the dating sim and it was
very funny, I thought there would be no one else.
I thought it would be a good pool to draw from for people who wanted to write some funny
gag strips for the dojin and it was you and Chip Wiseman and Ouroborista.
Yeah, yeah.
Right?
It's the name.
That was already a year ago, I think.
Almost a year ago.
It was already a year ago.
Yeah, I know.
But you've seen that I've been posting.
Yeah, they've been looking great.
A drinking moth has picked up the slack and has been making more pages and they look really good.
You know, one thing that I appreciate, especially, I'm remembering, I read the script when you
gave it to me, but seeing the pages that they're coming out, one thing that I really appreciate
is that there are jokes in the dojin that specifically reference the fact that by the
time the dojin was written, the PCP as it existed at the time of Radcon 4 was dead and
had completely changed.
Like reading the dojin, it's written for a post PCP.
It's a post PCP world, basically.
Yeah, it's like a combination of making fun of what's going on right now and how everything
has changed, but also capturing some nostalgia for the good old times.
Yeah.
Yeah, come back.
I don't know.
I wrote that little snippet of you getting tentacle molested by your tentacle crew.
Collapse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was just...
Rearadno.
There was just remembering the good old snotlock times.
Yeah, those were good old times.
I meant to do another one and I've had other things occupying me and so I have not gotten
around to my next snotlock, which I had plans for and they have been pushed back and pushed
back.
What would it be?
Would it be another Pokemon?
Yeah, I wanted to do Platinum and I had some story elements, I had some ideas for it.
I never played Platinum.
And you know, without spoiling anything, I will say that if those were to be relevant,
I would probably have to do it before 2024.
There's a time limit.
There's a deadline.
Are they making a remake?
No, that's not why.
Why 2024?
I'm not telling why.
You'll just have to guess.
There are externalities.
There are externalities in the real world that would make the ideas that I had for the
plot of my theoretical next snotlock obsolete if I did it post 2024.
I wonder what the fuck could be happening on such a year.
I don't know.
Could it be the Olympics?
No.
Could it be the FIFA football?
Well, I just don't know then.
Could it be the terrorist attack that I have planned out?
In Minecraft.
In Minecraft, guys.
Of course not.
Anyway, I just wanted to give you kudos on the script and I am really looking forward
to it being done.
Do the same.
It is coming along again.
It was in production hell for a long time, but it will, it is getting there.
At long last.
It's very exciting.
Did he plan?
He got us to Drinking Month for being a, yes, yes queen, yes queen, slay, slay.
I'm happy that still people out there, like new people coming in, making fan art and sending
it through voicemails, like, I don't know, that's, this is great.
I'm glad that the short period where the PCP had a voice, no, it had a fan art section
just got returned by the voicemailers.
There was this in 2018, there were like a few episodes where you did like a little fan
art thing, where you showed fan art that people drew and then you stopped.
Because I don't, I don't remember that.
Yeah.
No, we did do that.
I think it was, I can't remember the reasoning, but it was something to do with it being like,
there's not that much fan art.
So making a whole like thing about it would be like, I don't know, some days we just wouldn't
have any.
Maybe like the fan art was exploding around the time just because you did that.
Were those, those must have been in the Nate days, right?
I mean, of course.
Yeah.
Oh, of course.
Nate was always so like, so rigid about like the, it like, it's structured, like if there's
a segment like the segment, the segment format must be adhered to, the topics must be, the
topics must be obeyed.
I think the actual problem was that you also did the theme song contest at the same time
and also still had to ask PCP.
So yet three little segments and you just got annoyed by that or something.
Too many segments.
Very annoying.
Yeah.
And they were, yeah.
It's, it's just, I think it should have been definitely allocated just like the fan moment.
Let's look at fan stuff.
We got some questions.
We got some video, some audio.
Yeah.
Got a picture or two.
They validate us for our existence, for our stupid podcast that has been going for years
and years, which is very odd.
What can I say?
Odd, but I appreciate it.
What else would I draw to?
Like I need something.
I, you know, not, not to be a, well, I don't know if it would be a downer, but I guess
in podcast news, in terms of like blasts from the past, from the PCP history, did you, did
anyone see a DeVoo, DeVoo's tweet the other day?
I don't think so.
I saw you respond to it.
Made me mad.
Something about like the being in the Christian lecture and disavowing it or their involvement
of DeVoo.
DeVoo, DeVoo.
Yeah.
Basically DeVoo disavowed her involvement in the lecture because of, because it's mean
or something like that, I don't know.
Something stupid, some dumb shit made me, it was annoying.
It was annoying.
It's, it's, it's meaningless, but it's annoying and I don't like it.
I never felt that bad about those lectures because like in terms of, of Christian stuff,
it was more lighthearted and less like spiteful and like toxic than other things I've seen
I really think that I was not, that I was, that I tried not to be like particularly venomous.
Like I pretty much used kid gloves through the whole thing as far as I'm concerned.
I'll also say someone posted for me a screenshot of someone in, in someone asked DeVoo on Discord
like, Hey, what's up with that?
DeVoo explained her feelings about it and she said that she had not only not recently
watched the video, she had never watched the video back.
She just remembered sitting in it and she explained what she thought the problem with
the lecture was and I'm not kidding.
Yeah.
She never watched it.
She never watched it back, but she explained what she thought the problem was and her problem
with it basically is that the story of Chris Chen is a story about Chris getting harassed.
So it's basically like, you know, you know that, that, that list that's been going around
Twitter, I've seen people talking about that list of problematic authors.
I have heard it, but I haven't seen it.
I haven't seen it, but I get the impression from what people say about it, that it's stuff
like, that it's, it's stuff like fucking catcher in the rye is on there because like Holden
Caulfield is like a jerk and misogynist and stuff.
And he like stuff like that, you know, it's like, it's like, it's like problematic because
they wrote about a character who is flawed and like that flaw is a problem, right?
That's basically DeVoo's problem is that the story of Chris Chan is sad because people
were mean to Chris.
So it's bad to be in a lecture where I talk about how that happened, do a, I mean, I,
I will say that a lot of the part of Chris Chan is that the harassment is, it's like a
disabled person who can't deal well with bullying is like very funny when the bullies bully her.
So it creates a cycle.
And like, you could argue that playing into that cycle at all is not moral, I guess.
Hmm.
Well, like, you could.
Yeah, I don't think if you were a pussy.
Yeah.
I mean, there's, there's an argument there.
I don't particularly think it's worth me disavowing my sitting in watching somebody talk
about it.
I don't feel bad.
I don't feel bad in the slightest.
That's it.
I think the thing I get that like people who make content about Christian can be like real
assholes about it and don't have the nuance of realizing this is like a kind of fucked up
thing the internet did.
But I think in comparison to yours was a bit more not, I don't, you were more focused on
the comics and also it's not like you weren't like the other people who just say, oh, Chris
is a bad person who deserves to get misgendered.
I think, I mean, I, you know, I did misgender Chris in that first video, and it was, and
it was out of, it was out of talking cast sense on my own part.
Yeah.
Well, it's because I didn't, I didn't really understand because I hadn't really like read
up on like recent Chris.
I mostly knew Chris from when I had read about her like in the old days.
And I was, I was mostly just going on what I remembered.
And when I read the quickie to, you know, find out, you know, new developments, you
know, the quickie always says he, and so I just, I just kind of did that because I sort
of didn't didn't really look into it and then the content is from people who don't have
enough empathy to some degree.
No, the quickie, the quickie is written by bad, the quickie is written by bad people.
Who like went out their way to get all this information are really bad people, but it's
really interesting to learn about Christian.
Like I fell down a hole, I think like last year.
It's, it's, it was my bad.
It was my bad to take their word about that was my, that was my error.
But so, you know, but that was a mistake.
But shit, where was I going with that?
Um, yeah, I, uh, I, I think I like, I feel, I think that I feel, I felt a lot of empathy
with Chris.
I mostly saw Chris as a sort of harmless kook who is not really hurting anyone.
And I think I made that point clear many times in that lecture that like, Chris doesn't
really deserve to be harassed.
Bad things happen to her.
She was harassed.
It's not good that those things happened.
But here are some funny things that she said.
Uh, here are some, uh, here are some, here are some, here's some facts about her life as
related to the comic was hurt in the making of this story about Christian, but would you
like to hear the story?
Right.
It's really good.
It's a funny story.
I will not, I will not, I will restrain myself from, uh, exploding.
I will restrain myself from giving a full explanation of what I think about DeVoo as
a human being.
Uh, I will, I will, I will simply not simply see those teeth.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Oh, they're grinding.
All right.
You don't have to burn everything down all the time.
Just reserve it on Sunday.
Oh, wait, it's Sunday.
No, wait, no, it is Sunday.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, loser.
I mean, there's like, you know, there's like, you could wish that you changed, like, didn't
say things in a certain way, but you don't have to like, throw out the whole, uh, pot.
Right.
I, I don't understand.
You know, DeVoo messaged me a while ago and basically said the same thing.
Like, Hey, Ben, uh, I'm thinking of posting on the internet again.
And I just want you to know that I kind of don't like that I was in that lecture and
I got mad and I said, why are you telling me this?
Like, I don't care.
She, she, she worries so much about it and nobody would care.
Like, she's so worried about it.
And you know, it's really, I got to say, it's really self absorbed of her to even
think anyone gives a shit that she was in the audience.
I get, I get why nobody cares.
Man, she wanted to disassociate from his lectures completely.
Like that's, yeah, that's completely reasonable.
But that one's fair enough because he was the one doing it.
But DeVoo was just sitting there.
She was just, I mean, fucking.
Uh, mother's basement was in the audience and like mother's basement is not
having a fucking, we also have us having a fucking nobody.
Nobody gives a shit.
Nobody just wait until Jeff, just wait until Jeff's runs for senator and
then they'll pick up the PCP episodes and then he'll be fucking ruined.
Have me executed.
Yeah.
Uh, oh, well, you know, that's, that's, that's life.
So, so Ash and me have been listening to, uh, Chris story that podcast, uh, by
Asteris and Sri Lanka about the entire story of Chris Chan.
And I want to ask you, Ben, they said, they, they said they were going to have
been on an episode, I think you're both like, you're both just being like, Hey,
I'm wondering when that person's going to come on it.
And you're just kind of a standstill.
Someone needs to go.
Hey, they keep saying it every few episodes that that's going to happen at some point.
They want to, I haven't, I haven't, I haven't really talked to either of them
in, in quite a while.
You know, I think the plan might have been that I would be on like a live episode.
Like I think at some point they were planning on like traveling to the area.
And then it was like, okay, I'll be on an episode in person and then COVID
happened and then travel plans all stopped.
And so I think that might have, uh, down to go to Boston.
Well, I mean, I would be on an episode, I'd be on that any, any time I was invited.
Okay, I'll tell Sirius myself.
I think he follows me.
Yeah. I mean, does he?
Yeah, he follows me on Twitter.
Oh, that's cool.
He follows me too.
Uh, he's, uh, okay.
Uh, yeah, I don't, I don't, I mean, okay, I would like to be on, I'd like to do this.
That sounds like fun.
It is just fun hearing Sirius be very disgusted and distressed by everything Sirius tells him.
Um,
Right. Sirius, Sirius, like is the one that knows stuff and is like explaining.
Yeah.
Basically, yeah.
Okay.
I, I, I haven't actually listened to it myself.
Uh, I, I know what it's about.
Cause I mean, I'm already, I know everything.
Yeah, of course.
I don't need, I don't need to be educated.
It's fun watching a older man be horrified.
By the horrors of the internet.
Just, just horrified.
Just in general.
Yeah.
How old is, how old are you?
He just turned 40.
What's he like, 40?
It's basically dead.
Okay.
I would, I would have thought he was maybe like,
He's younger than Dan ever, Dan, I think.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't think I like Dan.
I don't think I like that he exists.
That he exists?
Are you gonna do something about it?
Maybe, maybe I will.
You know, maybe I will.
You could complain about him on your podcast.
I, yeah, I don't have any specific grievances.
I just kind of think I don't like his vibe.
And that's all I got.
Well, that's where the world stayed.
Okay.
Uh, true.
Um, shit.
Well, what else is going on?
I have just got back, this is the reason I've been on the last episode is I just got back
from a family holiday with the dog at, at Bog Neregis.
Just the dog?
You?
No, the family.
Why do you go, why do you go to all these places with silly names?
The Agunary and the, and the Bog Neregis.
Bog Neregis is a very silly name.
Agunary is also a very silly thing name.
But, uh, I don't know.
It's the UK.
What do you want?
Everything silly over here.
Going to the old, the old, the old cobbler down to the cobbler down on the, the Haberdasher
Street and an old, an old London town.
Okay.
That's the silliest thing I could think of.
Beans, beans on toast.
Beans on cobblestone.
Yes.
Delicious.
Uh, yeah, but that was nice.
It's the seaside town.
Um, when I say with the dog, it's like every so often my family wants to take the dog with them on holiday instead of just going on holiday without him.
Um, but obviously he's a dog and he's very wriggly and he very hard to control so we can't just go anywhere.
So it's usually a local place and this time it's, you know, a beach.
So he's running around on the beach, doesn't understand seawater, would splash in the seawater and lie down to keep cool.
Get a mouthful of seawater and then pick it up later because he didn't know it was bad.
So classic stupid dog stuff and it was great.
That's, that's sweet.
Uh, how old's the dog?
He's pretty young, right?
You just got him like a couple years ago.
He's like, yeah, he's all, I think he's four or five and we've had him since he was a tiny baby puppy the size of a tennis ball.
Aw.
Geez.
He's so cute and he's, he's a good boy.
It's funny that I say tennis ball because he loves tennis ball.
He's always got a tennis ball in his mouth.
It reminds him of himself as a young good dog.
Uh, um.
Yeah, I basically just wanted to mention Bognoregis because Bognoregis is such a silly name and I like saying it.
The name is wonderful.
The name of a town?
Yeah, Bognoregis.
You would think it's a swamp, but no.
Yeah, no, definitely.
The ocean's just the biggest swamp.
Well, I've been, I've been frantically working, trying to get my secret video project recorded before I move.
I'm moving at the end of the month.
Actually, I'm moving on the, I have to move out on the 30th instead of the 31st because my lease is fucked up.
I think my landlord was trying to trick me, trying to trap me into staying too late so she didn't, wouldn't have to give me my security.
I really, I genuinely think it was a trap, but I'm not going to fall for it.
But I'm, I'm scrambling.
So I have, oh God, I have only nine days left.
It sounds like nine days to record.
But to get ready to record and then to record.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It sounds like a lot of time.
You also have to pack and stuff.
Get your stuff ready.
Yeah, I do.
I have to hire a van to get everything.
I do have to arrange for a truck.
I have to arrange for a truck.
And then I have to figure out what I'm going to do because I have to be out on the 30th and I can't move in until the first.
So I'm going to have to find accommodations for two nights and I'll probably have to park the truck somewhere.
So I'll have to rent it for three days.
Yeah.
It's, it's, and I have to.
So I have to sort all that out in the next nine days or so.
Okay, but what if you just put your bed in the truck and sleep in the truck?
Your bed's already in there, right?
It would be dark in there.
It'd be like camping.
It'd be like, it's like a big metal tent.
Bring a flashlight.
Oh God.
Bring some slime that I feel like glows green.
Yeah, bring my jug of fluorescent slime and my black light to illuminate.
To read by slime light.
All the blood stains all over the truck.
Illuminated, yeah.
Okay, well that's, well that's a, anyway, so all that, yeah.
Nine day, nine days to record a video sounds like a lot of time, but I have things I want to get ready and I don't know if they're ready and I don't,
I don't know if it's going to take me one or two or three or four days to get them ready.
And then I don't know how many days it's going to take me on top of that to be doing all these preparations and stuff and sorting shit out.
And I don't even know, it's really late.
I'm really late to getting a truck.
Like I've left it way too long and it's a big problem and I might be fucked.
I'm sure I can figure something out, but I should not have waited this long to get a truck.
Do it right after the recording.
Yeah, that would be the smartest thing to do.
But would it be what Ben St. would do?
Yeah, but you know, historically, I have not done that.
So what are the odds I'm going to do at this time?
Wait, if you know the exact time you need to go, just call a thing now.
Well, not now, but like after the podcast.
Look, all I'm saying is that I might, I don't know, there's a chance that I might call up every U-Haul in town and they might all be like,
nah, we don't have any trucks.
Nah, it's too late.
It is summer.
People are moving.
It's summer and yeah, start of September is when everybody moves.
That's the busiest time.
So like, no, I really fucked up.
I've really fucked myself.
I don't know.
Time to build a truck.
I don't know exactly how fucked I am.
Do you have a large wheelbarrow?
100%.
Do you have like a really huge piece of like polka dot red?
Red with white polka dot like fabric and a long stick.
You could like have everything like sling it over your shoulder.
Oh, you know, just call an Uber and let them drive back and forth a few times.
That'd be so expensive.
Yes.
No, it wouldn't work because I can't move in until two days later.
Oh yeah, right.
You dingus.
Yeah.
Can't move in until first.
Take it straight to wherever the heck you're staying.
I just need, I need to get it.
I need to get a big truck by some somehow.
Somehow I need to get one and I need to have it for two days, maybe three days.
And then everything's all that's all I need.
That's all I need.
Is it going to be easy?
Well, good luck with that.
So easy.
Yeah, I would prioritize figuring that out before recording whatever the thing.
Yeah.
You're right.
Because even if I don't get it recorded before I move, like it's kind of fine and doesn't matter.
I just wanted to, you know, like I sort of set myself a deadline and I'm like, I don't
want to miss my deadline because like keeping deadlines is how you get things done.
Yeah.
But I mean, yeah, like whatever, that's just a psychological trick and things that are
in your mind aren't real.
You don't easily get tricked by yourself.
No.
You don't have to fall for it.
I don't.
I don't get tricked by myself.
I can't trick myself into doing things.
And that's why I don't do as many things as I should do.
You trick yourself into not doing anything.
Because I'm so smart.
And I think that's just me trying to trick myself into being productive.
But I know better.
I won't fall for it.
And I'm too clever.
Yeah.
So I've been scrambling.
I've been scrambling with that and it sucks.
Shitty week.
Shitty week, all things considered.
No.
I'm sorry.
We had a really great week.
We've got another shitty week coming up.
Oh, well, good for you.
I'm so happy for you.
We had all our friends over from the sketchy peoples.
Not all of them, but everyone who could make it.
And we had a big old meetup at my place for like a whole week.
Do you guys all live in like a similar area?
Absolutely not.
Yeah.
Who could make it?
Well, James came from Madrid.
James Tolbert.
Exactly.
The very one and only.
I know him.
Stefan Tantana from Austria.
The artist, right?
The artist almost became PCP editor back in the day.
Oh, that's right.
Back when he was green flowers.
Green fleshy flowers.
Oh.
Did he make, he made the one that was all the TV screens?
Exactly.
Yeah.
And we used this kind of a similar thing for the sketchy people later.
I think I pushed for him.
I did like that.
I really liked that sketchy like CRT monitor setup.
Yeah.
He's a professional animator, boy now working for ads and stuff.
Rules.
Wait, who else made it?
Oh yeah, Alex.
Alex C. Bell.
The music boy.
Is that Alex SSSS?
Yes.
Exactly.
Where is he from?
Germany as well.
Yeah.
The very other side of Germany from where I live.
And me.
And you.
Are you two like roommates?
No.
We're just dating.
Oh, okay.
I see.
So are you just visiting?
Yeah.
Or do you work together?
No.
Okay.
No, we have some very city long distance thing going on.
Oh, damn.
Yeah.
That's pretty far.
Yes.
Very.
Like we've been together for like two and a half years now and we first met each
other last Christmas.
In person.
Yeah.
Because the pandemic kind of just prevented everything.
Like restrictions were pretty bad for a long time.
At least on the Canadian side.
And also I had to run away from home first.
Yeah.
Is that true?
Yes.
Well, what?
Is that a thing you can talk about?
Yes.
I don't know the sum it up really other than my family's like weirdly controlling.
Okay.
My mom's a weirdo.
Yeah.
And she took advantage of a lot of me being sick to like make me dependent.
Hmm.
And then.
Sounds not good.
Yeah.
And.
Sounds not the best.
Plus I like going against kind of my religious background.
So, you know, like there's no way I would have been able to just go to Germany and see
never paint.
Hmm.
So I am and also just living them stressed me out.
And so I secretly moved out.
Okay.
Ran away.
You left.
You left a dump.
You left a ninja log decoy.
I did.
And one day your mom is going to throw a kunai at it and it's going to poo.
Shit.
Tricked.
Very nice.
Impressive.
Impressive Jutsu.
No, I literally just like went through all my stuff took the bare minimum necessities
I needed.
Hmm.
And like gone Uber and just hauled.
Oh my God.
Wait, so where did you go?
I just know I just moved to like an apartment.
Hmm.
Like I've just prepared all this in secret.
Yeah.
Yeah, I see.
I see.
And then they didn't and they like don't know where you're at.
Well, I let my sister know at this point because I trust her.
But like, I'm used to tell really anybody.
Yeah.
Where I am.
I'm just like, I'm just going to stay away.
Yeah.
Got to do what you got to do.
And then I had to like demand my IDs back because my mom kept them all in safe.
Oh, got to have your IDs.
Yeah, I mean, that's a serious situation.
That's a bummer.
Yeah.
Good for you to get out of there.
I could probably I probably could write a comic about it someday.
But it's a story.
It is a tale.
That's what all artists thought about.
And then I got as soon as a guy, I'm like, let's get ready for Christmas.
Let's go.
I mean, that was like, all right.
That was, yeah, that that had to happen before you two could meet.
I understand.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
But very, very lucky that that all worked out now.
And also that Asha could also meet some of her other friends besides me in real life finally.
It's annoying how you like make friends through internet podcasts.
And then they are like all over the world.
You meet the best people in the world and then they're all really far away.
Yep.
Yeah.
True.
Still a problem for me.
Yeah.
I guess there are a few people around that I could visit in the UK.
And you know, Europe is not very far away.
But Boston is like the hub.
That's where I need to go for like maximum like, oh my God.
But also you really wouldn't want to move to the US though because that sounds like a hellhole.
It's not that bad.
It's scary with all the news of like, I don't know, rising like completely bloodthirsty
transphobia in war.
Sure.
Like that's a little scary.
Yeah.
But what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
You know, you got to take the good with the bad sometimes.
I'll just come over and I'll like I'll buy a gun because that's easy to do and I'll just
defend myself.
Exactly.
Easy peasy.
You're sounding like an American already.
I mean, Massachusetts is not really America.
It's basically like Europe, but on the other side of the ponds.
I guess it's the only part that is not completely spoiled yet, maybe one of the few parts.
No, we're good.
I swear, I promise.
You know, I guess it's pretty fortunate that, you know, I just happened to work out that
I live in the same town now as Munchie and Kazi.
That's pretty cool.
Although, although I haven't seen them in a while, it's been like more than a month,
actually.
They've been traveling.
Yeah, they've been.
I've heard about it.
Yeah, they've been, they've been.
Summer holiday, various things.
Yes.
Yeah, I should.
I should reach out.
I think Munchie is getting back soon-ish.
I think he's back now.
Oh, shit.
Well, neat.
Cool.
But, yeah, just sort of worked out that we ended up in the same town, so that's kind of nice.
But, what were we talking about?
And next Thursday, we're going, we're both going to Canada.
So, I'm going to visit Archer first.
She visits me.
I visit her.
I actually have to, I have to go to Canada because of my university, because I have to
spend a certain amount of time in an English-speaking country, as that's part of my requirements.
I see.
So, I can do that two in one, because I'm going to be an English teacher one day.
Like, English as a second language.
Epic.
And art.
Yeah, that's going to be a lot of fun.
You know, teaching English as a second language is a job that you can do anywhere.
I mean, anywhere-
Not really.
No?
Well, the thing is, you kind of also need to know the language of the country that you're
in.
Yeah, you kind of need to know.
You know-
Get by with just some eyebrow-raising and body-movements.
At least on lower levels.
I guess on higher levels, it works better, but I couldn't teach fifth graders in Poland,
because I don't know Polish.
And if they have a question and can't speak English yet, I don't have a chance.
So, I'm kind of limited to German-speaking countries.
What would you say is the closest other language that seems like it could-
German would be similar enough that you could switch to-
Dutch?
Yeah.
Yeah, Dutch is kind of like-
It sounds very German with some English and French mixed in.
Yeah, that would work, I guess.
Perhaps.
I mean, there's also German schools in a lot of countries.
Right here.
That could all work.
I mean, I remember when I went to Poland, a lot of people that I met there were English.
They worked teaching English, and I guess maybe they did know Polish.
I didn't speak Polish, really, but I wasn't teaching English.
I was teaching physics, so I didn't really-
And I was teaching in English, so I didn't really have to-
What age were the students you were teaching?
They were just out of high school.
It was like a college prep.
It was a college prep class.
Basically, I must have been 24, 24, 25.
So, I guess that'd be like 10 years ago, wow.
It's older than I am.
No, 20, I think that was in like 2010, so I would have been like 22.
And they would have been like 18 younger than I am.
No, it was later than that.
It must have been 2012 or 2014 or something.
2016, 2018, you know.
I want to say it was about 2012.
But anyway, the kids were like 17, 18, 19, something like that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
They should know enough English by then.
Yeah, because they were basically just relearning subjects
that they had already learned in school in Saudi Arabia.
It was like a university prep class or something.
They were basically just relearning them in English.
Yeah, we have those to get ready for university
because schools don't actually teach you
already enough for university requirements and STEM stuff.
So, that's often required.
Yeah, but like I said, I didn't have to know Polish.
Because the kids didn't speak Polish.
They spoke...
Shit, what language do they speak in Saudi Arabia?
Arabic?
Arabic, yes, there you go.
Probably?
I don't remember the Saudi part of it.
I just remember you were a physics teacher in Poland.
Yeah, they were from Saudi Arabia.
They were...
They sometimes talked about the king.
As you do.
The...
Elvis?
They didn't have anime in Saudi Arabia,
but they could watch anime in Poland,
so I thought that was pretty cool.
Did they hear about it in Saudi Arabia?
Is it like a secret?
I believe so.
Yeah, I think they just didn't really have much access to it.
It's a lot of it was banned or something for whatever reason.
Yeah, but surely they could have watched it online,
like we all did.
I don't know.
I mean, this was a long time ago.
VPNs didn't really exist.
Oh, yeah, fair.
Maybe.
You probably would have had to get it on some kind of black market,
the USB drive or something.
Get it on three parts on YouTube.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Yeah, in 240p quality.
Yes.
3x4 resolution, of course.
That's how we watched the Dungeons & Dragons episode of Community today,
because it got pulled off Netflix.
Right, they've been pulling shows.
No, there was services be pulling shows.
No, this was years ago.
Yeah, that was a while ago.
This is a specific episode because it had a joke
where a character did blackface.
You know, have I complained about the episode of Golden Girls
that got pulled for blackface?
Because they straight up just aren't doing blackface
in the episode of Golden Girls that got pulled for blackface.
Wait, episode of Golden Girls got banned?
Yeah, well, it got taken off Netflix.
The joke is that Dorothy has a black friend
and the black friend comes over and B,
no, Blanche and Rose,
they're doing spa treatments, so they're wearing mud masks.
So they come out wearing their mud mask and they're like,
oh, no, no, this isn't, we're not, this isn't,
they're trying to explain.
So like, the whole joke is that they're not doing blackface
and yet that episode got pulled from Netflix.
It's a misunderstanding.
For blackface.
I mean, that's a sad thing there.
Who woke SJWs have gone too far this time?
Or it's just the producers weren't understanding.
Where's my Golden Girls?
It's a funny joke.
Okay.
It's a shame because in advance,
Dungeons & Dragons is one of the best episodes of community.
It's great.
I always love when a show does a D&D episode.
I'm a sucker for that.
You should watch Stranger Things.
I have not seen the new, I did watch the first season
of Stranger Things.
Did they do a D&D episode of My Little Pony?
Yeah, it was Boys Gamer Night with Discord, Big Mac, Spike,
and Discord like made like,
I think there's some other character there, I forgot who,
and Discord like made things real because he's Discord.
And they were like, oh God, Discord,
you're actually going to kill us with these monsters.
He said, I'm just playing.
I don't think that's what they were trying to, but okay.
Never mind.
That sounds terrible.
I think I would have hated it.
It was later season MLP.
Yeah, I've definitely have not seen that one.
Do you watch that, Asha?
Yes, I've seen all of MLP.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
100% completion rate.
Yes.
I stopped at like season five, I think.
No, no, Asha, Asha, it's like an old movie.
The last few episodes of the last few seasons are such a weird like...
They are so strange.
There's the final battle between all of the biggest villains
coming back together to team up.
Plus all of the kids from all of the different races
that come to the school and the main six
and a bunch of other people.
And they all come...
And Starshall, the birdie and all of his ancient friends
who came back from the thing when they did that.
And they all come together and they go...
Yeah, that's what they do.
It's just, I can't remember what happened.
But at the end, Twilight has a really long neck
and that's the main thing that matters.
I can't remember what happened,
but I remember that I didn't like it.
She became a long-born.
And her friends became old boys.
She's right.
The age is the very first, very last thing
is that we confirmed that Twilight will live forever
and her friends will all age and die
and she will just have to watch.
She's again making new friends.
No, she can't.
Celestia never made friends.
Yes, she does.
Pony's made for life, I'm sorry.
Once your friends die there, you can't make anymore.
What happened to Twilight in the new metal pony, Jen?
We don't know that, huh?
It's very...
I saw the movie, I don't think...
Well, she's been relegated to myth.
Yeah.
So...
I don't know what the new lore is with the new TV series.
Is that out now?
No, but there's a special, at least one.
And it's terrible.
At least it looks and sounds terrible.
The movie came out like two years ago.
What are they waiting for?
I don't know.
But at least I think the show is not on.
But I really like the movie.
I like the performances and the songs a lot.
I thought the movie was alright.
The movie had its moments.
It was neat.
I didn't hate it.
The thing is...
Which is a lot for me.
The TV special or the Netflix special that did a bit ago,
it looks horrible because it's kind of the same CG style of the movie,
but much worse than it was the animated.
And it looks very stiff and weirdly shaded.
And also they replaced all the voice actors, which were pretty good.
And yeah.
All the swabs doing it for the actors.
They didn't get Ken Jeong back to play a red guy?
It's terrible.
I guess they can't afford him.
Why would you do that?
Why would you make such a big event movie and not followed up?
Just like how they couldn't get Robin Williams to play Genie in the Aladdin sequels and the animated show.
So they got...
They got...
Ugh!
Guess we got to settle for Dan Castle and Edda.
God!
Do any of these Disney TV sequels have the original actors?
Some of them must.
I think they did get Gilbert Godfrey to continue to be Iago,
because I mean, what else was he going to do?
Well, who else could be that voice as well?
Yeah, I mean true.
But I mean, if he were as big a star as Robin Williams,
they would have just had to say fuck it and suck it up and get someone.
Fortunately, he's just...
Fortunately, Gilbert Godfrey likes doing things.
Fortunately, he's just Gilbert Godfrey and he...
Yeah, did he die?
Yeah, he died recently.
That's too bad.
Yeah, I thought so.
Did you see that episode of the Angry Video Game Nerd starring Gilbert Godfrey?
I think I saw parts of it.
As Fred Fuchs, the explorer.
Yeah, I think I saw parts of it.
I don't think I watched the whole thing.
I think it was awkward.
It was awkward.
I think I remember it was really awkward.
James is such an awkward person on camera with other actors.
He's not good at that, but it was funny just the fact that it happened.
It wasn't good, but the fact that it happened is worth celebrating.
No worth celebrating.
I'm just like, wow, wow, what?
Noteworthy.
It felt like Gilbert didn't really know what he was doing either.
Yeah.
Can you imagine getting there and having the nerd direct you?
You're like, okay, your motivation in this scene is that you hate this video game and you're really angry and you're going to yell at it while you play.
You're going to yell at it.
You're going to talk about how you'd rather put your balls in a blender.
I want you to compare the game to poop, but I want you to come up with some different kinds of poop that you could compare it to.
Different consistencies, different animals.
Okay, go.
Spitball.
Right.
James Rolfe is a character.
What do you call it?
Character director?
Yeah.
I forget the term.
I'm not sure, but I think I know what you mean.
Name Gilbert Gottfried sounds like an Elden Ring character.
I think it might just be an Elden Ring character, actually.
Yeah, my player character.
I hope not.
Hey, Gimm.
Elden Ring streams.
When?
Oh.
Well, the reason I stopped that was because no one watched it.
I watched it.
I killed Mog.
I killed Mog and there was no one watching.
I was like, what am I doing?
Damn, I'm sorry.
I was probably sleeping.
No, no, no.
I'm not trying to kill people.
That is the reason I was like, okay.
I was taking it very seriously for some reason.
I really wanted to get my whole Elden Ring experience streamed,
and I was sort of doing it even though I didn't want to.
And now I will continue it.
I do want to, but I'm still playing Elden Ring for a while.
Yeah.
I don't know when, could be soon, could be a million years.
I've only been playing Elden Ring for the past half year.
There's no other video game that's important.
That's the only one.
I'm also really bad at it, so it takes me a long time.
I saw the new Never Knows Best video about how Elden Ring is bad.
I've heard a few people say Elden Ring is sort of, it's huge
and it's impressive, but replay value isn't that high for some reason.
What was Never Knows?
I mean, he didn't say bad.
He said it was disappointing because it could have been a lot better.
What did he say?
Boss variety, bad.
The game is easy if you look up the meta and build according to the meta
and hard if you don't do that.
The game assumes you will use guides to play it.
If you do that, it's easy and otherwise it's a nightmare.
That's what he said.
He said that's bad.
That's bad design and it's bad game philosophy.
I've always felt similar just because I never like looking at guides,
but as guides and as games have come out, as the internet has grown
in relevance to gamers in the world,
the idea of looking up something when you're stuck
is something that game developers have had to work around.
They can't really make something that's secret.
If you can look it up and solve the secret,
they've got to try and make it, I don't know, design it differently.
Now, I think there is a blanket sort of acceptance that,
yeah, people use guides, they'll go on the wiki,
the wiki will be made within a month,
fully formed with everything you could ever possibly want to know about the game.
In the game, you don't really need to explain that much
and for people who don't like looking up guides,
it sucks sometimes.
I understand that there's sort of like Dark Souls
and the whole Souls series and all the FromSoft games that have come out
since then, they're sort of built around this idea of the community.
They're all kind of built around the idea that people will come together
and help each other and sort of tell each other
what they're doing and advise each other
and warn each other about danger with signs and stuff.
I like the in-game versions of that,
with the people writing stuff on the floor.
I think that's all right.
I don't like the expectation that you should go elsewhere
to complete the game experience, as intended.
Yeah, that's kind of...
I sort of had to do that my first playthrough of Dark Souls.
The interface was so opaque and the character building
was so like, what is any of this doing?
I think I did go and look up some guides for stuff
and I was like, oh, okay.
And I think the game would have been stronger.
It would have had a better overall experience
if I had not had to do that,
if the game explained itself a little better.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I played Dark Souls for the first time
after having watched the Digi Bros. Let's Play,
which is what made me realize that it was cool.
I was like, oh, look at all that.
That seems neat, and I bought it.
But I already knew a lot of the secrets.
I knew about Ash Lake.
I knew about what you should put your stats in.
Yeah.
And I had a very smooth time,
but I could imagine myself getting extremely frustrated.
If my first try at a character was a complete failure,
I put the stats in the wrong things
and it was extremely difficult going forward
and it would have been better for me
and much quicker and more efficient
if I deleted my character and started again.
But I wouldn't have known to do that
if I just played the game
and I would just assume that it was too hard.
Yeah, I picked it up blind
and I just fucked around in it
and I was like, what am I doing?
What am I doing wrong here?
I had to resort to a guide
and it was not fun to have to do that.
TBH.
I think guides as part of a gameplay experience
are at best neutral.
At best they don't negatively affect things,
but they don't improve as an experience.
I feel like it's always cooler
if you play the game
and then you come up with these things yourself
and then if you check the meta,
it turns out that the thing you naturally came to the conclusion of
was the way you should do it.
I admit, I think I use guides a lot,
but I'm also very new to playing video games in general
because I grew up with parents who didn't like video games
and I never had any consoles or computers that were good enough
to play most games.
So it already takes me probably five times as long
as most people to beat most games,
so I'm fine with having a guide
just to save my precious lifetime.
Some games just really waste your time
if you don't have that.
I looked up a giant map of the Hollow Knight thing
just to kind of know where I have to go
because it gets confusing at some point.
Hollow Knight is very...
Actually, I don't know.
I can't remember my first playthrough of Hollow Knight.
I don't know if I had seen content of guides before.
You streamed it too.
I streamed it and I had stream chat helping me sometimes,
so that would, I guess, count as extra help.
I was playing Mega Man ZX Advent
and ZX and ZX Advent have like...
They're sort of Metroidvania.
They kind of have big open worlds
and that's cool and I appreciate that,
but I also kind of just wanted to beat the game
and I didn't want to spend a lot of time
like kind of wandering around looking for stuff.
I know that's kind of the point of a world like that
is you kind of wander around and find stuff,
but I kind of just didn't want to spend the time,
so I did use a guide for a lot of stuff
that just told me like, where do I go next?
What's my next objective?
And I probably did hurt my experience of the game a little bit,
but also I got through it a lot faster and that's valuable.
It's just like watching a movie and putting subtitles on
because all the characters have weird accents
and you don't speak the language
and it's not your first language
and just helps you experience the movie better and quicker
and easier.
I don't know if it's like that,
because if you don't speak the language, you literally can't.
No, I mean like...
Experience the movie.
I guess, yeah.
But it's just making your experience easier
or like a little more accessible.
It doesn't ruin it necessarily.
I think...
I think I'm coming from a perspective where like,
I played PlayStation games,
I played Rayman or whatever,
I played Spyro.
When you play Spyro, the level is very small
compared to Elden Ring,
so you go around, you collect as many gems as you can
and then it's like, oh, there's five gems left
and I feel like I've been everywhere.
Where is it?
You run around the level,
you check everything twice, three times,
and it doesn't actually take that long to do it.
And there's a chance that you could actually figure out
a place that you maybe could glide to
that you haven't seen before and is that possible?
Oh my God, it is.
There's the gems.
You 100% completed the level without using a guide.
But if I was stuck on like something that would take me,
I don't know, 40 minutes, an hour, two hours,
three hours to figure it out for myself,
I am going to get tired
and I'm just going to YouTube like,
where do I fucking go?
So for small little games,
guides are not necessary at all.
And I prefer a few failures,
a few like little trials and errors to get to the end
and 100% complete.
But for something huge,
for something that's even like middleingly large,
or for a game that sucks, guides are great.
Guides are a good time saver.
Using a guide on Mega Man ZX
was the difference between me completing the game,
you know, like knowing where to go
instead of having to sort of wander around
and like check every door I've been through
and like talk to every NPC I've talked to before
and see if their dialogues changed
and see if any of the old doors have opened now
and like try and remember,
oh, was there a yellow door over there?
Oh, I should try that again, see if that leads anywhere.
It was the difference between me beating the game
in like seven hours versus like 12 hours.
And I just wanted those five hours.
I wanted to save those five hours.
I don't want to spend them fucking around.
Yeah.
You can only play so many video games.
I did, but I, you know,
I understand that by doing so,
I robbed myself of the joy of discovery going,
aha, I found it.
When Silk Song comes out,
I want to try to play it completely blind.
Oh, Silk Song.
Because it's going to be new
and nobody's going to have played it yet.
I'm going to play it first day and like know nothing
and have the pure experience.
That's a good one.
Is there any news on that?
Do we know when that's coming?
It's supposed, I think like a month ago or something,
there was an announcement and like a new short trailer
and they said it's supposedly coming out
within the next 20, no,
within the next 12 months.
Within the next 25 years it will come out.
No, within the next year, apparently.
Maybe.
We don't have a date though.
I feel like that's always the Silk Song news,
is like they've released
another three seconds of video footage.
That was the first news.
We don't know anything else.
There's this one channel on YouTube
called Daily Silk Song news
and they upload a video every single day.
Just like a tiny like
30 second thing.
Welcome to Daily Silk Song news.
Today there has been no Silk Song news.
And they talk about
every single snippet that releases.
It's a good channel.
And yeah.
I hope on like a day
when there's actually big Silk Song news
they forget to upload or like they give up
on that day and will be very sad.
Oh, I guess you know what?
You know what I've realized?
I think it's when it comes to
like a video game,
like what the appeal of the gameplay is.
If the point
of the game is about
figuring stuff out,
like a point and click or a mystery game
sort of thing.
Guides are
absolutely damaging to the experience.
If you get like
a little impatient or frustrated in a point and click game.
I mean some point and click games are just
obtuse to the point of
absurdity and it doesn't make sense how you
could figure stuff out. But some of them
you can. You just have to think
and
like it's so much
more satisfying coming to
the correct conclusion in a game like that
instead of using a guide.
But if you're playing a game
where the appeal is
like Minecraft, right?
The fun of Minecraft is building stuff
and
mining and
crafting and stuff.
Figuring out the lore or
rather just how you do
things is
completely impossible.
Like you can, there are some
fits of clues.
I guess they changed a bit.
They have like a recipe book now.
They changed a bit, but like if you wanted to know how to get into the Nether
you would just, and you had no
Minecraft experience, you would come across
you would have to be lucky enough
to come across like an unfinished Nether portal
and then
put the pieces together that you need to finish it
and then set it on fire so that you can go through
so you can get like access to a whole other section
of the game with all these important items that you need
to do all these other things.
They've only put these unfinished Nether portals in so that you have
a kind of a guide
that you play as one or something.
It was just expected to go to the Minecraft wiki
that was
part of the game kind of.
But that's the reason it's fine in Minecraft
because like
that experience of
understanding how the game works
is not as satisfying as finding a cool cave.
You don't need to do like
any wiki searching to know
what a cool cave is when you find it.
You know all the, you can look up
a guide on all of the things. It's just
whether you find them or not. That's the fun part.
Yeah.
Nobody agreed. Like
to the same extent if I want to look up
hey how do I get to this specific
boss in like
Elden Ring or Hollow Knight or whatever
like I can look that up and I still
have fun fighting that boss
that doesn't really take away from it that much.
It always depends on what you want
out of it and
what's like, what your time is worth
spending on certain tasks
in the game.
I really care for my time
which is why I play RuneScape
and I mine
iron for hours upon
hours every day.
I have no idea what RuneScape is. I heard the name for years.
I have no idea
what it even looks like.
I've seen it and I have a vague idea.
I have a general idea of what sort of things you do
in it. I can pitch RuneScape.
RuneScape is
an MMO
like a massively multiplayer online
role-playing video game, but instead
of being based off of World of Warcraft
like everything else, it came out
like before that or around the same time
and it's more based on
point and click
adventures and dungeons and dragons
where the world
is
it's more lived in.
There are NPCs that just talk about stuff
and the game is not about combat necessarily.
So there's fantasy things
but
the core of RuneScape is that you're in
just a fantasy realm
and there's lots of different skills you
can get higher.
There are many quests you can complete.
So you're running around as a little
video game guy and fight things too?
You run around
and you can do anything.
Combat level is like
a thing that you need if you want to live
in certain areas obviously. Enemies will throw rocks
at you, they'll punch you.
Certain quests require you to
defeat demons and vampires and stuff.
For some reason I always mentioned it
as like a puzzle game, like Candy Crush.
I don't know.
Something about the name. I told you about it?
Maybe? I don't know. I imagine
like a Candy Crush but with stone plates
that have runes on it. I thought that's what
RuneScape is. No.
No, you're a little polygon dude running around
doing medieval literature. You're a little
low poly. It's like a Java based
demo. Let me find
it's like the lowest poly models
you've ever seen. The lowest poly
this
is an okay image.
Here's an image of a RuneScape
character
who has a lot of levels actually. Fishing.
Fishing in a little pond.
That's adorable.
They're gonna get some fish and then they can
if you see the mini map in the top right
there's like the fishing spots there.
It looks like there's a fletching
or an arrow shop you can buy arrows from.
Thank you.
It's a quaint adorable
and
very, very, very, very, very
time consuming, old style
video game that I love playing. Does it still exist?
At the moment. I don't know.
Old school RuneScape does exist
as like a
like the fans wanted the old version
of the game because they updated it as time
of course.
And the old version of RuneScape
exists and is like
in like
what do you call it, active
support. There's like a team
that supports it.
And yeah, I've
I remember talking about RuneScape like a couple weeks
ago. I don't know whether I mentioned that I'm
on like a stupid
challenge run
that involves being extremely inefficient.
I think you did, but I mean
I don't remember the details.
Yes.
Because it's all gobbledygook to me.
It's all nonsense.
Yeah. No, I did
I do remember saying it, but basically
what I'm doing right now is I'm
mining iron in the mining guild.
I go up to a little ore rock
and I click on it and my guy does
a little animation. He gets an iron ore
or she does because it's she.
I change the gender. You can change your gender
in this game. You just walk to a little
witch and she says, what do you want?
I will change your face and you're like, okay.
I mean, that's just how it works in real life, right?
Yeah, basically.
And
actually this is funny. There's a quest
in RuneScape
that requires you be a female
to access a certain area
so that you can
do something. I can't remember what the quest was.
But
all of the characters who choose female
the beginning of the game
don't need to change their gender to do that.
But every male character is
force found by that quest.
So that's funny.
They have to be a female for like
a few minutes.
Got them.
Damn.
Yeah, but the moment I just
passed the point where I've got
50,000 iron ore in my bank.
I've collected
over 50,000 and I'm going for
100,000 because
that's the amount of iron ore I need
to make enough steel bars
to get my smithing level high enough
so that I can smith rune itor
into bars.
And that means something to somebody
and it certainly means something to me.
You're welcome, RuneScape
knowing audience.
Well, that sounds great.
You gotta do it.
You gotta rune it. Yeah.
I wanna do it.
Like runar or morse.
I always wanted to do it whenever
since I was a tiny little speck in the ground.
Since I was one atom tall.
Here's what I can say.
If I were you,
I'm sure I would feel the same way.
That's the most
condescending generic way I can agree
with someone.
So you're welcome for that.
Here's another image.
This is showing
in the chicken farm.
Somebody has been killing chickens
and getting the raw chicken so they could
make roast chicken. Lucky.
Ooh, that looks tasty.
Look at all the bones.
You can make some good
stock out of them bones.
There's some giant bones in those chicken.
Yes.
Full of femurs.
That bone goes from
it just replaces
its entire spine.
Everything drops bones
if you bury the bones
you get prayer experience
because you're giving it a proper
send off.
Prayer experience allows you to gain buffs
in combat or other things.
To protect you from magic
damage or melee damage
and things like that.
So if you kill
a million chickens, you may as well pick up
their bones and give each one a burial
and get prayer experience for it.
Cool.
That's what I do.
That's what I do with my time.
Chicken mass grave.
We can only do it one at a time.
They're all tiny little graves.
Do you get more prayer points
for a bigger creature
being buried? Literally yes.
If you get giant bones, if you kill giants
and you bury their bones, the mass
equates to more burial experience.
It's a bigger funeral. That means it's more
sacred.
If you get dragon bones, you bury those
as well as even more prayer experience.
Of course.
That's just how
religion works in real life as well.
God just likes
the amount of bones.
Bigger souls, please.
Yeah.
Good.
I agree.
Runescape.
What's it called?
World of Warcraft Fantasy.
It's based on
Tolkien or something.
That's what I wanted to come on this episode.
That is why
you pitched yourself as coming on
because I talked to a Tolkien.
Yeah.
You said you're a Tolkien guy.
No. I saw that episode
titled two weeks ago. It was mid-journey
and Tolkien. I already expected it
to be like, you always do that thing
or I guess Elgazar does the thing where
you do something for like five minutes
out of three hours and that's in the title.
Look, blame Elgazar
for picking the titles.
That happened with Hollow Knight 2 once.
I was really excited. He had like a whole
Hollow Knight thumbnail and Hollow Knight in the title
and Gip mentioned her stream once.
I don't know what to tell Elgazar.
We don't tell Elgazar what to put
the title on. No, no, no. It's fine.
I mean, it's working. I guess it's working.
It's clickbait and it's just
bait and there's no content.
No, it's great. You've been duped.
It's perfect never paint bait.
Yeah, I guess. You're a sucker.
What the procrastinator is talking
about Tolkien? Like the one thing
I know about? Talking about them?
Incredible.
Wow. I don't really know.
No, I really don't know that much about it
other than I read the books
when I was in like
high school, middle school.
Yeah, I'm insane.
That was a long, long time ago
and I saw the movie.
I don't even think I saw all the movies.
I think I saw the first two movies.
And you know, everybody likes the movies
and I hated them.
I remember viewing
well, I remember viewing them with disdain.
I remember thinking that adaptations
were like cheap and not art
and that these movies are just a...
Yeah, I remember turning my nose up
and being like, ugh, they just remade the
book. Like, why?
The book is already good.
I know. And like, clearly
culture has...
I was not vindicated by time
on that one. But that was my take.
But that was my take back in the day.
So your problem wasn't that they
were too different from the books.
Your problem was that they were just the same thing
and it wasn't
creative enough.
That's interesting.
I was about to say that's a really hot take
but then I'm like, maybe not.
It's still...
It still is.
Because these movies are kind of like universally
praised
mostly for being like, oh, this is like the
ultimate adaptation. This is the best thing
you can do. This is
perfectly true to Talking Spirit
which is like not completely true.
But...
Yeah.
Look, when Aragorn punched
that guy and went slash
kill that orc
I enjoyed it.
Did you know that when Aragorn punched
that guy, he broke his toe?
No. It's when he kicks
the helmet. Yeah, I know.
Did you know that when he kicked the helmet
he deflected the blade?
Oh, wait.
The actual fact is that when Aragorn
kicks a helmet or an orc head
in the movie, he actually broke his toe
and they kept that take in and he screamed
and...
You screamed in character.
He screamed and just fell on his knees
and it was like, ah, so sad.
Doesn't Aragorn
kill the mouth of Sauron
in the movie that he doesn't in the book?
Yes, it's horrible in the movie.
It's only an extended edition, but...
And it's literally just him like killing a
peaceful ambassador. Yes, it's great, right?
Like, sure, he's from the evil empire
but like, they sent you this guy to negotiate.
Like, that's what the
fucking Trade Federation does
to the Jedi.
He's one of those fucking
Asian stereotype
lizard people.
He's as bad as fucking...
What's his name? Anakin.
Remlazar.
No.
Trade
Federation. We're talking about Tolkien.
I gotta look up what the aliens in Star Wars are.
Trade Federation.
Aliens.
Lexivarack?
I think. Is the...
The dudes?
That's not even a really constructed language.
Newt Gunwreck. That's the one.
Aragorn is just as bad as Newt Gunwreck.
Okay.
I don't remember this
from the film.
What are you talking about?
What is the mouth of Sauron?
At the black gate in the end of the third movie.
Only an extended edition.
There's a guy coming out with an ugly face.
I haven't seen the extended editions, so that makes sense.
They're pretty good, except that scene.
I don't know the scene where they jump over.
I remember seeing the mouth of Sauron
and thinking that he looked very striking.
I mean, I thought he looked cool.
I mean, the artisan of these movies.
These movies are incredible in general.
That's the best thing about them.
And the music.
I learned from Tolkien Untangled
that the mouth of Sauron is...
What is he?
He is a black Numenorean.
Exactly.
And now I didn't know that.
He's a dude who works for Sauron
for some reason.
We don't know a lot about him.
But there must be more of them.
But there are others, too.
He's not the only one.
We don't even know if the mouth of Sauron
is one character or just a title.
Like...
That guy. I thought that was the Witch King.
No, Witch King.
It's like a hollow Nazgul dude.
Witch King is a race.
There's a Tolkien Untangled
Black Numenorean who's like a woman
who is like this witch
that has these black cats
and her cats are like her spies.
And she...
That's Queen Baruthiel.
But we don't...
I don't actually know...
I don't actually know that she's a Black Numenorean.
I don't think we know a lot about her.
I think that...
He said she was a Black Numenorean.
That might be it.
You don't have to take it up with him.
I'm not even familiar with Queen Baruthiel.
Queen Baruthiel is one of these things.
It's just a name drop in the Lord of Rings book.
Like Aragorn says something.
To walk from Moria, we need eyes
as good as the cats of Queen Baruthiel.
And...
Talking himself didn't know who Queen Baruthiel was
when he wrote that probably.
That's why he was...
That's why he was writing mostly.
And then maybe he came up with
Queen Baruthiel.
He would brighten it in the
unfinished tales.
He's like, oh yeah, she's like a witch
with these cats that she communes with.
And she sailed on a boat somewhere.
Or something.
I don't know.
God, I love talking.
It's been my mainstay.
Just like George Lucas.
The music they listen to
in the cantina is called
Jizz.
What else?
You seen that
Tuesday
JK Rowling versus
George Lucas?
I haven't actually.
Hold on, I'll post it.
It's about retconning things.
It's the two of them.
The stupid dumb shit they come up with
about their stories after the fact.
Hang on.
We need Tuesday
JK Rowling
George
How do you spell George?
Geodude
Like any other George.
Here we go.
It's in two images.
You're going to have to look at both of them.
Sorry, I brought this topic up.
We have to discuss it thoroughly.
We have to
dissect every morsel
of content
out of this.
The thing is, is that all
actually George Lucas
because the extended Star Wars
was like all different authors doing stuff
and George Lucas just waving it
and be like, yeah, it's okay.
I don't think these are real.
I don't think there is an actually
I don't think Qui-Gon Jinn's hairdresser
is actually a blue rat named Fungo
hairstyle.
I can believe that.
But all the
Star Wars shit, all the novels
are written by different people
and
back in the day before Disney took over
George Lucas was just like, yeah, sure, it's all canon.
I don't care.
Let's just probably make it canon.
You might be right.
I mean, I think George does say
goofy shit like this, but yeah.
Some of the goofy shit is probably
from like the extended books
that other people wrote. That's fair.
All of the things J.K. Rowling
is depicted saying here are exactly
one-to-one. She said them
for sure, definitely.
I hope so.
There are no Jews at Hogwarts, but don't worry.
All the main characters are about
Zion.
But they talk about it off-screen
all the time. They're always
really mad at Palestinian terrorists.
They're getting fucking fuming.
They can't even
they can't even fight against
the master red corner J.R.
Tolkien who's literally the best
red corner in the world
and also it's like
kind of one of the coolest
things about his work.
Well, okay. Do you know how
in the Hobbit Bilbo gets the ring at first?
Basically, he walks into a cave
he finds the ring just on the ground
doesn't think much of it. Then he meets
then he meets Gollum
and has like that riddle
game with him.
You know, yeah, I forget the details
but I think I've heard
he stumbles upon.
He stumbles upon the ring
and finds Gollum
Gollum wants to eat him and they make
like a bet. Hey, let's do a riddle game
and if I win
you have to, Bilbo says if I win
you have to show me the way out. If Gollum wins
Gollum eats him and
Gollum had this ring but lost
it earlier and Bilbo found it
didn't tell Gollum.
Towards the end, Bilbo runs out of riddles
says like a fake riddle
what do you have in my pocket
and Gollum has to guess exactly
the ring and
then Bilbo in the end just runs away
from Gollum and
yeah, basically
he got this ring
kind of dishonestly and like in not a
very cool or honorable way
but that's not actually the original
version of the story because
in like the 1937
version of the Hobbit that got first published
that story was completely
different and that story
he met Gollum and Gollum was
much more friendly and goofier character
and he actually
bet the ring in the riddle game
like Gollum was like hey if you
win this riddle game you can get the ring
and Bilbo won the game
won the ring
honorably and they said goodbye
and Gollum showed them the way out I think
even. I'm not entirely sure
but then
that wouldn't make sense with what the ring
ended up becoming. Yes, exactly
then the publishers came and were like
okay, JR
talking we want more
Hobbit stories and he was like
can you publish my silver ring?
They were like no
it doesn't have Hobbits in it
that's weird stuff
give us Hobbits and he was like okay
I guess I can write the Hobbit too
and then he took like 15 years to write
and while he was writing that
and turned out that the ring might be
actually way more important than he thought
because Tolkien didn't plan out it
he just wrote and explored
the world as he was writing
and
so while that was happening
he was like okay this is too important
the ring is too important. Let's
republish the Hobbit
change that story but
the original story in the original
published version is still in the book
the story that Bilbo tells to the other dwarves
when he meets up with him again
so he justifies
to the dwarves
that yeah that's how I got the ring
it was all
he also says it to Gandalf I believe
and it was all honorable
so now it's not just that he got the ring
dishonorably but he lied about it
he lied about it and that's the original
story that went into Bilbo's diary
which became the published Hobbit
and so most of the Hobbits
are back again because it's framed as
this is the record that Bilbo wrote down
of what happened
so most of the Hobbits
in the Shire at the beginning for Lord of the Rings
have heard Bilbo's stories
from that book
but they've heard the fake story
from the 1937 Hobbit
so it's that
both versions are canon in the story
that rules so much
and basically only I think Frodo
and Sam and Gandalf
know the real version of the story
and it's so thematically fitting
because Bilbo
only hours after finding that ring
felt the need to lie about how he got it
like he felt the need to justify
his ownership of the ring
it's already influencing him
there was no real reason
that's a clever retcon
that actually works with how
he intended to use the ring going forward
that's really cool
and there's so much like that
he kind of
I mean all of the Legendarium
all of the Lord of the Rings
Hobbits and everything and stuff
all is kind of
there's multiple versions of it
and it's all kind of canon
or canon is not even important
because it's all told stories
and written down manuscripts
from people in the story
that got translated many times
and given to different people
it's kind of beautiful
I love it for that
so like the story
canonically is written
or finished by Frodo
the Lord of the Rings
but Frodo wasn't
at every event
so he had to hear it from
from everyone else
I'm pretty sure the final version
that Tolkien came up with
is that the Lord of the Rings
and the Hobbit are Bilbo's diary
Frodo's
reports of the events
of Lord of the Rings
combined with
I think after
Frodo gave the book to Sam
when he left to the Grey Havens
and Sam completed it and I think Sam's family too
and then the book was given to Minas Tirith
to Gondor
where like historians
kind of added annotations
and changed a few things
and like added some
information where it was needed
and so on
and it got like stored there
and retranslated in other parts
until I believe
in one version of the Legendarium
there's actually like an Anglo-Saxon
human person from the real world
finding that manuscript
and transcribing it into
old English
and Tolkien pretended to be
the final translator to translate it
into modern English
that's commitment
it's all really fucking neat
that commitment to the bit
that is great because it's like
from fantasy
fantasy
is like stories from history
that were passed down by word of mouth
and then written down and translated over
years and they become myths
and he made his own myths
and then came up with a canonical reason
why magic exists then
but doesn't in the real world
because it's like
it's a story
it's like was there
Sauron, huh? What?
Could it have been just a guy with a big axe?
I mean
sorry if this is a
shit everybody knows already
but are you all familiar
with
oh god
The Princess Bride
No
I also don't
Okay, well
Aasha have you read the book or have you seen the movie?
I've seen the movie only
I haven't read the book, I've read parts of it
The movie
is framed
as
the
grandpa is
reading the story
to his grandkid
and it's sort of every now and then
it jumps out of the story to have a conversation
between the grandpa and the kid
and the grandpa is like
nah, let's skip past this part
nah, this part's boring
nah, you don't want to hear the romance stuff
or whatever
Well, the book
which is much less famous than the movie
is sort of like that
the book is written
as like an edited manuscript
of another fantasy
sorry, it's written where there's
notes in red ink
written by the quote unquote editor
this part went on
for pages and pages describing
the lineage of this
and nobody cares, so I cut it out
like a fake
meta
the author wrote it
with these fake editors
notes about how I cut this part out because it sucks
I
haven't read the whole book, but I've seen it
and it's got a similar
meta
framing device to it
I mean, Tolkien's
not many people have read the
not many people have read the book
I think a lot of people don't even know that it is based on a book
sounds good though
yeah
I mean, Tolkien's original intention
was to some extent to
create a mythology for England
because he felt like England doesn't have
its own fairy tales or myths
that just belong
to England because of its history
of the nomadic invasion
and
a bunch of stuff going on
I don't know the history facts well enough
yeah, I mean we were just like a bunch of peasants
sitting in mud
and flooring mud around
and then we got invaded like 18 times
I guess we have culture now
I mean, English got kind of banned
for a while and then mixed with French
and
a lot going on
but over time
I guess we're Anglicans
now over time he kind of went into the direction
yeah, I'm just going to
have my own
sub-creation
he wants his own
what we do now all the time
it's so fun but he was like
this is my own thing
and it's not directly based on our history
or whatever
it's not super supposed to be our world
but our world on a different
imaginary
stage or layer
and
it's
really cool
of course
he commented once
that whole thing that he wanted to be
a mythology for England
and that means that when you make an adaptation now
you can't possibly cast
BPUC actors in it
because all the fans would come and say
no this is a mythology for England
you can't do that
you can't do
black fish and chips
black people in England
can't be happening
it's not true
no
thank you
so brave of you to say it
so brave of you to say it and risk cancelling
no I'm parroting
a lot of stupid people I've heard
over the past few months
there's a tv series
being made right?
or is that also a Game of Thrones one
being made?
there's apparently
several sort of perspective
Game of Thrones side stories
series that are like in production right now
that dude should just finish his book
what damn it
but he's like
involved in all of them a little bit I think
he's involved in all of them
and
also he seems to be
like he's
according to his updates it seems like he's
yeah
his updates seem to suggest that he's more
focused on the tv shows
finishing
it's a classic like I'm gonna start a bunch of new
projects because I want to procrastinate
really hard on this one that I have to do
and I know I have to do it
I mean
what if I did anything else
what if I did a writing game
I mean song of ice and fire
we should get George R. R. Martin
from the podcast
yes Ben have you seen that
so that he doesn't have to write his book
have you seen a Preston Jacobs video where he like
figures out how much he has written
since
that was really depressing
I'm glad you're a Preston head
I am
I don't
he
he's a Game of Thrones guy
he is kind of known in community
as a little bit of like tinfoil
because he has really advanced
crazy theories
all kind of make sense though
the man is a misunderstood
genius
the man knows George better than George
knows himself
maybe we'll see
history will vindicate you Preston
no history won't because
the books are never gonna get done
we'll never know
we'll never know if Quentin survived
oh god
true
but he made a video
he made a video where he basically went back
through like everything George
has ever said on the subject
and like pretty much constructed
a theory of like okay based on
everything George has said how much do we think
he's actually written and the answer
is like some
but like maybe like a quarter
of a book now the worst thing is that
he kind of figured out that George has
probably written anything for like the first
like eight years
after the last book
because he wrote too much for the
last book he had like a few chapters
left over and so
like he could kind of just
said yeah I have so this much done of the new
book but he could have just referred to the old chapters
that he already had done
from the beginning and
he probably hasn't really started writing
anything new until like two years ago
oh boy yeah
and he's well
busy
yeah and he also said that he doesn't
want anyone else to finish it
when he's dead so
I wonder how's that gonna work out
come on just let
someone else finish it
come on you're gonna be dead
someday
who cares
who cares at that point
Preston tries to finish it right now
I want to on the subject
of black characters
in Tolkien I did see
that one dwarf
and I was enraged
she's barely got a beard
it's bullshit
it's bullshit the story
clearly says that female
dwarves have beards just like the men
and non dwarves can't tell them apart
and then they get the oh they get
oh here's a girl dwarf
and she's got oh she's got these delicate
little sideburns oh these cute little sideburns
she's got a beard guys no
no that's not what it's
that's not textual
you cowards
okay the thing is
the thing is
it's kind of debatable
if that's actually in the books because
of the nature of how Tolkien's
writing works
there is a book where he says that
all dwarves, male and female
get born with beards
and that's fine there's also stuff like
oh dwarves never get their beards cut off
because that's like really
shameful for them so they don't shave or whatever
the thing is
yeah that's in one of the thing that's like
somewhere published in History of Middle Earth
so not even in any of the main
big publications
in the Lord of the Rings
it just says that
dwarf men and women are like
close in appearance
not specifying more
and there's also different
older writings where
he says that's another retcon by the way
do you know how Gimli in the movie says
oh there's like a legend that
a dwarf and women get born
oh no like dwarves just get born
out of stone we don't even have women
that's actually something that Tolkien
wrote in an earlier version of the same
universe
back in the day dwarves were just like
constructed stone beings that were also
I mean that's how they were originally
made by
what the fuck is that
yes Aula made
them out of stone
the first dwarves
yeah the seven dwarf fathers
we don't even know if there were any women
where did the first ones come from
it's all a little unclear
yeah exactly
I think Tolkien hated
Snow White the Disney movie
a lot and his daughter really loved it
and
he had a big problem with that
but yeah and that's a thing
there's like multiple versions of that
I think in a Tolkien book that
just came out this year or last year
by the way
there's new Tolkien books coming out every year
because there's so much writing to it that still gets
published there's still not done
from his like from his
like old like journals and stuff
yeah yeah there's still
material there's a new Tolkien book coming out
this year called the fall of Nmenor
which will have
more original text probably
that haven't been published
there's so much
but yeah and in that
new book it specifically states
all male
capitalized dwarves have beers
and that's one of his latest writings so
it seems like he changed his mind a few times
but in general I agree
with you I think it's cool
I just want to be mad
that's what the internet is for
listen
obviously I'm actually just mad
that she's black but I can't say that
so I have to pretend that it's about the beers
okay?
let me have it
yeah that's the point actually
I actually also would like to see
dwarven women of beards
that would be great and
yeah I agree
even if there's a textual
reasoning for it I still think it would have been cooler
if she just had a beer
they could still make
they could still give her feminine features
they could give eyelashes or whatever
they did add a bit in the Hobbit movies
there's a few background dwarven women
that have bigger sideburns
at least and a little bit of chin and beard
but
it really doesn't make sense why beards
are a thing anyway
why doesn't hair come out of the
chin on some people and not on others
why the hormones is that
is that why?
what's the purpose of this?
I don't get humans they don't make sense
keep your chin warm
women need their chin warm
everyone not likes a warm chin
no they don't
women should be cold all the time
and God said
you know
when Eve ate the apple
God said women will always be cold
in the office the AC will always be
turned up a little too high and they'll complain
about it forever
and so it was
on earth as it was in heaven
I read the bible
makes sense
it's the only mythology for england that I need
there's a weird thing going on with the new tv show
that
they casted a few B.P.C. actors
for it
and that's
one of them was an elf
that's probably the most debated one
but
I just read it don't care
I think middle earth is big enough that it's possible
and
I mean there's like
I've been watching this guy's videos
and I know there's a bunch of different elf
tribes
there's a lot of different elf groups
I don't think I can list them all off
they have many different names as well
there's like way more regions
in middle earth than
just the ones that you hear about
in lord of the rings
it's all underwater
there's a ballerian
and numinor
ballerian is bigger than middle earth
that we see in lord of the rings
and it's all underwater and gone
numinor as well
wow middle earth is a planet
well
wait no middle earth is
the plate
middle earth is like the land
the planet is called
I forget what the world is called
I got it
I think outer actually
includes all creation
including space
and everything around it
I see
but middle earth is like
the land in the middle
and it used to be actually a flat earth
and then turned round at some point
wait what did I want to get to
oh yeah
the elf of color
the EOC
yeah exactly
the thing is melanin
like doesn't even
it's not even a thing
I mean the thing is
what do you mean
middle earth is not based on science in most ways
the most scientific thing about middle earth
is like the language development
that's like because Tolkien knew
a lot about that and he made sure
that that's all correct and actually
really detailed
the sun of middle earth is not our sun
it's like a magical glowing
fruit from
one of the two trees that lit the world
before sun and moon existed
and it's like a magical glowing
fruit that gets carried by an angelic being
over the planet
and then like under the
I guess under the flat earth plate
and then on the other side up again
and the sun has kind of like
a relationship with the moon
and that's why the moon always wants to get closer to the sun
is also being that's carrying a magic
flower or something
and like that's why he has like
stains because he gets too close to the sun or something
like
and elves got kind of
made before sun even existed
like they should be all albinos
I guess
but like middle of biology doesn't
make any sense there's no real reason
why specific people should have
specific skin colors
it's all fair game really
I mean in earth
different peoples
living in different places
developed different physical
attributes so why not
elves why not
dwarves etc
oh god there was a
I was watching a Trey the explainer
video you ever see that guy
I was watching one
it was about the um I think
I hope I'm remembering they're called the Ainu
the indigenous people of Japan
right for saying that I thought you meant
the Ainu or as in like all the
Valar and the Maya but yeah
no no no the Ainu
are this um this indigenous
tribe
or something that was there in Japan
before you know what we think
of as the ethnically Japanese
colonized it more or less
and the
he was going into like um
oh god I forget the terms but like
the gene
like groups right like you can
you can track um
like gene groupings right like
different ethnic groups sometimes
share these like
gene packets
and by like oh this
these people have these gene these people
they look different but they have
they share this gene packet so we can see like
okay well they must share a common ancestor
they they these two groups must
have somehow been like a split in
this other third group that came from a third place
and it's like you might not think they were the same
but they actually share a relation and you can
tell by looking at you know these
these gene clusters and uh
the frickin these
these Ainu like they're not
uh they they have
curly they're they're
light skinned like
lighter than than Japanese like they have
like Caucasian like white skin
they have curly dark hair
and blue eyes
uh and yet they share
genes
like they're most closely related
to um this like
dark skinned
uh people that live like exclusively
on like the coast of like
the Indian Ocean or so they're like one little
place they don't look anything
alike but they have like a remark they
share these these gene packets
and like the only two groups that do so
so even in the real world
it doesn't always make sense obviously
the video the video showed
like oh god I wish I had
the diagram but it was like
it was like basically a sort
of like a flow chart of like
you know human genetic
uh like ethnic groups that had like
split and split and split and split and
split and like it's
it's totally like it's way
more complicated there's so many
more branches than I could even
think of and some of them yeah and
some of them split in ways like that like like these
two different groups that ended up looking
totally different but they are kind
of related to each other
like more closely than than
some others uh that even ones
that like look similar so
yeah this kind of thing
is just a thing that like
humans and human
adjacent creatures can be
like expected to do over
you know but uh
over you know geological
periods of time
differentiate themselves
physically right
yeah but don't you know that there's
only white people in Europe
like of course
everything I just everything I just
everything I just said was a test and you pass
I'm just
I'm just gonna disappear now
whew
like that's the wind
the second I hit Europe
ground dude it's
it's crazy how much the outrage
against this casting and the Sean
general has been
very weird for me to
witness because
like Tolkien hasn't really
been that relevant for
a while like ever since the Hobbit movies
came out like for some reason
companies didn't touch it that much
like there were no
like there was no big sequel
series that will accept the Hobbit movies
really well I feel like video games and stuff
but it was very quiet yeah
I feel like the rights must have been
really expensive at that point
oh it's the most expensive TV show of all time
because of that
really yeah apparently they
I don't know how well the Hobbit movies did
the Hobbit movies did
obviously had the brand recognition
to get a lot of money but like
I don't think people liked them
critically I think they're kind of disliked
yeah in general
they're kind of forgettable
the last two especially the first one's
really good
but
yeah and so I haven't really
seen like the internet
the very bad
racist gamer internet
fandom descend onto my
fandom
as like happened to Star Wars
or whatever when they cast like
a black stormtrooper
a few years ago like I saw that
in Star Wars and I was like oh yeah my talking fandom
that's like everyone's nice
everyone's good but then they all came
we're not like those
we're not like those toxic Star Wars
yeah it turns out we actually are
I mean they are
it's there's
there's a lot of really horrible
YouTubers who
like promote that stuff
it's I mean
some YouTubers will
don't even really give a fuck
they'll swoop in
to any
subject if there's a
if there's an SJW
if there's an SJW to be owned
yeah I mean
the Lord of the Rings
is not like
there's a niche of like
super nerds who read the entire
Silmarillion but then there's like
the vast majority of people
who know what the Lord of the Rings is are just people
who grew up and
saw the movies with when they were out
or relevant and they're like
oh yeah
killing orcs
do you remember when Legolas killed
that big elephant all by himself
like that's the sort of people
who could forget
who could easily slot into like
a random like gamer racist
stereotype later in life
and they would just be like
I can't believe that my favorite
show where they kill elephants
with one elf has
black people in it now
I can't believe it
it's problematic because
I like elephants and it's
bad that they died in that war
leave them out of leave the elephants out of it
I can't believe that
I know exactly what they're gonna do in this show
they're gonna have a black elf and they're gonna kill two elephants
that's just unrealistic
they can't kill two elephants
the white elf has to kill more elephants
has to kill
kill cow
that's just more realistic
I think so
and talking is all about realism as you know
that's right
there's also
a bunch of critique from the other side
just because of like
for example the beard thing with the dwarven lady
who
and also the haircuts in general
are a little odd of the characters
like for example that black elf has
like very short
like
super short cut hair
and a bunch of other
a bunch of other male elves also have short hair
so it kind of seems like
they're trying to make them
like more masculine in general
even though they were kind of like
transcending that in the Peter Jackson movies
there's nothing
there's no real textural basis
I think a black elf would look pretty cool with like dreads
yeah
like long dreads in a big like
you know tail or whatever
that could be cool
they gave Elrond very short hair
which is odd
they did that in like animated movies before
but
theoretically I don't really care
but it does seem like
either they just wanted to make the characters
more distinguishable
or they just wanted to make some of them
look more masculine more traditionally
masculine also like
making the gender roles a little more clear
I'm okay with it
if like there's like maybe one
elf group that like
oh yeah other elves grow their hair long
we cut our short because like
I don't know we live in the
in the hills or whatever
we live in the rolling
hills and it's hot
out there so we cut our hair
or just cut them short for war
or whatever
you can make up anything
it doesn't exist
yeah but don't you know that they are like
ruining Tolkien's legacy
they are actually going to rewrite the books
and he's dead
he's dead it doesn't matter
but before we achieve the England
how would you fear if they cast a white guy
in black panther
but never paint
I want to be a puppet
give
no
never give never
never paint is just
he's just concerned about the integrity
of his homeland of England
you just got to let him
you just got to let him have this one
okay one last
thing on the hair thing
seeing a lot of fan art over the last few years
of the Simmarillion characters
I can kind of understand why they wanted
to give all the elves different hair
cuts because you couldn't distinguish
them otherwise
like I just
posted the fan art of like the entire
like House of Finnaut
and Fingalfin
I guess House of Finnaut
and like they're all just long
haired pretty boys
that's all what they are
they all part their hair
the same way
and if you have a cast where
like in Lord of the Rings moves you only had
like one elf that was important
they go last for most of the time
and if you have a cast with like 10 elves
yeah makes sense
you got to do something
you got to do something to make them look
the show can still suck though
but I'm hopeful
I'm always hopeful
I don't know
one thing I always liked about
World of Warcraft is
obviously since it's a game where you can play
as all of these different fancy races
customization
is always like key
like the ability to have
many different hairstyles
with new ones added every so often
various skin tones for
every race
it's great
I like character customization
and
you can make stuff that looks
so different
but still fits within what is
understood to be that kind of a race
like a goblin still looks
like a goblin even though it's got all these different
things about it
the Peter Jackson movies
work great in my opinion
at least the first three
but I think they did
a little bit of a damage
to the general perception
of Tolkien's world
because they were so successful
that they outgrew the books
and every new adaptation
has to fight against that now
they kind of marvel-movie
way more people have seen the marvel movies
than have read the comic books
so the movie versions are
the version that most people
or elves have to have long hair now
forever or else everyone will complain
wait weren't you
just complaining about
an elf not having long hair
yeah
I can see both sides of the argument I would say
I hate people who dismiss it
just because they have long hair
but I
can critique it but I can also see
why they would do it
it's fine
I can also
it's just a thing
it's a hairstyle
you can change your hair and if there's a clan
you have to wear your hair this way
then it would make sense
that's the fashion
that's what we like
us elves we like doing this
if there's different elves that live in different places
that wear their hair different
you just explain it that way
it's not like a
you don't
baby elves
don't come out of the womb looking
like with that hair parting
with the long hair
you know what's weird
in Song of Ice and Fire
that I sort of knew
but hadn't really thought about
but is totally
true
in Song of Ice and Fire
in Planetos
there's
never straight up just like
pseudo human
basically like Neanderthals
or like even more distantly related
like almost humans
squishers
and there's one from
Sotheros and there's one that lives on that
one little island up to the north
of like
the Dothraki continent
I don't remember what they're called but like
yeah there are these like
people that are like
sort of human and some of them
can sort of speak
like human language but like
they can't breed with humans
or they'll only have stillbirth offspring
which is like really
freaky
Neanderthals
Neanderthals could theoretically
maybe breed with
Homo sapiens
but I think that's what that's alluding to
the time in history where
Homo sapiens sapiens and Neanderthals
existed at the same time for a bit
yeah but like even more
different right like even more
like I don't know
there's one that are down in like the
southern
place the Sotheros that are like
they're very like ape like
it's actually called Sotheros
I don't know if that's like an official name
that might just be a fandom name
there's Westeros and Essos
and that's all I know
I think
I don't know if it's a fan name or if it's a
planetos is definitely a fan name
that's true the planet doesn't actually
have a name
oh shit I don't remember what these other
people are called but like
imagine if that was real in the real world
I mean it used to be
I know but like
imagine if there were like
some place in like a jungle
in like I don't know Africa
or like South America or
where you could go and there
yeah and there were like
and there were bigfoots and like you could
talk to them and they could kind of learn
English and talk back to you and they sort of had
a little village they built little huts and lived in them
and they would forage for berries
and stuff and you could even like
go and trade with them if you wanted to but like
and like
someone at some point
discovered that
if you fucked one
you could get it pregnant but the baby would be still born
and like
you don't know who figured that out
but somebody did and we know this
we know this is true
but don't ask out
probably true of almost anything else in the animal kingdom
except us
it's just for
it's a freaky idea
if I lived near
creatures like that they would freak me out
a lot
that's all we would show them your mobile phone
and they wouldn't understand
your apps
like how do I explain my apps
to this creature
I can't even
begin
to answer that question
hey guys
do you know
why they didn't just ask the eagles to bring
the ring into more door
cause they were still eggs
they haven't hatched yet
the Ibnis are they like the one
they just live on this one little island
what are they
what's their special thing
they're short
but heavy, broad shoulder
broad chested, have long arms
they kinda sound like neanderthals actually
short and thick necks, massive jaws
and large square teeth, small sunken eyes
yeah they are able to reproduce
but the offspring usually come out deformed
they can speak
but not very well
I think
Preston's theory is that the others are also just like that
and they're just like another
people that
struggles up there and that's
why they're attacking us or something
I think he did a video
talking about these
and I think he said
that the others are a little different
the others seem like they have some magical
or technological
explanation
like ice and stuff
Preston's whole thing is that
everything in Game of Thrones
is actually sci-fi
that's his big theory
but the show just kind of
went against all of that
and explained nothing
and it's all just magic
the oily stone
Preston thinks it's plastic
and
I guess that kinda sounds like how someone
knows what plastic was might describe plastic
there's a lot of fun things like that
I mean the biggest
clue that convinces me personally
is that George R.R. Martin is just a sci-fi writer
and he's written so many other sci-fi stories
that have kind of the same things
going on that go on in Game of Thrones
like Hive Minds
and
weird like
genealogical stuff
a song of bits and bytes
the people that may say Preston
just don't understand
that like everything that he says
is like, he only says it because
it's like George R.R. Martin has written
that exact same thing in a different story
and like
he's got reasons
for everything
and it's like, I don't know, people come in
with preconceptions, they come in with preconceptions
about what a fantasy story should be
but then Preston was like
well, okay
but like when George
wrote a very similar thing
back in the 70s
here's what the twist ended up being
and it's like
oh, yeah, that is
basically the exact same thing
that's how his writing works most of the time
the children of the forest or whatever
yeah, oh
kind of sounds like he's kind of telling the same
story again
yeah
it took it back to Lord of Rings
for a second
I have a question
this is a hypothetical
I want to talk about the Ibn Is
no
this is way more important
if Sauron got the ring back
and all the power of Mordor
and all the things he wanted
and then aliens showed up
would he win, would he be able to defend
Earth with his powers
sorry, would who? Sauron?
Sauron
could Sauron defeat the aliens?
well, there are no aliens
that's a problem
no, no, no
imagine if there were aliens
no, no, no, no
imagine aliens came down
and they were like, beep boop
we're gonna shoot you with a laser gun
like Rick and Morty, you know that show
well, they wouldn't because that's not Iluvatar's plan
for creation
I'm sorry, that's not in the heavenly music
because I love God
Jesus, and I know these things
no, no, no, Iluvatar
made more than just the things
on Middle Earth, he had other planets
this is so heretical
right now
he's got so many other projects going on
so many irons in the fire and he still hasn't finished his book
he's gonna make
okay, but you know what?
Sauron maybe couldn't deal with the aliens
but Morgoth at the end of the
first age where he had
giant dragons the size of mountains
and
armies of Balrogs
yeah, maybe
I don't know
Sauron's
whole empire
is kind of a pale imitation of what Morgoth had going on
he's just
Morgoth's underling trying to recreate the good old times
on the other hand, the moon
does exist
in Lord of the Rings
so if there was an alien invasion
maybe moon aliens
would be the main aliens
okay, no, but the moon is not actually big
or like
the moon is not like a celestial object
the moon is like a flower
I think
it's a flower of a tree getting carried by an angelic being
it's not our
stone ice moon
little tiny flower bugs
little tiny flower bugs, little tiny hollow night bugs
would come down from the moon
and they'd come down
exactly
that's what I'm saying
that's what I've been saying for years
great, we solved it
yep
would cowboys defeat Mordor
think about this
if cowboys rode into town with their guns
well, Mordor was working on
like, I mean, his Sauron man
was working on like gunpowder
so
they were getting there, they were not that far from cowboys
I'd like to see that
I'd like to see a future where
Sauron got the one ring
and they invented guns
and then we had orcs
riding wargs
with rifles and guns
going yee-haw
actually, I have good news for you
orcs ride wargs or goblins
goblins ride wargs
goblins do, I don't know what orcs do
I guess they would walk like idiots
are goblins the same as orcs?
in the hobbit, he calls them goblins
because it's more of a children's story, it sounds cuter
I guess, and at some point
he just switches to calling them all orcs
just like the elves are also called gnomes
in the earliest writings
in the hobbit, are the goblins
bigger than Bilba
or are they like human size?
they're like smaller than humans
but bigger than dwarfs and
hobbits
so about how the movie
depicts them
they're a little too big and mighty
like the urokai are these
giant monsters in the movies
and they're supposed to be
are the urokai sort of like orcish super soldiers?
they are, but they're almost as big
as a human, they still don't get there
because all evil creations
have to be inferior to
the original
god made beings
I kind of like
that they're giant in the movie
it sells the
scary factor and the danger
it absolutely works
all the practical orcs are amazing
and that's one of the things
that I really like about this new tv show
is that they're going back to practical
effects for all the orcs
and they hired the same studio
that did them for the movies and they're gonna look disgusting
I remember
I remember people complaining
about that shot in that one hobbit movie
of like the molten gold
in smog's
smog's treasure
and it looked really bad
it melted faster than
chocolate would melt
the CG is so stupid
gollum looks amazing and
a lot of the orcs
effects look really bad
gollum was like a triumph
gollum
nobody has
done what they did with gollum
maybe that's not true
but it was a real benchmark
in
not before
but even since
who else even
what's another CG creature that looks as good
as gollum did
I struggle to think of any
off the top of my head
I think one of the greatest things
about gollum is that they always had
them on set, on location
they had the actor
scrub
scrubbing through that little stream
in the landscape of New Zealand
and then they like replaced him
digitally so there was like
kind of little green screen involved
they always had him there
and then they redid everything in the computer
so it was like a lot of real life reference
I think that's why
gollum is so
so memorable as being
like a really good CG characters
because you know
when gollum picks up a rock and moves it around
or shuffles on the ground
and then you see the environment
react in a very physical
real looking way
so like things could technically
be better CG characters
but like the way they did gollum
I think is the reason it's so good
that reminds me of
Who Framed Roger Rabbit
you know how like
they would have real props on like
sticks and strings like manipulated
by people off stage
and then they would animate the cartoon characters
and bring them around
yeah
they would make it as tough
as possible
to add a 2D character into the frame
they would have like shadows moving across the
the set
in like dynamic ways
it's like what if we made it the
most impressive we possibly could
it would take a lot of effort
and it wouldn't necessarily make the story
better but it would just be cool
nobody does that anymore
there's too much effort into things
for cool factor they just do
what they are told
I mean that's
I wouldn't say there's nobody but
in general it gets this
I haven't seen anything on the level of Roger Rabbit
in terms of like overdoing
like a 2D animation thing
there was that one like Chip and Dale movie
that tried it and it didn't look
even as good as Roger Rabbit
like having that
combined style
with the voice they had a similar scene
I think they took
one of the funny things
is for some reason they took
the wrong lesson away from Gollum
they just started casting
specifically anti-circus
as CG characters
like the actor who played Gollum
got really successful playing other
CG monsters and stuff
it wasn't just
he had a great performance but the technology
and the inventiveness of that
like whole production
made it great
and they put him in every other thing
like he's that big evil guy
in the new Star Wars movies
like yeah but that's not
wait which guy?
that's funny casting
Snoke
Wait Gollum played Snoke?
yeah
he also played
Planet of the Apes
Caesar and also
King Kong I believe in the Peter Jackson
King Kong movie
I mean okay I guess
he's everywhere
sure why not
he also played Jon Snow
Jon Snow was completely CG
yeah
I see
actually it would be kind of cool
if they completely CG Jon Snow after
Steph to make him more in canny
that would be neat
oh like make him
like after he died
they do like
the thing that they do with actors
to sort of recreate them
digitally
but they do that with him even though the actor is still alive
but it's like yeah we want you to look weird though
we want you to look like a zombie
that's one of the worst things about Game of Thrones
is that his death didn't affect anything
nothing happened
it affected people going what's gonna happen next
I better buy anything
hang on no follow up
well it was technically
he got out of his oath
of being a black
knight not a black knight
but he went back to that anyways
who cares
it was a loophole because
if you made a promise
they didn't even
listen
I know power resides
where men think it resides
but like
you could guard until his death
and there's simply no way around that
you simply cannot
circumvent that unless
there's a tricky little magical
resurrection loophole
so fuck you
Sam also
I think Sam at some point said
hey we're supposed to guard the realms of men
doesn't mean we have to do it at the wall
we have to do it in general
yeah
that's another tricky little secret loophole
you gotta find a tricky little secret loophole somehow
and they don't even question it
actually that would be fine
that would be cool
if they said oh that's a secret loophole
but then it just goes to other kingdoms
and it's like hey I'm Jon Snow
I used to be a knights watch guy
and nobody questions it
he's not even questioned that people say
hey aren't you an oath breaker
don't you suck
but nobody does because they don't care
in the later seasons
how's Asha
you know I'll be honest
I didn't watch past the death of Jon Snow
I didn't see the show
after that
I heard it was really bad
I heard it was really bad so I didn't watch it
we're actually watching it together right now
and we just spoiled everything for Asha
when I get the end of season 4
there you go
I would say Game of Thrones is
good even a bit after
Jon die
death
scenes
gasp
no
he dies
that's not what the pop culture zeitgeist says
the production design is so pretty
I rewatched Game of Thrones
semi-recently
and I came to the decision
that
I like shows even when they suck
when people say
stop to this episode and don't go no further
no that's stupid
it's most of the time not worth
like I don't know
I'd rather watch the thing
and get all of the good out of it
and be a little disappointed
than never know what happens
even though I'll probably hear about it
really bad shows can be interesting as well
I love the Hobbit movies a lot
even though they have tons of problems
but I just know so much about
the history of them and how they got produced
what all went wrong
and it's just fascinating to see all of that
play out and the potential that they had
and what actually
happened with them
I think that the beginning
of the Hobbit movie is quite nice with the dwarfs
it's so much stuff
they sing that deep deep song that's like really deep
it's the best scene
it's the best scene that whole trilogy is in
and then Bilbo says
literally because they're going downhill
under hill and over
mmm yeah
I like that song by Leonard Nimoyd
about the Hobbit
oh yeah
oh I don't know
that's the best Hobbit adaptation
it's the only valid one
no the best Hobbit adaptation
is National Lampoon's
Board of the Rings
oh no
which I read the first like chapter
of
and oh man
I forget
what they call
they have some stupid other name for Hobbits
in Board of the Rings
but I remember that like
habits I don't know
but they describe whatever they call Hobbits
they describe them as like
like yeah they're small
they're small but they're tough
they can easily defeat
they can easily defeat a creature half their size
if they get the drop on them
and I just thought that was really funny
that's basically all I remember
can you just
now I wonder if you can just do that
like make a parody
a book and publish it
of some big franchise
which is like obviously that franchise
I guess they don't need
it's been done
if you've seen the Barry Trotter
but freaking fair use
and parody law and whatever
true
I should read those honestly
because now that I know that JK Rowling is horrible
I might actually prefer those
parody books
I mean those are old right
yeah they can
I remember seeing them at the same time
the books were coming out
I don't know anything about them
isn't there like a musical
isn't there like a stage play
that's like a parody of Harry Potter
no that was an official thing
it was a real
no not
not cursed child
the burst child
there's a freaking
Harry Potter
parody musical
nope never mind
maybe it's a YouTube video
I mean there is one called a very Potter musical
but that's not what I was
I thought there was a
is that the little puppet show with Snape Ghost
Snape Snape Snape
Severus Snape
do you know who made that
it was Neil Cisariga
Neil Cisariga
the guy behind
the guy behind everything
the guy behind fucking everything
you've ever heard of
Minecraft
the guy who did
the freaking ultimate showdown
of ultimate destiny
he did the Harry the Potter
puppet pals
he's lemon demon
mouth sounds
he did
fucking
there's probably like 18 other things
he called John Tron a piece of shit
that one time and it was really funny
yeah
his crowning achievement
yeah all that other stuff
is alright
yeah that's his master piece
I'm telling John Tron to go fuck himself
was the piece to resist
he made Brody Quest
if you know that meme video
yes of course
he's a meme master
he's good at making things
that go viral
Potter puppet show was really big when I was in school
same
whoa
how do we even
get on this topic
I've lost the thread
we're just circling from
we're circling the drain
of eternity
Game of Thrones to Lord Rings
back to Harry Potter
as all things go
what would happen
if you gave the ring
to a cricket
no
you know what
it's rock paper scissors
Game of Thrones
Game of Thrones beats
Lord of the Rings
because Game of Thrones is a dark
is a dark
subversion of fantasy tropes
Lord of the Rings beats Harry Potter
because Lord of the Rings is good
and Harry Potter beats
Game of Thrones
because it made more money
I don't know
Harry Potter should not be
made to all the money
you know
they all made a shit ton of money
when it comes to
childhood film franchises
it used to
that I like
there was Lord of the Rings
and Harry Potter coming out at the same time
but then there was Pirates of the Caribbean
I think Pirates of the Caribbean is better
than Harry Potter
it's not based on a book
it's based on a
Disney ride
no
it's not based on a book series
give me a break
it's got to be based on a book series
I could write a book about it
and then it would be based
still
Princess Bride
that's based on a book
is Princess Bride better than Harry Potter
in my current estimation
I would say
it's better than Harry Potter
I probably wouldn't have said so as a kid
people say that
Percy Jackson is the good version
of Harry Potter
I've never read it
after my time
but I have heard that
during my time
the people that read
Percy Jackson
are too young to have real opinions
so I won't trust that until
maybe for like 5 more years
and if they still say that then maybe
maybe
you guys ever read the Spooks
series of novels
good question
they probably have a different title in German honestly
it's about this
it's been a long time since I've read these
but
it's like a wizard thing
but with very specific rules
vampires
can't cross like a line of salt
so if you're summoning a vampire
for a thing you have to make sure your salt line
is done and there's pentagrams
that's a classic vampire rule
yeah it's a lot of classic
mythical wizarding
rules and
you're a spook that's the name of your job
as you go to places and you
sort out problems as a spook
and there's the Spooks Apprentice
who's the 7th son of a 7th son
means you're allowed to be a spook
this guy
he's a wizard spook man
and he gets this youngster
under his wing
and there's an adventural 3 or 4
and I enjoyed them very much
that sounds like something I would
have been really into
it reminds me of the
Bartimeo sequence
Bartimeo's trilogy, Pog, yes I read those
it's like 4 books I think
but I think the 4 porn
is actually like a prequel
that takes place in like
super long ago times
I don't remember
those were good too
Ever heard of Wizards Hall?
Nope
Wizards Hall is
a single novel
about a kid
who goes to wizard school
and it came out 6 years before
Harry Potter
and I actually had read it
before Harry Potter
and it was like wow
this is kind of similar to that other book
but nobody knows about Wizards Hall
it never
kept, it never continued
so I don't know
that's it, that's it, that's the thing about
Wizards Hall
Did everybody see another British
book series that came out before
Harry Potter
was like
the worst witch
it's like a book franchise
I've never seen that somewhere
they made a TV adaptation
oh yeah there's also a movie
that features
what's his name
something curry, Tim Curry?
Tim Curry, Tim Curry
yeah as a wizard that the girls
spoon over
hmm
oh these are from
oh wow, okay I mean
some of them came out in like the 70s
but they were
they were still coming out in like
the 2010s
I remember this book cover
I don't know if I read it but I remember
seeing this in a library
post
image
the worst witch has been running for longer than
The Simpsons
Holy shit, yeah
I thought nothing has
before The Simpsons
we didn't have
what's known as a televisions
oh no
the tragedy
yeah I feel like I
missed out on a bunch of those
because I was so hyper fixated on
Harry Potter and Lord of the Rings when I was young
hey you know
what though? I think
this book
this book came up in my image search
and I feel like we should
talk about it
I'm sorry my internet is being shitty but the
image will load shortly and it's gonna
blow you away
with how funny and silly and goofy and
kooky
the thing that it will show you
is
just you wait
and he's second now
that bar is almost full there we go
I assume this is like a Christian
like an evangelical Christian thing
why don't we celebrate
Halloween
I try to witness this don't celebrate anything I think
I mean that
and like Christians who think
anything that's remotely about magic
is saintannic
yeah that's I think there are more
I think there are more evangelicals
than there are Jehovah's Witnesses
but I mean I guess their reasons are similar
yeah I'm
trying to read the description here on
faithandflame.com
where
and the description
cuts off I can't read the whole description
it ends in a dot dot dot
so I don't oh wait
this is why you should be
ready to explain Halloween to a kid
sharing the dangers of Halloween
and discussing Halloween as a pagan
holiday yep this book
will help your child have a Christian perspective
on Halloween making it clear
why you don't celebrate the holiday it
reveals in story form the truth behind
the activities that have become such an accepted
part of Halloween traditions
children who read this book
and talk about it with their parents will learn how the
quote fun of Halloween
harms them they will also
learn what to say to others who do not
understand the true meaning of Halloween
oh my god
no no customer
reviews oh cringe
the Christian
kids on Halloween will don their paladin
armor they get their sword
and they just lay all the monsters
go out and slay all the other kids yeah
well you shouldn't
told you told you told you
your quote unquote fun would harm you
you didn't listen
you know I never celebrate the Halloween
and I would have liked
an explanation because all American cartoon
shows had Halloween
yeah
they didn't
when I was in Poland
I mean they did they did Halloween
they didn't really like do it
to the same extent
like
we definitely didn't
have trick or treating like I saw yeah
I saw some people walking around in costumes
but I didn't really see any like trick or
treating exactly
which is I only ever went trick or treating
with my mom
when I was very little which is very weird
because like our country is like way
safer than the U.S.
like yeah if anything
we should go out trick or treating
even more
yeah I mean
all right I mean
there's a I mean I'm taking
this based off of like just seeing
American TV and movies where like
Halloween episodes they're always
in the suburbs
and oh yeah
there's more of like cul-de-sacs
and like more of a I don't know
just I have like two streets to go down
and there's not much that can happen
where everyone's looking outside all the time
yeah it's sort of a
contained but I don't know how much more
safe that is than like a London suburb
where the houses are smaller
and closer together
but it's still like a suburb
where I grew up was not good
for trick or treating at all
I mean we did it a little bit
we would drive to a neighborhood that was a little bit better
for it but
we were like super big on trick or treating
I mean we did it
I dressed up one time for Halloween
because I found a book in a library
that was like fun
children's crafting tips for Halloween
and I dressed up as a spider
at like
face paint at like multiple eyes
painted on my face and had like a green
like net for like trees
to like put trees in or something
around me I was walking around like that
all day just going to the mall
with my parents or something and people
looked at me very weird like
it was not expected
for a child to be in costume
at Halloween
When do you ever get the word costumes?
Fushing
Well we have like Carnival
like that's like our costume
thing
but that's also kind of regional here
like it's not happening everywhere
One time I went to
I was in Dusseldorf
and there was a
there was a festival going on
and there were people in costumes
there were some I remember
some people were dressed as the Beagle Boys
there were other costumes but I remember
there were people in costumes at the point
and it wasn't Halloween it was some other like
some other holiday that people were doing
We have that period between
November and February
where it's like fushing season
and at the beginning at the end the celebrations
like I said it's kind of regional
and there's a lot of like
parades and stuff
like dances
That's when we would like dress up in school
and like play games
and gym hall or whatever
But it's not spooky themed
Halloween is cool because it's
spooky themed. Carnival is just like
general dress up
So you get two opportunities to dress up
in costumes
Yeah kind of
Yeah
It's not but it doesn't have the trick
or treating it doesn't have going out at night
without your parents and getting sweets
That's cool
I wanted that
like in my
American cartoons
It's just like one of my American cartoons
TV shows and movies
I like never went trick or treating without my parents
because like
when I was a kid parents would drive me
to a neighborhood that was like
trick or treat friendly and like by the time I was
like old enough that
I was like drive myself
and I didn't really want to be like
doing it
You know
It's a little cringe if you know what I'm saying
Yeah
They get the point
At some point it becomes less cringe again
and you wish that you could do it
I mean I guess
I've been googling the worst witch
because I've convinced
that I did see this TV show
on CBBC at some point
and I think I did
and I think I did also have a crush on the main actress
Wait what?
The worst witch
Oh yeah
1998 to 2001
That's the one I watched as a kid
Look at this opening like
credits where they're like green screened
like swiveling around
on the brooms
It's funny that this did come out before Harry Potter
It does look a lot like it
And it's basically
just the plot of
Little Witch Academia
because it's an old girl's school
Yeah
But they're all British in this one
I assume
That was a BBC thing of course they are
I'm sorry the best
The best Harry Potter
alternative is still BP Blocksberg
That was
that was my
big Harry Potter alternative
It's like a big German TV show
and like audio book character
She's a witch
and she goes on adventures
and there's a movie that came out around the same time
as Harry Potter and it's
very much copying the Harry Potter aesthetic
and the music and
but still good
still good and not transphobic
and great
That's all I wanted to be
Now I'm thinking about it
Was Harry Potter the first
big male
witch thing
Because there's a lot of witches
as a female archetype
Well
Wizard's Hall is about a boy who goes to wizard school
So Wizard's Hall
You did it
I think it's amazing that Hogwarts
is called school for witch
craft and wizardry
You have to
gender divide that
If a witch does it
it's a witchcraft
Why?
That part of it has always been
in history
Witches are women
and wizards are different
But it's a real world for them
So they should just have one term for it
Okay
But it's not like magicians
It's not like JK came up with that
Yeah
It's like historically grown maybe
I mean JK Rowling
would come up with like some stupid
like oh it's witchcraft
if you were born a woman
if you have like a womb
it only counts as witchcraft
It's like biological
You will never be able to wizardry
Uterus magic
We can always tell
This is how we can explain
This is how we can fix
this is how we can fix JK
because there literally is no difference
between witchcraft and wizardry
We can just explain gender to her like that
and she's like oh I get it
it's just about the words you use
but it's the same oh
I've been so wrong
She would literally say
that the power of the testicles
is what makes it wizardry
I don't believe it
If you had a testicle you can't do witchcraft
Absolutely would
You're wrong
They are the same
They are the same spells
and the same potions and whatever
and I'm pretty sure there's no difference at all
it's just two different words
for the same thing
Expelliarmus he him
Yeah
Expelliarm
Wait you say
Expelliarmus
Women
I don't know
No, no, no
Men say
There are no pronouns in Harry Potter
Women say
It's the ways to do it
I don't know if people heard
my funny joke
Yeah
I gotta listen to it next week
I'm gonna really listen to it
My head
Back to Lord of the Rings though
I'm sorry
One last Lord of the Rings fact
Galadria's husband
Not a guy
Caliborn
What's his name?
From Homestuck
I've never seen a single Homestuck
You should read Homestuck because
Alright
Here's an obscure fact
that I'm not sure about
but you might be able to recall
talking about a green sun
as like if you're thinking of
making a world
and you make a green sun
As just an example of
a fantasy thing
you should have a reason for it
or something, I don't remember
There's a quote attributed to J.R. or Tolkien
about a green sun
with regards to writing
theory
or how to create fantasy worlds
and Andrew Hussey heard that
and he thought, well, yeah, I could just take
that exact thing
That's the lesson
that was supposed to be learned from that
I mean, I'm sure he liked
Tolkien's work in general
I just thought that would be a cool thing to lift
There's a green sun
in Homestuck
I mean, the green sun could have been any color
It could have been any color
That's the point of Tolkien's
Yeah, Tolkien's
just came up with some random shit
as an example
I mean, it's like
it's sort of like if he had made a
if there was a fish
and he'd made it red
because it's a red herring
and it's just a reference to a thing
Okay, okay
I didn't know that actually
Yeah, Caliburn
Great guy, completely irrelevant
for most of the time because Caliburn
is like the most important person
and super powerful
Caliburn is one of the wisest elves
in Middle Earth, but that's
they all are
Yeah, there's no real evidence
He doesn't really do anything, he's just a trophy husband
But the thing
of Caliburn is
he has a very funny name
because his Teleri name
from the elves that lived by the sea
and they have their own language
called Teleri
I guess it's like an accent of Sindali
like that, but his original
Teleri name is
Telepono
like
Wow, cool
Sounds almost like a request
And I think talking
every day for that
and I'm very happy that this is in there
That's your Tolkien fact
That's why he's the best
writer ever
Yes
That's
That's it
That's a freaking George Lucas
Oh yeah
Well this guy's name in the original language
is Telepono
because it's like
it rhymes
with
Teleponography
Because he's a really sexy guy
I think Tolkien didn't have a choice
on television
You know
I think Tolkien didn't have a choice
He couldn't name him anything else
because the languages make so much sense
that just historically
it must have been Telepono
This is just the words that are his name
You can't call him anything else
What does it mean?
Oh wait, I should look that up
It probably means something important
Tree of the silver bird
How does elf language work?
Is it like
based on your place of birth
and how many
thumb wars you won
you get named a certain thing
Your parents both give you different names
and then at some point
you choose your own name based on
That's just like warrior cats
Maybe
Okay, alright
Elves are warrior cats, I get it
By the way, Telepono means
silver tall
because he had silver hair and was very tall
This is literally no other way to describe him
He's teleporting
It's kind of a boring name
actually
Yeah, even how it sounds
Elves just
I think name themselves
after the legends that they make
You know what, that is
kind of like a warrior cat's name though
isn't it?
Well, no, he would be called
Can a cat be tall?
He would be called silver thrush
or something, or he would be called
tall leaf
or something like that
because you have to have an adjective
and a thing
in nature, or it's two things in nature
right?
Is it a cat name?
Yeah
Is it why warrior cats can have names?
How can you say that? Wait, isn't that
the same generation as Percy Jackson
I feel like that's the same thing
Maybe a little older
I think it's a little older than that
Maybe
It's one of these series with way too many books
I mean, I never read it
Yeah, it's still going
I mean, so is Percy Jackson, I believe
at least some of the spin-off series
Wow, okay
How could you write all the time?
How could you do that?
I mean, they probably have
I mean, warrior cats
they have ghost writers and stuff
They're dead?
Yes
They die?
They kill them and they enslave their spirit
and they said, you will
You will write about these cats
You'll work off your sins
in the typewriter minds
you will type
until your spirit is cleansed
of evil
I know nothing about no warrior cats
but I just assume they go with the lore
that cats all have nine lives
and that's why the series is so long
It's like eight times before
that story's over
is a thing in them
or something
I don't really know too much
about it
What do we think
about
Frickin' Ask PCP
questions? Hell yeah
I feel like we've been gone for a while
Okay
Well, I've got one, this was actually asked
of me before
Ask PCP, so I'm gonna honor it
This is from
Coco Peloton
It's also ugly
I can't leave a voicemail for the podcast
I wanted to say, one piece
Dragon Ball Super and one punch man
all ended their current arc this week
and they were all shit endings
Tell me why, Benzane
Why is Oracle
It's because
I don't know
I know
why people would be upset
there's like a choice was made
Wait, I know what happened
I actually know what happened
Can you say it?
Someone didn't join the crew
right?
Yeah, it's like a potential
crew joining thing
I have no real opinion
I mean it was to say, it's Yamato
I
from my perspective, I heard people say
Yamato joins the crew and I thought
that seemed like really quick
but then again
it probably took less chapters
for Sanji to join
for instance
I think at this point, a character
joined it because it was like Jinbei took
so much longer
than you would have expected from officially
They were teasing Jinbei
they were edging with Jinbei for years
and years
and people really wanted
carrot to join
which I don't
hate her, but I don't get
the appeal of her being in the crew
she's just sort of nice
She's cute and nice
but does that
mean you should be part of the sohats?
She doesn't have quite as much of
a role to play
either socially
or strategically in the crew
so that's that
but then Yamato's
coming in
as another potential heavy hitter
in the late game of the one piece
story
but he's like
he's a
he's a powerful ally
to protect
Wano when they leave
so I feel like
it's not like he's not gonna be
in the manga anymore
there's gonna be
stuff happening with all these characters
and I feel like being literally on the crew
doesn't mean much because there's so many characters
that are allied with the crew
that are going to show up again
either as enemies or allies
in whatever huge conflict
is gonna be coming up
with the coming to the end
of the actual story
so I don't feel like
it's the same as having a new character
on for another like 20 years of adventures
do you think that's what this person
is saying it's shitty because
of that? I think they're just like
they wanted it to be like an official thing
lots of people did
but instead no
and I'm like I don't mind
I think it's cool
I just want to see what happens next
I mean I
was surprised that when Jinbei joined
because I kind of felt like
I didn't need any more members
and I guess I kind of still feel like
that but I mean
whatever
I'm not like against the idea entirely
so I guess I
I'm pretty neutral on it although I haven't finished
I haven't actually gotten there
I'm like 12 chapters behind or something so
I should catch up
so I can have a real opinion
um okay
uh well anyway
let me
someone else asked me
is Ben caught up to one piece yet
and I just answered that question
I did catch up a while ago but now I'm behind
um alright
so let me
see here who responded
to the tweet
okay
Sankishi Seidel
if I'm saying that right
says everyone is talking like the voicemail
era is over can't you just back up the existing voicemails
uh yeah
the reason why it's not
ready is because
I cleared a lot of it out
and I thought I just had to clear out some
space
and it didn't work and I guess actually I need
to clear out like all the space
so it was sort of my bad
but not really
it should have worked
it just didn't
um okay next one
hey Ben I got an asked PCP for you
uh spotify
yeah
I think um it's not just spotify
the problem is like you can't download
the episodes conveniently anymore
really
I can't listen to them if I don't have internet
and that's a bit annoying
yeah I know
I said before
I think I'm just gonna have to accept
that like some of the apps will just
not have the first episodes on them
like they're just gonna have to delete
the old episodes
they're all on the website
almost all on youtube
so I don't know at some point
I give up
I will do that
I just haven't done it yet
but yeah I gotta do it
you're right
demonica knight asks
PCP who has the biggest butt
between Ben and Gibb
and rank the butts of all PCP members
thank you
and wait there's an image
um
no
here
oh well yeah
I would agree with this
I mean I personally been working out
like doing squats more recently
and more regularly
so my butt's bigger than it was
that's a point in my favor
I don't know
I don't think I have a particularly large butt
um
I don't know
I genuinely don't know
how to answer
uh can I
can I rank the butts of all PCP members
no
yeah people say Nate has a big butt
which is very funny
that does kind of have a big butt because of all the exercise he used to do
lol
actually he might still but like
I assume so
I don't know if that's
no
because it's not like he was like
big all over
because he was like really buff
no but like his butt was
yeah
his thighs were quite large for
okay well here's the thing
his squats were bad
he was bad at squatting so I don't think
that it was like oh he just worked his like
his glutes out that much
and naturally is like that
well yeah good for you
I guess
all I noticed is that one screenshot from the
Brad Garlinghouse music video
where it's gigantic
I
I don't know the exact one you're talking about
I think it got reposted in your server
two days ago or something
cool
uh
people be talking
as for everyone else I have no idea
I just wore like baggy trousers
or it wasn't looking
so I don't know
p-blade spirit asks
Ben do you have a favorite brand of
gummies as a gummy candy fan
I quite like the albany's brand
or alternatively is there a brand
that you'd compare the ones you'd make want to make to
um
is albany's the one
the bears that have the a on them
those are okay
those are fine
ooh I like um
it's kind of a basic bitch
but I really like
I really like gushers and like
fruit by the foot and that stuff
that stuff's really good
I really like um
I don't know if I have a favorite brand
uh
I like uh
I like grapefruit flavored ones
whenever I go to like a candy store I look for grapefruit flavored gummy candy
whenever I can find those
I really like those
um
I don't really have a favorite brand
I like a wide spectrum of them
I like the juicy ones
I like the jelly-ish ones
I like the hard ones
I like the chewy ones
I can appreciate
I appreciate all different
there's such a spectrum
I think so
I like to think so
um
okay next one is from
jjava arts
if you could trade any one of your talent skills
with one of your friends
which one would you choose and why
talents skills
uh
would I have to trade all of my talents
with all of their talents
well I'd say no
to all things
I like my talents
one I'm trying to think
if you could trade one of your talents
with one other talent
with someone else's
um
I mean I would I think I've said this
if you could trade any one of your talent skills
with one of your friends
which one would you choose and why
I trade um
my
here's the thing though
can I never learn that skill again
I think so yeah
because you'll never you'll never be talented
if you trade it away you'll never be talented at it
but like you can be
untalented but work really hard
and like like what does talent mean
here no talent is everything
you can't do anything without talent don't you know
oh god
I think I mean obviously
they just mean like look some
people some people are just bad at something
and I think if you if if we're
taking this question seriously
if you trade away your talent it means you
become bad at it like you you can no
longer do it well
hmm
I mean what am I talented at then
because I could
choose something that I'm sort of good at but I don't
care too much about losing and then just
yeah like a really good thing in return
you could definitely you could definitely game this question
I could I could be like oh my my
talent at crochet like I'm sort of
good at crochet I made those little booties
for risker
but like I could trade that for like
munchies
like speaking
to a crowd ability
I mean I know what I would trade for
is I would trade for Maryweather's
marketing savvy
in a second
that's the most valuable is just
liking anime though that's the most valuable skill
that anyone that I know
possesses so that's what I'm going for
what do I trade for it
I don't know
my huge day
what do I need it for
useless get it get it out of here
hasn't been used in years
my my ability to
grow a full beer
that can go
that's a talent that takes it out of dedication
oh yeah you got a home
you know you got you start with natural talent
but then if that's a talent I would also like to
get rid of that please
okay
can we instead
can we instead trade
like something we're really bad at
against something you're just
okay at
what
you've completely
spit in the
spirit of this question
okay yeah but I just
I'm just reconstructing the question I want to trade
I want to rather be bad at something
else instead of being bad at that thing
also trade like a bad talent
for a different bad talent that you didn't
already have
what do you mean a bad
what do you mean a bad talent
negative talent a negative talent
something that you're bad at
traded for something that someone else is bad at
yeah and the thing the thing that you were
bad at just you become neutral
you become I guess okay at it
neither good or bad
then I would like to trade
my inability to drive a car
safely
with you know what
yeah that is a good one to get rid of
yeah I don't know
like fishing
I don't need to be good at fishing
are you good at fishing
do you have a friend who's bad at fishing
oh wait no
dang it I need to find one
so now you have to pick one of your friends and
publicly say that they're bad at something
I should be like yeah I want that
what are your bad at
uh
self confidence
no I also don't want to be bad at that
that's that one
uh
all my friends are too talented I don't find
something you're calling your friend you're free
you're friend zoning it
ashi you're getting friendzoned
hmm
okay I guess I would be fine with
being bad at cooking
if you were neutral at cooking
wait you're not bad at cooking
at all
hmm okay
let's move on
I just haven't like
harnessed it