So Finn and Jake set out to find a new home. It's gonna be tough for a kid and a dog on their own.
Here's a little house, off and sticking his foot in. Well, that's a bad idea, dude, cause now that bird thinks you're a chirpin.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever. Yeah, you said it, buddy. Hey, what's up, Davoo? You're here.
Shippadoop boop poop.
Allegedly. Munchy is here.
Hey yo, my fucking shitty ex-wife reposed my entire house besides this tub I bought in 1999.
So now I'm recording this entire episode for my fucking tub cause my shitty ass bitch ass ex-wife took out all my fucking eyeballs.
It's the challenge of our generation. Ben Saint is here.
That's my name.
Oh god, no shit. No, I'm good, I'm good. Let's keep going, let's keep going.
Good, and digi bros here.
Hell yeah, nigga, reppin' that well laid and well paid. Maslow get blown the fuck out.
Before we get into the episode itself, so at the end of the last episode, as you probably heard, it's been a week since then as it happens.
And so at the very end of the last episode, we talked about the new PCP merch that is available right now on two locations.
We didn't give any URLs, we didn't say what websites it was, cause that was still up for debate at the time, sort of.
But it's all settled now, people, so I'm going to give you two links you can go to to buy official PCP merchandise, okay?
Here's the first one, redbubble.com slash people slash procrastinators.
This is all going to be in the description, but it's there.
There you can buy, it's going to be, there's the main PCP logo, you can get that on everything, shirts, mugs, whatever the fuck you want, it's all there.
They got a million things on Redbubble. Go buy that shit.
And the other thing is on, we've got a print all over me thing, which are the shirts that Ben had made previously.
Those are hosted there, they're a little fancier, they're more expensive, but they're better quality.
They're real fancy, they're there, they're all over prints, they're like, they're like luxury, they're like deluxe.
You can just be, you can just be swaddled in, in us, swaddled in PCP everywhere you go.
Basically you won't look like you have a shirt that was obviously run through a website, you know, that's an, like it's most of those shirts,
you can tell where the rectangle begins and ends, and it makes you think about the fact that it was obviously through a third party fuck shit.
So the print all over me thing is obviously supposed to make it not look like that, it's supposed to be like a real shirt.
Print all over me shirts are real fucking swank and choice.
They're great, they really are great.
These shirts are basically for fucking sultans only, and if you're not a sultan, then you don't get it.
Exactly, and the Redbubble, there's a more impressing announcement here about this folks.
On the Redbubble site, in addition to the procrastiners logo, it's not right now, but I'm going to put this up like as soon as we're recording.
There will be a PCP, Patreon thing, the Paceron PCP meme, that's going to be a shirt on Redbubble, and you know, you buy all the fucking items.
That's going up people.
We need more designs on the Redbubble, we'll make more in the future, but these, these are good.
We're going to expand this, but here's the thing, that's going up for exactly one month, and then it's going away forever,
and you will never have it ever again.
It's your only chance for the history of history to get this fucking shit.
So you need to buy it right fucking now, there's no time to wait.
You've only got one month.
You literally can't afford not to buy it.
Exactly.
This shirt, or mug, or fanny pack, or bikini top, will pay for itself ten times over.
It's so true, and just as the old Patreon logo is going away,
that's why this is going away, and it will be replaced with a vastly shittier new PCP Patreon logo
that will be the only thing you can buy, so you'll be condemned to that fate if you don't act fast.
It will truly capture the shittiness that is the new Patreon logo.
We'll just distill it down to its shitty essence for you.
We're going to pay them extra to spit on every piece of merchandise that that comes with, so, you know, just gear up for that.
Guys, I'm going to level with you, if you don't get this, the classic PCP Patreon shirt,
I'm going to make your wife bear it.
I'm going to take out her new shirt, and she's not going to be able to bear your children.
I'm just going to level with you, I'm just going to level with you right now.
Redbubble's a pretty, it's a good website.
The shirts are actually pretty good at you, but there you go.
Okay, folks, when we open the store, you can stop asking, you now have PCP merch, it's real, it's official, go buy it all.
Now let's get into the actual episode.
Yeah.
Homes and Homelessness.
Homes and Homestuck.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
What do you mean this isn't the Homestuck podcast?
Fuck it, I'm out of here.
I didn't even think of that connection, it's just going to be homestucked the entire time.
You crushed your mind.
So here's the urban dictionary definition of homes, plural.
Oh wait, no, this is terrible, let's go, okay, home, here we go, home.
A place where I can poop for however long I desire.
Yeah.
In the description, I had dinner at Taco Bell and then I went home and spent the rest of the night on the crapper.
Well, all right, that's fine.
Very descriptive.
Let's see what we've got for Homeless.
Okay, Homeless.
When one has exhausted all resources and reduced to the insane condition of toting a small travel bag,
aimlessly riding buses, selling plasma, knotting out in public libraries, standing in welfare lines, eating in soup kitchens,
walking in a dream, sleeping in shelters and parks, worrying about the next fix,
and knowing that going to jail is a step up in the social ladder.
Jesus Christ, that was descriptive and accurate.
It was pretty accurate.
I appreciate the thoroughness.
All right, let's get into it.
So who's got a home?
Me.
Not not.
Ben's?
Why is Ben here?
It's me.
No, I live in a house now.
I live in a house.
It's amazing.
Jesus Christ.
He's moving up in the world.
I've lived in a house and it's really nice and you should all move to my city and be my real life buddy friends.
Before we go into this, first we should have a show of hands or say I.
Who all has lived in a house?
I?
Yeah, okay.
So that's literally everyone?
I have not.
Wait, what?
Only ever lived in an apartment.
Who has been homeless before in here?
What?
No one?
Not us.
Has been what?
Homeless?
Yeah.
Have you ever been homeless, Ben?
No, no.
That was a vagabond for a while.
I wasn't a couch surfer or something.
No, I did like travel across Europe for a couple months, but I did technically have a home in Poland.
The room that I was staying at in Poland, I kept renting it for that time, but it was such a shit pile that it cost me five bucks a day to keep it technically owning it.
So I did technically have a home to go back to.
I just was like staying in hostels for several months there.
Well, you know, a home is where the heart is.
So I would say that Ben is sort of an internal homeless man, just for the lack of substance within him.
This is for the lack of soul in general.
Yeah, because I have no heart to put anywhere, therefore I cannot have a home by definition.
But similar to that, my mother called me brutal the other day and I just won.
How is that related at all?
A lot.
He's talking about how you had no heart.
I just wanted to say it.
That's right.
That's it is important, though.
Yeah, Jesse is the one who has been homeless for some period of time, living in his car, I think.
So it would have been nice to hear from him, but he's dead, so what can we do?
He's off celebrating his birthday.
Everybody wish Jesse a happy birthday.
A happy birthday, happy birthday, happy birthday.
Okay, fucking homes.
I hate not being alive.
I think you can all agree I want to continue being alive and homes are a great way to do that.
You do still have a unique perspective here, so you grew up in like an apartment or something?
Yeah, I've never been in a house ever.
Well, I mean, I've been inside of one.
But I've never lived inside of one ever.
Okay, are we making a distinction between home and house here?
No.
We all have homes.
Well, yeah, but what I'm saying is house is different than apartment, and those are both homes.
It's like an umbrella term.
It's not like sandwich in that way.
Yeah, it's vague.
You don't know it.
You can't define it, but you know it when you see it.
Exactly.
But it is different because I'm not a houseboy, so I don't know the luxuries that come with owning a house.
How have you gotten away with being as loud as you are in an apartment?
I know what you made, did you?
What are you talking about?
I was quiet as they come, bro.
I moved into an apartment, you know, like two years ago or whatever when I moved out to Cincinnati.
And yeah, like it's always been an issue having to be quiet when I'm recording shit.
Now granted, it's not just that you live in an apartment, but you also live in a shitty run down shack of an apartment.
Oh, mine?
Oh yeah, that's true.
Who are you talking to?
That's true for mine as well.
In this case, it's me.
I would bet money that mine is significantly worse than wherever you currently reside.
Probably.
I make it nice.
Do you get noise complaints, Monty, at all?
Well, no.
There was one time where someone threatened to call the cops just because they thought that I was literally dying.
Okay.
You better stop dying or I'm going to call the cops.
How is that a threat?
Well, you know how it is.
You never want the cops involved because they've got guns.
They will kill you with the slays.
Just stop all your health problems.
Monty's not quite white enough to be safe from that shit.
The thing about my neighbors is that I'm fairly certain that literally every single one is a drug dealer.
I'm fairly certain about this.
They're all up at weird hours of the night.
And the way in my apartment setup, there's like a window to my left here and I can see into like a house that's next to the apartment complex.
And that person always mows their lawn at exactly around 3 a.m.
And also they look like they're stumbling over.
What the fuck?
How did they get away with that?
That's literally dark out.
You cannot see what you're doing.
Yeah.
Yes, I know.
Not to mention literally waking up everyone.
Yeah.
I guess that's why Monty doesn't get complaints because he just planes right in.
That's very true.
I know I've talked about it.
That's like the most...
It would literally have to be entirely full of psychopaths for this to be able to happen.
Yeah.
For not one person in the apartment to put a stop to it, that would be insanity.
I live in an apartment where it's like this.
If I pay my rent on time, I'm like an exemplary tenant.
I'm like way ahead of the curve here.
So when I get noise complaints, what they usually amount to, it's not like they talk to the manager or anything,
I just get an intense pounding on one of my walls and then I know it's time to be quiet.
There are shitloads of studies that show that living in an apartment basically deprives you of humanity and dignity.
Studies show that people who live in apartments are 72% more gullible.
Gullible?
What are you trying to say about me, dude?
Well, I grew up in a house, so I'm bringing class to this joint.
That's what I'm doing.
Yeah.
I was trying to hit us with a fake stat and that was the joke is that it's gullible.
Yeah, it's one of those gullible results.
Well, I didn't call for it.
I didn't call for it.
Shit.
Only munchy fell for it.
Yeah, I looked up on the ceiling and said, you're adopted.
Okay, let's talk about this.
Who aspires to be a homeless vagabond?
Me.
Oh, me.
I personally was always, see, having grown up in a house and having only known people that lived in houses,
you know, like a bunch of cucks, I always just assumed it was the thing that you do, you know, like going to college.
Of course, it's just the thing that you do.
But like going to college later on in life, I like, I came, I saw what it's like.
I saw what apartments are like and I think I always was like, wow, why does anyone fucking bother with a house?
It seems like such a hassle when you can just pay some money and live in a place and not have to buy it.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't know.
It's like that.
When I understood that I could just go out and just like get an apartment, I thought it was nice.
And I was like, I'd be fine with this.
I would be okay with this.
Well, the funny thing about it is I think that the attachment to houses and everything is very much a good old American dream thing.
Like it's very much our fathers and their fathers' generations desire to like own their own land and be like, oh, I am my own man with my own land
and I can do whatever I want and I build this super beautiful house.
But then the funny thing is they all follow like the same blueprint of what they want it to be.
Like the idea is, oh, I get my own place.
I do whatever I want with and then you just make it look exactly like any other house that you saw in a fucking catalog on HGTV.
I mean, ultimately home ownership, it is like a better deal in the long run.
So like I guess ideally, no, you don't want to live in an apartment forever.
If you buy a house, you save more money in the long run.
But if it would be, if all else being equal, I don't mind the idea of living in an apartment, I think it's fine.
Let me sell you on this right now because I don't really care about living in an apartment right now.
Economically, it is fine with me to live in an apartment.
But like the recording thing is an issue and I need a place to build a studio where I can record at any time I want to
and I know exactly what I'm going to get.
There will be no disturbances.
I need that.
So like if you could like live in an apartment and like rent a studio, that's fine.
But then you're just renting two things.
So like Ben was saying, if you can get yourself a house and get yourself the exact kind of setup you want
with just what you need there and nothing extra.
You're not wasting your money on a billion dollar mansion or something.
Just something with the essentials.
That to me seems like really good.
Plus the fact that you have your own space.
If you can get a little distance away from other people, that seems nice.
But I just want the ability to do shit in my own place and not have to be concerned that I'm bothering other people.
Like throw a party with a lawn or something.
You know, just that seems like a nice thing to do sometimes.
I want to talk about that all American in parentheses dad dream of having a house, having your own land and stuff is that
statistically speaking, there's going to be a conflict of interest within yourself regarding time management.
Because if you're that kind of guy, you're probably also a guy who works a lot.
A guy who wants to make lots of money, right?
And in the case of my dad, right, he's really proud of this house that he's gotten for his family.
He put a lot of work into obtaining the house.
But he scarcely puts the amount of time that he knows he needs to put into, maintain the house to keep it even slightly livable.
Because he's always working all the time.
My mom is always busy doing things, barely has time for anything.
And I'm the same way.
Like, I don't really like doing anything other than just focus on one single very specific goal of what is my job that makes me money.
And I wish just everything else in my life just cleaned and fixed itself.
It's like they say you gotta...
Did you just like put a fan next to your microphone or something?
Well, there's been a fan on.
Oh, it just suddenly got really loud.
How come Benz gets to have a fan on and I fucking don't even though I need it more than he does because I live in California?
Benz lives in Atlanta.
It's real hot here.
I mean, I'm going to noise filter all of it out in the final recording.
Okay, Ben, what were you recording something?
What was the saying?
Well, I was just going to say it's like, well, now it's not funny.
I was going to humorously subvert a common cliche and say, you know what they say, get busy working or get busy dying.
But now the timing is off and I would have been legendary.
It would have been legendary.
Anyways, yeah, with what Davoo was saying, my dad is a big time house guy.
He's, you know, we've owned several houses, never like paid one off all the way or anything.
The house I'd been living in up until just recently was a fucking gigantic house where we had Radcon.
We'd been in there for nine years, but parents have done countless fucking things to it and they never stopped tinkering with it.
And like my dad, his basically the way he lives is like he works on weekdays and then comes home and he doesn't do anything to the house.
But on all of his weekends, it's just like obsessive house maintenance.
Okay, let me do everything I can to this house.
But it's never like he doesn't necessarily have the best priorities when it comes to fixing the house because sometimes you got to fix something that's broken.
Sometimes you're trying to add something new on and it's like this constant battle of like you want the new thing, but then the old things breaking down and you just got to, like the house is never perfect.
It's been nine years and the house is still far from perfect.
Yeah, it's never fucking finished.
Like when I moved in to this house for the first time a couple years ago, it was like that was when I was full force making videos and stuff.
So like I was just spending all my time getting home from window cleaning and then working on editing.
And it was literally almost a year before I started like seriously unpacking 80% of my fucking boxes.
Because it's just like whenever do I want to do these Mamby Pamby house maintenance things.
I never get around to it.
I just want to like find a maid who I can really trust.
You know, that's just all I really need in life.
That is exactly the right attitude.
Okay, let me let me drop a red pill bomb on this.
It's going to offend lots of people give a shit about their houses.
Despite the fact that I like the idea of having a house is just like a place you live in.
All these people I spent, I see on like every day as I'm driving out summertime, everyone's out working on their lawn.
They're out doing things.
They're out there out fixing up shit.
All these people spending on their time doing that shit.
I see as people who have given up on their real dreams.
They're now filling the hole in their life with maintaining their fucking lawn and designing their house.
Why don't you like, okay, like I spend my time pursuing like a second career full time.
That's how I spend all of my life.
And when I just think about like how much time, guys like, and this is my dad.
I love my dad.
He's the best man in the world.
But when I think about all the fucking time he's devoted to caring for his goddamn lawn.
I'm sure he really cares about it.
But for fuck's sake, you could have literally built like he wants to do be like a car sale or not a car sale.
He was thinking about during his life starting a car dealership.
I'm like, think about all the time you could have devoted into like the side dream you have had.
You could have done that if you hadn't just worked on your fucking lawn so much.
We need to consolidate work.
We need to have specialists who go around entire towns.
They're the ones in charge of maintaining the lawn.
They're most efficient at it.
They're the best at it.
You tell them what you want and we stop this shit about people maintaining their own lawns.
It's a waste of time.
The whole time sink aspect of it.
It's always like that's part of why I never was that was like an apartment doesn't sound so bad because a house carries with it all this maintenance shit and especially lawn shit.
Like if I ever did own a house, I would really be a big deal to me that there would be no lawn.
You guys go the whole self-help book for success tip of you are a bucket full of rocks and you could fill yourself up with big rocks and small rocks.
You guys all know this metaphor.
Basically the idea is you're a bucket.
Everyone's a bucket.
Say it right now.
I am a bucket.
Yeah.
And you could fill yourself up with fucking rocks.
And big rocks are your dream.
Wanting to start a family, wanting to become a businessman, wanting to become a billionaire, trillionaire, whatever.
Then small rocks are things like maintaining your lawn or things like making sure like you're perfectly fucking shaved every day or things like talking to each of your friends every day.
And the thing about rocks, the thing about like fucking physics and shit is that if you put all the small rocks in first, there is barely enough room for big rocks.
But if you put all the big rocks in first, the little tiny ass pebbles just find their way around.
The little pebbles bounce in and out of the big rocks and there's ends up being enough room for everything if you put the big rocks in first.
And I remember my dad giving me this lecture and he very much prioritizes his time like this.
Like he, this is a man who was never able to get into video games no matter how much they casualized themselves.
The whole Facebook Wii generations came and went and he was like, I can't justify, I can't find a video game that I can enjoy spending time with my family whilst playing so I'm not playing video games, right?
That's the only thing my dad will do.
Anything that either promotes his business or helps his family or the only two things he can justify doing with his life.
And I feel similarly.
That makes a lot of sense and I think that what I was going to say after that point is that I do understand that guys like my dad as well, like he clearly has his priorities straight.
And for him doing the lawn stuff is I think a form of relaxation.
It's what he does when he's not worried about his business or paying the bills and stuff.
So I get it but I still see that as wasted time and I don't care for it.
For me that's washing dishes, working in the kitchen, that's my relaxation time.
This is coming at a good time. I just got my first place.
And I've kind of found the perfect middle ground that does, this is what you need.
You need a townhouse because it is the perfect interstice of everything you're talking about.
Okay, so I was really worried when getting a place.
I was worried that an apartment would have the problem yours has of noise complaints.
I work all night into the dead of night. I do podcasts. I do raps. I'm loud.
I need to have space where people aren't going to give me noise complaints constantly.
A place like yours I would not be able to do it.
But staying in some of the other apartments that I guested in, we got away with a little bit more loudness because they were just a little bit more open.
I had thicker walls and stuff, just better apartments.
And it made me realize, okay, it's not like I need to be an entire yard away from someone else.
I just need one that's like as a center of the house, whereas yours doesn't really have anywhere that's not surrounded.
Yeah, that's right.
So a townhouse, you have nobody above and below you, so that's taken care of.
You've only got people on your sides.
The way that mine is organized, they're not quite exactly directly next to each other on one side.
So I've got my office set up and it's a split.
So there's an upstairs and a downstairs.
And the way it's organized is perfect.
It's just big enough that I can do my recording in here.
There's space for multiple people, but it's small enough that you can take care of it all really easily.
Cleaning the whole house takes less than an hour because it's so fucking tiny.
And deep cleaning it would take no time at all.
But here's the best part.
I've got a lawn, a front yard and a back yard, and the townhouse takes care of it.
Because it's all one giant yard that we all share.
So while there is a little chunk of it that's like, this is my yard.
It's all just one big shared yard and they just have yard maintenance people go around every couple of days
and they even fucking mulch the shit.
And they completely maintain the yards, like front and back.
It's pristine at all times and I never have to touch it.
And that's so fucking important to me for exactly the reason you're describing.
Like, I maximize all my time.
This past week has just sailed by for me because all of my time has either been spent making videos or fucking my girlfriend.
And those are the only two things that I want to be doing.
I don't want to have to stop doing either of those to go fucking clean the yard for an hour.
I realize the real difference here between these guys like our dads and ourselves.
And it's that, you know, at least they're later part of their lives when we knew them, when they're like established and they're all that shit.
Like, they're now thinking of like, they do have time in their lives when they choose to just not really do work, you know?
Like, they have already put in the work. They have now made it.
They've got a giant house or, you know, they've got a house. They've got a family.
It's time to relax a little bit. The hustle has been done.
I totally want that life. Like, I want to get to a point where I don't feel this constant pressure to fucking make videos at literally all times.
But all I want, I don't want to free that time up so I can mow the lawn.
I want to free that time up so I can play a video game.
That's all I want.
My big dream right now is that I can play a video game ever. That is my big dream.
I never want to get to that point because for me, life is struggle and when the struggle is over, you might as well die.
Exactly. But I suppose there's a degree.
Well, I feel like I want to have relaxation periods just because I see people who burn themselves out.
Even if they have energy, they eventually become hacks because they became artists every day, 24 hours a day to the point that they lost their humanity and forgot.
Which is why my plan after I finish my freaking video game is to then move to Atlanta and then be a friend guy who goes out with friends.
And then take a couple words off.
Ben, I refuse to believe that you don't spend any time just playing a video game for no reason.
No, no, no, no. I'm not saying there's no need for leisure ever.
But I never want to hit a point where I'm like, I'm done with work. I won't pursue anything else.
It's time to just relax. It's time to just take the rest of my life easy.
I mean this on more of a day by day basis.
What I admire is the ability to like, okay, I worked for eight hours and now I get to play video games and not work.
That's not how I've been living. I've been living a 24 hour work cycle for the last year.
The people I admire most are those who minimize that kind of time.
Digi fucking your girlfriend doesn't count as work. I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Well, that's my first escape from work.
Right. Well, because for me, it's all about like, if I'm not doing work, then there's the moment I walk away from the computer.
There is a timer I hear in my head that goes off.
Maybe even with the fucking Metroids now.
And so like, I haven't shut that thing off for five fucking years.
Like ever since I was like 18 and a half and I finally got a good work ethic, I haven't stopped yet.
I know I'm going to have to force myself to take a break at some point to renew that passion because I know it's going to run out at some point.
Excuse me.
God damn.
Um, okay, okay.
Should we talk about our deal house? Because I don't think, are any of us in like the best house?
Fuck yes.
No, definitely not. I'm pretty close.
Oh, okay. Yeah, my ideal house, and it is a house, or you know, town house I guess, whatever.
Like one room.
I hate big houses. I would never ever want to be in a big house ever.
Well, I fucking hate them.
What kind of big house is that?
Hang on, this is Munchie's time. Why?
This is Munchie's time.
Because I'm a little boy and I want to be in a little house.
I don't need to have, I don't need to have separate rooms.
Mika, you are six and a half feet tall. You ain't no little boy.
I'm a little boy.
In this future world, do you live alone?
Munchie is the littlest boy I know, you piece of shit.
No, Munchie is the babyest boy I know, but he ain't the littlest boy I know.
He's a big baby boy.
Are you alone in this place? Do you live alone in this place?
Well, okay, ideally I would want to be with two people.
Like each of our, like my section would be the small section.
Because I want, my ideal is just my room, then a bathroom, and then a kitchen.
Maybe, no, that's it, that's it, that's all I want.
I don't want anything else.
I just want to be able to walk up, walk maybe three feet and be at my refrigerator.
I don't want to like do anything.
I want to live the fucking 3,000 pound man life, have all my characters do everything for me.
But no, no, like, because I just fucking hate-
Did you say your characters or your caretakers?
Caretakers, my characters. The Undertale 587 is going to win.
Yeah.
In this fantasy world I'm constructing for results.
Yeah, I live in a house, and my OC's just take care of me, and they are my friends.
And you're in your room, and you hear a knock on the door.
You're like, who is it? You're like, it is me, the Japanese.
Today's anime is breakfast in bed.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, he's a wonderful man to love.
But yeah, okay, this stems from me living upstairs, and every single day I walk downstairs,
I get something, then I walk back upstairs and I realize, I forgot my fucking phone downstairs.
No! No!
So I have to walk back downstairs, I have to walk downstairs, and I have to walk back upstairs again,
and that's like 30 seconds waste where I could have been getting a sick fucking frag in Quake Live, bro!
I'm drinking that fucking Game of the Seed!
I hear that, my dude.
Do you relate to not even wanting to be seen at all when you're walking through?
Sometimes I'll take the long way into the kitchen, yeah.
Well, when I was younger and more stressed out, yeah.
That's amazing.
I did during the most shameful time of my life, that's not even true,
but during one of the most shameful times of my life, I was doing the classic Hikikomori technique of P-Bottle.
Pissing?
Yeah, man!
But the reason why was fear of being seen by the people that I lived with.
Oh, that's when you were in California, right?
No, not in California, it was when I was in Somerville,
but it was when I was in that place that was like, it had gotten like,
the lease had been terminated and the landlord had been like, get out,
and we had challenged the landlord and been like, you can't just kick us out.
So we took it to court, so during the six months it was in court,
nobody was paying rent and we just squatted there.
Sick!
It was legendary, but the point is that-
And they were ashamed of being seen by them?
Well, they were kind of a bunch of, I didn't, you know-
Assholes who won't pay rent?
Some of them were a little terrible and I would try to avoid them.
So yes, for a while I was just like, I'm just going to keep my head down
and pee in bottles in my room and let God sort the rest out.
I need to make this point, this is very important and it occurred to me
because I just went to take a piss.
If you, this goes to everyone in this call and elsewhere,
I'm just letting you know, if you live in a situation
where you have to put on pants to go to the bathroom,
you're living your fucking life wrong, alright?
This is everyone needs to be your life goal and I'll tell you why,
because for the longest time I had, you know, when I was living in my parents' house
that whole nine years I had my own room that had its own bathroom
so I never had to worry about this, like it basically was like I was living in my own apartment.
But when I came back to my parents' house for a week,
when they had moved back in and they'd given shade my old room
and it was me and my girlfriend who was staying at my house for a week
and we have to leave the room to go to the bathroom.
So of course we're naked constantly in my room
and we have to put on clothes every single time we want to go to the fucking bathroom.
I'm telling you right now, Digi, this is not going to become the Digi's girlfriend podcast.
This is extremely important now to the fucking point.
You motherfuckers, you weird anti-girlfriend fucking,
you're like an anti-sacrifice.
Thank you Digi, thank you for finally saying it.
Somebody had to say it.
It's extremely important to the point about homes,
because the whole reason I got a place is to live with my girlfriend
and it was so shit.
And he goes on about, oh, we're naked all the time.
Let's hear more about that, so everyone wants to hear.
Yeah, I'm not fucking bragging about it, Nate.
It's just the situation is that you have to put on your clothes to go to the bathroom.
That is fucking bullshit.
If you're covered in fucking sex funk and you want to wash yourself off,
you got to put on all your clothes just to go to the fucking bathroom
because your fucking parents are right down the hall
and you don't want them to see you naked or smell you
or have anything to do with you when you were just fucking.
So you got to walk to the bathroom, it's a fucking nightmare.
Having your own place, nobody has to wear clothes ever, it's fucking perfect.
I'm telling you, this is how you should be living your life.
Thank you, thank you for that delightful story that I deeply appreciate
and I'm glad you told them its entirety.
The problem is it's fundamentally wrong
because I literally prefer wearing clothes than not wearing clothes.
Nate, okay, okay, I have a counterpoint to that.
I would rather die than not be wearing clothes.
Nate, if you're going to have a fucking humble bragging,
do you realize that you're basically part of the hashtag proud
and happy with my body club right here?
Maybe you should check your fucking physicality privileges.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Actually, that's opposite logic.
Fuck, I got my logic backwards.
No, don't get me wrong.
I like wearing clothes too, but I like wearing underwear.
I'm not a fan of wearing pants, but the problem is not...
Did you? Did you?
I wear shorts.
They're comfy and easy to wear.
Yeah, I did it.
I wear shorts and all the time.
The problem is not like...
The problem isn't the wearing of the clothes.
It's having to put clothes on just to go to the bathroom
and then take them back off when you get back to your room.
It's just having to go through an extra process to do something.
One time when I was like 16,
my family finally moved out of a house that only had one bathroom
between the five of us to finally having three bathrooms.
I was basically the only one that used this bathroom
and I was the only one that stayed in my room.
My brother had the same bathroom, but he was almost never there.
So basically, I had a bathroom all to myself
where no one would ever be able to hear me.
No one would see me up here, because I was the only one up here.
And just my bladder and bowel shrink drastically over the next year
because I finally wasn't holding it in all the fucking time, right?
Like, oh my God.
Daveau, you and Ben...
Imagine what the diaper lifestyle would do to that.
Yeah!
No imagining needed, brother.
I have no idea how Daveau, Ben and Victor
managed to share that middle bathroom in the house for eight months.
Very carefully.
Oh, I think I may have mentioned this in a hi-joon podcast.
I had to hold my poop in on multiple occasions.
That would have been fucking insane.
I just had my toothbrush and all my toiletries in my bedroom closet
because I knew that I don't want other people's poop particles flying all over the place.
You know what I mean?
I don't want that.
Yeah.
Whenever I needed something, I would take it from the closet.
That makes sense.
I legit have never...
Like, I never appreciated how much I wanted my own place
until I was forced out of that room.
Like, again, the room I was in might as well have been an apartment.
Like, I only had to come downstairs to go to the kitchen or to leave the house
and everyone else was so far away.
It really felt like I was on my own.
Being put into the middle of the house for just one week
was like abject horror for me.
Like, I hated it.
It was so bad because you could hear people talking all over the house.
I can't record if I hear someone talking in the distance.
Like, if I'm worried that they're going to come in here
and interrupt my recording or something.
Stuff like that tries to be insane.
I really need a lot of space for the people in that space
to understand what I'm doing.
I hate the idea of I'm at home, so my mom doesn't know I'm recording
or she doesn't know how long the recording lasts.
So she comes, oh Conrad, what is going on?
God damn it, I'm in the middle of some shit.
The whole living with families, all the fucking stress of living with families stuff.
I think I found a cheat for it, which is that if you move away from your family's house easily
and you could still afford to do so,
but of your own volition through financially good ideas,
you realize and decide to just move back in your family's house temporarily,
all that stress magically isn't there.
At least that was the case with me.
Because I moved back in with my family.
The room I'm living in now is not the room I was living in before.
Because I used to live up in another room that was basically an apartment just like Digi's room.
But now I'm living in a room that's just across the hallway from where my parents live.
And for some reason, the fact that I felt like I was doing this out of my own volition
with all this agency made me not get stressed out about it.
It used to be if I'm down in the kitchen and anyone else is in the kitchen,
I have this fucking death glare at them of like,
I don't want to be in the kitchen at the same time as someone else.
But now it's like, man, I reach for a spoon at the same time you reach for a fork
and we have to make a slight grunt at one another because we're in the same general place.
I don't want to kill myself now.
I'm just going to say, if you ever live in a situation where you're afraid of encountering the people you live with,
I think that you have a problem that needs to be sorted out.
I don't know exactly what it is.
Don't worry, there's other defense mechanisms.
For example, the absolutely dreaded, what are you looking for?
You know, when you're like going through the shelves looking for a thing and you're just like,
my mom's going to say, what are you looking for?
I don't want her to know what I'm looking for.
It doesn't literally matter though.
I just don't want her to know.
And so you know what I would do to deflect that?
I'd be like, every shelf I open, I'm going to be like, oh, sweet, that shelf is exactly what I want.
Ooh, this shelf has what I want too, so that no one thinks I'm looking for anything.
I'm just like constantly happy when I'm looking around the shelf.
Oh, sweet.
I'm totally with you.
I'm totally with you on that.
I hate when people get involved in my business and I don't want them to be,
which is great because I've been living on my own for a couple years now and it's great.
But the time in my life when I was, I did this for a while too.
After I left college and was living at home and was just doing shitty jobs,
and I think it might have been even before I started doing YouTube-y stuff,
I was paying rent to my parents, but they would always be on me to be working harder,
to finish my degree, just go do the things that you obviously need to be doing,
that I would do to some small degree but not nearly enough.
So all the time, this is a big pattern for me throughout my life.
When there are people that I need to do things for and I'm not living up to the obligations I've made to them,
I will just avoid them, which is a common thing that all people do.
So for me, this was completely, I would avoid contact with my parents as much as physically possible
to the point of never ever seeing them and never leaving my room.
But it was entirely because I was not doing the things that I needed to do.
It was entirely my fault that I was making the situation shitty.
And I'm just saying that I see a lot of that on other people.
If there's something you're trying to avoid by not seeing people,
generally you're going to be better off addressing them.
The reason why I was peeing in bottles is because the people that I lived with at the time,
it was a bit of a rogues gallery, but one of them was like super OCD.
And if he happened to catch a glimpse of you,
not OCD, he was bipolar.
And if he happened to catch a glimpse of you while you were walking through the room,
while he was in a manic episode, he would rope you into some complete fucking nonsense.
There were multiple occasions where I would just be walking through and he'd be like,
Ben, can you help me? We need to rearrange this furniture.
He can't stay like this.
Ben, have I met this guy?
No, no, you have not met this guy.
But he was...
No, no, no, I just want to say.
And then we would move furniture for two hours and he would be like,
yeah, we need to move this couch upstairs.
And then two weeks later, he would catch you again and he'd be like,
okay, we got to move furniture again.
And then we would move it back.
So I just wanted to avoid that so much.
I'm with you on that, Ben.
But really, that's a surface level issue.
The deeper problem is you had put yourself in a situation where you were living with a bunch of degenerates
who were willing to do this kind of squatting, weird, not leaving when they're not watching the situation.
Of course it had problems, but you know what?
It was fucking worth it to live rent-free.
So fuck you.
Okay.
If it was worth it.
It was the right thing to do and you'll never convince me otherwise.
Objectively.
I've pretty much been doing my best for a number of years now.
In fact, and with my family, really what my parents could have been doing was flying to wherever did you was
and be like, hey, when you're going to write him a video so he can edit it.
You know what this really is?
It's if you can look in the mirror at the end of the day and you see and you look in your own eyes
and you see I am doing everything in my power to fulfill my obligations to the people in my life.
If you can do that without wincing, without shying away, then you shouldn't be afraid of looking at anyone or facing anybody.
Yeah, I don't fulfill the obligations to other people in my life, but I make it very clear to them.
There you go.
Well, alright then.
As long as people know.
It's like if you're lying or hiding things from people, that was me.
That's what I was thinking.
You should have a lying podcast.
I'm very pro lying.
Who, lying?
That's a good idea.
I'm very pro lying.
Hey, okay, let's completely shift gears and talk about what are we going to do to end homelessness?
If we're going to...
No, hold on.
What are we going to solve that issue?
Apparently only Munchie has shared his dream home so far.
Wait, I want to go again.
This is the Munchie podcast now.
No, it's not.
Just quickly.
Just fucking quickly.
Other people are talking about I don't want to talk to people.
Okay, I've never been like that except for recently because my uncle.
I'm sure many of you have heard murmurs and rumors and stumbles and mumbles about my uncle.
Uncle Alex, right.
Here's the red pill.
Here's the quick explanation.
He is 55 years old and he loves pole on 4chan.
Sick.
Yes.
Whoa, shit.
He goes on pole every single day of his life and he's always making threads.
Is he Barack Obama's half brother by any chance?
Probably, probably.
He's just not black enough.
He's still black but just not enough.
Anyway, every time I walk past him, he's on his iPad fucking just checking like upvoting
of 4chan images which I'm assuming is a thing.
He's buying that 4chan gold status.
Of course, yeah.
That gold pass.
Yeah, yeah.
Every single day he's buying more 4chan gold.
Yeah, exactly.
And then when I walk past him, he's like, hey dude, you see this fucking Pepe image?
Check this out, bro.
I'm like, oh, that's pretty nice.
Yeah, it's a pretty rare Pepe.
Yeah, please, please just let me, please just let me get my fucking drink.
Nah, bro, dude, check this shit fucking out.
You see what Trump's doing?
He's going to fix the fucking moon, bro.
He's going to fix it.
The warming's going to be gone, bro.
What?
Fix the moon.
Why?
Yeah, he's going to fix the moon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's going to make the moon great again.
He's going to take all the excess heat from the greenhouse gases on earth and put it on
the moon to make the moon nice and warm.
Oh, shit.
And we can then start agriculture on the moon.
On the moon.
Of course, we recycle everything.
Exactly.
Makes a lot of sense.
Precisely.
So basically, my uncle is completely incoherent and whenever I walk past him, he always
wrote me into a red pill conversation about Trump or Pepe or any sort of 4chan dub memes.
And I want to avoid that as much as possible.
So I just stay up in my room and wait for him to leave.
Oh, and the reason he's always over at my house now is because his life is falling apart
because he goes on poll too much.
Well, it sucks when you're young and you still live with your parents and you don't have
a job to afford your own place yet, which happens until pretty recently.
Yeah, there's just nothing you can do.
You've got to deal with it.
So my dream home is to basically recreate Owl Farm, which is the place that Hunter S. Thompson
lived.
Hunter S. Thompson lived on his own, like, acre of land up in the hills of Aspen, Colorado.
And he had this relatively small house.
I would probably put a bigger house there because I'm obsessed with living in a labyrinth.
That's also my dream house, is to live in a labyrinth.
But he has this giant yard and he would just have shitloads of guns.
And he was just always firing guns on his property and, like, fucking...
He had, like, a whole shooting range and he was just fucking around.
He had peacocks everywhere, just roaming.
And he would get into gunfights with his neighbors and shit.
Like, they'd just shoot at each other's property when they were mad at each other.
And, like, it's basically a libertarian utopia.
And that's what I want to live in.
I just want to have space to do literally any batshit crazy stuff I want to do.
Dude, dude, dude.
You said Owl Farm, right?
Owl Farm?
It's called Owl Farm.
Instead of any of the shit you just described, I'm just picturing Drake from Hotline Bling
with his Owl sweatshirt.
Just, like, that place is Owl Farm to me.
Did you?
So you described it as, like, a libertarian utopia.
Imagine if it was, like, on a very specific mountain where, like, the Colorado Capitol
building was, like, within view with a telescope.
So you would have a telescope to see the tiny government.
I mean, he...
Yeah!
That may have actually been the case, because I think he was pretty close to the sheriff's
office, which he also ran for sheriff of Aspen.
But, yeah.
Yeah.
His...
Just seeing...
There's videos of, like, his property out there.
In fact, there's a video of Conan O'Brien going there and, like, hanging out on his shooting
range of firing shitloads of guns.
And he has, like, a bar set up at the shooting range.
This is a man who literally has a giant stash of alcohol next to his giant stash of guns.
And he can just do that.
Pretty perfect.
You know?
And shoots.
It's Colorado, man.
You can do whatever.
I don't give a single fuck.
He's already attained greatness.
It's time to enjoy it, I guess.
Yeah.
Who gets the fuck anymore?
Anyway, my dream house really is just a labyrinth, but I guess I can be more specific.
I don't need the guns and shit.
I don't need it to be, like, a farm.
But I do like the labyrinthine idea.
I can get more specific.
I want it to be in the woods.
You know, I want it to be far away.
I don't need it to be in the mountains, because generally that's a lot more expensive.
I'm fine with flatland.
I don't mind flatland.
But I do like trees.
So you have that.
I don't know.
Like, there'll just be a lot of specific ways to make it labyrinthine.
I want a lot of basement shit.
I'd like one somewhere, like, you kind of go into a mountain, and then you come out the
other side, and there's another door over there.
That'd be pretty cool.
And especially the best thing to have a labyrinth for is to have, like, this own little sectioned-off
area that a teenage offspring could live in without having to get, you know, that way
it would really facilitate when they're going through their phase of not wanting to be near
their parents and shit.
You can make that really easy for them.
You'll never have to see them, right?
That's what I would love to facilitate to my progeny.
Yeah.
That's basically it.
Excellent.
I guess here's where I want to live.
It forces me to consider, like, what I want my life to be like as well.
So, basically, it would be a house by itself, similar to the one I grew up in.
On Mars.
Yeah.
The center of the Earth.
It'd just be on, like, I don't know, some pretty quiet street fairly far away from another
house, but probably within, I don't know.
It could be, like, 50 feet away.
This might be an important point.
That even though I want this labyrinth on this, like, acre of land, I want it to be
immediately surrounded by, like, nothing but stores.
Like, I don't want it to be in the middle of nowhere.
Like, I want it to be, like, right in the heart of a city.
Like, it's a public park that I've built a house in.
Yeah.
I was going to say, my ideal house would be just like, it would be just like a dungeon.
It would be just like, or, it would be just like a single, like, dungeon room, like a
spacious dungeon room at the top of, like, a stone spire.
And it would be totally ice, but it would be, but it would be a tall stone spire that
you had to climb some, like, spiral staircases to some stir, spiral, like, like, hours and
hours of climbing a styrofoam staircase to get up to.
But it would be right in the middle of a metropolitan city so that I could just, like, look down
and observe.
So I'd be isolated from it.
I'd be isolated from all that hullabaloo, but I could see it.
And if I wanted to, I could put it, I could maybe go and get down there if the mood struck
me.
You might be interested in the house that I'm currently living in, my family's house,
because it's like, you've seen it in some of my videos.
It's 10 acres of land.
You can do whatever here, but it's like near the highway, and it's like six minutes away
from a Walmart and a quick trip.
Not good enough.
Okay, there you go.
I want to literally, like, if I leave my property, then there is a store.
Like, that's what I want it to be.
Like, I am living on the, like, just build a mall around my house is what I'm saying.
Plus, you've got shit internet, so that's definitely the worst part.
But there's, like, good internet just a little bit out of reach.
I think if you could, like, drop, like, a 5K investment, you could probably get someone
to stretch it out.
There's also a hospital, like, four minutes away from here.
It's on this, there's this giant fucking hospital on this pure road.
I don't necessarily want to live right next to a hospital.
Well, dude, like, you're saying, go, let me go.
God damn point.
Okay, so, so, so it's, it's whatever.
It's a fucking suburb, fairly close to the center of the metropolitan area.
Like, like the outside of Boston or something, that would be pretty cool.
And, and, so about the house itself, it would be, I don't know, like, medium-sized, but,
but the size is important, because I want to have a family.
I want to have kids.
Two.
Two, Vincent and Charlotte.
Twin perfect godchildren.
The wife doesn't matter.
She'll probably be there, but I don't care about her.
Just stop.
Okay, I was going to say, like.
And here's the important part.
Here's the important part.
The house can't, okay, so first of all, it's got to have a studio where I can do all my
work.
That, that's a, that has to happen.
It has to be a nice place.
But other than that, the house has to be small enough, not as big as the house I grew up
in, because that house was too big and it forced us to be able to stay away from each other.
I want to be forced to interact with my family so that they can't avoid me.
They can't get mad at me.
We will always be forced to communicate with each other and none of us will ever be low
nuts.
What do you mean, though?
That's what I want.
That's not how fucking it works.
That's not how it works.
If they're forced to interact with you, they're going to get mad at you way more often.
He means, he means they can't like, storm off to their room and be alone.
That's not, they, that's fucking not, no.
Every, the best of students I've ever made in my fucking life was run away to my room
and say a reaction.
David, David, you've got, you've got your perspective.
And here is my perspective.
I lived in a big, big house where I was far away from everyone where I wanted to be and
that had negative consequences.
And what I'm trying to say is I'd like to find ways to avoid those.
And being too isolated from my family made me a lonelier person and has made me the person
I am today.
And I'd like to avoid that from my kids.
Nate, Nate, having, having been in the same fucking family, let me say, let me say that
being isolated from...
Wait, you guys are brothers?
Oh my God.
I know.
Being isolated from said family was just the greatest thing, was the only, the only respite
from, from the terror.
Well, that's a great opinion you guys have.
I'm sure love your opinion there.
Being separate, being separate was the best part of it.
Well, consider this Ben, consider the fact that you're two years older than me.
And, uh, uh...
You two are brothers?
Everything that that entails.
And maybe I'm just a lonelier person by nature.
But nonetheless, I don't want that.
And I want to avoid that.
That's what a family is literally for.
So that's what I wanted to serve.
No, no, it's not.
No, it's not.
I mean, who?
I don't give a fuck.
Fair enough.
Nate, Nate, Nate, Nate's lonely.
He has post-attack.
I'm just saying, I'm just saying, like, I, like, I would, I would fucking chafe and get mad
if I lived in some place where I was like forced to interact all the time.
Like, I mean, what I would do for my house, like I said before, is there would be this area
where some teenagers could live there all by themselves, but have some other rooms that
are right next to each other in case some or all of my kids are like that.
You know, I'm sure that Pete, I know that people fucking like grind that whole introvert,
extrovert thing into the ground, but it's fucking true.
You can observe it.
There are people who get tired when they're around people and get energetic when they're
alone and vice versa.
It's just a fucking fact.
I, I literally get tired if I'm around too many.
If people are in the room, it like sucks my life force away and I'm going to get fucking
mad and tired and dead.
So, like, yeah.
I've been, I'm an introvert.
I need people to come up to me and say, I fucking know, but it's just goddamn true.
All right.
That's fine.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
Oh, I got you.
All right.
Let's move on.
Oh my God.
Is that best guy ever?
When did you get here?
Everybody.
All right.
I'm the best guy ever.
Oh my God.
I'm, I'm speaking, I'm totally speaking here from a purely self-serving perspective.
I'm aware of that and yeah, I don't care.
Which one do I shoot indeed?
This isn't objective at all.
This is purely subjective.
Okay.
This is a related note.
How many of you, when growing up, were allowed to lock your doors?
Oh shit.
We didn't even have locks.
I don't think, yeah, I don't think we had locks.
What?
Yeah, it's fucked up, right?
It fucked me up.
It's not that fucked up.
I literally locked my door even though my door, like, I'm upstairs, so if anyone wanted to
come back and just...
No, no.
See, that's the sort of thing.
No child needs to lock their door from their...
Oh for fuck's sake.
There's nothing to do.
I would have, I forgot all about this.
I completely forgot just how angry I was every fucking day of my life that I couldn't lock
my door.
My life would have been so much better if I could have locked my door.
It was honestly, I think it was cruel.
I honestly think it was cruel that I was made to live in a room that had no lock.
You know what, I'll give you the peace of mind that can come from having a lock if you
feel like you really need it.
You know, I can understand that.
But I don't really like the idea of living in a house where everyone's got their doors
locked all the time.
It's just weird.
I don't fucking know, man.
Especially having kids, that means you're creating all new human beings who did not fucking
choose to be part of this.
I understand the idea of a locked door between, like, a romantic relationship of two adult
people who like...
You give the children too much credit.
They're worthless.
They have no interest.
But children do not, did not fuck...
This is one of the things that Stefan Molyneux, world's smartest and best guy ever, said
about is that children did not choose this relationship.
And so if they want to fucking lock you out or kill you, they have that fucking right.
So...
Stefan Molyneux thinks way too highly of children's intelligence and agency.
Yeah.
Anyway.
But yeah, I had an issue with my younger brother because he wanted to just...
One night, he decided, hey, David, we all have separate rooms now.
We've been sleeping in different rooms for a few years now.
But what if I just sleep in your room for tonight?
It'll be like a fun sleepover.
And I was like, sure.
And then the next night, he did it again.
And then two days later, he did it again.
And I was like, all right, Aaron, no more sleeping in my bedroom.
And then he just kept doing it.
And then eventually he knew I was going to say no.
So like a few hours before bedtime, he would just start hanging out in my room.
And he'd sort of get comfortable in a chair that's right next to the bed.
And so, you know, but this is where the fucking immovable object meets the other fucking immovable object.
And I'm just like, no, you're getting the fuck out of my room.
And he would get mad at me.
He felt entitled to my attention.
There was times where, like, he knocks on the door and he starts opening it.
And I know he's going to be warming his way through a three-hour fucking espionage plan
to get into my room for the night.
So I just immediately bang on the door the other direction, block him out.
By the time he got strong enough...
He just heard some bullshit.
What's wrong with his room?
But he's just a fucking lonely person who has to be around human beings all the time.
Now that he's an adult, he says that he borderline passes out on the road whenever he's driving to work
because there's no one to talk to.
So yeah.
So it got to the point that he was, like, taking pocket knives and stabbing holes in the door.
So mad I wouldn't let him sleep in my room.
No fucking, I'm not fucking joking.
Two separate doors among two separate houses, he'd be punching holes in my door for being mad at me.
To the point that I had to start, like, I enacted an absolute policy of,
no one opens my door at all, ever, without knocking and then getting permission.
That's how it should be, of course.
And then years, years, years later, well, I guess seven, eight, nine years later,
like, that my brother has since greatly matured,
but that policy is still in place and everyone locks the door because I'm a fucking psychopath
who doesn't like being fucked with.
Anyway, that's why you need locks and doors, you know, because of that.
There's this personality difference.
Davoo, you're not a psychopath for not wanting some fucking rude foreign invader
to destroy and dismantle your fucking lands.
Some goddamn room immigrant trying to take your goddamn sleeping jobs
and then ruin your economy, understandable.
You're the only one sane in that circumstance.
That's debatable, but sure.
I'm open to the idea of having the locks on the doors,
but I think I definitely feel weird about, like,
if my kid, like, locked his door every night for no reason,
I would object, I would object.
You are.
I locked my door every fucking night.
Yeah, dude, like, who are you to tell him, like, dude, you should...
I am the father.
It is my house.
I paid for the house in the situation.
What are you gonna tell them to do instead?
You're gonna be like, you're not gonna be in your room.
You're gonna be down here.
You're gonna be my fucking friend, you little cunt.
Is that what you're gonna say?
Yeah, like...
That's exactly right.
I won't even give him the choice because I'll just buy the house I want.
I'm that far ahead of him.
I have such a fucking vivid image of what kind of dad you are gonna be.
Like, it's gonna be really funny.
I imagine Nate as the dad...
I doubt any of you have ever seen the show Arakawa under the bridge,
but the main character is this guy who's like a lawyer
and his dad is like a rich lawyer guy
and his dad taught him, like, you always have to repay every debt in your life,
including when he, basically, when he comes of age,
then becomes a baby who he then has to take care of
in order to pay back the debt of having been raised by him
by making him then take care of his dad.
Well, that just doesn't make any sense.
That's just the circle of life, my dogs.
No, that's the son having to pay for both his own children and his parents.
That doesn't make sense.
Like, you pay it for the next generation.
Well, I don't know how that works.
It's an anime. An anime is not.
Yeah, you're right.
The point is that it's hilarious.
Yeah, I'm with ya.
Did he become a literal baby?
Did he, like, turn into one?
No, he just, like, he just...
You only see him for, like, a minute.
Like, this is just the backstory of the main character,
but his dad, like, puts on a bib and gets in a high chair
and is like, you have to feed the dad.
Oh, my fucking god.
I understand the one for that kind of justice.
No, Nate, let me explain.
Just real briefly here.
My door is always locked,
but no matter what...
What are you hiding, Munchie?
What are you hiding in there?
This life!
He's got my fucking dick!
What do you think he's hiding?
I wanna see you jack that dick, my son.
I'm gonna watch you.
I'm gonna watch you touch yourself,
and you're gonna show me what you've learned,
and I'm gonna correct your technique, you worthless baby.
Your dad has to be ashamed of our penis.
Exactly.
He says no.
Whatever.
I don't want you ripping the skin, Munchie.
I don't want you ripping the skin.
You're ripping the skin.
You're gonna learn.
But no matter what,
whenever someone knocks on the door,
I just let them in,
because they usually just like, hey, hello.
Fucking Nate's gonna be like,
his son's gonna be jacking off in his doorless room,
and Nate's gonna come in and be like,
you know, it's more efficient if you turn your hand like this.
I'm just saying,
I'm not telling you how to jack your dick,
but turn your hand this way.
I'm just saying it'd be more efficient.
You guys are all coming from the perspective
of our parents who are like,
they still, there's vestiges in culture
of being ashamed of masturbation
and being ashamed of your body.
You wanna watch your son jack off?
You wanna walk in on him?
I'm down to clown, baby boy.
Let's get this going.
Okay, this is like,
it doesn't make any fucking sense, dude.
None of us here are ashamed of mastication.
Would any of us masticate in the same room?
Yes.
That makes one of us.
Dude, we went out,
we've masticated in the same room together.
We went out and we all masticated together
in public, my dudes.
It's true.
Under the, before the eyes of God and man.
Yeah.
Basically what I'm saying is
if you don't give your child a lock,
you should be locked up in jail, that is.
Agreed, I agree.
Yeah.
You know, I'm willing to entertain you.
I remember as a kid,
one of the things I did as a kid all the time
was hear about parental policies
of other people's kids
and scoff at them for being
totalitarian and shit,
because my parents only befriended
other even Christian or Christians,
and like one family I knew,
they had a policy of
if you're going to the bathroom,
you have to keep the door slightly open.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
Okay, that's fucked.
Why?
It's like four to eight year olds,
but still, that's like 80 fucks.
I'm not, well, I mean,
if they're like little babies,
I sort of get it.
Yeah, eight is like,
what are you,
and like third grade by them?
Jesus.
Fuck's sake.
Yeah, it's pretty fucked.
At a certain point,
really there is a cut off point,
where you have to be willing
to let your child drown in the toilet
if they fuck up that bed.
It's just, you have to take that plunge.
I mean, I could see not having a lock
on the bathroom door
if you're worried about your kids.
Yeah.
I completely understand why Nate would be
hesitant to take any of our
stances into consideration,
because I'm sure that he has
no desire for his kids to come out
at all like any of us.
Of course not.
So any of the things that we take as wisdom,
because our parents did it,
or because we think it would be a good idea,
I don't think it's going to be stuff that Nate's going to listen to.
My kids are going to be the most Chad
Thundercock alpha children
of all time.
Nate, here's some basic fucking logic.
When you were a teenager,
did you need that lock?
Do you really think that that lock
really made your life worse,
or that it,
you would have been even worse
or without it?
You know, to be honest,
thinking about it,
like I would have been more comfortable with the lock.
It's true.
Right, so here's the thing, right?
You're probably thinking,
oh, well my kids,
I know all the ways that I was
like fucked in the head by my parents.
I just won't do those things.
And indeed,
most parents who give a shit
are able to,
roughly,
not make all the same mistakes
their parents did.
But the fact is,
you're going to make your own mistakes.
Parents never know,
parents never realize that.
You know, I mean,
my parents are definitely like that.
None of the problems that they were given.
But you know,
it's just, you can't be perfect life.
That's just not how fucking life works, right?
I know exactly what problems I'm going to create
for my kids.
I know exactly how it's going to go down.
I know which problems I'm going to fix
for my parents,
because my parents are terrible at communication
and just using words.
Dude, the problem you're going to have
is that your kids are going to walk down the room,
walk out of their room,
and they're going to see you
walking down naked through the hallway.
Just fuck my girlfriend up, everybody!
Just got me on my body right now.
No big deal.
Exactly the problem I'm talking about.
My kids are going to grow up
with a psychopath.
They're going to grow up with someone
who has never known how to be normal,
trying to teach them how to be normal.
And more likely teaching them
how it doesn't matter to be normal.
First of all, my kids are going to know
from the time they're born
that there is no God
and that school is bullshit.
And they're going to have to go to school
with this knowledge and talk to other kids
and be like,
I know, I can see it in my head.
A kid being like,
oh, are you Christian?
They're being like,
no, Christians are dumb.
My daddy said so.
And the next thing I know,
I'm in school fucking
at a parent-teacher conference
having to put my kid
in some kind of fucking weird,
satanic private school cult
or something.
Yeah.
Burn it all to the fucking ground, dude.
By the way,
I'm just imagining right now.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold the fuck on.
If your kid says there's no God in class
and they get taken to Satan's school.
Well, the Satan guys are more open-minded
than the Jesus guys.
Did you guys know that basically,
there's an organization,
like the Satanists,
every time there's like a new
bit of legislation passes
that gives Christians permission to do
XYZ, teach Christianian schools
in some bum-fuck-nobody town.
There's this cadre of Satanists
that I wish I could remember their name.
But they then go in
and make the same pot.
They try to be like,
okay, well, we're going to now
promote Satanism in this place.
Yeah, oh my fucking god.
It's the best.
Well, what I'm going to do with my kids
regarding religion
is I'm just not going to say shit,
or if they ask me,
I'll be like, I don't think there's a God.
But then obviously their grandparents
will be able to talk their fucking ear off.
And I will love to see what decision
they come to on their own.
Because I know there's kind of a trend
of grandchildren to latch onto the ideology
of two generations up rather than
one generation up.
So that would be really fucking cute
if my kids are like Christians.
It definitely, definitely skips a generation.
I was just, I was only,
I was just talking to one of Jackie's friends
the other day and he was telling me that,
he was telling me that like,
every other generation of his family
is a preacher,
and that every generation in between
is an alcoholic.
Yeah.
That's perfect.
It's perfect.
Yeah.
Well, my parents are,
my parents are a nihilist
and a guy who just believes in
weird random spiritual shit
that he doesn't even get into.
So like, between me and my parents
it's the same exact thing.
So I think my kids are going to be the exact same.
The only reason that I won't beat
into the heads of my children
how evil religion is,
how brainwashed all the other sheep
out there in the world are compared to them,
is because I'm afraid of that teenage backlash
that they'll just switch around to the other side.
They will.
You know what?
Jesus fucking rules.
Well, I can't take that chance.
I cannot take that chance.
The problem is that,
that your kids will get made fun of
for like believing something different.
It'll make them strong.
It'll make them powerful.
Unless you put them
into a completely distinct scenario,
like a weird satanic cult school
where like everyone thinks that shit,
you know?
But it's just like all the arguments
for why God is real
that people just bring up
are just so easily defeated by like,
remember guys,
you have no reason to believe any of this.
You're just going off on all these tangents.
Like once you're armed with the logical tools,
I mean, fuck, you know,
people talk about this for fucking centuries.
Like there's no argument anyone could make
that is any value.
No man, talking about being a bad parent,
I know that the place that I would fuck up
if I'm not really careful
is I'm going to be the fucking adoptive dad
from Three God to No Lion
who only cares about Shogi
and all of his children,
his actual children,
end up being scarred for life
because they're not good at Shogi enough
to get his attention
and his adoptive son is.
And so they hate him
and they become dysfunctional abortions forever.
You know what?
I might have to adopt.
That's what I'm going to be with,
that's what I'm going to be with fucking
like YouTube videos and video games.
It's like if my kids aren't
as obsessed with art as I am,
I'm not going to hang out with them as much
unless I really discipline myself
and I'm going to ruin them.
And yep, that's going to be my problem.
Like your kids,
like your kids coming like,
dad, want to hang out
and you're like,
guys, look,
you're just kind of embarrassing me
in front of my cool art friends.
Yeah.
I actually love this idea.
You kids are just too square.
I've got to adopt
a superior athletic older kid
to motivate my younger children
to advance to that level
and be cool and badass like that.
That is kind of genius.
Like adopt a kid to be
the older sibling to your kids.
That is kind of fun.
Oh, well, I didn't catch that at first.
That is pretty fucking genius.
I think I've seen that in an anime actually.
I think I've seen that be used
in a show and it was, yeah.
The eldest kid always has
like a thing like he feels bad
because he's not as
clearly not as loved by the parents
because he's not their progeny,
but at the same time,
the siblings really look up to them
and so he still feels like part of the family.
You adopt yourself a commune
to motivate your younger shit children
and then...
And obviously the number one place
to get adoptions from is Africa
where they have the best athletic ability.
So it's pretty much...
There you go. It works perfectly.
Did you even adopt one of those
like Russian babies?
I know like at one point in the 90s
they were adopting a lot of Russian babies
and that way you had the best alcoholic.
I already know my kids
are going to be fucking clones of me.
Like they're just...
Really?
Yeah, they are.
Don't you want to experiment with improvements
like Gohan and Dragon Ball Z?
Experiment with improvements.
Yeah, let's just let the kids
tinker with them a little bit, you know?
Yeah, that's where we're going to.
Just hammer them out a little bit
in my laboratory.
I didn't mean literal clones.
I meant they're going to be figurative clones of me.
Oh, well I meant literal.
Yeah, I see.
When you think that way,
that's like an idealistic way of thinking.
Like I've already thought, you know,
the idea of...
Okay, I'm going to have kids
who are going to be into sports.
That's just what...
I just have to get ready
for that right now, right?
I want my kids to be into sports
so I can get into sports
so I can play tennis with my kids.
That would be fucking awesome.
But like...
Yeah, I got it.
Why tennis?
Yeah, that's what Raito Koon
and Elle played.
And tennis is by far my favorite sport,
so that's why.
See, Deji, there you go.
You're still idealizing.
Look at this.
Obviously, the most obvious way to rebel against you
is to be super like western culture
and fuck weed shit, right?
I don't think my kids are going to be rebellious, though.
I was...
Me and my brothers were never rebellious.
We had no faith in it.
But your parents are like
the most rebellious people ever.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing.
That's why I think...
My attitude...
Like, everything about how I am is like
if you just put my parents in a blender,
you get me.
You know?
Like, I am exactly like them.
I don't know.
When you think that it's going to be predictable,
that will be your folly.
If you have an idea of what you want your kids to be...
I don't want to fucking talk out of our ass here anyway.
Yeah, you're completely making that up, Devu.
There's no logic to support that.
Well, so are you, though.
So are you.
You have no idea what your kids are actually doing.
I'm just saying.
It makes the most sense to me
that considering that me, Victor, and Shader
are all exactly like our parents,
and I know I'm the kind of person
who's going to be extremely close with my kids.
I'm probably going to be like right on them at all times.
Maybe they'll get annoyed with me.
Maybe they'll get sick of me
when they get into their teen phase.
But like, by the time they're teenagers,
it doesn't matter if they get rebellious in the teen phase.
You've already fucking built their mind.
Like, you know, they're already you.
Like, everyone...
But the building process doesn't go smoothly all the time,
and you never know what you're actually building.
Dude, almost every rebellious, like, kid
is like a carbon copy of their parents.
Like, you know, my mom, like,
all the things she can't stand about her mom
is just the stuff that is exactly the shit she does.
You know?
Like, everything that she criticizes her mom for
is something that she just has a different version of.
So, like, I think almost everyone,
like, anytime I hear somebody be like,
oh, my mom, she's such a fucking bitch,
she does this and this,
I'm like, you basically do that
just in a different form, you know?
Yeah.
This has been a really enlightening discussion
of homes and homelessness.
Yeah, it has.
Yeah, it's true.
Well, join us for the sequel to this in ten years
when we all have kids.
I want us to have a proper
how we raised our kids' cast.
That's a good idea.
And don't tell anyone anything about your home life.
We want it to not spoil it
for the ten-year podcast.
Yeah, don't spoil it.
Don't spoil it, anybody.
I imagine that's what Dick would do if,
like, if he gets a girl pregnant,
he's like, okay, I'm not going to see until
it's like five years old.
I want to, like, get my live reaction on the show,
like, see what the kid looks like.
I don't even know what color it is necessarily.
I mean, pipe it for 20 episodes before talking about it.
Yeah.
So, today we're going to want to close.
Yeah, go on, Munchie, go on.
Me, I just, to go with Digi,
I have never been rebellious against my mom ever.
She's always just been, hey,
shut the fuck up, you're retarded,
and also tiny.
And I'd be like, yeah, that makes sense.
Munchie, if she says that,
your mom must be enormous.
Your mom must be the largest woman in the world.
No, no, no.
Rhonda Rousey, the largest woman in the world,
aka Munchie's mom.
But it's made me think,
because I'm not rebellious as in, like, fuck you, mom.
But I am rebellious in the sense that I'm not retarded
and also angry all the time.
Oh, like, she says you're retarded,
so, like, you don't be retarded,
like, just to stick it to her?
Yeah.
You're like, joke's on you, mom.
I know what's fucking up.
Oh, okay, it's like, she always,
she's pretty, like, gullible,
and she's super hard, like, you know, lib-cuck.
Yeah, she's super gullible
because she lives in an apartment.
Exactly, exactly.
And she's also, like, really angry.
She's, like, car-cat, basically,
like, twenty-five-seven.
Yeah.
All right.
But specifically, like, in between...
Unresolved character arcs out the ass.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Anyway, so I'm, like, in IRL, offline,
I'm, like, calm, I don't really, you know,
I'm not really fucking crazy,
except for when I go out in public.
Like, when I say in real life, I mean, like,
in my room, not on the computer,
but then when I walk outside the room,
I'm just like this.
There are slivers of sanity in that.
Yeah, slivers of sanity.
Anyway, so in that, I'm, like,
very different from my mom in the sense
that I'm not fucking weird.
But, you know, I think it's the way I rebel
in the sense that I am still crazy.
Never mind, my point makes no sense.
Yeah, that's what it's like.
No, that's what it's like.
The pendulum swings.
The pendulum swings back and forth
with every generation.
Or, except for the times that it doesn't.
And except for the times that it kind of does
and kind of doesn't and falls somewhere in the middle.
No, Ben, it's pendulum within pendulum.
So that's what it is.
It's like, it's like a, it, yeah.
It's like wheels within wheels.
Hey, you know what's cool?
It's like turtles all the way down.
Title screen with the pendulum on.
I gotta be right back.
Yeah.
Oh my god, I cried.
That animation is so good, dude.
It's three minutes of pure masterpiece.
I love pendulum.
Nostalgia.
Oh, right.
That was good.
Okay guys, we're going off the rails.
We need to talk about fucking homelessness.
We don't have time to crack the code
of how to fix homelessness in America anymore.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just want to say, I just want to say
one day, if I play my cards right,
I want to be homeless.
And if at all possible,
dead in the gutter with other dudes pissing on my course.
If at all possible, that's why I'm painting.
Luckily, luckily, I mean,
you have all the tools at your disposal
to make that happen.
I'm just going to say, yeah, through God,
all things are possible.
True.
Have hope.
Take heart.
All right, let's switch to questions here.
We got a whole bunch of questions.
So let's see what we got.
Okay, here's one to start us off.
Here we go.
At Sizz White Scum 69,
who I know has asked the question before.
Yeah, that's much his alt count.
Thoughts on those who leech off your content
without patroning?
So just like thoughts on in general people
who watch our shit without paying patrons.
Remember that crime wing re eliminated?
Remember that?
That was pretty funny.
Does he mean,
does he mean wait?
Yeah.
Wait, no.
He doesn't mean people like reposting content.
He's just talking about like free watchers,
just people who watch and don't do anything.
Well, I mean, that's their prerogative, you know?
Yeah.
Like we put it out there for free.
We are not charging for it in the first place.
And it would be,
it would be really hard to gain patrons
if our content was gated to begin with.
Like you got to get an audience of people
and like most people aren't going to be that interested
or they don't think the content's worth it.
I mean, fucking Ben and Nate are both huge proponents
of never pay for any art ever.
So they,
I am not a proponent at all.
I just do that for me selfishly.
That's the whole thing for me.
I used to be on that,
but then, but then I started,
then I started making exceptions.
Like when I pirated Undertale
because I was mad that Toby Fox
didn't retweet my fucking fan art.
But then I ended up liking Undertale so much
that I went and bought it on Steam anyway,
even though I'd already played it and beaten it,
just out of guilt.
Then when was the last time you bought a game
that costed more than $15?
More than?
Well, well, I mean, that's not a fair question
because I have not, I have not,
I have not played a game that cost more than $15 in years.
Wow.
Listen to this, listen to this.
I just yesterday bought Shovel Knight on my Switch
because I have beaten, I had 100% at Shovel Knight
years ago, but I like that game so much
and there's new modes.
And so I, and I bought it specifically
for the convenience of playing on my Switch,
which is the greatest thing in the world,
every other console's garbage.
It's gonna be sponsored by Nintendo.
Yeah, exactly.
No, it's fucking great.
So I paid for that because there was a,
it was the only way I could play it on my Switch,
and I did it because I had no choice.
If I'd been able to torrent that shit
and play it on my Switch like for free,
I would have done that because that's easier.
So I'm saying people,
force me to pay for things.
That's what you gotta do.
I cherish the time when I get to pay for something.
Whenever I get like some throwaway,
like I always just save money.
When I get throwaway money,
I'm like, finally I can buy that fucking Bandcamp album
I've wanted to buy for a long time.
And then I can get in fucking flack, bro.
Fuck yeah, flack.
You're morally clean.
Flack.
Flack, bro, yeah.
I don't think any of us has problem
with people watching our shit without being patrons.
It's fine, but give me good patrons.
I wanna clarify my stance.
My stance on paying for art
is not that you shouldn't pay for art.
My stance is that you shouldn't pay for art
that you don't care about.
And I just happen not to care about any art,
especially not my own.
So that's why I don't pay for anything.
Do we have any questions now?
Yeah, we're in questions.
Okay.
Yeah, my stance on paying for art
is if you can do things in the general...
That's not really the question.
Oh really, oh shit.
I went to pee for a minute,
so I'd miss the question.
Okay, no matter.
Let's just go to the next one here.
Okay, this guy's been asking this question
for like, I think weeks now.
Let's just do him the favor of responding,
because it's really simple.
What's your favorite colors?
Ask at Spidey Juice.
It's like a picture that he made.
Black and white.
Black and blue.
Crush them.
Crush them black and white.
There you go.
Purple.
Purple's my favorite color.
Oh, me too.
My favorite color is every color
from red to blue.
All of the in-betweens.
Well, that's actually a pretty good answer, Monchi.
Oh my god, that's a good answer.
I picked the same.
Yeah, I didn't have to do something like that.
Honestly, I'm into every color right now,
so I don't have a favorite color.
My favorite color is everything
on the entire color wheel,
but with the saturation turned all the way down.
No, no!
We can't be friends anymore!
Colors are overrated.
I think my favorite,
aside from red to blue,
would be also anything on,
what's the word, shade of red?
Like pink?
Yeah.
Oh, I sent that to me back too.
Oh my god.
Okay, hopefully that was enough.
Guys, we got it.
This is a fascinating question.
This is another one from
atsyswhitescom69,
and this man needs help.
All right, listen to this.
At a super Christian wedding right now,
what can I do to have a good time?
Well, this man needs advice.
How can he have a good time?
This won't help him,
because he's going to be a weak lady.
Oh, fuck, I forgot.
I forgot.
Just drink all the sacramental wine.
Yeah, that's the thing to do.
Find alcohol.
Get wasted.
Just do everything you can
to make everyone regret inviting you.
That's what I would do.
Give us another question.
That guy's is out of date.
He should have thought about the fact
that it wouldn't get to him for a week.
You're right.
Just tell everyone there
that Bernie would have won.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Well, no,
because nothing can win against Hillary.
Hillary is perfect.
Oh, how are you doing that pop-out stand thing?
My pop-out stand is the greatest thing
in my life right now.
It's bigger than me.
It's huge.
It's massive.
And I got to tell you,
I got to tell you,
she's been standing behind me for days now.
Every fucking time I turn around,
I jump because she's just looking at me.
She's just looking at me
with that fucking smile on her face.
Oh, man.
There's actually an old photo of me
with an Obama cut out from like four years ago,
because we went to this one like catfish restaurant
owned by like a black family,
and they have an Obama room.
Obama room.
Okay.
Yeah, it's an entire Obama room.
Is this like a good Obama room
or a bad Obama room?
Where are they going with this?
It's a good Obama room.
It's a black family who owns a business.
Oh, I see.
We got to get a picture of Hillary.
You're a Hillary cut out
with my elated Arab gentleman.
People have been tweeting about that.
You definitely need that.
Next time, we'll make sure that happens.
I just imagine Nate has the same relationship
that Dave does with the little cow.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
She's constantly up in my shit,
moving around, spazzing out, doing crazy stuff.
Looking at you with that knowing look,
because she knows how to fix America.
And she is, in fact, puppeted by the speed of light
moving actual Hillary Clinton around my room.
Moving her every time I blink.
That's what's happening.
Okay, here we go.
This is a juicy question.
All right, here we go.
At PopVulture asks,
rank every race from best to worst
on how hot the women are.
Well, that's easy.
That's easy.
The Pokemon race,
the Dark Souls race,
and then the Kirby race.
Kirby is the last?
Where Kirby's got to be first.
They're the hottest.
Yeah.
Nate, you really phoned it in on that Kirby race.
People were disappointed.
Yeah, I was actually reading those replies today.
They were disappointed.
But I don't have fucking time to do all this shit.
That was the problem.
The problem is that we didn't have enough people.
If it was just three people, it was just lame.
We didn't have like five people at least.
You need to have someone who sucks ass
so that the show lasts long enough
for everybody to discuss their strategies.
You really kind of do need two people
who really care.
Yeah, you need at least two people
who are real competitors.
And the problem was there was really
only one real competitor on that one.
So yeah, it's true.
It's true.
So yeah, there you go.
Nah, that's a shitty one.
No, these are all shitty questions.
Are any of these fucking good?
No.
Oh, no.
I'm just responding to how bad all your questions are.
Get the fuck out of here.
You got the best things.
Here we go, guys.
Here we go.
Add Benjamin Whistle as,
is Nicholas Cage the worst or best actor ever?
Fucking Benjamin.
What the fuck?
Stupid retard.
Benjamin Whistle.
You're a fine bloke.
But get this meme shit out of here.
All right.
Can I just find one decent question?
No, these are all bad.
Why don't we not have fans asked by Munchie?
Here's a good question.
Who's better?
What's a better show?
Kill La Kill or Hey Arnold?
Wait, we already answered that question.
And you could find the answer
by listening to our bonus episode.
If you donate $5 to the Procrastinator's Patreon,
you get access to no less than three bonus episodes.
There's four now.
Four episodes.
The fourth of which is a discussion
on whether Kill La Kill or Hey Arnold is better.
I'm there.
Davoo's there.
Nate's there.
Jesse's there.
And Hippo's there.
It's a good question.
Not only that, gentlemen.
Not only that.
All those bonus episodes.
Hippo's spiritually there.
He asks us to the fucking sickest,
fuck aesthetic Patreon lounge.
So true.
Get this exclusive PCP Patreon lounge discord chat room
where you can chill with all your favorite characters,
like Nate Best Guy Ever, or Munchy, or Donald Trump.
All of them here in the chat.
Ready to talk and chat with you.
Yeah, Nate and Munchy.
And you can talk to all of your personal problems.
We do.
No one else there.
I like that discord.
And so there you go, folks.
There's that.
And don't forget.
What is it?
Redbubble.com slash people slash Procrastinator's
or whatever.
The links in the description.
You remember.
Buy our shit.
It's all there.
There's the other store, the print all over me.
Everything you can fucking want.
So go buy our shit.
Don't buy a house.
Your ex-wife will take it from you in the divorce.
I shouldn't have gone to prenup.
No.
If you ain't no punk, hola, we want prenup.
We want prenup.
Yeah.
It's something that you need to have,
because if she leaves your ass,
she gonna leave with half.
Leave with half.
All right.
It's fucking enough.
Wait, do we have another question?
Did you ever find a good one?
No.
No, I didn't.
I was just going to end it there.
I was just going to pay that right.
Bye, bye.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
I'm supposed to be working right now
But i'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I come jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am a stupid
I got a deadline
Don't wanna do it