Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever. Oh, who's in the Rapscallion crew today? Nope, it's Gibbontake. What's
up?
It's me, the host of the show. I'm the main attraction. The guy who can fire you all with
a moment's hand wave. His managerial powers are unparalleled. We've got Ben Saint. Who?
Don't ask me. I'm sorry, what? I thought we killed him. Tom Oliver, welcome. Welcome
again. Did you know that I have a long running podcast series on my Patreon? 23 episodes so
far and more, new one every week, new I am Games video coming out in three days, probably
out by the time you hear this. Go give me money and watch. My spine is back. My will
is back. Everything is back. Back puns. Get it? I'm back. Let's do it.
Tom Oliver pulled off an epic Zandatsu, stealing and crushing those electrolytes from his enemies,
and now he's stronger than ever.
Yes, it was fucking great. That's what I have to do tomorrow. I'm going in for a post-op
tomorrow and I have to crush my surgeon's spine and get the electrolytes to finish
the...
You can only graduate if you show that your spine is stronger than his.
Yes.
Well, so we got a mage, of course. A mage is here. Hello.
Hey, hello, Pokemon. Am I right, guys? I want to talk about it.
T-minus five days. When you hear this, it will be out, I think.
Exactly, exactly. Yeah, that's why I want you to bring it up.
Let me just stop for one second and say that I was so mad yesterday on Twitter. I saw that
the trending hashtag was like, thank you, hashtag thank you, Game Freak. And I just
thought that was so vile, so utterly loathsome.
I don't care. They're a fucking business. They do not deserve your love. If you like
their products, cool.
Oh, okay.
Oh, let's celebrate. Let's celebrate how much money they extracted from us.
There was the inevitable backlash, because everyone was mad at Game Freak for fucking
up the National Dex, but now that that dust has settled on that, people are now swinging
in the other direction.
Oh, yeah. Oh, maybe they fucked it up and ruined everything, but oh, but they're giving
us a new game, though. Oh, thank you so much. Oh, thank you. Thank you, thank you, master.
Can I have another, please?
Look, I'm in, look, Ben, they cut, they cut scissor, all right? They fucking cut scissor
for the fucking game.
Thank you for only belting me across the face 23 times instead of the traditional 24, sir.
Everybody, let's clap, consume product and then consume next product.
Yay.
Okay, but Mega Gigantamax Gengar is really funny looking at you like that. He's really
funny. And Google it, you know, let's find an image. He's, he's, he's like doing that
thing where he's like, he's like in the ground, like Mega Gengar, but like only the top half
of his mouth is like open like a big cave in front of you. Can you, can you like that?
Fuck?
Ben, it's sick. It's totally dope.
No.
I'm just ignoring all of that. I'm just like Corviknight.
Please look at this Gengar.
I'm sticking to my guns. Still, still Corviknight is badass and is one of my favorite people
in the world.
I don't even remember who Corviknight is.
Corviknight is the, the fucking Demo Dark Goth bird.
It's, it's the Goth, it's the Victorian Dark Souls bird.
Yeah.
Isn't it, isn't it weird when they present like Corviknight was like first introduced
and you know, we all thought pretty cool, but that's like the third evolution of the
line and it feels weird to me that they introduced the like third evolution before we ever saw
the first or second.
Because they know that the third evolution is the only good one in the line.
I think it's probably because they like doesn't like Corviknight like do something in the
lore of this world.
It's used as like a transport bird all over the place.
That is true.
It's a taxi bird.
Um, okay.
So, so Gigantamaxing and Dynamaxing are like different things, right?
Cause I, cause I see, cause I see a Gengar and I'm assuming this is a Dynamax?
No, wait, wait. Dynamaxing is making the Pokemon big. Gigantamaxing is when they have a specific
form. Cause I see a giant Dynamax Gengar, but he doesn't look any different from normal.
So I'm not seeing what you're talking about.
Yeah.
Certain Pokemon can Gigantamax, which is when they get a different form.
Dude, I'm, I'm searching for this right now and I actually cannot find the image I was
looking at yesterday.
Yeah.
That's just big Gengar, but that's not what I was looking at.
There was one with Gengar's mouth.
Was it a fan at it?
Was this not real?
No.
You've been duped.
It was 3D models.
Oh, I mean, okay.
That's really cool, but that's not, that's not what that looks funny as well.
I'll get back to you.
I love that.
Gengar is a hilarious great boy and I'm way into him, but you know, whatever, I'll get
back to you.
I'm just getting my fucking Tyranitar if he's in this game.
I haven't checked.
He's going to get fucking Tyranitar back.
He is in the game.
Tyranitar is in the game.
And that's the only reason I'm buying this game.
Oh, that's going to be good.
There was, there was a thing I was, I was thinking the other day, like, you know, some of these
new Pokemon look pretty good.
Corviknight, you know, nice, nice looking design.
It's such a shame that it's in a Pokemon game, you know, like that was my first thought.
Like, what a shame that all these like nice designs are in a game that sucks.
And I don't like-
Damn.
Give with the harsh fruits.
And I'm not saying that, I'm not saying that because like, I'm a, I'm a bandwagon Pokemon
sucks because of this or that.
I just haven't liked Pokemon since Emerald.
So you know.
I, I was very critical of Sun and Moon as well, because Sun and Moon had tons of stuff
to infuriate me.
Sun and Moon was a nice little thing, but that was like the first time I'd played Pokemon
for like 10 years or something.
I got a set.
I have not seen this before.
Surfetched is fucking awesome.
It's the evolution of Farfetched.
It's so good.
Oh, with the really long fucking leak.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
Farfetched finally got an evolution.
Super.
I can't wait, I can't wait for him to come out in Pokemon Go, so I can just look at him.
It's always good for.
Yeah.
It's going to be in Pokemon Sword Farfetched, I think.
I'm getting Sword.
So let, let's just go down the line.
Let's self-segregate as we like to do.
Shield, pony.
Sword boy, sword over here.
Shield.
Mage.
Pony, pony, pony.
I'm getting it.
Fuck it.
I'm getting Sword, but, but someone's getting it for me as a gift.
I would not be buying it otherwise.
I still haven't got to have found a reason to get a switch.
Okay, fair enough.
Fair enough.
But all the ports give.
Don't you want to pay for game again?
Nope.
I know I do.
Poltergeist is pretty, pretty cute, I guess.
It is.
I like it.
And it has a pre-evolution that's a little teacup.
Does it?
Yeah, that one's cute.
I don't see that.
Poltergeist.
Yeah, it's, it's a T.
It wasn't the leaks.
Oh, sorry.
I like MLP ponytail a lot.
That's in shield.
I mean, that's, you know, that's cute.
I like it.
What can I say?
Which version has sandile?
A sandile even in this game?
Am I going to get mad now?
Who knows?
I'm not sure.
Disgusting.
They cut scissor.
And they cut fucking all my favorite Pokemon.
Scissor is the one who usually does the cutting.
Cause he slice and cut with the HM.
I was like, I was thinking to myself, guys, scissor, incredibly popular Pokemon.
Like one of the most iconic bug, but he's one of the only reasons why anyone likes
bug at all, right?
There's no fucking way they're cutting scissor, right?
No, it can't be.
There's no, and then I see the big black, red fucking X on his face.
You know what?
It's really a shame.
Can't believe it.
That the Pokemon company didn't have the balls to do the really hardcore move and cut Pikachu.
Let's just fucking move on.
We've had a lot of fucking Pikachu's.
It's time to move on.
Can you imagine if they just cut Pikachu?
They just was not there.
There was a, this idea doesn't make sense in practice, but I did see some fan art of
Mimikyu, right?
A Gigantamax to Mimikyu.
It sure would be funny if, when a Gigantamax is, it's now wearing a costume of Raichu.
Instead of its costume of Pikachu, but nobody cares about Raichu at all.
People only like Pikachu is that doesn't actually make sense.
Even though Raichu is objectively better.
I have a feeling that Pikachu has like almost all the shares in the company and he's like
calling all the shots.
Oh shit.
He's the Mickey Mouse basically of the Pokemon company.
Yeah.
That's fair.
Yep.
I will get it and I will have at least a kind of decent time as I even do with the worst
Pokemon games.
I'm sure.
Why?
Because I, look, they're making a product and I do want to be part of the conversation
of the discussion of the game.
What's that worth?
And I just enjoy Pokemon.
If you notice that discussion worth when most of it is people going, ugh.
Because frankly, I think you guys are slightly exaggerating how bad this game looks.
Oh no, it's fine.
It's just, it's just like the same old shit and therefore it's like.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah.
You know, Pokemon, whatever.
They're still going to have A&M's, right?
I like Pokemon and to be honest, I ain't too bothered.
Fuck it.
I don't know.
No, I don't think so.
Have they removed A&M's from this game?
There's no way they did.
I can't remember what their...
They removed them from Sun and Moon.
I don't think they would...
They weren't in the last game though.
They were removed.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll fuck it up.
I'm sure they'll only do bad things.
Yeah.
Well, if they have the taxi Pokemon and the Corvik Knight, then there's no reason to have
flies, so I'm guessing, you know, they're going to remove them.
Well, they got the whole thing with like open world, you can sit and have a curry or whatever
and camp out in the wilderness.
Traditional English dish curry.
So like fast travel might not be a thing.
But they might have trains.
Have you guys seen this?
I found this.
It looks kind of legit, but it's really bad.
It's really low res of like all the new Pokemon or something.
Oh yeah, that's based on the leaks.
Yeah, I think that's all the ones, at least at this time.
Oh, Karkol.
Karkol is the best one.
What's that?
I hate his eyes.
He is the middle evolution of the rock faggot thing.
The small one looks like another one.
The big one looks like Raihorn or whatever.
But the middle one is like a golem head, like decapitated and put it on a bed of coals
on like a stone slab and he's got tiny little leg things.
And he's got a really stupid expression.
He's pretty good.
I love how stupid he is.
The edges of his eyes are protruding.
I don't like it.
I think I really like...
Have you seen the fucking apple?
Are you seeing this fucking apple on the left?
It's a fucking apple.
All right.
I really like the snow version of Darmanitan with its big orb head.
It's good.
Although I am keen on having Pokémon in my life again, one thing I want to complain
though is the Pokémon designs.
I don't want to say they're ugly necessarily, but they don't give me like most of them,
most of the new ones, don't give me that Pokémon vibe anymore.
They kind of look weird.
I mean, look at fucking impendip and his two weird evolutions.
What is that thing?
Morkrim is like a sex demon, I'm pretty sure.
Did he find a revolution of impendip?
I mean, I think it's that weird purple one.
Oh yeah, the middle one.
I don't like the green.
Why did he add green?
Otherwise, I would like it otherwise, but that green is just...
Just green screen it away.
Key it out.
It's okay guys.
We've got all the original Kanto Pokémon in, so you can just use those exclusively
like you do every game.
The only ones that anyone cares about.
I know.
Hey, I just want to rent.
I just want to rent for one second.
I hate Goldeen.
I can't believe they put Goldeen in again.
It is.
Probably to fucking kill my Pokémon with Horn Drill again.
The new evolution of Corsola.
The new evolution of Corsola just is the white lady from Hollow Knight.
Yeah, and it's dope.
It's dope.
It's like it turns into Sea King, which is uglier, and it's a generic boring fish
in every single game, but Magikarp also is one of those.
It turns into a cool thing.
Goldeen is the worst Pokémon in Pokémon.
That's great.
That's good lore.
It's definitely up there.
No, it gets a horn.
It's not just a fish.
It had a horn.
No, man.
The horn is consistent between evolutions.
It's got a horn.
Yeah, yeah.
It gets a horn.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm saying it's got a horn though.
It's not just a fish.
It's got a horn.
We know you are hung up about horns, Ben, but other people don't have that tism.
Look, I got a horn, but you don't see me waving it around everywhere.
I'm tugging on my horn right now.
I really don't like Santa Conda.
It's fucking...
I really don't like Santa Claus.
This fucking image is small.
Silly snake.
Don't like it.
Okay, I mean, I've just got...
Have you guys noticed the fucking B-52, like the semi-legendary dragon, ghost type of this,
that launches fucking dragons out of its missile launchers on its fucking stealth jethead?
No, no, no.
It's a dragon puts, dragon quits, whatever it is, in the middle there.
I don't like it.
I mean, I think it's fucked up, but I'm way into it.
Yeah, I like it.
I don't know.
I like that one.
I don't like the literal penguin was just an ice cube on its head.
It's just an ice cube head.
Yeah, that one's actually really bad.
Man, have you seen it?
I thought that was like...
It's all just formed directly below it with the melted head.
Oh, my God.
I'll defend fucking vanillax, and I'll defend clefty, but I think I have to draw the line
at ice cube?
Ice cube.
It's very bad.
It's an ice cube with a penguin for a body.
I mean, aside from obvious habitat things, what is the significance of like a fucking
mascot looking ice cube?
That's like what a fucking elementary school I would come up with.
It really is.
Unironically.
I don't like it.
I do like it.
It's so that purple thing.
Oh, it's all shit, boys.
We're going to hell in a handbasket.
I guess I'll just say spoilers or whatever, but have you seen the big mega-ultra-legendary
attorneys or whatever?
I mean, that thing's pretty sick.
It has a fucking city on its head.
It looks like a fucking...
What do they call it, an Eldrazi for Magic the Gathering?
The Cthulhu fucking demons?
Those are pretty sick.
It's got like two different forms, and it's other...
I want to know the lore behind that thing.
What the fuck is it?
I mean, it looks like an Ultra Beast.
You said Eldrazi, and now I just want to play Magic, because it's cooler than this.
It just looks like an Ultra Beast, basically.
It looks like...
It does.
100% true.
I don't know.
There's like some deep King Arthur lore about like interdimensional Cthulhu demons or something
that I'm not aware of.
I guess we'll find out soon.
Maybe there's no.
Find out in five days, or after you're listening to this, because it's already out, you can
tell us how we were totally wrong about all these things in the comments.
I can't wait.
I mean, you know, I'm just thinking back.
Now is the appropriate time.
I'm thinking back to my experience of playing Sun and Moon.
Core gameplay loop.
You know.
Good.
Fine.
I hated the reduced number of gyms to four, effectively.
There was those trainers that each one around the world was the one elemental boy, but those
weren't real gyms.
Wait, and Sun and Moon?
Yeah.
Remember, they were only like...
No, they had the Kovunas.
The Trials.
Yeah, they had the Kovunas with the big boss, and the Babunas, the small ones.
But they also had the guys who would give you the Z-Crystal, the different elemental guys
who were sort of like gym leaders, kinda.
Okay, that all sucked.
I don't want any of that.
I just want gyms.
Gyms are classic.
They're good.
Well, there's definitely gyms in this one.
We know that.
Thank God for that.
You have the perfect formula.
I would buy just like a new Pokemon game of the exact same formula as like Heart, Gold,
and Soul Silver, basically till the end of time.
If you just give me new thing of the same style, because it's a fucking winner, and I
love that game.
I'm really...
Just the way I buy every Metroidvania I can find, and I play them, because I just love
the game.
I'm really curious as to how this curse can end.
People...
There have been alternative games that have come up and tried to be Pokemon that do the
things that the fans are looking for, or whatever, better gameplay and not shit and good and
stuff.
Pokemon's a monopoly.
We need to break it up.
Because it is not the designs that people have grown up with, and grown old with at this
point.
They just never get off the ground.
They never grab people's hearts and attentions.
It's like, how are we going to stop giving the Pokemon company money?
Gabe, I've got it.
I've got the solution.
The designs are kind of bad, though.
Have you guys seen fucking Mr. Mines Evolution?
Mr. Rhyme?
What the fuck is Mr. Rhyme?
Buster.
Okay, but I have the solution.
I have the solution to this, and here's what it is.
It's that we pull a Teddy Roosevelt, and we bust this fucking trust, and what that means
is...
In the old days, there was Pokemon Red and Blue, right?
We're going to split the fucking games along company lines.
Certainly half the Pokemon Game Freed gets to keep.
Half the fucking Pokemon you put in a separate company makes a competing Pokemon game, but
you can trade between the two.
And with this new system, we'll get two different games, and it's going to be the competing
gameplay development styles that each game does.
But you can trade between the two, and this is how we make actual competition.
We could do more than two companies.
We could make each Pokemon have its own game.
We got enough Pokemon.
It makes sense to me.
This is... do that, Game Freak.
Sell half Pokemon or something.
We just got to release Pokemon a Lightning Edition with all the Soniches in it.
That's it.
That's the solution.
Well, that's just going to top the charts.
It's not even a fair competition.
Oh boy, I sure do hate Pokemon.
I'm going to play it.
I'm kind of interested to see if they've learned any lessons from the last one, or if things
have gotten worse.
I'm very invested in that.
I'm not.
So I'm real curious.
Everything I've seen that's new in this game looks bad.
You can change their natures now.
I like that.
That's nice.
That's a plus.
Forcibly time-warping their backstories.
You would never shy.
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of a negative thing, because now we're just saying that we're making it
more gamey and less personality-y, and there's some trade-off.
People do like the gamey-gamey shit.
Have you seen the 7-hour Omega Ruby review?
A couple times I've started, and I've gotten 20 minutes, and I've been like, I'll definitely
get back to this.
I know what you're saying about how it's gamey-er, but he makes a pretty good argument towards
the end that, okay, it's cute, and everything that, once you catch a Pokemon, you're stuck
with it.
But the practical effect of not being able to change anything is basically just, like,
if you want a particular nature, you can get it.
It just takes you 14 hours or whatever.
Yeah, it's not good.
But what if you want it on a shiny?
Well, that's going to take you forever.
Infinite time.
Yeah.
I think the implication of the game is that you're not supposed to grind until you have
the right nature.
You have to just work with what you find.
People like min-maxing, so they will play the game for 14 hours to get the right thing.
I feel like the game as it exists now could exist parallel along something like Pokemon
Showdown.
And I'm perfectly comfortable for all competitive Pokemon to be played on Pokemon Showdown
or something like that.
To me, I don't know.
If you...
Okay, something like...
I'm sure that changing your natures is a post-game thing that's not available right away.
You probably have to grind for it at some kind of battle arena.
Items.
Yeah.
I just don't know how you get those items.
It's probably...
Probably post-game.
There was the thing that you could change a Pokemon's ability.
You could switch between if a Pokemon had two different abilities.
And to do that, you needed an item, and you had to earn that item in the battle arena.
So it's probably something like that.
It's not going to be something that just any casual can do.
It's still going to be something that only hardcore players would care about.
I think it's probably good.
I think it's probably good for more options like that.
I'm just wondering the fact that it's going to be the hardcore players doing it.
It's hard to object that much, but at the same time, canonically, it's like we're changing
Pokemon's personalities, which is supposed to have...
It's already fucked up.
I mean, it's a little fucked up.
Kind of.
I guess that's true.
I mean, like all you do, I think you give it a mint.
I think that that's the item, and it's a specific kind of mint.
So you're just giving them a treat, and that affects them.
It's such an impact in their life.
I won't, sir.
I won't.
Well, we shall see.
We shall see.
Let us know, folks.
What do you think of New Pokemon?
I'm honestly excited.
I'm probably in the very vast minority of this, but...
I wonder if there's going to be a new Pokemon for Smash for this game.
Definitely.
I want you to see Ice Q's true form.
Okay.
This is like a larger version of what's in that.
I was thinking it looked like a fucking Internet mascot thing or an Android device.
Okay.
Ignore the stuff on the left, but the two on the right, these are the images from the
leak.
They are.
Yeah, that's right.
Incredible.
It's a nightmare.
I hate it.
I know.
It's really bad.
Look, I feel like this is on a new level from Klefki.
Everyone complained about Klefki.
Fuck off.
It's fine.
I like it.
It's cute.
Yeah.
But everyone hated it, and everyone hates Garbador, and everyone hates Vanillux.
It's cute.
And I just feel like compared to this, those don't even bear mentioning in terms of bad
Pokemon.
Yeah.
It's like, I guess the idea, like concept behind this, is a penguin fell into the ice
and got frozen head and different kind of head based on what's something, but like...
That doesn't make this Pokemon.
It doesn't make it an animal in pain.
It's like the ice doesn't have any relation to the rest of the body, even in color.
It's just a fucking penguin.
It's shit.
It's real shit.
It's not great.
I think it might be related to the melting ice caps, environmental message and stuff,
because...
Disgusting.
Because it doesn't justify...
Keep politics out of my video game, goddammit.
You could have done a fucking better job with that concept.
No, okay.
I got it.
It's a new form of Avalog, and it's ice water, and it's just sort of drooping, and it looks
like it's had a stroke, and it's like in constant pain.
That makes sense.
All you need is a fucking emaciated Polar Bear Pokemon to show like, oh, it's bad.
We already have one.
Okay, an entire line of Pokemon just based on the melting ice caps.
You have horrifying melting Avalog.
You have emaciated, like losing its fur, mangy fucking, oh, what's the Polar Bear?
The big Cub Chew evolves into...
It's like Volar Bears.
No, that's the fucking League of Legends character.
Okay, you know the one I'm talking about.
I know it's done.
I think we literally made a better ice Pokemon in like an old procust, the freezer one,
right?
Yeah.
The cooler, the ice steel type.
The refrigerator.
Don't we already have one of those with what's-his-face Rotom, the refrigerator version of some
30-dice?
Yeah, but ours was cooler.
Okay, all right.
Fair enough.
Ice Rotom is electric.
Wait, what form?
Fridge form.
He's an electric ice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It started as a cooler, it evolved into a fridge, and then it became a fucking iceberg.
It just went from human size to continent size.
Sick.
Now, okay, so just despite all our misgivings about Pokemon and whatnot, now that's all
true, it's dead boys, but the spirit of Pokemon lives on.
The real Pokemon game is over on PCP Minecraft server, patreon.com, PCP Minecraft.
It is the greatest place.
You can ride your Pokemon, you can sail through the sky, and it's literally where Pokemon
lives on.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but if you're listening to this on Friday, then tomorrow, Saturday,
we will be streaming, right?
No, no, no.
We're streaming before that.
That's when we're recording the bonus episode, which is unrelated.
But when are we streaming?
Like on Tuesday, a few days before this goes out.
Okay, we shouldn't discuss this on the show, but that's not what you said.
And the bonus episode, Claude, that is what he said.
We will read back the transcript, and that will be vindicated.
Okay, well never mind, ignore everything I just said.
You will have seen a stream and come play with us on the stream, and there will be
more to come, so, you know, get involved if you want.
I'm fine, I'm fine with this, because that's not what you fucking said.
Okay, fine, and Mage actually is looking forward, or is in the planning stages of a Pokemon
tournament on the server, so we're gearing up for that at some point in the future.
I need to work out some details.
I worked out the prizes, thankfully, so...
What are the prizes?
I'm immediately curious.
Okay, because people were a little bit wary about getting like OP Pokemon or something
that has prizes, the elected that maybe I should look into giving away like statues
of Pokemon, which could be doable, I just wasn't sure if I could do it on the server.
And with a little bit of fiddling and stuff, and googling things, I managed to find out
away how to do it, so yeah, I'll be giving prizes like statues of certain Pokemon.
You get to choose which Pokemon or something?
Well, I mean, for each...
You should have your team of Pokemon erected as statues, and put, oh, wouldn't that be
amazing for all time?
I'm sick.
Well, if we're going to do this monthly, which people have been actually asking to do it
like bi-weekly, but I said I couldn't be able to do it, yeah, so monthly, so no, I think
like each tournament or so will have its own Pokemon as a sort of like the theme mascot
or something.
Okay.
And that Pokemon will be the statue that you receive.
That is a...
We have like a pedestal where that Pokemon stands, and then next month it gets traded
out with the next person's winning in like a plaque or something.
I mean, that would be a great idea.
The thing is though, with the statues, they're not the kind of items you can put in your inventory,
so I'd have to place it somewhere in their claim, and they won't be able to move it.
I was wrong.
You said Monday.
Hey, there you go.
I'm the genius.
I did it.
So it's Monday now, Tuesday?
We are doing the stream on Monday.
That's correct.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
And this will be long past for all you people.
No, it'll be on Monday.
We'll do more in the future.
Wait, no.
No, it will be here.
We'll have happened on Monday.
Whoops.
Okay.
Fuck it.
All right.
Now, Pokemon talk.
No, never enough Pokemon.
Let's discuss other things in our lives.
Who's got some?
What else?
What else is there in our lives that there's in Pokemon?
Well, there's Slime and Punishment, which continues apace, developments are occurring,
Chris is tampering in the continuity some more.
My goal now, I will never compromise my artistic vision, but part of that artistic vision,
part of something that I find adds value to it, at least for me personally, the more of
Chris's lore that I can incorporate into it, the better.
So I'm eager when Chris does things or says things or says such and such about it, I'm
eager to be like, hmm, how can I work this in?
Because it's funny.
But he's making that complicated for, I mean, she is making this challenging for you, as
I recall.
I have mulled it over, she made a, yes, she made a, she drew another card showing Chris
Chan Sonichu retrieving Phantom Horn from the Time Void.
And I was distressed by this, because it, well, it wasn't what I had planned.
And also, because I, like, it was, I think she thought the comic was over, I think she
thought that was the end.
Like that was where that was the end of Phantom Horn's fate, which is so ridiculous.
You should have said to be continued.
I guess I should, I guess I should have not assumed that it wasn't obvious, that was obvious
that there was going to be another update.
Like, why would I even, why would I even show that version of Phantom with the Podron Horn
if that was going to be what ended, he would, if he just had no relevance to anything and
he just ended up drifting.
Because it's dark, dude.
I, you know, I guess, you know, I guess maybe, but no.
But it's fine.
I've mulled it over and I think I can work with what Chris made actually just this morning,
this morning before the show, before this recording, I cranked out another four panels
and posted them incorporating my redrawn version of that card.
And we'll, we'll, you know, maybe later today, there'll be more developments.
Excellent.
Yeah.
By the way, people do your favor.
And also, I guess I might as well mention this, Chris did suggest that she might show
up to my stream tonight, as in tonight when we're recording this, which would be really
fun and really funny and cool, but who knows if it'll actually happen, but she said it,
so I'm hopeful.
Does she mean like in the call or just in the chat?
She said she would be on Twitch.
So I mean, make of that, which you will.
You gotta make sure to add her when you post it your live, last ditch attempts to pull
them in.
Yeah.
Very true.
I probably will.
But I think you'll find yourself swallowed whole, Ben, all by the sheer power, much like
if you go to the gross disgusting audio links where I just posted the picture I was looking
for of Gengar with this giant gaping mouthful.
Oh my God.
Isn't it glorious?
Now, that's what I'm talking about with Jaycanta Max.
I'm way into that.
Okay.
I can get excited about that.
Mega Gengar is like a little...
His little hands.
Look at his little hands.
Yeah, it is.
He's going yes.
Yeah.
It is.
It's Mega Gengar, but just like with his mouth really wide open.
No, it's not Mega Gengar.
Mega Gengar has three eyes.
Oh, that's...
Yeah, that's true.
And he's not.
It's just because he has those Mega Gengar Liggies, that's why I assumed.
No.
Okay.
I mean, maybe this is...
No, this is just regular Gengar hands sticking up out of the ground going, boo.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
But while we're on this, just look at this other art I found.
This would also have been a dope-ass Mega Gengar, but this is not real.
That's cute.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, I saw that one.
I can Google things too.
All right.
Good work.
Okay.
Enough of that.
Yes.
We did it.
I was just going to say, I'm putting fucking slime and punishment up on Topastic and Webtoon.
I would really like for it to get followers and especially likes on Webtoon, and it's
very hard and I hate it.
It's got like 40 followers, which is like nothing, and I'm depressed.
That's pretty low.
What I'm going to do is say like when you update from Twitter, just say go over to Thing
to read it, and then they'll have to go in.
Yeah.
But a lot of people just don't do that.
A lot of people wouldn't do that.
You've got to force them to do that.
Otherwise, they just won't.
They just won't follow you.
I would do that.
But in particular, the thing about that is that Chris would never see it.
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
Chris would never see it if I weren't posting it on Twitter.
What if you just post a preview of the page without the whole page and just like if you
want to know what actually happened, go to this page.
You can expect only a bare minimum of effort from Chris, I think, and other people might
work.
I mean, you could do like a, you know, it's live now for people who are following and
then, you know, three, four hours later, you post it on Twitter for Chris, just so it's
all there on Twitter as well.
Even though I have been doing more and better work than I have ever done in my entire life,
for months now, my Patreon has stagnated and in fact only gone down a bit.
So that's cool.
That's good.
Life's gone great for me.
I feel that, dude.
I feel that hardcore the worst.
But you know what?
I don't care.
I'm going to do it anyway.
I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing my thing.
And that's it.
There and out.
That's what I've been thinking.
That's what it's about.
That's how it's done.
In terms of like public things, I've been doing really nothing, but I've been working
very hard on comic things in the background.
Uh, yeah, I have, I have a vaporette to draw now.
I have read no art to finish.
I have a whole thing, uh, I won't say.
But then after that, after all that, I've gotten more comics and more things and more
scripts and writing and it's like, ooh, I wish, I wish I was like, um, posting stuff
regularly and being like, you know, keeping up with, uh, stuff and, and, uh, engagement
or whatever the fuck it is.
Mm-hmm.
Engagement is good.
You would, which you can find plenty of over on me and Digi's new channel kind of intent
with, with, you know, I was thinking, if I put up a green screen, would you throw me
into an episode?
Oh, we, we made this specifically with the hope that we could involve you guys in various
projects that would be of note to you.
For example, Tom, uh, talking about Beastars is already intended to be done at some point.
Uh, I didn't see your video about it, but I wanted to because I like Beastars.
It's worth it.
Beastars is fucking sick.
Yeah.
Tom will tell you all day.
Oh, I'm glad.
I'm glad.
Shout out to May for dropping into my DMs like two weeks ago.
I was like, can you to watch Beastars?
Main character is you.
And the first episode you was like.
Oh, she told you to watch, huh?
She, she did.
She was the one who turned me on to it and then I became addicted.
She's the one who turns you on to it and then you got turned on all by yourself.
Yeah.
The rest is all me, baby.
Are you, I'm interested.
Now I'm kind of curious because I've seen some of the show.
How do you relate to Lugosi?
Do you, I mean, you are a very tall boy.
Similar to Lugosi.
Uh, I don't know.
I didn't, uh, uh, uh, just, I asked May like what, how I was the main character because
the two main characters are just like sad, not socially functioning people.
Kinda.
And I was like, I guess that's true.
I guess that makes sense.
And that was just like, he's like tall and awkward and has like moments of rage.
I'm like, yeah, that's about right.
I guess so.
He doesn't, and it kind of looks like you a little bit.
This is a tall thin thing, I guess, but, um, I'm okay being compared to Lugosi, especially
as his arc continues throughout the manga and becomes fucking sick.
Does he ever go beast mode and unlock his superpowers and, you know, I will not spoil
anything, but if you think that this show is what it appears to be, you are so mistaken.
It's not even fine.
People have been saying that it's, I thought it was just a high school drama.
People are like, no, no, no, no.
And I'm like, okay.
All right.
Fair enough.
I've been watching it and I, and I keep thinking just like, I still don't have a feel on this
show.
It just, I don't know what it, what I'm supposed to feel about it.
Like, what is this?
What is this show?
I don't know.
You know, cause I was so just thinking just, oh, like it's literally just a J drama, but
with animal boys, but I, and it's hard for me to imagine how it's going to not do that.
But I guess it's going to.
Wait, haven't, didn't you do a calm turn?
On Beastars with Digi?
Well, yeah, but it was only four episodes long or three.
You couldn't get a feel for what it was about from four.
Well, yeah.
What we're saying is what the feeling we got seemed very much like a J drama, but everyone
is saying, nah, nah, nah, you guys don't know what you're in for.
Well, okay.
Okay.
Just like, okay.
The show is a drama.
Like that is what it is about.
It's just that the scope and the stakes and the scale expand far beyond what it initially
seems to present.
Sure.
Oh, so it's like Homestuck.
I wouldn't know.
Shut up.
So it's like, it's like, it's like Dogstock.
It's like Catstock.
I mean, Homestuck from the very beginning was about, at the very least, all of Earth
in jeopardy of, yeah, I mean, it was destroyed or, kind of, kind of.
It escalates real quick.
It got to like multiversal stuff though, so fair enough, I guess.
Act One is like a boy in his room, fucking around, and then at the end of Act One, there's
a meteor coming to kill him, and from there it escalates.
All right, Gib, riddle me this.
Who would win in a fight, Homestuck or Gurren Lagan?
Who wins that fight?
In terms of like the characters and their power levels fighting each other, or like...
You know, we already thought too much about it, never mind.
No, I think Homestuck would win, because of Kaliope, of dead Kaliope making the big black
hole that would suck up a giant, universe-sized camera.
Well, here's your problem, Gib.
Kaliope is a weak...
She's destroyed.
Could never defeat the masculine energy of God-community-spirited.
Nah, she'd suck him right up.
She'd suck him right down into that black hole, if you know what I'm saying.
She'd probably give him...
I was gonna say she'll give him a Me Too moment, he'll never forget, but I just hope to be
a part of it.
All right.
What are we talking about?
I can't remember.
I don't know.
We got here.
Obie Stars.
We subscribed to Can-Tent to watch our fan page.
Recently.
We subscribed to Can-Tent.
Oh, but Gib, you were saying if you could be on a green screen, yes, and I'm curious
if there's anything that you are interested in.
Well, I don't know whether I'm interested in discussing anything, but I have recently...
My brother bought like five green screen sheets a while ago, but he's never had a use for
them, and we were clearing out his room, and he gave them to me, and now I have enough
green screen to green screen an entire room from all around me, and I was just thinking
of...
Nice.
Green screen is like the progenitor of creativity.
If I have a big green screen, and I'm thinking, I want to make a video now, I'm just going
to sit here with a microphone in my hand in a void of green and talk about nothing in
particular, and I want to film it.
You know who does this good work with that formula?
Green screen power, and yet here we are, a whole room at your disposal.
Indeed.
Truly terrible.
Nakey Jakey, with his writing and stuff, people like him a lot, but he generally sits
on a bouncy ball in a green screen, and then edits himself moving around.
Yeah, it's a good thing.
I like his style with that shit.
I probably do a combination of that top-down green screen thing, but also the stupid...
If you remember all of the green screen videos I've made, I forget the names of them, but
there's all give and take videos where I'm just holding a green thing, and I'm fucking
around and saying stuff to the camera, and it's just fun.
It's just fun keying things.
The spirit was continued into a GRPJ to increase that.
GRPJ throwing the final fantasy, I just threw the green screen in the background, and that's
the green screen, that's the game footage.
It's really fun.
It's good.
And then obviously the huge universe-shattering video, GRPJ Super Mario RPG, where it's just
my floating head.
Right.
Some people, maybe you guys, I don't know if you saw this or anything, but on some of
the content videos that Digi and I have done, the initial ones were in person with a green
screen, but in the later ones, the whole premise is we green screen ourselves separately so
we can kind of add them together.
Digi's video quality is so much better than mine, and yet you still have people being
like, or rather on one video, where we actually were together, that was released after this,
where we were like, man, this one's weird, because it's weird to see Digi and Nate pretending
to be in the same room together, because now I know they're not, but no, we actually
were in the same room in that video.
Look at the fucking film.
It's amusing to see.
So people are fooled.
People are convinced by the rudimentary trickery of the style, so low bar to cross for all
that stuff, I guess.
Ooh, and I'm happy to report, folks, we have crossed the threshold where we now are applying
for monetization on content, and the pennies are just going to roll in, baby.
Very excited.
Speaking of monetization on content, so I had trouble when I was uploading the Ben
Saint vs. Digi Bro stream, it kept, man, I was so careful with it, I would go in and
I would change the title, and I would change the thumbnail, and I would change the description
and the tags and stuff, and I would like, and sometimes, and it kept tagging it as unfit
for monetization, limited monetization, and I uploaded it, and I re-uploaded it a bunch
of times, and I finally got it, I finally got it, so that it was not flagged for that,
and then I released it, and then immediately it gets flagged, and this happened twice,
this happened twice, but, you know, I actually, I, okay, it sucks, because, you know, it's
already got a couple thousand views, and those were not monetized, but I applied for review,
and they approved it, so it is monetized now, like I wanted it to be, so I guess that's
a win.
You know, I don't know if people are aware of this, but public service announcement,
like just for example, the PCP, now the PCP does not always get monetized, but, or rather,
it'll get like the yellow lower monetization thing or whatever, which just means it doesn't
run ads, right?
Which basically just means it doesn't run ads, right?
Or it doesn't make money from ads?
It gets like the very lowest bottom tier ads, or none at all, I think, is, I think that's
the idea.
So, so when I upload the, right now, we try to get the episodes done by Wednesday, because
the episode needs to go up Friday, and the reason we give it a big window is specifically
so we have like a full day at least, to, we upload it, it will basically always get limited
monetization, we appeal it, and then most of the time, in that day or two, it will get
like, you know, manually reviewed, and then it'll be monetized.
So like, we have to build in like a day or two of waiting period for this shit, for the
whole system, which I do on my channel too, and I don't know, you guys probably do on
yours, it's a big fucking pain, but now that just seems to be what you gotta do to make
sure you get, you know, all the full money you're trying to get from it.
It doesn't even guarantee it, because you can always get re-hit later.
That's, yeah, I mean, it's always true.
And I guess I will double this by saying, use this opportunity to say, go to my channel,
watch me debate Digi about Yang and Bernie and stuff.
Did I tell you that video got 1,000 views on the VOD on Twitch, which is like, ridiculous
for Twitch, to get 1,000 views on one VOD.
Like 20 views on a VOD is like, wow, this is really, really popping off.
That's pretty normal.
Maybe 50 for like a real humdinger.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Nobody watches anything on Twitch, because I can't watch VODs as much.
It's terrible.
The player is terrible on Twitch, so I don't blame them.
You have all that live content right at your fingertips.
I'm not going to watch something from a while ago.
That's bullshit.
Make some sense.
There was one time when I went on to like an RFCK stream, and I didn't realize that
what was playing was an old stream that I hadn't seen before.
And the chat was rolling, and I was talking to people as if they could hear me.
You can type in the chat while it's like past history chat.
Yeah.
Nobody responds, because you weren't there.
And I was like, what the fuck?
I'm getting flamed by everyone.
When was an old stream playing on RFCK?
No, it's just the thing that happens.
If you go to a streaming channel when they're not currently streaming, it will like maybe
auto-play like the last thing that was like saved.
I have never seen it do that, but perhaps it's true.
I mean, maybe I clicked on it, I can't remember, but like either way, I was really annoyed
at everyone, and then I paused it.
I paused the stream and realized that the chat stopped as well, and I felt stupid.
I just wanted a response of some kind.
I was thinking of going to Discord, and I was like, wait a minute, they're talking about
old shit.
Oh no.
Weird.
Yep.
How very dehumanizing.
You're making like real solid posts, you're like having a real good time with your friends,
and like hours later you suddenly realize, wait a minute, it's fake.
Nothing was real.
Like I don't know why they allow you to chat unless like VODs can have-
That's strange.
It's like-
Why would you want to?
I think potentially it's like if multiple people watch the video back and they add their
chat in the moment, then it shows up if somebody watches it again.
So like you can continually add to the chat, it's just the chat is no longer talking to
each other, really.
You're just going in and adding your thoughts or something.
Yeah.
Very weird.
You're changing the stream.
So for other people who watch it back later could see it, I guess, I don't know.
I don't know if it displays separately, because you can do this on YouTube too, if you like
watch back live streams, I mean at least you can see the chat going.
I'm not totally sure if you can comment or not on those.
I don't think so.
I'm not sure, honestly.
Yeah.
I don't think so.
I'm not sure, honestly.
Imagine if you made the mistake of sending a super chat of an old stream.
They didn't even say your name on stream.
Somebody did cheer me while I was sleeping on stream.
Okay, but that was a live stream.
Yeah, it was technically live, even though I was dead.
You were probably saying, Ben, we're reaching out to you from the real world.
You've been unconscious for 50 years.
We're trying to wake you up, but oh, but you've missed out too bad.
How did you fall asleep on a stream?
Did you, what happened?
Did I not talk about that?
Maybe you weren't here.
I did talk about it.
You got drunk.
I just accidentally, yeah, I got really drunk.
I ended the stream.
I accidentally restarted it.
I have no idea how, but I did.
Then I went to bed and slept for like six hours in a pitch dark room, and that's what
happened.
You should upload that to YouTube.
You got a lot of watch time on that.
No, I deleted it because I was embarrassed.
I don't blame you.
What did the camera show, just like an empty chair or something?
No, it was just blank.
Because I turned the lights off.
Did the people hear you snore in the background?
I don't know.
I mean.
No, no, no.
Now it's gone.
It's been banned.
Some devious man has like a bank now of Ben snore clips.
No, don't even joke about that.
I don't think I snore.
No one's ever told me that I snore.
At least not regularly.
Yeah, so you'll never know if you snore or not until people tell you.
I mean, everybody does it sometimes.
People are going to start like, here's some proof.
Like a black video and then just a snore sound effect.
This is Ben.
Oh yeah, you just play that.
Proof.
So that's what's up.
What else is on your mind, ladies and gentlemen?
Well, speaking about that YouTube stuff, what was that the p-score thing?
I watched that video Tom mentioned.
It was fucking weird, right?
There was this thing, people, like a community of people, there was this video of this guy
talking about it.
Remember that there is a hidden p-score that you can find that is basically, I don't know
how it's calculated, but it's definitely tampered with to inflate on YouTube, right?
On YouTube.
To inflate the importance or whatever.
I forget what the p stands for, I think like profitability or something of that.
There's like four or five different p's that they average, like you rank your channel on,
then average them out to give you your p-score and that determines whether your ads are limited
even if you have green monetization on them or not.
Just as one example, you've seen Munchy rack up a significant p-store score on this very
podcast on occasion.
Yes.
But like the gist of what they found was people with lower p-scores, they get a green monetization
ding or whatever.
They're not like yellow box demonetized, but the ads they get, the rates are lower than
people with higher p-scores because their work is like dubbed less or more ad-friendly.
Ad-friendly stuff that's still technically monetized, like the PCP, I'm sure, has lower
ad rates than a baby cat channel or whatever that is completely safe and gets exactly the
same amount of watch time.
It would get more money.
And they found this out through inspecting the metadata of the website.
And that video was, I watched it a week after it was uploaded.
By that time, it was completely gone.
You couldn't actually do it anymore.
The YouTube stuff were very quick to act and edit the code so that you couldn't see it.
But they made a huge list of a bunch of notable YouTubers and their p-scores.
And of course, the very, very, very top of the list where people like Stephen Colbert,
the late show with some fuck, this, that, and the other news thing, the BBC news or whatever.
All these big companies that are varying levels of watch time viewers, ship and subscribers,
but they've all got perfect p-scores regardless of the content they post because YouTube wants
to promote them and give them money so that they will stay on the site and bring viewership
to the site, I guess.
But it's shady, shady and shitty, and I don't like it.
I mean, I get it, I get the reasoning, but it's just like, why'd you gotta be so sneaky
about it?
Obviously, we don't like it when we find out.
You're gonna, when you're gonna learn that, like, they talk so, they talk such a big game
about like, we're gonna be transparent with you.
That was all in 2018.
Such transparency, Susan Wojcicki was going all over the place saying, we're gonna be
so straight with you, and then we find out this, and it's like, okay, sure.
I'm like, you're not even surprised, you're just disappointed, you're just like, of course.
Yeah?
Well, let me play Hitler's Advocate for a moment, as I like to do.
Your favorite game to play.
I mean, every company is gonna have some things they don't share with everybody, and we know
that there's these degrees of, oh, okay, like, a company has to decide, like, YouTube.
Obviously, they're gonna have some algorithm for, at the very least, to determine, like,
they've got ads, companies pay them to put their ads on videos, okay, they've now got
to determine what goes where.
Presumably, not everybody's paying the same amount, and I mean, there's multiple ways
they could decide which ad goes in which place, or whatever the fuck.
So they need some system, and I guess this is that system, in effect, anyway.
I mean, the literal number is not really, like, nobody could find out how the number
was calculated exactly, it was just the fact that channels, based on something, were determined
to be teens, or for kids, you know, suitable for kids, or teens, or adults, or there was
like a scale, and you were in a number of classes, the more risqué you were, the less
money you would make.
But you know, it's one thing to not have the information of what your channel is deemed
as, like, but it's also very confusing, because some of the channels were like, that they
looked into were like, they're seen as like teen channels, I forget the terminology, but
like, suitable for teens, not for children, some swear words, this or that, but the content
was not like overtly anything bad, it was actually quite safe.
You have to be, like, strangely safe in order to get the super safe category.
I see, I see.
I mean, maybe you could link to the video, because it was pretty in-depth, and I liked
the discussion.
It was just sort of like, I don't know, I mean, I'm not in the YouTube game anymore,
but this stuff still annoys me.
It concerns me, I mean, at the very least, if you're on YouTube as I am, like, you really
need to know these things, and watch, like, the Creator Insider videos that they release
about like updates, and just be aware, because like, you know, it's their platform, and you're
a guest, and you want to make sure you are aware if your efforts are being used in the
best possible ways.
But this reminded me of a couple other things I heard about this recently, like, I mean,
for one, Filthy Frank's vomit cake got taken down, specific, like, there was a specific
reason for why it was taken down, that I think, like, Bedhead Bernie noticed or something
retweeted, and it was like, due to it being not in alignment with like, YouTube's values,
or like, something like that, it's available online, maybe we'll see if I can find it later
on.
And then there was another thing.
There was something about how, like, there's a, I don't know if this is manifested in any
negative ways yet, but I heard some people, I think Sticks, Hex and Hammer talked about
this, there's a new, there's a new, like, degree of determining if YouTube channels
are like, wanted on YouTube at all, or possibly for monetization, it's not quite clear yet,
but the criteria for this now is specifically commercial viability of YouTube, not of the
channel, of YouTube, like, so seemingly the idea here appears to be that, will this channel
being here be commercially viable for YouTube itself?
Sounds like they're being a bit of a publisher right now, sounds like they're not being free
speech boys, I mean, that's fine, make your choice, but you know, let's not have it both
ways.
But there's a lot of shit that comes with it that they're not proven to at this point.
So I mean, I don't know, again, the full ramifications of that, I don't know yet, I just heard about
that recently, but well, I mean, you know, we're just marching down the path of, I mean,
again, it's fine, it's fine, be a publisher if you want to be, but it's just frustrating
to try to have it both ways.
Yeah, it's always been about like, they couldn't possibly explain that they are like, they
have values, because then everybody who doesn't share those values will be upset, so they
have to keep everything secret and just tweak things in the background, and it's like, everyone
hates that, everyone dislike that, stop.
Yeah, there it is.
Well, just got to know that going into the game, baby, I'm aware, I'll keep that in
mind as I make business decisions for myself involving YouTube going forward.
Yeah, that's all there is, I guess.
Oh, fuck YouTube.
Why'd you say fuck you to me?
Because I want to get demonetized.
Are you calling it a tube as well?
How rude.
Oh, guys, what's the point of it all, you know, what are we doing it for?
Oh, you want to get a secret of NIMS, a reason to live?
You want to know the meaning of life?
Right.
Please.
Okay, here's the meaning of life, it's to play the new Pokemon.
Oh, we're so starved for Pokemon, we need that to live.
I can't wait until next week's episode where we'll talk about Pokemon again.
We will discuss it to some degree, I'm sure.
Why?
Oh, because the game will be out.
It'll be out, it'll be out, you know, things to say.
Like, yeah, it's good, like, huh, yeah, it's Pokemon.
It's pretty good, I got a Pokemon, you know, I caught one, that's pretty good.
I got Pokeballs.
Yeah, it's a hell of a life.
It made me remember how I liked the other games, because it was the same, 10 out of
10.
It was able to distract me enough from playing this game to remember the old games that,
you know, pretty positive experience overall.
The meaning of life is stupid, like, as a question, so I don't care anymore about it.
I'm just going to live, and I'll find out after I'm dead, I don't need to think about
it at the moment, I'll figure it out later.
In terms of philosophical discussion, you know, I was playing on stream, Twitch.tv
slash definitely best guy ever.
What was it?
Metal Gear Rising Revengeance, and there was an intellectual philosophical discussion
between Monsoon and our boy, Raiden, and they were like, why do you kill Raiden?
People, they don't choose their circumstances, why do you kill him?
And he just said, I'm going to let her rip, baby, I'm just born to kill, and I kill to
be born, basically an appeal to nature, which is a logical fallacy, if you ask me.
But nonetheless, just do what feels good is basically the argument.
Nade's trying to make his stream out to be like, it was like, you know, a deep philosophical
conversation, but Nade over here is like the maestro of memes with the whole soundboard
of like constant reaction sounds, oh wait, this conversation's going on, so I'd use them,
but you guys wouldn't be able to hear it before recording them, too bad, too bad.
I've thought about like having a soundboard, just so that I can have my own lexicon of
funny sounds.
My vocabulary has expanded a dozen fold based on this meme menagerie I have in my fingertips
on my streams.
Oh, I know how I deal with blobs, because my language would not be complete without
including blobs every now and then.
I have one of you, Mage, in mind as well, it's you going, she's such anormy, as famously
everyone knows.
It's a wonderful little clip.
No, no.
You know what, there was one classic Internet Nate boy, you know, the other day, Michelle
got a call from her boss and the boss just said on the phone, I could hear it, because
it was just loud, she just said the clip, you're a rockstar, just like that, and I wanted
so bad, I mean, she was, because she like agreed to like take a shift or something,
and just you're a rockstar, and I just wish I had that captured, because it was so fucking
funny.
What's that?
Needlessly.
I mean, it was her voice, she was saying, this is a human being, she was speaking to
you on the phone, there was no recording, there was no...
Oh, you wanted that to be a sound, I see.
I wish I had captured that in some way, so I could make it a meme sound, because it was
really funny.
Maybe I'll use my own voice, saying it here on this very podcast.
You've just got to have Odess seem like recording at all times.
I wish I, if this was going to be like Michelle, okay, call her back and just ask, what am
I again?
Michelle, I'm going to need you to walk through that conversation one more time, and I'm going
to be recording this time.
That would be ideal, I wish I could do that.
I wish I could do that.
Oh well, that's life, baby.
Fuck, yeah.
I'm gamifying my whole life.
We got any more shit to talk about, do you want to go to voicemails, is it too early
for that?
I'm curious, I'm curious if the quality of the voicemails improved since the last time
we did.
We had one last week, didn't we?
Just one.
I can tell you one.
Well, I can tell you we have six this time, so that's an improvement.
Hang on, I'm wrecking my brain right now.
I thought I had a topic right here, right here in my brain, in my noggin.
Is it coming?
My topic is the tropics.
Is it here?
Is it going?
That's gone.
I mean, if you think of it, we can get back to, if you think of it, let's fucking talk
about it.
But all right, let's fucking go to the voicemails, and that'll take a good two, three hours to
get through, so let's see how it goes.
All right, let me see here.
Okay, first one.
Oh, of course, everybody, speak pipe, link down below in the description, leave us your
epic voicemails.
Make some short and sweet, baby.
Brevity is the soul of wit.
I can tell you most voicemails that otherwise might have made it are just too long.
They're just too fucking long, and they're not fun.
A joke gets so much less funny when it stretched out over like a minute, as opposed to being
20 seconds long.
Keep that in mind, folks.
That is the biggest determiner for me, if you get on or not.
Oh, wait, I remembered it.
It was tangentially related to meaning of life.
Meaning of life is to work hard and be cool, and I have, for the past month, two months,
I actually remember, I have been strictly regimenting my online habits, my internet usage, my phone,
and it has been really good.
I've got that schedule, I've got that lifestyle, and I think I said a while ago I was going
to do exercising.
I've kept that up every other day, 20 minutes on the exercise bike, on the old leg thing.
That's got to the point where it's not even a question.
I just get up, if it's like, did I do it yesterday?
No, I didn't.
And then I go, and I do that, and I'm exercising, so that's one good thing.
Two good things is the cold turkey thing I have, so I've made it so that, because today
is a weekend.
It's a weekend as a free day, and I was planning to work a bit on the weekend.
But of course, I was spending the entire time watching on cinema at the cinema and playing
Kenchi all day, not doing the work I was going to do, but that's okay, because throughout
the whole week, I have been like keeping with, like been unable to not fuck up my work schedule.
I've been making great progress on my comic things.
The other, yesterday, I drew like five pages, sketched five pages of the thing, and there's
like, yeah, it's really good.
And also going to bed, and waking up at the right time, and having a cup of joe, and uh...
I got mine right here.
Like a real boy.
Yeah, I'm like a human being or something.
I'm waking up early enough so that I get the early morning news and be like, ah yes, Brexit.
Yes, that sucks.
Ah, the election.
Yes, Jeremy Corbyn, Boris Johnson.
Oh yeah, we're past Halloween.
That didn't happen, did it?
No, it didn't happen.
There's an election going on now.
Oh yeah, right, right.
I could talk about the politics of that, but I don't think any of you know, maybe Mesh
does a little bit.
Who are you voting for, Gil?
Are you voting Corbyn?
Are you going for Corbyn?
I'm going to wait until the manifesto is out, and I'm going to actually read it before
I decide.
Because Jeremy Corbyn, you know, he sounds pretty good compared to all the other candidates
that are out at the moment.
And in terms of like who could win, it's either Boris or Jeremy, most likely.
And I'd rather Jeremy just on the face of it because the Tories are...
There's lots of things that they do that I don't like.
And it's generally like the other party of the rich in a very broad sense.
They improve structural things in the, you know, they do things so that they can say
that they're improving like schools and hospitals and stuff.
But it's usually just like schools and hospitals in certain places that are already pretty
good and that they're sort of like letting lower money areas sort of turn to dust and
all the people die in the streets in a sense.
And you know, they'll get around to that in a while, but you know, that's how it seems
anyway.
I've been keeping up with the news and it seems like that's the Tory idea.
That's consistent with my impression of the Tory party and like Boris versus Jeremy.
I have the feeling that Jeremy is the better of the two, but I don't have a lot of knowledge
about it.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know how good he's going to be at running the country.
All I know is that people hate him and the people who hate him are usually people, fat
old white men in suits.
So I have a feeling that he's a man of the people and the same people that hate Bernie.
Yeah.
It feels like that.
But I need to read the manifesto.
And if I don't like it, I'm thinking I'll read the Lib Dem manifesto.
And if I don't like that, I don't know what I'm going to do because either the Tory party...
Are you not going to read Boris's manifesto?
Do they already have one or something?
In like a list, they will have one.
Like in the next few weeks, they're all going to have those.
I don't know how this works.
Like policy and all that.
Like I'm going to read the Labour one.
If I don't like it and I don't want to vote Labour, then I'm going to look into Lib Dem
and maybe vote Lib Dem.
If I don't like that, I might look at the Tory one.
And if I don't like all those, I guess I might just vote Brexit party because as much as
Nigel Farage is like a crazy evil man, probably a big racist, he is one of the only politicians
that is really like clear about his intentions.
And I was like...
Okay, but are they bad?
They sound bad.
Well, they're like a single party, right?
I mean, I really don't expect the Brexit party manifesto to be appealing to me.
It should be one fucking word, right?
Brexit.
Well, no, they got to have all like policies on schools and health and all that sort of
stuff.
But like in terms of Brexit being a good thing or a bad thing, I've heard so many conflicting
reports on whether it will be a good thing for the country or a bad thing for the country
from all types of people that I don't actually know whether I want it or I don't want it.
So voting Labour is like, there's going to be a referendum that they're going to do.
So the people will vote and I will just, I'll see then what I want to vote for.
Wait, what's the referendum for?
The referendum will be after the election.
Labour government say, if we win, we're going to have a referendum to put the Brexit to
the people after they've gotten a better deal than the one Boris Johnson has with the European
Union for leaving.
Do we already have a referendum on that?
It's not like the whole point Brexit's supposed to be happening.
I know.
There's been a lot of talk about like the people generally have changed their opinion and is
it right to go back and do it again without actually doing it in the first place and people
were misinformed before, people are going to be misinformed again.
It's like, it's a whole big fucking mess.
I think at this point, a referendum would be all right.
I don't think it would be a terrible abandonment of democracy because maybe the referendum
will show that people still want to leave and then it'll be like, okay, well, we're
leaving.
That's tricky business.
Did you guys hear about, Bernie tweeted about this.
The former president of Brazil was in jail and everyone says, everyone that I've talked
to says that he was like, they trumped up some corruption charges to get this guy in
jail, to get him out of the office so that they could elect their guy, Bolsonaro.
And Bolsonaro is like a far right fucking monster, apparently.
And I guess Lula, just the Supreme Court, just were like, yeah, we're actually going
to fix that.
So they got Lula out of jail.
Sorry, the Supreme Court of Brazil, I guess.
No, of America.
I don't know.
I was checking.
And Bernie tweeted about like, he's like, fuck yeah, Lula, you're my guy.
And Lula was like, Bernie, you're my guy too.
And I'm like, fuck yeah, dude, this fucking epic, I don't know.
I don't really know much about it other than that.
I just saw that Bernie was happy and I was happy too.
I see Bernie smile.
I hope it works out for everybody.
Yeah.
Hey, to your point though, Gib, at the very beginning of this, that worrying about the
meaning of life specifically is less cool and good to do generally than doing the work
and being a good boy and doing things.
Reminds me of the legendary Bestie Boy video, existentialism is a dangerous thing in which
I geniusly clipped Casey Neistat saying that existentialism is a dangerous thing.
Forget about it, get back to work.
So true.
Great clip boys.
Real editing shots, clip that on Twitch.
Clip that everybody.
Okay, that's all I have to say about that.
All right, let's get to these dang old voicemails over here.
Yes.
Let me see here.
Okay, as I said before, speak pipe, blah, blah, blah, you know the drill.
Okay, first one is of course from Hero of the People, racist Elmo calling back in.
Let's see what he has for us this time.
Go.
I'm gonna say it.
No, no, don't do it, Elmo.
No, Elmo.
I swear to God, please don't.
Please don't do it.
I don't know anything about it.
I'm gonna say it.
I'm gonna say the bad word.
Okay, Burmer.
Yeah.
That's it.
Yas, clean.
How could anyone find that offensive?
Have you guys heard about this?
Yes.
Burmer being a new slayer.
Yes, it's disgusting.
A new N-word for old people.
What?
It's not acceptable.
It's like old people have heard about it and are now actually angry.
Some people are pushing for it to be considered hate speech, to call someone Burmer.
Did you guys see that New Zealand member of Congress who's like 25 or whatever, and while
she's giving a speech about how fucking what assholes all the Boomers are, like the real
Boomers, like someone's like heckling and she just goes, okay, Burmer, and then just
keeps going with her speech in fucking Parliament or whatever.
I didn't see it, but I heard about it pretty fine.
It was New Zealand Parliament.
New Zealand Parliament, you know, one of those funny states, one of those funny places.
It is really funny that they exist over there.
Absolutely true.
What do you think, Ben?
You're a Boomer.
You're old.
You're dead.
You know.
What do you think?
Well, I mean, obviously we shouldn't ban okay, Boomer, because Boomers are bad and we
should mock them all the time.
Right, of course.
Don't you find it a tad hypocritical that after surviving a decade of having millennial
be used as a backhanded term, as soon as it comes back to bite them in the ash look,
that's the new end word you can't say.
You can't call me that.
Obviously ridiculous.
You can't say mean.
You can't use that word.
That's our way.
I'm really curious who is pushing for this to be considered hate speech, because I think
people on Facebook are starting petitions or something like that.
Which obviously means nothing, but yeah.
Boomers do not even understand social politics.
Boomers are all over Facebook.
No, that's what I mean.
They wouldn't even understand that you could get something classified as hate speech.
Would they?
I'm not sure.
Probably at this point.
Yeah, I would think so.
I mean, my parents are Boomers.
Certainly they would understand the concept of, well, it's different between making a word
hate speech.
That's a political thing they'd probably understand, versus specifically banning it on Facebook.
That they might, I don't know.
I feel like this is such a strange, stupid idea, because boomer is...
Maybe they're probably just being blown out of proportion as an issue.
There's so many other words you could use.
They can't fucking hate speech all of them.
Okay, old man.
Okay, pensioner.
You can't hate speech all of us.
That's a challenge, sir.
Okay, creaky bones.
You could say all sorts of things.
Well, but this is the leg they're standing on, and it's caught on as a pinnacle of this
ageist side.
Okay, skeleton.
This oldist.
That one hurts, my creaky old bones.
Yeah, they just...
I mean, whatever.
It's obviously fucking retarded and ridiculous, but...
Dude, hate speech.
I mean, I don't like when people's ideas are dismissed based on their immutable characteristics,
such as age.
Well, but nobody says okay, boomer, to someone just because they're old.
They say it to them because they're acting like a boomer, and they're being stupid.
They're being stubborn and old-fashioned for no reason other than to be stubborn.
Don't you think that an accusation could be made is, let's say, of me in this group for
like, I like to plan things, I like to nitpick, and I'm like, I need details.
Is that me being a boomer?
Am I going to be okay boomered by...
Am I going to be Judas by one of this group?
You might be.
What's your point?
My point is...
You're not a boomer.
That's rude.
And I will destroy people who say things I don't like.
I am in the Teen CP fan group, and I am labeled cruelly a confirmed boomer.
Dude, you just got mocked day in, day out by those people who are not fair.
Just own the word.
Own the word.
Just say, yeah, I'm a boomer.
What of it?
Yeah.
Some day, Nate, we will be the boomers, and then we'll show these kids how it's done for
you.
We're millennials.
We'll be the boomers when we were dropping the fucking bombs on their communes, these
fucking zoomers.
We're already called boomers by the zoomers.
I mean, boomer is just a funny word anyway.
I wouldn't mind being called a boomer.
It's funny.
We're millennials though.
I know, but...
The words just change.
It's simply changed now.
It's bullshit because it's...
I don't like it because boomer is actually a bad thing.
But it referred to a specific group of people who are bad and should be oppressed with hateful
speech.
But it sucks that people joke that the fact that it's expanded just mean anyone.
The fact that I don't think it applies...
It's not that I'm thinking, oh, you shouldn't be able to say it to me.
I just really don't think it applies to me, but people use it for people like me.
So Ben, if I'm one of the good ones, then I'm not a boomer.
It's about a state of mind as opposed to a demograph.
You wouldn't say okay boomer to someone who's not acting in that shitty boomer way.
But I've seen so many people just call to boomer simply for being old and for no other
reason.
No, you're lying.
Okay, but listen.
There's people who get dismissed for having an anime icon on their Twitter.
It doesn't matter what.
You ban boomer, something else will crop up.
People will dismiss other people based on very superficial things.
It's stupid.
We'll share.
We can all agree on that.
The thing with boomer...
But I'm saying it's not superficial.
People don't say okay boomer for superficial reasons.
You say it when you're acting shitty.
When someone...
Anyone ever says it for superficial reasons.
It's great.
Believe them acting shitty.
They're disagreeing with whatever the other person is believing, so they're dismissing
them and their points by saying no.
Okay, but disagreeing with your ideas is not superficial.
It's not just because they're old.
That's what I'm saying.
It's not like the N-word, which is just something you can say to someone because they're black
and it is bad for that reason.
You don't use boomer in the same way.
Wait, I can say it because they're black?
Okay, I've got license to say that.
I'm loading my barrels, boys.
Here we go.
It's not like that at all.
That's my...
Okay, there you go.
It's definitely different.
Yeah.
All I'm going to say is, if someone ever calls me a boomer simply for being old in them,
I will say, my big brother said you're not allowed to say that to me.
That's really fucked up.
What are you talking about?
That's not what I said.
No?
Isn't that the point that it's about...
No, you got everything wrong.
...the things you're saying?
Okay, what?
The point is that it's not just about age.
Aren't we agreeing on that?
Yeah, I'm saying, yeah, you can say it.
Yeah, you can say it.
Okay.
You can say it.
The point is that you don't just say it because someone's old.
Nobody fucking does that.
I was literally called a boomer in the Teen CP fan chat because I'm older than them because
I'm like 29.
But they didn't mean it.
That's it.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my man.
They didn't mean it.
They didn't mean what okay boomer means.
That's the problem.
They'll learn the word from meme sites and they won't know what the context is fully.
As the word gets circulated more and more, people will misunderstand its usage more and
more until it doesn't actually work as what it was initially intended to be.
Yep.
Oh, boy.
Nothing means anything.
It's just gonna be a phrase of dismissal of someone's point.
Well, sometimes it is.
No matter the reason.
Sometimes.
That's what it's gonna become.
Do we agree?
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway.
Got another voicemail here.
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Here we go.
This is how tanky is Ben.
Let's hear what he has to say.
All right.
Here we go.
Nate only likes musical mail.
So here's a voicemail as a song.
What are all of your hot takes on revolution in Hong Kong?
That's it.
Cool message.
See, short and sweet.
This is fun.
Good.
I've heard.
I've got no hot take.
I saw this fucking YouTube channel called Nathan Rich, who is this American expat living
in China, who sort of debunked a lot of the claims made by the Hong Kong protestors.
I can't remember exactly what it was about, but it was interesting that they're bound
to exaggerate as every side will.
That is like...
Nathan Rich.
Yeah.
I mean, he looks like an evil man, like a skinhead.
Oh, I don't like the look of this guy at all.
But there was a video that was like...
He was just looking at policy and like the reason for the thing in the...
I don't know.
I remember it being compelling.
It was a while since I actually looked at it.
But worth checking out just to see what argument there is against the protests.
Everybody's diesel position is going to be...
I've heard nothing of this position from anywhere because no, I don't follow Chinese
media at all.
So like, I don't know what they would think.
Look, even if Hong Kong turns out to be 100% right, everything China is doing is fucked
up.
Like, okay, that's fine.
But I have actually never heard China's argument.
I've only heard the Hong Kong argument and I'm just saying, I'm just, I'm a little bit
agnostic.
Seems to me probably this seems wrong, but you should definitely hear at least the argument
if it's just, no, we own you.
That's it.
We're going to do whatever we want.
Then I'm like, oh, okay.
Then I mean, that seems a little unfair.
Well, if they haven't said anything other than that, then I guess that's all they got.
I have paid no attention.
Well, maybe Nathan Richier will open my eyes to why China is a benevolent dictator.
The initial thing Hong Kong was built for was like a UK base of operations in case the
UK wanted to invade China.
They took the land from China.
They built it up and it became its own thing.
Then they had like, you know, you can't really have this said China and UK was like, yeah,
colonialism was kind of bad.
We're going to stop doing all that stuff.
So we're going to give it back to you.
Here's a contract for how this is going to happen.
And then the year came when that happened and it happened and it was just sort of like,
it's supposed to be to come back to China from what I understand.
So it's not like Britain is like, no, this actually still is ours.
It's that Hong Kong itself wants to be independent, which is fair enough.
But, you know, like I can definitely see that there is a lot of case on the Hong Kong side.
I'm not just suddenly saying, I saw this YouTuber and I'm like a big evil man now and I fully
support China.
Not true.
I just was interested to see that.
I mean, it's quite handy to have like a Chinese, like an English speaking man saying the Chinese
point of view.
That's otherwise I would never, I would never know.
Apparently, we all agree, fuck Hong Kong, which we're, you know, take it over China.
Apparently, one of the things that the protesters want is universal suffrage, which I guess
they don't have.
Oh, it's because like, I think if they were absorbed into China, I think that they would
lose the current like democratic system that they have.
And obviously they're kind of into that.
They want to maintain that.
It's hard to argue against that.
That seems like a pretty reasonable, you know.
I think the thing Nathan said was like in the contract, there was no guarantee of universal
suffrage to be given.
So like in any case, like it seems like the UK was just like, yeah, just fucking deal
with it.
And they left.
And Hong Kong was just like, they didn't like that.
They wanted more out of this deal and they're kind of getting fucked over.
It seems like China is scary.
China is scary.
It seems like China wants to do its like fucking like silencing of dissidents and journalists
and activists.
It sure does.
It wants to do that in Hong Kong.
And this is like part of what started the whole thing.
I mean, I linked a video, you know, maybe if we link like whatever, this guy, Nathan
Rich's video.
Okay, great.
I saw another video that was like way on the other side about like China.
Like I, when people say China is bad, I'm like, I believe that sounds reasonable.
I actually know like nothing about how China operates, but I watched one video fairly recently
and I was like, ooh, that's not so good, China, you really fucking over these boys.
That's not cool.
Like if it comes down to it.
I forgot the specific link of video.
That's the word on the street.
That's all we need to know.
Yeah.
I mean, when it comes down to it, I like underdogs.
So I'm generally in Hong Kong.
Oh my God.
Chinese President Xi Jinping has warned against separatism, saying any attempt to divide China
would end in, quote, bodies smashed and bones ground into powder.
Yeah.
That is a quote from the President of China.
Maybe a red flag or two.
I don't know.
I don't want to jump to conclusions here, you know, it seems, there could be some explanation
here.
Oh yeah.
Was it bones ground to powder?
Jesus Christ.
Body smashed and bone.
Well, I don't want that.
So I guess I shouldn't support separatism.
You know, I like the cut of that man's jib.
Imagine a Winnie the Pooh smashing your body to pieces and grinding your bones to powder.
Isn't it funny?
To make these delicious honey pots.
Isn't it funny that Winnie the Pooh and the Chinese flag are the same colors?
Oh, very interesting indeed, Tom.
What a coincidence.
Wait, which flags?
The Chinese flag and Winnie the Pooh are the same color.
Same color scheme.
Hmm.
Well, I guess.
Did you ever see Winnie the Pooh's label?
Maybe it was made in China.
Oh.
Makes sense to me.
Okay.
I think I'm pro Hong Kong on this one.
I think I'm coming down on that side.
This guy, he asked for hot takes, so you've got two hot takes.
One, go Hong Kong and the second hot take.
Go China.
Fuck yeah.
Do it up, boys.
My hot take is see the two sides of the story at least.
That's my hot take.
We can please everyone.
We must.
They said it couldn't be done.
And they said bipartisanship was a myth.
All right.
Let's go on to the ghost of scumbag, Chris, is calling back once again.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Oh, wait, wait.
Last time he called him, he was just scumbag, Chris.
Now he's the ghost of scumbag, Chris.
I guess he killed himself.
Yes, he did.
Maybe he was in China a little bit too long.
Maybe he had his bones ground to powder.
We can only hope.
Maybe he killed himself like Epstein did.
Of course.
It all makes sense.
Now there's a story I can believe.
All right.
Let's play it.
Go on, Chris.
Take it away.
Yes.
You're a piece of shit.
Oh, shit.
I tried to make an emotionally poignant finale to the scumbag, Chris Trilogy.
You failed.
After you said to tell more of it, but my third voicemail was never played.
Quality always matters.
You were worthy in favor of some garbage about the dimensional murder.
Better start drinking from the cup, because this is the final straw.
Oh, shit.
Now my character arc has been cut unjustly short by your hand, and I wander the PC purgatory
as a vengeful spirit of vengeance.
Get your shit together.
Start taking better voicemails.
For next time you're on, get ready for a mouthful of ghosts.
Scary.
I guess a current example, not a good example of these better voicemails that you're helping
us to play.
Halloween's over.
Ghost of scumbag, Chris.
Get the fuck out of here.
This window was closed on this opportunity.
I like how I half-assed that voice was.
I know.
He didn't even put any stank on it, which I mean reverb.
That would be the way to make it easy ghost.
I think we've just seen an example of exactly why your character arc was cut tragically
short.
Scumbag, Chris.
Can't even do a little reverb.
That's not much to ask for, really.
It didn't need reverb.
I liked how shitty it was.
Really?
Scumbag to the bitter end.
Appreciate that, Chris.
Better luck next time, chief.
Okay, let's go.
We've got next up a humble request.
Okay.
Ready?
One, two, three, go.
Hi, guys.
Please consider uploading your shit to Spotify or updating your Google Drive more often,
because when I want to listen to the new PCP, there are usually two websites they use to
convert your video to an mp3, so I can listen to it on my phone, but sometimes it doesn't
work on the website for some reason.
So yeah, please do Spotify.
Spotify would make my life a million, a gazillion times easier.
I will pray.
Can we make money through Spotify?
Good question.
You can make money, but last I checked when I tried to get the podcast on Spotify, they
were not accepting podcast submissions at the time.
I don't know.
Well, shit.
Just call it an album.
I do grind my face against the whetstone that is the internet every week to get the podcast
up on iTunes, Google Play, and a bunch of other things.
It's just not on Spotify because Spotify is its own thing, and it's not on Stitcher
either.
Maybe that will change for a nominal fee.
Would that cost money to get it on Stitcher or something?
I don't know.
I'd have to look into it.
Okay, well, fair enough.
Is the Google Drive not up to date?
The drive is up to date.
The problem is, once it hits a certain amount of downloads, it stops working, and that happens
almost instantly.
Wait, what?
That's why I wanted to play.
What?
Yeah, that's right.
I wanted to link for a limited amount of times, which is why I keep saying, or I mentioned,
like last week, we should put the iTunes and Google podcast links in the description.
Which is exactly why I wanted to play this, because I think I did it for the last episode.
Did I?
Remember to do that?
I don't think you did.
Oops.
Well, okay.
We can go back and fix that, and we'll put it in the future.
We probably will stop linking the Google Drive one, especially because of this cap thing.
Like, what's the point?
It's not really very useful.
That's the worst.
Pretty good.
It is bad.
But if we give you people the fucking iTunes link, and whatever the other one you said,
I can't remember.
If they're there, then I mean, that's the better option, just to use those podcast things.
I don't know why we haven't been linking up to this point.
So from now on, I think look for those.
Those are better options overall.
You have 4.7 out of 5 stars on iTunes.
We're doing good.
Not bad.
That's quality.
Guys, I have news.
We sold a first loser of Fine Purpose November shirt.
Yeah.
He's the last loser.
Yes.
Show them out.
There's one loser.
Who is it?
I don't know who it was.
I want to know so bad.
Right into the show.
Leave us a voicemail.
Make it short because I won't play it.
Tweet yourself.
Take a picture of yourself in the mirror.
Please.
We need that picture and tweet as soon as you can.
I want to see it.
Well, I mean, I'm sure it's in the mail right now, but...
Well, okay.
But as soon as you can, as soon as you can.
We love those.
We love to see the merch and the pictures and whatnot.
Actually, it sold this morning.
To day.
Let me see.
The episode's been out like two or three days now, so, okay, that's not...
I guess it's not that weird.
That's not just right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Excellent.
Anyway, just wanted to let you all know that the system works.
It did.
It does.
And I just want to know so bad, who is the first loser of Fine Purpose November?
Who could it be?
And so far, the only one.
Who has found no purpose.
He's got the title and the crown.
I'm glad that everybody who is considering buying this shirt now will know it.
For them, it is a lie that they are not the first loser anymore.
That's true.
No, no, no.
To be fair, just because you bought the shirt, that doesn't mean that you, before this person,
didn't, in your own way, lose Fine Purpose November first.
At a minimum, you're going to need to buy the shirt to compete.
Yeah, yeah, buy the shirt.
So you really need to get on your game and buy the shirt already.
You don't lose Fine Purpose November by buying the shirt.
That's not what does it.
It's already a thing about you.
It's just a mark.
Wait.
It's like the mark of Cain.
How do you fail?
You have to not find a purpose in November.
You have to be certain that you will not find purpose.
I was the first loser.
You must have disqualified yourself from possibly finding purpose.
For the whole month.
Yes.
That's right.
Demonstrating.
And that's up to you.
I'd love to hear the story of how that was done.
How did you lose Fine Purpose November?
For good.
Citizens.
Good.
Cool, cool.
All right.
Next voicemail, we've got, let me see.
This is Lil' Bobo Spitten Facts Freestyle.
Okay.
Are you ready for this?
Get ready for some straight facts from Lil' Bobo.
Okay.
Take it away.
More gay facts, please.
Yes.
Obscended it himself.
Good.
All right.
Nate is over in games.
No.
Mages of female.
There it is.
Gibb is probably a creep in your life.
Ben is straight up writing fan fiction.
No, come on.
When you have bad taste in energy drinks.
I don't like, end it.
Cut it off.
And I love it.
There you go.
All right.
It's not fan fiction.
It's a social experiment.
It can be fan fiction if it's canonical.
Yeah, which it all is.
Yes, yes.
And it's also a fact, everybody.
That's right.
It's not fan fiction.
It's fan fact.
Perfect.
Put that on a fucking shirt.
That's genius.
What did he mean say, like, I'm probably a creep in real life?
No, notice how he couched that in, probably.
Those fucking wiggle words and shit.
I thought you were spitting facts, man.
Yeah, I mean, it's not a fact.
But also, like, on what basis is this made?
I don't know.
Who can say, man?
I don't like that.
I don't like this guy spitting at me.
That seems like a creepier thing to do than whatever you do.
Ooh, damn, true.
He's got to justify himself.
Yeah.
Defend your, debate us.
Debate us on stream power.
Call back in.
I want more freestyle defending your claims here.
Give us more hot free styles, dude.
The burden of proof is on you.
It's true.
It's very true.
Oh, those wiggle words.
Wiggle words.
No, no.
The wiggle words do not discuss me at all.
Please.
All right.
We've got one more voicemail.
Now, this is Mozilla Fennekin on voicemails.
He's got some information to deliver about voicemails.
So, let's give him a minute and 12 seconds to sue Diaz to say.
That's a lot.
Okay.
Take it away.
A piece of advice on how to get your voicemails played on the PCP from the actual god of voicemails.
The god of bad voicemails, that is.
If you have, like, a joke or a skit that you want to do, maybe just think about it for a day or two before actually submitting it.
You know, the whole reason why I did the human core thing is because I thought my answer of bathrooms was funny for, like, 30 minutes.
And so, when it came time for me to actually follow up on that, I didn't think it was funny, but I, you know, had to follow up on it.
I was fucking trapped.
So, I did it anyway.
And now I'm trapped here in this prison to rot forever!
Don't be like me.
Be funny.
Be creative.
Do something interesting like this.
Yes.
Amazing.
Oh, wow.
I'm supposed to be saying the n-word now!
You have been banned from the Mickey Mouse Club for inappropriate behavior.
You know, I was about to say, don't listen to this guy.
This is a bad email.
Right.
This is a bad voicemail, but he saved it.
He saved it at the end.
Good work.
What's the Mickey Mouse clip from?
I don't know, but I want to.
Sounds like the voice of Mickey Mouse himself.
That might have been him.
Maybe he's been calling in all along, pretending to be Mozilla Fenniken, but really he's been
Mickey Mouse.
Mickey Mouse sounds more like, hey.
Hey.
Hey, it's happy days.
Happy days are yours.
Okay.
I'm going to get some of that Gabagool.
Goofy.
Hey.
I'm eating.
I'm walking my New York style pizza.
Where's Mickey from?
Is Mickey like from the deep south, you know?
He's from the south.
He's a rat.
He's a fucking rat.
Oh, dude.
Oh, fun, totally unrelated story.
I had close encounter with some rats yesterday.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
You know, I did too at a taco stand.
We just saw a big delicious looking rat
run under the taco stand.
Delicious looking.
They were delicious looking.
Ooh, it was great.
Yeah, go on, what do you got?
I saw, I was out, we went to,
I was with Munchie, Kazi,
and Kibun and Fat Yoshi from RFCK.
And we went out to a Boba Tea place
and I was standing outside
and I looked at the trash can
and these two rats,
one rat just crawled up the trash can
and I realized there was a second rat already there
and the two of them just like hung their heads
over the lip of it,
looking into the trash can
and then someone walked by and they scattered.
And then I was like, hey guys, check it out.
I saw some rats in this trash can
and they all went up to the trash can
and then like more rats like exploded out of it
and they all like fled.
They all like started running
and screaming down the street.
And I was like, what are you guys so worried about?
It's just rats.
They're just mice but big.
These are my people.
Do not be afraid.
Embrace them as you do me.
They were fine, they were cute.
I liked them.
Rats are cute.
I love rats.
Yeah, they were okay.
Yeah, the rat bit the taco stand was pretty cute.
He was a good boy.
Rats are smart and cute and I love them.
I've seen the rats of Nim.
They're as smart as human beings, as I understand it,
if not smarter.
It's crowd-pleasing.
Because they know there's free food in those trash cans.
They're not wasting time earning it to buy it.
They live off the teat
as any wise individual would do.
Yeah, I agree.
I'm with it.
There you go.
Oh, there might be.
No, no, no, wait.
Hold on.
Rat idea.
I just remembered.
Rat idea, yeah.
Okay.
I've seen a rat recently, too.
Well, not too recently,
but the last time I was in Burger King,
I think that was like a while ago.
Oh, no.
We were just eating burgers, me and Byter,
and I looked out the window
and we saw a little rat scurry away
with a little packet of ketchup in its mouth.
Aw, that's cute.
A feast for a king.
That's pretty cute.
You know, this whole equal distribution
of resources thing,
like I can get aboard with it to the human student degree,
but what about the animals?
We gotta distribute our resources to the rats
and the pigs and the cows and the chickens.
No, we have to exclude someone, and I think they're it.
We all know that human nature requires an underclass
to step on it and make it feel worse than us.
A certain baseline level of bigotry,
and I think we found our marks, ladies and gentlemen.
I think we've done it, blue girls.
Mouses.
Hashtag animal racism, we're doing it.
Yes.
All right, thanks for being here.
Hey, thanks for all the voicemails, everybody.
Appreciate those, those are good.
Leave more at the Speakpike link in the description,
and give us money for all the hard work we do here
on the show at patreon.com slash PCP.
Wait, the procrastiners, yeah, you know the one.
Link below.
Yeah, what's up?
Mouse, mice, rat, rice, really makes you think.
Really makes you think.
Chinese, really gets the old ticker tickin' away,
if you know what I'm sayin'.
Twitter.com slash P, what is it?
The procrastinators, I'm fuckin' it all up today.
Yeah, yeah, you know, we do things there,
updates and whatnot, follow us there, information, et cetera.
And anything else, buy t-shirts.
Find no purpose in November,
and prove it by buying a fat ass t-shirt
for your fat ass body.
I recommend the whole neck.
There you go, there you go.
And I guess that's all there is to say about that.
Let's keep it short, you know, why drag it out
like the Jepstein murder investigation?
No, no, no, just call it quits right here, folks.
Let's just wrap this thing up and send it down the Y.
Why drag it out like a fucking protest?
Like, for fuck's sake, what happened to protocol?
For Hong Kong, just submit, just submit already.
Like quit makin' a ruckus, okay?
Yeah, yeah, we got trades to make,
we got Bitcoin to invest in,
I don't have time for this human capital stuff
to worry about.
Hell yeah.
The capital I care about is Cincinnati?
The capital of Ohio where I live?
Yeah, there you go.
Why riot, why riot, why riot for suffrage
when you can just vote to get it?
Oh, wait, whoops.
That's what I thought.
All right, we'll see you next week, everybody.
Have a good week.
Bye.
Peace out, bye.
Nerd, bye-bye.