Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's ya boi Ben Saint and ya girl Gibbontake.
Hi-ya! Hi-ya!
I don't know, okay. I don't know if this might be a voicemail. I haven't checked, but I want to post something that was posted in The Pro Crastinators Patreon Lounge.
And I just thought it was epic. So if you'll indulge me.
Yeah, dude, I don't think I may have seen this.
I probably did.
I don't want you to see it. I want you to hear it.
Oh.
Here it is. It's a little soundbeat from I'll Die.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you saw this, dammit. 3, 2, 1, go.
I'm only the only thing I'm a slave to.
Is the grind.
Is the grind. Is the sigma grind. Is the rhythm. Is the rhythm of the jungle beat.
I'm also a slave to such beats.
That little, that little, what is it, like a little cat's meow?
Ow, in the background.
That's exactly what I'm talking about. This guy fucking gets it.
I think that noise is like Diddy Kong going, ow.
Yeah, I think it is. Yeah, I think it is.
Ow.
All right. That was pretty cool. The discord.
Did I say on the show what I want to do with the discord?
Or do we just talk about that? Because I might mention it now.
I can't remember.
Well, I'll just say it.
When we release the Perfect Comic Party, I think I would like,
maybe we'll just make a new channel for people to do dedicated comic discussion.
Just the new comics that are in this, the latest episode of the,
of the Perfect Comic Party.
Maybe that would also be where people might do like,
reader surveys.
Or something, you know?
Yeah.
Talked about like doing like Shonen Jump style reader surveys.
But at the very least a channel for like,
discuss the comics in the thing.
Yes.
I have, I have about eight and a half pages of Beescapades done now.
Yo, nice.
Yeah, it's coming along.
Maybe I can get the rest done this week.
It's a bit ambitious, but you know, I'm going to,
I'm going to keep trying and keep trying my way at it.
What is your goal for pages?
Around 20.
20, okay.
Around 20, I think, because I feel like a page of Beescapades
is a little less substantial than a, than a Clarissa page.
So I thought I should have at least as many as there are Clarissa pages.
Probably more.
I mean, I don't know about substantial.
Like it's hard to, it's definitely a single page of Clarissa takes longer to draw.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a lot going on with all the text and stuff.
I watched a bit of your stream when you were drawing it.
Yes.
Yeah, that was this week.
I did my first draw stream in like years.
And I got like, I got like, I think I got like three pages done.
On that one stream, which is pretty good.
That's, that's pretty good.
As I've said, over and over again, Beescapades.
I'm, I'm not going to, I'm not going to say what it is,
but like I was working on it like yesterday and this morning.
And I'm, I'm, I'm introducing some stuff that is not going to be relevant
for a long time.
Beescapades has room to grow, let's just say as concepts.
That's all I'm going to say about it.
I'm pretty, I'm pretty excited about it, but like there's a lot of like,
there's a lot of like setup that needs to happen.
And I'm not sure, I'm not exactly sure what is going to happen in the rest of this first chapter.
Right now he's, it's been Bees, Bees hustler exploring like the town.
And then where he goes after he fully explores the town.
It's like, I don't know, I could, I could take it in like one or two different,
I could take it in one or two different directions.
I guess that's the beauty of being able to ask people to do the decision making part.
Yeah, I kind of miss it.
I kind of miss it because I have not had consistent like reader suggestions.
Like a lot of my, I kind of just, a lot of panels just, just drop like the command format.
Like he just, it's like a real comic.
He just does something instead of like there being a text command that he then follows,
which is, it's fine.
It's fine, but it feels a little, there's just like less text.
And I, I don't know.
I kind of, it's sort of a, it would sort of be nice to just have someone tell me like,
have him do this next. And I'll be like, okay.
Kind of takes the pressure off me a little bit.
I don't have to construct anything.
I just need to do as I'm told.
Well, it's like this. Well, it's like this.
I know there are several things he could do and I'm not really committed to like,
oh, he should do them in a particular order.
So I guess it's just kind of nice to have the audience be like, oh, do that, do that.
Oh, what about that thing?
And then it's like, okay, I'll follow the direction that, that someone is telling me,
that someone's interested in seeing it.
Now, without that, I have to decide what the most interesting order is.
And it's like, I can't be trusted.
That level of responsibility.
I need to go back to my old Baaljape draw streams because I can't remember
how much it was like, I didn't stream drawing the entire comic, but a lot of the beginning,
when I was just like making stuff and there was a few people in chat and I know there was this idea
that it would be like, you'd say something in chat and I'll see if I could see what happens.
But I don't know if much of it was like that.
I think a lot of it was just sort of, and then they go here and then they go there.
And it was kind of fun just making stuff up.
And it was like serendipitous how it came together at the end with all the little stupid things,
all the things I'd just drawn in the background, like the big wooden slingshot outside became like,
the snakes got stuck to it and then it became a slingshot and then the ball came and it smashed through the wall.
It's like, oh wow, I made it all fit.
But it's hard, it's hard to think so far ahead that you know that that's how it's going to be
and that that's going to be left there.
That's a, what's the thing, the gun, the Chekhov's gun?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh sorry.
No, no, that's the main point, it's hard to do that.
Did you know how jailbreak, I mean, Bale-Jape was going to end?
No idea.
You had no idea?
Okay, because like I pretty much-
I didn't even know what the location was until I drew like, oh, what if it's like in a big lava place,
like she looks out the window and there's lava and then you look out, you believe the window
and then it's like a big cathedral and it's like, and then there's ostriches.
I don't know why I put that in there.
I know the kind of general arc of Beescapades and I think there's only one way it really can end,
so that's like not really-
Consider this Beescapaded.
So that's not really up for debate and like how he gets there is kind of not, you know,
there's room for fucking around on the way there, I feel like, is why, you know, the reader input format there,
it's like, yeah, let people just tell me, like, oh, do this, do that, and we'll just see what happens.
Because like, it won't affect the ultimate end.
I mean, I don't want to go, I guess I shouldn't say anymore.
You're in that artistic state where you really want to tell everyone, you really want everyone to know like how cool this is going to be,
but you can't say anything to anyone at any point.
If I say anything about it, it'll spoil everything.
If I said like, you know, Beescapades, it has concepts, it has guiding principles,
and if I said what those principles are, it would be like, I think it would spoil like, it would spoil where it's going.
There's going to be some reveals, and I want those reveals to be surprising and make people go, hmm.
You know what I mean?
Yes, I do know what you mean.
There's like, I have ideas for Belle Jape too, that I'm cooking right now.
Cooking, cooking.
Let me cook, as they say.
Let them cook.
And the larger, like for Belle Jape too, what happens is just stuff.
Like there's no huge revelations, but the idea that there are revelations is like, oh yeah.
I don't want anyone to know exactly what could happen, but it's not like one piece, right?
You know that the idea is that pirates are searching for treasure.
Obviously, the end of the thing is going to be they find the treasure.
It's all of the things that happen in between that is like, are they going to make it through this obstacle on the way to their ultimate goal?
Yeah, is this guy going to join the crew?
Is that guy going to join the crew?
Yeah, and it's like the journey is what's interesting and the ultimate goal of like, you know, will they find the treasure?
You know that there is a treasure that is not aimless.
I think in Belle Jape, they're sort of aimless.
And so I should reveal some sort of a goal, but I don't want to show my hand as to all the lore that I've been building up.
I don't want to have like a, I want to have it like come out in a sort of, I can't think of words.
This is why I'm a writer.
To be revealed at a pace where each, if you take the whole thing, each individual part of the lore, part of the story is not interesting necessarily all by itself.
But if you know everything, like if you know the big secrets, the smaller secrets aren't as interesting, but you want to start with the smaller secrets because they'll be like, oh, interesting.
I didn't know that.
And then you like, and then it causes more questions.
I'm really explaining this badly, but you know, you know,
You lost me a little bit.
I mean, I get to start with the small stuff and build to the big reveals.
That makes sense.
Start with the small stuff, build the big reveals.
Nah, I honestly have lost myself.
I don't know where I was going.
I was trying to relate to you as an artist.
I couldn't do it.
Impossible.
I'm not a real artist.
I'm just pretending.
All this art that I'm making, fake.
It's me.
It's mere artifice, actually.
You there?
Yeah.
I don't know why I'm out of breath.
Is it COVID?
No.
That's my first thought.
That's my first thought is it's COVID.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just the room is stuffy.
I'm going to open a window.
It's cold, but like, it's not that cold.
It's the sun's shining.
I'll be in a second.
Sorry.
Did I talk last week about my licorice experiments?
You did.
Well, they've continued.
I continue, I continue to get a result that is either too,
too soft and chewy, like an airhead,
or too stiff and almost like if you chill it in the fridge,
you can actually snap it into like a hard candy.
So I continue to, I think the missing ingredient might be
like palm oil or palm kernel oil.
I think that might be what lets it get so dense and chewy,
but not hard and crunchy.
So I might have to get, or maybe glycerin.
So I might have to get some of that and fuck around.
I'm getting closer.
I made one yesterday that was pretty close.
It was pretty close to a Twizzler.
It was just a little too firm and you kind of had to melt it
in your mouth for a minute before you could chew on it,
but it was like 85% there.
And that was pretty cool.
That was, that was pretty exciting.
I would like to make a licorice flavored one.
I'm going to get some, some licorice extract.
And I got that, I got that the ammonium chloride.
I got the salomonia, which apparently is used
in licorice flavoring sometimes.
I tried tasting it.
I put a little bit on my finger and I tasted it
and it was a little bit painful.
It hurt my tongue a little bit.
So don't.
That's the right stuff.
It's like, that's, that's how you know.
It's got the, it really packs a punch.
Yeah, it tastes, tastes weird, weirdly enough,
just putting a weird powder on my tongue tasted pretty bad
all by itself.
So, but you know, yeah, it's just a little surprising.
That's all I have to say about that.
It's fun.
I like making various goose in the kitchen.
Hell.
That is good.
Hell fucking yeah.
Sorry, it is, it is just sort of like stuffy in my room.
There's no oxygen here.
Even though you open the window.
Now don't worry everybody.
There is a carbon monoxide detector.
It would be going haywire and it cut, cut, cut to the thing
with no batteries are working.
It's not working.
That's, that's Chekhov's, that's Chekhov's.
Chekhov's carbon monoxide detector.
Chekhov's depleted batteries in the carbon monoxide detector.
Yeah.
Okay.
Chekhov's gun, Chekhov's bullet currently flying through the air.
I have, I have a horror story from this week to share with you.
Do you want to hear the worst thing ever?
I don't know.
It sounds pretty bad.
You know how in, you know how in Beescapades, the beast hustler
occasionally learns baleful secrets.
That's what you're about to hear.
Oh no.
No.
Okay.
This is so fucked up.
I can't believe, I can't believe I have to say this.
I can't believe this is my life.
One of my roommates has seen my videos.
He like knows who I am.
Oh dear.
Yeah.
That's the price you pay for making a big Mega Man lecture.
He came to my room the other day and he asked me if he could use my printer
and I was like, yeah, sure.
And he was wearing a Mega Man shirt and I was like, nice shirt.
And he was like, yeah, cool.
And then he said, he cosplayed as Mega Man at PAX East like last week
and I was like, lol.
And then he asked me about my like setup.
He asked me about my dual monitor setup and my tablet.
And he was like, are you an artist?
And I was like, yeah.
And then he asked me like, what do you do?
And I was like, oh, I make comics and I make YouTube videos sometimes.
And he was like, do you make like long form content?
And I was like, yeah, yeah.
And he was like, I think I might have seen your video.
I was like, no, no.
So it was only like a, like he wasn't familiar enough with the video.
Okay.
And you in it to know instantly that it was you.
He, yeah.
But he has seen it?
He didn't explicitly say he'd watch the video.
I think he might have.
I'm not sure, but he pulled it up YouTube and he showed me the thumbnail of the Mega Man video.
He was like, is that you?
I was like, yeah, that's me.
And he spat at you.
He slammed the door in your face.
Okay.
So I was surprised by that, but I was more surprised by what happened next because he asked, you know,
I was trying to print a document for him and he asked me like if I was making any new videos.
And I told him, like, yeah, I'm kind of working on, I want to do a battle network follow up,
but I have to play the games first.
So in the meantime, I thought I was going to do a history video about the history of this podcast I'm on.
And he was like, oh, you mean the, uh, the, uh, the procrastinators.
And I was like, I can't fucking believe you know what that is.
This is a nightmare.
Wait, wait.
Did they, how did he learn, did he learn about the Mega Man first and then the procrastinators?
Or is it unrelated?
I think so.
I think he might know that just because I mentioned the procrastinators in the Mega Man video,
I think that might be why he knows what it, which is.
You do that right at the beginning, right?
Yeah.
I'm surprised he would retain that information unless he was familiar with it.
But I mean, yeah, that's probably where he learned it from.
But like, I don't know, terrible, just, just terrible.
I don't know this guy.
This is a total stranger.
I've been living with him for six months.
He knows my YouTube channel.
He knows about my podcast.
He's at the door right now listening.
I'm going to, I'm going to die.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm not going to make it.
This is it.
Some toast.
It's over.
Do you think, I mean, what was the, what was the body language expression?
Was he excited by this revelation that he was living with a YouTuber?
Oh, he was ecstatic.
No.
I mean, he was, he was just surprised.
He was just kind of like, wow, I can't believe I've seen your videos.
And I was like, yeah, I can't believe you've seen that either.
Oh, he asked me, he asked me if I made one about Kingdom Hearts.
And I was like, no, that was my brother, Lamal.
And he had, he had seen, he had seen the Animorphs one, but not the, um, oh no, he was, because
he'd seen the other lectures when he knew about the procrastinators because he'd seen
at least some of the other lectures.
He'd seen the Kingdom Hearts one and he'd seen not the Guilty Gear one, but he'd seen
the, the Animorphs one.
How fucked up?
How fucked up is that?
I mean, I, it's, it's not that fucked up.
No, shut up.
It's fucked up.
It's so fucked up.
You put those lectures out to be seen by thousands and thousands of people.
No, I did not.
I didn't, I didn't ask for this.
Do you think he's going to listen to the podcast now?
Do you think, do you think he knows?
No.
Or is he just not going to be that interested?
I, I sincerely, I mean, that's a big leap.
That, that's a big leap from, I've seen a couple of the posts you made on YouTube too.
I'm going to become a regular listener of your podcast.
I, I would, I would sincerely doubt it.
Unless he's like, what if, what if he feels like, unless he has like a morbid curiosity,
which would, yeah, he might have morbid curiosity.
I wonder if, I wonder if that Ben guy like shit talked me on the podcast that he does.
Sam, go to hell.
Don't listen to that.
I hate you.
You shouldn't be hearing this right now.
This is a betrayal.
That guy's fine.
He's my, he's my, he's the, I would say of the current crop of roommates that he's the only one.
He's pretty much the only one that has not annoyed me at all.
None of my roommates are that bad or even particularly bad at all.
But you know, once in a while I'll have a little annoyance with one of them.
This is, this is the least he's the least annoying of a mostly not very annoying group.
So until now, until now.
Yeah.
This is the sin of watching your YouTube videos that you post publicly.
That's terrible.
I really, I really resent that.
Anyway, that was a nightmare.
Yeah.
I know.
I can imagine.
It's over.
But like if somebody, if somebody knew, it's like the same feeling I get when I remember
that my mom follows my Twitter and I'm like, oh, mom.
Does she follow big girl squish?
No, she has no idea.
Okay.
That's, that's a lot of the reason why I don't do that stuff on my main.
I see.
Even though I do post like weird stuff on my main.
So it's still, I guess she reads it, but she doesn't use Twitter.
Yeah.
Just every so often.
But still it's like, oh God, I know that's who I really am, but I don't want you to know.
About it.
Yeah.
Um, I remember, um, I remember like Nate said that like a kid at like his school like
knew about a best guy ever.
He got recognized by like a kid in a class with him or something.
And one time, uh, I remember when I was living in Georgia at a party, there was a guy who
came over to my house and he was just a friend of a friend who didn't had never met me.
And he was like, are you that son of a shoe guy?
And I was like, yeah, that's me.
Uh, and now it's, it's happened again and he's my fucking roommate.
And he lives in my house.
Terrible.
Wait, what was the thing with a Nate in the classroom?
I just, I feel like I remember that Nate said that he was going to like a college class
and a kid in the class with him like recognized him as best guy ever.
Oh, so it's, hmm.
Wonder when that would have been.
I don't remember Nate talking about going to a college thing.
What?
I think he was still doing, or he, or he was like doing like, he was like finishing school.
Oh, that's right.
He had some sort of school thing.
And yeah, he had to like complete his degree.
Yeah.
That was must have been like five, would have been like five years ago, I think, four or
five years ago, maybe more.
Crazy.
Yeah.
Um, so, you know, very strange, very, very strange.
Oh shit.
Speaking of, hang on, I need to check a number, but I think this year is my, my 10 year anniversary
of having posted videos on the internet.
Uh-oh.
As Gibb and take as like the pony.
Yeah.
As the pony.
This December, 10 year anniversary of my first Gibb and take analysis video.
That's what it is.
So it'll be 10 years in December.
Wait.
Since I first made my analysis assemblage in fucking, I guess 2013.
Hang on.
My first TBAP in like 2014.
I don't, I mean, there was my little pony season three and then season four and you started
on season four.
And maybe you're thinking of that, but it would have been, yeah, I think I, my first
video was like December 13th.
So it was right at the end.
2013.
Oh my God.
It was nine years ago.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Wait.
Oh no, it was the end of 2013.
Yeah.
The first, the first TBAP was, yeah, December 9th, 2013.
Which means it's coming up on, on the 10 year anniversary of the horseshoe crew.
Jesus fuck.
Cause that wasn't that much longer.
Yeah.
You're right.
It would have been sometimes in the next year.
Oh my God.
Well, perfect time for a PCP retrospective by yours truly.
Are you doing that?
Are you doing like a lecture about that?
People have been saying you should do that.
Oh, have I, have I not mentioned it on the, yeah, I said it in my Patreon podcast.
I, yeah, I think I'm probably going to do a lecture about the history of the PCP.
Yeah.
I think that's the plan.
Are you going to try and keep it like bio-free, spite-free?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not going to, you know, like a historical.
It's, it's, you know, I can't, I can't say it's impossible to, to do anything completely
bias-free, but like, yeah, my goal will be to recount the history more or less factually.
You know, I might, I might let an opinion slip in here and there, but no, the goal, the
goal will be to like, if you don't know what the PCP is, here's, here's what it was and
what it is now and the, the story of how it happened.
You know, it's, it's, it's meant to be genuinely educational for someone who, because I mean,
a lot of people that have started following, there are a lot of people who have started
listening to the PCP, believe it or not, like post pony and then like post rad con.
There, there's people who still find it through like the Mega Man lecture, for instance.
Yeah.
That's, and those people need to be brought up to speed.
They need to be brought to justice.
They need to be, they need to be stopped at any cost.
Yeah.
Uh, so, yeah, I think that's what I'm going to do.
Uh, as soon as this freaking comic is done, as soon as this freaking periodical is published,
uh, that'll be my next, it'll be my next priority after the perfect comic party is.
I've got to, yeah.
Uh, I mean, I want to get ahead on Clarissa chapter five just because it will take probably
a little longer.
Well, I want to be, I want to give myself plenty of room to like fuck up a bit so that when
it's next month, we're not pushing it back.
Yeah.
Um, but yeah, I haven't done any of the other things like the, the contents page or whatever.
Um, I, you know, I'm, I'm, I'm working on my pages.
So, I mean, if you, if you've got time and you want to, you know, uh, do some like layout
stuff on some of those pages, you know, it would be, uh, helpful.
But, uh, you know, I'm going to, I'm going to keep getting my stuff done and, uh, and
then we'll, you know, we'll see what, what has yet to be finished when, when I'm through
with that.
Uh, uh, we need, um, I don't know.
I don't know if you want to do anything fancy for like page layout.
We can, we can always, we can, we can, we can always get fancier later.
We can.
I'm notoriously bad at choosing fonts.
I hate typefaces because there's so many of them.
I mean, I like them, but there's all, there's too many and I never know which one to pick.
And so I always end up using many different ones and it's just not, it's never cohesive.
And I'm like, uh, if only I knew about 7,000 different fonts that I could choose from, but
I only know these ones.
We should use the defaults.
Well, since we're, since this is a comic publication, we should use a font designed for comics.
The Garfield font.
I was going to say comic sans.
Uh, there's the anime ace that comes with like Clip Studio.
Yeah.
I mean.
And I think, I think that for like a letter from the editor, I feel like a pretty, like
a pretty normal freaking career.
Honestly, courier.
No.
Well, maybe, maybe, maybe bold courier.
I mean, I was just going for a letter from the editor.
I was going to say like fucking Times New Roman.
Uh, is that boring?
I mean, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
That's not quirky enough.
But like the, like a normal font with it is normal.
Ariel's pretty normal.
Times New Roman just, it feels, although it is a newspaper font, I guess it would fit.
I mean, for something like a letter from the editor, I feel like the font should be more
or less invisible.
Uh, shouldn't, shouldn't draw attention to itself.
No.
Yeah.
Um, maybe, maybe something like, uh, well, hang on.
Well, hang on.
Let me, let me, out.
Are we gonna go font th Haven.
Yeah.
We're doing this.
We're doing it.
Um, all right.
What we got?
We got courier new de chavoux, uh, cracked Johnny.
Oh, yeah.
That's a winner, uh, oh doc Champa.
Oh, what the hell, uh, ethnocentric sounds good.
Fighting spirit. I've never even heard of any of these.
Bonshrift is a good one.
Bonshrift.
No, Bonshrift, like German, B, A, H, N.
Bonshrift. Yeah.
Pretty good. I use that, I think, for Clarissa Gunsmoke book.
Honestly, Calibri.
And that's all websites use that.
Wait, what's Calibri?
What's Calibri look like?
Oh, this is pretty normal.
Yeah, something like Calibri would be fine.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, we can get we can get a little funky with
what about Karima, you know, Karima?
You'll know, you'll know what it is if I tell you.
Oh, the fucking.
The like Tim Burton kind of looking.
Wait, no, that's the death note.
Is it?
No, Karima is the it's the font.
It's the prospect and derse like titles.
It is. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course, I have that font block.
That one's pretty good.
We should use Karima.
Karima is a good, good meme, good meme.
Yeah, prospect, derse, who's who?
I think I'm Derse.
I mean, yeah, you got the color palette for it, I guess.
Yeah.
I always liked how
Prospect is not just the good characters on in Homestuck,
like risk is on Prospect.
Yeah, I mean.
Gamsie as well.
There's not.
There's not really any like real.
There doesn't seem to be any real logic to like who's a
Prospect dreamer and who's a derse dreamer.
I mean, with the humans, it kind of is just because it's like,
oh, look, the sweet, innocent.
Idiots and nerds are on Prospect
and the edgy, rebellious, like we don't give a fuck.
Kids are on Derse.
It might also be because like they're related, like like like
Dave and Rosa are siblings sort of.
So maybe it's maybe it's their bloodline.
Probably not.
Yeah, they would be together either way.
But like, yeah, I think that's the idea of like, oh, John,
because we learn about all these things from the humans,
John and stuff.
And they'd like, oh, John's a good boy, Jade's a good girl.
They're on fucking Prospect.
Therefore, the dark one is the other ones.
True.
Oh, yeah.
But then with the trolls, it's not it's not really like that.
The trolls, it seems kind of pretty random.
I mean, I mean, I wonder if you could read stuff into it.
I don't really know.
I mean, I never tried.
Vriska is a light player.
So wait, but Rose is a light player.
And she's and she's a dirt streamer, so never mind.
There's probably some sort of Tumblr theory somewhere.
Yeah, I'm sure the guy I'm sure I'm sure a blade kind eye wear
who wrote all the articles about type inversion
probably has a I'm sure I'm sure.
Dersen Prospect dreaming ties into it somewhere.
Type inversion.
You mean like Karima.
Yeah, give.
Yeah.
Type inversion inverted to Cooper.
Let's see. All right.
Let's let's all right.
Karima, that's that's a winner.
Oh, Charlemagne.
Oh, yeah, Charlemagne STD.
And by STD, I mean standard.
Oh, ethnocentric again.
Why do I keep seeing that?
That's why do you have those?
I don't know.
I didn't I didn't.
I must have downloaded a pack or something.
Silphane is my favorite like normal looking font.
I don't exactly know what's different.
It looks like Times New Roman, but it's not Times New Roman.
Franklin Gothic medium.
Oovani.
Oh, yeah, font script.
Be feel free to look up all these things we're saying at home
and be like, oh, yeah, I like that.
Eleazar, Eleazar, throw up.
Eleazar, throw up images of all these fonts as we would cut a whimsy
Waverly, Vrinda, go, go, go.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, Hope Gold.
That's that's something I got from.
That's Homestuck.
No, well, yeah, it is a Homestuck looking.
I forget where I think I got it from like a pack of fonts from.
What's itch here?
Itch.io.
OK, I mean, whatever.
Fucking we don't really need to get we don't really need to get that weird with it.
You know, for like letter from the editor page, a patron, thank you page.
But now I'm thinking of like Prospect and Duris.
We should have our own Prospect and Duris and you're the Duris.
I am the Prospect.
And that's how we slice the editor page in half.
OK, sure.
Yeah, but yeah, let's just let's let's just do that for no reason.
Let's just do it.
What if there are two things and they had a line in the middle
and they were different just like that thing that remember those images
with the pony smiling and then angry on the other side.
Oh, sure.
I can be your angle or your devil.
Yes. Yeah.
That's that can only be done with two people.
True. We should lean into who is the angle?
Who is the devil?
We should lean into the fact that there's two of us.
That's like our that's like our bit.
That's like our thing.
Yeah, what's what's our gimmick?
Well, there's two of them.
Maybe on the maybe on the submissions page.
Biblically, biblically accurate, give sorry.
So I was thinking angle and devil biblically accurate, give I.
OK, I'm thinking about submissions.
And I'm thinking how are we just going to have people like send an email?
I want I just I want people to have to like click a box or something.
Maybe maybe we'll have a form.
I think maybe we'll have like a form that you can fill out that's like
your name, the name of your submission.
I think I think I took some notes here.
I wrote down some crap.
Let me let me get my document.
I wrote down some notes make a specific email for it.
I think there should be a form and you should have to include this filled out
form with your submission.
And it would just be things like, you know, you you you agree that like,
you know, you own all the relevant copyrights to all the content you're
submitting, you know, you you grant us permission to feature your content on,
you know, digitally and archive it.
And this.
Let's see, sir.
Yeah, methods of contacting you just is is the is the work already
published on some other site, you know, include links to where it's published.
If so, is it based?
Is it cring check a box?
Check. Is it a dirt?
Is it a dirt streamer?
Is it a prospect dreamer?
And I think that's pretty much there is a prospect.
We'll have to come up with our own names for these stupid things.
I want this and.
Uh, poor, I can't think or bus.
I porpoise porpoise porpoise like a dolphin.
Yeah, I just think, you know, we should this.
This when you submit your thing, you should have to submit it along with a
thing that's like, you know, acknowledging I grant, you know, I affirm
that I am not stealing this content and it is mine to submit.
And I am I, the copyright holder, am granting you permission to feature
it in the thing and, uh, you know, it's not it's my fault.
If this turns out to be stolen, it's not your fault.
I assume all liabilities therein.
You know, uh, so we'll probably just have like a link to a page on the website
that has the form and it's like download the form, fill it out, send us an
email with the form attached, set the, the, the, the, the email, uh, we'll
have a certain include a certain something in the subject line that's
like perfect comic party submission, name of submission.
And that's, and that'll be how you submit.
I feel like that's probably the easiest way to do it.
Um, sure.
I think it's like a Google forms thing.
Oh, they can like automate that instead of having them download an image, you
know, yeah, there probably is like cheesy uses Google forms to like do pre-orders.
Yeah, I think that would be, yeah, that's probably making it a lot easier
for the, for everyone.
Yeah, I've never, I've never used that, but you're right.
That probably would be easier.
That's probably easier.
Okay.
Well, maybe we'll do it.
Maybe we'll do it like that.
Um, but, you know, we'll have a page being like submit your comic.
Maybe we'll feature it in the next issue.
Um, and that's pretty, and that's pretty much it.
And then maybe in the second issue onward, we will have another page for
like, you know, reader response where like readers can like write us a letter
or something or write us an email or maybe even just like add us on Twitter
or something and we'll, we respond to those feature of Q and a page or something.
And that'll be, but that's, we don't have those for the first one.
Oh, and like a link to like on the thank you page be like, you know,
support us on cofire, patreon and get your name featured.
And yeah, yeah.
What if, what if all the submissions are bad?
What if everything sucks?
Then we put a red man comic in its place.
Yeah.
Okay.
If there's no, we're not like guaranteeing people be on the comic.
We are just sort of like, we are publishers now.
Yeah.
You must be good enough or we will smite you down.
But that's not like a nice thing to say.
So we'll say, no, no, no, no, no, this is good.
This is good.
We should include that as a clause in the form like check the box.
You will be smote if your stuff is not, it's not good.
Uh, you know.
I like the idea of encouraging people to draw if they haven't tried to draw
like a comic before and they just want to start and it's like a good thing to
like a good reason to try.
Yeah.
Um, but yeah, the, I don't know, there will be, there will be possibility
of destruction that comes with that.
I, I, you know, I don't, I don't require that everything be like drawn by a,
you know, a professional draftsman.
I don't, I don't require like everything be executed at the highest level.
No.
But I'd only feature something if I thought it was good and had some quality
to it, some kind of hook to it, something to latch onto to be like, oh,
this is a good comic.
It has such and such going for it.
And if the, and if the submissions don't meet a certain level of that,
then, uh, we just won't feature any stuff and it'll just be you and me.
Yeah.
And that's, and that's okay.
We can have a thing as well.
If we disagree on a submission, you don't like it.
I do.
Or the other way around, uh, we can have it as like a Gibb pick or a Ben pick.
Sure.
So, so that the other is not, um, not, yeah, not liable, not, no, no blame.
Okay.
It's like Gibb endorses this, this comic.
Ben withholds his endorsements.
Well, I think, well, I think we should.
I'm thinking maybe like, maybe like once a month, like after, if we get, if we get
into like a monthly release schedule, maybe once a month, like the PCP of that
week is like, it's the perfect comic party episode of the procrastinators
podcast where we talk about the content.
So wait, PCP episode, something PCP episode one.
That's right.
Correct.
It's, it's, it's the PCP.
PCP.
It's the PCP.
PCP PCP.
It's the perfect comic party procrastinators podcast.
One.
So PCP, PCP, PCP, PCP, PCP.
It's, it's, it's PC, it'll be PCP three, five, six, PCP one.
Perfect.
Perfect procrastinators podcast episode three, fifty six, perfect comic party episode
one and I'll be the subject line and and and like cowboys or something.
You know.
Yeah.
I like the idea of it being like episode one of a different podcast
called the PCP, PCP, PCP is not PCP, PCP, PCP, PCP, PCP episode one.
And then in small writing like procrastinated podcast episode number just so just so people know the number like
It's a different show. It's exactly the same show and it looks like that's the same show, but it's about a comic
Right, I mean a naming convention is fucked. It's funny. I mean it's still a podcast
It's just on this episode of the podcast. We will be discussing the comic the the the cut the comic. That's that's my idea
And then I thought I don't know if we if we feature certain artists, maybe we
We might have some of them as guests and like talk about their submissions. Maybe I don't know
If they're if you'll be a more of a themed episode. Yeah, and that's good. Yeah. Yeah
Well, but but but you know good good good comics only please good comics only, okay
It's an amateur amateur hour. It's an amateur hour. All right. This is serious business
You the the viewer listener will do not know what good comics means. So just submit anyway, and then
You know find out fuck around and find out. Yeah, please. Yeah, please. That's the that's how you do life. You'll know
You'll you'll know
You will find out. Yeah, that's good. I yeah, you're encouraged to fuck around
Okay, well, I I
Don't know if I can get all of Biscopades done this week, but maybe and probably by next week
I feel like I can crank out another
12 pages
12 pages. I mean, I mean, like you said, I guess it's not that hard to draw. It's it's mostly um
Yeah, just thinking about stuff
The it's fucking around with the layouts and
And uh, just like
Getting it on to like a page because I'm still kind of figuring out like how to arrange it in page format
I kind of miss the gifs. I actually really miss the animated gifs
Uh, there's like a bunch of panels so far that I'm like, I wish I could just animate this
Hmm
Do you think you would make it gif version for your website?
Yeah, yeah, some parts some parts I I might go back and gifify them
Do you think all right, here's a
Suggestion because I know how it feels to have to go back to something and you never get around to it
Do you think it would be better to make the gif version?
While you're making it so that you're you know, the idea of how the motion goes
Then exists and can be put on your site whenever
And then you just take a still from it to put in the the the perfect comic party because
When I feel like oh
Yeah, I'll do that later for lots of things but in it definitely with comics
And stories writing lore and stuff. I'm like, yeah, I'll like I'll elaborate on that later
I'll I'll do that later and then I come back to and I'm like, I don't really remember what I was thinking
Yeah, oh no, I can't make it now. It's gone. You know
Maybe you're right
But I kind of thought of that and I thought yeah, I sort of wish I could animate it
But like if I just have to accept well, I can't
So I'll just do it
in a in a static image and just just make it the best static image I can
and
Part of me is like I'll come back. I should come back and animate this later
But on the other maybe I should just resist that urge and just accept that like, you know what this this is a comic of static images now
So I'll just draw it as static images
And I can I can I can tell myself. Oh, I'll come back and animate it later as cope
But it's maybe it's better to just accept that like
This this is the form it's in now, but the the gifts were good. They were they were good
Some of them were good
yeah
I know but like
Is it worth is it worth
the stress of having to be like
Keep it in my head. I must come back to this and I must
Well, that's why I'm suggesting. Yeah, like take a little longer with it and then maybe make less pages, but then get the gifts ready
There are
I think people would appreciate the gifts
If and and would be happy if you took the time to make them
I mean I would I mean
uh
I don't know because it's like the people that are the people that read it in the perfect comic party are not
Going to then need to go to my website and read it on my website where they'll see the gifts. They'll they'll have already read it
So who is it for?
um, well, it's
I mean, okay. Here here's how it is, right? Bale jpe has gifts
Yeah, if I make a physical print version of bale jpe, which I probably will do at some point
um, well, it's I'll definitely do at some point because right now I can put it on amazon. There's no hassle, but
um
It's going to be static. I'm gonna have to un-giftify all these things. Yeah, and so
The reading experience is going to be different reading it physically than it is on the internet
uh for
so
There will be a reason to go to your website
Even though they have the perfect comic party because it's a different experience. It's it's an it's an additional
layer to the images that they can't get on the pdf. I
I I I get what you're saying
I just
That it's I get that
Are you
Okay, what's your angle here is your angle that the comic is just better with gifts because I don't disagree. I like the gifts
uh, I I mean, I think the
Uh for the for the fact that it needs to be
Uh, you know a singular document and you can't put gifts into a pdf
Then it's just like an unfortunate reality. If you could put gifts in a pdf
I would say make gifts and put them in the pdf. Yeah
Um, you can't print a gif obviously
And those are like limitations. I don't think
The biscuit page needs to now be limited because of one publication when the original
You know how as you would making it
Is so cool with the gifts. I don't think it needs to I don't think you need to like
To alter it permanently. I don't know. That's what I'm saying
I don't know. I I kind of think that like if I'm if I'm publishing biscuit page in the perfect comic party as a pdf
I should make it for that
format
I
Kind of feel like yeah, some of these images might look nice with a little bit of animation
But
It sort of feels like
It's putting effort in someplace that there's like little return
I can appreciate that I can I can appreciate
that like
It's more work, but like
I don't know
A lot of things are a lot of work
Phantom's revenge was a huge amount of work and that's really cool
Yes, but you can't put that but you can't put that video game in the book
I know but it wasn't made
Well, I I tried to translate it as best as I could to the book
But it wasn't made for a book. It was made as a game
But if biscuit page is made for a pdf
Then it's made for a pdf
and and
Maybe and I and I feel like the thing to do
Is to be like well, this is now a comic of static images. I'll make it out of static images
I
and
If I'm doing if I were to do the thing where I okay, I'll make static images for the thing
But then I'll make I'll gifify them for the website. It's like I'm making two
Different comic. I mean, that's not entirely true
I just feel like why re why make it twice
Uh, if I can just make it once and put it in one place so people can just read it there
I'm otherwise I'm like splitting the audience
Yeah, sort of
I don't think yeah, that was the thing
I don't think you're splitting the audience because people who read it in static form
Will be encouraged to go to your site to see it animated. Here's
I
I think
Most people are only going to want to read it once. I don't think most people
Who are going to read it on the thing are going to be like, oh, let me go see how it looks animated
I think they're going to read it once and and so I feel like it should just it should be in one one place
Uh, so in other words like go here. This is where to read it
I don't know. Um, it's
I mean commenters, let me know what you think
There are
Yeah, there are there there's a there's a there's a one particular there's one or two
Okay, in the old
Chapters of Beescapades, uh seeing the like the the shopkeepers behind their desk with a little like bobbling animation
I thought that was nice. I thought that was cute
Uh, and there's there's a couple of scenes in the new ones where things are like sparkling
And a little like and a little like shimmering sparkling animation. I think would have added a lot to it
But it can live it can I mean it it it it doesn't like ruin it that it doesn't have those things
And I guess it doesn't ruin it
But I still I'm gonna I'm gonna champion gififying or or making gifts first
And then static making you know making a taking a screenshot whatever
single frame because um, but
Yeah, I mean, you know my opinion now. Yeah, I mean, yeah
When you talk about like there's one place to go to see the thing
I was always thinking about
My comic in terms of like it it can like it'll be on my website for free
So therefore there's no reason it can't be on every comic hosting site. There is I just haven't gone around to all that
but um the idea is to get as many eyeballs in many different places as possible to read it wherever they are
so that then I can funnel them towards maybe being interested in buying the volume or
You know following my social media so they can keep track of new ones
And so it's like I think I see what you're getting at large large web and then all follow coming towards me
So that then I can say hey, did you like that comic you read on all those different websites or like one of many different websites?
You can buy it now and then more customers potentially you're saying
That even if I even if it's in the pcp in a non-gift form if I have it in gift form on my website
some people
Might check it out on my website as well. And that's a way to funnel an audience from
To my other stuff because they'll be yeah website. I mean that's that
That's true. That's it's not it's not it's not about like as well
It's like some people will only find it from your website because they'll go to your website from watching a youtube video
And they won't go to the pcp potentially and they won't find the perfect comic party
Like there's there's no reason for it to be all over the place
if it's online for free anyway, I
I don't think a substantial amount of people are going to discover Biscopades through my website. I just I just don't think that's gonna happen
Oh, how do the people discover your website like?
Through they they they find my website through my twitter or my youtube channel
Nobody finds me through my website
No, no, no what I mean is
Uh, they'll follow they'll see you make a man lecture. They'll see you do stuff. They'll go to your website
instead of
Going to the podcast
so if
I mean if you're gonna post it on your website anyway in non-gift form that would be fine, I guess
I just like the gifts
you know
I think
Maybe if I you know, uh, maybe if I just
Rain it in a little bit and just do very specific
gifts
for very very particular scenes
Just just in moments when I think it's like most appropriate just it would just take just one every here in there
uh
I mean when I used to post it on twitter
There was the limitation that I couldn't I would normally post it in like four image
Sets because a twitter lets you post four images at a time
But I couldn't post four gifts at a time if I had a gift I could only post one gift at a time
So it was kind of limited in that way. So already like most of the images were not gifts. Most of them were were pngs
um
Yeah, there's I'm thinking of one or two panels that I'm like that that could be
That could be a gift
uh, so
Yeah, I don't know maybe
I just um
You know, I really like to not
Create work for myself
True. No, I'm only saying I'm only uh sort of pressuring you because it's because you seem like you like the gifts
You wanted to keep them. I do
like them
I think I was a little bit
I think the I mean it was kind of part of the format of
Biscopades the first time
Is like
It's sort of made to be that I can like simply like make these somewhat simple assets
And put them together into an image and and animate them lightly
And that was kind of like the mission statement of Biscopades, although I don't know it's not like key to the story or anything
It was just a format thing
uh, you know if Biscopades is
on the
In a pdf form then, you know, it just has to it has to lose that aspect and
That's mostly okay
Yeah, there's trade-offs. There's trade-offs that come with it and those trade-offs could be
mitigated with extra effort of making of gififying them for my website
I mean, there's some
audio elements to it that
Are
Going to have to be on the website and will not be able to be heard in pdf form
obviously
So like the jungle beats like the jungle beats. I mean I'm talking about the song of longing you remember the song of longing
I actually haven't reread Biscopades in a while. Well, there's um
There's a song that he attempts to sing and he fails
But that's cute. Yeah
Uh, so that'll that'll come back at some point
Uh, so yeah, that's that's that's that's not gonna be that's not pdf friendly
Um, you know our art
Is so hard and it's impossible actually
I might as well not do any you simply can't you simply you simply can never fully
Actualize any artistic vision you will ever have in your entire life. You'll maybe your entire life will be lead
Giving into a series of trade-offs and compromises
True true
Negotiating
How much of this is is reasonable to actually do and is it still worth doing if that's all I can make happen
And you just gotta and you just gotta make those choices you make those hard choices sometimes
Uh, and that's what I'm freaking doing
Uh
Life's hard
I feel real busy these days. I'm drawing and I'm and I'm streaming and like I'm lifting and like every fucking day
I've got
Shit to do
That's good though
Better than having nothing going on. I mean it's kind. Yeah, it is better than having nothing going on but
I kind of sometimes I wish
I just want to sleep. I just want to stay in bed all day
You're allowed days like that
but it's it is good to be busy with stuff because then
uh
I don't know the mind likes to be occupied. Yeah, it's true
It's true, but then I'm always like
Every day I'm always like I could be doing one thing. Do you have the days off?
I I purposefully do not work on a weekend
I do not allow myself to do work on a weekend and that's very that's allowed me to be like
Pretty fine with with all the amount of stuff I do
I mean, I mean lifting is not like an all-day activity. So I mean
the well
I mean, I don't have really have any days. I don't have designated days off
I have days where I have no
Particular responsibility and those are just the days that I'm supposed to draw on
uh
I I don't have designated
I don't have designated we've talked about this before you give yourself designated days off. I
just
feed
Feel like I should be drawing whenever I have anything else that I shouldn't that I don't have to do
I know but that that's entirely the problem because it's not designated you could feel that stress at all times
You're maximizing stress potential. It's no it's not it's obviously
Bad for for for burnout and stuff
Oh god
Um, yeah, you should have you should have a day and just say that's my self-care day
And I'm just gonna do whatever I want
But no work, I guess because you might want to work
I mean
You should resist the urge
genuinely
Do you find that resisting the urge to work on your day off
Increases your motivation to get your work done on your day's on
well, I think
now that I'm into the in the
I'm used to it. So it's like it's not even a question
It's not like I wanted work, but like early on it was like, but I could get work done
Uh, you know, I feel that stress that anxiety about like I'm supposed to be enjoying myself and relaxing
But like this is a whole day. I could be doing something
And that sort of goes away after a while after a routine is set
Um, I mean and yeah, it does I as to answer your question. It does help
I mean, I definitely I definitely waste days. I'm I don't work every day
There are definitely days that I don't do any work, but they're not days that are designated to not work
They're days when I think I could work today and maybe I will but then I just never do it
Yeah, I think that having a day where you're not allowed to work
goes a long way to making
Waking up on a Monday and being like, all right, let's get some stuff done that that that's so much easier for me now
than it used to be
Even though sometimes I still just have like a I can't fucking think of anything and it's just nothing nothing happens
It's still easier to wake up and be like, all right, let's have some breakfast. Let's get a coffee. Let's go
Let's do something I get a little bit done. Even if it's not a lot
It's it's always like possible to for that to happen. Well, I mean
um
I don't I mean, okay. I guess uh, I guess to be like
I mean, I guess I'm like my Saturdays. I don't really have I mean I I lift on Saturdays, but other than that
I don't like do anything
Uh, there's nothing like I don't know
I I have I have no particular thing that I like want to be doing on my day off
uh
Other than just like fuck around
Just just waste time
Fuck around play a video game play. Yeah, I mean, that's the thing like you can have
If you get like obsessed with a game like noita if you have your designated no work day
It'll be like, well, I know what to do today. I want to play that game. So I'm gonna play the game all day
Hmm. Yeah, so it's like easier to like slot that activity into that time slot
And then the work into the work time slot so that you're not
thinking about doing two things
For the rest of the week. I've been um
I've been playing a rain world if you played rain world
Is that the one where you're like a little liquefied rabbit?
A slug cat. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I haven't played it, but I seen the clips it looks it's very tough. I think
Yeah, it's pretty tough
And it's very like it doesn't tell you what
You need to do you you have to like figure out stuff through experimentation
And the world is very much like kind of doing its own thing
Regardless of what you do like there's an ecosystem of all these creatures and the creatures just go around hunting on their own
And some of them will hunt you and some of them will ignore you and and just hunt each other and stuff
Uh, I'm about like three or four hours into it now and I feel like that's not long enough to have really like figured it out
um
I'm getting a little bored of it
uh
Everyone tells me it's really good and really deep and stuff
And I feel like maybe I'm just bad, but I'm starting to get bored because
I think every every I'm just like wake up go out
Hunt around
Oh, there are animals avoid them eat food
Maybe I'll maybe I'll get killed and then it's like okay. Well, I didn't make any progress
Maybe I'll find a door that I can get through and then it's like okay. Here's a here's another ruined area
Oh, okay. I'll find a new place to sleep. Oh that now that's my nest now. Okay, cool and then repeat and
I don't know. I have I have yet to feel I've I've found new areas
I have yet to feel like I've made any significant progress
of any kind other than moving to different places
And that's not a good feeling and I don't like it and I get that the game is like not holding my hand
but I
I'm I'm really I'm really hungry. I'm really needing the game to give me some glimmer of like what am I doing here
What's the point? I get that I'm hunting my buddy or my brother or whatever he is
uh
Just feels like
No progress has been made
And I don't like that
Uh, I'm more like lame world. I'm getting a little fed up. I I want I don't want to write it off
I want to keep giving it a chance because I really like a lot of stuff about it
It's just not giving me anything
Uh, but maybe I need to keep at it a little longer
I'm sure I think I feel like
Tio is always in my stream asking me how's you played rain world you're playing rain world. He's gonna be so mad
He's gonna be so mad that I said I said this
Um
I'm not I'm not gonna give up
I'm not gonna give up
You're not gonna give up just like I did with inscription
Ah, it's so good. You were you were getting there. There's there's secrets
The secrets give you don't even know you understand. Are they baleful then?
Um, yeah, some of them are a little bit. Yeah, some are a little bit baleful. Um
Are they bale shape?
They are not
I'm sorry. Oh
Uh, yeah, they should have been. Um
I try I tried to play noida the other day and then I realized I have a save file going where I have like an all-powerful god build
Made I have a wand
That simultaneously teleports me and for one frame creates a giant black hole
Where I teleport to and then deletes the black hole before I can do anything
So the wand like rapid fire machine gun shoots out teleport spells that travel instantaneously
Create a black and so they it deletes any matter that's in front of me
So I can just travel in a straight line through anything through like a mountain
Just dig right through it and like it like it's not even there
Uh, it's pretty funny
It's it's pretty cool. But uh, you know, I'm at that point and I'm like, well, I pretty much built the ultimate wand
Uh, I could just go win the game. I guess but
But it'd be such a shame to end the save file when I'm so powerful
So I like booted the game up and then I remembered. Oh wait, I have like a god mode run going
Ah, never mind games boring games sucks. Don't want to play it
Played rain world instead was like, ah cool game. But what am I doing here exactly gave up on it? Stop playing it
Uh
You know, there's just nothing good in the world on on earth. Yeah
Video games are the worst thing
That anyone ever thought of what if you went outside?
That don't even get me started on going outside. You think video games are bad
Don't even freaking talk about that. Uh, Jesus
There's so much to be found in nature. There are birds and rocks
Who cares who cares genuine genuinely who cares? Um, who gives a fuck me?
Stupid annoying. I like I like the nature. I like seeing
The sunshine dance upon the leaves
I'm shaking my head in shame in shame and bemusement and confusion. I
We're just not gonna we're just not gonna agree on this one. We're not gonna make it
We're not we're in gmi
No, I hate outside
There's COVID out there
There is COVID out there
I'm surprised I haven't gotten COVID again. Well, actually, I'm not that surprised. The only place I would get it would be on the bus
Uh, but I haven't gotten it. So that's pretty good. I thought I was getting sick the other day
But I it was fine. Didn't didn't come down with anything
I um, I'm expecting a sickness
People were coughing my dad was coughing and he's like, oh, yeah, there's this thing going around and I hadn't gotten anything yet
So I'm like, fuck. I'm the last one who's gonna get it
Oh, well, it's not COVID. I probably not nobody's having a problem
Yeah
Cases are really cases are quite low in my area right now. So I seem like like I'm pretty unlikely to get it
soon
Even in the worst case scenario
So that's nice, I guess
Um, well then if you don't like video games if you don't like the outside, what about anime?
Uh
What about it, uh
Uh, what do you want to watch some?
No
Why do you is there one in particular your no, well, I um
Somebody asked me
I think it was prince isolation and on my stream
Asked me what my favorite anime was and it seemed like just a genuine question
Uh, yeah, and I'm like I I couldn't answer immediately. So I went today
I tried to figure out all the animes that I've seen
Uh, all of or most of which is not that many
And I put them in a tournament bracket and I tried to figure out who is the best of my favorites is animes
Which is my favorite anime here's an image of the tournament. Yeah, I was gonna say show me
I mean
Monster, okay
So what's your thoughts on these these choices?
Uh, there's a there's a bunch here. I haven't seen
I have not seen monster. I have seen a little bit of inferno cop
I've never seen onigai teacher never seen revolutionary girl utina never seen bleach
Never never even heard of wait kenpu denki berserk. What is that? Is that like berserk?
That's the berserk from the 90s. It means like the
The the you know the golden age arc or whatever
Because the the the the more recent one is just called berserk and it's the one that sucks
I have not seen oh the 3d one. Yeah, 3d one. I guess there's another one as well. I don't I don't know what that's called
Never seen hands off isa can never seen sungatsu no lion
Sungatsu no lion is so good. You would like it because the guy is uh, uh, he's got glasses and he's sad
That's all I need. That's all I need
Uh, never seen I've seen some of the melakara of hara hara isusami
I've never seen gun demore in the pocket pocket. I've seen all of
I've seen all of uh
The rest I think you've seen space runaway idiom
There's a few in the second round that weren't in the first round. Oh
Death note space
runaway idiom
Gorin lagann and lucky star
No, I've never seen space runaway idiom
I think I've seen all the all the rest um
so
Did you so
Am I reading this right? Did you say that sungatsu no lion is your favorite anime?
Uh, no berserk is my favorite sungatsu is very good and it's second place
And then in the bronze the third third the best is kari kano the the romance one
Kari kano is really good and it's so
Doesn't it just end like it doesn't have an ending right? Yeah, it just sort of ends. I think the manga
Goes on a bit longer, but it's sort of also it just ends
Can't remember if I read all of it
Have you you have not seen um
Samurai shampoo. No, that's one of those ones I kept hearing about and I just never go around
I think it's better than cowboy bebop if I'm if I'm well honest if I'm honest with myself
I like it more
um
I mean, yeah, these are
pretty good
pics I guess
I
I don't know
I don't really have uh
Don't really have okay. You thought you thought cowboy bebop was better than kill a kill
No, I guess I'd agree with that. It's it's close. You know cowboy bebop. I love it. He thought cowboy bebop was better than
diebuster
I
I know I you know, you know, I'm a little I'm a
I love diebuster
I'm a little bit of a cowboy bebop hater
Like I don't like it as much as everyone else does like I just think it's kind of good. Uh, you know
It's hard on reflection. There's so much about cowboy cowboy bebop that I like that is
mostly vibes
Rather than like oh this episode. So there are a few episodes. They're just sort of like I don't I don't really
I don't really vibe with it. I don't really love the vibe cowboy bebop. I know I I
I feel like it's heresy, but
I don't know. It's it's cowboys in space. It's it's exactly those vibes combined in a very brown
great
the the kind of like
Jazzy noir vibe is just not my
It's not super my cup of tea. I think the I like I like shampoos viable a lot better. Mm-hmm
Where is um
Where's gun buster on here? Oh gun buster
Gun buster lost to one piece which is you fucking idiot you fucking moron. Fuck you
I was waiting for you to find that one
One piece beat death note. What's wrong with you because I just I like on reflection all of it like one piece is
Got a good anime actually. It's actually very good. Nothing doesn't it's it's good in places. It's good in parts
Yes, I think that's not really falls off after L's death and it's just sort of like yeah, it does
Okay, but the first half of death note is like
I don't know. I mean it's a good anime. It's it's
Obviously the manga is better as it almost always is yes if this was a manga thing
It'll be different. It would be different very different. Although. I don't know one piece might
Soundcaster no line also has a manga and it's also very good
Die buster and gun buster for me would make it like all the way at least to the semifinals
For these wait a fucking second. Do you think try gun is better than fully cooly? Oh, no
You're fucking cracked. You're fucking cracked in the coconut. All right. I I had I thought about it and I'm like
Fully cooly is pretty cool. It's not like I didn't like anything. I think I like basically everything except like
pokemon
and a lot of bleach and Naruto are lame
um, yeah
But like fully cooly is great. Try gun is it edged it out?
I don't know what to say. I couldn't think of like a smart reason
You
You just don't know I don't know just like oh my god. Is it just because there's more of it? No, no, no
That's not I haven't even finished try gun
I just really like the the aesthetic
I I I get that I do like the aesthetic of try gun
I'm with you on that try gun's a fucking mess like the original try gun show like it's a total
It's a total mess. Maybe maybe
I it's it's it's all aesthetic
And I I don't know honestly try gun try gun does have a good aesthetic. I I I strongly agree
But so does fully cooly. It's so does fully cooly. It's hard. I think I think the thing about fully cooly
Was just I was completely confused and I need to rewatch it
I need to rewatch it and then I'll I'll I'll put a higher up
Yeah, I mean sure true true. I watched it and I was like, huh?
Oh, it's over. Wait a minute. You think neon genesis even galleon is better than bleach?
What the fuck?
They don't they don't even have a single giant sword in neon genesis eva and galleon
They do they have like a like a they just have a big lance. Yeah, it's uh, it's basically a sword
It's basically a bank. Hey, you know, it's in that's incorrect. It's not it's not accurate. What if shinji was a shinjigami?
Oh my god, what do you what would I don't know what I would do in that scenario?
I just I just I've been I've been like getting further and further for my microphone
I'm sorry if my voice has been getting quieter and quieter. Well, you're screaming you're screaming about anime and it's it's
I've just been leaning. Yeah, I
I gotta say I do now that you say I do strongly disagree with a few of a few of these match-ups
I really don't know
What is going on with you dog?
Well, that's the reason I brought it into the show
Viewers at home, please seize and cope
and rage against me
Also, um, I
I like I do like I like the karekano beats melancholy of haruhi susumi agree agree with that. Yes agree with that one
Where's utena? I was I was annoyed that utena went up against gurren lagann immediately because I really like utena
And it's stopped to the first round
You you think you think eva you eva beats gurren lagann for me gurren lagann beats eva no question
But I mean it's a little hard. I understand I understand why someone would like eva better. It's a it's a different sort of feeling
Um, obviously eva is very dark
Shinji's a little fucker little fuck boy
and he's
life sucks
And I think oh, you know what I was going through my head as I was doing this
I was like I clearly have a preference
um for four by three like
drawn on cell animated shows
Things that are like hd digitized stuff
I tend to not like the look of them so much
Which is why san katsu no line getting all the way to the finals is quite good
I really like that. I I I I understand that aesthetic preference. I I really do
um
I mean, okay
I try to rewatch gurren lagann not too long ago. It's not like I it's not like I don't understand
What there is to like about
These shows even the ones that I don't think should have made it so far
Uh, I mean, you know pretty good. You know what I like you know what I like about this list is that there's not too many
Items on it. It's comprehensible if you'd seen like 40 anime this list would be a nightmare. Oh, yeah
I would have multiple different images. I suppose there'll be like brackets
It'll just be like, you know, what's funny. I realize I had not seen a single dragon ball, you know anime
I've only read the manga
Maybe I should make a uh
A tier a thing like this because I haven't seen that many anime. Yeah, I would love
I would love to see probably seen more than you but not by like that much
I would love to see you do a tournament bracket anime thing. How did you?
How did you make a list of of anime you see?
I google's tournament bracket generator and this website came up
But it was really annoying because it asked me to sign up so that I can start the tournament
Um, I've you I've used this website before this this tournament
Yeah, I remember it not being quite as annoying the last time I used it
But yeah, you have to sign up now. Um, I can't remember what website it was on and I closed the tab
But how did you come up with your anime list? Did you just think of them off the top of your head?
I thought of the ones I could think of and then I went to my anime list and I scrolled down
Did the top most popular animes and I was like every so often I'd be like, oh, how did I forget space dandy got to put that on there
Things like that. Yeah
I haven't really seen any like super obscure stuff other than like garzi's wing. You didn't put garzi's wing on here
I don't think I actually watched the whole thing or like a lot of it. You didn't put mad you didn't put mad bull on here
Oh mad bull. Yeah, we watched that how much did we watch all of it? We I
We watched a couple episodes. I don't know how much of it there actually is
Mad bull mad bull should be on this if it's like an ova
Which plebeian weave episode what what what plebeian weave show did you watch?
I watched the k-lon movie and this this doesn't include animated
Anime movies just ova's and yeah serialized tv
Yeah, one of the ones that I would have to put on my list would be I think it was called planetarian
The show that I watched for that. Oh, I guess that I guess that's a good time to mention that
I have I have made the plebeian weave blu rays. I'm no longer selling them. They're free now
They're on my website. The files are downloadable
stcomics.com
Slash store.html the iso file is just up for download and if you have a burner you can download it and you can
Burn your own plebeian weave blu rays
If you I've the power to the people
Uh, they're democratized now lol
Uh, okay. Yes, uh, there are four episodes of mad bull
And I think we would have watched the whole thing. So I should have put mad bull. I forgot mad bull that mad bull was great
Mad bull was pretty good. It was pretty
I don't know if I would I don't know if I would have liked it as much if we didn't watch it in a big room with people yelling
And getting drunk and getting drunk
Yes, um, it definitely benefited from that
But I think it's I mean we were all like cynical at the beginning like uh, this is
Is this like a really cheap shit thing?
And then and it kind of was it kind of it was it's pulpy. It's like really like pulpy
I would maybe maybe say exploitative exploitative and like, um
Um
We we really came to like it because it was insane
But then it became self aware about how insane it was and it just kept going and it was like, oh now it's now it's now
We can like it normally
And we're not laughing at it. We're laughing with it now that that now that they have shown
That they understand that this is like
You know
It it is silly, but like it insane and cool and mad bull himself
It's like the coolest guy
He's so cool
He loves the ladies
Just like me
It's like he's an american
And then the the little guys like a japanese transfer or something
Wait, does the show take place in like new york?
Yeah, yeah, he's I think it's in new york and his the main character is like a japanese
Officer that's on like fucking exchange program or something
Yeah
See to see how the real cops do it in nypd
A cab includes mad bull, but you know what I still support him
He's he is a bastard, but he's a he's a lovable bastard, you know, he's just you love to hate him
Uh, what was what was this website used to make this tournament? Um
Mad bull monument
He could vor the little guy so big
Jesus
tournament
Bracket generator. Yeah
Challenge is it challenge? Yes. That was the website. All right, cool
Well, I won't I won't make it now. Um, but that will be fun. I will try and make one of those for the next episode
Yeah, once I finished utena, I will be looking for a new
Like cool anime to watch that's
Uh, give her watch, uh, give her watch. Okay, should I include anime that I've seen like two episodes of?
I could have added so many to this if I included like one or two or three episodes
I've seen like two episodes of i've seen like two episodes of musishi
I don't know if I should include that one
Oh
Fuck what was the what's the what's it called?
Um, oh
No, I can't remember it. Um, munchie loves this. It's a cg anime
With a guy with wearing a red and white stripes like full body something or other
And there's a little dog demon guy with a mask on her face
Chainsaw man
No, not chainsaw man. It's it's like a kids show like 3d animated
But like creepy looking
And it's kind of insane like are you talking about like poppy the entertainer poppy? Yes
That's not an anime
That's an anime. That's not japanese
Isn't it?
No, that's like an adult swim original poppy the performer
Is a series of 3d cg shorts produced for kids nation one of the old time
Well, the all anime satellite stations in japan. Yeah, no, there's japanese
Oh, what the fuck poppy the performer the show is produced by husband and wife team ryuji misuda and waka
Wakako misuda
Okay, well shit
Maybe it counts as an anime. I would say it counts because it's like it's I mean, it's an odd sort of thing
But like it doesn't it doesn't feel like an anime. It doesn't
Feel like it should count. Uh, well, I I feel I feel like it should count
Yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah, okay. I I get it
Okay, so poppy the performer mad bowl. I'm gonna do like right now who wins. Oh, no, that's too difficult. Ooh
poppy versus mad bowl
Who could who will survive
the battle
I've actually seen a lot of
I've probably seen a lot of like crappy anime like if I if I combed through mal
I could probably remember a bunch of stuff that I like completely forgot that I
Watched once upon a time like show bits. I've seen show bits for some reason
Yeah, on a guy teacher was one of those like steel angel karumi
I I I learned about anime and I watched like Naruto on some site and then I was like, oh
What's these other things and I think on a guy teacher was one of them
And I was wait, have you know?
Oh, sorry
Yeah, I've never seen on again. I don't I think it's just sort of like
Oh wait, no, I remember the guy there's a man boy teen boy
Um, he wakes up man boy teen boy. Gotcha. He wakes up from a coma and he is
A teenager on the inside
Or something. No, I can't remember Conan detective Conan
No, no, I read detective Conan for a bit
There's something something
like
Waking up out of a coma and being like too old for all the people around you or something
I don't remember I hate that's how I feel every day when I wake up one day K Kusanagi notices a strange glowing woman by the lake
What he discovers that the woman is actually an alien officer from the galaxy federation. Hang on. This isn't the right thing
She's also his teacher and in spite of the setback he and his teacher gradually get to know each other romance blossoms
What
They get married
There's no way I watched this doesn't seem right
Have you have you not seen full metal alchemist?
No, I did
There's two shows and I didn't know which one to pick because they people say oh, they're both good in their different ways
And I'm like, okay. Yeah, I've I've only seen the old one
Okay, there's lots of like things I've heard about and I'm like, oh cool
Never did you did you never watch Yu-Gi-Oh?
I I caught like an episode a hero there
I actually caught an episode of like Yu-Gi-Oh gx or like some Yu-Gi-Oh movie
I actually watched a somewhat can I would probably have to include Yu-Gi-Oh not like gx or any of the sequel series
But the original series I watched a bunch of it just because it was on
I'm getting distracted if I if I let myself all oh just make my list right now
Oh ichigo marino. She is uh, yeah, I remember now. It's the loli character, but with the she's aged up
mentally
She's young. She's not a kid, but she's 15 outside and she's been in a coma
For a long time and her real age is 21 wait, huh?
Wait, how does this make sense?
She resembles a 15 year old
But her real age is 21
Her physical development was stunted due to stand stills
To the same way they affected k
stand still
What the fuck is that?
You know
I guess I remember it making sense while I was watching
Is that like a magic thing?
No, no, I think it was I think it was
It was all well the teacher's an alien. I don't remember that part. I guess it is my teacher is an alien
Oh, do you mean the series of children's novels by bruce coville?
That I read when I was a little kid and that taught me to be a communist before I even realized it
Yes
That's what you're talking about, right? Yes. Yes
um everyone everyone everyone should go read we should we should have a
We should do a podcast. We should make a new podcast
We should make a new podcast where we just read my teacher is an alien
You know, you know the animorphine time guys. It was tyler who was a big animorphs fan making nate
Read animorphs for the first time. I should do that to you. I should make you read my teacher's an alien for the first time
He's like third grade reading level children's novels and be like, yeah, yeah
Isn't brach's home based and you'll be like yes, and I'll say thanks
Yes, it's brach's home kreblem
There was the blue one
And I think that's it I think there were just three aliens
I may have also watched
Onigai twins. I thought it was maybe part of the same series
Might be but it's like a different guy
So so anime movies don't count like paprika doesn't count a millennium actress is not no
I mean, I think they count in like my anime list people would say. Oh, what's your favorite anime?
And they say spirited away and like it's something about it feels wrong just because like I associated with like a serialized long running
Or other ways multi-episode little thing
Okay, I won't I won't yeah, no no if I included movies there would be like a lot more
Yeah, and how do you how do you compare spirited away to like uh inferno cop
To inferno cop. Oh, you know what I watched uh like this past week in a call in the in rfck
Uh, I watched porco roso for the first time
Yo, that's a great one that one. It was great. It was awesome. It might be my new favorite ghibli
My old one was kiki's delivery service, but the porco roso might be better
It's it was so good. It was awesome. It ruled. I love how he's he's not recommended enough
He's a piggy
Okay
So I'm not supposed to understand why he's a pig, right?
I think it is theme. Well
That it's not like it's
Only we can see it people do refer to him as a pig. I think the girl the girl asks him. Why are you a pig? Yeah?
I think um, it's a thematic reason
Like he like yeah
Something something pig. I I don't actually know why something something pig. Yeah
But I think if you analyze that you could come up with a good, you know theory as to why
Well, well when she asks him why he's a pig
He says
Basically, he tells that story about how his whole squadron was shot down and he basically he told he should have died
He had a near-death experience where he saw his whole squadron
Go to heaven basically and he was like on his way to heaven
or maybe hell
But then like god sent him back and I guess
He was a pig after that
I guess is is what i'm supposed to take away from that
I love that scene by the way of them rising up through the clouds
Yeah, I just kept
I just kept wanting him to reach down
And scoop up some of the cloud
Like liquid that he's like floating on in his plane. He was it was like right there. It's just just scoop up some in your hand
um
Yeah, it was a good scene, but
Is it is it like a is it like a joke about pigs fly is is that it?
I mean if it is a joke it would be a japanese joke
So it might be something that doesn't make sense in English. I wonder if I wonder if they have that expression in japanese
It's something about like almost going to heaven but being turned away turned him into a pig
Maybe like and then okay, but then it feels like he's not good enough to be alive
And like god has rejected him like he should have died with his people
Yes, he said he said loathing. I'm a pig like it's sort of something he said all the good. He said all the good ones died
Yeah, and like maybe god would reject you if you're like a little beastling a little pig guy
And so he sees himself like that and it's manifested physically literally just the plot of that of that bones in the ocean song
same
Same story. I was like as a shanty. It's not a real shanty. It's a it's a it's a modern
It's a modern band made it in the style of an old shanty. So it's not like a genuine worker's song
Uh, but it's the same the plot is a guy like has like survivor's guilt basically over the fact that his whole crew drowned
And he was the only survivor
Uh
There's this scene. Okay at the end the end credits though. They show all those like
drawings of a whole squad
of pigs
and I I think
I I wonder
If that's his his crew in heaven
That's the only thing I can think of is that when you go to heaven you become a pig and he
Went but was turned away and he became a pig
But he didn't go to heaven and now he's just he's a he's a heaven pig on earth
Hmm
Like like the idea that he sees himself as like a worthless guy who you know, he's not one of the good ones
He should have died then
Um, he sees himself as a pig. It's like like on the face of a derogatory
But then it turns out
God loves pigs more than anyone else. I kind of feel yes
That's kind of what I came is that it's some sort of like weird like heaven blessing
Yeah, is that his like his brush with heaven turned him
Maybe he comes back. This is what an angel looks like. He came back with an angelic glow and he doesn't realize it
That's what I think and I might be reading too much into the like
I feel like the drawings at the end of like the whole like everyone's a pig
That might just be like concept art that they use and they didn't mean for you to like
Read into it that much but like reading into it is like who are these people
And the only thing it's they show a whole squad of pilots and they're all pigs like is this his
Or is this his squadron? And that's the only that's the only thing I can think of unless it's like
No, that's the that's the only thing that makes sense
I I if I either I discount that as like not canon or
What what else could be that's my interpretation
And it's very it's very smart. Thank you
Uh, good good good movie though and now I understand
You remember mr. Boop
Yes, did he do a porco rosso thing?
Yeah, the gina gina from porco rosso is like his ex-girlfriend
And when he's like and when yeah when he's um
I think it's when mr. Boop or it's when betty gets kidnapped by her dad mr. Boop
Uh, he like goes to see his ex-girlfriend gina from porco rosso and it's like I don't know what to do about my marriage
And she's like if you love her you got to go after her
Uh alec and he's like, yeah, thanks gino from porco rosso
It's too bad our relationship didn't work out because you don't like having orgies and I love having orgies and she's like, yeah
Okay
Good old mr. Boop
And I was like now I get it now I get who gino from porco rosso is she's a nice lady. She's a nice lady
Yeah, like a little
Weird world war two speakeasy sort of place
She like a server or like a singer or something. I don't remember. I think she was a singer
I I wasn't sure if porco is supposed to be like an old guy, but I don't think he's not like that old
And he's like 30 or something because like he's a world war one pilot and this is like
The interim in between world war one and world war two. So like it hasn't actually been that long
Since world war one at first of the movie began. I thought he was supposed to be like an old old guy
But no, he's just a somewhat his his little
He looks old being a pig being a pig really really puts years on
in photographs
on film
It has that effect. Yes
Yeah, okay. Well, I'm glad we anyway. I just wanted to talk about how good porco rosso is. Um
Just the the the the exuberant joy of flying really comes through and
porco is just a very
Fun and funny and likable
Dude and just the vibe of the film is immaculate
Yes, I always loved the uh
the way it's I mean the
The vistas and the
The the shots of like of like the clouds
Um casting shadows on the ocean flying through that like that's
That's real shit. That's what I like to see in real life
Yeah, the the vistas and just how like you you're always seeing you're always seeing just like people in town
Just like going about their lives and doing stuff and like the whole team working on the plane. It's just like
What a nice time everybody's having
Yes, just great
um
Yeah, well, I won't put that on my tournament list because it is a film
But it was good, uh, okay
I have another thing to say about this week and it's uh another horrifying
terrible nightmare
Uh, so there was like a an april fools video from gino samuel
You know
Do you know about this? Do you see this? No, I didn't see anything about that
Yeah, well, they they recently uh got to the part where I have the conversation with chris on twitch about
the merge and stuff
and uh
I guess the april fools video includes like an ai generated conversation between me and chris
And I guess it ends with like chris
gets the good good it's like good ending
And I I I didn't watch that. I just heard second hand, but uh apparently good ending is like
Fully transitions gets bottom surgery goes on to become a you know a fully realized
woman leading a in the big city leading a
Prosperous life or whatever, uh, and it's a you know
Whatever they they aide me is the is the point the ai convote me over on gino
And that's fine
I I guess it's fine
It's fine. It's fine
That's the worst part
No, it's okay. Everyone told me like it's someone told me that like it's it's obviously a joke like nobody's gonna watch this
Yeah, I mean, I I think it just sucks that like
people who have interacted with chris chan are gonna be part of those
3000 hour documentaries on youtube
it it it does
Make me look a little escance that like
Yeah, gino
It seems like he'll just read any series of tweets that like anyone had at any point with chris
And like that's a video like that's a dot in goes into in the documentary
uh
How on earth could really really feels like scraping the bottom of the barrel for like relevant content
How is that the the big playlists that gino samuel?
I guess
It's like 70 episodes now 78
How is there like a like a thing you can do to see how long a playlist is?
Uh, I think it says if you click on the playlist and it and it opens it up in its own window
Like the playlist list on the right side should have the number of videos in it
But I mean like the the watch time like how long have people I've been watching this for
How many hours of their own lives have they wasted?
I mean
I mean by that metric lots of things have wasted huge amounts of
Yeah, but like the chris chan documentary does not like you could tell that story so much more succinctly
Like it's so bloated whatever it's going. Yeah
It's it's bloated
I I get it. I I get
I get that like you can continue to make content
So why not just continue to make content and I get that like people just want stuff to listen to
I get it
But it it it really does feel like scraping the bottom of the barrel
like it's it there there's not actually 70 episodes worth of like
Explanation required to understand this we're just kind of we're just kind of rolling in the slop now
We're just kind of reveling in in the same old shit, which is okay. I'm not judging anyone
I don't I don't even I don't even begrudge it. I mean I I get it
I get I get the appeal from both the creator's perspective and the audience perspective of you know, pretty repetitive
Not particularly edifying. We're not actually gonna learn anything from this. Whatever. We're just here to waste time. That's fine
Well, yeah, um, yeah
That style of content. I guess it's just the fact that it's like it sort of betrays the real reason
people
like
Think about chris channel all the time is not to
Answer questions like wow wonder what's going on there and then they need a like a explained video
It's just to like revel in the slop
forever
That playlist will never end. I don't think
People will will want to just think about how much chris is cringe
Over and over again for the rest of their lives and it's the fact that it's the fact that it's made it to 70 episodes
Yeah, tells me that there's pretty much no bottom to like how irrelevant something has to be in order to like be included
I guess he's going in like roughly chronological order. So I feel like it's
It has to run out at some point
I mean when they get to the the trial
Or the you know the incarceration. Oh, she's out. She's she's free. Did you know that?
And I think that was mentioned last episode. Oh, sorry. I think so. I can't remember
It all runs together. Yeah, okay
I I got a little boost to my chris chan videos because she was in the news
Well, you know on twitter a bit
Uh, because she's fucking been bailed out
No word on like what she's doing or I don't think there's been any further details about it
I mean, I I'm kind of curious like who bailed her out. Where is she?
Uh, I'd like to know
but
But uh, you know, we'll probably won't know until she gets back on twitter or something if if that even happens
I've soured on it
I was curious when I heard about sonichu for the first time. It's like wow, this comic sucks. What the fuck?
But I always felt like it really does. I always felt like it was kind of like
You know
um endearing in a way that somebody has this little idea and they just keep drawing a comic and I'm like
That reminds me of when I was like five. Yeah, I like that
But then it became so much more horrible
Over time, you know, I like the outsider art aspect of it. I like to think about like, you know
It's it's interesting to read this comic and be like this this comic is so weird and then to understand like
You know what the thought process was behind why the comic is this way. It's like, well, that's interesting
Uh, yeah, and that's why, you know, my videos about it are about the comic and like they reference the author and they talk about
What was going on with her at the time? But that's not
You know, you can't avoid talking about that, but that's not like the focus
Now the focus is clearly
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're talking about your thing. Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, but you're saying yeah the focus of like on
on her personally, I mean, I'm just curious because
Like where she is now because like, you know, the the bad
thing is that like did a troll bail her out is some troll like
Holding her hostage or something. Uh, it's possible
I think it might be more likely that some relative might have might have bailed her out
I don't know. I I'm genuinely just I'm shocked that she was bailed out on on the charges
I'm shocked that like that that was apparently not supposed to be an option
But somehow it became one and it's very strange and uh, you know, it doesn't seem
Like that should be
the case
Seems dangerous. It seems like a dangerous situation
I don't know. I feel like I don't care
All right. All right. I get you. It's it's just like the only reason we're hearing about any of this
is because of the
status of chris chen as a
Public figure that everyone's paying attention to
Yeah
Otherwise it would have been it would have been this, you know, we like the comic and if if chris chen wasn't well known
This may have happened anyway, and it would have been like a small article
and we've never heard about anything and
This all could have happened the exact same way
And we just would not be none the wiser
And I think that's that's just, you know
Doesn't need to be looked at honestly
Uh, I guess I guess you got a point
um
Well, I mean, I'm not like
I'm not like looking into it, but I assume that someone will tell me
Like people just messaged me to be like did you hear did you hear chris chen?
Was bailed out and I was like no wow
Wow damn
Uh-oh
So I'm sure I'm sure bailed back in did you hear she was bail japed?
Now you're interested. Uh, I'm not interested in a heartache. Yeah
Uh to beat bail japed is to be put in a prison surrounded by lava
That's probably what should have been done
Uh, but I just uh, yeah people said gino samuel ai'd me and I was like, okay. All right fine
Just have just have your way with me then
If you do it do what you must
Uh
It's fine
Uh, it seems it seems like there was no like uh, the the particular
The mockery or humiliation perpetrated so can't really complain
Uh, and that's all I had to say
About my week really that's the end of my
List of things
All right, I think I had something else to say but I forgot it
Uh-oh
I was talking about anime. Oh my oh my yeah, it's a gun smoke
Uh, I got oh, I got mine mine arrived
During the stream. I think it was during the draw stream and you were there in the chat and I said
I found it in a box on my
counter in the front hall
I have it right here. I can see it right now. It's on my table. Have you read it? Have you read the new chapter?
Read the new chapter. Yeah, it's got the first four chapters in
That's the that's the idea is that you can see I thought
The fourth chapter if you pay early
That that was my my relationship. I didn't I didn't realize there was new content in in the book
I wonder how many people didn't realize I didn't realize that. Okay. Well, I'll have to read it now. Okay. Um, yeah, it's it's
The way I'm gonna do things going forward is gonna be like I'll make the chapter
Post it on, you know, amazon
pdf kofi so people can pay for the privilege to see it first
And also that's just nice. Thank you. Um, and then
Uh, it'll come out on the perfect comic party and then it'll come out on my website
So it'll be like staggered release
Okay
That's the way I want to do things. Oh also my patreon. I guess I don't know how that's gonna work. I want to give them something for it
But I don't know if I want to just give them the chapter maybe like
To get it before my website
or something
Anyway, uh, I got some new orders today just I refreshed I got two more
Based total orders 33 33 books. I got four books today
You know, I hope I hope they continue to to trickle in
Oh, we got a new one from canada. So canadian's gotten a getting gonna get a print clorissa gunsmoke
Uh-oh
uh-oh
We got united station at a kingdom australia germany japan and canada those are that's uh six countries
That my book is in it's so cool and so easy
I know
Did I did I complain on here that amazon doesn't let me print in landscape format?
I don't know if you mentioned it. Uh, I remember you're saying that somewhere
I I might have said it in the stream or I might have just messaged you about it because like yeah, uh, I looked into the amazon printing and
Printing my book would cost it would be about 19
19 to 20 dollars
Just like to print and ship it which is like
Say it does that saves me money
If I if I if I only printed a certain amount if I printed enough it would eventually become cheaper than that for me
To ship to america, but not to ship abroad
It would never it would never become cheaper than that to ship abroad
But so there's like a potential monetary benefit there to using the amazon and of course the the fact that it's just easier
but
They don't give me that much freedom in terms of choosing like book size
That so that I can't print in the size and landscape configuration that I wanted and there's a couple other little
Niggling issues too like the fact that they don't let me uh, they don't let me put
Uh, they don't let me print on the inside cover
Which is I mean, it's not that big a deal, but like, you know, the other company will let me
Oh, yeah
The back cover of the things. Yeah. Yeah the the interior side of the of the cover is just you know in in mine
That's where I put like, you know copyright information and like a little bit of credits stuff and
You know just looks nice
it looks nice because like in because uh
Simon punishment like the pages are black like everything is black and it's it's like colored print on black
Background so, you know, it just looks nice to have the inside cover black as well. I can't do that on amazon
I see yes
I guess that's just because i'm very like
particular with how uh, I set this
book up
No, yeah, the amazon is is like it's quality
To a point. I don't think you can really do like bespoke luxury goods in terms of print on demand
Yeah, you can make
Books honestly printed somewhere else and then sell them through amazon
I think if I didn't if if I if my book were a little more normal looking
I I think I probably might do it like like for the vapors or something
Like if I ever made like maybe a vapors volume
You know, uh
Put them all together. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Because that I wouldn't care about like printing on the inside cover or landscape orientation or whatever
Oh, I think I may have already mentioned this but I can't wait
I can't wait to be able to make a volume in the same shape as all the manga volumes
If I have enough pages of like Clarissa
Probably Clarissa at the end like I'll just have a little tiny baby version
If you want a tiny baby manga version of Clarissa gunsmoat, I want to make that
Because I just want to have that I just want to have like it with like the the low quality paper as well
Isn't it just the same but smaller
It would be the same but smaller. No, well, it would be not just volume one
I would do like all the volumes like the whole Clarissa every all the chapters together
So you would so you if you made like an omnibus, you would just make it small
Well, I would probably make like a large one or the one that's the same size as like the other ones
But then I just really I just really want a small like the idea of a manga size. That's funny
Yeah, I get why not. Yeah, maybe some people would prefer it in manga size
Yeah, and the the fun thing about that is that I can just put it on Amazon for no
Like I don't have to pay a commission for it to be listed. I just put it up there
So even if nobody buys that one, I can buy it and I can have it and it's like it's for me
Okay, I get you I get you dog. Uh, yeah, why not?
Why not have it in multiple sizes?
um
It'll also be very cheap because like the the manga
volumes they use that slightly
Lower grade like cream paper instead of white paper. So it'd be like a little rougher
And it'll be like a little I don't know nostalgic. I guess I've got like manga volumes from years and years and years ago
of like Dragon Ball and I'm like, ah
The the ink's fading. This is so cool
Uh like an ancient tome
The pages they're they're all dog-eared and fallen out like oh, but that's just the authentic manga experience
They're they're all going like crusty brown-ish
Sun baked a little bit
More like sun-based hot hot. Yeah
Yeah, that's right. So yeah, I'm gonna I have been sort of using my kindle
um management thing
Link in the description to buy gibbs book Clarissa gunsmoke volume one get a copy get a copy and if you don't
If you don't want a if you can't afford or you don't want a physical version you can go to the co-fi
Right. I also have if you go to gibb and take that site you can there's like links for for both versions
I don't know where I'm gonna put it. I have I have like a drawer that I keep a bunch of like
Comics that I've purchased from people's kick starters and stuff. So I'll probably put it with those
Along with my problem sleuth volumes, etc. Yes when I make a bell jpeh book
I'm also going to make it similar science to problem sleuth
And even if nobody buys that it's like I mean it's a lot of work to make it into a book
So I hope people buy it when I do that, but it's
uh having
I finished I finished organizing the book version of slime and punishment and like I I still don't feel like I'm done
I'm still thinking like maybe I should shrink it a little more like maybe I should uh
Maybe maybe I should add a couple more like pieces of like fan art in the index that I forgot to include
Uh, maybe I could shrink the text more and and squeeze it into fewer pages
uh
It's literally harder than drawing the panels is just putting the panels on the page is the actual hard part
And as my biscuit page is hard even though I draw it like a fucking baby scribbling
It's because the scribbling is the easy part
Yeah, I I I reference the homestuck volume and the problem sleuth volumes
I have a lot to figure out when I when I was doing the pages I have like a
Like a photoshop document of like bell jpeh in book form
But I'll need to check with amazon what the sizes are so I can I'll have to move everything around probably
Yeah
Oh, it's exciting though. I love books. I love physical media
Uh, I feel you know, I had to I had to put I had to put my printing aside for a moment
For the slime and punishment to get the perfect comic party set up, but that's okay
Uh, biscuit page is all important too. And now that I'm back in the swing of it. I'm glad that I did
uh, but
I'm excited for my book as well. Uh, that'll be pretty cool
Maybe they'll sell a million copies. Maybe I'll make a hundred thousand dollars on Kickstarter
Oh, thank god, and then maybe I'll finally like the face that I see in the mirror
Nah, you'll be able to plate it gold. Hmm
gold face
Hey guys notice anything different about me. Hey, homa. You're the biggest man in the world now and you played it in gold
Remember that
Yes, that iconic simpson scene great. Yes. He said he first says like, uh, I don't know homo. You got a new haircut
Look closer, Lenny. Oh, yeah
The biggest man you're the biggest man in the world
Because you got lots of money and now you're huge
Uh
I have food now there was food given to me. That's great. So I will make noises with my mouth. I will mute myself a bit
Uh, I don't really have anything else to talk about for this. Yeah. Um, I think maybe we could go to voicemails
Okay, uh, but let me go to the bathroom real quick. All right. I'm gonna take a hiatus
So
All right, uh, I'm back
You there. Mm-hmm. I am still here. You're still here. All right. Well, hey, we're
damn
Depending on how long these voicemails take we're on track for an under three hour episode if you can even believe such a thing
You know what that'd be great. That's horrifying. I can't I I I don't I don't even know our audience will riot
Our audience and we will feast we will feast on all the free time that we've saved for ourselves
Yes, I need that. I need so much free time. I'm I know no more seven hour episodes, please
Translate it it literally translates directly into like more biscapades done. Yeah, more biscapades. That's what I'm gonna do. Yeah
Uh, all right more healthy hearty happy hosts
And you want that don't you?
No, they want us to suffer. That's that's why they watch
All right first voicemail
Oh
Gotta open up speak pipe
Okay
Well, the the first one is just a twitter meme
Say the line luffy
What does what does that mean? I'm gonna be the pirate king probably kaizuku is the pirate
king
Yeah
Oh, or it doesn't mean pirates kaizuku is pirate
I feel like the funny the funniest part of this meme is the fact that luffy's iconic like bursting out of the barrel
Like is posed in the same way as all the kids in the classroom. That's the only that's the only thing that saves this meme
The fact that the he's they're asking him to say the line and he's just happy to do so and he's happy and everyone's happy
I love to say the line
Uh
Next one is oh
Sorry, no good voicemails this week either. Who is this?
Is it a postman could this be could this be the voicemailer?
Is this a self portrait maybe
What had it what hat is that?
Where who wears a hat like that?
Um, now we'll see now. We'll get some good ones. No, no, no, we're we're we're gonna make it
Uh, next one is
Write a tweet in the style of act drill about ben saint
I asked ben saint what his favorite color was and he said the void
This man is a walking black hole and I mean that in the best way possible. Hashtag bless hashtag ben saint
That's good void void void void. Yes. I'm into it. This man is a walking black hole
I don't I have no idea what that means
It's pretty drill like
Um, uh kind of yeah a little bit. Um, it's a little out uncharacteristic of drill to be so positive about someone
Yes, it's also like a little bit too coherent
It's a little bit too like spelled correctly and like sounds normal
Um, but um hashtag blessed hashtag ben saint. Yeah, true other with that true
Uh, okay next one is called mad from cars suck at gmail.com
three two one go
Hey, so y'all were always or are always like oh post food post leave can't wait to change my body to
robotics stuff
Iro guys post car too
Because a lot of younglings of my age like have no interest in owning a car and stuff
Like I hate traveling too. I
I'm never traveling again. Fuck you mom. I'm never going
I have no interest in cars
Yeah, I hate cars
I'm I'm happy to that's literally why I live in boston is so I don't need a car
I feel like I can just take the bus everywhere. Yeah, that's why I like living in london as well
It's like yeah, there's buses everywhere. There's trains like so far into london beyond it's like
such a hub such a hub of
Going to places like literally almost I mean not every day, but like most days I hear
Not not the roommate that knows my videos
But two of my other roommates I hear one of them come upstairs and knock on the other one's door and be like
Hey, man, can you move your car so I can pull out
And it's like I would kill myself. I couldn't I couldn't deal with that every imagine
It's like one of them has to move their car for the other guy or the other guy has to move it for the one guy
They're just they're big and cumbersome. They're expensive. So if something happens to them, it's really bad
You have to pay insurance just to own them
You have to pay more money just to operate them in gas
You have to get them in for repairs every now and then I can't even be bothered to get my human body in for repairs
As often as it needs
I don't need a freaking mechanical thing dragging me down even more. I I would I I hate I literally hate cars
I hate them. I'm so grateful that I don't have to be fucking yoked with one
I feel sorry for anyone that does
And if I want to like feel the experience of driving
Um, I could just play a video game that does that and I can drive off a cliff. You can't do that in real life
Uh, if I that's what I would do if I were a dirty filthy car owner
I would drive up a mountain
And like in gta and I would and I would jump out of the like I would drive off cliff jump out of the door
And I would get my parachute when my bazooka
when I was at
astro camp
Uh, the drive up the mountain to astro camp. I mean some parts of it had guardrails on it
some did not and like
Some parts you were kind of close like the road went kind of close to an edge that like
You would die you would go over the edge and you would fall a long way and die
And it was really scary
uh
That's not really the car is fault, but i'm gonna blame the car for that anyway
I do like the the um the experience of being driven sometimes like on like a cool
I don't like country trail that you couldn't reasonably walk to
And there's no trains like when when infrastructure falls away
It is nice to have a little bit of a car moment, but like
Not for the not like you don't need them in the city
We don't need motorways as much as we think we do
I don't I don't really like the car moment. I don't really like the experience of being in a car with people
Honestly, I guess right driving by myself is like it's okay. I've done it before and
It's not that bad other than the fact that driving is dangerous
And I feel like I am extending my potential life expectancy by avoiding it as much as possible
The experience of driving by myself. Okay the experience of being in a car with people. I don't like it. It's awkward
I I would agree. I think it's it's just the sort of like um
The the independence you have with a car to go to various locations is cool
Yeah, it's just the fact that
it's so
Like people who own cars don't all go on cool road trips off-road to amazing places
They usually just have a car and then they use it to go to like go and yeah to go into normal places
It's a waste if you get a car you should have an adventure
You should not replace your
Like use it as a replacement for a bus because buses is easy. You just get on
And I mean I get my groceries delivered and that costs me more than buying groceries regular
I guess theoretically I could save money on groceries if I drove to the store and bought them myself
But then I'd have to pay for car insurance and gas to do it. It would probably like not even make up the difference
Uh
I think if you're in a car you should go on like the cool you could go on on a magical adventure
I think that's the only reason you should have a car
You should go on a fucking jeep drive through the Sahara desert or not
Sahara desert as savannah african savannah and see the lions
I feel like there are other kinds of magical adventure
That I could do carless and I think I would probably pick one of those
Oh, yeah, I mean there's lots of adventures you could do but if you if you had a car
That's that's the that's the morally correct way to justify it for you
If they used it for that if they if they said they were gonna do that and they just never did then it's like
Oh, yeah, well, you're wasting a lot of money betrayal betrayal
Uh, okay, I guess we're I guess we're pretty much on the same page. Yep. Fuck cars
Wars walk wars
Fuck fuck fuck and fuck you
Uh listener, uh the next one is uh from prince isolation. It's an image
Sorry pinkie, but I just don't get what's so darn funny about a farm supply store
What does it matter what the previous owner was called? Uh
Uh, oh is that the
The chuck suck and fuck. Yeah. Yeah, you mean sneeze feed and seed. Uh, whoops whoopsie
I saw I saw a chat gpt to failing to explain why sneeze feed and seed joke is funny
Uh, that was kind of that was pretty good. Uh, okay next one is from prince isolation
Okay, so this is this is me
I was asking people in my discord like
I I asked you the same thing about like shipping to the uk because I thought it might save money to have the books
Shipped to a country or to the eu or to south america and then have a guy
Or somebody in that region who would then
Send the individual ones for me and I maybe I could just pay someone to do that. So I was asking around in my discord
And then uh, okay
So, uh, here here I am you're in chile, right? I got a question for you
How much would it cost you to mail a one kilogram package from where you are to someone in another country in south america?
I asked alias. I said it would cost him like 50 plus from argentina, which is insane
I guess anyone in south america could theoretically answer this question
we've got the
I'm making drugs. I'm making drugs
Yeah, you know, uh, was it gustavo fring is from chile, I think
Uh, is that right? I don't remember
well
Here I am making drugs with slime gusts and slime jesse and slime waltz and they're they're jealous
And this is what my room actually looks like pouring like liquids into beakers
That are glowing. Oh, um, yeah, uh, one of those beakers that had the um
The alcohol solution of the glowing, uh, quinine that I had extracted from the
That I had extracted from the diet tonic
Uh, one of the the alcohol eventually evaporated off and it started growing mold
So that I need to get rid of that. Uh, I just noticed that yesterday. It's like dammit
Dammit, but I got to examine it under the black light. I wonder if the mold would grow would glow
Probably not there'd probably like a layer of the of the glowing stuff underneath it and the mold is just like on top of it
is this slime to be
What was the slime for just it was that to put on your teeth or like the stuff you were gonna put in the bottles
The original idea was that I was going to cook it down into something that I could paint my teeth with to make them glow
Uh, that is like not
There's such simpler ways of doing that so I'm not gonna do that anymore now
I was just like cook it down to just see what happens and
turns out what happens is
Uh mold starts to grow on it when you let it grow until the alcohol evaporates. Yep
Now I know, uh
Next
Next one is uh another image. It's an album
Uh, I love images. Oh wait, wait, wait, wait. That one had an audio with it. I forgot. Oh, okay. Three two one go
Yeah, this is the most shy drawing I've ever done, but I just needed to get the thought out there
Okay, it's fine. I am not sorry
It's a good drawing prince. Uh next one is um an album
Let's see
Uh
No, Ben sainte supports non consensuals
You do
It's not for me to have sex with someone it's two other people
You do this is exactly
It's exactly what happens. It's exactly how I would act in that situation. Yeah, I would think
Let's let's let's let's intervene and fix this problem. We got a problem here and I got the solution
Something funny just about the because these two people they're lying down on the bed
And but you're standing straight up like next to the bed. I just walked past them
You do actually actually, uh, I think uh
Uh
Thank you for that. Uh next one is called pretty good at I love card games at gmail.com
three two one go
You two are probably already occupied with trash. I mean games like fire and the mega man
But if anyone wants to ruin their own life
Check out monster train
No, so train
No
I've already got a bunch of bad games that I don't like
Even aside the ones that i'm contractually obligated to play monster train. Uh, it's got like it's got like the the the color
red and blue
Is that a problem?
Well, it's it just sort of is the the main thing that every
video game looks like on the cover
Of this one's this one's a better image
My first impression is oh, it's home. It's hearthstone and it's also generic in other ways
It does look generic. It does look like hearthstone. I mean the yeah, I know a lot of people use the orange and blue like whatever
I'll never use orange and blue ever. This is a terrible voicemail. This is a terrible voicemail
Just like hey, have you heard of this game?
One no and you didn't even tell me what I why I should care about it
Why even why?
Oh
We're in your life
This is an awful voicemail. It's a waste of my time. Um, next one is uh called
Well, it's uh god. It means a youtube link. Um, I said
Hey, you missed one. There's another image. Wait, did I? Oh, yeah
Uh
This is me. Let's look at it. I guess
Huh, it's give and take circuit to 2015
Oh
No, not the pretty dress. I guess in my coco pomel
Uh, give and take review
Uh, where I had a little of something guesting. I think
They did the art
And there was a joke about a pretty dress and I said no
Oh
Well now yes, yeah, I get it
This is just like the end of the witch when the devil asks would you like a pretty dress?
Would sell like a pretty dress
Would sell like the taste of butter would sell like to see the world. I think that's what he has. Yes to all three
Yes, please
I love butter
I do
I wonder how many other things like that there are of me saying no, I would never be a female
Uh, I don't remember that video in particular
But I would never want to wear lipstick
True
Okay, next one is uh
It's a youtube link. It's a it's a it's a geo center. It's a seven
Okay, it's a it's a it's a flat earth conspiracy thing. Who cares? Okay
Uh, next next one next one is goku sucks three two one go
All right, you guys are artists, right? No
The real question is
How many of our original characters can beat goku? I have
at least
Five so so
None
None of my original characters can be goku
Yeah, I guess I can't mine can't either so but but Clarissa has a gun she can shoot him
She could just shoot him
You ever think about that? It's true. Mm-hmm. It's like launch
Yeah
Did you I was looking at launch talking about baby goku?
Yeah, baby goku. I mean if you got the if he got the right beast the beast hustler could maybe give baby goku a run for his money
Yes
But like launch in in dragon ball the lady who sneezes and changes her personality in her hair color
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I love I love launch
She I realized uh, not too like just the other day when I was looking for some reason at at her
I was like wait, that's the reason I like girls with guns. That's the reason I like like the idea of gun girl
She's blonde and she's got a gun and she hates you. That's funny. I like blue hair launch
I don't like blonde launch
I I like both of them
They're so pretty. I like I like the I like the blue one. I like the one that's nice
Actually, I have just like marge simpson just like just like marge simpson. Yes
What if marge simpson sneezes and turns into
Lisa uh lisa lisa's blonde. I just I just I just now have realized that
Why are they blonde are the simpson's are the simpson's kids blonde? Is that what they're
I mean, they they do not have a different color from their skin color
Hair, they do not have brown hair. Homer had brown hair
They do not have a marge had blue hair so marge was it
Yeah, when she was a teenager it was blue
But did she always dye it? I forgot if that was ever like established that she has a canon real hair color
Uh, she dyes it blue now, but when we see her as a kid, it's still blue. So I mean
I don't think she was dying it ever since she was a kid
Oh, yeah, and our dad had blue hair. Yeah, so that that's just a thing not not not in every time we see him
I think there's at least one time we see him when he had although that might have been when he was old his hair might
I feel like the one where we see him and he's an a flight attendant. He had brown hair
But I think there's another one where we see him with patty and selma and he had like you had like light blue hair
I feel like it's inconsistent with with mr. Bouvier
I am pretty sure the flight
Oh clancy Bouvier. He's got orange hair
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, that's true. Yeah, and I'm seeing the different images now
knew it
Because I watched I watched that uh, that uh, who's that one simpsons tuber?
Real gyms. I'll watch the real gyms video about the mr. Bouvier
So I know this look at the back of my hand
Um, yeah, but gun girl is his lunch
She shoots you she doesn't change her personality. I guess she does. I guess she does shoot me
Yeah, she shoots you with angry eyes. It's like the perfect woman
True
I love a girl who'll
shoot me
Uh, next one is called. Um
Wait a second. I didn't download that one. Next one is called a lost vagrant husk
3 2 1 go
When I saw the ova
I thought that what I desired was
Nate
But I realized something
Nate has not been here for years
What I saw it was
nearly a
simulacrum
The memory of him
Is dust in the wind
being grown away
Where they ever crushing
obsession of
time
I
Had an epiphany
I no longer crave
for
succulents
Ben
I have lost
my purpose
What am I to do now?
That I no longer desire to
fuck
a member
of
the
PCB
Well, you better figure it out before find purpose november rolls around. Oh my god. Yeah, remember that
Wait to find my purpose. Yeah
It's a few months away. So you got time, but uh
Don't dilly dally because if you end no no find purpose november with no purpose
The freaking uh, the the collectors come around like in homestuck and they say spit your purpose into this bucket
And if you don't they kill you
Uh true true
So, you know, I I thought he was gonna say he wanted to fuck you
Yeah, but now now he now he just has no one to want to fuck. No, it was it was it was Nate or nothing
As the saying truly a tragic tale
Uh, next one is called hey gibb comma three two one go
Hey gibb, how do you feel when people sexualize you on the internet?
I would ask ben but he already violates enough social contracts that I have no respect for him. Mm-hmm
I
Honestly don't like it all that much
Hmm. I think
It's it's fine up to a point
But like weird comments. I've actually got a few weird comments. I just like
so like
You're a little presuming that I would be like just fine with you saying that
Are you talking about on twitter or in youtube comments on twitter? I don't think I've seen that many youtube comments
maybe a couple um
And I guess I guess the the guy who does the voicemails where it's like whenever
It's like oh, I saw gibb on twitter and he does like a oh come thing. That's his voicemail gimmick
Uh, not a big fan of that but like
It's obviously a goof. It's just sort of like ick
A little bit achy. Yeah
Yeah
I feel you dog
um
Okay, and that's the answer next one is how to penetrate a social group
Uh, wait, let me download that last one. Okay download how to penetrate a social group three two one go
Okay, so let's say
you um are
know somewhere
And you don't know anyone there and everyone there knows each other like
How are you supposed to um
Interact in such a scenario like
Um, are you supposed to like I don't really
I mean, so it's a tough
Question you just got it. You just got a pipe. You just got to find something to say
You just got to think of something. I mean a lot of the time
I have a lot of trouble with this when like everyone knows each other and I'm like, okay
I know what I should do is like engage with a conversation. They're already having
um
But then they end up talking about nothing that I care about and I'm like, you know what I don't care
Like it's I should I should try a little harder. I guess if if they're already having a conversation
I wouldn't necessarily say like butt into it
Well, no, but like sometimes they're always they're always having a conversation with each other and you're never like considered
so
Yeah, you have to try and worm your way in somehow by either
being something like a subject of the conversation or by just
Having a quip having a point on what they were saying. Oh, I heard you were talking about this
Did you know or like just I don't know. It's difficult
It sucks
you you kind of yeah, you kind of just got to try and uh
You kind of just got to look for an opening and just say something
And uh, you know, I guess if you're there for like first impressions
Yeah, first impressions are like people say first impressions are very important
and the reason I
I don't think people like say this part because I didn't get it for a while
The reason the first impressions are important is that's the only time that it seems normal
to talk about yourself
And what you do and who you are and what you like because if you know them from like having seen them already
And you just sort of say hello every so often
It is weird to suddenly come up to them
Unprompted and start talking about what you like and asking them questions. I mean, it's not impossible
But it's sort of the weird, you know, it's weirder to say it after you've met them
Then well while you're meeting them, you know, I guess so. Yeah
um
Because once they know things about you they can think about you
When topics of conversation come up and think to include you or like to talk to you about something because they already know stuff
I would say that if you're talking about be you're in like a I don't know maybe like you
just
Joined a new school or something or you're in a new job or something
uh, I would say
First thing is is don't be weird
and don't
Like you do want to like eventually break into the conversation and think of something and say something
But you don't want to be weird about it
So like I would say just be chill and like if there's if if they're not talking about anything you have anything to say about
And there's nothing and you don't see any natural
Way of like opening a conversation
Don't force it
And because you'll be weird about it if you just like be okay with like not saying anything
Because it's normal to not have anything to say to people you don't know just be fine with that
But if you see an opportunity or you see something you have an observation to make about or they're talking about something you have an interest in
It's okay to pipe up and be like, hey, I have a thing to say about that
Yeah, don't yeah
It's it's always weird when the person is hovering because nobody draws attention to it
But everyone can know
Everyone notices when somebody's hovering around a conversation and not involving themselves
If you're just chill and doing your own thing like I was imagining it like a work environment if you're at a new job
You're all there to do work. So it's not weird that you're in airshot of whatever they're doing
Yeah, but like if it's more of a social setting
It is odd to just go up to the group and
Hang around
Yeah, you definitely do not want to be some freaking uh silent orbiter
That's not good
Uh next one if you're gonna orbit you should do it in outer wilds
Hey, honey, uh, did you bathe you smell great? Did you bathe? No, I used the Orion scent
Well, may I orbit your belt?
Sonichu
next one
It's a fake a fake ad that chris put into one of the issues of sonichu for uh, for uh, axe body spray
Great. Yeah. Yeah. You yeah, you're welcome. Uh, next one is, uh
VVV work doodles, baby
Oh my god
This is grotesque. Oh, this is the version of that. Jesus the image where you're big and I'm small at the table
But it's wait what
Remember that image from a while a little while ago where you're pointing at my plate someone else do it. Oh
Yeah, vaguely
sort of
Just eat your dino nugs give and take
Oh
Full of turkey two thousands. Oh internal view
Eat and clean plate twinkle twinkle my turkey two
Give will not be forsaken. Jeez. Oh, you're like standing in my guts. Ah
I you know, I like turkey 2000. I would kill ben. I would kill anyone to get a turkey 2000
They're just the turkey nugget that makes me feel terrible because I would definitely kill you to get my turkey 2000
That's just awkward
Uh, I'm like bloodshot eyes. Oh god. This is horrible. Why would you do this?
Ah, I don't like it. Thanks for that, Vinny
I hate it. Thank you. I hate it. Thanks a lot. Yeah
uh
Next one is uh, wait, there's a two second voicemail. Okay, it doesn't there's no sound
Next one is dan olson is my adopted father
From streets of rage at avarice.org three two one go
Oh, you know, I'd just like to take a moment to appreciate the length of the podcast because I think the podcast should be generally
only
Only three hours this week long idiot. They are the more the words they are and
I can listen to them and I just
So true
Podcasts because my life is boring and I listen to
The podcast and it's like I'm
I'm
Thank you, Ben and give before making my boring life
more boring
It's what we slog. That's what we what we strive to do
Uh, the idea that the person who's having a boring life just wants it to be more uninteresting
Yeah, I love having a boring life more of the pcp to that end. I've made my life boring on purpose
I want more of it. Uh, thank you length appreciator. Uh, voice grail voice grail for the length appreciator. No
No, no, not quite not quite not quite very funny voice though
I could tell you having a lot of fun with that. That was a good one
Too much fun. It should be more boring make your next voicemail more boring
Uh and longer this was this wasn't even the full minute 30. Come on. Come on
Uh, next one is an image
So many image
Oh, no, ben sains life in weeks
Here's when ben sainte disrespected my vtuber wife
So you will remain dead for those years following I will remain dead for those 90 years. Yeah, it seems likely
It seems likely that implies you come back that implies there's a resurrection spell
Well, I hope so
Well, I sure hope so
If you got resurrected after you were dead long after you were dead and you were a skeleton
Um, uh, how would you what would you what? Uh, what's gonna happen? Huh? What are you gonna do about it?
Uh, do I still have all the capabilities that I had from when I was alive?
as a you you have the sensation of sight
despite not having eyeballs
Um, and I think that uh, I guess
Hearing but I guess that's it
So you can move around and you can hear and see can I speak?
Nope, you're a skeleton. Well, I would probably um, I don't know. I would probably
Probably draw and write stuff then I'll just start drawing. I don't know
I can still do that
true
Yeah, be fun to be a skeleton so not so you don't have to worry about not much would change anything
Yeah, you could you could go for a walk uh and stand at the bottom of the ocean and you'll be like, yeah, whatever
The more you know what I'm liking it. I wouldn't have to worry about my my mortal flesh
I just chill in my room just chill in my room and draw
Dude, you could play video games. You could vape as a skeleton. You wouldn't have no lungs problems. No lungs
Uh, you you could get a little a little bellows that you can operate with your hands
To act as a lung
I mean, you could you don't even need to put it inside you
You could just put the vape into the bellows and just and they just blow it at people just run around with it
In your hands the phantom is real the phantom
Uh, there's like one of one of when a fog rolls in it's a huge vape cloud that you're blowing everywhere
And then you come through the the cloud
Little skeleton an appropriate entry for a skeleton. You know the more you know, it doesn't sound that bad
Yeah, I'll take it. Yes, please
Uh next one. Oh, uh, so that one next one is
Aiden dot jp
What is aiden dot jp? I have no idea
Wonder of wonder art
Click to start please enjoy this content with sound on
Wow, okay. Oh, it's too loud
Uh, okay. Well, I should turn my volume down then
Oh, wow
Okay, the top the little
question mark stops it
Oh
Each he changes it. Hang on. This is very loud
I'm wondering if I watch long enough if he'll change his uh his animation
Oh, oh, he's he's flailing. Oh, I'm flailing
Yeah, you it looks like you have two dance moves
Uh, hang on a side to side and then a flail in with your arms
It's I don't know how to turn it down the little the little okay. I gotta stop it the little slime oids
There's a there's a little divu. There's a little divu slime
on the slime oids
Oh, there is a little podrans and a little vape cloud
Uh, I've never seen this before. This is a cute little. Yeah, that's a cute little thing cute little app
I think there's another one. I think it's you
Oh, that's the next one. Yeah
These are these are pretty cute. Will it be the same song? Let's find out
It is
Oh, it's you're holding a turkey 2000
You got a gun in one hand the turkey 2000 and the other
Wow, watch where you're pointing that thing
All right, pretty cute pretty adorable. Oh, sorry. I couldn't hear you because it was too loud. Uh, what were you saying?
Oh, I just said I I just said pretty cute pretty adorable. Yeah
Yeah, I like I like the
It's the pump and the lord ghosts a little I think the hypocrite hat and I said watch where you're
Pointing that gun. Yeah
I've got Clarissa's gun. I'm gonna kill you around. Yeah
What's the other thing in my other hand? It's a it's a turkey 2000
You got your fingers through a turkey. It's gonna burn. It's gonna hot hot hot oils
It's called you that's what you did back in the day at that's not what I don't think you we didn't do that
You wear them like brass knuckles to pummel your foes
Oh, that's why they they recalled them because kids we get into violent
Punching each other with their brass their turkey knuckles
Yeah, I think that's probably true
Uh next one
Okay
Okay, all right. All right
Uh
The virgin ben sain versus the chad endless endless one
receding hairline
Rents with flat mates. He hates covid brain fog says lol out loud. Uh, dumb
Can barely speak
Explo these are mean. Oh, these are these are like mean. I wonder if this is someone that genuinely hates me
Uh exploited. No, but correct collaborated with chris chan
Duh workers are entitled to the fruits of their labor except for jesse lull has said the n word more than jesse. Oh good
Uh grifts a dead podcast to fund his artistic ventures that no one cares about terminally online
least industry bcp member
Still wearing nate's shoes
How's that a that was that a downside those are good. Those are cool shoes
Uh
Lives with hot girl. Uh, uh debatable
Full and flowing main. All right. No brain fog. Yeah. Yeah, you got me there. Ken rap. Yeah
Dozen stutter speaks with confidence. Sure
People listen to pcp for him because digi bro told them to
Uh freed from online bullshit except, uh, he's still, uh
Dependent on his patron. So no makes whatever stuff he wants to yeah
Like like 18 let's plays a month that he charges his patrons for
18 times a month. Uh, very good. Uh, this this is this is not this is just someone that sincerely doesn't like me
And I just think they're stupid. I just think they're stupid
Uh, so that's all I have to say about that
Uh, next one is
avocaru link
Here we go. This is the wait. Is there any more after this?
No, this is the last one
Let's freaking go
Japanese
This is a quiet part, what can I say? What can I say?
I was just I was just vibing
It was a vibe
Little embarrassing.
Yeah.
Japanese niggas.
What's the happen of these niggas?
Hey, come on.
Who among us?
Who among us has not been cringe in the past?
Right.
True.
I do not say it anymore.
I don't say it anymore.
We left it behind.
It was everyone else's fault.
Everyone else was just a bad influence on me.
Ben, you're like the oldest.
You're like the oldest one.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean I'm the smartest
or that I have the most
resilience to peer pressure.
Certainly not.
None of us have like the we were just too young to understand.
No, we don't.
Except for Munchie.
Except for Munchie, yeah.
And none of us stopped him.
Well, hey.
I'd live and learn.
Live and learn.
As I go.
Hanging on the edge of tomorrow.
No, the sonic one.
Yeah, live and learn.
Yesterday.
Yeah.
I forgot that part.
If you beg or if you borrow,
something find a way.
Right?
I'm pretty sure.
I don't know these things.
I'm a big sonic fan.
That's more sinful
than having said the N word a bunch of times.
I would agree.
Agree.
Did you see the sonic, the visual novel
that they just
released on April Fool's Day?
Yeah, the murder of Sonic.
I thought it was pretty funny.
Yeah, it was pretty funny.
I like when they do an April Fool's Day
and then they actually do it.
They didn't just do it.
Say it as a joke and then not make it.
No, they actually made a little game.
And that's cool.
I think I've had my April.
I hate April Fool's rant before,
so I don't need to say it again.
I don't really hate it so much
as I'm just
apathetic to the whole thing.
Just like, yeah, okay.
I don't think it's super amusing
to just see someone
and like, oh, hey, they posted a thing
that they would never say.
They're pretending they're going to do a thing
that they would never do.
Oh, it's misinformation.
Yes, I love the April Fool's.
Like, April Fool's,
even though some people just do
things that suck
and all that,
I do generally enjoy
the feeling that it's
a time where
everyone is on board with this one thing
and they're all doing something.
You know, it's a holiday
and everyone's taking part
and it just feels nice, I guess.
The only thing that sucks about April Fool's
is that for people
who don't upload a lot and then they suddenly upload,
it's just disappointing.
And then the next day,
all of the things in your feed are like,
oh, yeah, that was from yesterday.
That's a joke. Don't need to click on that.
It's probably not going to be funny.
That's a joke. That's a joke.
There's nothing to watch today.
Yeah, exactly.
When it's fake content,
when there's not real content,
people will say,
if they just said, oh, what if we made
this visual novel where you
solve the murder of Sonic the Hedgehog
as a joke, that would be lame.
It's cool that you can actually play it.
But I didn't play it because I don't care
that much, but I just thought it was nice.
And that's the last of the voicemails.
We're done.
Oh my goodness.
Plebenweeb.
Underneath three hours.
Plebenweeb, Blu-rays, they're free now.
The file, the ISO file,
you can burn it to a disc.
The Plebenweeb Blu-ray is free,
stcomics.com.slashstore.html.
Jesse and Trixie both have my permission
to make their own Blu-rays with the work
that I did for them. They will not
because they do not care.
Lamal.
I'm still looking at this version
in Saint vs. Chad Endless One and just seething
because it wasn't funny.
I thought it was going to be funny jokes, but no.
It's just some cringe, Lord.
Genuinely coping and seething and
malding about my
own, about my savage
own of their favorite idiot
that they probably
give money to on Patreon for some reason.
For 18 Let's Plays a Month.
Die, die, viewer.
Sorry, I was in a fugue state. What were we talking about?
We were ending the show. That's right.
We were talking about Clarissa Gunsmoke.
Go buy it on Amazon
and Ko-fi
and look forward to the perfect comic party
where it'll be new
and fresh and
it's the new thing.
So this
the volume one
is all the Clarissa that is
done at the moment, right?
Yes. Chapters one to four.
So the first three were already done
and the fourth one is
exclusive for now.
I...
Well shit, I'll have to actually read that
new one that I didn't realize was in here.
Lol.
Thanks for telling me.
Um...
Become a patron
patron.com.
We will give you a shout out
in the perfect comic party when that
comes out soon.
Also bonus content
so many bonus episodes
and the Radcon
OVA commentary
if you want to hear us opine
about what all that means
to us in the year 2023.
Anything else?
Uh...
Nope. I think that's it.
Alright, that's it. End of the show.
Thanks for listening. Under three hours
we're out. We did it.
A clean break. Okay, that's... Goodbye.
Goodbye.