Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
No unexpected guests arriving. Welcome to episode whatever of the Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint. I just got done recording my Patreon Q&A podcast, which I said last week on the PCP that I was going to record right after that episode got finished recording.
But instead I did it right before this episode because I had a busy week and I didn't feel like it. Patreon.com slash Ben Saint, if you want to hear that. It's a bunch of questions about my game and just some other general stuff. It's just whatever anyone wanted to fucking ask me.
Uh, it's true. Uh, it's true. Um, this week, I've been doing shit. I've been hanging out with Munchy and Kazzie, who moved and I would, well, generously I could describe what I did as helping them move, but not really.
Um, and then they had a housewarming party and uh, so everyone's always wondering, oh, where did Munchy, everyone's calm, getting bombarded with, with emails and voicemails. Ben, where's Munchy been? Where's Munchy? That's not true. That's not actually true. But once in a while, someone brings it up. I think everyone, anyway, whatever, we hung out. It was cool. Uh, that's, I don't know. I guess that's all I have to say about that. Oh my God.
What would, hmm, what would the PCP audience like to hear me opine about this week? I know after the last two episodes, maybe some of you might be clamoring for, uh, for updates on, on the Trixie situation. Did, did Ben take an L this week?
Did Ben, did Ben increase his W streak to two? Um, unfortunately, no. Unfortunately, I have nothing else to report on that. Uh, there's no, no developments there, which is good. Everyone makes fun of me. Everyone says, Ben, you're a fucking loser. You're a big asshole jerk, picking on poor, what's her face?
Picking on the poor little golden witch. You can't defend yourself. Oh, you so mean. So, you know, everyone, you're such a bully, Ben. So, you know, I gotta, I gotta, I just gotta do what people tell me to do.
I just have to just accept that that is the truth. And also there's no more developments, which is good. Uh, that's, that's not, it's not important. No, no. It's no big deal. It's no big deal. I wasn't mad. I was never mad. I've never been mad and I never will be.
So, yes, apologies. No, no more drama there. Oh my God, I'm only three minutes in. I'm only three minutes into the episode. I'm floundering. I'm floundering. I have, I have no material. I already used all my material for my patrons in it. And that wasn't even good. And now I've gone through all my best material and there's nothing, there's nothing left that's even passable.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm a hack. I'm a fraud. I'm a, I'm a, I'm a joker. I'm the joker. I'm joker fine. Baby. Um, she, I'm tempted to go right to voicemails. I'm tempted to go right to voicemails. Um, I can mind fucking do it. I'm sure I'll find some stuff. I'm one, I'm sure I will find some stuff that bears.
That will prompt me into speaking on something else too. I'm, I'm sure I feel like probably Gible show up at some point. I don't know. I don't know if that's true. Whatever. Let's just fucking go to voicemails. And if I, if I think of something else to talk about later, I will.
There are no rules. I made the rules. I can, I can make up new ones. So here we go. First voicemail this week is called Ben taint two, three, two. Wait, wait. No, I do have one more thing. I have one thing that I do want to bring up. This is relevant in that it's about YouTube shit.
And I feel like stuff I've been watching on YouTube is relevant PCP discussion. So I will bring it up. I found a YouTube channel. And I feel like I've, I feel like I've discovered a little bit of a rabbit hole here. And I feel like if I feel some people I mentioned this to seem to know who this was and knew a lot more about him than I did. And I felt kind of dumb, like, Oh, am I an idiot that I've never found this person before that I don't know who this is.
But I feel like there's a rabbit hole. Um, there's a YouTube channel called action button, which I found due to a, a five hour review popped up in my recommended for a, a.
Well, I don't, I don't think it is obscure, but I'd never heard of it before dating sim called toky meky memorial. And this was a YouTube channel called action button is a five hour review of this. And I was like fuck yeah, long videos of a guy talking about a video game. That is my I'm the I'm the target audience here.
Um, so I listened to all that. And I was like, well, this was, I had, I had some criticism of it. I thought that his voice, the guy, Tim Rogers, he does a very, he's, he's always putting on a voice. And sometimes it bugs me. Not all the time, but sometimes I don't like his voice. He's like mostly tongue in cheek about it, which is fine.
But in this video in particular, it felt like he was trying to be, he is jokey, but he was more serious. And in the serious times, his like kind of fake putting on a voice stick. I found it a little irritating. But anyway, I watched, I think I've watched like most of his, I think he's only got like four videos up and they're all really long videos where he talks about a video game.
Um, and I, his channel is not huge. He's only got like, he's got like 65k subs, which is like modest, modest, medium, large, large ish. And I look, but he's patron is huge. He's got like making like 50, 50, sorry, $15,000 a month. That's really big. And I, I'm like, so who is this guy? And I, I, I guess he's, I guess he's some kind of.
Journalist, he's a games journalist, but like in some of his, in at least one of his videos, he's explicitly said, I am not a journalist. I do not consider myself a journalist. So that's confusing. I guess most of the time he just describes himself as a game designer, because he's made like a couple of games, but they seem like they're games that no one's ever heard of.
And I, and I wonder if maybe that's more important to him. So that's what he talks about, but he's known more for journalism stuff, but he doesn't care as much about that. I don't know.
Um, but this, I mean, the fact that I'd never heard of this guy, and I found him and his channel is modest, and yet he's, he's apparently got like a huge base of support from something. I mean, I don't know where it comes from.
I think it's from, because he used to write for Kotaku. I think that's the deal. And it just made me reflect on, it made me reflect on indie stuff and what it means to be indie because like I'm, I'm indie.
I have no institutional support of any kind from anywhere. And I have, I have squeezed out a little niche on the internet where some people know me, some people follow my work and support me a bit. And it's pretty great.
But this guy, I mean, I'm sure he's had a longer career than I'm even aware of. I'm sure he's written for various things for a long time. But like the fact that he is known through a like, through a like an institutionally supported outlet like Kotaku, that makes, that dwarfs anything else.
Right. If you get, if you get institutional support from like something big, it makes everything else look like nothing. Am I making sense? I just made me like, damn, if you are, if you're some guy making YouTube videos, 75k subscribers, you're nobody.
Right. You might have a couple hundred dollars through Patreon a month, if you're lucky. But if you're, oh, you're that, you're that Kotaku guy. Oh, you've written for all these, these publications. You're $15,000. Right. If you're, if you're successful and popular at that.
If people know you positively through something like that, you're just, you're just in a whole different league. And I, I don't know how it makes me feel mad, despair, discouragement, horror, terror, existential dread.
Yeah. I guess I don't have anything else to say about it other than, boy, what a gulf. What a fucking gulf. I don't know. I guess I would recommend his channel. I'm saying all this, I'm sure this comes off as negative. But I say this with the, I don't know, check his videos out. They seem pretty good.
Also, I'm sure him doing videos seems like a new thing. It seems like he's been writing for a long, I haven't read any of his other, I don't know what he did before action button. Well, I guess, I guess action button is the name of his game studio, but also the name of his YouTube channel.
Oh, I don't know. Feels goofy. It feels goofy for me to be opining about this guy who has a much longer career than I even know about. And I know only like this very slim segment of the stuff he's put out there to be like, oh, wow, I found this guy on YouTube.
And anyone who probably knows anything about ethics and games journalism, like, um, I've been following his work for a million years, and I am a genius and you are a room. And I would agree with that.
I don't know. I've been, I've been listening to that. His videos are really long. So I've had a lot of that to listen to. I'm like, basically done. I think, I think today I, oh, no, no, I, today I finished the last of his five YouTube videos that I had seen.
And now I went over to an older series that he did for Kotaku called Let's Mosey, wherein he goes basically not line by line or anything, but he goes pretty granularly through the English translation of Final Fantasy seven and explains like, why is this line weird?
What did it say in the original Japanese? Why did it get translated this way? What was the original intention? What was the translator's intention? Etc. That's like, it's like 14 videos, and I think I'm like seven away through there.
It's neat. It's pretty neat. Um, I don't know. So maybe I'll find more shit that that guy's made and check it out in the future. I don't know, because I don't read. I just watch YouTube videos and try and do sprites as I draw sprites and whatever for my video game project.
Phantom's revenge in the works. Check it, check out the updates, check out the patrons only exclusive updates and progress reports at patreon.com slash Ben St. And in my patrons only exclusive discord.
Another channel on my disc public public channel. No private channel patrons only channel public server. Actually, I deleted all the I deleted all the the links to the server so that server has kind of been private, although I think I think I'm ready to maybe put public out the links to that server again.
Also, I want to I have been feeling.
Because we were getting trolled some some some fuck boys were trolling us spamming us. So I close all the links so that we forget about that.
I might make links public again and update the links and like my old, you know, lecture videos and on Twitch and wherever Twitter and I don't think I have any links up to that on Twitter, but whatever.
I have been feeling.
I've just been thinking lately that I love my discord server.
I really like my discord server. It's really active. And you know, it's mostly it's mostly familiar faces. It's mostly like the same.
Now there's a little community of maybe, I don't know, 20 plus people that talk in there regularly. And then maybe there's some more people that chime in occasionally a broader number.
And I just think it's really nice that I have this server that I made and I'm, I guess, the leader of or whatever whatever it even means to be the to be the server owner. I'm the server owner.
It's my little space. And there's people in there. And it's pretty active and they're always talking. There's always some kind of usually there's some conversation going on.
And I've been looking at it more lately. In the past, I have sometimes neglected or not looked at it for a while, but lately I'm looking at it pretty often.
I'm just like, it's, I appreciate, I appreciate that these people are in here in this online space that I created that they choose to spend their time here and interact with one another and me and I think that's nice and it makes me happy.
Cool.
Very embarrassing. All right, the whatever.
Fuck, let's let's start the voice let's let's listen to a voicemail. This one is called bent how far in how far into this.
Wow, I stretched that I stretched out to 15 minutes. Pretty good. If I do say so myself. Okay, let's first voicemail Ben taint two three, two, one, go.
Where is it? Where is it? The scroll only one person could have done this or scroll one person could have taken the scroll. Ben taint.
That's right. My nemesis. You must have stolen the scroll from the league of night scrolls. Let's get some scrolls that you take a scroll with all the secrets of how to fuck.
This scroll is 300,000 yen.
We didn't realize you were into that. Let's get it.
Then you have two ways out of this. Either return the Nate fucking scroll.
Unacceptable.
Or join the league of Nate fuckers.
Okay.
I don't have to pay dues, right?
I'll sign me up. I'll sign me up. I'll sign whatever. Just put a name in front of me. I'll sign it. I'll join.
Okay. Easy. Easy.
Next voicemail.
SM part one, three, two, one, go.
And now Yig Studios Riley performing discord.
Is this real?
One behind you.
Oh.
Oh, that's that was rough. Is that real?
It did sound like him.
I don't know where that's from, but I hope that's real. Very funny.
Sounds like a little fucking baby.
I don't know. Maybe it's maybe it's not actually him.
I can't tell.
You can never, you can never be sure.
Okay. Next one is called SM part two, three, two, one, go.
All right, boys. How do you make a lot of money? Let's say you're 18 years old. What do you do?
You go to college, get a CS degree, be an entrepreneur.
Let me know.
Computer science.
No joke answers, please.
I mean, I mean, just based on the people I know.
Yes, that's what you do.
You get a computer science degree or you even just no computer.
You don't even necessarily need a degree.
But you, but you understand computer science and data structures and whatever.
And you get a friend who's got a job doing that and they recommend you.
And then you get a job and you just get like pretty good money because that's like something that people need.
Yeah. If you want to make, you don't want to make a bunch of money, go to school, learn computer science, get a job doing computer science.
Seems like the most straightforward way that I've seen.
I don't know. I don't know any better ways with a higher degree of success off the top of my head.
Do you answer your own question in a good, good work?
You already knew you had it inside of you all along.
You didn't need me.
Okay.
Next voicemail.
I am L three, two, one, go.
Greetings.
I am L.
This is a message to the one who calls himself Ben Saint.
That's me.
Ben.
I know that you killed your brother Nate shortly after the end of the show called content.
I also know that the videos recently posted to his channel are part of a backlog.
And they have been uploaded by you to try and cover up his death.
I'm a weekend at Bernie's in his channel.
And then I'll know your motivations for killing your own brother.
I am close and I am justice.
L doesn't sound like that.
Okay.
What motivations do you need?
I just did it because it was funny.
I just did it because it was funny and cool.
And I was just being cool.
And I'm the reason people are dying.
Those two together form all the motive necessary.
The first one is called interrupting death pig three, two, one, go.
Okay.
I have a serious question about the like the patreon and when you buy like the bonus episodes,
how do you get them?
Is it like a private YouTube set of videos and then you get the links to them?
Or is it like mp3 shits?
You have to download.
Because like, I just want to know how you, well, what way.
I get it.
No, I get it.
At first I was confused, but then I realized the title of the, of the voicemail explains everything.
The, I think, I don't even know.
I think I'm just going to pretend the pig didn't interrupt.
I think that when you patron, you get a, there are posts that you can then see, which have links to the bonus episodes,
which also link to a master list playlist, like a private, or not private, the other one,
an unlisted playlist that has all the bonus episodes in it.
I think that's how it works.
I mean, I'm not a paid, I'm not a patron of this bullshit.
Yeah, I think, I think that's, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called if Ben can relate three, two, one, go.
So this is an argument I've been having with my friends for the last few days.
And I felt like Ben, because I was explaining my point and they didn't get it.
And I would just get angrier and angrier.
That's me.
My point being, I think it's fucking illogical to believe or to.
Yeah.
Great, great bit.
Great bit.
Definitely won't get old.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Two was too many.
All right.
That was a little annoying.
If I hear a third one like that, I'm going to get actually annoyed.
Okay.
Next one is called how could you been three, two, one, go.
You know, I sent a voicemail last week, Ben, and I was super stoked to hear you and give
talk about it.
What?
Which one?
Behold, you did not misgender me.
Great.
What the fuck?
I specifically send voicemails in to be misgendered.
I'm so sorry.
And you did not give me that luxury.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Very shameful.
I apologize.
Ben, I hope you feel bad.
You should feel bad about yourself.
You guys got a va.
You're horrible.
You just got a va all the time.
And then no one ever gets the opportunity to be, and it's the satisfaction of getting
to be mad at me.
I'm too smart.
I head off all criticism at the past, nip it in the bud, chop off its dick.
Next one is called turn off the PCP comments three, two, one, go.
I mean, true, true.
Yeah, someone in the comments last week asked when can someone tell me when and the answer
is if you listened to the show, you would know because obviously I've been asked that
question a lot.
So, you know, I don't know, but whatever, no, comments are good.
Most comments are good.
Usually I like reading the comments in an episode, so I will not be turning off PCP comments,
but thank you for your input.
Next one is called turn off the PCP comments, but actually do it three, two, one, go.
I do genuinely think the comments should just fucking be turned off if you have something
to say, but it's not worth the effort of making a fucking voicemail, then maybe you
should have be saying it at all.
No, I can't believe it happened again.
Like the exact same thing happened where the new GeoWizard mission across Scotland straight
line mission video dropped and I'm like, I gotta sit down with a nice cup of tea full
screen there so that I can't see notifications and sit down and watch exactly, it's just
the same time the PCP records.
These things are predictable.
You can know in advance.
I could have seen it coming.
The upload schedule for this would be consistent with the time the PCP happens.
All I'm saying is I was happily watching part seven of Tim Rogers' Let's Mosey a slow
translation of Final Fantasy 7 and I had to painstakingly wrench myself away from that
in order to deliver this pig slop to our brain dead audience who will eat it up from the
trough.
My excuse is that I have to full screen that shit and because it's full screen I couldn't
see notifications because discord was underneath.
True.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again or will it?
That's the reason you come back next week is to see whether I do the same mistake.
Does give beat times in a row.
Well I have been listening to some voicemails.
Listen to some voicemails for my entire fucking podcast.
I just kind of talked for like 15 minutes and then had nothing else to say and just kind
of went into voicemails expecting that you would eventually show up.
None of the voicemails have been good so far.
Sorry everyone.
Okay.
But it's true.
They've all been bad.
You haven't missed anything of value.
Wait.
Am I right?
Yes.
Bad.
Well.
Okay.
What's up?
Good.
Well I've gotten into a new life ruining thing.
It's called number go up.
It's an idle game and you know how I am about those.
I play them too much and then I have to wrench myself away from them and it's always painful
and I don't know.
I saw like it in a video and I was like oh number go up.
That's fun.
Oh look at the numbers go up.
What a quirky self aware title.
It is self aware.
But the numbers do go up though.
But they do.
They do go up though.
They do.
Okay.
And so I've been playing that for the past few days and that's stupid.
Sure.
But it's fun.
Other than that, the Lord of Ghosts Kickstarter, I don't know whether I talked about it last
time on the PCP.
Maybe I mentioned something.
I feel like maybe you mentioned that you were thinking about it or considering it.
Yeah.
It was like hoodie gave me the idea when they were on with the cat-o thing.
I was like yeah that's a good idea and I spent the time to make it real, make it happen and
I've got to the point where I've ordered a sample of the pin.
There's a pin involved.
I have made a video to promote it.
I'm just waiting for the cat-o.
I saw the video.
The video is very funny.
Good.
I like it a lot.
I was stressing out over the video for a while because I'm like I don't want to record my
voice speaking the things that I'm going to have to type.
Like I'm going to have to type all of this into the Kickstarter.
That in itself is painful because I'm like how do I make this interesting and fun to
read such that people would actually want to do any of this stuff.
It's impossible.
And it's just a slog.
It's just a slog putting the necessary information in a line and then also making it in paragraphs
with full stops impossible.
But then the prospect of then taking that and then saying it in a video was like no
that sucks.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to put myself on camera either because I don't have my camera mostly.
Is that home?
Where's the parents?
I was saying earlier that I'm considering.
Wait, no, this.
No, I wasn't saying earlier.
I was said this in my Patreon podcast, which is different, but I'm confused because I recorded
that before and now I forget which one I said which thing in.
But I was saying there that I'm considering dropping a little money on like a better web
camera because like my my let's read video.
I think it looks amateurish.
I think the video quality is bad to the point that it like kind of detracts from it.
And I'm I think I want a good one to make crisp.
Film.
Yeah, it's always good to have a nice quality webcam.
To make, you know, to, you know, to make some high quality people movies as as I as I am
want to do the math.
I didn't have a webcam for the longest time, but then there was a there was an
up is a moment where I needed it for like a Zoom call or like a Skype call with a person
who wasn't like an internet person.
So I was like, oh, you know, it feels kind of unprofessional for them to be in their suit
with that with that Zoom call and me just audio.
So I got one, but I still look like shit, so I will never turn it on.
Um, so actually I was wasting money.
Absolutely.
Anyway, the Lord of Ghosts, I got the video made and I'm I'm Kickstarter went through
the review process and it's ready to go.
I could launch it at any moment.
I've been going over money things.
There's a plush idea.
Oh, we did talk about it because we talked about the funny Lord of Ghosts.
I saw.
Did I see some some like design shit?
About that.
I drew up a little, a little crude little design of a Lord of Ghosts plush and I sent
that over to to get a sample made, which is like, I'm considering that like my own
personal money, but if the Kickstarter ends up reimbursing me, then that's good.
Just so I can see what it would look like.
It's probably going to be good quality and I've given like specific instructions and
they're going to get the same people that made the pump one.
Yeah, it's the same people.
Yeah, they they have the good quality and they have the power and I just need them.
I'm very good.
They have the know how they have the skills to pay the bills.
Yeah.
So everything's all set up.
I'm just waiting for the Kato anthology Kickstarter to end or near its end, just so
I don't like step on their toes or anything.
It's fair enough.
That's fair enough.
And that's like halfway done now.
So we.
They are they had a they had a live stream as they were approaching their second.
Wait, I think it's their first stretch goal, actually, the thirty five hundred,
which they hit during the stream.
So they have reached they are on to their second kicks stretch goal now, which is
pretty cool, pretty cool, pretty happy for them, I guess.
Pretty congratulations are in order, I suppose.
Oh, yeah.
OK, so I don't know what was I talking about?
Yeah, you would the Kickstarter.
I don't know, I was I was half thinking I could just launch it
because they've already reached their initial goal.
But I feel like it's it's sort of bad form to just I don't know.
I mentioned it to them and they said they appreciated it.
So they can wait a little bit.
Yeah, I mean, I've still got to like to write the the stories for the the ghost
story, vaporette-esque things.
So there's things to do in the game.
And it'll help that I'm able to probably like get the sample of the
the enamel pin of the ghost so I can look at it and be like, oh,
I now can take a picture of it and prove it is real.
It would be it would be pretty nice to have pictures of the pin and the plush
to like show.
I yeah, I did that.
And when I was doing the my previous kick starters, like I've yeah,
I've sent off requests and printed up the at least like sample versions
of the books and stuff so that I can have it in front of me, take pictures of it,
be like, this is the product, this is what you get.
If you this is what you get, this is what you deserve.
Yeah, you just show the actual product in a picture
instead of it being a hypothetical, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
So I don't know if for some reason I looked at the the printing company
for the comic, I don't think I can get like a sample in like a like a,
you know, order a check out style.
I maybe I'll have to email them and ask, are you are you printing with
Kaplan or using someone else?
I'm printing with what is it called?
Mixam, which is also a UK based and it's very good quality
from what I can see for press.
And yeah, they've got a lot of good options for stuff.
And yeah, I think I'm going to go with them, but I need a sample.
I we we have to we have to pick a printing service to print the
road to Radcon book when it's done.
I feel like a comic printer might not be the cheapest option
because it's mostly text, but I don't know.
Well, I feel like it should be the case, but I don't know if it's the case.
You can you can make like leaflets with these sorts of services,
like small little things, brochures.
Because it's it's only like 20 pages, I think maybe 30.
It's yeah, if that be like I feel like that would work.
Maybe the printing cost would be higher than it would otherwise be
because it's mostly text and it's expecting images if it's a comic thing.
I just feel like I don't know.
I just feel like text printing is cheaper.
And I don't I feel like it should be, right?
Like it should be pictures should cost more to print.
Yeah, you're right.
It will have some images in it, but mostly mostly text.
Whereas like the dojin, I think would I would probably just say,
yeah, let's just use Kablam.
That's the one that's like cheapest for me.
Well, we're going to like physically print the dojin.
I thought that was just like a thing like it needs to exist.
Shit, I thought so.
But I could be wrong.
I could be misremembering.
I remember specifically like the Rotoradcon will make a Kickstarter.
Make a book and then send it to backers.
And the dojin was just like
if I feel like it was different, I feel like that wasn't like a physical reward.
Well, shit, I don't even know.
I don't even remember.
We have to have to go back and dojin dot com or whatever.
We'll have to go back and listen to the stream and listen to our specific wording.
Like what exactly did we say we were going to do?
Because I don't remember.
Well, whatever it was, legally binding.
Well, you look at the Kickstarter itself, what we said in the stream.
I don't know. What would be legally binding?
Well, I mean, nothing. Nothing's legally binding.
OK, you don't.
You don't you like I don't you don't have to explain.
Yeah.
If you if you just fail to complete your Kickstarter stuff.
I mean, they can't sue you as long
unless they think that you like deliberately lied about it.
Unless it's like fraud.
Well, I don't think I think somebody could attempt to sue you, but like nobody bothers.
Like, there's plenty of starters that have made like fraudulent bullshit claims.
They never deliver on the product.
And yeah, it just never turns into anything.
And then the creators of it just make a new thing later with a different
eye coat of paint and people get hype all over again for the new thing.
With like under a different company name, like they just move on
and nothing ever comes back because an individual would need to like
know about the Kickstarter and then file a lawsuit.
I think I mean, they would probably have to file like a like a like a class action lawsuit
where all the backers like cosine and are represented by like a single attorney
that brings charges something like that individuals or LLC.
Let's meet.
I mean, to be clear, it's all a moot point
because we will be delivering on everything.
So this is none of this applies to us.
True.
We're untouchable.
We're untouchably responsible.
Are you looking at that?
Are you looking at the I'm looking up the legal like on Kickstarter?
I feel like I've seen something where they've said, oh, I
they're kind of vague about it.
The actual language that they use is like
we do have like legal expectations for them to follow through on their stuff.
But like there's no I mean, you're right.
There's just no history of like anyone like successfully.
It's like so rare for anyone to get sued over like an undelivered
Kickstarter provides a funding platform for creative projects.
When a creator posts a project on Kickstarter,
they're inviting other people to form a contract with them.
Anyone who backs a project is accepting the creator's offer
and forming that contract.
Kickstarter is not a part of this contract.
The contract is a direct legal agreement between creators and their backers.
And then there's so what so what they're saying.
So what they're saying is don't don't blame us.
Yeah, don't blame us blame the creator.
I mean, it's all just a bunch of it's all just whatever.
That's just that's just them making shit out of being like, oh, yeah,
it's it's a contract between you.
It's like if OK, if you say so.
It's it's kind of solely responsible for filling the promises made in that project.
If they're unable to satisfy the terms of this agreement,
they may be subject to legal action by backers.
So just basically like do it yourself.
We're not involved.
Do it yourself.
It's the backers problem.
It's the creators problem.
Don't tell us about it.
We don't want to hear it.
We got out of that.
That's the thing.
Like if a backer is not financially able to do anything
individually by themselves, yeah, like by themselves legally,
they probably won't get any money back and they can't they can't appeal
to Kickstarter to help.
Yeah.
So that's it.
No, yeah.
Yeah.
Kickstarter is not responsible for.
Strong arming an irresponsible backer into giving a refund or whatever.
I suppose this person comes to that.
But I don't know what they are and I'm too dumb to think about them.
The pro is that Kickstarter doesn't have to do anything.
True. That's that's that's what they get out of it.
Makes sense.
If I were Kickstarter, I would do the same thing.
I'm just an intermediary.
I'm just I'm not you're not forming any kind of contract with me.
I mean, that's like I mean, this is like PayPal would never want to be like
if you pay someone with PayPal and then they don't give you the thing they paid
for, they PayPal doesn't want to be like,
oh, you can appeal to PayPal and say that like they were responsible
for that broken contract.
Like, no, no, deal with it yourself, guys.
I mean, yeah, can you not go to a bank and say can say like this?
Like, can you not go to your bank and look at a transaction and say,
actually, I'd like that taken back if it's like fraudulent?
I think it depends on the bank.
I think I think it depends on the bank and like what you how you paid.
Like, did you use a credit card or a debit card?
I think you can in many cases appeal and be like, that's a fraudulent charge.
And the bank will be like, OK, we'll cancel that charge and refund you sometimes.
Something like kind of kind of kind of subject to their whims,
kind of subject to their whims and whether they feel like letting you do it.
Like, like imagine a kid playing some sort of a game that has like money
transactions in it and they have their parents credit card information
on the console or whatever, they they rack up like huge debt.
You know, that happens.
They what how do they get their money back if at all?
Do they have to hope that the company.
I think they just allow to take that like to refund them.
Yeah, I think it's it's generally just like either the bank has to agree to be like, OK,
you're claiming these charges is fraudulent, we can cancel them and refund them.
Or the company can be like, OK, you're claiming that these charges were illegitimate.
We can cancel them and refund you.
But it's all at the whim of the bank or the company.
Like if they if they do that for you, they're basically just doing you a favor
or doing it because they they want to like either like retain you as a customer
through their gracious act of goodwill or they just want to look good
and or not give you like a reason to complain about them publicly.
If you were to do it and probably drop like
ten thousand dollars on something and you went to their bank and be like,
refund my ten thousand dollars, they'd probably just be like, no, fuck you.
We don't feel like it.
That ten thousand dollars is worth more to us than your goodwill.
So get fucked.
I think it's it's it's so it's so like, oh, unfortunate.
Oh, how terrible.
I spent my ten thousand dollars.
I spent my my ten thousand dollars of backup safety legal fees in case of a mishap,
just such for this occasion.
But now that I don't have the money, I can't pay for a lawyer to sue the guy.
Now I can't get the money back.
To a tragedy, a tale as old as time.
Says a lot about society.
Hmm. And yet we live in it.
We do. And yet you.
Hmm. You say something about society and yet you live in it.
Curious.
Very good.
Duh. Yes.
So that was anything.
OK, Kickstarter Kickstarter happening.
Cool. It's all by one.
Thanks. I'll buy your stupid book.
And I'm thinking of a price tag of right around zero dollars.
Oh, never mind. That's too much.
Oh, it's never mind.
Oh, no, I can't afford it.
Oh, no, no, no.
Like L.A.S.R. cut that.
In fact, bleep it out and like replace it with like zero.
Replace it with saying zero and zero dollars.
Like, ah, it's so cheap.
You just can't not buy it.
I can't. I can't afford not.
I can't afford not to buy it. True.
Wait for the. Hell, yeah.
Wait for the video to drop.
And then you'll be so hype that you can't help it.
You'll be you'll be hook, line, and synchred by that.
The video is pretty hype.
The video is funny. I think people like it.
Based. It's pretty based, as one might one might say.
You could say that that video is just being cool.
It is.
Buy buy a t-shirt.
Link in the description.
Yeah, buy a t-shirt with the entire
all of the pages of the comic printed on the t-shirt.
Right. Sure.
So you can read it while you're while you're wearing a t-shirt.
While you're admiring yourself in the mirror.
Yeah. Well, you're admiring your new fit.
Like all like one hundred fucking pages of the comic
like mirrored on the t-shirt so that you can stand in the mirror and read the comic
and like adjust the the the fabric folds to be like,
what the fuck does that say? I squint.
Oh, that reminds me.
I am going to be applying for a table at shit.
Stop me if I've mentioned this before.
I'm going to be applying for a table at not.
You know, I did. I talked about mice,
the the Massachusetts Independent Comic Expo
and how I want to get a table at it and how they're doing a mini and out an outdoor.
You don't remember they're doing an outdoor mini mice.
Shit, I should have talked about this on my Patreon podcast, but I forgot.
They're doing an outdoor mini mice where
yeah, it's like an outdoor con basically, but it's like only for local people.
They're not having like out of state people table.
And I think it's going to be smaller than a usual mice.
This was the one mice was where I met.
I met Abby Howard and Casey Green at the last one I went to,
which was God, like almost two years ago, because they didn't have one in 2020.
So the last one would have been in like summer of 2019.
Yeah, they're having this one in August.
I'm going to get I'm going to get a table.
I don't expect to like move a lot of product or anything like I'll have my comics.
I'll have a table.
I'm mostly just doing it to like, I don't know.
Take a take a seat in like the comic scene,
maybe meet some other creators.
Because like when I went to mice before, I hated it
because I was just walking around seeing comics people sitting behind tables,
making small talk like a nice comic.
And then they're like, thanks, you want to buy one?
And I'm like, no, and that was my con going experience.
So I want to be on the other side of the table.
I think that sounds much more gratifying.
I don't even care. I don't even care if I sell anything like fuck it.
I should have applied.
Actually, I should have applied on the first of the month.
It's the sixth of the month today.
So I hope I didn't miss my chance because when I applied to be at mice 2020,
they have like immediately sold out and there were no tables left.
So I may be fucked.
But then, of course, mice 2020 didn't happen.
Lamal. So I guess it didn't matter.
Whoops. I don't know.
I should probably do that like immediately after I've been putting it off.
I've put it off for almost a week.
So you're not in yet?
You still have to apply?
I haven't. I haven't sent the application yet.
Today, I was putting I was putting together a portfolio
because they asked you to show a PDF or JPEG portfolio of your work.
So I was going through all my old vapor stuff
because I because like the books I'll be showing will be vapors books.
Because that's the only books I have.
I was going through them and converting them to JPEGs
before putting them in a zip file.
And I didn't actually get around to finishing
doing that. I have to do chapter one still, I think, and then send it off.
I don't know why they're so particular.
They could literally just they asked for my website, which, you know,
StComics.com, they could just look at my website to see my portfolio.
But they also ask, please attach a PDF or zip file or whatever of your shit.
And we prefer to look at the file.
Why would you prefer to look at the files?
Why wouldn't you prefer to just look at my website and you can see it there?
Like, why do you want to download stuff?
I don't get it.
They said that's what they like.
So I'm just going to do it that way, I guess.
Well, that's going to be pretty cool.
I hope so. I have been this this it must be like two years now
that I've been thinking, damn, I should really table at a con.
I'm a little disappointed that, like, it's not like a normal con this time.
It's kind of like it's the mini version, the outdoor.
I think the idea is that if it's outdoor and the tables are spaced apart,
it's like social distancing friendly.
I feel like social distancing restrictions will be lifted by August
because, like, I mean, in Massachusetts, like, everyone's vaccinated.
Like, almost everyone's had at least one shot already.
So I feel like it's going to be fine by then.
But I think they're just not sure about what their restrictions will be.
So they're playing it safe and being like, we're having an outdoor,
socially distanced mini version of our kind of little.
It's a little bit of a shame that it's not the normal one.
I mean, it's better than if they did have a normal version.
I'm sure I would have missed.
I'm sure I would have missed the the sign update by now.
So whatever, trade off.
Yeah, better than being canceled, sure.
You got to do it, though.
But if it's local, well, Casey Green might still be there.
Abby Howard won't be there because she's from Portland or lives in Portland.
Wait, does Casey Green live in Massachusetts?
I feel like he does. Hold on.
It's an Andrew.
He lives in Boston or around.
I think so.
I'm pretty sure he does.
I mean, I have I have.
You know, the you know, the like ethnic mural in a problem sleuth
in problem sleuth, I've seen that mural.
I've walked by that mural before.
It's it's great. It's even better in person.
Do you think he like he actually took pictures of it for that thing?
Yeah, I do. Yeah.
Well, he could have just Googled it.
Well, I mean, I mean, if it's
like I assumed it was just like a thing he had found online.
But if you've seen it in person and he thought that's really funny,
I'll put that in my comic.
I think he picked it because he lives in the area and he's seen it around
and he thought it was funny.
Yeah. And he put it and he put it in problem sleuth.
That's even better than just like finding something funny.
Um, yeah, from Googling.
I mean, I guess it makes more sense if you have like a you just notice it.
Because like, why would you ever think to Google murals like that?
You wouldn't.
Now, he must have seen it around in real life.
And yeah, Casey Green does live in Massachusetts.
He grew up in Oklahoma City, but I guess he lives in Massachusetts now.
Not sure where exactly.
But I was right.
So he might be there, actually, which would be pretty cool.
I guess I wouldn't say I'm like a huge Casey Green fan or anything.
I mean, I I haven't actually like read any of his.
I guess I read the anime club comics, which were fine.
I haven't read like what's the one he was making for a while.
He is a good boy.
I think it's called.
I haven't read that one.
The only Casey Green I know is the collaborative dog.
Oh, that as well.
But like the collaborative effort with him, Hussey and drill on this super
not super sweet bro and hella Jeff.
A new adventure quest for the missing spoon.
That was fun. Yeah, that makes sense.
That's the one that they that's the one that they kickstarted, right?
Yeah, they kickstarted it.
And it's such a weird book and has a spoon tucked inside that I still have.
I never got that one.
And I feel damn, I wish I wish I had it.
I would love to own a copy of that.
But I don't. It's it's great that the the they made it so
that the it's not like a perfect
like rectangle, it's like slightly angled
like the top half is slightly angled upwards from the spine.
So it's just sort of a weird, annoying shape.
And it's hard to notice at a glance, but then you have it in your hands.
You like, wait, this isn't like a proper book shape.
So many little things like that.
Obviously, it must have taken a lot of work to to like mass produce something
so stupid, because there's like 40, not 40,
like a few hundred pages at the end that are carved out
in the shape of a spoon where the spoon is.
Hmm. Hmm.
And that's called Oh, yeah.
That's the into incorporating the physical nature of the medium into the into the work.
Yeah. So dumb.
So dumb. I kind of love it.
Um, yeah, I got I got that book with the with the with the fidget spinner reward
here and I still have that fidget spinner.
It's the only fidget spinner I ever bought based based.
I have I think somewhere here, I have a fidget spinner that Econ gave me
that is really cool.
It's silver and gold and it has yin yangs on it.
It's made of metal and it kind of rules.
It's probably in a box somewhere.
So if if I get into that, if I get a table,
I'm looking at the page right now and I guess many mice will be August
twenty eighth and twenty ninth at Starlight Square
in the Central Square neighborhood of Cambridge.
I know where Central Square is.
I don't know what Starlight Square is.
I don't think I've ever been there before.
And I'm a little surprised because previous
mices have been at Porter Square inside of the
I think it's a Tufts campus building that they've been at before
or maybe not, but it's some building in Porter Square.
But I guess this time it's Starlight Square.
How how magical, how mysterious and a pony full, how pony.
Pony up.
Hey, when's that new pony coming out?
Sometime this summer, I remember something.
Oh, I can't wait.
I can't wait to be Pony Boy again.
I can't wait for the new Minecraft thing to come out and the pony.
And it'll be exactly like it used to be.
It'll be exactly like 2001, a space Odyssey.
I should mention.
I think I think I mentioned this on Shekels for heckles.
No, no, it was after Shekels for heckles.
I talked on Shekels for heckles.
I talked about how I was really into the Thaumcraft mod
that was in that's in there.
It's on their server after the the stream.
I grinded, I grinded Thaumcraft.
I grinded through the like quest line of it.
And I got it and I unlocked all the shit and I made the void metal
and I crafted the cool hood and not just the cool hood.
I crafted the cool evil fucking void alchemists hood and robe and pants.
And now I look like a fucking demon and it is gratifying.
I am so pleased with myself that I look like a void wizard now.
I just wanted everyone to know that I I did it.
I beat Thaumcraft.
Nice is very nice, very cool.
So next time we check all I will be looking scary.
And is that the Thaumcraft what thing is it called?
What do you mean?
The the mod is called Thaumcraft.
No, the gear. Oh, the gear set is called.
I think it's called the void Thaum.
Wait, hold on. Void Thaum.
The void Thaumaturge hood.
Yeah, you make you make the you make like the void helm
and the void armor and the void leggings.
And then you you do like rituals on them.
You you enchant them or you know, you infuse them in the infusion altar
to turn them into the void Thaumaturge hood and the void Thaumaturge
robe and the void Thaumaturge leggings.
I've seen I've seen these born by certain players on the server for.
Yeah, I always thought they were really cool.
There's some the shoulder pads on the on the robes are somewhat Samurai-esque.
A little bit. Oh, oh, I didn't know.
Apparently, there are there are boots, too.
There are boots of the void walker that I didn't even know or a thing.
I guess I'll have to figure out how to make those, too.
I didn't I didn't.
OK, what eldritch I what the I think this might be part of like a secondary mod.
This looks weird. This looks a little different.
I'm not sure if this is part of vanilla Thaumcraft.
I just wanted to brag about it.
Thaumcraft is really cool.
You like you do all this fucking extract essences from shit.
And if you do it in a certain way, it like boils over and like tainted essence
like infects the world.
And then these creatures start showing up and they spread this stuff called taint.
And then you have to like do all this weird shit to like contain the paint.
And then these rifts start opening up and if they do damage to you
and they spread more taint, they let more creatures out.
And you have to like do all this like involved stuff to make these
like bombs that like collapse the rifts to close them.
It's very cool.
A lot of the stuff in the PCP mod is or in the PCP server is like
it's like kind of a nerfed a little bit, like apparently mage said it
so that taint doesn't spread because if it does, it can like spread really far
and like fuck the whole server up and just like and I think she didn't want it
to have the possibility of that happening.
So it's a little bit nerfed, but it's still pretty neat.
It's very cool. Love it.
I use talking about like like taint spreading reminds me of a mug.
Yeah, what is it?
What is you is talking about taint spreading remind you?
Well, it's reminding me of another Minecraft mod that I can't remember what it's called,
which is very annoying, but I found it.
I saw it on YouTube.
It's basically like a certain infestation, like a parasitic
like set of mobs and and systems where there's like tainted,
not I guess it's not called taint is like played or ruined land
that spreads from, you know, grass block to grass block.
And then creatures that are like parasites spawn in that in that area
and they jump around and they they're not very dangerous on their own.
But then they can infect like villagers and zombies and pigs and anything.
Anything Minecraft normal can be turned into a like a parasitic version,
which is like extremely fast and like evolves.
And if you kill them, they they like sort of.
I think there's like a weird thing where like if enough of them like get.
Well, no, no, they turn into parasites and then they start attacking other Minecraft
mobs, so like a sheep will become like a parasite sheep.
And then that sheep will start eating other things around it until it gets
like engorged enough to explode into a into a bloody mess.
And then that mess of like writhing flesh, if it connects with another writhing flesh
mob, like evolves into a higher being of Cthulhuid paracet, like weird gross shit.
And it's extremely disgusting.
And it was so cool, but I can't remember what it was called.
There's a lot, just a lot of the whole.
The whole Minecraft modded Minecraft
just seems like a whole separate game experience to like delve into.
Thaumcraft just happened to catch my eye
because I thought it would be cool to have a dark hood.
Oh, it's it's it's called scape and run parasites.
Scape and run the parasites.
OK, pretty, pretty neat.
Pretty. There's like there's like a different
levels of like of like being that can be created and the plague area,
the parasite like infestation area can spread.
And if it spreads big enough, it sprouts these like trees that summon things
as it grows bigger and you have to chop them down and purify the area.
Otherwise, it'll summon like flying big, dangerous things
that'll get you and they'll really scare you.
And then you'll poop your pants about it.
Did you did you ever watch the old
the old I've talked about it before.
Fuck, what's it called?
The guys who made Polaris, the the.
The Maker's Studio.
No, no.
The guys who made Polaris was like total biscuit and and color.
I think they use the head of it.
Am I fucking crazy?
I'm sure these guys are like.
Oh, my God, what would the Yogs cast?
Oh, no, you ever see the the old the old Yogs cast of Minecraft videos?
You know, I didn't.
But I did watch a video like talking about like like video essaying.
The thing you had talked about before, the the Let's Play Shadow of Israel,
Shadow of Israel.
Yeah, it goes through like all of the twists and turns and like how it
starts out small and the the it really does.
It really doesn't know that it's like set up like that.
And it's yeah, very interesting.
It's genius. It was genius.
It was genius, genius storytelling in a new medium of expression at the time.
I'm not sure if there had ever.
I'm not sure if there was ever anything like it before.
And I mean, it's fun.
It goes on like like there's sequels to it, too.
Like if they didn't stop after the end of Shadow of Israel,
like they spun it off into all these like side series where like
they they started making the Jaffa cake factory while like
while they're being, you know, harassed by their enemy Sips over at Sips Dirt Co.
And meanwhile, Sips Dirt Co. has like its own like side story series
that is, you know, that he's kind of just running in parallel at the same time.
It's great since it's inspirational.
I love what they did with it so much.
I'm so impressed with it to this day.
On I wonder, man.
Shit, I wonder if I went back now and watched it.
What I think like it's not as good as I remember.
Was I just impressed with it because it was good for the time?
It's probably overly long, honestly.
But like, I don't know, even though it's long at the time,
like the fact that it starts out
plotless and then sort of evolves a plot as it goes that while like the players
kind of sort of know that something is being done, but they don't know what it is.
And they're genuinely like experiencing it as it happens.
Oh, I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I guess it makes me want to gush.
I'm just going to gush about it.
Like what what a great what a great what a great conceit.
What a great conceit for a let's play.
I wonder if maybe they weren't the first to do it.
And maybe they were like cribbing their idea from someone else.
But I just don't know about it because they were like more popular.
The Oaks cast were like one of the one of the first one of the first
like big Minecraft channels feel like they weren't that many other people
to crib off in Minecraft.
They were a world of Warcraft show before they were a Minecraft.
Yeah, guys, I think.
Honestly, a few of them X X from X's adventures in Minecraft
was like a World of Warcraft guy.
I remember watching their like tank tutorials, like how to do how to do good
tanking in World of Warcraft, Wrath of the Lich King.
I was the only World of Warcraft that I played was Wrath of the Lich King.
That was a good one.
It was it was pretty all right.
It was pretty OK. It was fine.
It was pre pre Cataclysm, which everyone hated.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I guess I got involved.
The getting was still mostly good.
First for that one just for that one golden summer.
I could talk about World of Warcraft, but I really don't know too much about.
Like I've played Cataclysm.
I played like Missa Pandaria after that.
And then the rest I'm not sure about.
And then I came back for a while and I enjoyed Legion.
I heard that one was a good one.
But then it sucks again.
And then it was good again.
So really, it's stupid that it never even heard of Legion.
Yeah, there's a bunch of expansions.
You know, the Burning Legion.
It's like a big bad that all the demons and fell stuff.
Well, there's the that was like the expansion
about the Legion, specifically the first time
as they've been like a main antagonist.
Wasn't wasn't the Burning Crusade about fighting the Legion?
Well, I guess it was.
So forget it.
But this was like this went there.
This ended up going to a different planet
using like the Draenei's
like they the Draenei likes aliens and they the ship crashed.
And that's the capital city.
Well, they use some of that technology.
I know that because I started a Draenei one time.
Yeah, they they at that point in the story,
the ship is like or not their ship, a ship, technology, whatever.
I didn't actually play all of the quests, so I don't actually know.
But you get on a ship and you fly to the Burning Legion's
military home base, which is the Draenei's previous
previously inhabited Draenei world of Argus,
which is like full of demons.
So green because the the demons
aren't the demons like bad Draenei, like the bad Draenei turned red.
But like weren't the Draenei based on the the demons.
But it was like it was retcon to be like, oh,
the demons are like the offshoot of the Draenei that turned evil.
But the Draenei are like they're they're naturally good.
Like the original people that they came from
were these good guys called the Draenei, right?
Yes, the Draenei are just a race, an alien race on a planet.
The Burning Legion itself is a collection of conquered and corrupted races.
So all of the demons that are, you know, all of the different types of enemies,
they used to be just a race of people on a different planet
that was once conquered and enslaved and corrupted and enlisted by the Legion.
And so kind of like some of them.
Yeah, so kind of like the Zerg, but like demons instead of like
gross, like parasitized bug creatures.
Yeah, OK, I see.
So I got you.
And then there's a bunch of stuff I didn't actually get to play on Argus.
I didn't get that far because there's a lot of stuff in Legion.
And it's quite good quest writing, honestly.
But the cool thing.
And I don't know whether people actually think this is cool,
but it was like, oh, Warpog is the biggest thing I've ever seen.
So it's so big.
It's the biggest moment in World of Warcraft.
Sargeras, the the originator of the Burning Legion, who is like an ancient Titan.
If you know the Titans, they're like really big and they go around planets
creating life by planting like they're like weird robots.
They put like the the iron dwarves and the mechanomes to cultivate the land
and create like they put stone people down, like carve the land into a thing.
And this is this is where all the lore of the Titans is.
The Titans were literal Titans who created life on on Earth, on on Azeroth.
They go around the universe.
Sargeras is a Titan who is like, actually, fuck that, I would rather destroy life.
That's better, I think.
And and he started the Legion and he's going around like undoing the Titans work
because he doesn't agree with it.
He arrives and this is this.
This is like the expansion about the Burning Legion.
Sargeras should be or could be the final boss, but they don't I don't think they kill him.
I think they banish him at the end of spoilers.
But he gets his giant sword.
He's bigger than the planet.
He gets his giant sword and he like throws it as just as he's about to be like
cast away by the other Titans and like locked in a prison or whatever
to presumably come back in like five other expansions later.
Because he's the like the main villain of all of the entire universe.
It's kind of difficult to just kill him.
He throws his giant sword and it like stabs the earth and it's in the earth now.
You can go to it like physically.
It's in Silithus, which is like the southwest.
So there's nothing there, nothing was there.
But now there is literally nothing there because there is a sword
that is the tallest thing that has ever existed in the game.
And you can actually fly all the way to the top of it.
It's so fucking big.
You can see it from like 15 zones away.
It's like, oh, the horizon is permanently changed with this giant sword
jutting out of it. And I just thought that was cool.
That is cool. That reminds me of isn't there like a giant sword
sticking out of the ground in diaries of a spaceport janitor?
Like somewhere near like a lake, I think.
There's like just a big sword sticking out of the ground.
I thought you're about to say diaries of a wimpy kid.
In the lore of Diaries of a Wimpy Kid.
Isn't there a legendary titan sword stuck in the ground?
No, spaceport janitor.
Yeah, I heard you cackling and I'm like, what did I say?
What did I say? That's funny.
Oh, man. Yeah.
Good game, diaries of a spaceport janitor.
Pretty neat, actually kind of a weird game.
I don't know if I'd call it a good game, but a neat game with a cool world
that's fun to walk around and look at.
I have been.
Oh, you're going to what are you going to say?
Because I was going to change your game.
I was going to change the subject completely.
So go ahead.
Well, I just want to mention speaking of cool,
little funny indie games that are interesting.
The there's a new palestinian bundle.
I bought that I bought that this morning in the bundle for a palestinian aid.
I saw it and I was like, oh, great.
Yeah.
But last year, I got the friend of the show, Jim Storm Dancer's game.
Yes, I know.
It's called glitter, glitter, mitten, grove.
That's good.
Fragrance, too, is on there.
Now I have that.
And that's going to be fun.
That's worth that's worth playing.
That's worth the five dollars easily.
Yeah, all by itself.
Yeah.
But yeah, like last year, itch.io had a similar bundle
for like Black Lives Matter, like support.
Yeah, I bought that and I was like, it was a great deal.
That was a great deal.
I played a bunch of those games and some of them were pretty interesting.
I played so many of those.
I enjoy the process of coming through those and like looking at one
and seeing that looks kind of interesting, clicking on it.
Obviously, I've already bought all of these by them being in the bundle.
So I don't have to worry about cost.
I just sort of treasure trove diving, like finding gems, finding things
that are like not traditionally marketable or good.
Or you wouldn't see this on the front page of Steam.
You wouldn't get recommended this by anyone.
Nobody would ever talk about it.
And yet, and yet there are some really fun little games in here
that otherwise would never be seen by anyone, at least not by me.
I have the page open right now after I bought it, because I just did.
And I saw a couple on here, just on the first page randomly that seemed neat.
Let me just pick one that I saw that was called.
There's one called, I don't know.
This one just caught my eye.
It's called to dual lists.
Just a common, beautiful day, completing a list.
And there's like a fucking, you know,
nude, alarmed adventure time looking boy, girl, I don't know, looking at a list.
And I guess maybe you play as this person going around and dueling people.
Like Yu-Gi-Oh, I don't know.
I might I might play it and see what it is.
Yeah, I really enjoy it.
Yeah, it's it's the having access to and being encouraged to try out
all of these secret games.
And and this palestinian aid bundle is, you know, good excuse to do that all over again.
I did skim through to see if it was like mostly the same, but it's mostly different.
I actually didn't recognize nearly any of the ones.
And I have scrolled through all of the pages of the BLM one.
So definitely worth your money.
Give it a give it a five dollars.
Give it even more than that.
I gave it twenty five.
Yeah, link link in the description to that, because I would say it's worth.
Even if you don't want to play these fucking games by any by it anyway.
Yeah, I mean, I was going to say value for money is like it's one thing.
But I really like the experience of it's both having all of this.
This like it feels like secret knowledge, even though it's like you put put it a game in.
I played one of the games the day I bought it.
Which was like this time traveling puzzle game where you have to like walk around
a very small like level made of like cubes and stuff.
And you've got to like stand on platforms and press buttons.
And then like another version of yourself from the future plays like you play
in the same zone as the one you just played.
And you can't like lock eyes or like your past version of yourself
that was like pre-recorded through your actions cannot see your future self
or your present self from your perspective.
So you've got to like stealth hide from yourself.
And then if it you fuck up, you can rewind and you have to like plan
where you expect the blind spots need to be so that you can run through them easier.
It was good.
And I was just like and I played the whole thing.
It was a short little game.
It was a really cool concept adequately made and done and good music.
And I really liked it.
And that was like just the first one.
Hmm. Hmm.
Hmm. Makes you think says a lot about society.
It says a lot about the video games.
It really does.
Short games are based.
I'm just scrolling.
I was thinking, you know, I was watching.
I was talking earlier about I was watching all these videos
by this guy fucking Tim Rogers.
And I don't think I agree with his taste in games
because he talks a lot about big ass games, long games, triple A games,
last of us, Final Fantasy 7 remake.
And I honestly, I don't care at all about how I don't care how good they are.
I don't want to play them.
I don't want to play those games.
They're not interesting.
They're big, bloated, cinematic pieces of shit.
I couldn't give less of a fuck about even if they're perfect, irrelevant.
Give me a game that I can like last through in like five minutes
and have a nice experience.
Give me give me a give me a hundred of those.
Give me a goofy, weird, little like indie thing that is like.
Like, I don't I don't want to see the last of us
because I've seen it before.
I have it's it's its own story, but like all the stuff in it I've seen before.
Um, I don't know.
What is I'm look, I'm strong.
Cats are liquid, a light in the shadows, a minimalistic 2D platformer
about a cat with the ability to transform into liquid.
What could that be?
Maybe I've never seen anything like that.
Maybe it doesn't matter.
Maybe it sucks.
But I don't know.
It seems more peaks my interest more.
There's always going to be a few that suck.
And there's always a lot of like
tabletop rule sets and things that aren't even games like tilesets.
But like, there's over a thousand, I think things.
And there's so many of them that like the vast majority, I think are like games.
And of those games, there's going to be at least like 20 to 30 to 50,
like actually good ones that you enjoy.
Probably it's like there's there's there's no way you can go wrong.
True.
I was I was going to say, if you remember when we talked a couple
episodes ago about distress at the thought of having one's head destroyed.
Ha, I mean, that doesn't sound distressing, but I don't remember.
I I remember I talked about it.
I talked about how it.
The point is, I've been thinking a lot.
I have I've been having
at the time, I said, like, boy, I think about like,
what if I died by having my head crushed?
That would be so bad.
And I freak out thinking about it.
I've been freaking out more and thinking about it more.
I've been having like a lot of intrusive thoughts about it
that make me like sort of spaz out a little bit and like recoil and like kind of like
have to like stand up and like hit my head and be like, ah,
like I'm so I'm like so bothered.
The experience I imagine is like this.
The experience I imagine like this.
It's my it's my head on a train track against the metal of the train track
as the train comes towards me and crushes me under its iron wheels.
I mean, a train track, a train track would be so quick
that it wouldn't even you wouldn't even feel the pain.
You I don't know about that.
I wouldn't you feel it for just a moment?
Maybe wouldn't you feel it for just a moment?
You would.
And I can only imagine that it would be the worst feeling that a human could
experience. It would.
But like I think I think the way I think the way to solve this is just
think I'm thinking is hyper focusing about that moment.
Like how would that moment feel?
And I just got to face your way out over it.
You've got to face your face.
You've got to try it out.
Oh, yeah, I'll let you know.
I'll let you know how it goes.
Oh, you just got to where I tell you.
And then it like a little thing we like fly off into the sunset.
Oh, you know what? You know what's in?
Oh, wow, you know what's in this bundle is Mouse Corp by the catamites.
That's the guy who made that's the guy who made Space Funeral.
One of his slightly later games.
It's a it's a weird game that I never quite figured out.
Mouse Corp.
OK, about the head crushing thing, I don't know.
I've started to wonder.
I've started to I've been thinking about it so much
that I'm thinking like, what if I'm seeing the future?
What if I what if what if that's the future that's becoming it's coming?
Like it's getting sooner and sooner.
And that event is reverberating strongly into the past.
And I was receiving a message from my future me that that is how I will die.
And it was getting closer.
It's giving you it's giving you subliminal messages
so that you're afraid of putting your head on a train track,
whereas otherwise you would usually do that normally and that would be fine.
But now you're afraid of it.
I am afraid of it, but it's but it's my future.
So I'm going to do it anyway.
So it's not accomplishing anything by sending the message back.
It's just making me feel bad and it's working great at that.
It's accomplishing that goal of flying colors.
Something that is similar, kind of, is when I move my jaw in a specific way
or I yawn like too strongly, there's like a weird sharp,
very short lived pain.
But it's very scary in my skull where it's like, oh, you shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't have moved your jaw in that exact way.
And I'm like, OK, I won't.
And I don't know what it is.
I don't think it's like a fracture or anything.
I don't think it's anything serious.
But it's like it's happened like on like occasionally for the past few years.
And I'm like, God, if I if I push that, if I decided to continue moving in that way,
it would maybe it would cause irreparable damage.
And I'm so scared that like there's something wrong there in my skeleton
in my it's probably just like a weird nerve ending.
That's like, I don't know, brushing up against something and going,
telling me that I'm going to die.
But I'm not sure. I mean, there's a feeling that I get.
Haven't done it in a while and I don't want to do it.
But if you like try to open your mouth as wide as it'll go,
like really try to open your jaw really wide.
And then when it says wise, it goes like try to push it even further.
It it's not a pain, but it starts to feel weird.
And if you do it, if no, like you you you it when I've done it,
when I've done it before, it makes me think like.
It makes me like kind of want to keep doing it and let's like see what happens.
And I feel like you could.
Yeah, like unhinge your jaw and like injure yourself
if you did that hard enough.
And it's it's the curious like, oh, I just kind of want to flirt with that.
Like, I've never felt this before.
What if what if what if we go even further beyond?
This is super super broken jaw three.
Hell, yeah.
I don't know. I just hate.
Being a corporeal being having a brain,
having a body, having organs, having parts of me that feel things.
I hate I hate I hate my corporeal existence.
Yeah, I mean, you should try being incorporeal, such as the Lord of Ghosts.
I would love I would love to I would love to wait.
Is he even in corporeal?
He's just like a blob.
Yeah, he's not. Can he go through?
So he can't he can't like walk through walls or anything?
No, I mean, I think in the comic and I make it sort of imply
that he's not really a ghost when he goes underneath the other thing.
And the guy says, I'm going to revive now because I'm dead
and I'm going to go up the pipe and I'm going to become a real person again.
And then Lord of Ghosts goes there and does it and nothing happens.
It's like, oh, he's not really dead.
Oh, oh, oh, Pog, oh, so it.
No, you're right. I remember that.
I just I do that makes.
Yeah, he doesn't seem like a ghost or I don't know what the fuck his deal is.
I do, but I'm not telling.
But I sure do love that.
But I sure do like that little scamp.
Whatever, whatever his freaky is, freaky being might might be.
Hell, yeah, hell, if the plush, if the plush like stretch goal
gets reached, reached and like people, people have him,
then they'll be able to tell for sure what he feels like in real life
because he'll be finally corporeal, even though he already is.
It'll be. Will will he retroactively be like, oh, yeah,
he's actually like a plush all along.
He was always been made of fabric.
This was from the very beginning.
Probably. Yeah, they do zoom in on the on the pages like, oh, wait a minute.
Is that is that a a steam, a seam, a little tag on him?
Oh, it was there all along.
Go you got to do it'll be like in Homestuck when Hussie went back
and added John's arm and all the frame.
Yeah, go back and add a little tag, add a little a little tag
and a little like stitch off of a little like fucking.
How are they called?
Beanie baby tag.
Yeah, the tie tag.
Exactly. Exactly.
You've got to do it. It's canon.
You've got to respect canon.
Oh, no, I'm a slave to the canon.
And I just assume I just agree with whatever people say it is.
That's the true communism way to make art is to is to have no autonomy at all.
That's the thing about canon.
It just is whatever people believe it is.
And if enough people, if you can delude enough people into thinking
it's something else, then it just becomes that.
Yeah, there's nothing anyone can do about it.
You know, I know the death of the author is an applicable term here,
but I've heard it so many times in so many contexts.
I forget what it actually means.
Do you and I just assume I'll be killed and I'll be dead at some point.
Yeah, that's what there is.
It can mean that if you want it to like if I'm if you become an author,
you're destined to be killed by the audience, they'll get you.
It's like it's it's when you when you go to like a book signing
and you you shoot them, but you say you say death of the author first,
you get a freebie.
The cops can't arrest you if you say death of the author.
Like death caused by the author.
Well, if you become an author, you're allowed to death death.
One people. No, I was saying you're allowed to kill them,
the fans or anyone or maybe they maybe it's just a free for all.
I don't know. It's just anyone fucking kill anyone when book when books are involved.
When art is involved, it's it's it's this.
I mean, maybe that's maybe maybe that's the canon of death of the author.
Maybe I believe that to be true and that makes it true because I say so.
If enough people are convinced.
What about the breath of the author, though?
Breath of the author is like when they're speaking.
Yeah, that one's pretty simple, actually.
It's not a lot to say about that.
It's exactly what it's like if you stop the breath of the author,
you cause the death of the death of the author. That's right.
That's right. And that's why the and that's why when aspect inversion
occurs on a breath character, they become a doom character.
No, wait, it's blood.
They become addicted to meth.
They become a meth character.
Yeah, yeah.
Boy.
Have we said all we need to say about that?
Well, about that, yeah, I guess.
Less little thing is that I'm thinking I might I might.
I've got a few little things to do,
but I do want to get back to like drawing the Clarissa comic.
And I feel like, yeah, even though it's like strange,
like conflicting marketing, I feel like it would be a good idea to do that stream
and then talk about Lord of Ghosts while I'm drawing the Clarissa comic
while that Kickstarter is going on. I don't see. I don't see why not.
There's there'll be no detriment to to either thing.
So I'm probably going to be doing that once I get a few things.
In order I want to finish that smaller comic and I'm going to go into Clarissa.
I'm going to hopefully be live streaming at some point.
And I'll I'll show the Kickstarter and it will be like,
oh, everything's suddenly happening.
It gives doing stuff suddenly.
Mm, that'll be weird.
That'll be that'll be the day.
Yeah, that's how I mean, yeah.
That's how I'm going to feel when I put the game out.
It's going to be like, oh, my God, Ben finished something.
Oh, my God, Ben actually made something.
And then the lecture comes out right.
It will. It will be like it rains at poor is kind of like, oh,
all of a sudden a cascade of content.
What the fuck? I don't even know.
I don't even know what's going on, man.
I don't even know which thing to which which media to consume first.
I'm a consumer. I love content.
Soy, soy, soy.
Soy, soy, soy, soy, soy.
Yes, yes. Perfect.
Perfect. Soy, soy, soy.
Oh, there was a there was a voicemail
that purported to be
Miss Mr. Vizier of the Voidgazers singing the discord song discord.
I'm howling at the moon and screaming.
And I don't know if it was real, but boy, it was.
You know, did it sound like him?
It did. It did sound like him.
It could have been real, but I don't know.
I just don't know. It could be a forgery.
I don't know. I don't trust my senses.
Well, let's just assume there was an forgery and then suddenly like Riley.
Yeah. You know what?
This guy's pretty based, actually.
You know what?
Anyone who likes the discord song.
Old discord, old discord between parties goes away.
Once you sing the discord song, I mean, it's got to remember that friendship
at the end of the day is magic and we just we got to we got to do it.
We got to have friends.
Friendship is magic, but magic is fucking fake.
So I don't know.
Oh, yeah, by the transitive property of fakeness
and friendship is fake as well. That's a shame.
Dang, uh, you want to go do some more voicemails?
Yeah, we're floundering. We're floundering.
OK, we're floundering like that fish from the Little Mermaid.
Wait, wait, wait, actually, let's OK.
Let's listen to that one again.
Just I want to hear if you think it's it's it's true.
It's the one called S.M. Part One.
Oh, hang on. Let me get there.
Yeah, OK.
Speakpipe.co.
I just I just don't know what.
Like, when would he have been singing that it sounds a lot like him,
but I'm just like, I just doesn't seem like which one seemed like that would have happened.
It's called S.M. Part One.
Oh, oh, there. Yes.
And OK, three, three, two, one, go.
And now Yig Studios Riley performing Discord.
I'm not a fan of redditors.
And I've been nagging for someone else is pulling all those strings.
Something terrible is going down to the entire town.
Can you do it?
Brings I can't sit on it.
No, I can't move at all.
I curse the name.
The one behind it all.
What do you think?
I think the because there is like it's it's made to sound as if it's like played at a venue,
but we can't hear any people at all.
I think it's fake.
There's no crowd noise.
There's no nothing.
So why would he just be blasting this and then singing it?
I don't know if I'm convinced by that argument.
I feel like if the music was loud enough, you just and like it was just recorded at a low quality,
you just wouldn't hear the crowd.
Yeah, but I know what live music said.
I mean, the video they made of that thing, I glanced at it.
I looked at it just to see what was going on.
Does not sound like you could hear stuff.
They didn't they didn't sing at that one.
I know they didn't, but like.
They recorded it.
They had a camera.
I don't know what if if Riley sang, I don't know why he I don't know why it's
Redditors.
I don't know why the it says Redditors instead of puppeteers.
Like, is that an ad lib?
Wait, he says, I'm not a fan of Redditors, but I'm a nagging fear.
Someone else is pulling at the strings.
I'm going to turn up.
I don't know.
This this is inconclusive to me.
No, no, no, it's it's there's the bit where after he says, and I can't move at all.
It takes a breath.
The music isn't there.
You can hear nothing.
There's nothing there.
He's either performing in an empty studio, a whole whole of place, venue.
Or it's fake.
And I think it's probably fake.
I I don't know.
Maybe maybe you're right, maybe you're right.
Just so disappointing, just disappointing if fake.
I need any big, big, if true, big, if true.
I would need a story video.
Then yeah, I was I was doubting it too.
I would also need visual if I saw that that's what it would take for me to be
sure without it.
I can only I can only wonder.
OK, but the next the next voicemail that I didn't listen to before is called
Ultra Numerary, do you see it?
Yep.
Base OK, three, two, one, go.
Hello, PCP.
I come to you today seeking some advice.
You see, I would like nothing more than to start a simple, modest,
Welsh speaking family.
But I can't reconcile this with the additional fact that I.
This is a terrible bit.
This this guy, he he's he's sent in a bunch.
He's sent in a bunch of voicemails where he starts asking a question
and then he has metal music start playing with pig squeals.
And I guess he just must think it's really funny.
But it was it was it was it was it had worn out its welcome by
probably the end of the first one to say nothing of having
being three voicemails in.
So I'm sick of this guy.
Next one is called Toma.
Yeah.
Boo, bad.
Next one is called Tomaso Choco Taco three, two, one, go.
Hey, everybody, I just wanted to correct something Nate said last week.
He was actually still can download stuff from Emu Paradise.
It's just you have to download an extension called is a monkey.
We're going to have a pick on a script through it.
We're going to be easy to set up.
You just Google it.
It works fine.
See you later.
What does he mean that Nate said last week?
What does that mean?
He probably was responding to a very, very old episode.
And I don't know.
Didn't realize or it's a joke.
I don't get what helps.
Lane, what a fucking moron.
I'm I don't know why I'm so mad.
I'm irritated.
He didn't know.
No, you're a fool.
You're you're you're.
Yeah, you move parent.
Yeah, whatever.
I don't even remember what you said.
Next voicemail is called Your Average Passive Listener.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys were talking about having kids last week, and it was basically
talking about symbolic immortality, a psychological term coined by Robert J.
Lyft and they'll naturally strive for it because we're fear of death.
There's four categories, biological, children, afterlife,
religion, natural, trees and the good shit, creative immortality.
I think all artists have that little comfort inside them that at least
something will still be there after they're dead.
I sure do.
I think I need a question.
So is anyone religious in the PCP?
And no matter the answer, how is.
Great voicemail.
Love that.
I mean, I guess they're just not up to date.
I don't know what the joke would be if they're just putting.
I don't know if this is a joke.
No, no one's religious in the PCP.
Great question.
Thanks. Creative immortality is pretty cool.
That's pretty.
That's that's pretty cool.
I don't know.
You're not really at the conversation that he's responding to, huh?
No, you're not religious, right?
I don't think any one of us is religious at all or has ever.
No, I am actually Sikh.
Because I see.
A lot of inshallah, save, save Palestine.
There is no God but Allah and Muhammad is his prophet.
That's not Sikhism.
That's something else.
Actually, I don't know much about Sikhism.
Wait, no, you're right.
What am I thinking of Islam?
Sunni and she Sunni and Shiite.
Sunni and Shiite are like Islam branches that I'm thinking of.
OK, whatever.
Next voicemail is called Requiem for Lamal.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, what's up, PCP?
Here to ask some relationship advice
because that's been interesting.
Not been enough.
Not been enough of that.
Basically, what I'm wondering is I got this chick who's into me
and she wants to like date and stuff.
But gay.
I don't really want to because my life is like super busy with like
just going to college now and like all that kind of stuff.
So I don't.
Is it the pig?
Is the pig coming?
Are we going to hear the pig?
This is a bit.
This is like building to something.
Oh, my God.
Just fucking hit me with the pig already.
Just hit me with a fucking pig, you motherfucker.
It feels quite deliberate what he's fumbling with.
Like, this is not the sound of fumbling where you're actually just fumbling.
If it sounds like he's trying to fuck with the audio.
Are these like are these like old voicemails
that someone has like re-recorded and added
like microphone distortion to make them like inaudible?
I mean, potentially, but they would need access to the old voicemails
and we never provided them.
Did we?
I just had them on the show and that that would have our voices on them.
He might have picked some that we like largely didn't interrupt.
And then he added like the microphone fumbling sound
that like might cover up any like later interruptions that we made.
It's possible.
Uh, I don't know, man.
I feel like there's a joke that I'm not getting here.
OK, next one is trolled.
Emma, I pretty, pretty good.
You got me.
OK, next one is called Pony Lore.
Three, two, one, go.
Since major is going to be appearing on podcasts about now,
I want to ask this question.
Why is major the PCP?
I don't know what he's majoring.
Yeah, this is a bit.
What is this?
This is all the jokes.
And they're taking old voicemails
and then fumbling with a microphone so we can't hear them.
But why? Why would you?
Why would you do this?
Also, how?
That's the the question I would have.
How do they get access to these?
Or are they just fabricating voicemails and then doing it?
Very strange.
I think they might just be like
snipping the audible portion out of the old episodes.
Again, I don't know why you would you would do this.
OK, next one is called Henlo Corgo for Ben.
You're a straight edge turbo version.
Three, two, one, go.
Vaping. That was me hitting nitrous, by the way.
So in older episodes of the podcast,
you guys have had a fairly negative attitude towards drugs in general.
But I was just wondering if it's not true.
Anyone on the show on the episode
has any experiences that they, you know, with drugs that they haven't talked about?
I just figured that this would be like an interesting prompt for a story or two.
I don't know. I don't have a negative attitude toward drugs in general.
I just don't really like them myself.
I think I've explained that, like, I've smoked weed a few times
and sometimes it's been fine.
And other times it's made me feel uncomfortable,
paranoid, giving me like a weird body high sensation that I don't like.
A couple of times it's been really bad and very uncomfortable for me.
And I'm just not that into it.
I don't think I have ever I don't think I've had any like good
experiences with drugs that I haven't talked about on this show.
Yeah, I've talked about my experiences with drugs.
But I guess I can just mention I've only tried weed.
That's about it. A couple of times.
Smoking it and I took a bong, a bong or two.
And, you know, I got high once the first time I tried it, nothing happened.
And that's it was good.
I don't know whether I would turn it down if it was like,
hey, do you want to do some weed? I'll be like, yeah, all right.
But I would never go out of my way to purchase purchase.
I would never go out of my way to purchase drugs because it's like, I don't know.
Whatever. People say they need drugs to unwind and I never take them.
Maybe I need to unwind more often.
I don't know.
I don't I don't really get that unwinding.
I don't I like I like alcohol.
Alcohol is the only drug that I really like.
I guess that kind of helps me unwind.
I guess when I when I have a little the drink, I get a little more
loosey goosey, but it's not like, oh, I feel stressed.
Therefore, I will drink alcohol to feel less stress.
It's if I drink alcohol, I will enter a more
rambunctious state of mind, which sounds fun.
So I'll do it.
Yeah, I mean, when I feel stressed, I don't tend to like.
Like desire any specific thing.
I'm just sort of thinking about something and thinking about it is annoying.
And I'm like, oh, shit.
So I suppose like taking my mind off it would be beneficial.
I don't like drinking, though.
It's not that great.
It's all right on occasion.
But like I need to I need to get like the right amount.
And I don't know how much that is.
And I don't like buying things.
Sucks. I drink tea.
He's actually really relaxing.
Just a nice cup of tea.
That'll do that'll do me a little the time.
Sure. Make sense.
Uh, OK.
Next one is called I'll die.
Corp. Die another day.
Three, two, one, go.
What a great day for me.
CEO of Aldi Corporation spending the bustling Aldi
Corp business sector.
Nothing could possibly go wrong.
Oh, let me answer that.
Hello, see.
It's not funny.
It's a waste of my fucking time.
It's annoying.
You're not funny.
Don't do it.
Stop.
OK, next.
I just got to pee.
Look up.
Boo.
OK, Eleazar, cut this out.
Cut this part out.
I don't feel like entertaining these freaks during the wait.
Actually, leave in the part where I say I don't feel like
entertaining these freaks.
I want them to know what I think of them.
But cut out this part where I tell you to do that.
I'm Beck.
You're Beck, the musical artists of notes.
Yeah, I appeared on the new album,
the Gorillaz made song machine.
I was a feature guest artist.
That must have been that must have been such an honor for you.
No, I hate them, actually.
I fucking suck.
Damn, that's that's a bummer.
You're here first on the PCP.
Next voicemail is called when the link doesn't work
and you do a DIY solution.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, kids, who does this remind you of?
Colin, Angela's face.
OK, hold on.
Where does it hurt?
Ah, my stomach.
Do you know what this is?
I can't breathe.
I can imagine it's Hentai.
That would be like the most shocking thing to do.
Boo, next next voicemail.
No, not listening to it, garbage.
OK, next one is called three, two, one, go.
Wait, are you ready?
Yeah, this is too five, too five, two.
Oh, and there's a big, we got a new one.
Yeah, you're right. Okay. Two, five, two, five, two, three, two, one, go.
Just asking for your personal opinion.
Do you think Nate will ever come back?
I don't know.
I don't I honestly have no idea.
I'm not sure. I don't understand.
I get the feeling that he's just done with appearing online and speaking.
If it's not in a heavily edited context, but he does stream occasionally, so I don't know.
He just doesn't like the podcast.
But I don't know whether that's like a long lasting thing forever.
See, I know he doesn't like he's not in bad terms with us.
We're still talking occasionally.
Yeah, mostly about recon stuff.
But, you know, yeah, honestly, it's a fair question.
And I but I don't know.
I don't know if I have you put a gun to my head.
I would say probably yes, at least in a little capacity.
Like I feel like at some point, maybe he would want to come on to discuss
the rad concept, just like because it's been going on and being dealt with in the background.
Maybe I could be wrong.
I don't know if I were him.
Well, if I were him, I would be on the podcast, which I am.
So I don't get it.
I can't explain anything he does.
OK, next one is called three, two, one, go three, two, one, go.
Three, two, one, go.
Bay, three times in a row.
You know, I mean, that's a good one.
That's a good gag voicemail that I like.
This is like the first voicemail that I've liked this whole episode.
I hate all of you.
Next voicemail is called Jonathan slash John J.A.W.N.
Three, two, one, go.
Pump purple, no shirt, win.
I can't hear it.
Next one is called shut up and take the money.
I heard punk, so I want to listen.
Pump purple, no shirt, win.
Oh, I did make a punk purple, no shirt on Teespring.
But it was like, hold on.
I can't. I can't.
I want to listen one more time.
But that is what he says.
Oh, OK. All right.
Pump purple, no shirt, win.
Yeah, I've had one.
Let me just see.
T.
Fucking Teespring.
Gibo, Crit Store or something.
What the fuck was it?
I had it for a while and I never advertised it because I'm stupid.
But I have a few things on there.
Yeah, the no shirt, it was just sort of like.
It's just a black words on a purple t-shirt, so it doesn't look.
You can't really see it.
Yeah.
So I wanted to like make it a little more like stand outy so that when it's
printed printed on the shirt, you can make out the no.
And so I put like yellow and orange around it because that's the punk colors.
But yeah, but that's not the iconic shirt.
Yeah, so maybe I should just redo this and then you can buy it.
God, but Teespring sucks.
I hate making things on Teespring.
I don't. What's wrong with Teespring?
I think it's the least sucky.
It's the least sucky shirt site that I'm that I'm personally aware of.
I mean, maybe it could maybe it's improved since I last used it.
But is it Teespring or is it like, what is it called?
I don't know. I use Teespring.
Oh, no, it is Teespring.
Yeah, slash dash spring dot com.
You just put up get a PNG of the image.
It pretty much just automatically puts it on the shirt where it needs to be.
It's just the sort of like setting up like what
things it shows because like a general customer
when presented with every possible permutation,
like every single item of clothing that that thing could be on on one page,
they sort of get overwhelmed, like, oh, do I go for this
very similar to this other T-shirt T-shirt or this other T-shirt
that's slightly different with a different V like a V cut?
Or like people don't know what they what is the the right thing
so I like it to be easier and just like there's one T-shirt
and you can get it on a hoodie as well.
But like I have to go through the menus and like D list
all of the things that it's not that's like confusing.
What you should do and what you can do and what I have done is you can make one shirt
and then like choose like, OK, this shirt design is on this T-shirt,
this T-shirt, this T-shirt, it's positioned like so.
And then you can just duplicate that shirt settings to make a new shirt,
apply a new image, but it's automatically chooses, you know, the same items, right?
You can if you go to like your items menu and you look at all the listings you have,
there's a button for duplicate and you can just be like, yeah,
make it the same as that other shirt, but, you know, apply a new design to it.
It's pretty convenient. I recommend it.
Yeah, I got to spend like an afternoon or a whole day like doing that.
I probably like update my my lot of ghost design.
Because I made I made this store when I was like,
well, less artistically good than I am now.
And I think the lot of ghosts thing is just sort of not cool enough.
Or like it's just a lot of ghost thing on the on the Teespring.
I'll link it. Show me, show me, show me, show me, put it in general.
The Gibbo crit store creators spring dot com slash listing slash the Lord of Ghost product.
Oh, yeah, it's like, it's like, all right, I have like leggings.
Well, I mean, you can put them on leggings, which is in my opinion.
The obvious thing to do for a Lord of Ghost shirt is just to have a black shirt
that is an all over print with like the eyes and the teeth on it.
Yeah, I don't think I had the option to do it all over print when I made this one though.
But I did unlock it at some point.
They do. Yeah, they unlocked it.
Hey, I've never asked this, but is the way the Lord of Ghosts looks at all
based on that on that vapors page?
Do you know the one I'm talking about?
Oh, the one with the teeth.
Now, I think the one that question for.
Yeah, I'll post the image.
It's it's not like it's not OK.
It's it's from other things that have those that same sort of tooth design.
Yeah, yeah. OK, fair enough, fair enough.
I'm thinking of like I'm just looking at the shirt.
I'm looking or I was looking at the socks.
I was looking at the socks with the eyes and the teeth.
And I'm like, that reminds me of something.
Hmm. Hmm.
I don't know about the.
I bought a pair of those socks, but because.
I don't know, they stretch.
They they're not black.
Yeah, they're not actually black when you print on them,
even though it looks like that in the preview image, the the the socks you get.
They stretch a bit and then they're suddenly gray all over.
And it's like.
That's not. Yeah, I think I think an all over print.
No, no border, no like jagged border with like the white gradient.
I would just want all black articles of clothing with the eyes
and the teeth kind of just around, you know, because Lord of Ghosts is amorphous.
I don't know. That's what I would do.
Oh, you can get it on a baby onesie.
I can have my fucking baby and put these fucking teeth on him.
I just thought it would be funny to add that one.
Hell, yeah, the base.
You know what? I should get my own like brap leggings.
You look at the brap one at the bottom.
That's like the the Gibb and take like sweet bro and hella Jeff esque.
Yeah, yeah. JPEG fuckery. Of course. Of course.
I've sold a few of those shirts, but the leggings are fucking.
I know about brap.
I should buy these now that I wear leggings and that's the thing I do.
So before I was like, oh, I can't wear leggings.
Well, yeah, girl article of clothing.
But now I can.
Small, small mind, small mind, small imagination.
You had to expand.
You had to expand your reality to make it a possibility.
So cool. We've arrived. Yeah. Yeah.
Honestly, that's.
Honestly, yeah, it looked pretty cool.
The brap. I mean, the brap is iconic.
Everybody knows everybody loves the brap.
Let's do the next voicemail.
It's called shut up and take my mom take the money.
Three, two, one, go.
Man, I just really don't understand
why the gig editor was so hell bent on not getting paid.
Like, why?
Why don't you want to get paid?
Davoo got his Ben was advocating for it and they didn't like their right.
I don't know.
I mean, I just think it's kind of scummy
that the guys are kind of letting them work for free.
You're right.
They really should have put their foot down and be like, no,
like, let me fucking make it up to you.
I wish this I wish this wasn't going to go on for another 40
milliseconds because I have an answer right now.
Do this just because it's a kind of way to avoid
having to deal with headaches down the line or like bands getting too attached.
Yeah, to it, you know,
they keep going on about parasocial relationships,
but I guess it's parasocial convenient for bad bad when criticism good when money.
Fucking you were absolutely right to bully this person
into taking money to do their fucking job.
The reason why?
Anyway, PCP forever, Tom will never die.
Call me back. Thank you.
Thank you. The reason why, in my opinion,
the reason why they were hell bent on it was because
Yig had probably told them maybe in a kind of like sort of suggested
that like, oh, we'd love to have some videos edited,
but we can't really afford to pay anything.
And this person, you know, parasocial dick sucking lampry scum.
I don't think they would have done that.
I feel like this person like just assumed that it would be
it would be really cool if I if I did that for them.
And they just wanted to do it for free.
Like, it seems like it's possible like money never came up.
And then they was like, OK, we'll pay you.
No, no, no, no, well, they well, they claimed they claimed
that they had been offered money and refused, which sounds like a lie.
Honestly, I don't know if I believe that.
It's possible.
I mean, the I mean, the answer to the question is
creepy parasocial dedication to a weird
to a weird cult of personality run by a bunch of freak grifters.
That's the answer to all your questions.
When you get like stuff of stuff offered for you for free from people
who, you know, are parasocially like invested in your brand or yourself.
You got to you got to not just accept it.
Like the the times where it's acceptable to accept it is like when you're like
like with an actual friend and they're like, hey, let me pay for your drink.
Let me pay for for like this.
And it's like, oh, thanks.
You know, that's when you accept free shit is when they're actually friends.
This is this is this is this practice in general is just like mixing
mixing friendship and business, which is just not good.
Right. Yeah.
Like when you even with friends, it would be weird to like
to ask someone, you know, well, to do something,
hoping that they won't want to ask for compensation for it.
Because adults, they got to pay bills.
They have I would say valuable, you know, if you are like a noob, right?
If you're like a if you're like just starting like I want to start a YouTube channel,
I want to start making video essayist content.
And maybe your friend is a YouTuber, does that stuff?
Maybe is a bit of a professional about it.
If they maybe like said, hey, I'll edit a video for you,
like to help you get started or something.
I would think that was fine.
But in that case, it's like the person who's higher up on the totem pole,
doing something for free for someone who's lower down as a favor.
It's not, you know, someone
it's not some nobody being like, oh, let me edit videos for you for free.
Let me I'll do it for free. I don't care.
I don't even need to get paid.
I just oh, I'd love that.
Oh, I'd be I'd be on the channel.
Like that's gross.
That's gross to even even if they offer it, it's gross to accept it.
Because like it's just a fucked up dynamic there.
It's like we got like offers of people who wanted to edit.
The the PCP for free.
It was like, no, we're going to set up a payment and we didn't let them do it.
We didn't let them do it.
It would there were.
Yeah, there were people that said they wanted to like design the website for free.
And no, we yeah, you're you're right.
We've never people have made the offer like I'll do this for free.
And we've always been like, no, that's messed up.
And it will cause problems down the line.
And it will lead to dissatisfaction.
It will lead to strife.
It will lead to claims of, oh, you took advantage of me, which would be true.
And also, it just wouldn't be ethical, so we don't do it.
I don't know. It's bad.
I don't want to dwell on it any longer.
It's upsetting.
Next voicemail is called, I'm sure you care a whole lot.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm the caller who said the thing about the graves and the other real people.
I'm not offended. I'm sorry.
I said your podcast sucks.
It's still good.
No, it's OK. It sucks.
It's fine. No, podcasts suck.
I wasn't sure if you were being sincere or or whatever.
If you were like.
If you were like, shit, that's literally like my grandpa's grave
that you put your face on to flash when you talk on your podcast about Pokemon
and whatever, honestly, I would be offended.
And if you were like that, I might get it.
But I assume that like the odds of that were really low.
But like the outside chance existed, maybe.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. OK.
Next one is called the productive team, 17, three, two, one, go.
Hey, what's up, PCP?
Hey, it's your boy, 17.
And I knew it. I knew it.
I was just about to say pig.
Yep. Not funny.
I like still not funny.
I'm a culinary student.
Not a good bit.
You really you really went you really went all in on this bit.
Like this person was like he they be in the change I want to see in the world.
They listened to the episode on Friday and they were like,
you know, I have an idea for a bit, but it's going to take preparation
because I'm going to do this bit over the span of the whole week.
So they will be sprinkled throughout, right?
I'm going to plan this out and I'm going to commit to it
because I have a great idea for a funny bit that will really get the people talking,
that will really like get people's imagination going
and like be compelling to the audience in one way or another.
And they planned it out and they they they scheduled it in their mind and they were,
OK, I'll make a call this day, I'll make a call this day, I'll make a call this day
and it will all lead up to the big finale in the end.
And then it will all be a whole it'll be it won't just be one voicemail.
I will transcend someone who just makes a single voicemail.
I will be an arc.
I will have a character.
I will be known as the interrupting pig guy.
Everyone will appreciate it and they planned it out,
thought about it, decided that this was a thing that was worth doing.
They planned it out.
How are they going to do it?
Here's the plan.
And then they followed through and they executed on it with confidence.
And this is what we got.
And I hope that that paints a picture in your mind.
OK, enough.
I know it's going to come.
There's going to be more.
Got him. There's there's going to be more, though.
We're not even.
Honestly, I just I.
Part of me just wants to give up
because I know there's going to be another fucking interrupting pig.
What do we have?
We have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
We have like 15 more.
There's like at least four more pigs.
And I just feel exhausted.
I just feel tired and and sad.
Thinking about having to respond, having to react and have some opinion
the next time I hear the next time next time you just move on immediately.
The more you react, the more funny it might be.
I guess you're right.
I guess that's that's a more a more mature response.
I'm you're right.
I just I need to rise above it.
I need to rise above the pig.
OK, next voicemail is called a sincere apology.
Three, two, one, go.
It was then Ben St realized he should
have been auditing the voicemails all along.
Oh, I get it, OK.
After watching Prime Minister David Cameron fuck his mother's corpse for the
final time, young interrupting death pig realized his only question life was to
get revenge on the man who started it all notorious pig fucker.
Ben St killer of cops and dropper of balls.
If only his brother had been around and clean up the mess before it started.
That's a very long and convoluted way of saying, please don't play every voicemail.
OK, I get it.
I get I get the point that's being made.
So I can at least appreciate that the voicemails were bad on purpose.
But I mean, what am I what am I supposed to do now?
Now it's like you've got a choice.
You can continue the war by by by not doing what this person says and
continuing to not vet the voicemails and listen to all of them.
Thus, encouraging a retaliation of him to try and come back.
But it'll be like a war of attrition.
It'll be like how how how long will it be before he just runs out of energy to
make pig voicemails and and and how long will you be able to stand listening to them?
It'll be a cold war that interruptions.
Was that oblivion fall?
Is this is this an oblivion fall scheme?
I don't think so.
I don't think the voice was the same.
Also, I think he's British.
And I think it will be oblivion full is not British.
I have some reason to believe that.
Well, I don't know.
On the on the one hand, I appreciate that this person had a message to send.
And they and I and I comprehend what their point is.
They want the voicemails to be more vetted.
But I mean, if the point is.
Look how bad voicemails are.
This is what you get for playing them all.
I don't know.
I just feel like this this kind of thing is the problem.
The problem is that people make bad voicemails, which then clog the show
and waste our time and are annoying.
And they've sort of just.
I kind of feel like this almost illustrates that.
The voicemailers are the problem.
I mean.
I don't I don't want to vet them.
I don't want to vet them.
I just don't.
It would add it would add so much annoyance to my life.
And like, I would only remove a handful like I'm not.
Here's why you're wrong.
Here's what this voicemail is wrong.
I'm not removing this voicemail.
I'm not removing any of them.
And I wasn't going to, even though they're bad.
The only ones that I remove are ones that are like really offensive.
And I just don't want anything.
I don't remove voicemails just because they're bad.
So if I vetted the voicemails, I wouldn't even remove the ones that you don't like.
I just I just wouldn't.
To me, like part of the point is that anyone can say anything.
Yeah.
And also if you vetted them, if you if you yeah.
You ever vetted them would like the excitement, like a surprise.
If there was something like surprising, they wouldn't have that recorded for the actual show.
Like someone else would need to vet them if anything.
And then if you need to trust that they have the right idea of what would be good.
And nobody really knows because based on the conversation that was had previously,
it could be relevant or completely pointless.
It's just hard to know.
It's hard to know ahead of time what's going to make for the best show.
Obviously, some are just like really bad, but we can just skip through them.
Like we do.
Just make a make a conversation out of it anyway, which is the point.
Voice Mailer, if if you liked Nate's methodology of only picking a handful of
voicemails out of many and only and only listening to those, I can't begrudge you that.
But that's not how I do things.
And you making a bunch of deliberately bad protest voicemails doesn't change my mind.
Good effort.
Don't do it again.
OK.
Next one is called Are You Moving In With Me Yet?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
So I was listening to the bonus episodes on Patreon.com slash the progress
managers or whatever the fuck it is.
What?
And I was listening to like the last one Nate was on.
And I won.
I realized why people miss Nate so much other than his juicy boy pussy.
It's he was a good host.
He hosted the podcast really well.
You have grown into that ability.
You are you have grown so much in the last year.
And I just wanted to compliment you.
Generous.
Is when will your boy pussy ripen to his levels is, I guess, the big coming.
I'm like, I'm like, I like feeling like phobic about the pig.
I'm feeling like anxiety over the pig.
I don't know.
Thanks.
Boy pussy.
Yes, it's ripe.
Come and pluck it.
OK, whatever.
Thank you for.
This is I think I'm going to become better at hosting the procrastinators.
I'm doing a great job this episode.
I'm really hitting it out of the park.
I mean, somebody's going to do it.
Somebody's going to say hello and welcome to the show.
And that's you.
It's it's a tough job, but it puts food on the table.
OK, next voicemail is called Nate fuckers are cringe.
Three, two, one, go.
True.
Hey, everybody, it's other Riley again.
Now, listen up.
The fuckers are fucking cringe.
OK, the true chat of the PCP, who everyone should want to fuck
has been under our noses for all this time.
He's a man who has been long lost to us here at the PCP.
Jeff, mother's basement.
I want to fuck.
He's so flaccid.
Bring back Jeff so we can all fuck him in the ass.
That's it.
OK, all right.
I mean, Jeff is a large human being.
There's a lot of ass to go around, probably.
There's a lot of there's a lot of them.
There's more, more.
He's so more for the push in.
He's so big.
Oh, the next one.
There's an Imgur link.
I think it's Gib fan art.
Huh?
Oh, oh, Pog.
Is this Pog?
Oh, it is.
Wow.
Right. OK.
What do we show this on screen?
Eliza, what do we have?
We have.
The Ray Club.
Bucklebell spearfishing chick,
hazard, casual and maximal.
Wow, he's out.
I don't know what I don't understand.
Sharktooth scarf.
That is an error.
Is this Errori's art?
Is this an Errori piece?
I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
Errori has quite a distinctive style
from what I've seen.
That's that's true.
That's true.
Perfect for grabbing some lunch.
I don't I don't know who this is by.
This is by apology.
This is professional advice from Apologies at floodpunk.gov.
What the fuck?
All right, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
I knew it.
Feministly.
Spicy.
How does it how does it feel that someone is writing
spoken word poetry about outfits you could wear?
It feels pretty good.
Pretty base.
It is.
Does it make you soy face?
Yeah, a little bit.
Oh, it's it is kind of true
that confidence is key.
But I feel like these the pants as hat and the sharktooth scarf.
I mean, obviously, they're a little crazy of examples.
I don't think I would take a fishing spear to go shopping.
But, you know, anything's possible.
Perfect for.
Well, you don't you don't go shopping with a spear or do you?
I thought you grab lunch by stabbing a fish.
I go into the I go into the supermarket.
I go to like the raw meat section.
And I you go to the lobster meat and you just skewer one.
Yeah, through smash through the glass,
like stab the roast chicken against the wall.
I grab it and I eat it raw on the end of the stick.
I don't know why I don't cook it because that'll kill me.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Where was I? OK.
Next one, I think this is also from Arari.
It's called profuse apologies to the PCP
and the community for everything about time.
OK, three, two, one, go.
I must have all the guys for every one of these.
They are all mistakes like cheeseburgers with no cheese.
I'll make it up to you with a happy meal and fries.
We're heading to McDonald's now.
If you'd like something to leave a comment down below,
I'll have you ordered you in six weeks or so.
I know happy meal won't erase these crimes.
So feel free to get some milkshakes on my dime.
Give me give me a McDonald's song.
Give me give me a give me a McDouble.
Give me two McDoubles, throw away the bun.
Give me a and a and a Coke Zero, please.
Give me a chicken legend with the spicy mayo
and and the large fries and a fucking vimto or whatever.
What are those nice rhymes? Nice rhyme.
Binto chicken legend.
What are you fucking talking about?
It's it's the British menu.
Chicken legend is my favorite chicken.
Chicken legend. Yeah.
What are you telling me that in the Europe,
they call it a Royale cheese?
I've never heard of such a thing.
I mean, let me get a very small image
that is is not as good as other images that a chicken legend.
I'm just curious.
What is the American equivalent of a chicken legend?
I don't know. What?
I don't even know if they have this.
I don't even know if they have this one in America.
I like it because the chicken is like different
from like a chicken burger, whereas like
like a just a plain chicken breast that's been grilled.
This is got like it's a big flat chicken nugget
on a bun on a whole wheat bun.
This is making me hungry.
This is making me hungry, though.
And it makes me hungry. Damn it.
Arari, you fucked us.
You did this to us.
You should apologize profusely to the PCP
and the community for everything.
Then you did. So good job.
OK, next one is called have a point.
Three, two, one, go.
Guys, if you're going to leave voicemails about Trixie,
have a point.
This isn't directed at A1 in specific,
but I've noticed some voicemails are just like,
Oh, Trixie bad.
Oh, I'm all right, guys.
And like, yeah, we get it.
Don't waste your breath.
Have a point, please.
What do you think you're going to make a voicemail in general?
What do you think you're accomplishing
if you're just mindlessly raging at Trixie and Yeeg Studios
for no reason?
Like, who do you think you are?
Ben Sainz or something?
You got to fucking you got to you got to quit the quit that.
You got to be you got to focus.
You got to have you got to strike with precision, like lightning.
Oh, you know, it's really cool. Yeah, you say that as a joke.
And you do it all the time, though, and you know it's bad.
Well, the joke is that I'm being self aware.
The joke is that I'm being self aware.
Well, it doesn't make it good, Ben.
You got to you got to slow down.
You got to. Oh, my God, I'll kill you.
I'm going to fucking kill you.
I said before you got on the show
that I don't have anything else to say about the situation.
You said the thing about it.
Well, I say it when I get voicemails about it.
Oh, before the editor thing out, whatever.
I don't care who cares.
I'm not I'll quit.
I'll quit when I feel like it, which is now.
But not because you told me to,
not because anyone told me to stop talking about it,
because I wanted to me.
That was a really good idea, Ben.
I hope you stick to it.
Yeah, you're right.
Here we really show me if you stick to it
and and and like that would really own me.
Absolutely.
Completely 100 percent totally.
Yeah, you'd be there would be no coming back from it.
Yeah, I guess I just have nothing else to say other than, yeah, true.
Next one is called guest time three, two, one, go.
Keep the guests coming, guys.
They're great, lower person PCP is usually kind of dry.
Don't get a mumkey, he sucks.
Fair, based, fair and true, based.
I think I think Kazi wants to be a guest again.
I told her she could sometime.
Well, that's nice.
I like other than that.
Wait, Kazi's good.
There was a.
Was there someone else we were thinking of asking
or was I thinking of I'm I thinking of the Cato guys?
I think that might have been the last one I think somebody
somebody mentioned you should get the guy from Noita
who made Noita on the show.
I don't know.
I don't even know who those guys are.
I don't know if they do podcast.
I think they're probably kind of a big deal.
Well, now that they've had a very successful game
or at least a Disney.
I mean, they were lots of people.
They were already true.
But I mean, I think they were already kind of big deals before
because they made like the falling sand game.
These these guys were professional developers like before.
No, yeah.
They then it's so I don't know.
I feel like they're I feel like they're a little bit too big time.
Maybe I don't even know.
But I mean, again, the fact that I don't know their names means
maybe they're not maybe they're just humble devs who go unappreciated.
Um, next voicemail is called three, two, one, go to the polls.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, Ben, you could save like 20 minutes every episode
if you didn't start every voicemail with three, two, one, go.
Just something to think about, Benjamin.
I mean, it has utility because you say three, two, one, go.
You press the button and that tells
Eleazar exactly when to place the voicemail into the timeline.
I say it so that you know exactly when to start it.
I say it so Eleazar knows exactly when to say.
And I think that it probably has utility to the viewer.
Well, no, I guess they probably don't need to tell me when the voicemail is starting.
I mean, you're right. It's yeah.
I just feel like it's a useful thing to do and it doesn't take that much time.
So I'm probably going to keep doing it.
I'm sorry.
Next one is called TonyProGrammo.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, boom, Jim and Saint.
Hey, I'm here to talk to you about your creative process.
Spooky. Hey, you know, like you feel bad
because you're doing all the art assets and you should be doing the hard program and work.
You got to really like kind of like think about your project
and like what are the necessary steps?
Where are the time it's going to like be taken to get done?
And you know, you just need to make sure that like, hey,
if you're still like chipping away at the the time that you allocated to like,
you know, get your artwork done, you know, you shouldn't beat yourself up
for not doing the programming.
I think I said this, you know, honestly, doing that kind of stuff.
I think it's really good to like allocate an hour or two
where you just learn the like the framework you're going to do
and like not touch the thing yet.
You touch a thing you don't care about because that's going to be cursed
because you don't understand it right, you know, that's going to be a cursed program.
But, you know, after you get that out of your system,
then you take the logic and stuff you learn from that and you put in your real one
and then you don't have to deal with all that.
First of all, first of all, I said, I think I said last time that I
don't feel that bad, that it feels bad in the moment.
They're like, oh, I'm drawing when I should be programming.
But I know intellectually that it all must get done.
So I don't really feel that bad when I step back and think about it.
As for the like learning before I try implementing,
I'm not saying this is the right way to do it, but I treat coding
basically like chiseling a sculpture
and that I basically will write a little bit of code
execute the program, see what happens.
And if it is a little bit more like what I wanted it to be,
then it was before, then I keep that code.
And then and if it's different from what I wanted to be, then I deleted
and try it again and I iterate that process over and over until the thing
gradually becomes more and more and more like how I want it to be.
And then when it's close enough, I say, I'm done.
I wrote the code. I did it.
So I am like, I'm my whole process is constantly
just like tinkering with the thing, doing live experiments on the project itself.
I don't know what will happen, but I mean,
I always have the I have the control Z button at the ready
in case I do something completely catastrophic.
I mean, it's kind of like it's a little bit like how I always say
that the best like drawing practice I ever got was drawing Vapors one.
I just kind of did it and just kind of kept doing it over and over until it looked good.
The the programming, the game is the same way.
I just kind of start writing and if it looks bad,
if it's performing badly, if it's fucking up,
I just kind of rewrite and rewrite and tinker with it until it works.
And then I guess it's done.
And then I start that again on another piece of it.
Yeah, so I'm very haphazard.
And I don't plan anything.
And I think it's good because planning too much is real bad trap to fall into.
True anything.
OK, yeah, next voicemail is called Tim Timbuk to three, two, one, go.
That's crazy.
Me and Ben just kept smoking and drinking and smoking and drink.
It's all we did.
We smoked and drink the whole night away.
It was great.
Welcome, Ben, to the new house.
Is this Trixie back in the day?
Welcome, viewers, to Ben.
Is that Trixie? I think so.
It sounds weird.
Like it doesn't sound like I remember her voice sounding.
I thought it wasn't her.
But it sounds like she's saying this is when I moved into the digi house
back like before Radcon.
Two, I think.
I think I don't know.
Anyway, what's what's the point?
OK, that's a that's a blast from the past.
But what's what's your point?
OK, next one, Johnny's nothing.
Johnny Tsunami, three, two, one, go.
Hello, PCP.
My name is Johnny Tsunami.
I'm from Tokyo in Japan.
I don't like what's happened to the podcast.
You need to bring back the best guy ever.
He's a smart guy, a tremendous guy.
He's the only one of you with a triple vision like you.
Many people are saying this, Johnny.
He's a real loser.
I'm never listening to the podcast again.
And you need to go to church or something, no watch.
Johnny, no, come back.
How can we how can we pander to you?
I mean, Johnny Tsunami clearly represents a large segment of our audience
because he's saying what they're all thinking.
I wish he would just tell us what he wants to see
instead of just so cruelly, callously excommunicating us like this.
It's not like such a man's man.
So such an alpha Chad voice.
Sounds sounds sounds like someone who we should listen to.
It's this guy sounds like he knows a thing or two about public speaking
and changing hearts and minds.
And maybe we can learn something.
He knows the secrets of charisma, which we which we so clearly lack.
OK, next next voicemail is called a realization about Radcon.
Three, two, one, go.
So I just realized something that nobody has brought up in regards to Radcon.
If you guys do have another Radcon,
who are you going to get to fill up the PCP Royal Rumble?
Because like Nate is barely there.
Trixie is gone.
Mage is gone.
Davoo is gone.
And Jesse isn't coming back.
And that like cuts out a large swath of just characters that you guys can use.
And like, can you guys even use now?
I mean, there's like Ben, Tom and give, obviously.
Yeah, this is dumb. Vincent.
Pump. Yeah.
Vincent was in all the past ones.
Zoomy. OK.
If this were to happen, only seven.
And like, I really can't do so many other.
I have only I can only think I can only think of seven characters.
Like, did you really want to bring up this old joke?
Are you going to use anybody from the egg?
Like, would you be OK?
That's it. All right.
Hmm. Geez.
I can only think of seven characters that.
So if you did it, you'd have to do all these,
make all these really stupid decisions that sound dumb when I say them.
And you're not going to do that.
Are you? Short answer. No.
We would just think of more than seven.
I don't know. It wouldn't be that hard.
I mean, I have a lot of characters.
I have Red Man and Gun Girl who were in that endless war rumble at one point.
That was fun. I mean, if we we.
Yeah, we have there's plenty of goofy characters
we could draw upon from lore.
And if we needed more, I mean, in the past,
we've always just come up with some bullshit characters on the spot.
And they've just been funny.
They've just sort of become little short term memes of their own.
We just do that.
I mean, really, Bernie Sanders was a competitor last last time.
And you know what? He outperformed expectations.
He was a champion.
I mean, I feel like a red con with just three people
would be such a different feeling experience that we may as well not
do not even call it that. Not even.
Yeah, we wouldn't call it that.
We wouldn't have to do everything
that has ever been done at a red con before.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like the rumble, maybe we don't even do one.
Maybe we just play other games.
Maybe because a rumble does feel like a like a group like screaming at the TV.
That's one of those things.
A rumble would be different with fewer people.
Yeah, it would be it would it would be lower energy,
which I think would probably harm it.
Harm of viewing experience is unfortunate.
Yeah.
Yeah, the point is we wouldn't have to do that.
But if we did, I'm sure we could think of some
whatever to fill it out if we needed to.
There's no reason we can't have like characters of other.
All we would do if we had Action Giraffe or something,
would that really like break immersion?
Because Nate wasn't there.
I think it would be OK to have Action Giraffe.
I mean, at the end of the day,
if we did something like that, you know, a new PCP,
you know, three band rad con or whatever,
we would just do whatever seemed fun.
And if it seemed fun to do a rumble, we would do that.
Or if we felt like doing something else, we just do something else.
We just do whatever seemed fun.
Yeah. Yeah.
Next voicemail is called Regarding Archives three to one go.
Hey, Ben, I just wanted to say that I agree with you on the archive thing.
I've seen this mentality go around where people who want to venture
into new things think that their old works have to suffer
and they should just delete them, which I highly disagree with.
One example is Sue Slut.
She used to make mostly death grips mashed
up with a hotline having stuff.
And then once she once she transitioned into making like original music,
she did delete all her other mashups, all her previous work.
And I just think I just don't I just don't like that mentality.
I don't think I don't like it either.
I don't think in order for your
in order for your new work to shine, that your old work has to suffer.
That's why the archive exists.
If the people who discovered Sue Slut
for her death grips mashups can now find a new appreciation
for her original works.
But I mean, they may not get the chance
because I mean, they may not get the chance to look into her.
Your previous works, because they're all gone.
And all we have are reuploads.
It's a bit stupid, but I hate it.
Just because to anyone out there, just because you want to venture out
into new stuff does not mean your old work has to suffer.
That's all I want to say.
I mean, if you want to change direction
and maybe you don't want to be associated with your old work,
I mean, you could always start a new venture under a new name, right?
And you wouldn't have to destroy it.
You could just start making new stuff under a new name.
I I think that that I mean, there's somewhat of a precedent
that like if you are like you have like stuff that doesn't fly in other
like circles, if you become like a like what was his name?
Joji, like Pink Guy, filthy Frank, filthy Frank.
He was Pink Guy and his Pink Guy stuff is gone, I think.
Or it's like it's it's like unofficially reuploaded.
The original stuff is like gone.
And now he's a more traditional musical guy doing music
and he's getting all big like stuff.
And it's like Pink Guy would have, I don't know, hurt his career.
I guess is what he thought.
I don't. But I mean, I don't think it would have
because everybody knows he's the filthy Frank guy,
even if he deletes all his stuff.
He's still everybody knows filthy Frank and everyone knows who it is.
And it's him.
I don't understand what deleting it accomplishes.
It's the I think it's just the public stuff.
If you make it so that it's like unlisted,
but there is a way to access it if you want to find it.
Even if it's behind a paywall,
I would I would much rather that than just it being gone
and and like people having to like reupload
scraps here and there.
I think I really think that an official channel to these things
is always appreciated, even if you're if you cringe at it
and you really don't want people to see it.
Even if you prefer it to be like just in an unlisted playlist
for people who who want to do the digging and find it, I guess.
I would say like the only time that I think it makes sense.
And I would be like, I, yeah, I agree to like delete something
would be if if you think it's like immoral,
like you made something that is like harmful.
Yeah. And in that case, I mean, I think even that like
99 percent of the time it would you wouldn't even if you just paywall
that hit it, made it only accessible to people.
I mean, I think that that would probably be fine
in terms of like mitigating harm that a thing could do.
I really believe in archiving and like preserving history
warts and all.
And like, yeah, maybe you cringe at a thing you made in the past,
but it's such like a stupid trap
that so many people fall into so many artists fall into it,
where they're like, oh, I'm embarrassed by that thing I made before.
I delete it.
And like everyone knows that that's wrong, right?
Like everybody knows that, oh, artists don't appreciate their own works
the way that the fans do.
Like the fans like a thing.
And it's never the thing that the artist likes the best, right?
It's never like that.
So everyone should know that you shouldn't delete your old stuff
even if it's embarrassing.
But people do it anyway and I fucking hate it.
Like it's dumb.
It's conventional wisdom that you shouldn't do that.
But everybody fucking does.
It's terrible.
It should be illegal, is what I'm saying.
Yeah, I'm more sympathetic than you, I think, to the artists.
But I also I really appreciate when I can go to like a YouTuber
and go back to the very first video.
And it is actually the very first video.
I could see how like they've changed over time
because I know, like, you know, maybe the past things were said
could be said on something that would be like, oh, we can't say that today.
But like, I know that that's in the past
and that shouldn't necessarily reflect on the present day.
If I know that people do react like that sometimes,
like things get brought up and it's like, ah, you said this 10 years ago.
Fuck you.
And it does become a bit of an issue, but it's so minor in the grand scheme of things.
I mean, but like if people want to do that, if people want to do that,
they can find your stuff and they can.
Yeah, we're talking about like cancer culture, witch hunting,
if they can find your stuff and try and witch hunt you for it,
even if you delete it, like unless there's literally no record for it,
which like is very unlikely.
I mean, I think part of it is just like getting rid of the ease
by which people can search through your history
if they have to go digging even a little bit more than just scrolling down
and in a Twitter thread or or a YouTube.
Well, that's why I would.
That's why I would say like just just
privating or paywalling or unlisting is probably what you should do.
Yeah, most of the time.
Yeah.
I think she had like her old her old like a pony content
like in a in a Patreon
and like an unlisted playlist, I think.
Yeah, I wonder if that's existing still.
I wonder if that like went with the rest of her content.
I just I just don't know.
I just don't know. Throw it on the trash.
I throw it on the trash. Who cares?
Who cares if people liked it? Fuck it.
I don't like it anymore.
It's not even about whether people liked it.
I just like things to be like, I don't know, the records to be available.
Not for any specific reason.
It just makes me feel good to know that it's still there.
Yeah, no, totally.
I totally agree.
Just even even if I don't care about the content, I just don't.
If you if a thing can be archived, it's just good.
It's just good to have a record of stuff.
I just like that for its own sake.
I hate to think about stuff being like forgotten or like deleted.
And like it's like it's like no one will ever see it again.
It's like it never existed.
But it's so sad. It's a sad thought.
There's like you could either make it so that people
dredging up the past does not become as much of a problem
such that people feel compelled to hide things or you could just hide things.
I feel like, I don't know, advocating for people to not.
Give so much of a shit that their past is like still there.
Like it's people, yeah, I guess it's a bit of an appeal to like, you know,
I don't know what it's an appeal to.
But like saying that people reupload stuff.
So therefore it's OK is not necessarily a good argument.
But I I think it would be a better
like world if stuff being archived was not a problem.
Hmm, like if it ever causes a problem,
I think it would be better for the problem to be solved
rather than for more things to be hidden.
Right. Yeah, I mean, I agree.
I think if in a perfect world, I think
if in the past you said some shit, I don't know,
you said some racially insensitive shit and someone is like,
hey, this guy in his old video said some racially insensitive shit.
I think the best resolution there is you go, yeah,
I did say some racially sensitive shit.
I don't agree with that anymore.
I apologize for saying it.
Let's let's let's all let's all agree that what I said before was wrong.
And I don't stand by it anymore.
Like that's good.
Yeah, that's that's better than like deleted pretend you never said it.
In my opinion, generally.
And then sometimes people would say, well, if you really take it back,
you should get rid of it, you should take it down.
And then you and then you go, well, you know, I pay all that, you know,
I unlisted it, but, you know, I don't want to erase history.
I don't I don't believe in erasing history.
I do. I really I feel like some people might
maybe some people might say that and like sort of a bad faith attempt
to be like, oh, I don't have to actually, you know, be critical of media.
I believe I don't believe in erasing tearing down that Confederate statue.
Why are you erasing history?
But I promise when I say it, I mean it in a good way.
True, you know, right.
Yeah, I I feel strongly about this, mostly because
a lot of the time I would watch YouTube poops in like 2008.
And I love those things that make lots of like favorites list.
There was only a favorites list and I put so many of them in there.
And because of content ID becoming a thing later,
a lot of those like had clips from stuff in them.
They got taken down, channels got deleted.
People didn't bother archiving because nobody expected that to be a problem.
And there's just so many cool things that are gone.
Yeah. Only occasionally does it doesn't as a YouTube pooper
reupload their stuff.
Imagine being a professional YouTube pooper.
Yeah, professional pooper.
And yeah, I like genuinely respect that as an art form.
It's my favorite.
So fucking funny and sad.
The sad that's so like volatile and so easily like erased.
Oh, no, my headphones died a few moments later.
Hey, you there?
I'm OK. OK, I can hear you. Sorry, I'm back.
Well, you didn't miss anything.
I finished my sentence.
OK, sweet.
Next voicemail.
Yeah, sure.
Next one is called follow up on the archive three, two, one, go.
Also, would you would you delete history
because it's quote unquote outdated?
Yeah, I don't think so.
Right. Oh, this information is outdated.
Oh, it's not relevant.
It's not true anymore. We got to delete.
Obviously, it was written in the past.
It's an archive.
It's an archive of information describing the past.
I mean, you can update it if you want, but there's no.
Yeah, I hate I don't understand the the mindset of like
the information is out of date.
Therefore, it should be deleted as opposed to updated
or just archived and preserved.
You know, you know, it would be like a like a smart
like marketing strategy is just to have your own channel
called your channel name archive and then put things on there.
And so like if you take them off your main channel,
which is like your publicly facing forward like,
ah, this is my brand and this is what I am about.
And all of the things you don't like anymore are gone.
But you have the archive channel
and you can still get the ad revenue from it.
But you don't tell anyone that I mean, that would be a that would.
I mean, you'd still you'd still lose the views.
You'd lose all the all the old like metrics and stuff.
It would you would hurt viewership for sure.
It would be better than just getting rid of it.
Yeah, true. Yeah, true.
And I mean, it's archiving is good generally.
So yeah, I would say if you if you must, if you must,
if you feel that you must remove something from your main
content delivery vehicle, you must distance yourself from this content.
Sure. Putting it somewhere else is better than
getting rid of it pretend it doesn't exist.
OK, next one is Janess.
Three, two, one, go, Ben,
you mentioned weeks ago that you weren't interested in watching our taxi.
So I have to ask, what is your reference library like
for the champion and the vapors?
I think you would have playing real life examples for future
volumes of the papers, but are you just going to draw influence
for no time for the rest of the champion storyline?
What the fuck?
Yes, I'm just going to draw.
From Noida.
Um, is the is the implication here that if I don't feel like watching Odd Taxi
that I have a narrow have a shallow pool of influences and my work will stagnate?
Is that is that the implication?
Yes. OK.
Um, I don't know.
I will accept this and just do exactly what you said.
Draw from one pool of one influence only.
I I mean, I don't think the fact that I am not interested in Odd Taxi.
I mean, I think the general criticism that I am not broadly read or broadly
I don't consume broad enough media might be true.
I I reject the idea that
it matters whether I watch Odd Taxi or not.
So I'll just respond to the broader criticism.
Um.
Uh, I just I I do I do I mean, I do agree with it.
I feel like I am not broadly consumed.
It's probably a problem.
It's probably something I should work on.
I don't know what else to say.
I should watch more stuff, read more stuff.
Um, but it's so boring.
Yeah, media sucks.
I feel similar, like I'm like, oh, I got to draw from a large pool of influences.
But I feel like that's like a task rather than I don't know,
want something I want to do.
I feel like, yeah, if I actually want to draw from influences,
it would have to be something that I am influenced by naturally
rather than just like, I guess I could take something from this.
I hate it and I don't like it, but, you know, it's different.
Like I should I should be I should consume some media because I want to,
right, like because I want to read it or watch it because it appeals to me
or because I feel like I want to know what it says.
And I and just.
There's very little, there's very little that makes me want that.
Uh, it's like, you know, the the the media that you choose to consume
or you're influenced by, like you get into is not always going to be.
I don't know, the same medium than the one you create in.
Yeah, you watch movies and TV shows and play video games and read comics.
These all all these all will influence your art in different ways.
And I just think I think it's fine just to be into a few things at a time.
Like, oh, I'm watching Buffy.
That's obviously going to have some influence in what I do next
just because it's so good.
And I really like the storytelling and everything about it.
True.
Uh, I mean, this is like a people when you when you read like biographies of like artists,
they all it's pretty common that they're like, oh, yeah, this this mangaka
was like heavily influenced by like, you know, the Hollywood blockbusters
that they grew up watching or, you know, this this this game dev
was like really inspired by like a certain genre of literature that they were really into, right?
It's it's not always that like, oh, you know, you you got to read a lot of comics.
I think that's probably not bad.
It's like a misunderstanding of that is is to hear, oh, my favorite artists,
they were influenced by various things.
Therefore, I should go out of my way to try and find stuff to be influenced by
so that I can be as good as them.
And I have to have a certain number of things that I'm interested in.
And even though it's true that the best way to find like stuff
that will really appeal to you is to just look around a lot is to experience
a lots of different things.
The misunderstanding is that you need to constantly be looking
and drawing from a wider range as possible,
even though you might not give a shit about most things.
Like, I feel like it's it's a means to an end.
And the end is just to find something you like.
Once you find something you like, you can draw influence from that
and maybe a couple other things.
You know, it doesn't have to be like if it's just from one thing,
then you're obviously going to be limited in what you can create
because you're not drawing from a wide, you know, thing.
I think it's it's a balance.
You shouldn't be focused too much on just
doing things because you're supposed to.
You should also just listen to your heart and get interested in things
that literally just interest you on a whim.
You should do maybe hell, yeah, a bit of both.
Based, based.
Yeah, it's like.
You can't you can't force it like if you if you don't
if you're not if you're not engaged, if you're not interested,
you can't like force yourself to like read a book, watch a show
and then get something out of it.
Like it's got to engage you, which is almost like something that it
you can't choose. It's just it just happens to you.
It's like falling in love.
Yeah, I personally you don't choose it.
I personally find it very engaging to look through all of those indie games.
Yeah, in the Palestinian aid bundle.
Me too. That's what I almost said before.
Like, yeah, I'm not that I just look at odd taxi and I'm like,
yeah, it looks nice, not interested.
But I look at some of these, you know, a couple of thumbnails
and descriptions of this this Palestinian aid game list.
Catch my eye and I go, that could be interesting.
I just kind of want to see what's what's going on in there.
That that like bundle is like really useful
in that in that specific way of like opening your minds to new possibilities.
So you play one game, of course, of course, you will only know that one game.
You might know it very well.
But like it's like a shotgun, you know, you're shooting a lot of pellets.
And you some of the pellets hit the target.
I don't know where that metaphor is going.
Yeah, but me, I have a sniper rifle
and my sniper rifle is trained on one target and it always hits
going with a bullet going a million miles an hour.
And the target is Noida and I'm just pumping precision rounds every day
directly into nowhere else like like like like you shoot the target.
And then the target like blood splatter is your art.
And if you shoot one thing, you get like exactly the same thing out.
But it's sort of splattered.
So it's slightly different.
Ben St. version. Oh, yeah.
That's yeah, it's just that's the natural progression
is I just have to make my own version of Noida.
That's the only it's the only thing I'll know how to do eventually.
Hell, yeah.
Phantom's revenge is basically just Noida too.
She that's the last voice that's it.
That's it. We're we're done and some.
With the start of this one, I was like, shit, it's a Ben cast.
This is going to be short. I'm going right into the voicemails.
We're going we're be lining.
This is going to be a one hour episode.
Here we are at the three hour mark again.
Here we are in the future.
Here we are in the future and it's bright.
It's bright because the episode's over.
Finally. All right.
We'll go home. Any last words?
Look out for a future Lord of Ghost Kickstarter at some point.
True. Get hyped for that.
Save up some some coins.
Keep them in your purse.
In the meantime, get ready to throw my way.
And in the meantime, you'll be laughing about it.
In the meantime, check out the Kato anthology Kickstarter is still going on now.
If you got some some of those spare coins in your pocket, throw them at them.
Throw them at them hard directly in their eyes.
Blind them and patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes
and stuff and and also access to the Minecraft server for shekels for heckles,
which we do sometimes.
You also can become a void.
Thaumaturge like myself and master the the energies of the rift.
And I guess I guess that's it.
I guess that's it.
I guess we're going to send a voicemail.
Send a voicemail, but only if it's good.
No sending bad voicemails just to prove a point, because I don't care.
I'm not available to be persuaded, so don't try and get clever with it.
OK, that's the end of the episode.
Goodbye.