Let's go!
Let's go! That's it, that's the start.
Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We got me, Ben Saint, we got Gibbontake back from wherever the fuck,
and we got our special guest, Oblivionfall, who I'm sure most of you know.
Welcome to the show, OF.
Yeah, jeep.
How you, how you done? How you, how you living?
Half dead, as usual. Working myself to the grave every day, except this weekend I finally took a break and played Minecraft.
That's good.
Would you, would you like to introduce yourself to anyone who doesn't, who isn't familiar with your, with your uvra?
Oh my god. I've been like, I've been PCP adjacent for like almost seven years, I guess,
and I don't even think anyone was aware until very recently.
Like, oh jeez, like I saw it, I've been, oh man.
Wait, the PCP hasn't been around for seven years, hasn't it?
I know, like this goes back to the,
Maybe if you count, if you count like pre-PCP stuff.
This goes back to the pony days, like I remember watching Tommy Oliver, Anthony C, Cantalot Wedding Review,
like way back, and there's been a whole, there's been a whole bunch of characters who I have heard mentioned in your circle,
or even on the PCP every so often, it's like, oh hey, I live compostable a lot.
Lamal, or you know, FNGR, Keyframe, you know, Misanthropony, et cetera.
And like, I've been around those people.
These shadowy figures from the Misty Pat.
Oh, were you, were you ever in the Rift Cafe?
No, luckily, I don't think I ever was.
However, a lot of people...
You missed out on a real part.
I had a lot of friends in there, though, and a lot of them spoke to you guys,
and I'm like, man, I'd like to talk to you guys.
Why do all my friends talk to you, but I don't talk to you?
And that's how it was for years.
It's impossible, it's impossible.
I'm very hard to reach emotionally.
Yeah, either, there's two ways to get in contact with us.
Either be like a terrible, my little pony reviewer, Sokara 2014,
or be an incredible god of other worldly ability,
and then put, like, references to our things in animations and videos you make.
Right, right, that's the only other way to do it.
That's the only other way, and I found it.
I uncovered it myself.
You put, right, you had, you had a voicemail.
What was the song about cum?
What's the song about cum?
Your cum won't last, the sequel to the cum zone, I think.
Oh no, there was another one, there was a third.
They were free, they were free.
The cum zone is not even like, actually, maybe it's the first one.
No, I put PCP references in a couple of DA games music videos.
They're a channel with like a million sub scuba divers who,
they got popular doing like FNAF songs and let's plays and stuff,
and they branched out to a whole bunch of other like nerd core stuff,
and I was friends with that guy since he had like 200 subscribers,
and so when I was leaving the pony fandom,
when that, you know, collapsed and I'm like, I gotta escape in 2016,
they hired me on to make some music videos,
and I put PCP references in a few, in a few of those,
and then I made the cum zone, which is all PCP stuff all the way through,
like you see the broth, you see the fucking clannad crab with testicles in there,
a whole bunch of things.
So many people have seen those two videos,
probably more than have ever, ever watched like all of PCP videos combined.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah.
Like some, I think when it comes to video games videos, there's the Tattletail song,
which there's like a computer-y like glitchy part,
and there's like a little, I put a bunch of code on screen,
I just googled some code and had it scroll past,
and hidden in the code, like in the corners,
a bunch of like PCP references, that was one.
Then I did the Brothers in Arms Cuphead animation,
where I put an entire section dedicated to Gibbons,
Hippo tries not to die from skeletons, I put that in there,
and that's got like 60 million views now, I didn't even realize.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, 60 million, okay, oh fuck.
65 million.
I thought it was like five or six million.
It's so cool, and I think you had like a,
like how you animated the Hippo on your channel.
A little time lapse.
I think that same channel, and because people saw the DA,
not that same channel, your own after dark or something.
Yeah, my own channel.
Yeah, so my main channel is lesser than my after dark actually these days.
And like people saw the DA games thing,
they saw you had like animated in it,
somehow they found the Hippo thing,
then they went from that to the video that you linked
of me making my game, and then to the Itchio thing.
And I think I may have got one whole sale
from those 60 million people.
That's epic.
It system works.
The game wasn't free?
It was free, but you could pay for it if you wanted.
I think I definitely got a few downloads.
I don't think actually anyone paid for it, but you know, exposure.
That's okay.
Yeah, it's about reaching people at the end of the day.
Yeah.
It's about getting those eyeballs.
The only other big DA games video was the Baldi's Basics song,
which is very funny.
It's a very silly song.
I actually wrote the synth solo.
I did some music for it.
Why have I been hearing about Baldi's Basics?
It has just the past couple of weeks.
I've heard about it a bunch of times, and I've never heard about it before.
Oh, it's weird.
It lost relevancy like a year ago.
Maybe there's a DLC or something coming out.
I haven't kept up with it.
But in that video, there's a whole bunch of posters on the wall,
and all of them are PCP references.
Some of them really obscure.
Mysterious Rhinoceros even makes an appearance on one of those.
That secret channel.
Oh my god.
Imagine that.
Wow.
That's a deep cut.
Yeah.
Let's just fuck all this bullshit.
Let's just talk about the pony days.
Those are the good old days.
Let's just reminisce about the good times.
Do you remember Ben being in the Rift Cafe Skype group,
and then every few hours,
they'd have a call in which they played Cards Against Humanity,
and that was it.
That's all they did.
Yeah.
I remember Cards Against Humanity.
What a fucking shitty game.
For assholes.
I don't know.
Yikes.
I might have played once, just as a meme.
I definitely played a couple of times,
because it's like, I don't know how cool I am yet.
I'm just some guy just like one of the rest of these people.
I didn't realize that they were even worse than me.
I mean, you gotta do something, right?
Yeah, it's funny.
It's funny in hindsight.
Card games.
Very cool.
For very cool people.
The Rift Cafe was...
I got an argument there a lot.
I had beef with a couple of people.
Oh, I remember what I was going to say.
I had this idea.
Did you see what Mage did recently?
She made a Vtuber avatar?
Yeah.
She made a Vtuber puppet
and rigged it up and did a stream with it.
It was a little glitchy, but it mostly worked, as intended.
I gotta say, I asked her about it.
I asked her how she did it, what program she used.
She told me, I am very tempted to try it.
I'm very tempted to make a phantom horn.
Continue T-Bat plays or something?
I don't know.
I don't know what I would do with it.
It just seems fun.
It seems like a fun thing to make.
It does.
It's just sort of like...
There's multiple ways to do it.
I know the way you're supposed to do it, there's the program.
I think I downloaded it.
I just never got around to looking at the tutorials of how.
I'm like, whatever.
I guess I can figure that out eventually, and I never will.
I'm in the same place with Live2D.
I assume that's the program you had.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, FaceRig and Live2D, right?
Yeah, FaceRig, that's the other one.
I'm too lazy.
I don't like tutorials.
They suck.
I have too much other shit I should be doing
to even think about doing it right now.
If I had nothing on my plate, I might start fucking around in it
and see what I could cook up.
I mean, there's always something on your plate.
It doesn't matter how non-busy you try to be.
There's always going to be something more important
than making a puppet for live streams,
unless that's your career goal.
It's just a bit of fun.
It's always going to be less important than something.
My career goals are whatever I fucking want them to be.
If I want that to be what I'm doing, it will.
This doesn't make any sense now that I'm thinking about it,
but you should do gummy worm live streams,
creating gummy worms live and have phantom horn
matched to your movements somehow.
It doesn't make any sense because you need to.
What the fuck?
I don't know.
I just thought two things Ben St. does
and put phantom horn there.
It would be like footage of me cooking in the kitchen
with a little phantom horn in the corner
commentating on it or something.
You pre-record you making gummy worms
and then you webcam yourself as phantom horn,
stream the video and commentate on it
and say, what an idiot, what a stupid piece of shit.
Talk about what a piece of shit, garbage.
I am going to make a worm cooking video soon.
I think I complained last episode that it's actually,
I thought I was going to get great deals from China
on isomaltoligosaccharides,
but it's turned out to be a nightmare
and much more difficult than I thought.
And not even much cheaper,
actually more expensive than just buying them domestically.
I'm so mad.
I'm so mad that they don't just sell them
through fiber yam like they used to.
What a fucking joke.
Wait, phantom horn reacts.
You just do phantom horn reacts videos.
I got to pivot back to the pony days.
Just go back to being a full time pony tuber,
but this time with a V-tuber, a P-tuber if you will.
Yeah, like live reacting to my little pony episode.
The world's first P-tuber?
Dude, you have to react to your own T-Bap episodes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Me and Tom keep saying that we're going to make,
we're going to do bonus episodes
that are us reacting to old PCP episodes,
like doing commentary tracks over them.
Oh my God.
We haven't done it yet.
It sounds like a clusterfuck, but I want it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it would be so hard to determine
whether the person talking,
to differentiate between present us talking about it
and past us talking,
it would be these two identical sets of voices
like randomly cutting in and out
and interrupting one another
and commenting on what each other is saying.
I think we should do one of those.
We should definitely try.
I definitely think our voices will have changed a bit.
Mine, I feel like, would have been a lot meeker, at least.
And I'd be like,
oh God, did I sound like that?
And you'd be like, yes.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Well, that would be just the kind of thing
I would want to hear, you know,
us notice about an old episode.
Did I really used to say that?
Did I really sound like that, whatever?
Funny.
I like it.
We'll do it.
We'll make it happen.
You guys want to talk about current events?
Yeah.
Minecraft, I guess.
That's the current event that I'm interested in.
Minecraft has been...
Minecraft Steve is announced for Smash, first of all,
which was epic,
and I really like the game explanation Sakura did.
I didn't watch the full thing.
I watched some of it.
I think that it looks...
I didn't care at first,
but then I saw how he plays and I thought,
oh wow, that's really neat.
That's funny.
The idea of like randomly,
like at any moment placing blocks
that you have in your inventory
and to the stage to like block people's attacks
and then jumping away.
Yeah.
It looks so cool if you could get really good at Steve.
Like that would make great footage.
And like mining for materials
and like what materials you dig up
determine like the quality of the weapons you make.
Like that's so good.
Yeah.
That's super good.
Such a gimmicky character.
Yeah.
He got a mind for diamonds.
But yeah, it's like the first time...
I don't even play Smash
and I'm kind of excited about it.
Yeah.
The first time I had even considered like,
maybe I should get in on this like Nintendo Switch thing
I've been hearing about, you know,
so it's a little new.
Really?
I still haven't bought one.
You weren't tempted by animal crossing?
I don't care about animal crossing.
I've never played one.
They seem fun and nice and wholesome,
but it's like...
You didn't see like everybody animal crossing,
posting on the all across the internet
and be like, shit, this is a cultural event
that I got that I don't...
All right.
Here's my gamer thought.
I hate cultural events
and I hate games that are like destined
to become irrelevant at some point.
Any multiplayer game
that has like seasons,
like season one of like Fortnite,
I hate feeling like the idea of like,
if I don't get in now,
I'll have missed out on all of the cool cosmetic stuff.
You can only get in season one
and then season two and season three.
And it's like, I hate that.
I hate it so much.
It pisses me off to see that even.
So I avoid anything that is like,
designed to be like,
to catch you in like perpetually playing the game.
Not because it's good,
but because you're scared of missing out on all the shit.
Yeah.
I had played an animal crossing before.
So I did not anticipate the degree to which
new horizons would be like,
that thing you just described.
It was like, yeah,
I have fallen off it partly because it's like,
I'm not interested in playing it forever, you know?
And I don't,
I'm not interested in keeping up with the,
you know, yeah, the new,
like holiday expansion packs and so forth.
I mean, I get that it, you know,
it's smart business because it works
and people are constantly manipulated easily
by it all the time.
It's just, I,
I grew up on games where you play them
and then you go back to them if you feel like it,
not because you feel compelled to be part of the event.
Yeah.
It's like, it's kind of why I like,
stopped playing Pokemon Go because I missed a bunch of things.
I was just going to say the same thing.
Yeah.
Like once, like the,
they keep releasing new updates for it.
I've missed the last few and I'm like,
at first I was like, yeah,
I want to be like,
I want to get lots of Pokemon
and make them really powerful and be like,
a fucking Pokemon master.
But then like the fact,
it's like World of Warcraft,
like the fact that new updates keep coming out,
they keep rendering the old stuff obsolete,
you know, the CP cap keeps rising.
It's like, eh, the grind will never end.
God, that's why,
that's why World of Warcraft Classic is so fucking good
because it's all going to stay exactly the same.
That's the whole point.
You can just play it
and you can see all of the stuff that used to be there
that they destroyed horribly.
How big the shoulder pads are.
Oh my God.
That's what I think of Warcraft.
World of Warcraft,
shoulder pads used to look like,
they've always been chunky and big,
but newer designs are like,
spikier and smaller details
that you can't really see from a distance.
The early like,
classic ones were like really big,
chunky,
like, you know,
chocolate bar shoulder pads.
You just,
you want to bite into them.
You want to,
you want to have a little Lego figurine
of your Warcraft character.
Now it's like,
I don't know,
stupid and socks.
It's old, good, new bed.
That's what it's always been.
I've already had this rent before on the PCPs.
I don't need to say it again.
That's why we have,
that's why I got to go back to the pony days
and become a P-Tuber again.
P-Tuber?
If only I'd had,
if only I'd had face rig back in 20, whatever,
when T-Bap was happening.
Things would have been different, I tell you.
That's going to put me out of business,
though, with my commission model that I do
for these pony YouTubers,
pony in the corner people.
Oh, oh right.
Do you still do those?
I do.
Do people still want those?
Yeah, every so often I get a message
from people being like,
hey, can you make vectors of my OC?
And I'm like, sure,
give me a million dollars,
and they do,
and it's cool.
Ponies specifically,
or just like anything?
It's all ponies.
Okay, so,
oh my God,
this goes back a little bit,
I guess it's tangentially related,
so people obviously
want their character to look show style,
because oh my God,
it looks official.
How embarrassing would it be
if your pony OC was like off model or style?
Yeah, imagine having a unique art style, cringe.
But, yeah,
so this goes back to,
I think, 2013.
There were leaks,
a bunch of animation files got leaked from DHX.
I remember this.
It turned out,
I actually had the leaks before they were public,
because I was working on a project
with a guy who I won't name
for the sake of his,
I don't know,
I don't want him to get in trouble.
He works at Warner Brothers.
He's a big boy there now, apparently.
Let's just call him Pro Jared.
Yeah, Pro Jared.
So,
Pro Jared approached me in early 2013
to work on a project for free.
Oh my God, epic.
And he gave me some...
For exposure?
Yeah, exactly.
No, terrible.
He gave me some files,
and he's like,
don't show these to anyone.
And I'm like,
oh, I assume these belong to your old animator.
Then the leaks happened,
and it turned out they were official rigs
from fucking DHX,
and I'm like, oh, fuck.
But from there,
I studied them,
and I created my own rigs in their likeness.
I basically just traced over every single piece,
one by one,
and made it my own.
So technically not stealing.
And...
You just traced them exactly.
Yeah, traced.
Pixel, pixel perfect.
Yeah, and people got mad at me for like,
how dare you do that?
That's the same as using them.
Use our rigs where we traced it instead,
and I'm like,
they did the same thing.
I mean, I agree with them,
but for the opposite reason,
like, I do agree, like,
why do that?
Like, what's the point?
Like, if you're just going to copy them exactly,
what's the point in not using them?
I changed up the design slightly,
and made improvements to it,
but from there,
I have this animation rig,
and I'm like, hey,
I could just pose this character
a bunch of times in flash,
and render an image sequence.
Why don't I do that
for people who make, like, analysis videos?
And I did it for a friend who, for free,
to just start off with.
And then a bunch of air friends were like,
oh, do mine, do mine next,
do mine next.
And I'm like, okay.
And then I did it for free the first few times,
and then I thought, wait,
what if I, like,
what if people pay money for work?
What's that?
So I'm like, sure,
I'll make you, like, a hundred images
for $1 each,
but all I really have to do
is just make the image once,
and it automatically completes for rest.
And so I have done
over 40,000 vectors
in the last few years.
And it's going up,
because every character,
it's now 150 per character.
Do you, do you have, like,
do you have, like, an algorithm
where it's like, you make the rig,
and then, like, you run it through an algorithm
that creates, like,
vectors in different expressions,
or whatever?
What it is, is I have the rig,
all of the poses are keyframes
in my animation software.
I do it in flash, right?
So they're all just keyframes
with symbols.
And if you change, like,
what is inside a symbol,
it updates on every frame.
So I have, like, a temporary hair,
like, for the tail,
temporary hair on the head,
I have a temporary cutie mark,
a bunch of temporary stuff.
And then I, there is an algorithm
that automatically recolors
everything in the file,
so that's easy for recoloring.
And then I just vector,
like, the tail, the hair,
the cutie mark, whatever.
And once I've done that,
I can just go through all the frames
and, like, make small adjustments.
Like, if the hair is really big,
it might, like, clip into, like,
the neck or something
at a certain point,
so I'll have to find all the frames
where it clips into the neck
and, like, move it slightly
or, like, erase part of it.
Like, I do have to do
a bit of manual work,
but most of it's pretty automated.
And, um, yeah,
using the power of capitalism,
I lure people into buying the bigger packs
because it's slightly cheaper
than getting the smaller packs,
like, per image.
You say, you ask them
if they want a supersize.
Yeah, they want a supersize.
You get 150 images
for only $20 extra.
And they're like, yes.
$20? Oh, my God.
God, the value.
Yeah, and I can get,
I can get, like,
oh, like, there was one day
where I did six in a day,
so, like, that was, like,
a thousand images in one day,
but I did.
That was my record.
But most characters of these days,
because I put,
I stupidly put more care
and attention into it,
it can take me a couple days
to do one now.
But if it's a really simple design,
I can knock out in, like,
two or three hours,
and that's, like, 120 bucks.
Not bad.
Wait, all right.
That's so funny.
Has your,
has your user name
stayed the same the whole time?
Were you always oblivionful?
I was,
oh, my God,
I used to be Pivot Master CF
way back.
I did Pivot Animations
forever ago,
and I just,
there was,
okay, there was a guy,
I don't know,
that's another tangent.
I got to stop myself.
A guy made stick figures on crack,
his name was Pivot Master DX.
I just put my initials there,
because I'm dumb,
and I was, like, 12th.
Yeah, I had oblivionfall as my name
since 2009.
There was an animation
on DarkDemon.org
called oblivion.fail,
because it, like,
back then,
if you didn't finish an animation,
you called it a fail.
Oh, look, here's an animation fail
or something.
I don't know.
And I'm, like,
oblivionfall,
that looks cool,
and I saved it.
And I'm, like,
that would be a cool user name.
Two weeks later,
my YouTube account gets hacked
and deleted.
And I'm, like,
oh, I guess I'll make that name.
And only later
did I realize it was fail
the whole time.
So, ooh, I'm an idiot.
That's for the takeoff.
That's a real fail.
That's my tragic backstory.
Yeah.
I asked because
I was wondering whether you,
the whole time,
were the vector brony,
but I think that's someone else.
I have his business card.
I have a physical business card
that he gave me, though,
in 2014.
I made,
I did not use a rig.
I hand drew them.
I drew some pony.
Have I ever mentioned this?
That I drew some pony,
like,
pony in the corner poses
for a brony YouTuber.
For free,
just because I liked him?
Oh, I think I remember that.
Who was it?
His name was, like,
his, okay,
I remember his pony was dark blue.
He had, like,
long black hair
and, like, a goatee.
His name was Tom Oliver.
No.
But,
his cutie mark
was the fee symbol,
like, the Greek letter.
And his name was, like,
the philosophy brony,
or, like, the Gnostic brony,
or something like that.
Yeah, I remember it.
That guy.
I think,
is that the guy who, like...
I know his face.
His pony face.
He had a video
that said that Twilight Sparkle,
he made, like,
a philosophical argument
that Twilight Sparkle
died
and was replaced
by the Alicorn version.
That it is,
that it is, like,
philosophically impossible
for it to be the same
entity.
What we have is not
Twilight Sparkle,
but a new entity
that has replaced the old one.
I think I've seen this guy's videos.
I saw, like,
one where he was, like,
comparing, like,
the characters to, like,
you know, real philosophers
in history
and, like, going off
on all this lofty shit.
And I'm like,
I can't follow any of this.
It's retarded.
Has he got a...
Has he got a deep British voice,
English voice?
I think so.
I don't know.
Maybe.
I don't...
Damn it.
I don't even remember, like,
any of his other videos.
He wasn't that big.
You know.
This was early in the
Brony analysis thing, so...
I think I saw him, though,
because, yeah, he had, like,
only a few hundred subscribers
when I saw it.
It sounds familiar, though.
It sounds very familiar.
I just liked his video,
and I had no creative outlet
at the time.
T-Bap didn't exist yet.
So I was like,
this guy is using, like,
the crappy, like,
show vectors.
It looks like ass.
I am going to...
The pony creator?
The pony creator vectors?
Yeah.
He had a pony creator avatar.
I'm like, this is unacceptable.
I get so many references.
So many clients
will send me their pony
creator character
as a reference.
Of course.
And because they all re-use stuff
for those characters,
I just open up a previous rig
I've done,
and I just take the hair
because it's exactly the same,
and I just recolor it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And then,
and then,
I drew,
I drew him his poses.
I drew him in a custom,
in a different style.
I did,
I did a whole, like,
custom background for him.
So he's, like,
his pony is, like,
sitting behind a desk,
and there's, like,
it's like in, like,
a wizard's tower,
and he's got, like,
bookshelves,
stuff.
You know,
it was kind of nice.
I thought it was pretty okay.
So,
you know,
pat myself on the back
for that.
And then he, like,
quit doing YouTube.
Keep making pony analysis videos,
philosophy,
brony,
or whatever your name is.
Where did you go?
I need a return on my investment.
You gotta be the change
you want to see in the world.
You gotta come back yourself.
You gotta,
you gotta
research the fandom.
Single-handed.
I don't even know
what all those people are doing.
Like,
the show is completely over.
They probably just went and got jobs.
Nah, it's impossible.
They never do that.
They probably just,
like,
got married or something.
I don't know.
I know K.P.
is reviewing,
like,
not pony stuff now.
What cringe?
I mean,
that's,
that's the normal.
Just,
like,
continue doing the same thing,
but with different media.
But,
like,
how successful is that?
Are people still clamoring
for pony reviews?
Probably not.
I mean,
there will,
there will always be,
there will always be
more audience for that.
Yeah.
But it's,
yeah,
it's not what it used to be.
It never will be.
Even if,
even if,
like,
my little pony,
Gen 5 or whatever,
came out,
and it was,
like,
a hit,
and it was popular again,
I think even if it rivaled
Gen 4 in its popularity,
the,
like,
brony YouTuber thing would not
happen again,
because it would be,
like,
be seen as sort of like
an old,
like,
sort of embarrassing thing
that they used to do
and it might get awkwardly,
like,
tacked onto the cartoon review
fandom quote-unquote.
I think,
I think some people would do it,
but I think more people
would see it as cringe.
I,
I mean,
if it's actually is,
like,
interesting,
if you could do philosophy
about fucking
the next gen of pony,
and people start doing it,
I think
people will appear
that have never heard of
the previous,
like,
even younger youngsters
will,
get into that
and then it'll become
a whole different thing.
Yeah,
you know,
I guess the itch
that that kind of content
scratches
is probably just part of
the human condition
and will never go away.
So yeah,
Minecraft.
Minecraft Steve, baby.
I,
I might get a switch
just to play as Minecraft Steve.
Although,
I,
the DLC pack
for,
like,
the,
like the second roster
characters is three more
that has to be revealed.
I kind of feel like
it's worth
waiting
to see if I want to buy
the,
the season pass.
I don't like
gambling on whether the,
they will be characters
I care about,
but like,
I don't want to just
get Steve,
if later on
I want to get
one of the other ones.
Um,
oh,
would like,
would like it save money?
It, it would,
like get the season pass
and then you get all of them
instead of having like
buy them separately.
You can get the season pass
for the DLC
and it will be like,
I think at the moment
the arms lady,
the spring lady,
Steve,
and then three more.
And once those are revealed,
I will know whether I want
to save money on getting all of them
or just Steve.
Who's it going to be?
Uh,
duh.
People have been not looking
for Gino for ages.
I don't know whether that's going to-
It's just not that many more
video games.
Um,
uh,
it's probably going to be
Gohu
right here.
Homer Simpson,
maybe.
Oh, yeah.
He's a video game.
That would be so good.
That would be so funny.
SpongeBob SquarePant.
I know people argue
that Goku is technically
a Nintendo character
because like the
Budakai games were on
a Nintendo console
or something like that.
So I like,
they could do it.
I,
I remember Digi's video
about like why Goku
could be a Smash character.
Oh, maybe that's what
I'm thinking of.
Cause it was,
it was like,
um,
if,
and Dragon Ball Z
have been in
tons of games
that people love and cherish.
And I'm like,
you know what,
that's a decent argument.
It just feels weird.
But I wouldn't-
I wouldn't like
flip my shit
if Goku got in.
I wouldn't be like,
this sucks.
Is the argument,
is the argument against it
that like the character
should have originated
in gaming?
Yes, I think so.
I guess I could see that too.
Uh,
yeah.
I could see,
I could see
the arguments for
and against Goku.
Uh,
I think it would be really funny.
I want to smash-
There's,
there's the Toho girl as well.
Who?
To- Toho girl with red
clothing.
I don't play Toho,
but-
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Ray, Riemu,
Mie-Maru.
Are those on Switch?
No, those are like,
well,
actually, I don't know.
But,
that's a big gaming thing.
What are they on Nintendo consoles?
I think they're-
Well, that doesn't-
I don't think that has
anything to do,
cause Banjo-Kanzui is still
well,
actually, I guess it's on-
Banjo-Kanzui,
those on the N64,
what are you talking about?
I thought you were talking about
like, current,
like, oh, if they can't advertise
on the Switch,
why would they put a character in,
but like-
No, I mean,
I thought the idea was that
they would only include a character
if it was on,
in a game
that was on Nintendo consoles.
So,
if like,
Toho's not on-
on Nintendo consoles,
then I think they're out,
right?
I suppose
they gotta make a new one
and put it on Switch.
I mean,
I don't see why not.
It's a big-
They're putting the fucking shit,
like,
Undertale on Switch,
so why not?
Crash Bandicoot,
the remastered trilogy,
I think,
was put on Switch.
Oh,
that's-
So Crash could be-
They could total-
Okay,
that seems like a no-brainer then.
Crash Bandicoot would be epic.
Rayman would be epic.
You know,
just like,
save all of the poor souls
who got like,
trapped in,
like,
PlayStation All-Stars,
Battle Royale,
the most, uh,
attempt at like,
like,
you know,
showing up Nintendo
at anything ever.
Um,
where Sony got all of its
beloved play-
PlayStation characters
and
somehow made it
terrible and boring.
Um,
like,
just take all of them,
take fucking,
uh,
Ape Escape Man,
Spike,
take fucking
Jack and Daxter,
take all of the play-
just all of the
PlayStation characters
and a new character.
That's-
I mean, yeah.
Yeah,
like the more-
Oh, oh, here's-
Nintendo gobbles up IPs.
Here's my-
The worlds are-
Here's my big, I wish,
please,
um,
one that,
it could definitely happen,
but,
I haven't seen any reason
or like,
hype around it,
is a Matarasu
from Okani.
The dog.
The white dog.
Oh,
that would be sick!
That'd be awesome.
She's got so many,
like,
cool weapons and moves
and attacks
and she's a dog
and that's funny.
And, um,
she's
so
cool.
Like,
imagine an Okami themed
smash stage.
Just-
That'd be so cool.
It'd be so fucking
sick.
I want that.
They already have
Bayonetta,
so like,
they have links to
the studio.
This is a hype.
This is a hype idea.
I like this a lot.
I hope they do it.
I hope they fucking do it.
I mean,
there's no,
it's Team Cherry,
right?
Is the one that made
Okami?
No, that's
that's Hollow Knight.
Oh, fuck.
What's the
what's the team that made
Platinum Games,
previously known as
Clover Studio,
made Okami
and then
Platinum stuff,
Bayonetta
and whatever.
Which,
that's,
yeah,
that's the same company
that made Bayonetta.
So,
yeah,
okay,
they already got the
they got the connections
now that'd be sick.
That'd be so sick.
Yeah, I hope they do that.
Yeah, I mean,
I've hope they did
they did that for like ever.
Yeah,
that's the sort of thing
I want Nate to do,
like a big like,
oh my God,
it's in video.
I want to see another one of
those, but with like,
I don't know,
some cool Japanese music.
Yeah,
I love,
I love Japan period.
Yes.
And manga.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um,
well,
uh,
so,
so Smash Bros.
Yeah,
so yeah,
I like Minecraft.
Hey,
you heard of Minecraft.
That's a game
that's still cool.
I played that.
I played that once.
PCP Minecraft,
where you can play Minecraft
while you're playing Minecraft
and play Pokemon
at the same time.
The PCP Minecraft server.
Subscribe below.
I totally said
that I was going to,
um,
stream another
uh,
Shackles for Heckles
like last week
and then just didn't do it.
I said,
I said I was going to do it
on Wednesday
and then I just forgot.
Well,
um,
because
uh,
I have in my brain
a brand new
build,
a big
building that I will build.
I,
because,
um,
uh,
I went to,
on the holiday,
I went to see some ruins.
This is ruins like
Priory,
a big old church,
monastery,
place where monks
would go
and,
you know,
be praying and shit.
Um,
and it's a whole big complex
of ruins
in this park
and they had these
um,
signs
with like,
here's some history
about stuff.
I took pictures
of all the signs
and all like the
blueprint layouts
of the place
and I got as many angles
as I could
and I'm going to use those pictures
to recreate
the,
the Priory of St.
Pancras
in Minecraft,
in the Minecraft
PCB
Minecraft server.
That's my goal.
Wow.
Pretty,
pretty cool.
Must have,
must have left an impression
on you,
I guess.
Um,
MarinPan
sent me
a screenshot
of the progress,
some progress
that's been made
on building a
New Los Angeles city
and it looks really good.
I guess that's what
they've been doing
while I was,
forgetting to stream.
So,
I'll have to,
we'll have to,
what's the word,
feature that.
I'll have to
show that off a little bit.
Maybe we'll do it
Wednesday,
which,
if you're listening,
we'll have been
this past Wednesday
if you want to see that.
Okay.
Cool.
What else?
What else we got?
What's going on guys?
Uh, well,
which one of you
gave the president COVID?
Um,
it was me.
Oh,
yeah,
me too.
Oh,
it was all three of us
at the same time.
Oh,
you sold your,
you sold your hair
so I could buy
these combs and all
you sold just
your swatch so I could buy
this chain and all
you gave the president
COVID,
but I was giving
the president
for the express purpose
of COVID.
Yes.
It was my plan.
Where do you live in America?
Where are you from?
I'm,
I forget.
I'm from New Zealand.
Like Swedish?
Oh, New Zealand.
I don't fucking know.
It's all the same.
Every English-speaking person
could live anywhere.
It's a fake country.
Low Australia.
It's not real.
It's a tiny little island.
I was there
for my whole life up until recently.
New Zealand,
like,
like Flight of the Concords,
right?
Yeah,
Flight of the Concords.
like Lord of the Rings.
Yeah.
Well,
yes.
Literally,
Lord of the Rings
the only thing in New Zealand
that ever happened.
And Flight of the Concord.
Well,
Flight of the Concord
is better than Lord of the Rings.
The two things.
Oh,
the hot take.
It's a comedy
band
show,
TV show.
Next,
next PCP bonus
episode is
Lord of the Rings
versus Flight of the Concord.
Oh,
we should.
We should.
Why not?
Oh,
we should.
I know
Flight of the Concord.
You know
Lord of the Rings.
We can do it.
Patreon.com
slash
TP Cratt.
Is it TP Crassinators?
I fuck.
I always forget.
The
procrastinators.com.
Patreon.com
slash
the procrastinators.
Link in the description
if you want to hear
soon to be
the bonus episode
of
Lord of the Rings
versus Flight of the Concords.
We will decide
this age old
debate once and for all.
Fucking
I promise.
Like America is so
different.
It is so fucking different
being here.
America is basically
a continent.
It is.
It is pretty much
like the thing
in New Zealand is that
everyone knows everyone.
Like
the common thing is
like two degrees of
separation.
Like the friend of your
friend like knows
like if you
if you took all your
friends and took all their
friends,
that's the whole country
basically.
Like
and because of that
like it's common
like for just to just
end up on TV
like that.
Really?
Yeah.
Like my parents have been
like interviewed on like
live television a few times.
Actually maybe that's
not as common.
Maybe that's just a thing
my parents did.
But I don't know.
Wait.
All right.
I'm looking into the size
because I'm
I thought it was
like the same size
as the UK.
Turns out
United Kingdom
243,000
square kilometers.
New Zealand
268,000
square kilometers.
So it's ever so
slightly bigger
and it you're saying
everybody knows
population is small.
Yeah.
Actually, yeah, of course.
There's like loads of farmland
there or something.
It's mostly farmland
and mountains and forest
and like a few cities
and like a fifth
of the country is in one city.
I mean, how much of America
lives in big cities?
It's like a lot of it, right?
Population of the UK
is 67 million
population of
new.
This is like 5 million.
Oh,
wall.
Owned.
We have more people
than you that
therefore we need
where we're suffering
and people are starving to death.
We have more sheep than people
and we'll trample you.
Is that true?
Yeah, we do.
We have like several times
more sheep than people.
Do they vote?
Yes.
Well,
if only if only if a human
marries them,
they can vote.
It's fucking you.
My parents
are trying to tell me to vote
in the New Zealand election
and I have no idea
what the fuck is even going on
in that country right now.
I'm not going to...
Are you guys
in the midst of a
fascist coup right now?
New Zealand is like...
Oh, that's cool.
I always like...
I wonder how that feels.
I always assumed
because New Zealand is
like extremely progressive
but I didn't know that growing up
because like my family
was always like sort of
like center right-leaning
but that's like right-leaning
by New Zealand standards
which is still pretty left.
Yeah.
So I'm like,
America,
I'm sure if a right over there
is pretty good probably
yeah, healthcare,
who needs it?
I don't have that.
It turns out,
I actually did.
It turns out I had
universal healthcare
of a whole time
and no one told me.
It's like weird.
I go to America
and I'm like, oh.
Well, yeah,
like why would they need to tell you?
Like obviously.
It's going to cost
$20,000 to stub my toe.
Actual statistic.
Look it up.
No.
A real statistic I learned
is delivering a baby,
$40,000.
Oh, you want to hold the baby?
That's an extra $150.
Oh, you want to,
you want to kiss it on the cheek?
That's an extra thousand.
Wait, wait.
That can't be real.
They can't charge
for delivering a baby.
I have heard this too.
I know.
I thought it has to be free.
But I looked it up
and several people have showed
like people took screenshots
of the bill,
people who didn't have insurance.
$40,000.
Unbelievable.
Just tell the child
they'll have to work
in the hospital.
It's even more expensive
to be born.
to be born than it is to die.
Probably not, actually.
Maybe it is.
I don't know.
It's easy to die.
You get like a rock
and you just hit your head
with it until you're dead.
I don't know if it's the same.
Yeah, but then everywhere
in America.
Insurance though.
They got to clean your carcass up.
That's not cheap.
Nah, it's easy.
You just drump in the
drump in the ocean.
Drump in a bitch.
Cool.
I feel like I should have more
to say about that,
but yeah,
that's what's up.
The only other thing
about New Zealand
that I know
is that they had
a flag referendum
not too long ago.
Oh, yeah.
To get a better flag.
Yes.
Yeah, our flag looks
just like the Australia flag.
You change one line, basically.
It's embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing.
There was a competition
to change the flag
and a bunch of people sent in designs.
So the New Zealand flag,
the Australian flag
basically just has one extra star
and the stars are white
instead of red, right?
Is that the difference?
Yeah, something like that.
Is that the Pleiades
on the flag?
It's the Southern Cross
for New Zealand, I think.
The flag referendum,
I was like all for it,
but a bunch of people were like,
yeah, but we don't like
the Prime Minister
at the current time.
We don't like him.
We don't like John Key.
So let's just vote no
just to piss him off.
And I'm like, guys,
I just want a good flag.
Some of the designs are really cool.
I heard about it
through the Hello Internet podcast
where they talked about it.
Oh, that's a good podcast.
Yeah.
It is.
Worse than this one.
Don't listen to it.
Way worse.
Some of these,
I just, I looked up
New Zealand flag referendum.
Some of these are like weird looking,
but I like them.
I like them.
They're all like swirling.
Yeah, I like,
because I think it was
something to do with
something,
New Zealand.
Are you the answer, right?
Yeah.
I think there was a reason
that it was a certain way.
No.
Okay.
I think it came down to,
I don't know if it was
the bottom left over top right
in the end,
but I liked both of those.
I liked the bottom left
a little more, but.
The top right is almost too cool.
Yeah.
It's almost like video game,
pirate crew sort of thing.
Yeah.
I do like it though.
The bottom left one
does look like,
I mean, that's just a pretty good.
Yeah.
I remember,
I remember looking at these things
and being like,
all of them have some aspect
that I really like.
The fur and the leaf,
but like the color choices
with all of these,
like I don't quite like
all of this color choices
that have the leaf.
And the black and white
with the swirly is great,
but it feels like it's
missing some aspect of it.
Yeah.
So the silver fern is like
a huge like New Zealand icon.
Our rugby team has it
as their thing.
And New Zealand is more
recognized for the silver fern
than it is for its own flag
pretty much.
Because like our rugby team
has like a ridiculous
like win record.
They win like,
I don't know.
It's like something like
80% of every game they win.
You know,
New Zealand is a great rugby
thing.
They're always in the big six.
It would be really funny.
I'm not,
I'm imagining like,
okay, Massachusetts has a shit flag.
Have you ever seen the
Massachusetts flag?
No, how do you spell
Massachusetts?
Fucking America.
Don't even worry about it.
American names.
I just have to say
American place names.
Stupid.
I don't like them.
That's great.
That's racist.
It's a Native American name.
I take it back.
You piece of shit.
I just about.
Massachusetts has two S's and two T's
and the rest sounds like it says.
Google fixed it for me.
Let me see this.
Massive cheats.
I don't like.
Oh, this is a weird flag.
Yeah.
It's a weird flag.
It's not,
it's not super exciting.
That's not so bad.
I've seen worse.
You shouldn't have text
on your flag though.
No.
But like,
like it's got two to three colors.
It doesn't look like a terrible
garish piece of shit.
And it's got a shield.
So that's cool.
My problem with it is like,
this isn't a flag.
This is a crest.
Right.
Yeah.
It's just white.
Like the crest is fine for what it is,
but it's not a good flag.
In my opinion.
So I'm thinking like,
what if we.
I like that.
I like the blue and pink stripes though.
It's pretty nice.
Yeah.
Where did.
They must have hired someone real.
But,
but like,
imagine they were like,
okay guys,
we need a referendum.
It's time for a new flag.
And then it's like,
hmm,
what do we like here in Massachusetts?
Well,
the Boston Red Sox are really popular.
So then like,
we made like the new like Massachusetts state flag,
like a pair of Red Sox or something.
And it's like,
yep,
because we like those guys.
We just made,
we just based the flag on our baseball team.
Or hell,
you can have all the sports teams in there just on one flag
and like,
that's it.
Just like put them all next to each other.
Make it one of those like,
those patchwork jackets where you have like a million like
band logos and emblems and things.
Yeah.
If I,
if it wouldn't,
if it wouldn't distract me,
I would go and like cobble together the new like
state flag of Massachusetts right now.
It has to be made out of denim.
I will,
I will post it in the chat after,
after I will make it afterwards.
It'll be,
it'll take me five minutes,
but it'll be very epic.
Yes.
Right.
What the fuck are we talking about?
We're talking about flag referendum.
I don't,
I don't think they,
they didn't,
yeah, they blocked it.
Didn't they?
There was no new flag.
It didn't go through.
People,
it got blocked because
young people were like,
we don't like the prime minister.
Fuck you.
And old people are like,
we're boomers.
Fuck you.
And that was it.
Did they like just,
did people just like not want change?
I guess it almost went through.
It was pretty close.
I remember,
I was,
I was still living there at the time.
I voted on it,
but yeah.
Cause everyone who knows anything in America
wants us to stop making the penny.
We don't need the penny anymore.
Oh, we don't.
No, no you don't.
We boomers are just like,
no, it's got Lincoln on it.
And that's America.
Okay.
What about national pride?
I've lived,
I've lived through coin destruction.
The five cent coin in New Zealand
got yeeted out around 2007
or 2006.
Fucking good.
And it was fine.
Like we handed out,
we handed out coins
and then everything was fine.
In fact, it was easier.
And that's the five cent coin.
Did you like have to go
and like give them back?
I mean,
I mean, if you held on to them,
they would just become worthless.
But if you hand them in,
you can get an exchange.
So it's worth it.
They would exchange.
Yeah.
They also updated all the coins too.
Like they completely redid the currency.
They changed all the coins
to be a little bit lighter
and a little bit more like
material efficient.
I think they did that.
They did that in England, I think.
Yeah.
In like the 70s or 80s or something.
Or like not that long ago.
Yeah.
I mean, it was only like
10 years ago in New Zealand.
And yeah, everyone,
you just hand in your coins,
they give you the new coins
and that's,
it's easy.
It's fine.
It's not hard.
They've done a few,
like getting rid of things
recently in the UK as well.
They've changed all the paper money
to be like plastic money.
So it's,
it's plastic.
Yeah.
It feels different
and it's more durable
and doesn't crinkle and rumple
over time.
Oh yeah.
And they changed the one pound coin
to be a little different.
I think,
I can't remember what they did with that.
All right.
Here's an idea.
$2 coin.
We got that.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah.
We have a two pound coin as well.
I think,
I don't know if they have two Euro coins.
I thought they had like
two Euro and five Euro coins.
I really like big,
big value coins.
High value coins are good.
I hate,
like we,
we have a $1 coin.
We have a couple of different $1 coins
that are like technically valid
currency in America,
but nobody uses them.
Everyone hates them.
I'm the,
I'm the only one.
I'm the only one who likes them
and I wish we had bigger coins.
If,
if I can't wait,
I can't wait for Trump to die
so that we can commemorate him
with the new like $5 coin.
It's going to be so sick.
It's on the back.
It says billionaires only, please.
It'll be the $5 billion coin.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
That coin's sick.
Uranium.
I love that.
Yeah.
I've always liked the two pound
because it's like double,
just silver and gold.
Two colors.
That's,
that's fucking sick.
That's a,
I love,
yeah,
I love the two color coins.
They got them in Europe.
They don't have those here
and I think they're nice.
The little gears in the middle.
So intricate.
It's so like,
it doesn't,
it's weird how it's like abstract.
Yeah.
I don't know why,
but they always have the queen on the other side.
So the heads is always the queen.
Yeah.
The head is on the other side for my team.
And the others,
and they're like,
well, nothing else is worth
minting on the other side.
So just throw a bunch of gears on there.
Fuck it.
Yeah.
So it's the queen in our coin,
even though we're not technically
like,
beholden to the UK anymore.
That's some,
Canada too.
Canadian money,
I think all has the queen on it.
Look at this old lady.
After America revolted,
when you,
when New Zealand said,
be independent,
the UK is just like,
yes, honey.
Did you know,
this is probably
recently,
common knowledge,
but did you know that as the queen is aged,
they update her face to be older,
to be more accurate to herself?
No, I didn't know that.
So you can look at the back of a coin
to see how old it is
without looking at the year.
It'd be like,
oh, she's young there.
There was a video I saw
that like showed like
how the queen's face like changed on notes
or coins over time.
And like early on,
she was like,
she had to be like a fucking kid
at the beginning
when they started.
Yeah, she was very young
when she got the crown
and everyone was like,
oh my God,
it's so cool.
I'm watching on TV.
It was like the,
the reason,
the reason most people in the UK.
The reason television was invented.
I mean, literally the first thing
that people bought a TV for
was to watch the,
the coronation live.
That was, that was the selling point.
Epic.
That is so fucking cool.
This is the longest running,
take a picture of yourself every day,
YouTube video of all time.
It's still being made.
Imagine like a time lapse.
I wonder if someone's made a time lapse
of just like every year of the queen.
There is.
I saw one a few months back.
I mean, on the coins.
I mean, with the coins specifically.
Oh, maybe it might exist.
I don't think there are that many.
There's like maybe every couple of years
they would have one.
So maybe it would take a few seconds, but.
My back when I used to play
dwarf fortress,
one of my favorite things to do
was to have my dwarves mint coins.
And I would just look at them
and examine them and like see
like what they decided to like,
what images they decided to press
into their coins.
No, they would have like pictures
of like historical figures
and pictures of like, you know,
the king or pictures of like noblemen
from like other places or hero like folk heroes.
Or like sometimes they would have like
insignias from like the region they're in
or like their country or like their town has every
it turns out like every like town
and like principality has its own like logo
and sometimes you you find out what they are
because they mint them on the coin.
You're like, oh, I see.
Like the national symbol of you know,
bronze hammers is two diamonds
in a pool of lava.
Nice.
Minecraft.
Epic.
Bringing it back around.
And then they and they and like
and you mint them out of different metals
and like they'll put different things
on like the silver coin versus the gold coin
versus the platinum coin.
So it's so cool.
So satisfying.
Yeah.
But it's useless though.
Like they're used dwarf fortress used to have
a thing called like the dwarven economy
that was this whole like sub game
within the game this whole system
but it was like completely broken
and it got taken out.
So you can still like the dwarves
would trade with each other for money.
So you can still make the money
but it doesn't do anything.
It's just like it's just bullying basically.
Like you can trade it away and that's it.
It's a little disappointing.
Okay.
I said to go on a dwarf fortress.
I'm I'm every time dwarf fortress is brought up.
I'm like how could possibly have there been
so many like things thought of to program
to make that they have all of these different logos
in the game that they could choose from
to make when they decide to mint a coin.
It's just like how could they do that?
There's no way.
There's no way that dwarves could have
unique coin minting abilities.
And yet they do and yet they fucking do.
It's so good.
It's so big.
How do they do that?
They I mean I guess it's like the game
the game just generates all this shit.
It's like generates like a huge amount
of like background information
that like you will never be privy to.
Yeah, I really like like the idea that
you generate the world and you see what you see
but then like other like a whole list of like
like the name of the place you're at
or like the region and stuff like they come up
with all this I guess they draw from a list
of potential names for things
and then mash them together into like a list
of those places and past kings or whatever
that it keeps track of and then it just
when it comes up it comes up.
It generates like the whole like geographical
and like geopolitical history of the world
like from the beginning of creation
to like whenever to whenever you're playing
and it knows like you know how different like
leaders like founded countries and like how
different countries like moved and like
changed hands and like power was exchanged
and like who ruled each one and when and stuff
and it's because it like because it tracks
like the individual like creatures right
like the individual like creatures
that like would let go on to become like
you know kings or you know whatever.
I mean there are there are common elements to it
like there's always there's like the goblin empire
always exists and there's always like a demon
who was summoned at some point who usually
is the leader of them but sometimes the demon
can like be killed and like someone else
might rule the goblin empire or something
you know but like yeah the specifics of like
you know the different towns that they founded
like it knows all that it decides like
okay this one had this was called this
this was its logo this is who ruled it
I love how it was founded it's these were like
the battles it had against other towns.
It's just like my favorite thing because like
the real world is like that you look at the
the etymology of like English town names
they just mean like this guy's house was
next to this river and he was his name was
like sex and then it looks like sex and
or something or Samson and then it'll be like
Samson forward or and then like the town
name would be like like sounding similar to
that and it's like wow this name that seems
like a bunch of random syllables is just wasn't
like normal language and it's all most of the
towns were just so like what's this
cliff town it's near a cliff
I like how you said it like you just see
what you see like you don't like the only way
you like know the history is like your dwarf
makes a coin and you pick it up and you look at it
and it's like oh yeah on this coin is an image
of like you know George George
like Mick Mick elf fellow the elf who
became King of the Dwarven Empire between
the years like 200 and and 410 who
was slain by a bronze titan yeah the image
depicts him being crushed under the foot of a bronze titan
it's it's like oh cool I guess that
now I know it's
but it's like it's all there for you to
like archaeologically dig up and that's
it's just like real life you go to a
Wikipedia article of a place and you learn
all about it and it's like wow that was
not apparent at all you can you can make
it I mean you can like generate a world
and then just go into like like I forget
what it's called there's a mode where you
can just basically like look shit up and
you can look up like names and figures
and like just like look up like what's
this kingdom who was its leader like what's
their history look through that oh where
did they live oh look at that town oh they
had a battle against this other place who
fought in the battle you know you can
sort of just kind of dig through all this
like information without not instead of
actually like playing the dwarf game
because who has time for all that shit
I'm looking forward to dwarf fortress
too when they they get the heavy weapons
guy I want them to when are they going to
put dwarf fortress in smash when are they
going to just have the little like
dwarven smiley face just like be just
like moving like like square to square
just like creating a little square
next to it that represents that's being
mined out and like that's it that's its
hitbox or whatever I don't know I have no
idea what that would look like they'll
figure the map would be very very
interesting though the stage I mean what
if yeah what if instead of like instead
of the character they just had a map and
them and like you know your smash
characters are in the map but the map
is like a grid based and like the little
dwarves are going around the map like
digging out and mining and like building
and rebuilding and filling in and stuff
and just like yeah changing up their
fortress and whatever maybe they build
some like arrow traps and like they
shoot like ballistas at you at some
point I don't know that'd be cool that'd
be pretty neat right Sakurai you
listening get on the phone with Tarn
Adams he's got like cancer or something
so he needs to make money now so I'm
sure he'd be I'm sure he'd be interested
in in working out a deal with you I mean
if you did mine probably get a little
fortress it's kind of inspired minecraft
a little bit so old old good new bed is
dwarf fortress older than minecraft it is
not solicited as an inspiration hmm bring
it back to minecraft yeah it must have
it must have been it must have been in
like the early days of dwarf fortress
though because dwarf fortress has been
developed for like what like 20 years
or something right and something crazy
yeah yeah long ass freaking time
yeah so minecraft yeah so minecraft yeah
minecraft Steve I hope we should just
call this episode minecraft Steve I
mean I've been excited about some
minecraft news outside of that because I
don't know what a smash is I don't know
what a Nintendo is but we're getting
that that cave update that people have
been asking for for years and lots of
cool shit I don't know anything about
that yeah it's quite recent they've been
talking they've been the minecraft
Twitter has been making some videos with
showing off a scree a creepy mob that
appears to be like drawn to you by the
sound you make not by sight which is
like a different aspect he lives so far
underground that he's blind and he
attracts you down and yeah which is
which is such wait like who is this
it's a new scary monster that in the
cave update and like usually you play
the game you jump around you break
blocks because all of the enemies all
of them only react when they see you so
if you're not seen you're fine and now
with this scary like sound man you're
gonna have to think about like whether
you're running and jumping in the deep
dark depths and that's that's pretty cool
make sense make sense pretty good pretty
solid every time I see like an I hear
someone talk about a minecraft update
I'll like see the game and I will like
not see anything different about it and
then when I do hear like what they added
I'll be like really that like the last
one I heard about was like the one that
added the like pitchfork that it was
like the fish update the Trident and you
could have the tree at the Trident
weapon that you could and I was like that's
that's cool and all but like why like why
that I was like that's just like one
small part of like they can they completely
redid the oceans and like added a whole
bunch of stuff yeah I'm aware I'm aware
that there was more to it than than that
but like I guess it's just that I didn't
know how the oceans worked before so I
couldn't really see the difference so
that's probably why they didn't have
anything in them before they had
squids right there's like squids and
gravel and that was and at some point
they are they added the the the sea
undersea like temp oh the ocean monument
yeah ocean monuments those are kind of
cool but yeah if I completely like
redid the oceans and then they redid
villagers and redid the never and now
they're doing caves and all these
updates are pretty good I like it
villagers seems weird
villagers seemed like a weird addition
to the game to me they've been around
so long they've been around since like
2011 and they were really they were they
sucked they were terrible but now they're
kind of cool but I didn't like know about
them and then when I found out they were
in the game I was like why are these people
walking around like why do you want like
NPCs like in a village
like I don't know like the more
I feel like the more I found out about
Minecraft the less I understood it
because it seemed at first
when I knew literally nothing about
I was like oh it's a game about
building with blocks
and it's the natural environment and you
dig for stuff and like yep got it
but then like I don't know there's these
other like sort of esoteric things in
there like the villagers system and
shit and it's like I mean that stuff
still pretty surface level there is a
like a lot of like other hidden stuff
about Minecraft though that and redstone
and stuff yeah like the redstone stuff
the Psycraft people and I don't know
I'm a big mind head is that
the word I don't know the word is it's a
blockhead probably blockhead yeah
about you a blockhead uh well I'm
glad you're not a fucking globe head
I know the Illuminati are trying to tell
us that the earth's not the world is flat
it just has six sides you know
yeah
I believe in six flat earths
all glued together
cubically
dude I got to the edge of Minecraft and I
went 90 degrees and I played
Minecraft again
started over
I you know
speaking of video games
that they should be in Smash Brothers
a spore
when I was waiting for spore
when I was waiting for spore to come out
they I was
so hype because like
you've both seen the
the old spore video
do you know what I'm talking about the one that
I've seen a little bit of it yeah
I watched it the old one that Will Wright did
showing off the game before it was like
really like finished
but it's got it looks so cool
it looks so robust it's so it looks
the animations they work so dynamically
it's so like wow how did they do
that and then the real thing comes out
and like half of that shit's gone there's no
aquatic stage it's like it's just not the same
it must have just faked a lot of it
it's just bullshit
it got bought out
by a big company and the company
fucked it
I think it was
being made by EA from the beginning
was it I remember it being bought
by EA and then getting fucked
but I don't know the details
I mean maybe EA had something to do with it
but like I don't know
if there was
if like the stuff that you
could see in the demo
was possible
there's no way that it would have
been taken out like it's just the final
product is like demonstrably worse
in almost every way
I don't know like it's to the
point that like if they had to cut all that shit
for corporate reasons
then like Will Wright could have like taken
it and just like made a second game that was that other stuff
I don't know
it was very bizarre but
one of the things that you could do in it
was you could do terraforming and you can technically
do terraforming in the
actual spore game but it sucks
so bad
at least in the base game I know there was expansions later
but in the base game all you could do
was like you could put down like stamps
like you could fly around your
your fucking
you could fly around your fucking planet
and you could just put down like basically
stamps like basically little mountains that were like
shaped like things like star shape
or like spiral shape whatever and it sucked
it's so fuck
it's garbage Will Wright
he shows in the demo he has like sliders
that he can like dynamically change like
the planets like water levels he can change
he can change like
he could like change the atmospheric
composition in a way that would like
dynamically change like the water level and it would
like cause like he
he does
in the final game
there is a there is a thing
that you can do to like terraform a planet
and basically it's just you like throw down
an object
and it like terraforms the planet and now it's like
a habitable planet it's green it's lush
oceans are blue great
but that he talks about that being like like a
late game like final thing
in before that like
you could terraform planet but like you would have to
do it you know you would have to like throw
down like
volcanoes that would like release the right gases
you would have to like increase the temperature to like get
enough moisture in the air and like da da da da
and add add add hydration and make it rain
and like move all this stuff add life
seed life let life spread over there
do make uh uh uh uh
what's the word bacteria start to grow
and in the final game it's not that
it's just like you like click up like you have
money you click a button and like oh planets terraform
just fix okay that's my
spore rant but the thing
one thing that I really wanted to do
was he had this beam
that you could terraform the planet like you had
fine control like you could go to one little spot of it
and like pull it up and go next to it and like push it down
and you could like sculpt the planet and I was like
oh man it would be so cool if I took one of
those and I just made a cube and if
I just like sculpted the spherical planet
into a cube and had a cube planet yes so
that's where this was all going is it was going to be
Minecraft world uh but it never
happened because will write
fucked me over you lied
every time every time you
say will write I think you're saying will
Ryan and I get scared
who is who is that he's
my boss slash friend
da games man
oh hello
I hope he's listening to the podcast
I don't think he is
if he does hello fine
cool
um yeah and I'm just like
you opened it with saying a character
that should be in smash spore and I'm like
like like would you just
dynamically change based
on the battle that's happening and by the end
they like the super smash is like to be
fully evolved
oh like they evolve right like
they have like a bite attack and every time they bite
they get like more dna points or whatever
and like you can like spend it on
the fly like grow extra limbs or something
I'd be fucking neat that'd be neat oh
dude you customize your
character mid battle to make a giant like
a penis creature is that
the strat yeah that's the strat
I think I played spore
for a little bit or maybe I just watched a let's
play but it was definitely big
penis is involved
there might have been the game grumps um
yeah probably well I remember that
Russ was playing or something oh no
I can't remember but that was fun
I think that's the only spore let's play ever
saw and it was pretty funny
they just made like dicks and
butts and it was
really funny and I was like hey that's
a good game yeah
you can make him hold his own balls
as he walks around and his penis is a foot
has a foot so like jack hammers down when
he walks
just like me
oh oh well your penis has
a foot yeah I thought you meant I thought you said is
a foot I mean the penis has a foot on the end
of it and so when you walk like your back legs
walk normally but your front foot is like
I made I made a mistake
I misunderstood dab
dab dab
uh
ooh
so how so how are we doing
temp check temp check how are we doing
what's our energy level at right now
audience temp check audience type
temp check in the put in the comments
down below how hype are you right now
how high energy are you feeling
I'm thinking like a low to mid
two degrees
okay I don't know that's good
that's good enough we can work we can
work with that it's not dead I'm not
dead yet
I'm alive same ish
oh here's here's the thing
on the last PCP episode
it was like September 13th
I think
the next day
I announced on this is when we recorded
the last episode that I was on
the next day I talk about
how I'm trans now and so I
realized I haven't been on the PCP since
I made that tweet so people
aren't aware lol
there's just an update
for you I
I don't remember I think
me and Tom mentioned it
a little bit you might have like briefly
discussed that it was a thing that occurred
was that in the most recent one
with cyber shell
maybe or one of them I haven't finished watching
that one yet but yeah anyway um
yeah
I am
I am one of those
pretty epic
I don't really know what to say about it
there's a lot of aspects and I don't know
whether people give a shit
in the comments let us know if you give a shit
if you give a shit
put a comment
give a little bit
give a little bit of shit
I've only had a few little like trans
thoughts in my head ever
trans thoughts
I think I had a dream
when I was like 11 and in the dream
I was just like a girl
in some kind of mech
suit thing and I don't know
it was nice but also
a penis good I want to keep it
I think that was
I think that was just the end of Metal Gear Solid
Peace Walker
maybe
yeah I mean I used to have
like thoughts like that
it's like what if I was a girl but I always assumed
that was just like a thing and everybody did
and maybe it is
I don't know if it's a thing
it was always weird like
after I decided
like you know all of these things they're clearly leading
to this one thing so I'll just say it
get it over with saying it
it's funny
but then like what about my actions
in the past
like was an indication
of this or was it
could all of them have been
like not related at all
and I was
just thinking about that a lot like
what about what I did
was like indicative of that
there's a few things that are very obviously
weird like girly
things that I wanted to do
like this one time
I really wanted this
at the gift shop
from this zoo
I think and I wanted a penguin purse
there's a little blue fluffy
penguin purse
and my parents were like
are you sure you want that
that's not very cool
maybe you'd like a toy dinosaur
instead you know something cool
and I'm like what
I didn't realize that it wasn't manly
to have a little pink
a little blue fluffy penguin purse
to put my coins in
but I don't know whether that was like
a gender thing
who says a man can't have a purse
exactly like it really
I don't think there's any like hard and fast
like oh this was a sign
and this wasn't like it's just
it's a very complex
web of stuff
I don't fucking know
sometimes you just want
big booby mommy milkers
and that's it you know
forget about the trans stuff
although there are like a hundred thousand trans
people in big booby mommy milkers
it's very trans inclusive
very trans positive
update on that server
it is turned into an ERP server
there's just people fucking each other constantly
it's completely debaucherous
like the worst
like AK the best and based
I you know
you know
that's cool
I guess
I'm in there I had sex
one time and I thought gay
I'm just gonna be the growth man
I have not had sex
just like in real life
I will never consent to sex
if you do question mark size
question mark size it'll tell you how many times
you've had sex
and there are a few people who are trying to maximize
that number by fucking everyone
all the time it's really funny
it's my favorite video game
for having sex
number go up
okay yeah sure
I mean I understand
that is all the motivation
that's really required
it's just really funny like at first
the server does having bigger boobs
make it easier to have more sex
no
but it is just fun to have
the way to have sex
alright here's the two avenues to sex
one
I want it to be like
cookie clicker where it's like
you start having sex
you have lots of sex but then you're like
man if I can make my boobs bigger
that will increase my rate of sex having
yeah every time you have sex you have
three times as much sex
every time you have sex you get bigger boobs
and every time you get bigger boobs you have more sex
so it's like mutually encouraging
a cycle
mutual reinforcing systems
crazy
until you're having more sex than there are
atoms in the universe
an exponential rise
to infinite sex
we could add that
I mean it's really funny
add infinite sex to the bottom
please
it's really funny like watching
the progression of the server
go from haha this is all just for fun
this is all just goofy
to being like
I want to like people were like
excited about the prospect of a
exclamation
question mark fuck command
where like consent
is not necessary
and somebody has to like sign up
for that treatment they have to
set race
sex object
set race sex object
and then people can
question mark fuck them at any time
and the flavor text
is like more
raunchy and sexual
and people are really into it and it's really funny
I like being a part of this
horny on main is like
actually cool
so if you
wanted to have the most sex
I assume you could just go where the sex objects are
and just like it would be like
exclamation point mining
exclamation point fuck them over and over again
you would and they also their number
would go up
okay if you want I mean listen
this broken game design right we need to
need to rebalance it needs a patch what you got
to do is you have to you have surely
you must have to like expend some kind of
resource while having sex like you must
you must have to like refill your
your testicles or whatever
whatever fuel it is that is
required right just so
the thing the thing
one or the other I mean I would
I was thinking of like adding
like a
penis size stat
somehow to the game that you could also
like
make bigger somehow
but I think
my thoughts initially
were like I don't want
people to be alienated
too much from
like okay like not everybody has
a penis there are actual girls in the
server
and they like if I
if the sex command includes
like
like mention of the penis
I was like that
that won't work that would be like
take you out of the experience
because a lot of the initial like commands
of the initial responses
for like question mark sex
and question mark accept is
you hold hands
or like you cuddle each other
and it's like whoa based
so lewd
and that was the joke
and then it just actually just became
fucking
but
you know
I could add penises in there
I think that would be a fun
extra thing like a little toggle
penis toggle
toggle have penis the thing is then
like if you don't have penis how do
you have sex is it
possible well I mean I'm sure
surely we can figure
something out
surely there must be some alternative
nipple pussy let's go
like what
is like what do the female
have they have the vagina but they
don't have little like nothing
nothing they have nothing else
everyone has a butt
it's true that you can expend
your butt resource he's right
you know okay
how can we solve
this problem of how to
have sex without penis
with regards to having
a resource specifically because like
I don't know
what do the lesbians do they just sort
of squidge together
they get maybe a dildo
a dildo
you just get a dildo you gotta
have a dildo I mean I guess in real life
the thing you're expending is like energy
because it's exhausting to do
so much of it to fuck
a thousand times a second
if you spam click
question mark fuck
over and over again
are people botting?
people aren't botting that
people are doing the
question mark squeeze to make their breasts bigger
in the titty bar
excellent good
but nobody's botting as far as I know
you could have like a libido
resource or something like that that's like a secondary
maybe I don't know if that would be good
I'm not a gay man
yes that that could work
so you can only sex when there's
libido is high enough
game mechanics
I guess it would like refill automatically but maybe
you can accelerate it by doing certain things
perhaps
yeah like chugging
libido pills
what are those things in like dojins
they always have where it's like I gave you
these secret pills that make you
want to have sex more
I gave you the penis having pills
no not those
those are different pills
they're like
they call them like aphrodisiacs that's the one
you chug aphrodisiacs
to get your libido back
so you can fuck more
and it's like I'm imagining like a black market
developing of like people
like it's a limited resource
and you have to like you have to work for it
you really gotta like what are you going to do for me
if I give you these aphrodisiacs like I just
I gotta have my fix because I want to fuck
maybe you could trade
like the estrogen pojins
for aphrodisiacs like if one person
wants to prioritize one over the other
yeah you could
maybe you could like transmogrify
an estrogen pojun into an aphrodisiacs
so you can decide to get bigger breasts
or you can get some stuff
to fuck more
choices this is good
like game design talk
you know what other game was designed
Minecraft
oh my god it was
hmm
they should add sex to Minecraft
um
wait they didn't
wait then who what have I been doing
like dude
you know you can put your Minecraft bed
next to someone else's bed
and then it becomes a big bed
oh does it actually become a big bed now
somebody
it just looks like it
somebody said like hey did you
see what happens when you use
sleep on Minecraft
I assume they mean like the jigglypuff sleep
yes he gets in a bed
oh well okay I thought that might be it
he puts down a bed and goes to bed
it goes to sleep when he jigglypuff
uh
sings at him which is funny
does he actually like put a bed down
or does he just become
he puts a bed down and gets in it
oh something
a secret Minecraft strat
that few people know about
that I discovered by accident and many of my friends
we don't use it for Minecraft sex but you could
in your options
you can actually you know how your Minecraft skin
has like an outer layer and an inner layer
have you ever mastered that before
don't really use it
because it never looks that good
basically your skin can have two layers to it
there's like an inner layer and an outer layer
if the outer layer can have transparency
it's usually used to like make hair stick out
slightly further or something like that
what you can do is in game
you can go to your options and you can actually turn off
the outer layers
so you could design your character to be
naked underneath and then put like clothes
on the outside
and then you could climb into bed with another
Minecraft player and go into your options
and just slowly turn the other layers off
it's doable
there would already be like
client side though they wouldn't know
oh no it works it works on servers
my friend made his head is a
giant like colon V looking thing
oh of course
occasionally he'll walk up to me and he'll just go
and his head turns black because he'll turn that off
and he does it to scare me
and it's actually scary
he scares me
yeah
that's cool
server side like you can see whenever people
turn their things on and off
guys here's a big question
when having sex in Minecraft
spherical boobs
or square boobs
that's tricky that's a tricky question
wait what say that again
when having sex in Minecraft
do you go for the
spherical boobs or the square boobs
the spherical out of this world
literally
I don't
I mean
where do I compare the two
the thing is with spherical boobs
they break the law of Minecraft
they cannot have curves in Minecraft
unacceptable
on the other hand square boobs
look stupid
and not attractive in any way
and it's really funny when people draw all have
like
some of the like Minecraft
source filmmaker porn
are you talking about a slippery tea
I don't know any of the things
I just know that they exist
I never looked at them
never
never looked at them recreationally
at least
it's just really funny seeing that
they animate these like
ooh so hot
and it's the Minecraft girl and she's got
like
cuboids coming out of her chest
and it's like oh yeah
cuboids like no it's stupid
um
I mean yeah it's stupid
but
everything is stupid
you know what you're right everything is stupid
I don't know why I have such a thing
against cuboid breasts
some of our listeners
might have cuboid breasts
and they will probably have their feelings
always
please don't cancel me
our Minecraft audience is going to be
uh it's going to be up in arms
oh no
they can be furious
I made
I made a tweet earlier
and I think it might have been misinterpreted
really
a tweet misinterpreted
maybe well I don't know
I'm not sure
I wrote I tried to join an org
last week and they straight up took my info
and never got back to me because this is a thing
I did
an org like an organization
like a mutual aid
not an orgie
see that's what I think some people might think that I meant
I think some people might think it was a typo
and I was saying that I tried to join an orgie
I did not
do that
there is a
I see these
signs on lawns around
in my neighborhood
for a thing called
sex
yeah it's called sex
and I thought hmm I should try it sometime
it is for
the organization is called
mutual aid
Medford and Somerville
because that's the area I live in
that
so it's a mutual aid org I guess
and I was like
I wonder what that is so when I looked at their website
and you know there was like a thing
you could fill out that's like what are you able
to contribute to like a community
fund and I was like well
it was things like you know can you like
babysit kids
can you you know like
deliver groceries to people can you like
contribute money can you like do tutoring
for people that like can't afford it
or whatever and I'm like well I don't have a car
so I can't transport stuff but I'd be willing
to like if someone
like like can't afford groceries I'd be willing
to like contribute to this fund
and maybe they like buy them groceries
I like I don't know if that's how it works but maybe
so I sent them an email I called them on the phone
I asked what to do they said
go to our website like we'll send you an email fill
out this thing like send send us
back to us and we will like contact you
and I did and they didn't get back to me
it's been like two weeks and I'm like
man I'm literally here
just trying to like offer you some of
my money I do want to like donate
money to you and why are you fucking up
so bad
anyway the point of the story
is no I didn't try to join an orgy that's it
Darren you should have tried
I just want to be
I just want to be in an
org so I can help people
and then when they say thanks thanks for the help
and I say yeah no problem I'm a
communist hail
hail Satan
I love Satan
feels like that's what I should be doing
in order to spread solidarity among the working
class
but it's hard
it's hard get back to me
send me my email back tell me
tell me you want my money please
mutual aid Medford and Somerville
I'm ripe for it to be plucked
okay
I just had to complain about that
what's oblivion fall
you said that you like wrote down some like topics
right yeah I do
did you have some shit
I don't even know
we sort of talked about some of it already
there was like another thing
with the PCP references being hidden in things
one that I don't think
anyone knows about is
an heir to the come throne
which is the second comes on video
is that the one with the boobies
no that's the one with the dick masterson
yeah the dick masterson one
that's been seen by two million people
and those two million people
have unwittingly seen
horseshoe finale without realizing it now
why
how okay so
all the videos have a bit of like a psychedelic
backdrop to them right
you have a kaleidoscope effect yeah
and I took horseshoe finale
I sped it up really fast
and that's it
and that's what I did for the video
no shit
yeah every so often you'll see like an arm poke out
and it's just Jesse
well they haven't
you say they've, is it the whole video
just sped up yeah the entire video condensed
into like two minutes that's so fucking
funny okay
I see I see the hand
well the cool thing is like he has so many posters
around his room that like when the kaleidoscope
they look really cool
I just saw
a face there's a face
at um wait wait
who is at
one minute 18 seconds oh I
had like extra things in there as well like
okay there's just a still
image of somebody's face yeah I had Chris
Ray Gunn's face in there because he reacted to
the cumzone once also
Call Me Carson and
Mumki Jones a few random people I hid in there
because there are people who had like reacted to it before
and I was just referencing them but yeah
that that was a thing I wanted to mention
because it's PCP relevant it is
I can see the bookcase
yeah
uh yeah
I would never have noticed
in a million years but
it needs
the only other interesting thing I guess
is something like I guess
I discovered it recently or I rediscovered it
it's something I forgot or repressed I guess it was
uh an early
I don't know if you'd call this a red pill or a black pill but
um you know
like those TV interviews you see on the news
sometimes where like the news presenter
like who you see every week I mean
I say this I haven't watched the news in like 10 years
but they're like talking to someone on video
and like they're having a conversation back and forth
like in two
screens like yeah there's like two screens
like not like a reporter on the scene
like they'll be like interviewing like some person
or like some professional or something about like
a recent event maybe
sure yeah my mother was on one
of those news interviews ones and
you assume that what happens
is you know they just
set up a live feed and they have a conversation
but it's not what happens
so this was like probably
like 2004-2005 this happened
but uh the news crew came over to our
house the day before
they sat my mother down in a chair
and pointed a camera at her
and they had someone read the
questions and they recorded
her answers and then they packed up and left
the next day
the news presenter
read out similar questions
um and they and they
needed to have a conversation where if they played
the clips of my mother like
him talking back and forth and every time they needed
to make a cut they'd cut to just the news presenter
and then they'd cut back again um
so that way it was like this fake live
interview that was all staged
um and the questions were also
worded differently so that way like if it's
like a contentious political issue and they wanted
to look like oh you're dodging the question
they'll ask you a slightly different
question so that way it looks like you're not
answering or something
really that sucks
it does suck and even
worse version of this
happened to my dad
probably 2010
2011 around that time
it was a channel 9 interview so no one watched it
we only have like free channels
in New Zealand that people watch
but um this was like another like
political discussion about
something um and like
so my dad sits down it's like
it was like a Jordan Peterson style interview
was the one from a few years ago with the
the lobsters and shit something like that right
where you know oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's like two people like like they're sitting on
they're sitting like they have these little nice chairs
and there's like a table in between them and it's like
a back and forth they're in the same room right
is it the is it the it's an Asian
guy interviewing him and Jordan
talks about like like women in
like wearing lipstick and stuff is it that one
it was the one I mean the Jordan Peterson
style interview I'm thinking of is the one where he was
with the blonde woman and
I don't know I don't know if I've seen
I don't know it was like there's a few years ago
people memed it a bunch I saw a bit of it
but yeah imagine interviews sort of
like that where it's like two people in a room
and there's like a table between them and they're just talking
um you know shot reverse shot camera
so my dad
goes in the lady shakes its hand
and they sit down and they're like all right you know nice
to meet you okay now we're gonna go through the questions
and immediately the lady
starts screaming like
very angry like oh how dare
you think this opinion what do you think about this
you idiot you you hate
women you you know you know whatever like whatever
the discussion is like throwing and hurling
insults yelling being aggressive
and my dad is like flushes like he's like taken
him back like whoa what the what the what the fuck is this
um and then he like you know he
loses his composure but you know he tries to answer
the question as best he can and the lady
so so it's not not the interviewer
it's like the person who's like interpreting
the interview questions for well no this time
it was the actual interviewer in this
occasion okay um the last time they sent
someone over to my family's house is a proxy this
time my dad was in the studio with the actual
person and so this interviewer lady
was being super aggressive and yelling
and you can see that my dad is
a little bit flustered um
you know he looks a little bit taken aback
but he answers her questions and I assume
he did a good job and then after they're
done like she immediately
like a switch she's calm again she's like all right
you know thank you for the interview and as my
dad's leaving he turns around
he sees the lady sit back down and they
record her asking the questions again
but this time really calm and polite
Jesus so
when you see it on the
on the TV it's like she's talking
it's crazy that that they would do it
just right there in front of it yeah
they wouldn't even try to hide that from him
that's no I guess I guess
this is a routine no they can get away with it
fuck yeah and so when you see it on
television she's all calm and polite
and my dad's looking all flustered and it's like
this idiot it's like
damn what did she want to like get him for
uh there's talking about
some thing I don't remember what
it was it was
my dad was a controversial figure he's like a
philosopher guy he's got a phd
um and like moral
ethics and they were talking about some like ethical thing
it might have been related
to euthanasia or like
I don't know something
okay sure but uh yeah
and uh
obviously these clips they're on the internet
yeah like you can't
find them like no one fucking watches channel 9
but yeah
my dad told me about it and I was like that's fucked dude
uh that reminds
me
I mean uh makes me wonder about
that thing I don't know if you happen
to see that that Nancy Pelosi
clip from like a couple weeks ago
I don't know it's been floating
there's a there was a someone
was in it was talking to Nancy Pelosi
on the um
I don't fucking know what network
but they asked they asked her a question
and she's just like
stares like I know there can be like a
delay or something oh right
yes and she just stares for they ask
her a question and she's like
good morning good morning it's Sunday
Sunday yeah no no no it was weird
good morning Sunday morning
so I mean the program I don't know
I guess that makes it well
maybe some weird shit happened and it
made sense at the time and it wasn't just
like her going senile or something yeah
we'll never know like we'll never know
you never know like obviously some of the conversations
you see on TV have to be real like when they're
having like proper arguments and stuff like some
of it has to be live but I wonder how much
of it is like just pre-recorded
where they've like manipulated it in some way
yeah
because that happened both time my parents
were on like TV for stuff like this
and like that's just New Zealand
you know and the techniques
have advanced it's been like over 10 years
it's kind of cool it's kind of cool to imagine
it like I don't know
I don't know what you said before about how everyone knows each other
so like
it's not that uncommon to just end up on TV
well yeah but
you all kind of like know everyone or know
someone who knows everyone
has at least one relative or friend of a relative
who was in Lord of the Rings
right like you were an extra
you helped make like the armor for the orcs
or you were a fucking like animator
like I um one of my best friends
growing up his aunt
like animated the spiders
in the Hobbit movies and she recommended me
to go to a certain school that she went to and I went there
yeah and when I was
yeah and when I was there like some guy from Weta
like came over and was like hey guys here's how we made
a Abraham Lincoln vampire
hunter and I don't know
give some presentation
how strange
yeah I remember
do you remember
or have seen the um
the Lindsay Ellis trilogy
of the Hobbit movies
and how the
like they
have fucked a lot with
the workers rights of New Zealand
errs
yeah I did watch that
I didn't know about that until I saw her video
and I was like fuck that's
that's stupid
they're really good videos and I can't remember
the points so I can't regurgitate them for the PCP
they're pretty long
and they're pretty yeah
I remember hearing a little bit about it
at the time it's like people the New Zealanders
like Lord of the Rings
is extremely like tied to like
like I guess national
identity in a certain way we have very few
things we're allowed to be proud of
it's like being proud of your country
a stupid cringe
unless it's rugby or Lord of the Rings
or Flight of a Concord I guess
you're not allowed to be proud of your country because that's bad
bad New Zealander
they were talking about
they were talking about filming it
and like somewhere else
and everyone's like no no you have to keep it here
we need it for vatorism and stuff
yeah it was basically like
like a
like a monopoly thing like
either you
either you sweeten this deal
by like undercutting
workers union rights or whatever
so we can film here for cheaper
or we'll just film it somewhere else
and of course a lot of a country
is the like 5 second explanation of it
yeah pretty much it's like do you want the film
here or do you want workers rights
and people voted no workers rights
that sucks
yeah we want
it to make sense right if it's like
a big part of the frickin
I don't know New Zealand economy
is like Lord of the Rings
and then
and then it was and then it's such a shame
that these movies weren't even good
yeah they sucked they were awful
Peter Jackson got fucked
they didn't give him any time
to do the first one
I was watching
the behind the scenes videos
with Peter Jackson working on the movie
as they were as the last
as they're working on the last one they're like
yeah we're gonna have like a free
months of crunch time at the end or something
like that and I'm like free months
like I can barely handle a week for my projects
and I almost
like if I had done
what my parents wanted me to do I would have
probably been working on those fucking movies
like at least for the last one
because I had like connections there
and I'd gone to the same school that the other person
went to like I could have applied but
I decided to do internet shit instead
hooray
sorry
no it's good
that's how I came to America it's epic
oh that is pretty epic
I'm actually earning more money than I would
if I had gotten a job there so
it's fine
wow just from internet stuff
yeah like two big
two big youtube channels
simultaneously it's good
you get some
do you mind me asking about your
payment models or whatever do you get paid
like per project do you make like a salary
um it's salary
times two actually right now
because there's da games
and there's pencilmation which
huge channel like 17
million subscribers they were in youtube rewind
last year they got like
I think they were in for the number free most viewed
youtube channel of 2019
crazy
yeah like every video gets like tens of millions of views
pretty much and they make like free
a week um I put some
pcp references in there too but they're
really subtle I have to be sneaky about it
ooh I haven't heard
of pencilmation references
I know you did pencilmation
I saw a few episodes
um I
I posted them in your chat
uh Gib at a certain point like
when they came out um I don't have the
screenshots on me right now usually it's like
for like one frame during an explosion
like I'll make a certain piece of the cloud
into the like brop face
that was one I did um
and there's one where there's like an abstract
painting on the wall and I again changed
it to look like the brop face like I just
kind of changed the
so it's just a bunch it's just a bunch of brop
references mostly that
it's I love it for one so
easy to hide it's so versatile yeah
yeah yeah I could see that
it's such a simple like little shape with
more specific pcp stuff like
next time there's an explosion could you maybe have
that spell out like patreon.com
I think
one of the supervisors would notice if I did
that
I don't like the thing is I don't animate
the episodes but I kind of
supervise every single stage like from
storyboard to color to like
through animation and I do like some
re-timing editing and um
so you can sneak a little thing in the background
I have accessed all the files yeah so like
when the animator finishes and sends me the file
I can go in and like tweak stuff and I do
because I usually there's certain problems that
sometimes maybe the animators
didn't do a good job fixing it so I'll go and fix
it maybe there's like a coloring error and I'll fix
that or and while I'm doing
that I can like hide in little references
one of my favorites is it's an episode
that my friend made did
I don't know what it's called on YouTube but the
production code was p migration
there's a TV static
and the TV static
is the pcp theme
audio wave just running by
really quickly
I'll put it
in the show notes you won't see it like you can listen
to it or is it just like visual audio
no like I opened it on audacity
and I took a screenshot of the audio
wave form and then I loaded it into
flash and I converted it
I right I converted there's
an option called trace bitmap that converts
the bitmap into a vector image
and then I like colored it like TV static colors
and yeah that's that's in there
it's like the most subtle reference ever
but wonder if somebody
could like reverse engineer that way
how could you possibly even know
I'll get a
screenshot it might take me a minute but you'll see
it in a bit I know that
wave form anywhere
yeah I see
it in my dreams actually I'll just
link the video of the timestamp and then you'll know
but based
on that
it's so cool that like
people we know are so much cooler
than us
yeah agreed
I'm not I'm not cool as a person
I just work on cool things
that's cool that makes you
cool
no you made a video about
come and you got 60 million views
I'm the only cool one
actually when you really think about it
well good thing I don't think
good thing I have no brain
yeah yeah
yeah
okay
there's a there's a timestamp the TV
static when he changes the channel
I think that's the way form there are a few
different way forms I think that last one was
the PCP theme but yeah
oh yeah yeah that in the TV
when it's static II yeah
string yeah I see it
I see it
that's
so
like
no one would ever know
that's the fun thing about it is I know
and no one else does until I tell them
yeah
pencil mate's great escape
from the cold
what is pencil mate is
just kind of like just kind of goofy cartoons
right it's goofy cartoons
especially for the recent episodes
the animation is actually really really good
like we hire
like we try to like
hire big name animators sometimes we've had
like 70 episodes done by Zurell
who's like a huge like
newgrounds animator I love that
guy's smooth animation
I've directed him on like a bunch of episodes
like he worked for me
and he's super chill
Zurell is
how do you spell that
Z E U R E L
yeah
that's the angel from Evangelion
but misspelled
true story
the animator for this episode
that I linked is made
who's one of my best friends
and he used to be a pony boy
he did some pony animations
and he talked to Jesse a few times actually
at a certain point
pony animation
imagine
whoa he spoke to Jesse
there's a PCP connection
and that's cool
well
I'm looking at Zurell
I'm trying to think what was the first
oh it was Sanfages
nine years ago god
that was the first one
Sanfages 30
I think it was the Pinkie Pie Cupcake song
oh yeah how do you make Sanfage
all you do is
take a couple flower but it was like
TF2 boys
yeah
this boy also
lived in New Zealand for a time
everything's connected what the fuck
so moist and delicious Sanfage
I'm coming for you
yes good
impressive oh my god yeah 2011
a million years ago
14 million views
for the show notes I guess
Eleazar don't forget
Eleazar
hey wake up Eleazar
took my job
oh yeah
oh that's right
oh did we even mention
people know
we didn't even mention that you were the editor for a while
I assume everyone remembers
people I mean I know some people
are like brand new and like
this thing like three months ago they might not know
imagine
being new to the PCP
there must be a few people like that
okay if you
watch the cumzone and subscribe
you have to comment I have to know
the one person who subscribed because of that
whoever you are
yeah I wonder
I fucking wonder if it could
oh yeah like from the cumzone to the PCP
you did have a link in that
first one didn't you
to this channel
yeah
nobody reads the description
oh one girl
one sandwich that was another zero
oh yeah that one
that's a booby animation
yeah it's got girl in it
I remember being like oh my god
I like girl that's a thing I like
I like girl I know what that is
I don't
what is that
aww
oh yep the boobs are going
this one's actually
this one's actually kind of weird looking
this is my favorite reaction channel
right now that we're doing
no one can see the video
yeah you can't see that
sorry I don't know
put it on screen or something
who fucking cares about youtube
uh no
no none of this none of this
uh
what do you guys think about voicemails
voicemails let's go
can I go
okay if you
if you think of any other bright ideas
not likely you can
just shit
where did I save the voicemails
I'm gonna post them in the thing
for you guys to see
yeah
fuck oh how embarrassing
Eleazar cut this out
Eleazar reverb this part
oh
I'm a ghost
nope
I shoot ghosts
hold it
I'm gonna find it
you know what music is missing
ghosts music needs to have
ghosts in it more
hmm
yeah all the people saying about
is like oh my baby left me
nobody talks about I fucking died
I got hit by a train
I mean like ghost as an instrument
like you're listening to a song and you just hear
a big reverb
in the background
there's probably like halloween themed songs
where it's like oh spooky time
I am skeleton man
I got a ghost for a friend
the skeleton fandom
the bony fandom
was epic the bony fandom
yeah the skeleton fandom the bony
I was a bony definitely
I am a skeleton
trapped in flesh and one day I will escape
and rule viewer I found him
oh you found him I found him I found the voicemails
alright first voicemail
I guess I'll put it in links
first voicemail
Ben made me cringe
oh sick
three two one go
so like
I was with my co-worker the other day
and I
dead ass used the phrase
my co-co-ro wish
without even thinking without even hesitating
I said that
in real life
to someone who is basically
internet virgin
and I 100% blame ben saint
for that and I want ben to atone
for his sins
for making me say co-co-ro wish
in real life
it's his fault
it's all of your faults
so I expect
compensation thank you very much
keep making this podcast
because if you don't I will actually
kill myself
don't do that
that's cringe
except
god damn I'm
so cringe
he admits it
just say co-co-ro wish
more people need to say it
he thought he was cringe for saying it
I normalize saying co-co-ro wish
I think it's more cringe
than the other things he said
co-co-ro wish is the only thing that was cool
he was just being cool
what else
what did you do that was cringe
I felt bad about saying co-co-ro wish
and then he said he was going to kill himself
if we stop making the podcast
that's fucking cringe
yeah you're absolutely right
next one is called
please help me
alright let's see
about four months ago
I discovered a youtuber
by the name of totally not mark
he then
decided to start reviewing One Piece
so I started reading One Piece
then youtube's algorithm
recommended to me
almost four hour long lecture
about One Piece
and that was
you guys
and then I said right
I watched every other lecture
from PCP University
based
I've listened to many of your podcasts
you've essentially ruined
my life because
I just
love listening to you assholes
talk about nothing
and I've started using based and cringe
and just so many other
things in my day to day life
I've alienated myself from my friends
and family
I have no one who understands
why
son of a shoe is cringe
I have no one who understands
why surskit is based
I've never even read fucking homestuck
and I know everything about homestuck
because of you people
you've ruined my life
and it's up to you guys to
to fix it
unruined my life
I have no social connections anymore
I spend all my time waiting
until it gets trolled
and hundreds of dollars
on Animorphs books
no
it just cuts off
it's the end
you know alright
there's an added layer
of interest to that
totally not mark
is a guy
who nexus mania edits for
nexus mania friend of the show
who has drawn a
vape red in your vapers 2 book
yes he did
so everything's connected
nexus mania now he's kai jukun
right that's his new handle
is that allowed
I didn't even know that
yeah
he changed his handle he commented on the last video
because he left a voicemail
yeah he's kai jukun
interesting
but that's serendipitous
sounds familiar
strange this is what happens
when you're a big youtuber
like us you get connected
you're in with the elites
it's funny we're like the most
connected least viewed
group of internet creators ever
I wonder
I don't know
I feel like our connections go a lot
further than our podcast
at least
would suggest
I feel
like you're right
I feel like you're right about that
but also do you think that a lot of big
youtubers exist completely
in isolation and don't have
any connection to anyone
yeah they probably talk to each other
all the time
I would imagine most of them probably know a few
I guess in regards to
the ratio of bigness versus connectedness
you're pretty good
yeah
which sucks I'd rather it be the other way around
I did stumble across a podcast once
which was like a bunch of big
Disney animators and people
and they were getting like 100 views
an episode
and they were quoting the PCP
and like saying
just be cool
you know what Dinsney
is actually cringe
and they said
that because of us
saying it because we invented those words
after he dropped out
but Bernie was doing streams
and he was getting like 300 concurrent viewers
which is like
I've had more than that before
so it's like
was he playing
yeah
Minecraft obviously
we have to build a better society
in Minecraft
I'm gonna build a better society in Minecraft
show you how it's done
that's
terrible for impression
impression of boiny sanders before
boiny
boiny sanders
it's me bernie sanders
hey why do I keep watching this dang
muppet show
um fuck
is this stand up now
I gotta run to the store soonish
we might have to lightning round some of these
oh shit
oh god really okay yeah we can do that
alright
okay here we go
I will just spit them out
3, 2, 1
hey this is a new baby bitch listener
at benjam
and I was wondering
who in the podcast would be what fast food restaurant
please discuss thank you
jesus
jesus christ
I don't know I would be like chippers
the fish and chip restaurant
dairy queen because
big booby
yeah that's pretty good
poggers uh I guess I would be
longhorn steakhouse
because I like me
stupid
fuck you is the answer to this question
I would be Aldi
I'm fucking Aldi
it's not a restaurant
it's not fast food but that's because I'm too
I don't I'm like the
instead of going to fast food
I just go and I buy some raw avocados
for 98 cents a piece and I just eat them whole
I mean that's pretty fast
yeah it's
faster if you know what you're doing
if you're trying to speed run
real answer water burger
because what is a burger
there you go
I've never had a water burger it's good I like it a lot
they got good fries
water burger gate
you ever had five guys
I have it tasted like home cooking
as in
when I make it at home it's bad
but it was okay
it's fair it's fair
a blast from the past
chip
on the subject of pornography that I will
have been talking about for the last two episodes
of the procrastinator's podcast
I Oliver Cromwell
as the long dead ancestor of one Mr. Gibbenteek
would like to speak up about the subject
what the hell accent is this
the fact that the wall sees pornography
as something that's okay to exist in the world
at all is a telltale sign
of its corruption on our own natures
now I'm also
close to realising
the runes affects the porn half
on the soul of every living man and a woman
whether they want to partake in it or not
through the example of jaden animations
but thou have us not
realized
I can only pray to God
that he will shine his light upon my faces
oh well I'm off the chop off king Charles's head now
have a good day
I feel stupid
because I kind of missed
Gaby with you
reverend
I kind of missed the
crux of that the main point of that
is saying something about jaden animations
it was something about the jaden animations thing
we got on a whole big
thing about it
yeah the thing about
whether it's okay to draw porn of jaden animations
answer yes
my take is
not a good look
but you do you
I know one of the artists who did that
why is it a bad look
why is it a worse look
than porn of anyone else
because
jaden won't like it and then she won't like you
and if you don't want that to happen
don't
I guess
kind of think if she doesn't like it that's her problem
I know but I guess if you care about her
opinion
I think what it is
there's an implied caring about
jaden animations if you are to draw
porn of her you probably care about her
or like her content or know about her in any way
and so there's
an implication that you don't want to piss her off
or make her hate you
that's why it's bad
I know who do a bunch of stuff
their
kind of thing is they just think that the character design
is really cute and they don't really
have attention to jaden himself at all
so like there's not necessarily any
problem
for the artist
they're like looting
really cute simple character designs
and they drew a bunch of stuff
and art is pretty good
I'll say
the reason I was conflicted in the first place
was because the art I had found
was very good and I was like damn
I don't know whether I'm allowed
but then again nobody cares
really nobody's watching me or judging me
so it's like I guess it doesn't really matter
yeah that's my take
that's my take as well
hey we got another one
fuck
the forbidden
good day and good tidings
gentlemen
today we hear a tale
as old as time
once more repeated
and not too long ago
within a cave that stretches
deep below the surface
into the crust of the earth
there lie a book
of legend
it was known in centuries past
as the necronomicon
book of the dead
and so it was
that an unlikely party of four
only two nights ago
would gather around the grave
of a fallen warlord
clutching that
olden text bound by human flesh
did they speak words
stricken from the Latin tongue
long ago
and the wind did cease
and the night before silent
there came a rumbling
as a hand rose from that grave
and a feared voice
once more did speak
go
no
return of samurai scroll
okay
until next time
sayonara
he got us, he's very good
that samurai
I'm like two episodes behind
is this still going on every episode
yes
he's such a trickster god
oh
oh my god
that was impressive
I don't know what he needs the scrolls for
when he's got the necronomicon
but
here's why
books and you scrolls old
old new good bad, there you go
oh yeah
scrolls much older, much better
necronomist scrolls
we got more voicemails
hall was way better than nirvana
okay
not a roughing material
betereiru
did you know
2 million america
areu betereiru
every dayo
and most of it
by your toretaru
benno sento san
this must stop
with your help
we cannot stop betereiru
and benno sento san
before it toretu
zoi no
the betereu
for oneru
but until next time
sayonara
until next time
how does that cut this out
this is propaganda
this is not allowed
this is banned here
max game
here we go
next one is ikben jam
faces the music
i know this guy
i'm back
i want to talk about the last voicemail
that i spent
ages making
i've come to realize now
that you can't compare your friends to fast food restaurants
just nonsense
stupid ridiculous
i already know that i'm in voice
voice chill now
when i die i know i'm going to hell as well
and there's no repercussions
for my sins
the best i can do now is to go into a room alone
and whip myself with cat tails
so
i'd like to
make amends the best i can
until next time
see you then guys
see you then
see you in the next shitty voicemail
that will make fun of you
i empathize with this man very much
there have been so many times where i've submitted a voicemail
and then immediately messaged nate
and said stop delete it please
it's like
it's a good thing
i wasn't in charge at the time
because
i don't engage in such
i don't negotiate with terrorists
absolutely not
oh god
it's just like when you have a big coom
and then you're like what the fuck am i looking at
you know
this is gross delete it
you look at your hand and you're like i'm so fucked up
like shinji in that one
sorry
to make amends
we're in limbo
oh is that
is that what he's doing
right
oh that's smart
my asshole
well he's slapping himself i think
i'm like i'm empathizing
i'm not convinced
i think he's just clapping his cheeks
i need some video evidence
show me the scars
wanna see him clap those cheeks
i mean that too
everyone's fine
we need video evidence
of something else
something whatever it is
either way we wanna see it
we're hungry for anything
next one
aka the untitled abridger
all right if donald trump
dies of covid does that mean i don't
have to vote for biden anymore
oh yeah that's a thing
they'll just run pence
but i mean
he won't win
i don't know kinda
i guess
they'll just keep trump alive in a robot body
it'll be like
future armor
put his head in a jar
i think they've made that technology right now
and then he'll be president forever
um i mean
that's literally already the case
well the head in the jar thing
no him being a robot i mean
i don't know it's pretty real to me
did you see
okay there was a picture
of him i guess at the debate
and like you see him from the side
and like there's like a part in his hair
on the side of his head
and like there's a piece
of his head that looks weird almost like it's made of
like metal or something
um wait
i want to see the image because i don't know what you mean
i want to see if i can
if i can i find the
it was floating around twitter
the other day
it was just like a weird
i don't
i never i didn't find any like
explanation
for what it is
i'd love for the image
to be like an obvious
photoshop of him with like a like a nuclear
rocket
stuck to his head or something
no it's it's like um
it was like a patch of some
like didn't really look like metal it was kind of brownish
just looked like solid like plastic
maybe it didn't have any like details
on it
but it was like just the
fuck i can't find it and i don't know what to google
in order to find it maybe that's his brain handle
i don't know
it's it's it's your brain force
you turn the thing and you speak
trump
head implant will i find anything there it is
whoa here it is head implant
okay this this is just a detail
photo
but um copy image
this is what it looked like
okay it seems like it might be
well yeah it doesn't seem like
anyone really figured it out but it might be a bone
like a bone implant hearing aid of
some kind
he's an old man maybe a hearing aid
i don't know what that is that does look
like a cyborg like
like iron hatch that you open
and like plug the
it looks like you could like open it up
and there's like a little plug
but it looks yeah it looks
like bone it looks it looks very unpleasant
looking i don't like it
but like yeah in
in in humans is
fucking it
yeah this is like the least
flattering image of a person you could ever have
is like the ear center stage
just the corner of the eye off the side
it is it's gross
it's gross to be a brain in a skeleton
in a flesh body
uh
yeah bone implant hearing aids seems to
be a pretty adequate explanation
that's that's that's what i'm going to go
with uh for the time- okay so mystery
solved but uh
yeah but gross but he's already a cyborg
so you're correct
lol
okay and next the voicemail
notsamurai.m bracelet
Really?
Sceptical To Say The least
I
Don't know man. I I enjoy what's going on right now. It's here. It's nice to hear you and
Tom talk about your things once in a week, but I don't know. I feel like y'all are trying to kill PCV as a brand
by continuing forward can't hint
maybe because of the cumulative drama of
Everything, you know, Jesse ragequitted DeVue dropped off the face of the earth. I'm key monkey seven years ago face of the earth
Mage went to dreamland and munchie became
They you know y'all have a new show I don't like anime though. I don't I like y'all personalities. I grew up with y'all
Kind of in a way over a couple years
You know and I didn't get it. I didn't get munchies or Jesse's humor
I do now I used to cringe at digi, but you know, I
Appreciate her for her willingness to defend her principles on free speech, you know, I feel like you guys were my friends and
Hearing what
Me and probably the rest of us as the end of an era
It's a little bit sad
All right, sure. It's coming out a weird time too. I have a one-year-old son and a wife and
Think I've ever have these things when I clicked on science you 101
You have them now you're welcome
I guess I did and that's what's happened and it's time-passing
That's it man
Yeah, sounds like it
Well, I mean you can mourn like the past, but I thought I thought I really thought there was gonna be a punchline
Yeah, I was thinking that but like he kept going. I mean sure like the the end of an era
It's sad like people feel it sad. I
I can't like
Worry about that in the same way that other people do and also, you know, we were never your friends. That's the first
Yeah, it's it's it was it we made like we did have discussions about like the dangers of like a
What's it called?
Parasocial relationships. I think he knows that I don't think sure I was saying
Yeah, like that's how he feels about it and because he feels about it. He's like
But I've heard and seen people say just end the show like what why should we end the show because you're feeling sad
It's not yours. We're the guys making it
Right because it's like different. I don't know. I mean I I liked like I
Certainly got a lot more entertainment out of a lot of the older episodes, but it's still nice
I still listen to it and enjoy it like
Wow, wow, thanks. Well, thanks a lot. Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, shut the fuck up
the
It's you know, it's
It's felt it's it's hard for me to I felt like it's the end of an era so many times that I think like I've kind of just
internalized the lesson that like
Everything is change all the time the only constant is change. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's ever everything is the end of an era
No, no, no, it's weird. It's weird to even be thinking about like like mage hasn't been on in like six months
Davoo hasn't been on in like oh what like years like Jesse hasn't been on in like over a year
You know, he was at rad con and that was like it. This is like. Oh, this is like past
This is like over and done once you becoming a real boy. What does that even mean? I don't know this this tone of fine
Out this took people talk about it with a tone of finality. Yeah, like today's the last time anything will ever happen
But like nothing is ever final and and life has changed. I know I know it's a river the real
That they're having is that like it doesn't it's not gonna bounce back and suddenly be like it was
And they're coming to terms with the fact that it was past is the past this time
Cuz like I don't know the PC views always had like a rotating cast of
characters and some of them are just not coming back and they're just sort of coming to terms with that and I'm like, okay, I
Simplifies before I don't understand. I don't know if I sympathize anymore. I feel like we've had enough of this
I feel like this has gone on enough times. It's like, do you not get it yet? Do you not understand that nothing ever stays the same?
Yeah, I mean, I don't like agree that like
You know, I don't think that there's nothing to it
I just think it's it's kind of an old meme at this point to be like tired of the way the Pope the show is
Being sad about the end of an era like it's almost it's itself a meme that needs to die
Man, yeah, I'm sad. I miss when you all reviewed pony
Man go back to it. Please
Yeah, we always joke about having to go back and it's like I
Think the thing that's getting me is that people aren't like
You know, I don't know they seem actually distressed about this
It was like people memeing about like, oh, we have to go back. It's like half ironic
It's kind it's like our pony was really cool and and all that like it's an era that's gone
We'll never have it back and it's silly, but it was fun and
you know
Previous PCP times
Like it was a different flavor and it's like yeah, it's gone
It's not gonna be exactly the same as it was
But like people I don't seem to be able to like have a laugh about that. They don't they just seem sad and it's annoying. I
Don't want to shit on this guy in specific too much
I don't I'm not like bothered by him saying anything that he said, but but the the I shouldn't have said annoying
It's not what I mean. Yeah, yeah, sure. Um, but um, I know what you mean the general
Okay, like when we talk about like how we have to go back to the pony days when we're nostalgic for the pony days
It's because I
Mean it was it was um, I don't know like that was like an external circumstance that made things fun
It was like a fun time to be like breaking into the to the YouTube sphere or whatever and then but like
to say it now to say I
Don't know if like you prefer how if you prefer the older episodes and newer episodes fair enough but to like
To like want to go back like to ask to go back is
To like in this case when you're talking about the PCP like what you mean is like
Those people that that have like declined to be on the show anymore is like make them come back
And it's like well, what how would you even do that?
Like it kind of doesn't even make sense like your request is sort of nonsense when you really think about it
Am I making sense here? Yeah, I mean, I'm just I feel like why would you wish?
Why would you wish someone to do something that they have like made it expressly clear that they wish not to do?
It's not even just that it's that but like
Even if they do realize that, you know talking to us about it isn't going to get them force them to come back
It's it's the it's the either they come back or you end the podcast because I don't like it now
Oh, yeah, like I just don't get that like it feels almost
Oh, yeah, that's entitled to say entitled. Yeah
I don't know. No, I agree. I agree with that. It's very stupid very cringe. I don't know
And I don't I don't want to be too mean to this specific voicemail or anything
He's not like a big problem. He's not just a jumping I get for the I get worries coming from like I was I was a little sad
When you guys stopped doing pony stuff and then I'm like, oh wait, the other stuff you're doing is cool
And then I followed over and then I stopped doing pony stuff and it's like that was freeing like being away from it
Was actually the best decision I ever made and so yeah
Yeah, munchy going off being a real boy, you know quote-unquote like I don't even I don't even I'm sure yeah
I'm sure like it's really good for him bow and that's good if it is. I hope he's having a good time
I mean, he's he's doing what he wants to do. Yeah, as it as is everyone else whether they choose to come on the show or not
It's their own choice and do you not want them to like do as they wish
Like whatever it is. It is what it is and
Everyone is everyone is acting according to their own agency and
Why would you have it any other way? Why why wish why wish for something else? What's the point?
It's terrible stupid. It's like, okay, okay
I feel like we've gone on too long about this
But the last thing I say is the tone and like I actually really appreciated the comments in the last episode a lot of people really liked the cyber shell
Episode they thought he was a good guest. They thought the conversation was entertaining a lot of a lot of positive comments
That's fine, but on like some of the episodes that had that people have complained about
The the the feeling that they are complaining at the people on the podcast about
People choosing not to be on yeah, like it's like it's like like we're the ones like like it's our fault
For the ones that chose not to be here like how it doesn't even make it doesn't make any sense
But I guess there's no one else if they if they're not in the podcast
You can't leave a comment at them. These only we're the only ones you can you can criticize because we're the only ones here
I hate that so that I really hate that attitude
Fuck you commenters
Yeah, it's it's it's just like well, we talked about it enough next voicemail. Yeah, it's that's more than enough
This one is morality free electric jamboree
So the original voicemail about morality that I sent was in response to a discussion
You guys were having where you're trying to find ways to like define or to describe a moral system
I offered the terms of utilitarianism in like a goofy dumb way and then
Elaborated on what I actually meant by that in the next week
I was saying yet when taken to its logical conclusion
Utilitarianism just means to look at the utility of actions on a case-by-case basis and make moral decisions based on that
Tom last week said
Basically that he agrees that that is a good way to describe how people think morally and then said that my original voicemail
Was dumb because I was offering utilitarianism as a way to just like as that
System but like the second voicemail was just a definition for the first voicemail
So if you agree with the second you agree with the first
also
It was brought up like oh, I don't trust humans to be able to figure out the utility of each action and like
The human fallibility is not something specific to this way of thinking if that's a critique of every moral framework
You could come up with that's like I'm not saying that this is something that that transcends the limitations of our minds
This is just a responsible way to handle things
And it's the way that people generally do handle things so I was accurate and it's a good like thing
So everyone agrees. I am right all your disagreements are just different ways of saying you agree with me
All right, I don't know that's a good. That's a pretty good dunk pretty good dunk on us
I think I I haven't listened to this guy's voicemails, but I feel like
Utilitarianism in this way of just finding the utility is useful some of the time but not all of the time
Like I think what he's because like with the case like the Jaden animation
I think you're falling into the trap that he described no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I'm saying that like for things like life and death
Utility utilitarianism in terms of like maximizing the number of lives saved
right? Is that how you would use that? But like on a smaller scale, on a smaller scale,
I don't know, you can't like, let's say somebody tells a joke and somebody doesn't like it.
Utilitarianism might end up with that person, like it's since it's only one person and more
people than that person enjoyed the joke, then the joke should be said or it should be allowed
or whatever. And it's a little more complex than that all the time. His first email was
utilitarianism means like whatever causes the most utility. And me and Tom were like,
yeah, but what is utility? How do you determine utility? His second one was like, yeah, what
I'm saying is, I'm not proposing that like we use this as a universal like universally agreed
upon yardstick to be applied across the board. The idea is that each situation should be
judged in a case by case basis, but with the understanding that like what we are looking
for is a resolution that maximizes utility. So he's saying, yeah, to me, that sounds
interesting. I just don't know how I don't know what is like on a large scale and a small scale,
what is utility? And like if we come up with two different examples, it's whatever you think
it is. It's whatever you think it is. I mean, I don't know. Let's say something like a trigger
warning or whatever. Somebody gets triggered by something, but most people don't. And it's
they're fine with it. Should, you know, the warning be in place? I actually, I guess it's
easy just to put a warning in place. I guess the thing would be like, if you don't like the
warning, just ignore it. If, if, well, it's not, it's not about that. It's like, should you put a
word in a thing? If one person will be upset and hundreds of thousands of people would not be
upset. Does utilitarianism have any like relevance there at all? Should you just not say it because
there's anybody like like utility is like you're choosing the better of two options. And I don't
know how you would like judge it in every situation. It feels like the word utility does not work in
all those different things. I really think you're falling into the exact trap that he described,
because I think I don't even know what he's saying. I don't know what utility means. Let me send
another voicemail, send another three voicemails. No, what he's saying, what he is saying is that,
yeah, you would just like that situation you describe, you would just have to look at it and
make some sort of like calculus of like, okay, well, how many people will be triggered by this
thing? How much distress will that cause them versus how much will, you know, including this
element in the work, you know, improve its themes or improve its quality in a way that like is
enjoyed by more people? Like, which, which does the negative outweigh the positive and just be
like, well, I don't know, what do you think? Do you think it does? Do you think it doesn't? And
like that's the, that's the decision making. I think it's not, yeah. It's very dependent on the
whims of the society that you're in too. Like if you have a society that really hates gay people,
then maybe it's more utility to just kill the gays because then you make more people happy if it's
only a few, right? I don't agree with that. I think, I think, I think the thing I'm having trouble
with is like, when it comes to like an individual, you know, you think of a situation, you're like,
okay, what is the, the most utility you can get out of this? It sort of is so wide ranging that
the term has no meaning whatsoever. It really just is do whatever you feel like it just means
whatever you think is good. Yeah. So therefore it is a completely useless term. I don't know why
it's even being used in such a like a, like a wide way. It's, I mean, I guess I agree in that if
you're going to be like, yeah, my system, my moral system is utility, utilitarianism, by which I mean
that I do things that I think will have outcomes that I feel are good. And like, yeah, I guess that
is too, you haven't really answered that question. That's why I mean, the thing I was talking about,
I think you've convinced me that it is a little overly broad. Yeah, like, like the thing I was
talking about, I think, before a couple of weeks ago was that it morality is, it's impossible to
have one rule that fits everything. And having multiple different specific rules for every
possible eventuality cannot have a word single, like a single concept applied to all of them. So
it's like, ah, fuck it. Fuck it. Fuck it. It's all just, it's all opinion anyway, at the end of the
day. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, based. Next one. Here we go. Oh, squad Zilla. Hey, Tom, I just wanted to know
that you have some competition on the Godzilla podcast front by none other than Maddox. He has
a Godzilla podcast called Godzilla versus podcast zero. Just thought that was pretty fucking funny.
Godzilla versus podcast zero. Is that like a theme podcast or just an episode of a Maddox podcast?
Sounds like an episode. No, it's um, Hailey Mancini and Maddox rules. No, it's a it's an entire podcast
about Godzilla starring Maddox and this other, this Hailey person. Kill it. What the fuck? Okay,
that's weird. That's funny. Did they know about this? Uh, it's been going since February of last
year. You should feud. You should, you should fight. You should call them out. They should
definitely start beef. They should definitely start beef with Maddox. I mean, in fact, they
should sue Maddox for stealing their ideas. I'm going to be honest. I don't know where this podcast
is located. Yeah, I, I see there's a Twitter account, but I, I certainly don't see a podcast.
I can't find like where it is in space. I'm not, I'm not, I'm getting a little lost looking for it,
to be honest. Squadzilla, though, I can find easily. That's, that's right there. That's imminent.
Yeah. Immediate, tangible. Uh, uh, fuck. Yeah. Okay. Funny, funny shit. Here we go. From Tony
again. Tony again. Yo, Tony again here. I actually have something to say this time. I appreciate
how at the end of the Tales Get Strolled video, when you're talking about gender pronouns and crap
like that, that you somehow managed to like circle around and independently discover the idea of
gender abolitionism and hell yeah, brothers. Fuck pronouns. Don't have them. Fuck gender roles.
Don't have them. Fuck gendered expectations. Don't have them. If I see a person walking down the
street, I shouldn't assume that they should look a certain way. That's weird. You say that I independently
arrived at it, but like, no, I've, I, I think I probably wouldn't describe myself as a gender
abolitionist for a while now. I think we've all had that even before Nate left. Nate, I remember
having a conversation about gender and he was like, yeah, like we shouldn't, it doesn't necessarily
need to have all of the, the, the stereotypes enforced. It's, it's all arbitrary. And we all agree
with that. It's just like, I think a little like real, like it's a, it's a, it's a fanciful idea
that is hard to implement. And it's, it's just sort of like easier to play along with, you know,
if you, if you decide that you like wearing makeup and wearing dresses and having long hair and,
and all that, then I guess it's easier to just call yourself a female because that's what people
expect. And it, it's easy. It just smooths things over. I don't agree with that. No, I mean, I, I,
I agree. I agree that you should be able if, and only if you want to call yourself a female
irrespective of whether you like makeup or whatever. Sure. Sure. I mean, I feel like I,
I would want to do that because it fits with everything else. Like I like, I like people
calling me. Yeah. I mean, I can understand if the way you are is more in line with what
is society expected of the female species. I understand that like, maybe it's,
that makes it more comfortable for you or whatever to do that. Yeah. It's, it's, it's because I
understand what you're saying. I grew up in a society and these expectations are like burned
into my brain that I can't easily just completely forget them. But I do agree that like, it would
be better to not have them in any way at all. Like you should teach kids that it doesn't matter.
And then maybe they won't have as much of like a, a feeling about it. And it wouldn't be an issue
in the future. It'd be the most based. Yes. It'd be the most possible, the most based we could,
we could get on a scale of cringe to base. Okay. Sick. Next one. Digimon Fox. Yeah.
Well, we're talking about Digimon on the last episode. And I am a Digimon fanatic. I've watched
literally every series, like twice, even the shit ones, even season six. And I just want to say
Tamer's easily the best one. But Tom brought up that, I think Hercules Kabu Teriman wasn't shown
and he is an idiot for that. Because Hercules Kabu Teriman and all the original season one cast,
mega evolutions were shown in Digimon Try the movie series. You fool. You absolute moron. Also,
Digimon Adventure 2020 Tom is back. It's airing again. And you should watch it because it's
really fucking good. It's just real good. It's fucking sick. And you should watch it. And Digimon
is sick. And then you were talking about Digimon. It's the best thing ever. Thank you. I'm glad
that this this guy got to flex his nerd knowledge about Digimon. I bet he doesn't get opportunities
to do that often to dunk on someone. I was a Digimon boy growing up, but I wasn't super into it.
Yeah, I was into the first series. And then I fell off it after they replaced the main cast.
I had the VHS of the first three episodes of Digimon. And I was annoyed because a VHS only
had three episodes. I was like, damn, how many VHSes am I going to have to buy? There's too much.
Fuck this. And I never tried to get any more. I saw Tamer's on TV and it was cool. My parents
bought a Digimon world for the PS1. And I think this was a discussion on the PCP recently
that your Digimon will take giant shits on the floor and you have to scold them for it.
No, you just clean them up, right? You can clean them up and then you have to yell at them
so that they don't do it again. And there's also a giant poop Digimon. Where else are they going
to shit? I don't know. I don't remember. I talked about Digital Dream, the guy with a couple
thousand subscribers. And I don't know if I specified, but I watched tutorials on him on how
basically to digivolve your Digimon in the latest release of the Cyber Pet or whatever
they're called, Digital Pets. And it's really funny that the screen is so small. The biggest your
Digimon can be is 10 pixels high, 12 pixels high or whatever. And so you got small ones
just a little blob. Then you got bigger ones and then you got ones that fill up the screen,
but even ones that fill up the screen or maybe just like a little six foot tall Agumon. But
then you got like Exo fucking Galaxy Super Novemon or whatever that is a fucking cosmic.
Yeah, that's like 50,000 feet tall and contains the entire universe within itself. And it's the
same like 12 pixels high. It looks identical. Yeah, I was like trying to strategize like which
one of these would I want to go for? Like which would be the most powerful base base?
They only have a Digimon thing. I know recently what I've seen is the Pokemon have good women.
They do. I think they're pretty good sometimes. And I saw this character and I thought cute.
I like them. That's a Digimon girl. I don't know her name. That's a Digimon girl. Yeah,
she's from like a new game. It's pretty cute. But it's pretty cute. Looks like a cop to me.
Yeah. No, no, she's like it looks like an airline. She looks like she works for an airline.
She looks like she works as a receptionist and she hates you for asking questions. Okay,
I found their name like Dotte Makiko or something. It's like it says like Cyber Sleuth. So I guess
she's like an investigator. I don't know what's going on. But a good character. Okay, I guess
she might be a little bit of a cop. Might be a little bit of a cop then. I like that she's mad
at you. That's good. Yeah, she's always pissed off, which is epic. I looked at Digital Dream again
yesterday and his newest video is a like Digimon fan song called like it's like a Halloween cover
of the Monster Mash, but it's like the with the lyrics changed to be about Digimon. Oh, dude. But
it's kind of good. Like it's like a hard rock cover with like electric guitars and drums and
shit. And like it's like it's like well produced and kind of good, you know, for what if you can
accept the absurd premise. He executed it with a plum. I just think it's very funny. Everyone
goes subscribe to Digital Dream. That guy's sick. Yeah, don't subscribe to Regular Dream. He sucks.
Yeah. No, fuck that guy. Like there's some guy called Regular Dream who's like got like
hundreds of thousands of followers. You're like, nah, nah, nah. Hey guys, I just had another dream.
Gonna take a make a vlog about it. I'm talking about fucking Minecraft YouTuber Dream, who's
actually kind of good videos, actually. But is there actually someone? Yeah, I didn't know.
He like does, he like speeds run. He's speed runs Minecraft, all his friends try to kill him,
and it's genuinely really exciting videos. And he's he's too good. He's too good at the game.
But everyone knows it's too popular. We can't talk about him. That's stupid. No, no, no, no. He'll
kill us. He will send his lawyers after us to kill us. We're basically by talking about him,
we're making the rich richer. We shouldn't do that. Damn it. And shut the hell is our edit out.
Sleep it. No, don't. No, I don't believe. Oh, I love I love I love this.
Peepie poo poo nine. Let's go.
Konnichi fuck. No, no, fuck. Samurai, fake or death. And while Samurai tell a story
about a necronomical, he steal, scroll right from the end of pocket.
It can't be true. What do you keep in your pocket, Ben?
From my scrolls. Wait, where are those fucking scrolls? No, what am I gonna wipe my ass with now?
Because I crave to be in your shoesy. Josh is the sweetest and the most powerful
somebody in the world. I your imaginal, she smell like a sakura blossom and the honor
your house, your girlfriend, your rightful death. I want to be with you. I crave to be with you.
And for that brief moment, I was inside your house with your girlfriend.
In that moment, I was with you and it was great honor.
Wait, this is not Samurai scroll, Ben. This is clean. What the fuck is that?
Fuck you. Ben no saint or son. But until you next time, sayonara.
I just, I was, I was just meme and I just wrote it as a joke.
On the Samurai looking like a snack. You can be my girlfriend, Samurai.
Tastes like, hit me up. She does smell, she does smell like sakura blossoms in honor though.
Let's be real. I know the smell of honor. Let's be fucking real.
Fuck. Here we go. Here we go. Your good podcast poise from, okay. I think it's supposed to be boys.
Nate Bestman. More like Nate Bestman.
Digine, more like, Digine collecting her podcast. Endless Jess. More like, endless just getting
that guy ended a long time ago. Munchy Shatsky. More like, Munchy Shant be on the podcast anymore.
Cause he's something. This is like, pitched down, Cassie. Anyways, it's a good show.
I really like the show. It's a really good podcast. I love you, Ben. I love you, Tom.
Love you, hippo gibbuchan. Bye. It almost could be pitched down, Cassie. I don't think so.
I mean, I was getting furry voice vibes, so you never know. Oh, dear. Here's another clue.
Another clue on the pile to be sleuthed by that, by Date Makiko. Yeah. Yeah, bringing it back.
I like, I like the, the obvious jokes were avoided. Good job.
I was waiting for Munchy Shatsky, but it never came.
Just like, just like me. Ah, you did the annoying obvious sex joke.
Fuck yeah. Okay. Top 10 albums potentially related to butt sex. All right, I'm intrigued.
Number 10, The Beatles, Magical Mystery Tour. Number nine, The Stooges, Raw Power.
Number eight, Michael Jackson, Thriller. Number seven, Hantara, Volga Display of Power.
Number six, Persev, The Ugly Organ. Number five, Sigur Ross, Open Parenthesy, Close Parenthesy.
Number four, Mos Deff, Black on Both Sides. Number three, Miles Davis, Bitches Brew.
Number two, Minor Threat, Out of Step. Number one, John Coltrane, My Favorite Things.
Okay. My favorite things, Singular Butt Sex.
It's actually, it's actually just about one thing.
Is, see, is to be like, Close Parentheses, Open Parentheses thing, like meant to look
like a butthole. Did I get that? I think so. Let me see. Let me, let me look up.
Sigur Ross. Oh wait. Sigur Ross. Or is it like that? Which way was it?
He, he think he said Open Parentheses, Close Parentheses. Yes. I guess it is a butthole.
Yeah, yeah. No, no, no. Yeah, the album is. Sigur Ross is, wait, is that a?
This is what it looks like. This is what the album cover looks like.
Oh, it is. It's, it's the, it's the, the band that Kezzy likes. It's another Kezzy.
It is, yes. Oh right. You could, you could put the Goatsey hands on that, pulling it open. That
could work. Oh, dude, it's gay primario. Let me tell you a story about Goatsey.
Yeah. I, well, it's not really. There's a, there's a, there's a bagel shop down my street.
Oh no. It's called, and their logo, their logo is a, no, no. Their logo is like a cartoon girl.
It's like, it's like a bust. You know, it's like from like the, the, the shoulders up.
Yeah. But she's holding a bagel and looking at it, but she's holding it with both hands
in a way that kind of looks like, you know, she's goat seeing it. She's grabbing that
Pona. Oh my God. Basically. What is the brand called? Could we Google it?
It's called, um, I'd rather not say it because it's like close to my, well, well, I'll, I'll put it
in the chat. Okay. I don't know if they, I don't know if like there's chains of it. I haven't heard
of it, but no, I think there's, it's just one. It's like in my, it's, I mean, I've said that,
like, I've said more or less where I lived before. If someone wanted a fucking piece,
it's called Goldilocks. I've already said that I live near Tufts University. So like,
yeah, there's a, there's a bagel place in my neighborhood called Goldilocks.
I didn't know you lived near there. Oh, I'll see you soon.
It's true. It's so fuck. Um, so, um, yeah, but, uh, do they have the, yeah. So you, so you see
the resemblance, right? I didn't realize her face would look so derpy. I was thinking of like a
Wendy's girl. Give, it kind of looks like your art style a little bit. It does. Not gonna lie.
A little bit. Yeah. A little bit. You got to draw her, Gib. You got to put her in a comic. Oh, no.
Um, but the story is I was walking by on the way to the post office to send off some more copies
of Vapors 2 available now on my Twitter feed. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. And, uh, and they, um,
and on my way back on the way there, I was, I was, I walked by them and they were playing music
inside and I heard a couple of notes that I recognized. I was like, wait a minute, wait,
what is that? What is it? What is that song? What is this? Is that like a Disney musical? Is that
like from a movie or something? Like, why do I recognize that? That's so familiar. And I went
back and I listened and I realized, no, they're playing, they were playing bad religion. They
were playing like old, an old bad religion song from like one of their like earlier albums. And
I was like, oh, fuck yeah. These guys are old school punks. So I went and I delivered my shit
and on the way back, I was like, you know what? I don't even want bagels. I wouldn't eat them
because they're not keto, but I'm going to just buy like a dozen bagels from these people and just
give them my housemates because like, fuck it, have them, have some, because I want to give them
my business because they like a band that I like. And uh, but I, but I went up to the door and I
rang and like they didn't answer. I think they're doing some weird thing with like because of COVID.
I think they're like, they're open for like, you have to like call ahead of time and order
or something. I don't know if they do just like, yeah. So I didn't, I was not able to complete
the transaction. Darn. But, but I tried. Ripperoni. I'll maybe, maybe in the future I will, Lamal.
Uh, yeah. Cool. So, uh, that's that voicemail. Where's the next voicemail? How many more do we have?
Yeah. How many? Uh, like eight. Oh my God. Okay. We're most of the way through. Okay. Uh, part one,
let's look, we need a direct democracy and the problem is like representative democracies, right?
They, they don't like the reason why they exist is because of two reasons. One, because direct
democracy used to be impractical before the digital age, for the internet age. And number two, because
if you have like a politician, they're expected to know about political things. You know what I mean?
And like, you can't expect the average person to know everything. Well, you can, but they won't.
And the problem with direct democracy is that the average person is retarded, like really dumb.
Like the average person doesn't care about anything and they're stupid. It really just
open your eyes and you'll see it. Uh, but the thing is like, you think the solution, right? You only
let smart people vote, right? And then you'd be like, well, how do you define a smart person?
Smart person, right? Is it because there are people who are very intelligent, who would be
extremely unknowledgeable and would make poor decisions. So I guess you'd have to test their
knowledge, but you'd also have to like make sure they're not like really dumb and would just come
to the wrong conclusion. And, you know, maybe the solution to that is to simply only take votes from
a intelligent group of people or only take votes from the most intelligent group of people. For
example, white males. Yeah, we got there. We got there. Woo. Uh, uh, was that ironic? Was that
like, was the point there that like, wait, was the point that we actually do need a direct
democracy or was that the joke that we, that it would be stupid? Uh, I think I mean, I feel like
there was a, like an implication that you could technically do a direct democracy on your phones.
Vote now with your phones. Uh, if, if there was like, like live stream Senate man is like, all
right, we're going to vote on, um, this thing and then vote now with your phones. Do you like it?
Do you hate it? And then everyone who gives a shit will use the app, whether they're stupid or not.
And then we'll know. I think that could work. Well, we can find out who's stupid by how they
vote. Is there, is it so then kill them? That was called part one. Is there a part two? Uh,
no. Okay. Thank God. Maybe. Yeah, I agree. Um, that's, that's plenty. Oh, wait, I want to say,
I saw a great tweet. I saw a great tweet today from my boy on Twitter. Posadas trap God. Um,
uh, and, uh, wait, what's his name? Well, he goes by, he goes by Aaron Dolphin emoji now,
whatever. Posadas trap God with no O on the trap God. He said, uh, he said, uh, uh,
said democratic socialism is, well, he said it was an oxymoron, but he meant redundant. He said
democratic socialism is redundant because socialism is inherently democratic. And you know what? He's
fucking right. That's your education. That's everyone's fucking anarchist education, uh,
for this episode. That's me going on my political run. I don't like everybody on subs. Everybody
unsubscribe. Um, I am, I am being messaged, uh, frantically that we, we got to go to the store
because it's going to close. Uh, okay. We ran too long. I'm sorry. It's our, it's on us. It's on
us. We've got like a couple more. It's right. Uh, what happens with foes? Are you going to try
and do them yourself or next week or no, there's no way we could, we could bear the burden of doing
we have to die. We must, we must soldier on. We must listen to the last seven voicemails. I'm
sorry. We have no choice. There's no alternative. There's no way. If only there was some way
we could cease to do it, but we cannot. Okay. I'm sorry. Oblivion. It was great having you on.
Yes. Thank you for coming on. Thanks for being a guest, buddy. Thanks for having me, uh, be gay.
It's good. Uh, um, everybody, I mean, everybody subscribed to oblivion fall. It's on YouTube.
Yeah. Or the after dark. That's the big one now. Like my secondary channel, like, yeah, I put
comzone on there when it had a hundred subscribers. Now it has 60,000 and it surpassed my main. So
I'll go to maybe rebrand. I don't know what's going to happen, but, uh, cool. Oh yeah. Go check out.
If you haven't seen, uh, comzone. Wait, is it comzone? Yeah, welcome. Welcome to the comzone.
Yeah. Go check out that. Yeah, the other is a link. Check out, check out the other, um, yeah,
check out all the oblivion fall links in the, down in the thing, down in the thing. Yes.
Thank you. Thank you for being on. Yeah, you're, you're welcome. And this is fyi. The last time I
was on a podcast also had to leave early because of going to the store. That was a podcast with
the store. That was a podcast with A and Y and keyframe. If you remember those names.
I remember A and Y and keyframe. Wait, when was the hell long ago? That was probably like 20 years
ago. Well, that podcast was like two years ago. I mean, even two years ago was past the, was past
the heyday. Oh yeah. I was out of, I was out of the community, but he escaped with me. He also
works at a DA games. So yeah. Oh, you are. Yeah. I, I have, I have, I see, I see keyframe.
I'll see a tweet of hers like every once in a while. She's like, I don't know. I'm like
peripherally aware of keyframe and everyone I'm like, huh, so she got like a real job,
huh? That's crazy. Yeah. That's crazy shit. She, she even, uh, the backgrounds for the
cuphead animation, the real big one. Uh, those are real, uh, physical watercolor paintings that
key did. So. Oh wow. Yeah. Fancy. Well, I guess that's, that's a very, I guess, I guess that's the
podcast. I guess that's the podcast. Bye. Bye. See ya. Okay. Next one is called society. Three,
two, one, go. I think we should all, we should all mature as a species. We should stop pretending
that memes need to be confined to the internet. We need to use memes in real life. Yeah. Based,
based, cringe, cuck, say, cuck, cringe, cuck, based, cringe, cuck, based, cringe, cuck. Everybody,
everybody get hype for based cringe cuck. I can't fucking. I can't do it. You will,
you will now. I say based in real life. That's okay. I say based in real life. I,
I would say, well, not in every company, but I would say co-cro-wish in real life. I would call
something my co-cro-wish. You're my co-cro-bitch. No. I cannot wait for the next time I get the
opportunity to embarrass myself and then, and then flawlessly recover by saying, I'm just being cool.
That's going to be a hell of a time. I've never, I, I never think to, I, I think it's just like
when I say something embarrassing, I don't really realize that it was embarrassing. And then by
the time I could have said something, someone else's like, I don't know, the awkward silence is set in.
And so I stumble. I won't get. Like I don't really get the good opportunity to say,
hey, I'm just being cool, like, like in a retaliatory sort of way.
I get embarrassed when I'm talking sometimes, but like, I don't know if it's always about things
that are genuinely embarrassing. And I think that maybe I don't notice when I say things that are
genuinely embarrassing. So I think there would probably be times when I would say I'm just being
cool, but it would be in a context where like, I didn't, I thought that I needed to say it,
but it didn't really need to be said. And like, it would have been better somewhere else.
It's true. You got to have a real, you really got to have a high self-awareness stat to know
exactly when to employ it. You've got to like, hold it in your back pocket as like a safety
measure when you are like, pretty sure that the people in your company are not going to like
the thing you're about to say. Yeah, yeah, emergencies only. Yeah. Like, do these people,
do these people like this kind of humor? I don't know. I'll just say I'll be, I'm being cool in
case. I'll just say, I just, I got a really, oh man, kind of really funny racist thing I want to
say, but like, are these people racist? Well, if they're not, I just say I'm being cool afterwards.
That's what it's for. That's secretly what it's for. Ah, shit. You know what? Don't use it anymore.
Don't use the, don't use it. It's not a trick. You're not allowed to. It's a PCP dog whistle.
It is a PCP dog whistle. It is though. Okay, next one. Anon moose PCP loyalist. Three, two, one, go.
Ben, the saint, you claim nothing is happening behind the scenes, but that's exactly what someone
who was hiding something would say. Your move cowboy. What do you think?
Uh, he's right. Everything is happening behind the scenes. In fact, there is no the front of the
scenes. It's like a big Rube Goldberg machine back here, back here in the land of inside baseball.
Rube gold boy. Moving, moving parts, moving pieces, big, the likes of which you've never seen
cosmic powers outstripping everything. If you think about it, the entire universe
is behind a scene that we are not privy to. There's like it like outside the universe. There's like a
curtain and behind the curtain is us. So everything's behind the scenes. Nothing will ever be on the
scene. Oh my God. And that means, and that therefore, if you say that nothing's happening
behind the scenes, then you mean everything is happening in the universe. Yes. Yes. Okay, next
voicemail. Oh, we got anon moose PCP loyalist PS post script, I guess. Three, two, one, go.
Also about three, the nipple like now women are cringe dude, hippo and digi have been better women
than like most women while you're there with you know, I don't know what you mean.
They're better women than most. Is that what he says? Is he saying, is that because you,
you two don't show the nipple? Is the implication that most women do show the nipple and it's bad?
I'll take the compliment. I don't even know what he meant really, but yes. No,
I don't understand this guy. I don't understand. I don't understand what this guy is talking about.
If he says that I'm gooder than someone else, that's good. I like feeling superior. I'll take it.
I'll take any compliment under any circumstances. Next one is going to be based. Ben is parentheses
not a sexist. Wait, three, two, one, go. A man is allowed to beat his wife so long as it is no
thicker than his thumb. That is the origins of the saying rule of thumb. You could instead just say rule.
Okay, I don't know why the music kicked in.
You mean if the rod, if the rod was no thicker than his thumb, that's what is
you're trying to say. Yeah, he's good. Only cowards beat their wife with a rod. Use your bare fists.
Yeah, if you keep you on your edge, you've got to be able to keep the marriage strong if you can beat
your wife and a bare knuckle fist fight in a fair fight. That's what it takes. If you're using a rod,
you've given up. You better end up with blood on your knuckles after the beating or you're not a real man.
Next one, next movie, that voicemail sucked. It wasn't even about me.
I think it may have been in response to you saying rule of thumb sometime.
Oh, did I?
Yeah, fuck it. It doesn't matter. No, it's terrible, terrible, terrible. Voice jail?
Voice jail? No. For you, Ben St, for saying that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, moving on moving on. No, no, we will we will not convene a vote on that question
Next one if monsoon was retarded three two one go
You are the only one girl up on the killfields or is cruel being
button thick teacher
final lesson
Deeper than my psyche
this world
All this people are disease
Free will it's myth. The legend is a joke. We're all pawns controlled by something greater
Memes the DNA of the soul
the shape our will and
Our culture I think this is this metal or solid to pass on
Exposed someone to anger long enough monsoon. They'll learn to hate. I don't know if you come to Karen and they
Be spare. What is this all means? Oh, that's that like first gun five major
Wean blows rain falls
I'm skipping a fun. No, I'm done. No, no more. This sucks. Fuck it. Thanks for the voicemail idiot
Next one is out. God. It's more. It's it's the same. It's if Raiden was also retarded. Okay, whatever three two one go
Reckon your rat about me. I mean, I knew something was off after the Patriots
Nah, that sucks. Nah, you fucking piece. Let's take it. Let's spend 15 minutes talking about how shitty all our fans know
Alright, alright. Thanks. Thanks for calling in
Next one. Oh
God, it's the same guy arm strong is a PCP fan three two one go
You know
A little bit there's no joke this the joke is just what if I read
Dialogue in like a terrible voice that you can't understand
Okay, no more no more. I'm putting an end to it and I'm putting an end to this episode of the pro
Crastinators podcast. Oh god. That was the finale
That's the finale. That's the note. We're going out on if you would like to waste our time and ruin an episode
You can do it at speakpike.com
slash PCP voicemail
and
Subscribe to our patreon at patreon.com slash
the pro
the
pro
Crastinators for bonus episodes, baby, and
Um
What else what do we come up with the Minecraft stream will be done episode of bonus episode the fucking
Something verse something. Oh
It was um Lord of the Rings versus Flight of the Concourse. Yeah, look at four to that one
Look look forward to that. Yeah, we'll do it
Should we have should we have oblivion fall on for that? I
Guess we could if he's if he wants to if he wants to I would I would invite him
And then fucking I don't know fucking buy our shirts
We got shirts in the description check every link in the description
You go down through the description make sure you've clicked every link if you haven't clicked every link
You can't have any pudding just to make sure you didn't miss anything. There's a lot of important stuff down there for
You how can you have any pudding if you don't click every link?
Don't miss it. Don't miss it. You're missing out
Okay
On that note that's gonna do it. It's the end of the podcast. Thanks for listening