I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Another week, another fuck.
Yeah, that's what we do.
Yeah, that's our catchphrase, it always has been.
I want to start...
The fuck is you listening?
Sorry, go on.
I want to start a little quick announcement for anyone, because I don't want to bury this at the end.
On the 29th of October, there's going to be a live band performance in Get the Image.
That's going to be about a week after this episode.
Yeah, it's a charity band event, and I'm going to be playing a couple numbers at the thing.
It's a fundraiser in aid of Parkinson's UK.
I have a link, I have an image.
The band my dad is in, and they're doing a fundraising thing, and I'm going to be there playing a few three little songs in the middle.
If you want to donate, you can donate, and if you want to show up, if you can, that would be cool.
Super sick. What are you going to play?
I'm going to play Dig a Pony by The Beatles, Black Magic Woman, and Sympathy for the Devil.
I'm going to play the bongos on that one.
What the fuck is Dig a Pony?
It's from Abby Road. It's one of the John Lennon silly songs.
The lyrics don't make sense, but it's like...
I'm digging a pony.
Yeah, look it up. It's a good song. I'm going to be playing the George Harrison solo stuff. I'm excited about that.
You're going to be playing in the band?
Yeah, they're doing the main set, and then I'm on for a few.
I just wanted to mention it because it's good to get some extra donations.
Are you going to be playing as part of your dad's band, or are you going to be playing by yourself?
As part of my dad's band.
Okay, okay.
Cool. Super cool. Super sick.
Wait, where is it?
The image has the location. It's the Bohemia North Finchley, and if you can make it, that would be epic.
It's 12 pounds donation.
I'll be there.
Yeah, it just comes all the way up.
Yeah, I've got a week and a half to get my arrangements.
Yeah, from 8 p.m. to 10.30.
That's the knowledge.
There you go. I've spread the word.
Radical.
Well, that just reminds me of international travel.
That just reminds me that I should really get that new COVID booster.
I still haven't gotten one.
Apparently, only 4% of people have gotten the new one, which is pretty cringe.
I've been meaning to get it.
I've been relying, or I was relying on news updates.
The vaccine is here, and there's two parts to it, so you've got to make sure to get two parts.
I'm like, okay, I've got to make sure to get two parts.
And now there's a booster. Okay, I'll get the booster.
But then news about current vaccine boosters has been very minimal.
So I don't even know what is required, how many boosters I am behind, or if I am even behind.
I'm just going to say that if I die, it's not my fault.
No, it is your fault.
I know that there's...
The new booster is omicron-specific, and I think it comes in a couple different varieties,
and I'm not sure what the difference is, and I'm not sure if I should be choosing, or if it doesn't matter.
Yeah, I don't know. I've been meaning to figure it out and go and get one.
I'm sure I could probably just call up CVS and go get one any day I wanted to.
And probably I should just do that, because it's better to get it than to overthink it.
As a Democrat, I'll just slavishly follow whatever my leaders tell me to do.
I love the mainstream media.
Susan Sarandon says I should need the booster, so I got to go do it.
That's just how it is. I don't ask questions.
I don't even know what questions to ask.
I'll just wait until they say, um, get the booster now, and I'll be like, okay.
Is it available over there? It's been available over here for maybe a month?
There's like five boosters at this point. I don't even know.
Are there?
Well, I feel like I've lost track. There was a booster and then another booster.
I think I've had the second one.
I think I've only had one booster.
I don't know. This is the thing. The news, I need a guide to tell me.
I know I've got the vaccine. I'm fully vaccinated, plus one booster at least.
And I feel like that's fine.
Yeah, that's what I'm at. I think that's it. And then the new booster just came out maybe a month ago.
I don't know why I thought there has been occasionally a new booster.
Maybe the things I've been reading have been like, now a newer booster for 70 plus is available.
And now it's going down the age brackets and now younger people can get the second booster or something.
Perhaps, perhaps, yeah.
But I just got to do it.
My stupid video is basically done, like it's basically edited.
I basically just got to watch it through and make sure there's no big fuck ups in it.
And I'm rewriting my Patreon a little bit.
I'm rewriting my Patreon to be a little more generic and not specifically about comics.
I'm just going to kind of make it like, I make stuff and every once in a while I release a big project.
And you love stuff!
Every once in a while I release a big project and if you're pledged at this tier, you'll be credited.
Whether it's a video or a comic or whatever.
Yeah, my Patreon is very specifically about comics and I really am a more of a generalist at this point.
I really am just kind of a guy who does various things.
So, yeah.
Anyway, that's exciting. I'll probably release it this week.
I know I keep saying it, but it really is pretty much done.
Yeah, I mean, if it's like 6, how many hours? 7?
Oh, it's about 7 hours 45 minutes.
I'm debating whether I want to put maybe a couple little bumper bits in there to just boost it up over 8 hours.
Put a dance number in there.
Put a thing where Evil Benson comes in and says, how do you get at my video and then shoot him?
I won't spoil it, but there is a sort of little...
It's nothing super weird or anything, but there is sort of a...
What do you call it? There's sort of a diagetic editing thing where Future Ben will chime in and there's a little bit of...
I made it a little fancy. I made it a little fancy and funny and goofy, but I think I like it.
I'm debating whether I want to add 15 or so minutes worth of future commentary and just sprinkle it in
just to boost it that extra couple minutes over the 8 hour line.
Just because I feel like 8 hours just sounds better than 7.
You could just have a thing at the end where you just blatantly say, I'm padding this out.
I'm going to play some video games. Let's play now.
Honestly, in an 8 hour video, I don't think anyone would be super mad.
And if it's at the end, if you've already watched the video...
You can just click off if you don't want to hear... Yeah, maybe.
But 7 hours is a lot of watching to do. That's a whole day. Just looking at it.
That is a whole day. Oh man, I watched... I kind of watched, listened to...
I think his name is called Dylan the Storyteller or something.
He had a five hour long AVGN retrospective. I listened to it and it was pretty interesting.
The thing that really stood out to me was how Yig like the screenwave era is.
I remember watching a video dissecting the hate AVGN has gotten.
Was that the Lady Emily video? Yeah, yeah.
That was going into all of the crap they were doing. They're gone now, right? I think they've left.
I don't know. Sorry, Dylan the Night Owl.
This is from February of this year, so yeah, screenwave might be gone at this point.
I'm not sure. But yeah, just very much how AVGN, when he would give updates, he would say,
everything was falling apart. My internet didn't work. It was hard to shoot or whatever.
But screenwave says they're going to get it right.
Screenwave is going to fix everything for me.
Screenwave hooked me up with a whole new internet and a whole new setup and a whole new da-da-da-da.
And then everybody hates the product.
Yeah. Very riley-esque.
Knowing that those Yig guys are on Tony from Hack the Movies YouTube channel a couple of times,
they know him.
Did you know that?
I think I remember that Tony.
It's the screenwave Tony, yeah.
The Hack the Movies guy had Yig Studios on and he looked at it for a few minutes and I was like, okay.
Yeah, I had forgotten that, you know, he's been in a couple of AVGN skits because he's one of the guys that ruined AVGN.
They had that show. It was like conceptually, like a bunch of guys in a video store, the set they had.
You mean Hack the Movies?
Not Hack the Movies. On AVGN they had this show that I never clicked on because they just were not charismatic.
I haven't really seen it.
I haven't really seen any Ladder Day. I've seen some Bored James, I guess.
I guess that's like Ladder Day, AVGN stuff, kind of.
But even that is kind of old at this point.
That is kind of old. They had like a big finale. There was like a crazy short film.
No, I haven't seen any of the Screenwave era, AVGN stuff.
I wanted to see old stuff.
I don't know, just to see what it was because it looked like the kind of content I didn't want to see and it turns out that I was right.
Right.
But that hadn't been that out of the ordinary because Cinemassacre, the YouTube channel, always had a bunch of stuff that was just sort of whatever.
Yeah.
Like the streams with James and Mike?
Yeah, James and Mike Mondays. They were sometimes pretty good, but ultimately it's like lower tier content than the actual episodes.
Like some stuff with Bootsy.
Yeah.
It was alright, but I would never click on it.
And so the Screenwave stuff happening was like, it's the same. It's just different guys that I won't click on.
So I sort of missed out on like the outrage because I would never engage with it.
And I guess I'm glad for that.
I think, I mean, a lot of people were already not watching by the time all that happened.
Just a funny connection because Riley knows Tony and it's like, I'm going to do for Yeeg Studios what Screenwave did for Cinemassacre.
It's going to be great.
Do you remember Maryweather, right?
Yeah.
I saw, did you see what was going on with him on Twitter these past couple days?
I saw, I mean, when I looked into it, the comments, the tweets had been deleted or something.
There was something like a goth comic.
There was a goth comic, tweets by like haters have been deleted, so I don't know what the controversy was.
But I believe it's something about like a goth comic where there's a quote unquote ugly bastard stereotype.
Yeah.
Okay.
And the ugly bastard stereotype is like defended because it's like, it's not very nice really.
It's just some like, come on.
And then people got really mad at that, I guess.
Honestly, I kind of had to reconstruct what happened.
Okay.
So to my understanding is that there is a sort of a like a continuing series called the goth girl and the jock.
And it's sort of like a, what do you call it?
Like a romantic comedy thing where like a goth, a goth chick and a jock boy, I guess, overcome the social barrier between them and fall in love.
I haven't read it, right?
No, me neither.
I've seen a similar thing where it's like nerd and jock that also has a goth girl involved.
Is that also?
By a different artist.
Oh, okay.
It's just sort of like in right now to have jocks in your comics.
Rehabilitate and jocks.
We're bringing them back.
Himbos sort of made a comeback in recent years.
So yeah, rehabilitate jocks.
I can see the appeal.
I think it was like trying to remember like there was a nerd and a jock, but they were super gay and they didn't realize it.
Oh, was a boy, a boy nerd and a boy jock?
I think that blew up and that was cute.
I don't know who made that or if that was a trend that was larger than just one artist.
That's probably why right now jocks are jocks are in.
It sounds familiar, but I'm not sure.
Jocks being the bullies that are always the enemy has sort of been like, yeah, but what if they aren't?
What if they're just nice?
Sometimes people who are physically attractive and exercise are not evil.
Wrong.
You're not ready for that conversation.
Uh-oh.
That's...
Wait.
Okay.
So, right.
The goth girl and the jock is sort of a series.
But on the side from that, there are sort of these side comics that he's been doing recently that are called things like the goth girl and the ugly bastard or like the goth girl and her boyfriend.
And they're about a...
These are not like continuing stories.
These are one-offs.
But it's just a hot goth girl and like a fat or nerdy or ugly or shrubby or whatever guy.
And in every single one, just some guy comes up to them and is like, what the fuck?
Why do you have a hot girlfriend when you're ugly?
And then the girl is like, hey, bitch, fuck you.
My boyfriend is hot.
No, she doesn't say he's hot.
They never say, actually, he's not ugly.
It's always taken for granted.
Yes, my boyfriend's ugly, but he's nice to me and he's good in bed.
And why do you judge him just by the way he looks?
You're an asshole and that's why you don't have a girlfriend.
Owned.
Yeah.
I think I saw one of them like that.
And they're very...
They're just very like, very straightforward, very like...
This is a mean comparison, but they're a little bit...
They remind me of Darman videos a little bit and how like a completely ridiculous scenario
happens in order to teach a like really like hit you over the head with like blunt level,
like moral of like, don't judge a book by its cover.
Don't be mean to people just because they're ugly.
Yes, very, very unsubtle, but you know, that's fine.
I think they are a bit self-aware.
The more I've thought about it, I think that the reason he makes them is because they annoy people.
Like I think he does it to make a certain kind of person mad because that generates engagements.
Yeah, I guess.
It's hard to imagine someone getting mad about it, but I guess it happens.
Yeah, I haven't really...
I haven't seen...
Apparently some people get really mad about them for reasons.
I don't really understand why, but I guess they annoy some people.
But anyway, so there was one this week.
It was called...
I don't even remember which one it was.
It was the goth girl and her boyfriend or the goth girl and the ugly boyfriend or whatever.
And you know, I saw this.
I saw it posted and I read it and I said draw, you know, make one where the girl's ugly.
I just said make one where the girl's ugly.
And you know, I scrolled through the comments and I saw some other people who had made the same comment.
They had made the same request that I had.
And some of them got dog piled and screamed at by like people that were like,
fuck you, you draw it yourself if you care.
You know, who are you to...
Don't tell them what to draw.
Don't...
Like that's the stupidest thing I've ever heard of.
Like what the fuck kind of stupid...
Who would want to see that?
Like what's wrong with the SJW cock pushing an agenda?
Get your politics out of this, right?
Okay.
Hideous.
And...
It's just a suggestion, buddy.
I know.
I didn't understand it.
It was deranged.
And there's this one artist that I follow whose name is Raven.
She made a...
She did a quote tweet where she was a little snippy about it.
She was like, I dare the artist behind this to draw like a gender swap version
without throwing up, right?
It was like, they would never draw an ugly girl.
That is so fucked.
No, I mean, I agreed with the sentiment that like this is...
The reason these exist is because it's sort of an excuse to draw tits, right?
Like a lot of the comics on that thing.
It's like, it's really a vessel for drawing like a hot girl with big tits, right?
Right.
So they wouldn't make...
So they would never make a gender swap version.
Yeah, but the idea that you would throw up because drawing an ugly girl is like...
I don't know.
What a way to say that.
I'm a Raven defender, all right?
Yeah.
She was being mean about it, but like, so what?
It's fine to be mean.
Anyway.
He did actually, he did make a gender swap version with a funny egg-shaped girlfriend
and a sexy goth boy, which was kind of funny.
Like, okay, that's when I saw it was when that was posted.
What was the controversy?
Was Mary Weather like holding out on drawing that?
No.
Or did he just say, okay, and do it?
It was just, I mean, just my experience was just I saw people asking for a gender swap
version.
I saw people really like being mean about saying like, no, don't ask for that.
Like, why are you asking for that?
Fuck you.
And then he did it and everyone loved it.
Yeah, it just, it made me mad because I feel like it's the same people that told, I'm thinking
of one girl, not Raven, a different girl who asked like, switch the genders and she got
shouted down for it.
And I think it was the same people that told her like, fuck you, keep your politics out
of this, were probably like, oh my God, Mary owned you.
Mary owned you by doing what you asked for, right?
Like the attitude, the gross attitude of the don't make requests.
It's just so like, I can't imagine getting so worked up about any step of this.
This is the hard part for me to understand.
Why would anyone get mad in the first place?
Well, the only thing that made me mad was the commenters dogpiling those people.
Yeah.
Well, whatever.
People are crazy.
I know.
Especially on Twitter.
I had to like, I had to take a step back from it and be like, you know what, Ben?
You know what?
Just remember, everybody, everybody sucks on Twitter.
Twitter comments are always terrible.
You know what?
This is normal.
This is just how it is.
Yeah.
You know, I'll say, I was worried because I made the request.
I said, you should draw the Judd Genderswatt version.
But in the back of my mind, I thought, you know, if they did, they might do, they might
cop out and draw like a quote unquote ugly girl, but like she wouldn't, she would still
be cute.
You know what I mean?
Like maybe they make, like maybe they'd make her a little chubby and like maybe give her
glasses, but like she'd still be cute looking.
But no, they, they, they gave her like a egg shaped body and like a very like fat lower
face.
And I feel like they, I feel like they followed through on the concept to an adequate degree.
So I was, I was pretty satisfied with it.
Uh, I guess it was a happy ending.
I don't know.
I think it's good to draw ugly characters.
I obviously don't do it that much because my characters are all so cute.
I just draw them with big eyes every time.
Right.
But like, uh, I'm reminded of, of this, this role doll, little, little, little thing where
like you posted something, I'm posting it.
Um, let me see.
It's a, oh yeah, for some reason, you said doll and I thought of dolly, but yeah, role
doll and it's like the, the idea that somebody can look ugly, but there as an, if they're
a nice person, they're the good vibes will shine from within, even if they got crooked
teeth and a, and a fucked up nose, uh, anyone can be nice and, and, you know, welcoming.
You don't, you don't need to have big tits to be the best person.
Yeah.
Actually.
No.
Wrong.
Yeah.
Um.
Oh, as an aside, quick to the, the whole goth thing.
Uh, I got my goth girl get up.
I got a bunch of stuff.
Good to your Halloween costume.
My Halloween costume was a ruse.
It was just a trick.
I was saying I was going to make a costume, but it's actually just an outfit that I'm
going to wear all the time.
Oh no.
God, I fell for it.
Uh, I got like fishnet top and a corset and a goth skirt and some black lipstick.
Um, I'm going to go crazy.
I'm going to go insane.
I'm going to take a picture and I'm going to post online at some point when I feel like
I look good enough.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Sounds like a plan.
Yeah.
Sick.
Wait.
What's the outfit?
Um, I posted the little rough drawing on Twitter.
It's basically.
Yeah.
Is this, does this include the witch hat?
I don't have a witch hat yet.
I think there's a witch hat in the old Halloween box and I looked on Amazon for like, oh,
a witch hat.
They suck.
They all suck.
So I'm probably going to have to go to a dedicated Halloween place.
Look around.
I mean, yeah.
Where else would you get a witch hat?
Nobody wears them just as a, as a normal thing.
You know, I've watched, I've watched Beetlejuice the other day and the movie, yeah, the movie
and the girl there is like, she's goth, but she's wearing like a Lydia.
Yeah.
She's wearing like a sun hat that has been painted black.
It's just like a summer sun hat, but it's black and it looks great.
So I could just get a hat and dunk it in like a vat of ink.
I mean, I, I feel like a black sun hat that seems like something normal, but like you
would wear to a funeral.
Yeah.
It doesn't sound that, that crazy.
So like, it doesn't need to be a witch's hat, although the witch's hat is the most
aesthetic for the occasion.
You know, I, I've realized there's, there's like a vintage clothing store, like right
down the street from my house, and I've been meaning to go and just see what they got and
see if I can find anything cool there.
It's really like an eight minute walk from my house, but I just keep putting off going.
That's it.
That's the whole story.
There's nothing else.
Nice.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm glad you liked it.
Ben, did you beat Outer Wilds?
Oh, yes, I did.
There was a lot of spoilers.
There was a lot more play the game to go than I thought there was.
Let's talk about it.
Yeah.
Outer Wilds spoilers.
I'm going to spoil everything.
Damn.
Um, yeah, I thought I'd seen basically everything on a friggin giants deep.
I thought I'd seen everything on.
I thought I thought I'd seen everything turned out there was like, I hadn't I hadn't
even gone around in like the hanging city.
I hadn't gone around in the Sunless City.
I hadn't found half the stuff in there.
What, what else did I did I end up having to do?
Oh, the the fucking.
You know, I did, there were a couple of things that I kind of spoiled for myself,
but none of them were like that big.
And at some point I was like, then you are not allowed to look anything else up.
No more spoilers.
And then I and I did.
And then so I feel like all the big stuff I was what did you get spoiled on?
I got spoiled on I look I looked up the solutions to I look.
Well, I looked up hints for the quantum imaging tower puzzles.
I also, OK, I looked at I looked up how to do it.
But I already kind of thought I knew how to do it.
And I just kind of looked up and confirmed how for how to get past the
angler fish and how to get inside the jellyfish.
Like I already kind of was like, I think I'm supposed to go inside the jellyfish.
But I but I died trying to do it.
And so then I went and I looked it up and and it was like, yeah, you could just go
inside the under under the tenant.
I was like, OK, that's that's what I thought.
I just the jellyfish was for me the first moment I got properly stuck.
And I needed a hint from a friend because because I I went to the.
Yeah, yeah, I got all the information.
I'd been to Feldspar and I'd gone and seen through Dark Bramble,
the dead jellyfish, yeah, hanging out.
And it's like, oh, this is probably good for insulation, but it's not good for much else.
And I'm like, OK, yeah.
Obvious jelly, jellyfish is an insulator against electricity.
The giant steep is electric.
The jellyfish are electric.
I can't touch the jellyfish and I assumed because of how jellyfish work,
that the tentacles underneath would also electrocute me, but they don't.
They just go up inside.
It looks like they will.
They have electricity all over them and it does not look safe.
But it doesn't look safe.
I did remember going up in inside the dead jellyfish on in the Bramble.
So I kind of knew how to do it.
Yeah, I didn't.
I looked it up and confirmed that like, yeah, and I I knew I knew that the anglerfish
were blind and they kept saying the anglerfish are blind, the anglerfish are blind.
And I was like, OK, and then I tried to sneak past them and it didn't work.
And I was like, what the hell?
And I looked it up and and it's like, yes.
If you do not use your thrusters at all, the anglerfish will not react to you.
Yeah, I was like, OK, that's the annoying part.
The worst part of I mean, I I would say the worst part of the game
is Dark Bramble, just because when you go into one of the entrances,
you have to stop completely and then point very accurately
in the direction of travel, thrust for a bit and then turning off
your thrusters and hope that you're not sailing right into one of them.
Because if you touch them, they'll notice you.
And if you smash into like a branch that you didn't see coming,
you'll have to use your thrusters and then you're dead.
So it's like, yeah, getting getting through that reliably is semi undoable.
You just have to be sort of lucky.
Well, I had to I did it over and over again
until I got to the point where I knew like exactly which paths I could take.
That didn't risk anglerfish attack.
But, you know, I had to do it a lot before I got to a point.
It was really annoying.
Right at the very, very end, I realized that the strategy you're supposed
to do is to shoot your probe ahead of you.
So you know that what you're about to sail into is free of obstacles.
Did you not?
Did you do that?
I figured that out.
Oh, my God, it must have been that must have sucked.
Not knowing that I knew that the lights because I would use.
I never got like, I never went in there blindly, just going towards the light,
except the first time where I went towards the red light and it was the fish eggs.
And I didn't know what else to do.
Well, strangely, I didn't bump into anything on the way there.
But well, the other times it's like I used my audio scanner.
And once I knew the locations, I could just use the locations.
If I go to the map, you type, click the thing.
So I never like used the lights as a source of like, oh, I should go towards the light.
Because I know some of them are fish.
I did.
I did use the lights as like, OK, I didn't think to go inside of the egg clutch until like, like, OK,
I would shoot my probe into the into the one with the three angler fish and the egg cluster inside.
And I knew that there were eggs in there.
But to my mind, that was just like, oh, this one's full of fish.
Definitely don't go in there.
So I just didn't.
I never went in there at all.
And I thought I wasn't supposed to.
And so I eventually was like, I know that there's because I found the murals.
I know that the vessel is somewhere in the dark Bramble.
I just have to find it.
So I tried going to I just tried going to every light in every chamber of the dark
Bramble that I could.
And it was a real nightmare because, I mean, there's the one that Feldspar is in,
which he's pretty much the only thing in there.
There's one that just has like a fish and nothing else.
There is the egg clutch.
There's there's one where it's full of the little like pods with holes in them.
But all of them like interconnect to each other.
And there's like six different ones.
But they're all and if you throw your probe inside that one, it'll come out the other side.
But then it'll just keep going and go through another one and then go through another one
and just go through another one.
And the probe will just keep going through an infinitely recursive series of these little pods.
I never found that one.
Well, there's nothing in there.
So because I because I never like I never just blindly because like I assume
when I was one of the yellowish ones when I was in dark Bramble,
I always assumed that the every path leads to like a multiple of different paths.
So like if you go the wrong way like the first time,
you're going to be on like you're going to have to like try 17,000
different permutations into until you find it like randomly.
So I didn't even try.
I didn't even explore that way.
I only went in there when I had like a solid goal
that I had from like reading a note.
I'm like, OK, there was there's a use the oh, the signal.
The the what's the what's the word?
The signal scope, the signal for specifically
abandoned ship pods, the distress beacons, distress beacons.
Like I followed that because I was like, oh, the mural shows that one of them didn't leave.
So I got to find that one.
And so I found that I followed them and they're like, oh, shit,
we got to get back to the vessel.
They followed the thing into the thing and there's like a seed and they died.
And then I shot my probe through that and I used my probe signal to get to the vessel.
Oh, God, I didn't even think to do that.
Yeah, I'm so stupid.
That's not very smart.
I felt very smart when I was like, wait, the probe.
Oh, I can just follow where the probe is.
I leave it on the vessel.
I go and get there.
And then once I'm there, the vessel, I have the the coordinates for that.
Wow, it's so obvious.
It's so obvious when you say it.
Yeah, this the probe, the probe would land.
Well, so you had to end up going into the egg, the egg pod, right?
No, I think you can you can go like a side from that.
You're joking.
No, I mean, it's so hard for myself.
Let me tell you what I had to do.
I, yeah, I knew that if you found the distress beacon, you could find that seed.
And if you shot the probe through the seed, it would land on the vessel.
And I did not think to leave the probe on it foolishly.
So I tried to go to I just tried to go through every permutation of
or no location.
It didn't take it didn't take that long.
I mean, it's kind of it's a lot.
It's a lot smaller than it like makes it look.
I mean, I did I did get eaten by a lot of anglerfish.
It probably took several hours, maybe like two hours.
But yeah, I just I just tried going everywhere I could inside the bramble.
And eventually there was nowhere else to go except for the egg pod.
And I'm like, I guess I need to go in the egg pod.
And, you know, I had to look it up so it'll be like, OK, you just
if you don't use your thrusters at all, the fish will not come at you.
So yeah, I just had to you go through the thing and you just let
your momentum sort of carry you slowly towards the the egg cluster.
And when you're in the egg cluster, there are a bunch of lights and yeah,
just kind of near the egg cluster.
One of there's a there's like a hole you can go through.
And some of them, what am I saying?
A few of them don't go anywhere.
Like a few of them just lead you back into the same room.
And I just had to like shoot my probe through those.
And if I got like like error, you know, duplicate signal, then I'd know, like,
OK, that one doesn't go anywhere.
And so I just had to find another one that didn't do that.
And then that ended up leading me to the vessel.
And that's how I found it.
It worked, took a while.
But the vessel was.
The vessel was kind of frustrating because like because I didn't.
Yeah, I didn't.
I couldn't figure out what I was supposed to do with like the coordinate input
thing. I didn't realize that.
I mean, OK, I knew the I coordinates,
but I didn't put it together that like, oh, those coordinates.
Are what you're supposed to enter on that thing.
So I spent a long time just fucking around with that console
without realizing that, like, I can't do anything because I need the warp core.
I did when I had the when I had the realization of like, oh.
If I oh, the warp core, it looks just like this thing.
If I bet that's what I have to do, I have to bring the warp core here.
I figured that out on my own.
I had I had a bit of a thing with that.
Like, I knew that when I got there,
I didn't have the information to solve this puzzle with the the coordinates.
So I'm like, OK, I'll leave that.
I didn't know the coordinates yet.
Yeah. And then I got the broken warp core.
And then I remembered that the black hole forage is where they made warp cores.
So what if I get to the vessel, bring the broken thing to the black hole forage
and then somehow repair it.
Oh, and nothing happens if you bring it all the way there,
nothing happens, you can't put it on anything.
Did you try it?
I was like, what do I do?
Did you try to like get into the black hole forage
while it is like down at the black hole?
Yeah, like I did the lever thing to make it go down.
And then I go down to the bottom using like the Ash Twin Zappy thing
to to teleport you up there.
And then Zappy thing.
You know, the the towers that black hole like transporters,
one of them leads you to the bottom where the black hole forage is like low down.
What?
Yeah, wait, no.
There's one.
Wait a minute, hold on.
The hanging city is upside down.
So when you say when I say down, I mean toward the black hole.
Oh, wait, no, I'm yeah, I don't think you're able to get there in time.
No, when you press the lever.
I don't I don't know.
I don't think there's any way to get into the black hole forage
while it's down at the black hole.
Yeah, what I did is I left the the warp car, the broken warp car in the place
and just did something and then I brought it back up and nothing happened.
Yeah, I was like, OK, obviously not the correct.
So much. Oh, God, that must have been.
Yeah, that was one of the things that was the most irritating
was getting into the black hole forage because because you have to go to the city,
find the control, use the control,
and then you have to somehow get from the hanging city to the black hole forage.
But you can't just like do that.
I mean, I guess, yeah, you can't just do that.
You pretty much have to go through the Ash Twin teleporter
because it's the only way to get like onto the the gravity floor.
I figured out. Yeah, that was really annoying, actually.
I figured out that there is because I looked around in the hanging city a lot.
And I think in one of the districts,
you can climb up to a shortcut that's on the surface.
You don't have to go like a special way.
So like really land.
Yeah, there's a little hole in the ice near.
I can't remember. Oh, where it is. Yeah.
But you can you can jump down that slide down a bit
and then you're in the hanging city.
You can click the the lever really fast, get back up there in your ship,
go to Ash Twin and then teleport and I could do it pretty quick.
But then when I had to do that after I'd gotten the thing from the vessel.
Yeah, I was trying to do all of this shit.
Yeah, I only just barely got in there and nothing happened.
I was like, no, no, I had the same thought.
I also tried bringing the warp core to the Black Hole Forge,
but there's just nothing there.
Well, once I once I realized, oh, I got to bring it to the vessel.
It I immediately was like, oh, yeah, obviously, obviously, that's what it needs.
It's got a broken warp core.
There's a working one inside the Ash Twin.
Yeah, I didn't really figure that out until I was in Ash Twin.
I was like, oh, yeah, warp core, warp core from here.
I got to the I got inside of the Ash Twin chamber
well before I found the vessel.
Crazy, I didn't figure that out for a very long time.
No, finding the vessel was like the last thing that I did.
Well, that's not quite true.
But yeah, I got inside of what it was.
Um, yeah, once once I figured out what the towers do,
getting inside of the Ash Twin was like the first thing I did with that.
OK, what is your thought process?
Because I was I was stuck on that.
There was the very, very last thing that I completely stuck on.
Yeah, and I think it was because of an assumption I made
based on a misunderstanding of of like the the thing they said
that there's a a a something point,
like a reference point in between the two planets, the Ash Twin and in between.
Yeah, they say that like it doesn't really mean anything.
Well, what it means, I didn't I didn't realize this at the time.
What it means is that in order to teleport,
you need to be looking up or like that is the point in between the two planets
has to be where you're looking because you can't look inside of Ash Twin
to go to Ash Twin.
Yeah, so that's why it works when like the other planet
and between is going.
But the problem is the roof is thing like I think.
Yeah, as soon as I realized that it does work,
it was fine.
It's just that I was running around the whole game
because every other thing, every single other mystery had been solved,
except for how to get into the Ash Twin.
And I just I just didn't understand
I that you could teleport into Ash Twin.
I thought it was impossible because I think I'd read something
where it says it doesn't work.
I was like, OK, there must be another way in and there wasn't.
I was just done.
I. OK, when.
I felt I felt stupid because it felt like the.
It felt like the Ash Twin Towers Twin Towers.
They were funny.
That's just to tower to tower.
Lord of the Rings.
OK, it felt like those would be like a really convenient way
to get around and explore stuff.
And I felt like I had missed out, you know what?
I guess not really, because like your ship is easy enough
to get from place to place, like whatever.
I felt like I was finding it out really late,
like I should have figured it out a long time ago
that the Ash Twin Towers let you go from planet to planet.
Like I had done it before by accident,
but I hadn't really figured out that like, oh, no, yeah, just
that's sort of the whole point of these of Ash Twin
is that they they lead to all these different places.
Yeah, I mean, you read up about like all of the people talking
about Ash Twin being like useful to come to get everything
towards the Ash Twin project really quickly.
Yeah. And it's like I only figured out all of that.
Like I flew through the the black hole into the white hole.
I was like, oh, I'm not dead.
I thought I would die.
There was there was multiple times where it did you talk to
Gabbro to learn to meditate?
Not the first time I met him, but like later,
eventually I talked to him again.
Yeah. And then sometimes I wished I had I had found that out sooner.
Yeah. I mean, that's very useful.
But like when I was be like falling in
brittle hollow towards the black hole, I'm like, OK, I'm dead.
Meditate. I didn't actually fall through it until a few times later.
I just let myself go and I was like, oh, you don't die.
And then after that, how to meditate until like way late falling.
I fell through the black hole like really early, like like pretty terrified of it.
I mean, I there was I fell into it and I was like, I guess I'm going to die.
But there was nothing I could do about it.
So I just did.
Like, oh, it's actually like kind of scarier when you're through the white hole
and your ship is like thousands of kilometers away and you have your jet pack
and your oxygen, which is just you don't have time to get back.
Yeah, you're just dead.
Well, then you find the the station and it's like, yeah, here's how to get back.
It's like, oh, cool, looking looking at the white hole.
They solve they solve this problem already.
Looking at the white hole, it's hard because it warps the light around it.
I I thought it was just rubble.
I didn't even see the station until I realized there was a station.
And then I went looking for it.
Well, when it when it spits you out, it spits you out sort of like
you're you're falling in the direction of the station.
Like you're going right towards it.
I mean, I can see it.
It's it's around if you like if you panic and you like, oh, shit, oh, shit.
And you and you start firing your thrusters, maybe like you go somewhere else.
But if you just fall through it and you just let like the momentum carry you,
you just land like on the station and you see the gravity floor you can walk on.
I didn't know that I fell through the black hole a lot of time.
So I got used to it.
But then the the high energy lab was like another tricky one.
That one that one was pretty hard to find.
But once I knew I was looking for it, I eventually found it.
And I was like, OK, like getting getting into that area really early.
And then that's on the same doesn't right.
Yeah, in between the Sunless City.
Yeah, the Sunless City is really irritating
because like you have to go there right away.
And if you go right away for various things, it's it's all buried.
Yeah, yeah.
There is another there's a shortcut into the Sunless City.
Yes, yes, there's like a hole.
I found it a couple of times. Yeah.
So that makes it kind of easy.
And then you get in there and you're walking through the sand
and then you've got the the the little test chamber
where you can switch out the black hole, white hole things.
You shoot your probe through it.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, did you experiment?
Did you have the funny thing happen?
I had the funny thing happen, but not there.
What do you mean?
You're talking about the you have broken the fabric of reality, right?
Yeah.
I did get that ending, but I didn't get it that way.
Wait, how do you not get it?
Where else could you do that for?
Wait, first of all, to OK, I know what you're talking about.
But to do that, don't you have to like?
Don't you have to like pull the warp or like the black hole core
out of the machine in a window of like a hundred thousandth of a second
or something to make the probe like duplicate itself?
Yeah, I mean, in the game, it's pretty easy to do.
You just have hover your mouse over and like and then like.
Because you shoot the probe it when it gets close enough
because they the probe appears outside the white hole
of a few seconds before it enters the black hole. Yeah.
But it's quite lenient, I felt like I got it on my second attempt.
No, I didn't even think to try that because, you know, all the text says,
like, oh, yeah, it's like a thousandth of a second.
It's like an irreceptibly small window of time.
That's that's like you can you can see it when you're shooting it,
that there are two of them and I feel like like like most of a second.
I did shoot a probe through the black hole.
I did not notice the the time paradox.
So I'd know I didn't do that.
No, the way that I broke the fabric of reality was
because I got inside of Ash Twin, I think earlier than you did.
Where because,
yeah, like basically as soon as I figured out what the Ash Twin towers were for,
the first thing I did was try.
Well, first I tried to get to the sun station and I couldn't do it.
And actually, the very last thing I did after I got the ending was I went back
and I got and I figured out how to get to the sun station.
And it turns out all you got to do is just fly over some cactuses.
There's just a little like the sort of trick.
You know what I'm talking about?
I do know what you're talking about.
You don't have to fly over them, though.
Yeah, get there really early.
The sand is still like going down.
You can walk over the sand and get there.
Like before the sun, the Sun Tower.
Yeah, the Sun Tower, the sand is like going down.
Like it reveals the Sun Tower.
If you get in there as soon as possible, the sand is still high enough
so you can walk over the top of it.
Yeah, it's what you can walk over the top of them.
So that's like the very first thing you need to do if you want to get.
Well, well, you know, I mean, it actually worked.
Like I just kind of, you know, I there I hit some cactuses.
I had to repair my suit a couple of times, but like it was fine.
I just kind of did a little bit of like tricky flying over some cactuses,
got into the thing.
Yeah, I should have just I should have just gone for it.
It wasn't actually that hard, but I thought it was impossible.
But yeah, so the first thing I tried to do was the Sun Tower,
but I couldn't figure out how to do it.
And then the second one I tried was, yeah, I could tell that the two towers
were for the twins and I just was figured out, OK, one of these brings me
to the Ember Twin, I guess the other one must bring me to the Ash Twin.
And I was like, oh, shit, I'm inside.
I'm inside the chamber now. OK.
God, it was just because I was so sure that I had read somewhere that it doesn't work.
It didn't even occur to me to because I was because I was just fucking around with it.
And like all the other towers, you're supposed to look up.
So I just looked up and it just brought me in.
So I didn't even think to look down.
Another thing, though, like I the thing with that
that I remember being difficult is that I did go there.
I did fuck around and I did look up.
But because the sand lifts you up.
Yes, it didn't work.
Well, yeah, you have to.
You have to go there a few seconds after the sand has passed,
which I didn't think to try.
Does that work because they have they have a note that says like
the five degree lenience, right?
There's a lenience of five degrees.
So you can wait a couple seconds, which means that the high energy lab
or no, it's in the Black Hole Forge.
It says like there's a five five.
Yeah, the one for one guy says that.
And like I shot my probe on the thing to see what the timing was.
And it really was like more lenient as long as you're not standing there
when the sand comes. You shot your probe on the what now?
I shot my probe on the the thing so that the probe would get teleported.
So I could see when it teleports the probe.
Yeah. What the fuck?
I don't know why, but I just thought I didn't like that.
That's a good way to test when when is like the right time to do it.
So after the probe goes through, I take I wait like half a second
and then I run in there and I shoot my jet pack down so I'm on the thing
and then it works. Yeah. Yeah.
That's that's so funny.
The way the first the first time I got it to work was I tried I land
because, you know, the reason the sandstorm picks you up off that pad
is because they're like the ceiling is open.
So I tried just like landing my spaceship like on top of it to sort of like cover it up.
And it actually worked.
It actually shit. Well, I couldn't replicate it.
It worked one time and then I couldn't get it to work again.
But yeah, that's how I got inside the Ash Twin chamber the first time.
And then the second time that didn't work.
So what I would do was there's a little alcove like behind the teleporter pad
with which you can stand in and you're safe from the sandstorm.
I would stand in that alcove and I would wait until Ember Twin was right overhead
and then I would jump up and then I would fire my thrusters down and sort of just like.
Rock it myself onto the pad so I could hit it despite the, you know,
the sandstorm pulling me up and that that would that would work fine.
That's very convenient, though, that you can just wait until a little bit
after the storm passes. Yeah, that's funny.
Because I yeah.
But.
You want the.
Was I supposed to tell you about how I broke the fabric of reality?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
The way OK. Well, the way that I did it, it's funny.
I went into the chamber and I'm in there and I read the warnings
and I realized like, OK, what's in this chamber is the whole
like it's the whole in game justification for why like you start over again after you die.
And I and I was really scared because I thought like if I if I fuck with this
warp core and then I die is the loop going to end and it's like game over
permanently and I have to start over.
I was very worried when I first took it out.
I was like, wait, yeah, this is powering this.
Yeah. But without this, like the whole the whole what's the word,
the diagetic reason why dying results in like not a game over is gone.
Yeah. And and it's so stressful because the the sun blowing up music
starts playing regardless of how quickly you've done that.
So like and then it's like the special version of the song.
It's like super tense and I'm like, no, no, I can't do it.
Well, I did I did eventually I just was like, fuck it.
And I and I pulled the thing out.
I pulled the warp core out.
Well, no, I was in there and I and I moved the ball to open the thing
to expose the warp core, but I was too afraid to take it out.
So I just kind of stood there and waited.
And and I and it was late in the cycle.
And I started hearing the supernova music and I was like, what's going to happen?
Did you did you ever did you ever die inside the chamber?
You know, I didn't.
I guess I would have assumed it just.
But no, the outside shell, the outside shell was supposed to like
like like retain its like it is.
It is like the it is supernova proof, but only for a moment.
Yeah, so like I guess I should have tried that that that would have been interesting.
What happens? I did I did try.
Well, what happens is if the warp core is still inside
of the of the of the the machine, but you know, the doors are open to expose it.
Like as the supernova is happening, a black hole forms around the warp core
and then, you know, you just wait.
And then after a few seconds,
there's well, there's like a like a know my like inscription pattern sort of
appears in your field of vision and you get you get time warped back.
You don't die, you just get time warped back in the loop.
If you take the if you take the warp core out
and then you let the supernova happen, then a few seconds go by
and then eventually, you know, the walls break and the supernova explodes
and you die and you die for good, you get the you are dead message
because the project was not online.
But so I tried it the first time and I saw that a black hole happens
when the suit went like right before the time warp activates.
And I was like, huh, so I went back and I opened the doors
and I waited for the supernova.
And as the Ashwin project is activating, the black hole forms
and I jumped into the black hole and it warped and it just restarted the loop.
And I was like, OK, it just I just died.
So I go to the map and I'm like, and I'm like, all right, well, I got to go back.
I got I got to try it again.
I got to try another permutation of like, what if I die after
taking the warp core out before I do this and after I do that and whatever.
So I go and I check the map because I've got to fly back to the Ashwin
and I see there's a duplicate signal.
It's like error duplicate signal.
And it shows me both where I am and inside of Ashwin.
Oh, my God. And I'm like, that's funny, the game glitched.
The game didn't expect me to do that.
So it glitched and and it thinks I'm in both places.
Well, no, that sounds like it.
They deliberately did that is because I went there and I went inside.
And there's another copy of you standing there and you can talk to yourself.
Oh, my God, I got to try that. Yeah.
But when when the supernova happens that time,
you get the fabric of reality breaking ending.
That's so strange.
So like, I guess I'd never really thought about it.
But of course, the Ashwin the Ashwin project is a black hole
that sends things to a white hole, but like so powerfully
that it does it like 20 something minutes into the past.
Yeah. Yeah.
It sends memories back.
But if you go back.
You are being sent 22 minutes into the past.
The apparent, I guess, just like one version of you
comes out the white hole inside of the Ashwin project.
And another version of you gets like sent back in time
to wake up on Timberhearth.
Right. Because 22 minutes in the past, you are waking up and you, you know,
the only things been sent back is your memories, not yourself.
So your memories of that are in your old body,
which was already existing 22 minutes ago.
So yeah, you duplicated yourself by jumping in.
Yeah, I guess so.
But but yeah, that's that's how I got
the break, the fabric of reality ending.
That's so funny. It was very weird.
And I was like, oh, my God, I found something.
I found the secret.
What else? What else?
What else can I say about what else I do?
But I got a little thing I can talk about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean, this was this was like,
I didn't want to say it last time because it was going to be spoilers.
But this was like the thing that really got me hooked
into like the exploration of Outer Wilds was I landed on Giant Steve.
That was the first planet I explored.
And I was like using like the little slabs
on the the scrying pools or whatever they are.
And the ones that like sort of let you see another planet.
Yeah. Yeah. And I did the one that was like the inside of the third probe
or the memory probe or whatever, when the cannon shoots the probe out.
Yeah, it sends its information back to this little data bank.
And I looked at the windows and it's like, oh, there's a lot of electricity out there.
That's funny. I don't know what the hell that is.
That's I never saw that until like way later.
I knew I had used those memory pools,
but I never I feel like I never saw the inside of the Ash Twin project
or like the the core of Giant Steve, even though
there are things around that can let you see that.
The Ash Twin project one was so scary
just because it's like there's no lights in there.
The sound to the like the humming sound is kind of like I have no idea what I'm looking at.
Yeah. And oh, I love, by the way,
I love when you look in the Ash Twin project, you can scroll around.
You see three of the six or seven.
So also know my masks or lit up.
And I know that one of them is me because I'm in the loop.
Gabbro is another one.
And I was like, and then who's the third?
And I realized later that the third is the memory bank for the probe launcher.
Yes. So it sends the the data from the probe
fired in the last cycle so they can shoot in a different direction,
which is why the probe always shoots in a different direction every time,
which is so fucking cool when you figure that out.
Yeah. Sorry, spoiled gamers.
It makes it make sense.
I was like, I was like, wait a minute.
But like if the probe always fires, like doesn't the probe like forget
where it went last time it fired?
No, it remembers for the same reason that you remember.
No, my statue mask technology.
It's so fucking sick. Anyway, so so the thing I was like,
I went to Giant's Deep once and I was like, what is this this thing?
It's like got like water and stuff.
And then I found later, I realized that there's a thing like floating around
the the orbiting Giant's Deep.
And I was like, oh, that's that thing that blows up.
I'll land on that.
The probe cannon.
So I went on the probe cannon wreckage and I was like looking in there
and I recognize the architecture as like similar to that one
with the water and the electricity.
And I realized that there's three like like a room.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, you mean you
recognize that the architecture inside of the orbital probe cannon
was similar to what you'd seen through the like the scrying stone
inside of the Giant's Deep core?
Yes. So I was like this and I learned that there were three
like capsules, like rooms.
Oh, yes. And one of them you can go into the other one.
You have to go outside the spaceship and go in through the window.
And then the third one is somewhere.
And I was like, it's there. Yeah.
And I figured out that that it was the third like capsule from the orbital
probe cannon and where it was based on the electricity.
I was like, I saw electricity.
It's in the core.
Like I think I got some information that says it's in Giant's Deep.
I was like, oh, it's in the core.
Now I got to find out how to get down there.
And then there was the the water like gushing, like pushing me away.
I'm like, OK, now I've got to find out all of this stuff.
And then I was hooked.
I was like, yeah, I love this.
This is like I have some information and it's leading me towards learning more.
It's great.
I, yeah, one of the first things that I think like the very first thing I did
on my first launch was I go I went to the interloper because I thought it looked weird.
And then on another very early loop,
you know, one of the first things I did was check out the orbital probe cannon.
And it took me a while.
I think I had to go back a couple of times before I figured out how to open
the doors with like the glowing balls, you know.
Yeah, I didn't quite figure that out right away.
But eventually I was like, oh, wait, if I move those balls around,
that is like a manipulating switches, basically.
So I went back and I went inside and, yeah, I found, you know,
there's three, there's three parts to the to the probe or whatever.
And I only I went in the one that it lets you go into.
And for whatever reason, I went back later and I figured like, oh,
there's three parts and I can just go into the second part.
I just have to get in my ship and go around the outside and go in the broken
window. I didn't figure that out because if you check, if you I think there's
a scrying pool thing that allows you to see inside one of them.
And it's like, it's got a broken window.
Yes. It's like, oh, I can get in through the broken window.
I did not even think.
Yeah. Thought that like, oh, the way is blocked.
I can't get in.
Oh, yeah.
There's a lot of those like doorways that would be so convenient,
but they're just they're just in the wrong place.
And then way later, I realized that like, oh, there's three parts and the third
part that I had already seen.
I had seen the core of Giants Deep.
And I knew that the Giants Deep core was full of electricity.
And then when I finally figured out that like the scrying stone was seeing
the third part of the orbital probe cannon, I'm like, oh, well, OK,
I see it's surrounded by electricity.
So it must be inside the core of Giants Deep.
How do I how do I get there?
And then, you know, I had I had already met Feldspar and seen the the jellyfish.
And I was like, OK, well, it's got to involve using these jellyfish
to insulate myself from electricity somehow.
Yeah, that I felt I felt like when I figured that out, I was like,
I should have figured this out like this.
I had like I had already been inside of the Ash Twin project
by the time I figured out like where the third part of the orbital probe cannon was.
And I was like, that feels like I did that in the wrong order.
But it's fine.
Yeah, I mean, I guess there's nothing stopping
a brand new player from accidentally beating the game immediately.
It's just very unlikely that you can go anywhere.
No, there's there's just it's just sort of the knowledge
of what the hell you're looking at.
I mean, you have to slowly gather after reading
like logs all over the galaxy, the solar system.
I watched a hundred percent speed run of it and it took about an hour.
I bet like I bet an any percent speed run.
I mean, let's see, you would just have to.
Well, you could go right to giant steep and you could go right to actually.
OK, well, actually, no, technically, you don't even need to go into giant
steep because the the coordinates are the same every time.
Like I think if you know the coordinates,
you could just go right to the Ash Twin.
Tower, go inside the Ash Twin project.
Wait, no.
OK, I learned this from the speed run.
In theory, you would think you could go right to Ash Twin,
go inside, grab the.
The warp core and then immediately go to the vessel, put it in
and then put the coordinates in without ever actually finding them.
Because if you know them ahead of time,
you don't need to find them in the orbital pro cannon in giant steep.
But you can't do that, actually, because and this is very funny.
There's until you turn the gravity on in.
What do you call it?
Yeah, until you turn the gravity on, there's no way there's something.
It's something about like you can't put the warp core down
to move the broken warp core.
Wait, no, you know, I feel like they might have patched this or something
because I feel like I did bring just I just brought this this particular
this speed run that I watched, he had to go to the vessel
and move the broken warp core out before he could go to Ash Twin.
Yeah, that doesn't make it because you could just like put things on the ground.
Right. Well, you can't just put them on the ground
or at least this guy couldn't just put it on the ground until the gravity was on.
Right. So he had to go to the vessel.
But like no, I feel like maybe they changed that or something
because I feel like I did not.
I definitely didn't go and move the the broken core before.
Yeah, it's just floating next to it.
Yeah, no. So that might be different.
Yeah. So I think if you just wanted to beat it right away,
if you if you knew or somehow managed to guess the coordinates,
you could just go to Ash Twin, grab the warp core, go to the the bramble,
find the vessel, put the core in and put the coordinates and go.
And you could you could beat the game in 10 minutes.
Yeah, the longest time you'd have to wait
is for the sands to go down far enough for you to get into Ash Twin.
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
And you could just sleep.
You could just sleep until it's long enough.
Yeah.
I am I'm trying to think I I did get the DLC,
but I wanted to like I'm trying to think like,
is there anything else I want to say about the core game before I start talking about that?
Well, I haven't played the DLC yet.
So. Oh, OK.
Guess you can talk about it for the moment.
There I'm not I don't think I'm that far into it.
I'm a little ways into it.
And there are some things that I think are cool about it.
But I I kind of feel like I'm not really digging what they did with it.
I feel like they did not.
If I if I understand where it's going correctly,
I feel like they didn't really lean into the strengths of their game
and they kind of just tried to make a different kind of game in their engine.
And it's like, OK, well, I'll try it out anyway.
Yeah, I mean.
I I'm I'm not I haven't given up on it quite yet.
But I'm not sure if it's really super my jam, but whatever.
What what do you think?
Oh, by the way, when you got to the sun station, how do you feel?
Oh, oh, OK.
I tried landing on it so many times.
Yes, I was trying not to like hint that you should not land on it.
No, no, I don't even know if it's impossible.
I had already figured even when we talked last week,
I had already figured out that, like, OK, I'm not supposed to land on it.
Like, I think definitely there's some other way to get there.
And yeah, of course, the Sun Tower is how you get there.
I did manage to hit it.
I managed to collide with it, but I like bounced off.
I cracked my windshield and I bounced off of it.
And I realized like, OK, this is theoretically possible,
but there's definitely this is not the way you're supposed to do it.
So I I quit.
I quit trying to land on it.
But I you could you could definitely do it though.
Hypothetically, if you if you go fast enough
and don't go too close to the sun, but you get you have
a fast enough orbit, yes, and like like resist the pole.
If you very carefully controlled your
if you very carefully controlled your your trajectory
and managed to get into a somewhat stable orbit around the sun
and managed to line yourself up with the sun station,
you could theoretically sort of lower yourself down onto it and land on it.
It'd be very hard.
Um.
How did I feel about it once I got there?
Yeah, because I thought that was a really cool,
like scary thing where you have to jump from one part of it to the other
right over the sun.
You know, I had I didn't get there until after I had already seen the ending.
And so doing that in the sun station, I kind of was just like, eh.
Eh, so what if I fall into the sun?
No, biggie. Yeah.
Yeah, I guess if you if it's happened so many times,
I hadn't actually fallen into the sun
until like much later in the game when I was just getting frustrated
and just flew in there deliberately.
You know, I yeah, I remember making that jump.
I kind of just didn't even think about it.
I kind of was just like, oh, I guess I got to just kind of float.
OK, it's one of those.
It's one of those moments where it's like relative
velocity is like crazy.
It's like I'm spinning around the sun as first as the sun station is.
You know, it feels like nothing is moving at all.
Maybe if I had just had taken a second and looked around,
I might have been impressed by that because I can imagine like if I looked down,
I would see the surface of the sun like shooting past me.
But I just kind of didn't,
although that's interesting and makes me kind of want to go check it out again.
What a thing.
What a freaking game, man.
It's all I feel like it's an all timer for me now.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely epic.
Definitely, I would say it's definitely epic. Yeah.
What do you feel?
How do you feel about like the way it ends?
Because it's it's not like a like you save the world.
It's like your world, the longer you play.
Initially, I was like, oh, we've got to stop the sun exploding.
But no, the sun is exploding.
Everything will be destroyed.
It's just how much are you going to figure out before that happens?
Yeah, it's your universe is dying.
But in your universe will be created.
So so the so the lore is that like the sun station was not able to induce a supernova.
And so therefore this is just they just had to wait until the natural end of the sun's lifespan.
Right. Yeah.
And then and then the know my like, dang, it didn't work.
Fuck. Well, hey, look, there's a comet.
Let's go see what what's that all about.
That could be interesting.
And then the comet spews like the radiation all over the solar system.
The old ghost matter, right?
That's where ghosts matter from. Yeah. Yeah.
Which is really sad when you think about it.
Did that did that wipe out know my civilization?
Is that like what I'm supposed to take away from that?
I think that's I mean, if you talk to what's his face with the playing the banjo?
If you if you come back to him because he's the archaeologist,
he loves hearing about all the information you you find out.
So you can tell him about how the know my died via the ghost matter.
And he's like, wow, that's how they died.
So I think it's very clear that that is the story you learn is that they died
from exploring this comet that entered the solar system and then exploded.
Yeah. It just it just the ghost.
There's just not that much.
I mean, maybe there's just not the much ghost matter.
And it's not very threatening in in in current in current year.
Yes, I think the idea is that it went all over the solar system
and killed everything, but then slowly like decayed.
And then there's only a few pockets of it left,
which is why life can continue to exist and how you evolve.
Yeah, it makes sense. It makes sense.
I felt like that was the implication.
But I was like, really, really?
It's like, I just it is a kind of I don't even talk about ghost matter.
But it's so it's so interesting, like the reason that there's all this stuff
to explore and no one to tell you about it.
Yeah, all these ruins across the solar system and all of these weird things.
And the Ash Twin project, which only is, you know, it it was just left running
because nobody was there to like turn it off or anything.
And then it just so happens to start working when the sun naturally hits a
supernova. Well, well, it was like a really cool setting for all of this.
It was it was it was designed to activate, you know, to be powered by the supernova.
So yeah, so it's not a coincidence, but it it makes it makes sense.
It makes a lot of sense.
It's like, yeah, I guess if they if they could if they needed a supernova
to power this device and they couldn't induce the supernova,
then just nothing happened until, you know, a billion years later,
a supernova, you know, is the inevitable result of happening.
And it just had to wait until it just happened anyway.
And then now you're here and you just it works out that the
this is how it this is how it shakes out.
Well, it's it's activated now.
And now we've got to do something about it.
Yeah, it's really great how you just.
I mean, there's tech.
Yeah, they they left they left scrolls and stuff.
Or I got to say, every time I like picked up a scroll,
I was just thinking like, oh, return a score.
I couldn't get away from it.
You put the scroll in the in the wall.
I love that the way that the technology is designed.
It's very funny.
It's very weird and cool.
And and the the way that the the scripts.
I mean, it's not very space efficient, but it's kind of a neat idea that
like the writing sort of spirals out in like branches.
It's neat.
And I don't think the writing was like amazing, but it was fine.
I I felt like it.
It I there was an element of like character development, but I didn't really
pay too much attention to the names of the people until much later.
I was like, I was starting to like I was rereading things because I was stuck.
And then I was like, oh, yeah, this person and that people.
I was a little confused about like the generations of Nomai that are taking place.
Like some people came from the vessel and potentially grew old and died.
And then younger people from the same, you know,
civilization that they built in the in Brittle Hollow and other places
grew up to build the Ashwin project.
Yeah, there were like it's a little hard to follow.
But I liked I liked the the dialogue because it it serves very good
gameplay function without being like, yeah, too clinical.
Yeah, I like that there's some humanity in these like ancient people.
The I could tell that there were like distinct groups of names
that were part of like different generations.
I didn't read and I could tell that like, OK, there's
there's there's the group that is working on the the Sun Station project
and building the Ashwin project.
And there's the guy who has to make the warp core.
And I think his name is poke.
Or something pokey pokey.
Yeah. Yeah.
And there's a there's another one that starts with a P.
And I know that like two of them.
There's two that are like flirting with each other.
And I think at some point they might get married.
I think at some point they might switch to referring to their spouse.
Or maybe there's another group that were married in another pair that were flirting.
Yeah, I didn't really I didn't really pay that much attention to like who's who.
The trouble with that is that your ship notes down the relevant information,
but isn't note down anything else.
Who said what? Yeah.
Who said what and what their names were and like the the quips.
They're they're definitely are you have to write it down yourself
if you actually want to like understand everything.
There definitely are little little stories going on between the characters.
And they definitely have a little bit of like a distinct voice,
but it's not it's not like that distinct.
It's not like it's not that I think I think it's it's good
though, because it's if if you're a little unclear about something,
seeing a familiar name will be like, oh, that guy, that guy's here.
And so you might have a bit of like you would associate something
that that other guy was talking about with this current thing,
which might help you piece together like how they're connected and like solve a puzzle.
There's something simple like that.
There's the one that had to build the warp core.
And then he says, like, no, it's not ready. I need more time.
There's another one who there's there's one that's like,
we should build this the sun station, even though it could destroy the solar system.
And another one's like, no, we shouldn't build the solar the sun station
because it could destroy the solar system.
It is pretty scary that their that their plan was to induce a supernova
and have this thing of this Ash Twin project
and relying on it to accurately send the memories back.
So yeah, they like would know.
I hope they were. I mean, I'm sure they tested it and stuff,
but it was like inducing a supernova so that they could send a probe out
to find the eye of the universe a million billion times.
Is a and I guess, yeah, little, little, little much, a little bit.
They hope they were really confident it was going to work.
And I guess I guess in theory, then they could do it over and over again
a million times. And then when they finally found the coordinates
they were looking for, then they could prevent it from inducing it again.
Right. Yeah, they just turn it off and not induce the thing.
And now we know where the eye of the universe is.
But that dang comet just had to come out of nowhere.
It's a pretty funny like conceit, though, that like, OK,
we need to find this thing out, but it's going to be really hard.
It's going to take a lot of time to find it out.
So let's just create a stable time loop
that will iterate itself 900 million times.
And we won't even notice that because then it'll like after the last time
it resets, we'll just cancel it, but we'll have the information.
It's funny. It's good. Yeah.
It's a well, it's a very it's a very well considered.
Uh, thing, I guess the only.
No, I guess it's not a plot hole.
It's not a plot hole.
It makes sense that the probe would fire in different directions
every time because the know my mask would remember
which it already fired in so it can decide like, OK, well, now I'll use a new one.
Random different one. Yeah. Yeah.
It is kind of insane that like it eventually did find the eye of the universe.
Like, how isn't it a quantum when it move constantly?
It does move constantly, but.
Well, I mean, it's, you know, I don't think that really matters because
at the end of the day, where it is is random.
Wait. Oh, are you are you saying that like once it's observed?
Geez, well, what would resetting that would resetting the time line
with that with that?
Would it? Oh, no, it's fine location.
I actually I think it's fine because it's not time travel necessarily.
It's memory travel.
So you are just experiencing linear time and then.
You are like adding versions of memories from the future onto yourself.
And so you're you're gaining things.
So you haven't technically observed it.
You haven't technically.
So like the probe finds the eye of the universe and.
That's where it is.
And so every time, every loop, which is the same linear time path,
it's in the same place because that's where it is.
That's where I found it.
Yeah, I guess I buy that.
I guess. Yeah, I mean, I never really thought about it before,
but like it's a lot of like half science anyway.
Because because in this in the timeline where you go there,
it has not the probe has not yet has not observed it.
No, you know, it is observed at once actually.
Oh, I kind of think I kind of think maybe you're right.
You're on to something there because.
Because since it's quantum, it has no location until observed.
Therefore, even if the locations in one time line,
if the location was observed in one place,
why would it necessarily be in the same place before?
It's quantum behavior would mean that it could be.
In any that it could it could be anywhere upon the next time.
That it was observed, I think.
I don't know.
I mean, I think the idea is that you are not in this in the cycle
where the probe found it.
You're in a new you're in a, you know, another cycle
where the probe didn't find it's just shooting continually.
Yeah.
And when you use the coordinates,
you go there and you immediately observe it.
And since you're constantly observing it,
you don't close your eyes, isn't move.
Oh, and also there's the whole thing like if you're on something,
you travel with it.
So once you're there, you're there.
But what? Yeah.
But what I'm saying is if it's behaving quantumly,
it's its location is not defined until it is observed.
And the act of observing it would basically make it pick a location.
So even if it's start, you know, it's its position is in a super.
It's its location is in a superposition of states until the probe observes it.
And then it has a location because it's been observed.
But if the same probe were to observe it twice,
there's no reason why it would be in the same place both times.
I don't know.
I know a list about quantum mechanics.
I mean, that's that's how the moon is.
That's how the quantum moon is.
I don't know.
I guess the the the eye of the universe could behave.
It could its quantum behavior could be different.
I mean, it's obviously a magical impossible thing. Right.
It's fun, though.
Like, yeah, getting getting there and doing all that stuff.
And like the the ending.
It was fine.
It was a little wacky.
It was a little out there.
I liked the noticing that
when I talked to the people, they were not real.
They were for similes that I understood them as because the Nomai was there,
but they didn't need the translating like rocks.
They could just talk to me, which is not something they could actually do.
So they were all fake.
They were all in my imagination.
That's interesting.
I didn't even think about that.
Yeah. But yeah, why would they be there?
And the the eye of the universe is based off of like, I guess,
things I have experienced because I see things there that I know of
as a as a little
Harthian is a little guy.
Just a little guy.
You know, yeah, it makes it makes more sense for them to be.
Imagination, imagination, projections, memory, projections.
And yeah, I know that guy does not speak your language.
He does not.
He really should have been talking with his little rock tablet.
No, it makes sense.
I.
It's a little bit.
It's I guess it's kind of what do you call it?
2001, a space Odyssey, like.
Go into the universe's core and what's there is like a projection
of your your own memory or something.
I mean, a little bit, I guess.
I mean, I think that the idea is that like you.
And your universe and your galaxy and solar system and the planets and all that.
When you're in the eye of the universe, I don't think you're really alive anymore
because you sort of get to understand that the universe itself is dying
and then will be reborn.
But the only thing that's odd about that is like afterwards.
I mean, I shot my probe into like the big cloud of stuff.
And then at the end, the probe was like flying around.
What? You mean over the fire?
Over the fire.
Like it's like like the after the big explosion, the big bang.
There's like a different race of aliens with their own campfire.
And then your probe flies around.
What? And I'm like, is that my probe?
Like, I think that's supposed to be my probe.
What do you what do you mean?
You're what do you mean your probe flies around?
What are you talking about?
Well, when you're at the eye of the universe, everybody sings their song.
It makes a big cloud of stuff.
Yes, you jump into it to end the game.
But I shot my probe in there.
So my probe went through into something.
And it seems.
Did you see what was did the probe show you what was on the other side?
I tried to take a picture, but it said like impossible.
Like I couldn't recall it.
I couldn't do anything. It was just gone.
So weird. OK, no, I didn't do that.
And then I just saw the probe in the image.
Yeah, like like there's the the the painting or whatever.
It's like a nice image of like planets, new planets, new universe.
Oh, so beautiful space.
And then your probe like flies across the screen
and then it goes to black and the credits and stuff.
That's so fucking funny.
No, I didn't I didn't do that.
So I don't know whether that happens every time
or if it's just if you shoot the probe.
I guess it didn't didn't happen for me.
OK, so yeah, there's like implications that you survive somehow
because your probe is there.
You physically would have gone through that.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, if you if your probe survives going through, why not you?
I guess.
So basically, it's home stuck.
And this is the new it is home.
It is home stuck. It is just home stuck.
Every every good story eventually becomes home stuck if it goes on long enough.
Well, I mean, I guess the probe could still
I mean, could theoretically last 14 billion years.
I mean, you wouldn't live that long.
I'm just thinking of like a stupid mud
where you just replace the the Nomai text with like troll texts, chat logs.
You just read about them talking about troll things.
Like, oh, who are these trolls?
Yeah.
Everything else is the same.
It's just that the trolls were doing it instead of the Nomai.
I feel I feel like.
I feel like it wouldn't even be that hard.
I feel like, yeah, if you just change some text, you could you could theme.
You could theme the game as though you're playing a game of spurb.
Yeah, with with simple with simple text changes, I feel like it could be done.
Damn, it's like it's like, man, I finally I finally experienced
what it's like to actually play spurb since home stuck was too fucking cowardly
to actually show any of the machinations of the game itself.
Thanks. Thanks, Outer Wilds.
I appreciate it. You did it. You made.
You made a game. You made home so good.
You made home. You've fixed it.
Man.
The it's like a Twitter reply, like, fix that for you posts game.
I want to I want to finish the DLC.
It's not it's not going to be like.
It's very it's different from the main game.
It's not it's not it's not going to scratch the same itch as the main game, though.
Well, I mean, for me, this the itch to scratch was like
exploring and learning and figuring out puzzle stuff. Yeah.
If that if it has that, then I don't mind like the the the world destroying
like super like, oh, my God, realizations are great.
But like the like moment to moment enjoyment is like OK, having a plan of action
and then going there and trying to try to find something out.
I mean, there there is mysteries to uncover.
I mean, yeah, they're.
It's it's I'm trying to I'm trying to decide.
Do is it actually different or is it just like?
It's kind of similar.
It's it's sort of similar in the act of that you go places and discover
things that might lead you to investigate stuff.
So, I mean, it definitely still has that going for it.
Actually.
Well, I don't get into it.
I I did enjoy it somewhat.
I don't I don't think I really like the direction it's going.
But I feel like but maybe if I push on a little more, I'll find more to like in it, perhaps.
I feel like I probably shouldn't give up on it.
Well, yeah, that's that's the Outer Wild spoilers.
Yeah, I think I think that's pretty much all I had to say about Outer Wilds.
Oh, one last thing.
Sure. Did you ever drive your ship so hard into something that it snapped into
and you couldn't repair it?
I did have my ship explode a couple of times.
What once once a couple of times it exploded while I was not in it.
And then one other time it exploded while I was in it, like trying to pilot it.
It's interesting.
There's like specific parts that get if they get hit like it can cause an explosion.
But I got like hit specifically so that it didn't explode.
But the two halves like snapped and flew away from each other.
So the front half of that I was sitting in, I was in the chair still.
I got out of the chair and the back half of the ship wasn't with me anymore.
Did the ship still like function at all?
No, I mean, I would have had to somehow put them together,
but they were just apart.
I couldn't interact with it at all.
I.
Yeah, actually, I think just yesterday I had it happen for the first time
that my ship blew apart and I was still I was still in the cockpit.
But like the ship, the cockpit was just kind of spinning.
And, you know, like I couldn't, you know, none of the functions of it worked.
I had, but I had to get up and just kind of like jump out the back of my
totally piece piecemeal ship.
And fortunately, I was near enough to my destination that I just like jumped out
and jet packed the rest of the way.
But I just was like, well, I guess I'm not.
Wasn't planning on going home anyway, so no worries.
Yeah, it never happened for a while.
I think there was one time and maybe I crashed on Ash Twin or something
and it it dealt a lot of damage to the ship and I got out and I was like,
ah, fuck it, like I wasn't planning on going home anyway.
And so I didn't bother repairing it.
And after a while, like, you know, the master light had been blinking.
And after a minute or two of that, the whole thing just blew apart.
I was like, oh, I didn't even know that could happen.
But it did.
I like how many how many different gruesome, terrifying ways you can die.
There were a couple of times when I jumped out of my ship
forgetting that I had not put my suit on.
And I was like, oh, fuck, no, I got to do it all over again.
Yeah, at some point, there was one time my my ship crashed
or like something happened to it.
And I was like, fuck, I have I don't know why.
I think I was trying to get through
dark Bramble and thinking my personal thrusters are probably not as loud.
And that is true.
You can do your thrusters with a jet pack, but only up to a point.
They will still hear you if you get too close.
But it was too.
It wasn't enough jet pack fuel.
So I sort of ran out of jet pack fuel floating through dark Bramble.
And then I ran out of oxygen.
I was like, fuck, this sucks.
Uh, what do you think?
I.
So I think some of the most one of the most frustrating deaths that I had was like.
I ran out of time a bunch of times while I was trying to fuck around in the vessel.
Like I tried to find like alternate doors and like other areas in the vessel.
There's I was a bit disappointed how little of the vessel you can actually like see.
You could basically only see like the bridge and the hallway.
I kind of thought it would be bigger, honestly.
I spent a lot of time like like going around it and trying to find like maybe broken parts
I could enter or like other doors that would open or something.
And I just you can't.
I guess you can't really run out of air.
No, yeah, you can in a vessel.
You can. There's no trees.
You're right. Yeah, it's broken.
Yeah. So I had to like run back to my ship and like refuel and reoxygenate a bunch of times.
And then I would run it.
I would hear the music like, oh, God, because getting back there is pretty annoying.
It's it's one of the one of the more out of the way places.
It's one of those those moments where it's like, you know, you don't have time left.
And so you're like, OK, well, I guess I'll just watch the solar like the explosion.
And in certain places, it sort of looks really like if it's if you're really far away
and they're the White Hole Station or something.
Yeah, it's like, wow, it's so slow.
Did you? Oh, here it comes.
Did you ever try to flee the solar system?
I I accidentally flung myself like near the boundary.
And then the autopilot kicked in and said, oh, you're going back to the sun, actually.
Yeah, it does that.
But you can turn it off if you want.
Yeah, I didn't try.
I didn't think that would be much happening.
I guess I should have tried it.
I actually got an achievement for it because once.
Well, I had a thought and it was a stupid thought.
But I was like, hmm, in this ship, there's, you know, the ship gives you infinite fuel.
I this is really dumb.
I feel embarrassed that I even had this.
I was like, what if I tried to reach a relativistic speeds?
I wonder if I just accelerated forever if I could exceed the speed of light.
Well, you know, obviously there's not enough time for that.
You would have to get going at like three times ten to the eight meters per second.
So I tried it.
I tried just like going just accelerating away from the sun for as long as it would let me.
And I think I managed to get up to like four or five, like like 50,000 meters per second.
You know, just just accelerating as long as I could.
And it's funny, you get far enough away that you can't even see the sun anymore.
And then it's so cool.
If you if you if you look at the map.
While you're really far away, all of the
like the indicators, like the names of of things and the like little
like crosshairs that appear over whatever you're locked onto, they're like jittery and shaky.
And and if you get really far out, they're shaking so much that like you can't read them anymore.
And I don't think that's like intentional.
I think that's just like the sort of the engine kind of like struggling with with the distance.
You know, something I heard I watched a little documentary on the making of it.
And they said, did you did you watch the the the no clip?
Oh, yeah, that was it.
I watched that, too.
And the guy mentioned something about how like things would jitter.
And I was like, I think I experienced engine jitter from trying to leave the solar system.
I think I found that artifact in the game.
What sort of blew me away was like they say that the planets are hurtling around the sun and stuff.
And they they're not necessarily on pre-programmed paths.
I mean, they do spin around the same way.
But like they are actually acting on each other gravity wise.
Oh, I'm like, wow, how the fuck.
And I guess it's sort of like your actions are not enough to change the course of a planet.
So you don't notice.
But like in theory, if you could like become huge, you could like if you could like crash yourself
into a planet and like send it off of its orbit, creating off his orbit and then falling into the
sun, which obviously they didn't program.
So it would just sit there, I suppose.
Yeah.
Or like fling itself way out out of the solar system, which is really very interesting.
There's a lot of technical problems.
I mean, I couldn't imagine how complicated it would be to make all of these planets
with their individual gravities.
And also having like interiors.
Honestly, yeah.
It's so like bizarre how it works so well.
While you're like on a planet, is it is the game still like considering like how the planet
itself is like moving through the solar system and like how it's being affected by the sun's
gravity?
That's that's fucked.
That's fucked up.
But that works.
Yes.
And and the the anti-gravity like chamber in in Timberhoff, you know, the little mining thing.
The reason it's anti-gravity is because that is the center of Timberhoff.
So there is no.
You're shitting me down what you're not gravity pulled.
So they didn't they didn't like custom code that area.
It's just like, yeah, in the center of the heart of.
Yeah, that's the reason you're yeah.
I mean, that's what they said.
I feel like it would work differently on something like dark Bramble because that's so insane.
But I don't know.
They have like an astrophysicist like rocket guy who was working on the programming.
So I'm like they wanted to be as scientifically accurate as they could.
Oh, hang on.
Well, I mean, in the real world, I mean, yeah, you would be you would be.
Well, that they they explained it like in the center of Timberhoff, there is no core.
It's just space and you're in there and the the mass of the planet is surrounding you.
So you're not being pulled to a center point.
Yeah, I mean, that is true.
The whole thing is like pulling you equally from every direction.
So it feels weightless.
OK.
But I but I feel I feel like that's their reasoning and it's sound reasoning.
But I still think that like they must have in the code like defined that like inside of this area,
you know, you're not you're no longer pulled towards the center of Timberhoff.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, maybe.
I don't exactly know how they do it.
I think they said one of them said something like
the way they calculate your position and stuff.
It wouldn't work if the because all these plants are moving.
They don't base it off of the world's location.
They work.
They base everything else off of your location.
Yes.
So like when you jump, the entire solar system goes down instead of you actually jumping,
which is how they explain that.
And I'm like, I can't wrap my head around that.
But like, maybe it's easier for the game to render it like that.
I'll say that the game the map had trouble displaying like when I did my
little experiment, like see how fast I could go, see how far outside this whole system I could get.
When I looked at the map, like, yeah, all the the names and indicators were fucked up.
Everything else looked normal, except that the twins were like not positioned correctly.
They sort of were like on top of each other.
And I just kind of thought that was like a glitch in the display.
Maybe the game actually thought that like it was like fucking up in the way it was trying to
position them around there, you know, shared, what do you call it, center of gravity.
But interesting thing that happened when I did that when I flew outside the solar system,
you know, obviously I was too far away for the supernova to get me.
So instead of dying, it was the same thing that happened in when I when I left the core in
the the project. But the supernova happened. I didn't die.
Instead, they're like a know my etching sort of appeared over my my vision.
And like, I just got time traveled back in time instead of instead of dying and going back.
Time travel. So like
when yeah, like when when the supernova kills you, it's like flashes.
It's like the screen goes white and then you die and then you go.
Yeah, I guess it's not actually tied to your death. It's just tied to the Ash Twin project.
Yeah. Yeah, that's what that's right. It's like, if you die, that's just a the time travel happens
whether you die or not. So if you die, it's just like, well, okay, you don't remember anything
that happens after that. But then you get because you did. Yeah. But if you survive and you if you
survive until the time travel happens, and you don't die, then you see this weird like
patchwork, a rectangular like thing sort of etch over your vision and then you travel back
and you still see the, you know, the mask and all your recorded memories and stuff.
So so what is implied to have happened then you didn't die.
But you just send back in time. So your memory is ripped out of your future self.
Yeah, I think into your past self. Yeah. Or is it or is it that
like hypothetically of this version of yourself is now alive and you're not playing them as them
anymore. You're now playing continually as the person with the memories. Oh, like,
like did you leave your that your that's like your other self in like an alternate timeline.
And that that person's memories were just copied into a new version of you in a new timeline.
I guess I don't like thinking of it as timelines because it's not technically
a timeline. It's not a different timeline. It's the same one. It's a stable loop with
yeah, it's a state. It's a mostly stable loop, a pseudo stable loop. It's unstable because the
memories like cause differences. Yeah, I don't know. I think
like do you because if I don't think it's just the memories I think it's just the
memories that go back in time as information. Yeah, I think it's just that the player the player
like is playing out a wilds. If you escape your memories that you have are sent back in time,
you know, but presumably you still exist in the future having not died. I think so.
I think so. And I didn't do this, but I read that if you take the warp core out of the Ash
Twin project and then you try to escape the solar system, you get a slightly different ending
where it says like you drifted forever until your your your fuel ran out and you died basically.
Okay. Yeah, that makes sense.
Because I mean you can't you can't go far enough to reach another star system in your
stupid little ship. Yeah, in tiny little shack ship. I guess that's the ultimate fate of the
the version of you that escapes the supernova is that you die eventually. Although and and
eventually your memories that are sent back come to you and you wake up again. Although
I do all the if if you had like, instead of 22 minutes, if you had like several hours or days,
you definitely could reach relativistic speeds and then who knows what would happen some some weird
maybe you could reach another star system with time dilation that way. I don't know.
I think ultimately though like your character is not immortal, so they will die of old age
even if they find another star system. Yeah. And then the the memory of you know, you'll wake up
back at the thing. Well, well, they'd only have the memory. They don't have the memory from before
only that 22 minute period that gets sent back. So so maybe when the thing is like blacking out,
it's like, it's just because the memory that you're having when you wake up does not involve
anything past this point. That makes sense. So even if you had memories and you had experiences
and you'll survive for a very long time and then eventually died, none of those memories get sent
back. You only remember when the solace of the supernova happened. I think that's I think that's
reasonable. God, so fucking good. I love it so much. So it's so it's so gratifying that you can
think about how this works and it's it's not and it makes sense and it's internally consistent
and you can be like, oh, yeah, yeah, I guess I guess I guess they thought of that. You know,
like, yeah, no, there is an explanation for that. Like, yeah. It's a very it's a very well considered
time travel story. Yeah, it's it's very cathartic when you think about it. And it's like, you're not
you're not like, you know, shushed for thinking too much. Like, oh, don't don't worry about it.
It's just time travel. Who cares? It's just for fun. Like, no, you can't think about it. This is
not for fun. This is serious. This is serious cerebral thoughts I'm having. And I'm enjoying it.
And I'm rewarded because it's it's it's logical. It's consistent. It's great.
Yeah, I think there were times when I probably did see with a ascending stone or whatever they're
called, I probably did see the inside of the Ash Twin project. And it's just like, I think you said
before, because like, what am I even looking at? Like, it's completely dark, except for the glowing
masks on the wall. And it's very scary. And what looks like stars swirling around, which is actually
just the timber hearth stone. But you don't know that at the time. I think I probably did see it.
And I just was like, it's just some spooky nonsense. Fuck it. Oh, you know what I could try
is going to Ash Twin, putting a probe there or like turning the gravity off or something
so that it looks different and then going somewhere else and using the scrang slab to like
see what it looks like and see if it's like a live feed or if it's like a memory, because I don't
actually know. I think it would be a live feed. I would expect that, yeah, it would it would show
you the the change state. And you could probably look up and see if you had taken the warp core
out, you could probably look up and see that there's no warp core. Like what if what if you did
like the thing you did where you jump in the black hole and you're in Ash Twin, and then you're
playing the game, and then you go find an Ash Twin slab and then you look at that and then you can
see yourself. I think you already there. I also think I think that the next time you die after
that, I don't think you actually have to meet yourself to have the like break the fabric of
reality. I think just the next time you die, the fabric of reality would break whether you go and
like find your alternate self or not. I suspect, I don't know. Because I mean, when you check the
map, you can see. Yeah, it was so funny. I was, I thought it was just glitching. I thought just
like, ah, the game, the game didn't account for me going through that hole. It thinks it has,
it has failed to update itself to reflect the fact that I'm no longer in the Ash Twin and now it
thinks that I'm in two places at once. Haha. Haha, I fooled you game. Haha. Oh no, the game fooled me.
No, it knew. It knew what I was going to do.
Ah, brilliant. What a fucking game. Yeah. This has been, this is now like the third episode in a
row we've been talking about, Outer Wilds. Yeah, but that's good. Definitely deserves it. Yeah.
I was honestly, a part of me was like, I should wait for a sale to buy the DLC,
but I didn't. I was like, nah, fuck it. Wait, waiting for sales is something I used to do,
but like it never happens. It's just sort of like, yeah, months and months go by and I'm like,
I could be enjoying a video game right now. I'm not. I want to save like 17 pounds. It's like,
who cares? Did I mention on the show, like when you told me about it and I checked,
it just so happened to be on sale and I was like, well, shit, I got to buy it right now then.
I was very lucky. Very lucky. It was like 40% off or something. I saved like 10 bucks.
I guess I got to buy it. Yeah. It's probably not on sale anymore, unfortunately.
But it is for sale. True. I think the DLC was like 15 bucks, which is like, I don't know,
whatever. The devs deserve it anyway. Even if the DLC was just like nothing.
They can have that 15, but they deserve it. Well, I think we should stop talking about it,
just in case somebody actually honored the request to not be spoiled for this game and
didn't listen to the entirety of the episode. I would feel bad for that person because they would
not get particularly much out of it. That's like most of this episode they're going to have to
skip, unfortunately. I mean, whatever. Fuck it. No, no, no. Well, they should
just go play out or wild and then they can come back and listen to all that and then
it'll be even better. That's their reward for playing amazing video games. They get to listen
to the procrastinators podcast. I'm happy for them. I really am.
Yeah. The only thing else I have on my notes is the UK is fucked.
The UK is fucked. I mean, obviously, but how so this week?
Well, this trust was doing a lot of stupid shit. That guy you told me about got fired.
Yes, he's no longer the chancellor. Nihwaj something?
quasi-quarting. Yeah, I'm sure. Same.
So Liz Truss had a terrible budget plan that she had in lockstep.
She's the new prime minister? Yes, she's the new prime minister. She was voted for by a few
Tory MPs to replace Boris Johnson, who was, you know, he stepped down because people were
saying you're a you're a you're a blagger. You're a bastard. You drank and had a COVID party
during lockdown. You fuck. Is that really why? It's mostly why, I think. It's just sort of like
bad PR and it's, I mean, whatever. There's so many worse things. So many worse things.
It's a little hard to understand. But I mean, lots of people hated Boris Johnson at the time.
But I think they would love him to come back because Liz Truss is so much dumber than he is.
But she had a shitty budget, which lowered taxes for the rich and
essentially just sort of like made the the economy like the whole people of all of the
economy people were like that's stupid. I love the economy. Like that was just a very badly
planned thing. She didn't know what she was doing. How long has she been in charge?
Like six weeks. Oh, five weeks. It's not. It's not that long. Okay.
I know this. I'm remembering that one guy who like got really mad at me for like
badly explaining British politics. So I'm sorry. Was that a voicemailer?
I think it was a voicemailer. The point is the budget was bad. And she stood by it until
she finally got the message and said, okay, I understand that it's bad. I'm going to change it.
And but I'm still I'm still going to work with my chancellor because he's smart and
I still trust him. Is that quasi? No, I yeah quasi. Oh, actually, I want to I'm going to throw
him under the bus and I want to still stay prime minister even though I'm so bad at my job and
nobody trusts me and I have no like, what's the word? No swag. No swag. She doesn't have any
government squad swag. And so she's got a new chancellor and it's Jeremy Hunt.
I can't I can't possibly be his name. It's Jeremy Hunt. But okay, everyone calls him Jeremy
Hunt because he is a real piece of work made it too easy. Yeah. Yeah. He was the the
health secretary for a while. And he's like, as far as I understand, most famous for being
really heavy on cuts for things that people need like the NHS. Nice. And, and, you know,
social programs and stuff that helps the poor. Good. He loves cutting funding for all that.
Well, he loves. Cool. All right. He's the man for the job. He loves selling off
things like the NHS to the highest bidder. And who doesn't, you know,
he's a relatable. I can have a beer with a guy that loves selling the NHS to private interests.
So now he's in charge of the economy or the, you know, the chancellor, the ex-checker or whatever
that actually means he's going to come up with a new budget. And predictably, he's being like,
yes, in order to pay for things, we're going to raise taxes, hopefully on the rich, but I
he hasn't specified yet. So I don't think it's going to be the rich. I think it's going to be
middle and low income people are going to have to have taxes raised because of course, but you
know, hasn't actually happened yet. Excellent. Excellent. And he's saying he's probably going
to be lots of cuts. And I'm expecting them to be cuts to things that people need to live,
such as the NHS, because he just loves hating the poor, because he's a, you know, he's Jeremy Cunt.
Understandable. So like before, Liz Truss was saying, we're going to lower taxes.
And we're not going to cut anything. And we're somehow going to pay people's energy bills because
of the rising gas prices, which is like stupid, because the question then becomes if you're not
raising taxes, and you're not cutting spending, how are you going to increase spending on these
things? Where's the money coming from? And she didn't have an answer for that. And eventually,
she's like, okay, Jeremy Hunt is going to cut everything and raise taxes.
Okay, it's like, okay, well, I guess it makes sense now. That's better than like,
not having an answer for how you're going to pay for stuff. But it's Jeremy Hunt. And
it's just going to be bad. I don't trust him at all. I mean, it sounds like he has vowed to do
bad things. I just based on past experience of things that he's, you know, obviously for. I mean,
he's a Tory. So he's like pro rich, pro rich anti poor, like generally speaking,
they'll always lie and say, we're doing this for the good of the country. What they mean
is for the good of themselves. Because if the country's rich and the rich are rich in the country,
then he can be part of the rich in the rich country. Regardless of how many people in the
poorer brackets are dead or dying or living in poverty or just having a bad time. And that's
just sort of like the Tory way generally. Right. And what's the problem? So the problem is I don't
like it. And I want to fuck an election. Well, have you tried not being such a snowflake?
I melted. Thanks. Yeah. Climate change. Well, looks like it was like everyone got what they
wanted then. Yeah, that was just sort of a little rant. I didn't really have anything special to
say. I just, you know, I think we got a voicemail about this, but I might as well mention it.
How do you feel about the soup on the Van Gogh? Soup on Van Gogh. Oh. Yeah. I mean, whatever.
Yeah. I don't care about that painting particularly. It's old. Vincent Van Gogh was pretty cool. Yeah.
Made some good stuff. But like, I don't hate them because they're trying to raise climate
activism. Yeah. It is just sort of annoying that the majority of the response is like,
God, these fucking stupid bitches. I hate the environment now. Like, I don't know. Yeah,
I don't like that. I don't like the petulant. Like, this makes me want to burn even more fossil fuels.
Like, shut up. No, it doesn't. I'm a little on the fence about whether I think like
it's good to... Part of me is like, well, they got people talking. Well, they raised awareness.
Uh, another part of me is like, yeah, but like to one end, like, does that accomplish anything?
Will anything be accomplished by raising awareness? Are we just perpetually locked in the cycle of
like, raise awareness for issues that everyone already knows about and it doesn't really do
anything? So is there really a point to it? I guess I think that the destruction of art is
generally bad. Although I understand that like, you know, if climate change destroys the world,
then like, art will have no value to anyone. So like, yeah, there are definitely more important
things. There are definitely... The climate is more important than Van Gogh's sunflowers. Sure.
But if destroying Van Gogh's sunflowers doesn't accomplish anything meaningful in pursuit of
climate change, then maybe it's not worth doing. So I kind of see both sides on that. What really
fucking gets me, though, is the fact that the painting is literally fine and nothing happened.
And there's literally nothing to be mad about. So when I see people getting upset about it,
I like, cannot understand. Like, what is even bothering you about this, sir?
It feels more like a minor Twitter drama moment than it does, like,
anything really significant. Yeah. I mean, it's totally just a thing that a certain kind of
person can point to and be like, ah, kids these days are doing this. Ah, society has inverted.
Remember that? Remember that line? I don't. What was that from? It was from the old
Digi Bro asterisk war. Society has inverted.
Because asterisk war is set in a place called Invertia, where people's morals have inverted,
or something. What a stupid fucking conceit for a setting. I don't know. Something,
I'm thinking about it. And I'm like, damn, if I understood correctly, because obviously I never
watched the show, just from that video, having it explained to me in as brief a time as possible,
it sounds like the setting of the asterisk war is literally just like society has generated.
These days, everything is fucked up and people suck. Not like the good old days.
But it's like text, like explicit text. Society has inverted. Morality has been turned on its head.
Evil is good now. This is all completely aside from the point I was trying to make,
which is that vandalism is good and artifacts should all be destroyed all the time.
I saw like one take that was like particularly annoying, which was somebody who was just sort of
not really saying anything, but pointing out that I don't think they realized that van Gogh
was like a working class, like low class artist, and he struggled. And it's like,
yeah, but he's dead. And this painting is worth a lot of money. I don't think he cares that somebody
threw soup on it. I don't know what they're trying to get at. They're just trying to appeal to like,
oh, but you can't hurt that guy's art. Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
He was a struggling artist, and you know, that's bad. You should be hurting like rich people art,
I guess. Like destroy a dolly because dolly was famous? Like whatever. Who cares? It's just a
painting. It currently exists physically in the world. Yeah, I agree. That's a stupid fucking
point. I mean, I've seen the opposite point, which is that like, you know, van Gogh was kind of like
a freak and a weirdo and engaged in all kind of like, what do you call it,
histrionic destructive behavior. So like, just just trashing some valuable shit,
just for no reason is kind of exactly what van Gogh would have done if he was alive.
Perhaps. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. It's just sort of like, besides the point, like it's a very
valuable piece of artwork. Yeah. And the idea of a valuable something or other being destroyed
is like, makes people mad. And I don't think the climate message got through in a way
to people who wouldn't already agree. I guess they're trying to push the envelope,
but I don't know what the idea of the point is. I've seen some... It's just sort of like,
outrageous for the outrageous sake. Yeah, it is. That's why like, I'm not really convinced it
was super helpful. I've seen some claims that like, the org that set it up is actually like,
funded by oil and it might be some kind of like, deliberate op to like, make climate activism
look bad. I don't know. I mean, I wouldn't put it past oil companies to try and do that. Maybe.
But how could they get, how could they get a woman with pink hair and pronouns to do it?
It's impossible. It's impossible. Yeah, I don't know. No, there was something about like,
that or something about like, that org that made those shirts that they were wearing is actually
like, funded by oil or something. So it's like, what's what's the motivation here? What's the
underlying point? And nobody knows. Like, climate activists look bad. Maybe. But the, and then
like, either way, I don't know. Question mark, question mark, question mark profit. Yeah, like,
will people like, purchase more unrecyclable plastics because of, because they're mad at
these two girls? Is to make pundits on Twitter go, this just makes me want to burn more oil,
and then everyone starts burning more oil. What if that was the point? They just buy
a barrel of oil and then don't burn in the backyard. Take a picture of it, film it like,
fuck you climate activists. Like that picture of Ben Shapiro outside of the Home Depot with
like the one piece of wood. But it's like, Hey, look at me. I bought a barrel of oil.
I'm going to slather it all over my body. Take the oil challenge. Speaking of oil,
wait a minute. Speaking of oil, oil challenge would be a real thing.
In this, in this day and age, waste as much oil as you can. Speaking of oil, somebody,
I think somebody threw out my bacon grease. I was saving my bacon grease. And I think someone,
just someone thought it was icky. I don't know. Maybe I can't find it. You know, I had a little
jar had a little glass jar. I cooked a whole over the few days, like I had some bacon that was like
nearing its expiration date. So I cooked it all and I ate it all over the course of you. And I
saved all the grease. I preserved it in a little jar. And now I can't and today I looked and I
can't find the jar. Maybe someone else ate it. Maybe they spread it on toast like a butter.
You know what? If someone else used it, I wouldn't even be that mad. But if someone just like got
rid of it, I would be very mad because like, obviously I put it in a jar and saved it.
Like what the fuck? Maybe they thought it was cum. Yeah, that would explain it.
I don't want that shit in my fucking house. Why does this guy's cum smell like bacon? Hmm. Oh well.
I can't find the jar. If I found the jar and it were empty, I would know like someone sabotaged
my grease. But until I find the jar, I'll just consider it a mystery and like maybe I misplaced it.
I think I remember where I put it. I think I know where I put it.
It's like someone's fucking with my stuff. Someone's fucking with the stuff in my fridge,
man. What the hell? I don't like it. You gotta label it. You gotta put a little tracking device on
it. I might be a couple days out from the power getting shut off at my house. I'm not sure about
that. Why is the power getting shut off? Well, because that girl, she was paying the power bill
and I think she canceled her account and I'm not, I don't want to do it. I don't want to take over.
So like somebody's got to do it, but like nobody has. And so like I'm not sure if like
there's a time limit on like when are they gonna, if nobody does it, are they just gonna
shut the power off at my house? It would be pretty funny if that happens.
Get some candles. Make sure to save your projects immediately, like every five seconds.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, in theory, it would be a solvable problem. I don't know. I'm not sure.
Okay. On the one hand, I kind of don't want to be responsible for it. On the other hand,
maybe I should be responsible for it because maybe I could generate a credit card, a cashback.
Hmm. So maybe I actually, maybe I actually should volunteer to take over everything.
Hmm. Currency. Hmm. Money. Did I mention that I got those bonds? Did I mention that I got the
treasury bonds? Oh, you got them? I did. Yes. You know, they said it could take up to 12 weeks
for them to approve my account. Fortunately, it did not take 12 weeks. It only took a few weeks.
And I was able to, yes, I have the bonds. I'm gonna get that interest for the
July, June to October period of 2022. And then next year, and then next year, I can buy even more
and get even more interest. And I hope the interest and I hope the inflation rate stays high so that
my eyeballs continue to accrue. Hell yeah. Thank you. Thank you very much. Thank you.
And standing ovation. Yeah. The government didn't screw me over this time. So good for them.
Hooray. Hooray. And yeah, okay. Other than complaining about my bills and my bacon,
grease, I guess I don't really have anything else. Did anything else happen this week? No, not really.
Really, really close to being done with my stupid video.
I showed, I showed my patrons in my patron, in the secret patron channel of my Discord server.
I showed them some little funny animated bits that I made for the in for like the very beginning
and the very end. And they seem to find it amusing. And I'm pretty proud of how they turned out. I
think they look good. So I'm excited. I'll be excited to post that. Nice. And you know when I
post it, I'm going to message Mary and I'm going to say, Hey, Mary, you, you encouraged me to make
another video. And I made this and I appreciate the encouragement. So I'll let him know that he had
a hand in it. And I hope he is pleased. Did I mention that like kind of the reason why I made
the video was because Mary asked me like, why don't you make videos? I think you did mention it.
Okay, okay, okay. Well, I won't re explain it. But that was like, was like months ago at this point
now. Yeah, he might he might be he might be shocked to if I tell him that like, yeah, that thing you
said to me like seven months ago, I did it. Lamal. Hmm. Well, yeah, that's all I got. You want to go to
voicemails? Yes. Okay. Well, the first voicemail that I see is called this channel is trash and
you're lucky it's so big. It might be empty. It might be one of those empty voicemails.
It's just a sound. It's just a sound. Okay, never mind. Okay, the next one is called it's true three,
two, one, go. It's the same guy. I think he's doing like a bunch of nothing.
This is just a way is the point to waste our time on purpose. Yeah, the next one and the
next one after that, they're probably the same. Yeah, next one's called for real, though. What?
He said something. I don't care. He said for real, though, I think under his breath. Okay,
next one is called I'm not lying three, two, one, go.
What's the point? What's the point? I think a lot of these are the same guys just.
Yeah, next one is called call of three, two, one, go. We've taken the lead.
No, no, no, that's enough. That's enough. Next one's called my favorite PCP member is did you bro?
Okay. Then the new cod sucks. I'm disappointed in activities. Okay. The next one is called where
is Tom? This has got to be another. No, there's nothing. Hey, Ben new fan here. I hope we can
meet this Nate guy one day. Okay, he sounds really cool unlike you. Yeah, true. They should
make a death stranding to okay. PCP speak pipe is not a message board. Could this be a real one?
No, I really don't think so. I think it's still him. Next one's empty, empty, empty.
Next one's called art. Could this be real? Do you think this one's real or no?
Could be 35 seconds. Okay, three, two, one, go. What's the point to try to classify what
is an artist art? It feels like it's just a prestige thing how they're trying to get it for
yourself or deny it from others. Please respect me. Video games are art. Oh, that guy with his AI
generated images. That's not odd. What are you stupid? Like to some extent, every category and
word like this is arbitrary, but this feels way more arbitrary than most. Even gender is more
real than this, at least participating in someone's categories of gender has them treating you
differently. I can buy what's art feels more like an ad hoc thing. After you've already decided how
you want to treat something, you arbitrarily say that it is or isn't art to back that behavior up.
I wouldn't even say that's incorrect, because if I hate something,
when somebody says, yeah, but it's art, though, I would just say I don't care. I hate it.
I think sometimes it is sort of a prestige thing. If you like something, you want to call it art
because it sounds good, but something can be art, but still be bad. I do feel like that's a pitfall.
I genuinely don't use the word unless it's one of these conversations about what is art. I only
think about whether something is good and literally what it is. Oh, it's a painting.
If it's a painting, it's a painting because it's got paint and you use paint to make it.
At the end of the day, art or not, it's a very vague way of saying whether you like or respect
or whatever you personally feel the word art connotates. Because people feel slightly different
or vastly different things to it, it's just a conversation like deadlock and it's annoying,
and I don't like using it. At the end of the day, it is an arbitrary distinction. I generally think
basically everything humans do is art. I think I have a pretty broad, I think it's better to be
broad with it than exclusive. With AI-generated art, it's art if you want it to be, but I don't
like it because of what it represents for the people who are profiting from it. As a tool,
it's fine. The fact that you can do it is cool. I don't want to repeat the conversation we had
the last week, but it's a tool and that's true. I think if you said is it art, I would say yes it
is, but the talk about AI art and whether it's art, for me, it's not about though this isn't art,
and I have to say that in order to disqualify it from being good. It's like, okay, well who
deserves the credit for this is the pertinent question. Because credit in capitalist society
involves payment generally, which is a necessary prerequisite for being alive.
Yeah, resource allocation. So credit is kind of important, and that's why it's such a big talking
point whether or not something is art because we all want to live and it doesn't feel right when
people who could be considered worthy of the credit, not getting the credit, and therefore having a
more difficult life. I think that's why that particular thing keeps coming up. If people
didn't have to worry about making ends meet, I don't think it would be quite as heated a
discussion as it has become. Did you hear about the Bayonetta voice actress?
I did. I didn't watch the video, but I heard she was paid like $4,000 for the entire game of the
third in a series of extremely popular games where she's the voice actress, which is like
embarrassing. I don't know anything about the voice acting profession. I mean, that sounds pretty
low. It's very low. Voice actors are frequently shit upon by the industry of any voice acting,
whether it's for dubbing or video game stuff or usually that's the only two things, animation
or video games. I mean, for a well-known character, for the voice actor to reprise their role as a
well-known character in a highly anticipated AAA video game, that just does seem like a silly low
number. Maybe if there wasn't much voice acting in the game, it would be justified if there just
wasn't much of it. I think the reason was because Nintendo moved away from a union
for voice acting talent so that they could afford, so they could be allowed to pay their
voice actors so much less and the Bayonetta lady was like fuck that. It just seems like such a
drop in the bucket to quibble over when it's like this is like the, in so far as a video game has
a star like this is it like this is the star talent of the game basically and you're like
why would you fuck with them? I don't know. I mean game companies and the workers get fucked over
a thousand dollars like an intent like platinum studios or whatever are you gonna fucking break
the bank if you pay this person like 20,000 instead of 4,000 like what the fuck? What are you doing?
Super bad. Super bad press. You have not saved yourself any grief by doing this. You fools.
Everybody loses. And it goes in like in contrast to like the way that the Mario movie has all
of these super high profile celebrity voice actors instead of voice actors as like Chris Pratt is
gonna be paid millions to do like a shit Mario. Yeah. And everyone's like okay whatever fucking
but that's just that's how it works. If you're a celebrity you get big paycheck and if you're a
professional you get shit because the unions are not as strong. Sad. Sad times. I mean I can only pray
to Allah that like his wrath will be visited upon the undeserving inshallah inshallah I pray that
I pray that every did a triple A developer goes to hell no matter what that's all I can do.
True. Okay the next one is called I got a notification in the middle of this recording.
Three, two, one, go.
You do that. Do you ever have your wisdom teeth out?
Oh is that why he was talking? I didn't. Yeah he said he said he had his wisdom teeth out.
No um my teeth are dumb so they stay. Oh lucky. I had mine out in high school and I looked
really fucked up. I didn't they didn't hurt like they said like it might hurt for a while afterwards.
I didn't find it very painful but my face was all swollen and looked like shit for like a full
week afterwards it was terrible. I had a date I had a date with like an an older girl that I had
to crush on at the time and I had it happen and I had it while I was like fucking my face was all
fucked up. That's a nightmare. How'd it go? You know it wasn't like you know she wasn't like
interested in me or anything. It was just like we were going to hang out so I don't think she cared
because to her it was like I'm just hanging out with this guy. For me I was like I have a huge
crush on you and I want to hang out with you and I god I wish my face wasn't fucked up but
I mean it probably doesn't matter really. It wasn't like we were going to hook up if I had looked
normal. Just an extra layer of humiliation. Wisdom teeth really turned me on. Do you have any?
The next one is yeah thoughts on the Van Gogh incident. Three, two, one, go. Go. Three, two, one, Van
Gogh. Hey art is cool right? Paintings Van Gogh. I wouldn't care if every single painting in the loo
was scorched if it like accomplished something from the climate charts. Do people think that
paintings will be around to be appreciated after mass extinction? Like priorities.
Sorry, I mean Van Gogh would probably be on board with having his painting be vandalized.
Yeah. I think we're on the same page with this guy. It's just a question of like
is it effective? Yeah, was that the best way to do it? Did it work? I would have been like okay
saying yes try it and I don't know whether it would work but like you tried. I just don't know.
Yeah. Okay, we've already been over that. Next one is hey Ben new fan here. Where's this video being
uploaded to and how are you? Hey Ben, what's the channel this video will be uploaded on?
Hi Ben new fan here. What's the video and why are you making one? Ben, you're a good teacher.
You should quit the PCP and be one. Happy birthday Ben. This one's 12 seconds long. Three, two, one,
go. Oh no, nothing. Next one's part two. Three, two, one, go. Oh no, nothing. Okay.
And then there's a YouTube link which I will not check. So many nothing voicemails this time.
For Halloween I'm going as Ben St. What does he look like? So Ben is your new video going to
be a lecture. Ben's weekly reminder. Play Delta Room Chapter Two. Ben's weekly reminder. Catch
up to one piece. Voice Jail Request. Three, two, one, go. Can you guys voice jail the actually
carbon offsets NFT guy? Every voicemail they send is annoying. Humble request. Please accept.
I appreciate the sentiment and inshallah he will get what's coming to him but I feel like at the
very least his questions are asked in good faith and I have to appreciate that much. Yeah, I don't
find him like malicious. He's just sort of like. I don't think he deserves voice jail.
And but besides we've defunded the PC police so. That's true and thank goodness.
All right, skip another fake one. Okay, we got an Imgur link. Oh boy, I love Imgur.
Finally something. I love Imgur. Yeah, I love content.
Let's see here. Okay, it's more it's more video. Astronaut Ben St. or rather Ben's space.
It's another VD. Drifting aimless drifting through space aimlessly. My only hope
is not to collide with anything of greater momentum. I had some plan to stay adrift but
it's been so long I forget what it was for when I took lift off. I had an idea with doing math and
sounding smart but then I got a bit funny a bit a funny bit in mind. That's what he says. I do
have to keep in mind even if a small meteorite comes close to me that even if it doesn't collide
my center of gravity may shift and throw off my trajectory. My Eunice mission. My mission will
not end in failure. You have my word as an astronaut Ben St. I think that's Trixie on our
broomstick. Oh, hey Ben funny coming across you out here. Oh my fucking god Trixie space is my thing.
This is illegal. You have to pay royalties to be in space.
Uh you don't own space Ben. Oh no she's right. Who the fuck do you even think you are the mayor
of space? Shut the fuck up Trixie shut the fuck up. You shut up Ben. I was actually applying
myself with my college degree. College is fucking bullshit. You're out there doing jack shit.
I literally did math to get out here and to where I'm going. I literally did math to be
at lengtherspace. I did math to get here. Who are you? Who are you to criticize?
You're literally going fucking nowhere. Why the fuck are you out here? I just got high as
fuck weed as a hell of a thing dude. Get the fuck away from me Trixie leave me the fuck alone you
bitch. Whatever Ben I fucking do what I want. I'm just going to go get higher without you bitch.
Fucking bitch mother fucker. So true. Oh my god I've reached oh I see a finger.
I see a finger on the side of that one. Oh race reveal. True. Ha ha I've made it the sun that last.
The beautiful sun. Finally eternal warmth of my goddess.
Yeah I'm not sure if we can I mean it's probably fine to put this on screen but it's a giant
celestial but a posterior of celestia at the pony. I think we can put it on screen but we
shouldn't link to it because this was flagged as mature content so I'm afraid to link it so no link
but no link. I think we can show it what a lovely day to enjoy a book too. That's how I talk about it.
I love enjoying a book today. This might be my favorite of any content. Yeah this is great.
This is tremendous.
The beautiful sun.
Oh god. You know what I feel like all the characters were
were believably in voice. They all spoke in there in there just as they should have behaved
and I just appreciate it so thank you for that. I like to imagine this is out to wilds
and I'm just on the planet reading a book. I think that's while you're doing that. I think
that's the the inspiration for this right. Yeah outer wild space exploration. Beautiful sun.
Benny you're you're fucked. This is this is fucked. What the fuck is wrong with you twisted.
Keep posting. Does your wife know that you drew a big pony ass? What would what would she say huh?
She would say draw a bigger draw the Luna draw Luna but next draw Luna orbiting.
Next one is called unrelated. I love you guys. You had no reason to continue this three two one go.
Pokemon go go.
Okay Pokemon go.
What is this next one poke community dot com show thread link.
Okay. Let's let's let's let's find out poke community.
Yeah. Is it loading for you? Oh there it goes.
Pokemon emerald studio.
A rogue like Pokemon game. Pokemon emerald rogue v one two one the questing updates.
Ever wondered what Pokemon might look like as a rogue like yes it's a Nuzla right.
When you go on an adventure all routes encounters and items we procedurally chosen
based on your progress into a run. After a certain number of routes you will encounter
a random gym leader who have a procedurally chosen team they're assigned type as you progress further
into a that's neat. That's interesting. Huh. It's like Pokemon mystery dungeon but normal Pokemon.
Wow. Kind of. The fact that you go into dungeons and it's a bus. Oh yeah. Yeah that's true.
Hmm. That's pretty cool. I wonder if it's any good.
It sure is Pokemon. I might I might I might look into this a little more. I'm kind of
intrigued. That's pretty cool. That's pretty cool. Yeah. It's what is it called Pokemon emerald
rogue. Rogue version one point two point one the questing update. Fascinating.
What do we got next one is called son it's son of Marowak three two one go. Oh wait wait
a minute wait a minute wait a minute sorry there was a voicemail that went with that Pokemon one.
We got to listen to it three two one go. Do you like Pokemon do you like vogue likes
that you should play Pokemon emerald rogue it's pretty good. Okay that didn't add that much I'm sorry
sorry interrupted you son of Marowak okay son of Marowak three two one go.
So we're renting out a movie theater for my friend's birthday to play video games
given the chance and money not being an issue what would you guys want to play whether it be
games you want to play for your own reasons or any game you'd want to play with a crowd
whether it be you playing for a crowd or you playing with a crowd what would be your ideal
video gaming any theater experience. How do you how do you play like are you playing like on the
movie screen. Yeah I mean I don't know if this is how Game Grumps Live works but they've done
shows they probably play a game in a theater and riff live with an audience. Oh hmm okay I'm going
to assume you're just playing it on the movie screen yeah what would be a good game for that.
I guess like if there's a crowd I'm trying to think of like what would be
because you can't okay like it like with the twitch screen stream like the chat is like the
crowd for simile is like it's basically the crowd but you can easily ignore it by not looking at
what's being written but with a crowd they're speaking they're audible so like
I have something where you can hear them go whoa and cheer and stuff. You know what I think would
be fun but only if the crowd knew how to play is like playing like something like Dungeon
Crawlstone Soup in a theater and like the crowd if the crowd is like watching and sort of like
yelling and sort of like shouting out like commands shouting out like no don't do that like.
Yeah I think something that would be like make for a fun rowdy experience.
Something like that. No like backseat gaming but entire like like theater people doing it.
Something that like people I mean if the crowd knew how Dungeon Crawlstone Soup works they could
be like they could react to like if a new monster comes on screen or like you know if you choice
of class and stuff like that. If everyone was engaged in it I think that could be pretty fun.
So I mean if not that then maybe what would be another game that would be good in that way
like something something turn based. Something turn based but maybe something that you can play
in like a single evening. I mean I guess if I think about it like anything that's an esport
like a fighting game. A fighting game with two people is always going to be like oh cool I
hit him used the button but it's kind of normal. That's too fast for there to be like meaningful
audience participation. Oh right you're thinking like that. I don't know what like I'm thinking
of it being a large theater if it was like a smaller one we could actually hear what people are saying.
I'm assuming there will be a crowd of maybe like two dozen people or something like that.
You know it's hard to know. It is hard to know. Playing something like a walking simulator or
something slow is an obviously bad thing because it's just going to be a lot of dead
like nothing happening. Yeah. Something like Dark Souls where if you are good people would be like
wow cool and if you suck people like oh boo sucks I guess. I'm sure something something that's not too
long turn based and there's like choices to be made. Something something that like audience can
meaningfully like have input on like your strategy or whatever. I don't know I can't I don't know if
I can think of anything like that off the top of my head. I'm sure something like that must exist.
Shit. Fuck. Sonic Adventure.
I'm I'm I'm drawing a blank. I don't know. Commenters leave a comment if you can if there's you can
think of a game that meets those criteria because that sounds like it would be fun.
But I'm too dumb. The next one is called Son of Marowak promo three two one go.
For anyone who might like to rent out a theater for playing games.
Cinemark is the theater chain that I will be renting for. The prices range from 200 to 350 dollars.
Why are you telling us this because it's a presumably good.
I mean all right. It's not that much money though.
Well that was the last one. I think it's a reload. No no that is the last one.
I just feel like I should come up with a game. Come up with a Minecraft.
Honestly Minecraft would be fun. I don't know. A lot of Minecraft's like moment to moment gameplay is
chopping stuff and placing stuff and waiting for things to happen like smelting. It it would
be very boring because like yeah it's fun to like see a time lapse of somebody building some
amazing structure but like yeah I don't know about watching it. Speaking of which we should play
Minecraft on stream. We should play Minecraft on stream. We should maybe I could do that this week.
It's worth a shot. It's worth a shot. Even though my new internet seems a little weird it might work.
We got my Steam library.
Mm.
Cyclonials.
Yeah visual novels definitely a bad idea. You know what game I think I want to.
I think I want to try Inscription. Have you ever seen that one? I've seen a few GIFs. I've seen
a few clips. I've heard a little bit about it and I've had it recommended to me enough that I feel
like I should should give it a shot just to see. I've what I've heard is like confusing because
people say oh I don't want to spoil you about inscription. Yeah and I look at it and it's a
card game and I'm like okay so it's a card game with something that's hidden. It's about it because
you don't want to tell me. I know that it's a card game but it's a card game that you're playing
diegetically in a place and so I'm assuming that some stuff in the game happens in response
to how you play the game. Like if it's like Jumanji you play the snake and then there's snakes in
the room maybe. It looks like you're in a place and you have an opponent and the opponent is a
character. Yeah that doesn't seem so wacky though. I don't know why people would like so like oh
I don't want to spoil you. It's so good. I don't get it. What on earth could it possibly be? It's
a card game. Well I don't know but I've heard enough people have told it to me and I've looked
at it and been like what's going on here that I think I'm like I should check it out because like
I'm honestly I'm not I'm not drawn in by the promises like the vague promises of oh dude you've
got to try it but I can't tell you a dang thing about it. I'm like well I don't when I hear that
enough eventually I get curious. What I do is I try to think what it could possibly be
and I don't I I'm not impressing myself with my imagination so I'm not interested in actually
playing it. I could be totally off base. I'm imagining some kind of like some kind of like
portal style reveal where like it turns out that like instead of like continuing the test chambers
you have to like break out of the testing area and go into like you know some kind of secret
side room where you use what you learned in like a sort of subversive way. Yeah I just feel like
that's pretty good. Like that's not going to blow my mind or anything. I think the thing that I
think for me is that I don't like card games but they annoy me. So like saying it's a card game is
not enough. I guess I'm neutral about card I neither like nor dislike card games so I'm
that's kind of a wash for me. I think it's Hearthstone that made me hate card games just because
the idea of having a deck and then pulling a new card out and it being not the card you need
it's just sort of like well fuck me then. Well how am I supposed to win? Well what turns me off
about like card games is that you have to like buy and assemble your deck but like yeah I don't
like that. That's the part that I hate but like inscription is like you know you have your cards
the game gives them to you. So imagine if chess was a game like that we had to buy like booster
packs of chess pieces until you had a full set. Yeah yeah it's ass it would be it would be ass is what
it would be. No I can't I can't I want to give it a shot. I don't know if I'll have time this week.
Anything else? Wait how much is inscription? Let me find out. Let me find out real quick.
One billion rubles. That's right it is 20 dollars. Oh fuck. I can't oh you think I made a money?
If it were on sale though. If it were on sale I would I would probably buy it immediately.
I want it. I just don't want to pay full pay full price for it. That's all that's all I'm saying.
Um you have anything else you want to talk about before we wrap up for the day?
Just want to reiterate the thing with the 29th of October at the place that I said where it's at
the Bohemia in North Finchley. Check out that link the image for Parkinson's. Show it on screen.
Show it on screen again. It's the zone. It's my dad's band. It used to be called Dad Zone.
It's changed its name. Was it named after your dad? No it was like it was they met at like my old
school my old primary school. They were a bunch of dads and they were like hey we all play instruments
let's form a band. Let's call it Dad Zone. Like Kid Zone but we're dads. Why did they change the
name? I'm curious. Did they think it was just more appealing to a general audience if they didn't?
I guess so. I don't know. I don't know the reasoning. Less alienating for non-dads.
Yeah I mean whatever. I kind of liked Dad Zone but. Our music is by dads but it's not just for
dads. It's for everyone. Yeah although it is a lot of dad rock. Sure. Yeah Dad Zone is more I mean
it's funny. It makes me chuckle. Maybe that's the thing. It was too funny. It has to be very serious.
Very serious business. But yeah Saturday 29th of October if you can make it it's like 12 pounds
donation to get in to the charity and you can just donate if you want to donate to the charity
if you can't make it and that'll be great. What would you do if like a couple of PCP fans showed up?
If they came up to me like after the show or something I'd say hi. The fact that they came all
the way over and like you know paid to get in. That would be nice. That would be that would be
remarkable. Sounds like a good time. I'm excited to hear how it goes. Yeah. Yeah well I got I got
nothing else so I guess we're gonna let's call it there. Another successful podcast. Patreon.com
slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes 50 something of them. Send us a voicemail. Send us
a real voicemail to speak up.com slash PCB voicemail to drown out all these fake ones that don't have
any content that are just a waste of time. Come on guys these these voicemails where you're not
saying anything you're coughing. It sucks. I'm just I'm just gonna I think from now on I'm just
gonna tell Eleazar like yeah cut out those and like we won't mention them anymore because like
what a fucking waste of time. LeMau. All right but bye. Bye everybody. See you next week.