I'm sorry darling, I'm listening to the PCP right now, it's so addicting.
Ho ho ho, Merry Christmas.
Uh, soon, in like a couple days, hey, it's the PCP. We're here to, you know, say some
things about the various events. Uh, I'm Hippocrit, and with us we have Digibro.
Yo, yo, I'm a GameCube, trying to spread holiday cheer through some holiday fear.
Not gonna question how that works. And we have Nate with us.
Um, yeah. Best Nate ever.
It's, uh, it's just one of those ones, you know, just one of those fucking ones.
And least, we have Tom.
I have nothing to say because I'm so small and insignificant, except play my fucking game
that I made with my own blood, sweat, and tears, follow development, it's great.
Uh, it's gonna be, it's gonna be a GameCube launch title for sure, confirmed, check it out.
Dude, let's, let's talk about that just a little bit because, uh, recently I noticed
that four of the PCP, myself, Davoo, Tom, and, uh, well, Ben and Munchy together have
like technically made video games this year, uh, and I made a Twitter poll and it was cool.
It was just like, yeah, Game of the Year, but for us, we're all game devs now.
We do cool stuff.
So who won the poll?
I think it was Endless War.
Endless War did win the poll.
I gotta admit, I voted, I voted for Autonomous.
Autonomous was really nice.
Autonomous was fucking sick and was a game I would actually love to play.
Whereas Endless War is mean and they bully me and it's hard, so I, so I gotta say,
I haven't, I haven't found time to play Autonomous yet, but I did watch a little bit
of Ben's stream of it and I couldn't keep watching it because when I read the text,
I could hear Davoo's voice saying every single line in my head
and the way Ben was reading it was not satisfactory enough of a representation of that for me.
So I was like, I can't listen to Ben read this.
I have to go read this myself.
Fair enough.
Davoo needs to do a let's read of his own game.
I don't even need it.
I can literally hear him saying it.
Like every line is something he would say in a way he would say it.
So it's, it's somebody who lived with them for a while.
It's like trippy to play this fucking game.
So I guess go play it if you want to like have the experience of Davoo's voice in your mind.
Great.
It's a great, it's a super fun game and it's just, it's so chill and like relaxing kind of
because there's not a lot that goes on it.
It's just like walking around an environment and examining things,
but like it's such, it's such a very common interaction in games given center stage
and it's like really refreshing and it's got good sense of humor
and the art style is nice and clean and it's great.
I love it.
And it's a common interaction in games given center stage.
Is that like the descriptor?
That's just what he said and I thought it was really nice.
Shit.
So Davoo's, Davoo's off doing bug fixes, which has been keeping him busy for a while now,
but God damn it.
I like, this is funny.
Like I want Davoo to, to take a pause from doing things that actually matter,
making a real game, to come on this worthless meme podcast,
to talk with me so I can get a piece of the glory that he's produced
by telling him how much I fucking loved that game
and so I can hear his sick developer commentary.
That game was awesome.
Yeah.
We gotta suck his dick hard.
I can't say, I don't think it's going to be easy to get a hold of such a busy game designer.
A pro.
He, he was, he did, I, he's editing my video and I didn't hear from him for about 13 days
into the month.
This is what happens.
Oh, I'm working on the video, by the way.
We're all procrastinators right now, but Davoo has finally hit level 16 and has evolved
into a professional.
There it is.
He doesn't have time for this anymore.
Yeah.
I was going to say that.
Is that when we become next to the professionals?
Yeah.
That's when the podcast ends.
When we're finally doing real shit, we'll be the professionals.
Then we get to make up our own definition of what a professional is.
Yeah.
That's, yeah.
That's true.
Shit.
Speaking of something about game developer reminded me, you guys hear about fucking today,
the super best friends deleted.
It's gone.
They are ending their show.
They made a video saying, yeah, this is the finale of super best friends and the three
people.
Because they're not friends anymore.
At least one of them.
At least.
The woolly guy and Matt Pat and Pat Matt said, you know what?
I'm done.
And they were all like in different rooms.
So yeah.
Yeah.
I never really watched them, but they've been around for a long time.
They're an institution, man.
I'm kind of surprised they were still around.
Because I feel like you can't keep, most two guys doing a let's play kind of shows, you
know, eventually someone gets fucking tired of it or moves on.
Yeah.
They were doing it for a long fucking time.
Nine years.
Apparently the channel was around.
God damn.
Yeah.
It was that long.
It's, I mean, I was, this is not, like, I'm not trying to be snot or anything.
Yeah.
I was never like a fan or dedicatedly watched their content.
But just like going to V today and seeing all the threads about people being sad.
And like then the Janney, lol, Janney cleaning up my threads.
Clean it up, Janney, you get paid nothing.
Sorry, my inner Janney rage just came out for a second there.
And like just people being sad about it ending and then like mods deleting the threads and
then people making new threads saying janitors are literally cleaning up the most relevant
games news today, which is the end of the super best friends podcast and let's play
show.
And I don't know, it's just interesting.
That's a good point from those guys.
And I got to say, and this is 100% out of my own personal bitterness and resentment.
Yeah.
That they can't talk about me on a because they talk about extremely anti-e celebrity.
Like even more than V even more than more than anything.
Like I get talked about way more on V or on.
Yeah.
I get talked about most on V because of the fact that they can't talk about me on a because
it will get deleted immediately.
Like even if a thread, the longest threads that have ever existed about me about on a
are ones that became about me.
And usually the highest risk for that is in the three by three threads because my three
by threes get posted as a meme in there.
Literally every thread.
I don't know who does it, but someone is very dedicated.
So like I see that, but like nowadays it doesn't.
Barney fag is still put.
Are you familiar with the legend of Barney fag?
No.
To this day.
Just whenever in any way there is actually he's actually tapered off a little bit, but
for years, for years and years and years, every single time that someone would post
an image like a like you'd post like ponies.
He would say kill yourself Barney fag and post a little screen, a little screencap that
what it shows the airing dates of like my little pony airs that immediately afterward
like is Barney on like the Disney Channel or something or I might be flipped.
But like the point was like this is you.
Like this is who you are.
Fan of MLP.
But the thing was this got to such an incredible degree, such an incredible heights where any
like you'd see like human like a sunset glimmer, whatever the fuck her name was.
And like, okay, sure, she's kind of pony-esque.
So he would reply to that and be like, ah, kill yourself Barney fag.
Okay, that one's a little bit easier.
Even though it's not literally a pony, then it would be like obscure fan art that kind
like his interpretations of characters.
He would still be there.
Kill yourself Barney Barney fag every single time he would know.
And then it would be it got to such a level where the absolutely like tiny little cropped
portions of vaguely my little pony relevant content still immediately Barney fag would
be there knowing exactly what it was and would be able to pinpoint how this was MLP related.
So really, he's clearly like the biggest MLP fag that there ever was, but he just he
chooses to use his powers to, you know, punish those.
Isn't it more likely that every my little pony fan on that website has the copypasta
and do it on site.
No, no, don't ruin the mythos for me, man.
I was getting infested in this narrative and you've ruined it for me with it cold.
Well, I choose to believe he's one.
Even though it would be impressive if people could tell that quickly, you know, like it
tells you how many bronies are still around on these fucking sites.
That's true.
And the sad thing is that like these days, you'll see a thread where like someone will
post, you know, one of these like crops and people know and they're like, wait for it,
wait for it.
But but Barney fag never shows up and everyone's like, where's Barney fag?
We've been waiting like this thread's gone to like 500.
That means it has to be one person.
If it was a bunch of people, somebody would have hopped on the bandwagon, but it had to
be one guy, one star hero.
Maybe people only do it if they can get it first.
Like if they don't get it in time for somebody else to respond, they're just like, well, it's
not.
There's no credit.
It's like in the Dark Knight Rises where Batman is like retired and everyone just waiting
for him to come back, but he hasn't yet.
We're all waiting for Barney to make his triumphant return.
We need we need Catwoman to come in and steal his shit and kick him off his cane and get
back into shape.
It's going to happen.
Exactly like that.
And there's also the hero, Final Fantasy XV Koon, who is the biggest child like defense
force for any criticism of Final Fantasy XV.
It's such a degree where he's like a mythological creature where any defense of Final Fantasy
XV will be attributed to a post by Final Fantasy XV Koon.
I don't know.
It's there's a lot of great characters.
God, great lore.
I should make videos about these honestly.
These are fascinating.
Well, the only problem with that is that they would shit on you for being a trip fag, basically.
You'd have to do it on a channel that had no identifiers at all.
Yeah.
Well, I don't mean I'd like go fucking post like that.
You know that guy Wang, you know, that guy Wang who's been rising up in YouTube recently,
like posts.
Well, he makes videos about like internet lore, basically.
And it's like, I don't know.
I kind of similar to what fit MC does, I guess, where he like only fits focus is more narrow,
but like every YouTuber, like hundreds of thousands of thousands of YouTubers.
This guy specifically, his show is called Tales from the Internet.
Tales gets trolled.
You know what?
Let's move on.
They get the idea.
Digi, I've been rewatching Digi Bros. Let's Plays.
Oh my God.
I've been rewatching from the beginning.
Sonic Adventure 2 is legitimately really, really good, especially at the end of the hero play through.
I remember having always thought that they got better as they went,
but they do become more podcasty as they go.
They get like the Sonic Adventure 2 starts off pretty funny and it gets funnier around the middle
and it sort of mellows out, but then it gets really funny by the end.
It's a good Let's Play and it just reminds me of that time when, you know,
Game Grumps Dan was new and they were doing Wind Waker and it's like, whoa, nice.
This is Game Grumps-esque content that I can return to,
that I haven't rewatched a million times already.
I mean, that's kind of the reason.
It's really funny.
I'm like ass out on Let's Plays lately.
I used to watch so much of them and I realized how important they are to me
because I can just eat and have something to watch that is, you know,
just barely not mind-numbing enough to keep my attention for 40 minutes or so.
So like, right now, Vic and Hope have finally returned to start making Let's Plays again
and they're like slightly too boring because Victor plays fucking Breath of the Wild
and it's really not fun to watch.
I heard you talking about that, but sometimes they come in hot with their hot takes.
Sometimes they come in hot with some hot takes on the PCV, which is fine.
Did you hear all of those? Did you hear their hot take and my response?
The first thing I heard about it was your response to it,
but it sounds like Vic was getting pretty peeved at us for a while.
It was pretty funny. I listened to it.
You were deeply accused of like, why are you making Dozlocks and not doing We Agua?
You got roasted pretty hard.
What? I made my fucking Smash meme videos. Those were big. Come on.
I thought that those were a better idea than me and Maff of a person.
But you know what? I'll give them the credit.
I do need to be doing We Agua, so I'm totally with them on that.
Fair criticism. Fair criticism.
Anyway, I'm going to fight you one-on-one, Vic. I'm coming to your house.
I felt like a dearth of Let's Plays and it's funny because there was a time
where there were so many of them that they were competing for your attention
and it was like, when I first started mine, a lot of the people who initially were watching it,
as we kicked up the production cycle, there were a lot of people who were like,
I already watched Game Grumps. I don't have time for this on top of that, you know?
Yeah.
And then I think as a lot of people lost interest in Game Grumps,
like me, they turned to like, Monkey's Gaming Expedition.
Back when that was super at peace.
And then like, that stopped being entertaining.
So it's like, well, where do I go from here?
And then now there's like, there's nobody really doing those Let's Plays anymore
because nobody got big doing it.
Like, no matter how good your Let's Plays are, nobody is going to be the next Game Grumps
because just frankly, there's just not enough time in any viewer's day
to watch like 100 Let's Players.
And I used to know a lot of people who would say like,
oh, I've got like 200 subs, but most of it's Let's Plays I don't watch, you know?
Like, as in some people they are subscribed to.
So yeah, like, I think that Let's Plays have just quietly been dying
because of the fact that nobody's...
Market saturation?
Yeah, market saturation, which was already going on.
And we all knew that.
But like, I think everybody hoped that if they just did it long enough
at a certain level of quality, more people would pay attention.
And it's like, usually they hit a certain number of your fans
who will watch you play a video game and they stop there.
You know, nobody knew comes in.
It's like, how many people who watch Digibro After Dark
are going to watch me play...
You know, are going to watch me commentate over Pokemon Colosseum
while Mei plays it.
Exactly 2.2 thousand.
That is the view count on every video, you know?
So it's like, because nobody's blown up through it,
it's just like, well, I like doing it,
but it takes time out of my day.
And eventually everyone becomes way slower at it.
And then I'm sitting here eating my food and being like, wait a minute,
I needed those Let's Plays.
I needed there to be like 40 minutes out of every day
that I could spend watching really mindless content
and I don't want to watch another Needledrop review.
Because I don't give a shit about most of these ads.
Everybody also, there's like, streaming can get you big
and it's also a lot easier.
And donations are like instant advice,
so it's like more monetarily good.
So everybody kind of just realized that that's better as like a creator.
But it's not the same sort of thing.
You can actually put on an episode of Part of a Stream.
That's true. You can watch the back stuff.
I mean, you don't want to sit there for like three hours and be like,
okay, well, I'll pause it and come back tomorrow.
I don't know.
I mean, on the creative side, a Let's Play is difficult
because you have to constantly find things to talk about
or else you get boring.
And like, Back When Me and Victor did Digi Bros.
for the longest time, it was like, we just had an endless wellspring
of anything we could possibly think of to talk about.
At some point, we started running low, so we started asking the audience for questions.
So then we're doing like Q&A and we're giving extremely long answers to questions
just to fill up as much time as possible.
Well, you run out of questions and then it's like,
well, I guess we got to like do things now and have experiences
to have new things to talk about.
And when it came to that point, it's like, we can't do this show twice daily anymore.
It became like, well, we're going to make it, you know,
we have to record less often so that we have more to say.
And now like when me and May do our Let's Plays,
it's basically just like when we have a topic,
when we're like, oh man, I have something I want to talk about on a Let's Play,
then we sit down and record a Let's Play as opposed to, you know,
being forced to come up with new ideas every day,
which I think if that was all you did with your career would be one thing.
But like, I think that as soon as you try to do something else at the same time,
like obviously the quality of the Let's Play is going to diminish.
It's like, you're not going to have time to sit around
and think of the best possible topics to talk about on your Let's Play show
if you're doing a main show, you know, on top of your Let's Play.
I'm sure that's true.
Consistency is the death of me and I'm dead.
Oh, Victor put out my apology to the PCP episode.
Did he really?
Oh, God.
I have to apologize, Victor.
It's fine.
I'll have to listen to that.
That'll be funny though.
I mean, if you haven't heard his episode, Nate, you...
I have not.
Because you might...
Is he actually mean?
Is he actually bullies me?
He's pretty fucking harsh.
Like, on every...
Victor, why?
No, but it's...
He's harsh, but like, it's always about Victor,
the way that he's like, you can hear how much he's smiling at all times.
So he doesn't really...
Yeah.
He doesn't really like have like a vileness to it,
but it's like, he gets real.
He lays all the cards on the table.
You know what?
He literally says like, I'm calling you out, guys.
Yeah.
You guys don't do anything.
I bet there's a lot of truth in what he says.
I bet there's a lot of truth.
There's a lot of truth in it,
but he also just like misinterprets a lot of things
about like what everyone is up to, you know?
Man, I make no defense for myself.
I mean, if people think that I'm wasting my time
and focusing on bullshit, I want to know that
so I can fucking, you know, get back to shit.
Well, yeah.
I mean, there's one thing to like agree with, you know,
the way you come across is your fault at some point.
There's also like, you know when you're doing something
and if people don't, you know, believe that you are
and you tell them or like, you know,
you don't have to keep like a 24 hour,
like I'm doing exactly this.
I'm working exactly this much guys to keep them informed.
Like people are going to think things
that are kind of incorrect.
Yeah.
I'll tell you though, because I, Victor responded
in a comment to my response video
and he said of Nate's trajectory that he was like,
he said, I do watch everything.
He was like, I watch everything everyone in the PCP does.
I watch all of Tom's dev logs even,
which I was like, Jesus Christ,
you must have more time than I fucking realized.
I'm so sorry.
But like, he said that he thinks
that Viagra is more like the type of content
that like endears people to a creator,
whereas to smash videos are going to be bringing in
a crowd who doesn't really know about you on a personal level.
But like, I don't think that's totally true.
I don't think your videos are that impersonal though.
Like the smash videos are such a distinctive editing style
that like, if you see that thumbnail
and it looks like the thumbnail you saw last time,
you know what you're going to get.
And actually people have started to emulate.
There's been several like copycat videos
that people have made clearly.
Yeah, whatever, Tom, what were you saying?
I think what Victor's trying to say,
and I totally agree with, is that like
Viagra is like about Nate and Nate's on camera.
Like you build that personal relationship with the person
and that's going to get you to subscribe more than like,
I like smash, here's a smash video.
The smash videos are going to get views.
The Viagra's are going to get subscribers.
I mean, with every smash video,
because they're like music videos inherently,
I make no money from them.
You know, except for what like patrons give me and stuff obviously.
So like, okay, so they get a lot of views.
Does that translate to success, to like earnings and like a stable,
you know, like are they paying for themselves,
especially considering how long they take to make.
Doesn't really seem like they are.
So I basically just did it because I fucking wanted to
and I did and they're great and I'll probably do more.
But I mean, yeah, these are all relevant questions to think about.
So I get it. It seems reasonable to me.
I just feel like with Viagra,
it's so dependent on the independent,
the individual subject matter to carry,
whether this video is going to get views or not.
It's like Viagra is not going to get over 100,000 views ever
if it's not talking about something that could get that amount, you know?
That's definitely true.
Unless you were a much bigger YouTuber.
But you know, on the other hand, it's also, it's good for me
to have Viagra to force me to keep making stuff.
So I, you know, like an object in motion stays in motion.
Just to have that momentum, I think is a very good thing,
which is why I wanted that.
And I'm sorry everybody to keep you waiting for the next one.
It is in the editing bay, should be out soon.
But you know, it's, it's one of my other favorite things to watch
while I eat a fucking sandwich.
Hooray! By the time you're hearing this, it should be out.
Thanks.
Hooray for you people.
I'll be sure to send you an angry tweet if it's not the case.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
Speaking of growing a channel,
Monkey's channel's all got destroyed.
No, they're gone.
Let's talk about that shit.
Jesus Christ.
So, so in case people aren't aware, which you probably are,
our boy, Monkey Jones, had his two main channels deleted
for a whole bunch of copyright strike reasons.
And then when he tried to set up his backup jokes.
Well, I think they were community guidelines strikes,
but I can't, maybe I'm wrong.
I think you're right.
Yeah.
They was like content they don't want, that kind of stuff.
Hate speech, I think it was.
Like Elliot Roger is like now a dirty word.
You can't say it.
Basically, yeah.
And then when he tried to make his gaming expedition channel
that hosted all his precious, precious Nuzlocs
into his main channel,
like the whole channel just got taken down.
I don't know exactly how, like what the strikes were on that.
Yeah, he seems to have been blacklisted.
Apparently he was removed from Hornhub as well.
He was removed from, are you serious?
What the fuck?
He was removed from Hornhub.
I heard that.
Are you really?
What?
How is that even possible?
That's a fucking, that's a, wow.
I am shocked if that's true.
I got to go check this channel right now.
I mean, all right.
Maybe that's because one of his patron tears, I think,
was like, if he gets this much per month,
he'll put all of his Elliot Roger videos on Hornhub.
Yeah.
That's like a funny joke.
Maybe that potentially,
Hornhub was like, this isn't porn,
and they got rid of him for that reason.
But I just can't, I can't imagine Hornhub
being like in league with, you know,
people who blacklist things.
He said on Twitter,
Hornhub deleted two of my Elliot Roger videos last night.
So, yeah, I guess they just deleted it
for being the Elliot Roger videos.
Probably, yeah.
I mean, where in this wide world
can you go to watch a dark comedy video?
I just want to put it out there, people.
We've had our differences.
I 100% stand with Monkey on this issue.
There is no debate that this is fucked up.
No, I don't know if I do,
because I think this is the least surprising event
in YouTube history.
Monkey's channel's already been deleted
like three times before.
Like, obviously, the type of content he's making,
I mean, it is in breach of YouTube's guidelines.
Like, it's not as though this is like...
That's questionable.
How so?
Make your case.
I'm curious to hear it.
Well, first of all, he's shown,
I mean, the videos that got him taken down
the first couple of times
was because he showed, like,
explicit sexual content from Boku No Pico.
Oh, right, right, yeah.
This time, he's got videos that are, like,
essentially encouraging suicide,
and like, well, hang on, hang on.
I don't know if that's true.
You know, I heard YouTube say in one of their tweets,
the team YouTube, whatever,
they said that, like, they don't allow content
that glorifies or encourages violence.
And, like, okay, I've always thought that
I understand the case that making, like,
basically comedy parody videos about Elliot Rogers,
I understand the case that that is glorifying it
in the sense that it's, like, spreading notoriety,
kind of, it's making it into a thing.
Maybe this is just me being an idiot,
but, like, wouldn't the entirety of YouTube gaming
be glorifying violence in that case?
Like, if you're just playing Call of Duty,
and it's just, like, fucking murder simulator
all day, every day.
Sure, you can make that argument.
It's just, YouTube's terms are always so fucking vague,
and it's just, it's totally arbitrary
when they decide to pull in what they don't.
Okay, well, Digi, you're right.
I agree with you, Digi.
There's definitely a case to be made
that this violates content policy.
My response to that is only,
I don't believe that that is a good policy.
I agree with that, but, like, that is...
It's just that we've been on YouTube this whole time
under the assumption we were working under this policy.
Like, I don't...
There's a lot of shit that I don't put into my videos
because I'm afraid of getting kicked off of YouTube,
you know?
Like, I don't throw in jokes and stuff that I think of
that I would like to be in there,
but I think, oh, this will get me kicked off of YouTube
or this will get this video blocked,
because I've had my channel taken down several times,
including for community guidelines reasons, you know?
I lost my Ask Princess Malestia video back in 2014.
That was more innocent than anything monkey's ever done, you know?
Yeah, that's ridiculous.
So, like, to me, it's just like, I'm...
Like, I...
Yeah, it sucks that he lost his channel,
but, like, this is the least surprising event in history,
and he's made, like, he's, like,
tripled his Patreon earnings as a result of this.
Right, yeah.
So all he has to do is switch this shit on Google Drive
and he'll be fucking fine.
Well, that's the plan as far as I know.
Or if not Drive the fucking bitchude.
That they were...
He was making his own website.
Like, that's gonna be the new place.
Well, guys, I mean, we all know this is a terrible punishment.
Like, the question of discovery alone,
like, monkey was growing quite rapidly on YouTube,
and to cut off his future like this,
I mean, that's the real punishment.
Yeah.
Even if in the short term, he's gained...
Yeah, I mean, it definitely sucks.
It's one of those things.
The short term is gonna be fine,
because Patreon explodes, but, like...
For now.
Yeah, it's...
I mean, Monkey seems like somebody that the new clean Patreon would not want, right?
Guys, let's also be real about something for a second here, though,
because on the one hand, yes, it's a huge loss to lose your YouTube channel,
because the YouTube is easy growth,
which is why we all use it.
It's a platform that when you know how to turn the wheels on it,
you can grow pretty easily.
However, we are also living in an internet age
where it's even more interconnected.
Most people are in communities.
They're in discords.
They're on Reddit.
They're all over the place.
And, like, Monkey's heavily connected with the Dick Show.
The Dick Show is the ones who are putting up his website.
Like, Dick and his girlfriend, I guess,
are helping him to get his website launched.
Dick is a guy who...
His YouTube presence is basically non-existent.
He is just famous for having a podcast that has its own website.
He got all his fans back through Twitter, you know,
and now he's like the biggest Patreon,
one of the biggest Patreons out there.
Monkey's Patreon just triplicated.
He is gonna have his own website.
Anybody who's willing to go over there to watch him, you know.
And the only reason that this wouldn't work out for him
is if his content couldn't stand up to that medium,
if people were not willing to go seek it out.
I didn't really, like, bring this up just because, like,
he will be all right.
It's more like the idea of it is very unsettling
because, you know, the line is constantly shifting
a little bit towards, you know, banning things.
More censorship and shit, yeah.
Banning channels, like, in a blink of an eye,
like, whereas before you would have gotten a strike.
I'm way more worried about how Sargon lost his Patreon
than I am about serving.
Like, Monkey losing his channel?
Not a surprise because it's been, again,
it's been taken out from community guidelines before.
Like, I'm not shocked to hear, I'm not like,
oh, wow, censorship's gone even worse
when I hear that Monkey gets deleted.
When I hear that Sargon got removed from Patreon
for saying nigger on someone else's podcast,
I'm like, uh-oh, I've done that before.
You did that just now.
Granted, he did it in a way that they deemed to be,
like, racially insensitive.
But I mean, even a lot of people have argued
that in the context it might not have been.
It was definitely dumb the way he fucking phrased it
one way or another.
Well, okay, just so that you aren't misinterpreted,
did you here?
So it isn't thought that you are unsympathetic here.
You can separate the two issues.
On the one hand, there have been objective setbacks
in the real world.
Will Monkey be able to make up and, you know,
survive and grow from here?
Hopefully, probably, I don't know.
I gotta hope so.
But on the other hand, there's just the fact
that no one wants him to have had
to have dealt with this shit.
Even if just for the fact that things are getting closer
and closer to the fact where I'm gonna face
some fucking issues like this.
And I just want that line to stay way away from me.
Just protect every fucking buddy
who's even, like, a bit closer to being an edgy boy.
So on the one hand, will Monkey survive?
Hopefully.
But maybe not.
Maybe not.
But on the other hand, just a separate issue.
I don't like that this was done.
I know it's within their terms of service,
but I don't like the terms of service.
I guess what I mean to say, the reason I keep saying
that I'm not surprised is that I've already been
under the mindset that this is what YouTube does
this whole time.
This is what they do.
They just kill people.
This isn't surprising.
It's just disappointing.
And it's like, I've spent this whole time hoping
we can find a way to get off YouTube.
And the way I've seen it is that the only way
it's going to happen is when they finally ban
enough high-profile people that those people
can't rely on YouTube anymore.
Because the only reason any of us are here
is that we rely on the platform.
No one likes the platform, but we need it.
It's the easiest way to make money
and it's the easiest way to have growth.
But any of us could survive without the platform
as long as we worked really hard
and played our cards right.
And just created something that exists on its own
that doesn't rely on YouTube.
I mean, I would hope so.
But honestly, the biggest feature YouTube has
is the discovery and the way that that's where everybody is.
And without that, I mean, I don't know
that we could recover an audience if we lost it.
I think we could.
I don't know how.
I don't think it's as hard as people think.
I think that, I mean, first of all,
a lot of people have heard of us already.
So it's like, it's not difficult to introduce
the idea of yourself back into the world
as long as you are a part of a lot of communities
and you are somebody who gets the word out
about what happened and where you can be found now.
But, dude, that's the thing, though.
Like, fucking, like, Monkeys had his Twitter deleted
a bunch and like, sure, okay,
Twitter has the right to delete accounts they don't want.
Okay, I get it.
And he's made like a bunch of Twitters
and he's got one that's technically alive right now.
I guess I won't say it,
just so they can't fucking track it down.
But, like, they're really squeezed in that guy.
They're really trying to, like, erase him.
And I know these are technically independent things,
but you can just see the machinery at work
just saying this person makes content
that's unacceptable for the new world
that we're trying to make here.
I know that, because the thing is that, like,
the reason I say it's, I think it's always been this way.
It's like, this is exactly what happened to Dick Masterson.
Like, he was kicked off of, like,
dozens of hosting sites for men are better than women.
He was constantly sent angry letters.
He was, like, demonized on the internet.
He was banned from YouTube, like, early into YouTube,
not just his channel ban.
He himself, as a human being,
was blacklisted from posting to YouTube.
And it's just kind of like a,
it's just been long enough that I guess
they don't care enough to find out
he has a channel on there now for his show.
But, like, that's why when they did
the biggest problem in the Universal Live show,
he went under his real name,
because Dick Masterson was technically banned
and Maddox gave a shit about that, for some reason.
But, yeah, like, so, you know,
it can happen even with a more innocent satire,
even a more obvious satire than what Mumki is doing
on a scale that even exceeds
not only was he blacklisted from YouTube,
but also from, like, tons of, of, you know,
what's the fucking servers and shit.
So, like, you know, I know this can happen to people
and it always has been happening to people
and the way you get around it
is by not relying on those platforms.
It's like, if you are, if you are good enough,
you should be good enough to survive
without needing the platform to promote you.
You know, it shouldn't be that you are entirely
relying on that for people to care about you,
because that means that whatever you're doing
is not good enough.
And, like, I think Mumki'll be fine in this regard,
because, like, when you look at people who are,
who are really, who would really be in danger from that,
it's the people whose patreons don't succeed.
Like, someone like Dame Drops, the YouTube food reviewer,
who had, like, he put out, like, four videos a week.
He got decent views.
He had the, oh, my damn song made about him
and that blew him up initially.
And, like, even though he got pretty good views,
when he tried to open a Patreon, it made nothing.
Because, like, his content was just kind of vapid.
Like, it wasn't, it didn't, it was just, like,
hey, I want to watch a guy review fast food for three minutes
a couple times a week, because why not?
Nobody was, like, invested, you know?
And it's, like, it's a lot different for someone like Mumki Jones,
who has this overarching narrative,
who has all this drama and baggage,
who communicates with his fans a lot, you know?
Like, I'm sure that Twitter or no Twitter,
he's got a Discord somewhere that's probably got
a few hundred people in it, you know?
Like, even if I lost my, if I lost all my social media platforms,
I at least have my Discord,
which has, like, 400 people in it, you know?
So, like...
Until Discord decides that you're too toxic for there
and Twitter decides you're too toxic.
I guess we can cross that bridge when we come to it.
Yeah.
It's easy to learn fear of, like,
oh, oh, I can't say words anymore.
Because it's not entirely true,
but it is becoming truer in certain places.
We're gonna get back to a podcast to me,
and Digi did, like, fucking two years ago
about RSS and email,
about how, like, at least those things were, like,
hardcore in your control, and they couldn't take it away from you.
Guys, I've found an even better way.
Um, because just last month...
Is it Web 3.0?
No, even better than that.
Just last month, and now again this month,
the highest tier of my Patreon is a $40 care package,
where I mail people a USB stick full of exclusive content.
I like that. I like that.
So what I've been doing is I've been doing, like,
just full commentaries over movies,
and, like, just, like, having background music playing
in my vlogs, and just, like,
because they can't copyright strike me.
It's on fucking USB stick.
Hang on.
I have a question about that.
I thought about this myself a little bit.
Is it not theoretically possible that, like,
so the whole, it's not like that YouTube just, like,
came up with copyright shit out of nowhere.
That's fucking copyright claims, stuff out of nowhere.
It's specifically that they're trying to avoid copyright infringement,
which is a legal thing.
If you're actually selling content, you know,
in this way via Patreon, that uses copyrighted material,
you are still in violation of that.
You're technically illegal to do what you're doing.
I mean, the extent they would have to go to,
to even find out what content I have on these flash drives
that I'm sending to people, because there's only 10.
So, like, you'd have to get ahold of one.
All right.
You know, find somebody who will tell you what's on there.
Check it.
And then even then, I could make a fair use argument
for a lot of it, because it is common.
Yeah, it's a fair use.
Because, like, the reason that YouTube content ideas
is so terrible is because the robot doesn't know
how to understand fair use, and it doesn't care,
and YouTube doesn't care to make it understand.
So, that's always the problem.
It's hard.
You just can't use it in any way, even if it's fair.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know what, there's something to that.
Like, fucking Red Letter Media sells their, you know,
their, like, director's commentary shit over movies.
I think it's just a separate audio track or something,
but there's got to be something similar with that.
All I'm saying is consider that that's between 10 flash drives
at $40 a pop, and they sold out immediately.
That's $400 for whatever.
It's not bad.
You know, and not including the overhead,
because the overhead's like $100 in itself,
just a fucking, you know, well, not $100.
But, you know, there's a lot of buying flash drives
and mailing shit, depending on how many people are foreign.
And I charge people extra for that,
because after the last time, because it was like $10,
if you're out of the country in any way.
Sure, sure.
But, yeah, the, like, the, not with saying the overhead,
that's a lot of money to make off of a piece of content
that only 10 people are watching, you know?
That's true.
So, like, you really have to think creatively about,
like, where does your money come from,
what is your content worth, and who is it for, you know?
There might only be 10 people who would pay this amount of money
to get these things from me,
but, like, as long as those 10 people exist,
and as long as I can give them something
that is worth 40 bucks to them, you know,
which, for a lot of them, just the fact that they're receiving
a physical thing that has my name on it,
and, like, a little personalized piece of art is, like,
you know, worth something in itself.
So, yeah, I just think that this is the kind of way
that we can rethink the way we can release content
and monetize it.
I could not be more with you on the sentiment that, like,
we shouldn't rely on these platforms long-term,
and we should, it's our responsibility
to make sure that we can fucking survive,
you know, the storms to come, and the fireballs
that they're gonna throw at us.
I've been saying for a while that, like,
all these platforms should be a place for you
to advertise your content on top of just making it
and, like, drive it down a funnel
to, like, something you have more control over.
Diversify people.
Go to APSadventures.site to read Baaljeep
and other things.
Do it now before YouTube deletes us.
And, again, reminder that, for all of Mumki's
I've Lost Everything, like he said on Twitter,
again, tripled his Patreon,
has run successful Kickstarter,
has sold a book at, like, for hundreds of dollars,
you know, like, he has a ton of avenues he can explore.
I am not even...
I think he probably will have benefited more from this
than he loses out.
The amount that his Patreon spiked,
like, if he doesn't lose all those people quickly,
if he capitalizes on it by, let's say,
making a really epic, like, a real documentary
that uses all kinds of footage he couldn't show on YouTube,
maybe, you know, something a little edgier
than what he even could get away with before.
I'm sure he could keep those people.
Yeah, I mean, it's a time-tested term
that the best way to grow your YouTube channel
is to get unfairly deleted.
It's happened so many times to people,
though that's always been in the case
where they get it back eventually,
which could theoretically still happen
for what it's worth.
You have to milk it and be a crybaby for it to work.
Because I've had my channel taken away three times,
and it did nothing for me, because I didn't...
You need to make a campaign.
You need to make a thing happen where lots of people hear about it.
I mean, victimhood is the current social currency.
It is, like, or not.
You need to lift those sunglasses up and see the tears,
throwing the tears rolling down.
See the sharring guns I have beneath these shades.
Well, in any case, I feel deep sympathy,
and I hope things work out.
And I'm not gonna lie, I'm a little jealous.
Just when you get your channel deleted,
you just get so much love from the world.
I know I sound like an asshole,
but you really get a lot of attention and love.
People act like someone in your family died.
It erases many of your sins.
They don't matter anymore.
I'm just saying, this is why victimhood
is an extremely valuable thing.
That said, I totally...
The left got something right,
and it's being a victim.
It's very funny.
I laugh all the way to the bank.
By the way, so I have a...
So this isn't a story of deplatforming, per se,
but it's of deplatforming to come for me.
There was an event that happened over the last week,
or it might have been a little bit earlier,
and I might have forgot to mention last PCB,
but this actually is sort of a cataclysmic shift in my life,
in my professional life, specifically.
Oh, no.
And I'll share it with you now, ladies and gentlemen.
Okay, brace yourself for this.
So I'm at work.
I'm sitting at my desk,
and I'm just doing some shit.
It's like...
There was a luncheon that happened
that everybody at the company went to,
down the street, to a restaurant, or to go eat.
I just didn't want to go, because I'm like,
fuck it, I've got work to do.
And you made steamed hams.
I made steamed hams, yeah.
So I didn't go.
I was in my office at my desk,
and then I'm just working, just doing my thing,
and then all of a sudden,
somebody stops by my door, somebody looks in and says,
hey, Nate.
Hey, just so you know,
the president says that everybody can go home,
because it's like a party day.
Just yay, everybody can take the rest of the day off.
And I'm like, shit, dude, that's awesome.
I'ma do that.
And then he turns to leave.
And as he turns to leave, he pauses.
He pauses this young man.
He's like an intern at the company.
He turns around,
and he just says
five words that
will haunt me for the rest of my days.
And it's just, forget this one,
um, and then here they are.
Are you best guy ever?
Oh, no.
Yes, yes.
I've never spoken to this person before.
Just independently,
at work, one of the interns,
these damn college kids,
recognized me and knows who I am,
and is without a doubt,
spreading the word throughout the company.
And now that this is really
a crossing into a new era,
now that this is happening,
I have no idea how long
I can keep things under wraps
and, uh, and, you know, on the down low.
I told him like, yeah, that's me, man.
Do you, you know, you listen to the PCPs
like, no, I'm just, I watch your main channel
sometimes. It's, it's pretty funny.
I'm like, yeah, thanks.
Yeah, I like to keep that shit on the down low
here at work a little bit, you know.
So he was like, yeah, I heard you on calls
and I recognized your voice and I was like, that can't be.
But anyway,
this is, I'm sure that this is, uh,
this is getting around more
and people will be aware of my various activities
online. And I, it started
a doomsday clock as far as I'm concerned.
Uh, to one day
something will be unearthed
that's not so good that the people
aren't too fond of at work.
Uh, all they have to do is scroll back to
Lolly the Greatest Love of All
of my main channel and that might be,
that might be it right there, ladies and gentlemen.
What if you get fired because you don't upload
frequently?
Guys, I gotta,
I gotta interrupt because
apparently Victor's apology video
is like really, really
sad and at one point
there's a screen cap someone took where he put
text on screen that says, at this point
I just break down crying like a bitch
for like six minutes. I care
about the PCP a lot and they have been a big
positive part of my life for many years
and I feel closer to and care about
them more than any of my IRL friends.
Well.
I'm so, I'm so confused.
Victor, it's okay. It wasn't that serious, dude.
It's all right. It's all right.
Hashtag save Victor.
Go send him love. Go to vicanhope.com
I absolve you, Victor, of all
sense. We'll have to listen to this apology later.
I will definitely go listen to it later.
Uh, anyway.
What if Victor's playing all of us and he's like taking
our advice, he's already heard from his podcast
somehow already and went back into the past
and it's like, I'm going to play the victim card. I'm going to get all the money.
Oh, yeah. That's it. That's definitely it.
So, so on this subject
I just, this is more than ever.
The time the clock is accelerating
at rapid speed to depart from this land.
Dude, that is the most terrifying thing
that could possibly happen
on planet Earth. It was quite terrifying.
Uh, like, because there are
people at the company that like once
or twice I have discussed this stuff with
which I deeply regret and should not have done
but, uh, it's never like spread around.
But this is a guy I've never spoken to before
just independently. The only
like good thing to come from that
is like he doesn't watch the PCP
so he's watching PG-13 content
and not your NC-17
off the rails
talking with your psychotic friends.
Like, thank God because
that's not in the limelight yet
and you're still okay.
But who knows.
Who knows where it's going to go from here.
It's like, uh, sort of Damocles
is now in place.
Like the rope is getting thinner
and thinner by the day. It's splintering more.
It's going to drop. But, um,
I hate to tease everybody like this again
but like I'm just going to say again
looking over my finances, looking over
my future, the day draws
close when I'm at a place where I can
when I can do it, when I can make
this change. So, just saying.
Just saying.
Anyway, that was a big thing for me.
Oh, I've got another funny story.
No.
This is a small one. This is a small one.
Basically, so yes,
two days ago, my internet just died
and I didn't know what was going to happen
and I thought I was going to have to kill myself because I don't have internet.
But I was a big boy
called Cincinnati Bell
Cincinnati's best internet provider
and I just, I
talked to them like a big boy that Ham
having this issue. Can you guys help me?
And they said, not only can we help you
we're going to replace your router for free
but because
Yeah, that's right. Because
you are a two year loyal member
who as far as I know has literally never missed a payment
or even been late. We're going to
upgrade you from
50 megabytes per second
to 500 megabytes per second
and it's going to be cheaper.
It's going to be cheaper than what I was paying
before.
What the fuck?
Is it
literally because in this
age of millennial babies that you
are the only big boy you could ever
call in?
Probably. Probably.
This is the highest endorsement of capitalism I've ever heard
in my life. Exactly.
Like, honestly dude, I was
shocked to my core. But you know what, let me damper
this a little bit. I looked into it
and while we thought it was going to be less
it actually is $2
more out of like 64.
Now, I don't know if maybe there's like some shenanigans
that's going to be on the bill that's going to be less
but it looks like it was $2 more.
I mean, from 50 to 500, that's a pretty huge
10 times the speed.
I'm going to be
the greatest, I don't know, overwatch player
I'm going to be playing
Smash Online and having so many
gigabits per second. You can stream
Pokemon video games
in 4K. Yeah, exactly.
Get the pixels blown up to
big pixels.
You know, this is why capitalism
is the way the truth in the life, guys.
You know what's different from me to everybody else
that complains about this shit? They just
fuck up. They just fuck up
and they don't pay their fucking bills and they got
deadbeat ass jobs. They don't work hard
to improve at and become a fucking
manager and they don't go to school
and they don't tactically take out
debt in the interest of one day
paying it off in a timely
fashion and they also don't have really great parents
who will just help you and like absolve you of debt.
You're doing good for a while.
The point is
if what you pay into the system
you will be paid back most of the time
so fuck you
every socialist piece of shit out on the planet
I'm going to knock your block off.
Nate comes to all the Bernie Bros.
At once. I'm going to fight every
Bernie Bro on the planet because you know
they're at home, you know, fucking
jerking their dunk ding dong to
I don't know. I just imagined it's like
Smash 64 fighting
polygon team except it's fighting Bernie Bros
and just one Nate and smash them all
one after another.
That's exactly it.
Anyway, it was great
and what a wonderful time that was.
Although, you know, I checked my download speed
I don't think it's either ticked over yet. It's still like
54 megabytes per second or something.
I don't know if I'm getting mean. Disgusting.
I don't know if I need to like, if I need to wait.
If it was all a lie just to get you to stay with their service
then that's the capitalism I know. It's possible
it's possible. And by the way, I was very diligent
as you all should be two people and I was
asking like whoa whoa whoa. Now is this
upgrade going to like lock me in for like
a two year contract? Like what's
what's your angle here? But no, they were
very thorough. Nothing like that's
happening. You portray yourself in your own
stories. It's fucking hilarious.
Isn't it great? That's true.
Now
just one second here
it seems
that you're trying to dupe me
but I made the best
I'd like to think that is how you talk on the phone.
That's exactly how I do. You know I do
change how I talk on the phone versus
like as most people do.
I'm a very corporatized
person. It's the same as my work voice.
I've gotten a lot of shit for the way that I throw
my voice when I order food
at places because I always
say like yeah can I have a number
four? Like that
because it just makes your voice like pierce right
through that particular type of speaker
so that they will definitely fucking hear
you. Well it sounds like it's working.
I'm really good at like
figuring out how to
make a speaker or microphone
make the exact
loudest noise it can
make. Do you know what I mean?
It's called screaming. Well if you
sit there with like a megaphone for instance
if you scream into a megaphone you're not going to
get a very loud noise but if you put your
lips directly on it and you go like
it'll make a noise that is
just unbelievably shrill and
hear it throughout the whole fucking universe.
So you know it plays around
with your speakers. I'm now just imagining you in your house
with a megaphone. Just go like
Yeah. Well I used to use
a megaphone like
a toy megaphone very heavily
in my music. A lot of my old
shit. Oh yeah that blue fucking megaphone
thing. Yeah. Dude I
saw that in real life. Yeah
even before that I had the IMT
pain microphone which I would love to get another
of. It's a microphone
that you press a button and it makes you sound like
T-Pain when you sing it do it.
This is an app for your phone that does that too.
It's just like it's just any other toy
like megaphone thing. It's just shaped
like a microphone but like it when you
hold down the button it's sort of like auto-tunes
your voice a little bit. Oh you said it's called
the IMT pain microphone. Yes
IMT pain.
I think that was based on a phone app that
blew up really big back in like 2009
that would make sense. Well I
have a toy microphone of it and I used it on
like a hundred songs
and then it fucking broke.
Including
Diddy's most famous
I am a boat starring
Gigi Bro. I am a boat.
Yeah at first I was a GameCube
now I'm a boat.
Alright speaking of
music, speaking of like things
skills and various
abilities.
I've been on like one of those
distractoid mindsets recently
where I'm like oh you know
I should really work on
skill A, B, C, D, E,
F and G. All of these different
things I could be doing instead of the thing I should be doing.
You know the classic
like procrastination thing.
But like it's
very strong for some reason
at the moment. I think it was also
Munchie and Tom's
new podcast Killing Code
when Munchie is like really excited about
code and I was
like yeah yeah I enjoy
it when I learn the basics of
a new thing and I'm getting on a path
towards being a master at it. I never
go all the way because I'm a fucking idiot
but like fucking
there's so many things I want to do
there's so many like albums
I want to learn how to record
I want to draw
people I want to draw
myself I want to draw I was looking at
fucking
Jaden animations
the YouTube story time animator person
one of the better ones
one of the only ones that I
really really enjoy the content
of the thing despite it just
being you know similar
looking for those other ones
like I think Davoo's talked
about the odd ones out before and how he hates
the whole concept of that
channel where it's just a big blob of a guy
talking about stuff that isn't funny
and is very relatable and gets
billions upon billions of views
and and there's like hundreds
of different channels that are basically the same thing
where it's like you know 17 million
views my my
guys I had a hard time
in high school exams
oh they suck don't they guys
times I said something
embarrassing yeah you know
things like that I'm like yeah whatever
rolls eyes like I don't really care for
the relatable hashtag relatable stuff but
I just had this
like urge to like
be one of those people
and make my own channel
get a million subs you yeah
because I have like sad
like oh I used to be nervous in school
guys I used to be socially awkward
and I could I could easily do
things like that but I also wanted to be
like the only one of those
who was like really funny
because I can I can be really funny
of course and it's
just that's that's just
been on my mind and it's just one of many
things that has been like
distracting me from from
the thing I should be doing he just gave
me a big projects big new
projects the ideas of like making
new channels not necessarily to like grow
a channel and be a youtuber again
but to just to be to
to be able to do one give I think
I think you should
experiment in your free time
making content like this and I would say posting
it on give and take an established
channel with some sub base
exactly the start with something small
because I would excuse me
bet my bottom fucking dollar that kind
of content would do exceptionally well
as it does for so many hack fraud
animators on YouTube already
I think you'd find success there guys
I just thought of an idea for
a YouTube channel yeah it'll
be called everyone is terrible
and the the host
is like think of like a raven
from teen titans esk figure
like someone just like dark
hair in front of their eyes you know low
you know low misanthropic
and the idea of the channel is that it's sort
of an analysis channel but the idea
is that every video is about
prove is about how everyone is
provably terrible so the
idea is that they take recommendations
and you just tell like you leave
a comment who do you want them to prove is
terrible and then every video
is just about proving another person
is terrible and it could be literally
anybody you could talk about your fans
talk about
celebrities talk about whoever you want
just prove that everyone is terrible
I feel I feel like if
like Tara Strong herself did
that channel as raven people
would love it but if it was a guy then it
would be like just shut up dude just shut up
it depends on if
the guy if it's a guy it has to be
more funny if it's a girl
I want it to just be like just
a girl who's like just looks really dismal
and hates like legitimately hates everyone
that does sound funny hilarious
maybe there's maybe I'm getting head
Kennedy already but I imagine in my
world this show would be something that
the idea the conceit is to indeed
anything that you say wants to be
proved terrible this person will make it sound
terrible and find the way but what that really
indicates is that everything
can be interpreted terrible so just
don't assume
it's not everything it's every one
every one it has to specifically
be about humans like every
episode is another human being
why that person is terrible
sure
I want it to be like legitimately
being spirited I want it to be like
this channel
is about proving that literally everyone
is terrible and no one deserves
to live
I think we can combine these ideas
I'm gonna do an animation youtube storytime
and I'm gonna hire a
moody sounding girl to just say
the lines
it'll be called
the character will be
goth brisker
she'll be like really like even more
bitchy than usual
she sounds dismal enough though
she sounds too peppy
she can do a really she can do like a
raven voice okay yeah if she's
doing a voice fair enough
I mean I remember
when Jesse was always talking about his
idea of having an MLP
review channel hosted by
what was it it was
it was like a tropical sounding pina colada
like some girl pony that he wanted
to do and I still stand by
that would definitely do well not necessarily
pony anymore but like something like this
it's kind of weird how little
of people hiring other people to host
their shows there is on youtube
because like I understand
why Mr. Throps and Lonely and shit
I understand why a lot of us just
like have a point of pride we want it to be
our voice on the thing because we know how to
deliver it right because like I tried to
hire a girl to
to voice one of my scripts once and she
sent me like she sent me her test
version and I was just like no
like not happening like
the cadence is completely wrong
it doesn't give a point you know
but like
I do think that if if you're somebody
who can't do great delivery
like by all means you should just hire somebody
to read your scripts it's it's not
expensive you don't even necessarily to pay people
if you if you already have like a fan
group fan base like people do it
your fans will do it you know
yeah though I never want to rely on
fan goodwill pretty much for
anything personally but whatever
I get you I get the mic
uh yeah I stumbled
I stumbled through that that whole
thing I didn't really know what I was
gonna say I just know that
I should you like jaden animations
want to do stuff like that
yeah I want to be one of those
people and I want to go to jaden animations
when I've got like 20,000 subs
and say hello and she's going to be like
hey and then and then
then we'll say hey don't get on me
you silly animating boys
no got them no
is she like 19
how old is she if anyone knows I'm just curious
I don't know
I think she's like 15
but I have no idea if that's true or not
I've never seen this person's content
this person
the most recent video
was just something about
self-improvement
self-improvement and
and mindsets and stuff you know stuff that
most people in the PCP
like they're all right with that I occasionally
like the laps and I'm
stupid a lot of the time so I just need
some like
motivational but like like helpfully
motivational I think that's the way I would describe it
it's not merely like someone's here for you
I have this problem too
it's like she actually is smart in the way that
she goes about her scripts
to talking about this stuff
so I'm like yeah you're a reasonable
intelligent person the animation is
good and it's and
you know the jokes are pretty good and I like
them and I want to be your
friend jaden animations but not through the PCP
hey you know wanting to be
someone's friend is how you got into youtube in
the first place well okay not how you started
but like pony stuff it's
um wanting to be digi's
friend was how I became a brony analyst I think
right right right
it works
so keep it up
you know on that point give I've long
thought that it was kind of strange
that you didn't leverage more of your animation
skills on youtube
for your youtube content since it's kind of
like your primary skill
it's alright primary skill
primary skill is like one way
of putting it it is a skill that I have
and I know a lot about it
animation is very
time intensive and it's very
involved
if I can get away if I can get away with
not animating anything
I would
it's like one of the biggest things
I was thinking about how Tom spent
like a year and a half
animating like six pages of
emotion comic and Nate's like
why don't you just do it
two videos
if only it was that
god I'm smart
like it's
one of the major things I learned
because you know to save time
in animation
there is an art to
not animating
like over animator stuff you draw
on ones
some things just don't work on one some things
work when there's like just one frame
extreme frame and then another extreme frame
like a trigger does this a lot
with stuff they leave
out a lot of in-betweens to make it more punchy
and so I learned
that you can do a lot with
a lot less as long as you know when to
do a lot less
so I'm you know especially with editing
I apply that to editing and
anything visual you don't need to
show everything that's why a lot of the animations
I did for
my uni course were like
you know the first one the fish at the door
there is no background and the character
there's no color but like the point of
it is just to make you laugh with the joke
so as long as the joke comes through
with the right timing
it really doesn't matter what it looks like
and that's how I managed to make that
really good despite having no drawing in it
really at all
it's like yeah
brief history lesson the trigger style you're describing
is called limited animation
it's basically
all anime uses to some extent
however in the
70's animator Yoshinori Kanada
I believe was the guy who
started making like really dynamic
poses between extreme frames
and popularized that style
and uh, Gainax were big fans of him
especially Maishi so they basically
you know did that
I'm gonna tell that guy
if he shows me that shitty animation
take your ass back to Canada
where you came from
oh fuck you
to answer the question
of why I don't do animation in my
content is really just
it's a lot of work
it's a lot of work and it's easier to
just put a camera on and
dance for the camera
like how I look at my stupid dance in face
that's fair but now
I look gross and I want to never be seen
on live action ever again
that's excellent motivation
I'd say
uh, yeah
I mean it seems like animators
just get a lot of views
so it seems like
there's something
I can imagine that if I was
like more myself
in the way that I approached
topics and was like really
analytical or really edgy
that it wouldn't get really any views
because
part of it is like the hashtag
relatable me and
stuff and the teenage audience
and the demographic you see an animating
like channel
you know cool
but if you see the title it's like
relatable x thing
it's like oh you know what I'm clicking on it
yeah
even though I know that it's very often
like not interesting I do that
these channels are kind of like the youtube
equivalent of the four panel comics on tumblr
and twitter it's like the same kind of idea
of just like here's the thing that everybody
does and it connects with them
so they get views
you know this really this reminds me that
like so there's a resurgence a little bit
this happens every once in a while the galco video
which like start to get a bunch more views
and it's really fascinating
the success of that galco video is
not at all
what I intended and I kind of don't deserve
the like success of it
because while everything I said
in it was true
the message that people took away
wasn't as like 1.15
million views or whatever
the reason is because it struck
a nerve with fat girls
fat girls who like
think that they have such a great personality
love that fucking video
because they think when I'm talking about
thick girls I'm talking about them
when that was never intended
but that's just what is read into it
and uh
it's like almost a body positivity
video looking back on it now
as a like just be yourself
it's a literal I don't know
nay nay you should make a follow up
called fat is whack
I've been thinking about making a clarification
we Agua on that video
explaining it's just just like
you can take away from it whatever you want
I believe in death of the author for the most part
but I just want to explain what I meant
and I you're not gonna like it
ladies but I'm gonna tell you
what I meant to say
that honestly that's a great idea
it disappears
it disappears it's gone
I can see it now you just like start with like
a narration over like anime
or whatever like more of a galco
footage then just cuts to you like doing
pull-ups like without a shirt on it's like
do you really think I give a shit about you bitches
that's true that's true and it's like
like it was it's interesting because like people
like like jessica nigiri started following me
after I made that video and she's
basically the target I was
I was hoping to reach that's like actually
hot you know girl
and whatever you can have whatever thoughts you want
about old bald nigiri no offense Jessica
I love your content
I'm sure you're listening to this right now
but like so she she's
like a woman who takes care of herself
she's fit but she was probably always like
awkward weird anime girl
in high school who didn't fit in and
like that I get because
she's someone who works hard and I respect
what she does and
that's all cool but but then
you've got definitely definitely
a bunch of fat girls just listening
to this episode being like oh my god
galco looks exactly like me and I'm such
like a nice person but nobody can recognize
it because they just judge me based on McCurves
I am positive that that
is the demographic that like
resonated with the video the most
and I don't like you people
so you know
well it was big on tumblr so
I just get comments
unironically gotten comments
and yeah it was big on tumblr so that's how you know
I got
comments saying literally
like OMG and I'm sure this person was like
12 or something but with huge titties
like OMG
galco looks just like me
and also I'm super nice
but everyone treats me you know
like I'm just a dumb girl you actually
got comments like that one
absolute I'm gonna go find one right now
and read it off because it's it's it's
unreal if she if they say
galco looks just like me they're lying
they are telling a lie if they say that
or they're delusional what if there's a few of them
that are actually like that
those people wouldn't be dumb enough
to comment on this fucking video saying that
that's I unironically
think that
I'm gonna go find one right now
okay thoughtful a lot of shitty
galco does not have a body type that is common
no
absolutely not
hard to imagine dude I look just like galco
in my dreams
there's a lot of comments like am I the only one
who blah blah blah
shut the hell up okay now see this boy
this boy gets it uh sadly
there are no real women with
weaponized thickness for the forces of good
now this guy proud migtau such as
myself um okay well you know what
I'll I'll I'll let you know if I
find one but we can
we can move on here
uh oh here we go another red pilled individual
you know girls like her don't exist
irl good looking and kind
is a myth anime proved
it pretty well in showing us example
of perfect girls that you can't find
in our 3d world xd
that's a real comment
that's like that's like the v goer
that's just your mind on in in like
a text form like the minority
viewers of this video are like people on
4chan who just like want to watch a review of
galco or whatever like me
and that's and like that's
clearly coming from that crowd it's just
fascinating you know oh my god
here we go okay here's one here's the go
this is it this is a real
comment on the galco video an anime
heroine with my body type
and personality
well guess I'm a weeb again
that's no real
comment on this
video oh dear
can you believe that
that's real
your fat I'm sorry but your fat
you need to just address the reality of
the situation you need to move on
okay let's move on I'm sorry to waste
this is it this is the one this is the episode
that your work is gonna find
and you're done
Nate we brown out you
don't respect women and we have
a clear no discrimination
guys guys
you know all women are queens
Nate doesn't respect fat men
they're all women
I don't respect fat men that's true
it's not a sexist thing
our corporate policy dictates
that being fat is a protected class
and so you can't say anything
I mean that's true in some
fucking people's corporate
anyway anyway
we could go to voicemails
unless somebody else want to talk about something else
I just really want to get a drink
okay you can take a minute
somebody say something entertaining
well I'm gone
oh Christmas I said that in the beginning
it's coming
if you guys want to get us a present for Christmas
go to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
get your significant other
the gift they'll treasure forever at patreon.com
slash procrastinator by stealing their credit card
and signing them up for an account
you know go straight for the $100
tier would be my recommendation
the best Christmas present you can give your family
is 20 amazing bonus episodes
of the PCP they couldn't listen to before
it's $5 a month
it's funny to shill but it's not that funny
we know this from
from experience
alright
Christmas decorating
every year
my family
has the old tree
the cut real wooden tree
we put it somewhere we decorate things with lights
but this is the first time
we have the dog
on a Christmas
and this dog loves chewing
he loves eating
we were really scared that he would
destroy everything
but he's been very good
so that's my Christmas decoration
story
how do you guys decorate
during the holidays
you know just throw some shit around
I think we have a fake tree that we need to set up
or something I can't remember
no we definitely don't I should buy one
I'm feeling not Christmasy at all
have you guys just fucking scrooge that I didn't
even realize it was almost Christmas
yeah me neither
the holidays have ceased to exist
when Halloween came around
and Ben and Munchy just showed up
I'm like oh right
it's Halloween
I guess we should do something and we didn't
I don't like being a scrooge
if I'm not
thinking about it I will forget
but I also
I'm not huge into the preparations
and the music
it's just nice to have it around me
maybe saying scrooge is the wrong
I'm just like so in my own shit
and disconnected from all of humanity
that like
it doesn't even occur to me until it's like
on my doorstep, literally
when the children are ringing the doorbell
you're involved being a pure energy
I'm not even trying to flex
I'm saying it as a negative
that I'm just so disconnected from everything that happens
because it's fine
to be a little disconnected and all
but I get a lot of joy
from like specifically
I'm actually not going to be with my family for Christmas
for the first time ever because I'm going to Hawaii
to hang out with Michelle and her family
which is going to be dope
but it's going to be a little sad
because I'm not with those guys because I really like
being with my family around the holidays
but taking a year off
taking a year to be doing something else
my family is like
I won't say that they're
insufferable around the holidays
but it's like
everyone's harder to be around
when they're all like
worried about the holidays
when everyone's like trying to set up
for the holidays it's just like
anything about the holidays that stresses me out
I hate
I just want to relax and be happy
I've never understood why people do these things
that stress them out for the sake of tradition
it's just like
because they're the same people who will be like
the holiday isn't about this corporatization
it's about spending time with family
guys we have to get a treat
and I'm like
it's about family
but it's more about impressing the family
to let the parents know that we're doing well
and we're not fucked up
mom it's okay
I'm doing well
my children are fine, it's all good
my house is lovely and clean
oh my god
that's what Christmas is for a lot of people
the weirdest thing is that my family is like
three people
and I put on appearances
I live here
all the rest of the days
I understand what this house is really like
you're not fooling me, you just look like an idiot right now
stop it
very weird
there's one positive thing
when people come to visit
my mom came to visit a couple months ago
for the first time
and we had to clean up around here
because
we had moved in fairly recently
we were all just kind of around
having my mom come was an excellent motivator
to finally get our shit together
and actually clean up and make this place decently livable
and now it is
and it's nice and if she hadn't come
we probably would have been so lazy
that it still would just be like shitty stuff in boxes
not totally moved in
so like in that way
I kind of like having those kind of
fires under my ass
to actually get shit done be it like a holiday
or just people coming to visit or something
so I don't know
there's an advantage I kind of like about it
but I just like the traditions
I like having a tree
I like doing gifts even though it's kind of stressful
I just don't like
ever having to do anything
okay I'm with you
I like
I like some of it
I like the getting of gifts for
at least my immediate family
because it's something I don't really do
well
obviously I don't do it all the time
my birthday presents
but you know
it's just a big because I like getting gifts
I had a phase when I was kind of a little
younger when I was like
you know what Christmas
I'm just gonna not ask for anything
and then I didn't get that much and I was sad
because I like getting stuff
so like I
made a point to be like
you know I'm going to try
and just do the giving part
I never did that as a child
and my parents kind of made fun of me for like
because I remember vividly
there was an advert for like some
fucking thing
and in the advert a boy gave
his parents a present and there's like
enjoy the gift of giving with this fucking
product
and they said they look to me
it's like hey you never did that when you were young
I didn't know I had to do that
so then I started buying
gifts for parents and brothers and
it was good it's just
a nice feeling to be like
you know thanks
for thanks some for this thing
it's like yeah no problem
unironically not a joke giving gifts
just feels good I totally
subscribe to that
but it's annoying is all
it costs money Christmas cards
Christmas cards are the worst thing because that's like
the biggest obligation and it's easy
enough to send like
my mom has like
boxes of
upon boxes of like Christmas cards
that she's bought in advance ready to
like in like a
fucking celebrity at a book signing
to just sign a bunch of these cards
get everybody around the family to sign these cards
to send to every single relative possible
and friend and it's just
that's so much work
it's a lot of work for a piece of card that people
open they're like oh that's nice
I know I'm about to make an argument that I'm sure
someone else has made before
but like the problem I have with Christmas gift
giving is that giving someone a gift
is most fun when you happen
to find something that they will like
when you like see something
that makes a big difference I feel like this person
would like this before yeah and it's not
as much fun when you have to like go out
in search of something for that person
and you can't find anything and then like
so for me when it comes to holidays
and shit I just always
take people out to eat it's always been my policy
it's just like I'll buy you a meal
because
because I get something out of it too
I have somebody to go eat with
and I love to go out to eat
and like
so yeah because in any other
circumstances if I do just find
something I want to buy for somebody and buy it
and it's not Christmas I'm not
going to hold on to it
it's just like here just take the thing
you could use it now probably
why hold out
I never really like I
started off like the first year I did it
you know you never hear
of people just asking each other for gifts
it's always a surprise you have to get a surprise gift
so I bought some crap
at a toy store for my brothers and they didn't like it
and that was the end of that
so the next year I just asked them what they wanted
and
then they
asked me what I wanted and it was like
we just
very upfront about it and then we forget
what we asked for and then we get it and it's like
it's still a surprise because we forgot
by the time me and my brothers were adults
we were like ordering our own
off of Amazon like our own Christmas presents
like my dad's just like here's your budget
go buy as much whatever you
okay you know what I'll just say on the
on this subject I
my fucking
parents do this and I
hate that they do this and it's exactly
what you're talking about they'll say
Nate go find what you want
for Christmas and we'll buy it
I don't want a homework assignment
for a gift that I have to go do
and I hate it I will never
ever force anyone to do that
and no one ever asked me
to pick up my own fucking gift
the funny thing is that it got so much better after that point
because once we all finally grew up
and we were like we're too old
for Christmas I don't want anything anymore though
that's the thing I just don't want to bother
I don't want anything I have my own money
so then once it reached that point
like where it was like yeah everybody's like
because me and my brothers are all like that
we're all just like I don't buy anything
I can get it myself
because it got to that point my dad
still wanted to have Christmas he just started
buying people whatever the fuck he felt like
and it was way better
that's where my robe came from
like that's where my big fucking coat
came from
this is when your dad just started picking out stuff
yeah when he just started buying us whatever
he wanted us to have
he liked goofy coats and stuff
because he likes to see me wearing that shit
and those were sick
I'm like no problem dude
it's called
it's not giving if the person picks out
exactly what it is
I know some people are into it
some people just like to be pragmatic
I despise it
I don't know
I feel like it's
nice when you get something that you want
and you didn't have to pay for it
I don't know what it is
I'd even rather get something I don't want
that somebody just thought I would like
they put some degree of thought into it
at all
sometimes one of us just doesn't know what we want
and then the other person has to think of something
that's the real gift
that process of thinking what we want
as far as I'm concerned that's the actual gift
that they're giving you
the issue with
getting gifts that you've asked for
is that when you're in that situation
you usually have to get somebody else a gift
as well
let's say I'm
getting a gift from my sister
and she tells me what she wants
and I get her something
I haven't really gotten a gift
I've just paid for what I got indirectly
let's say I want a playstation game
she wants a switch game
I basically just bought the game
I just wasn't at the register when it happened
it feels
not the same
I'm still at 60 bucks
nothing's happened
I guess you're right
I don't know I don't feel so bad about it
and I don't want to start feeling bad about how
feel bad
I'm not trying to say that that's wrong
that's just
I think I'm too cynical about it
and I think over thought it
and I'm like damn it it's ruined
what sucks for me is that
I had outsmarted all this when I was a kid
but couldn't keep up as an adult
because when I was a kid
I would just make shit for my parents
I would always just write my mom
a poem or a song
give them a card
that had some cool writing a picture
or something
me and my brothers always made stuff for our parents
because my mom is impossible to buy shit for
she doesn't particularly like anything
unless it's like an Alice in Wonderland
collectible or the Sandman
collectible
those are the only sure-fire things
or some kind of monkey
plush or something like that
maybe a plushie I don't fucking know
she doesn't like anything
so you just make something for her
and she'll always appreciate it way more
but then I kind of ran out of ideas
the last thing I did
for my parents was on each of their birthdays
made them an analysis video
back in the early pony days
you could find thoroughly analyzing
Todd Collins or whatever in my playlist
oh yeah
but
once you've done that once
I'm not going to make up new shit to say about you
yeah
well you know
there's a lot I don't know about my parents
alright
this year
it was particularly
it felt good
because me and mom were going around
shopping for people
and mom was buying baby toys for
new members of the family
even more
nephews and all that
and she's buying baby toys
and she's asking me like
don't you know that my little pony thing
what is this
you know that was a weird moment
but there was this
this nice necklace
and my mom was looking at it
and it was like 18 pounds
and I was like I'll buy that for you for Christmas
and she's like oh really
there's really nice views
like a pound necklace
for a second
that's a chain boy
we call that a chain
yeah very good
very funny
god I've heard that so often for some reason
like every time I speak in my own currency
everyone's like
oh you idiot
that joke was the first thing that came into my head
when you said that
even to me that feels stale and old
I didn't say it as a joke
I legitimately thought that you were talking
about an 18 pound necklace
and I was like whoa
yeah I know
it's just I hate it
anyway I felt like a real man
because I had cash in my wallet and I paid
for the thing and I have it
and I'm gonna wrap it up nice and she's gonna open it
and she's gonna be like oh yeah
it's not really about like
the surprise or like
the
it's the thought that counts and the thought is
I'm going to give you something
yeah sure
I don't really
I mean my brothers I don't know how they feel about it
I assume they just don't really care
and they don't feel like oh man
I would have rather gotten something random
that you care to give me
they don't give a shit
they're just happy to have a new thing
my thing right now is that my parents
are still like we need to get you
something for Christmas and I'm just like
no you don't
you can stop because
my parents don't have a lot of money
but they still try and do those things
and I'm like on the one hand I don't want to like
I mean it's a matter of pride
I know it is because there was a time when
my family they couldn't afford to throw a Christmas
there was one time
my grandma actually did it for us
she didn't really have the money
to do it but she was just like it's too important
that they have a Christmas
then like
I get that but like I'm 30
it's okay because like they were talked
I was over there like a month ago
and I was talking with the parents and they were like
yeah we want to get your younger sister
because I have a younger sister who's like 17
and like she really wants a
switch and we're like is there any way we can
get it cheaper than $300
getting Nintendo products on sale hilarious
so I'm like no like it's gonna be
like that's just how much you're gonna have to pay for it
they might have a holiday bundle or something
it's gonna be $300
and so I was saying like
just get me nothing and put my money
that you would spend on me towards that
like it's chill I don't mind
you know and they were just like oh no
but like we already like bought it and stuff
like we're already planning on getting it
like we still need to get you something we got your sister a guitar
so like we need to get you something like
you don't have to it's chill it's fine
you know like use like because I don't
the only thing I think I know what I want
for Christmas now is a cheap guitar
it's like that's a good one that's good
because like cheap because
if they asked me like son like what would you
like for Christmas like what if like
what would you like a roof over your head
yeah yeah and it's like
roll it through your fucking brain
things that I would ask for like things
that I would like like want
for like production for like my work and stuff like
oh could you get me a fucking
like Dell XPS 13 with a 4k
screen and like yeah that's the thing
like the things that I quote unquote
want are like a grand
plus and I'm never going to ask for
something that's that much because it's insane
so I'm just like just don't worry about it
like I would the gift for me in that situation
is like I would like my little
sister who's becoming a gamer and is going
to have her life ruined forever to at least
have the console to console her when all her friends
thinks she's too weird you know what she'll be
she'll be one more precious
viewer giving that one cent of ad
revenue on imgames.com
so that's worth it that's a worthwhile
investment that is not fun sorry
sorry it's it's fun
patreon.funds
give me some funds you know when I
actually the microphone I'm using right now
was technically a Christmas
present I believe like three years ago
but like because it's so expensive
there's like 400 bucks or whatever I asked
my parents to put down like half the money and I'd
put down half and that's how we would like
you know kind of there's there was a lot of
credit in that way around my yeah
yeah Victor's camera
was bought that way
all right shit's expensive man
where the money go
I just need that dick
replacement but I you know it's more than
get the money they're willing to spring for
all right well guys good talk
is it time yeah it's time let's get to
these voicemails okay so we got
we got nine total but the first one
is a public service
announcement from
from stop please
is the name of this individual so
hang on I know there's a little dead
sound so I'm gonna let it play for a second here
but okay here it goes
stop
talking over voicemails
that's it but why
how are we gonna make comments about things
they say this okay this is an
interesting one which is why I wanted to play it
first so
talking over voicemails I think
is something that like adds to the experience
but I don't want to make things inaudible
for people either you know
don't we post them in the show notes
no we actually don't
they're all hosted on SoundCloud
I mean the most important thing
the most important thing to hear
is laughter when there's a joke
absolutely absolutely
yeah I mean that person would be fucking
probably devastated if they didn't hear any laughter
over their joke
yeah okay let's just try to talk less
over the audio I guess when would appropriate
but I'm not gonna fucking stop laughing
okay duly noted thank you
moving on here's Bobo the
addicted hobo calling in
what have you got
alright guys you know that funny ha ha
meme about the pcp being addicted like
ajo dust and you actually start
craving it well it's not a ha ha funny
meme for me it's actually real life
so let me give you my backstory
a year and a half ago I was
at the gym and I was a wee
weak boy and I was too embarrassed
that people were looking at me so I started listening
podcasts to distract myself
it all started with a monkey and didgy one
and I liked it so much that I was like
why not give the pcp a chance
yeah then
I started listening to it even after I was
doing the gym on my way to home
I liked it even more
so I started listening to it every single
time when I'm outside
and I'm walking and I'm not talking to another
person but I actually
realized how bad this shit is
two days ago when I lost my
phone I wasn't able to listen to the pcp
I was riding my bike to
uni my mind wasn't in
normal state I was confused
I was scared and I actually hit
a guy because
I was not doing the pcp
fuck
this shit is bad
it was probably missed that five more episodes
and I'll be caught up and I'll have
to wait a week to get my
dose fuck
I know you guys have other
shit go try listening to that
go listen hopefully
okay hang on it will be like
jesus christ good enough but
I don't know man
it's scary
it really is
alright look look
it's like the saying goes
the first 137 hits are free
but then you gotta pay
for the bonus episodes
that's exactly right
that's the right way to go
20 episodes waiting for you
20 bonus episodes
if you like digi bro
there's the every youtube video
featuring digi bro playlist with
two months of content plus on it
our boy here
he's talking about how he's listening to
all the pcp but he doesn't seem to have listened to any of
our solo content so that's a world
unto his own god there's a rabbit hole
there's multiple rabbit holes
watch the radcon playlist too but all three
radcon playlist check those out
and if you finish all our shit
the dig show is also good for the same
purposes
I am racist
but I couldn't understand
what he was saying
I got the gist of it
did he run over someone on his bike
he said he hit someone on his bike
cause he couldn't listen to the pcp
and he was getting the shakes
and so he just swerved his bike
oh like a drug
there it is
oh well good luck with your addiction
keep listening though
we're your sole provider
alright next up moonju
back at it again
munchie tom
I love the fact that you're starting
to code frankly it is my
favorite activity
and I too am learning to code through school
but why python
python like I
looked at it and it seems to be
a really hard language for beginners
like
you know me
and presumably you
seeing as you both have
little to no experience
in actual coding
so why did you choose python over any other
beginner friendly languages
like game maker
studios or
I don't know
anything really
game maker studios
is very specific to video game making
coding is not necessarily just
games well I know
the reason he's asking is because we both
said the reason we're learning to code is to
make games so the question is like
a fair one to ask and I have
the reason why is very simple
it's because munchie is learning to code
primarily to work on endless war
and that's a discord and you extend discord
through python so that just makes sense for him
and then for me the game engine
I want to use to make games in is godot
and gd script its language
is a derivative of python
so just for our personal purposes the tools
are going to be using pythons the one
that makes the most sense
I mean if I was just going to go into it
completely blind I would probably just choose
C sharp because it's like everywhere
it even can be using to go
they just added version to go that supports C sharp
and it's also in unity and
so like that would be like the most
logical one to do
but just because of the tools that we're both
using and they both happen to line up with python
python was like
the one to go with
I was curious about that
you know I was actually his assertion that python
is a particularly difficult language for beginners
I find that strange
I've heard the opposite I've heard python is a great
beginner language python is in fact great
in many ways one of which being
you do not need to compile code
in order to run it which is a huge advantage
though one of the weird things
about python is that white space management
is extremely important
and it will break your code
someone got really mad at us for using python
in the comments for that reason
because they were just like oh the white space thing
is bad and I personally because
I've done a bit of gd script which again
uses white space indentations for
breaking up functions
so I was like I didn't have a problem
so I was just simply asked why
and there was a paragraph
this huge essay about
how he worked on a professional project
and one tab
and it came up for days
and it was like the worst experience ever
man that's his fucking fault
python tells you when you just weren't
reading your fucking errors when you're compiling it
you dumb shit so fucking get in there
do it again and figure it out
I personally like the white space
because I am inherently lazy
because like when I code an html
it's a mess
and I have to force myself to go back in after
and format it so the fact that python
forces good behavior
shit in order
or you're an idiot and it's not going to work
I like that aspect
I suppose you could kind of consider it
training reels but whatever
it's I find it kind of nice
so whatever
the other hand is like when I code an html
tons of times I forget to close the bracket
and nothing runs and I have to look through it
everywhere trying to find where the bracket isn't
for a present
indeed
you're fucked either way
before the record I am in fact a professional
programmer and python is the
biggest language I use day to day
that in Java but mostly python
and you know what I thought might be fun at some point Tom
I listened to the whole show enjoyed it quite a bit
I thought that at some point maybe be fun
especially since you're doing python
to bring in
my code that I made for the
PCP pay calculator which is pure
python
dude it's funny that you say that because the last episode
we just recorded last night
I said I wonder when we're going to get to the
point when we could make the
PCP pay calculator yes
that's a and Munchy said he wants
to try and recreate it
in his spare time to see if he can do it
he should I'd be happy to provide just finished
version like 1.5
the other day which
incorporates now individual
this wasn't in the in the functions before
but now you can
attach a minor or major penalty
not only to editors but to
participants in the episode for degrees of
lateness so now that's a function
that's in there that I was using for the last one
because this was an issue
anyway we can talk about that later I just
like talking about this a little bit
code is cool and I'm excited
to learn more python I like it so far
and to be honest I looked at C sharp
because like the tutorials for
like Godot they have a toggle where you can
look at the code in C sharp or python
or Judy script and
C sharp looked really scary and python
looked
not scary so I've never used C sharp
so I don't know about it
all right it's in my code
let's go to the next one
this is from JustJapGirls
on Bowie
is the full name
let's see what he's got
okay so this question is for
Nate and I'm going to Japan
for summer
oh yeah
see the new one this film
and my question is what is the best
length of time to be in Japan under two weeks
because I don't have money
for more than two weeks
to get a good grasp of Japan
yeah
okay this is a preposterous question
did you just use the whole two weeks?
yeah the question was
how much of a length of time
under two weeks
is the best amount of time
to like get to know Japan
all of it
just use the two weeks
okay I don't know
if there's like some larger point there
I could imagine that like
I think he means bang for your buck ratio
like what is the best?
no what he means is that
if he stays there for like five or six days
it'll be okay but once you get over that
people are going to start to notice that he's not Asian
and they're going to start heckling him
so he's going to have to get out of dodge quick
it's one of those things
where like
potentially he could go for two weeks
but if he could save money
and go for a little less time
and see basically the same amount of stuff
he would rather go for less time
how big of
how much of Japan is he planning to explore
that's the important part
that's what I was going to say
you don't need to be in Tokyo for one in a week probably
so I spent all my time in Tokyo
with one trip to
Kuro Tamago mountain
I forget what it is
like I don't fucking know Japan very well
I was there one time for like two months
and I
lived in the city and I kind of know what that's like
a little bit but
basically I can't help you there
but I'll just tell you what I tell everybody
go check out the dope unlabeled restaurants
just go in and explore
go to Akihabara because why the fuck not
and go to the side shops
just do some research
just look up shit that you're interested in
you won't understand Japan after two weeks
by flanderizing Akihabara video
because shit tons of people
who either live in Japan or have been there
commented on that
and weighed in with not only their impressions
of Akihabara but also like what other places
you can go to get cheaper merchants
that was a truly fascinating video did you
which I absolutely loved
for some reason I thought that was
a super bunny hop video
it did not look like that
I copied his writing style on purpose sometimes
sometimes I try to talk like bunny hop
you didn't put epic noodles
going up and down meme though
oh yeah how could I have left that
I don't know if that's in Akihabara though
oh really okay
alright next call
let's go to Captain D
hang on play and go
hello this is the official
what part of discord representative
speaking
are these all the same guy like what
I don't know
but jesus
very poorly
in the discussion around pcp
discord lately
and those would like to announce
that we are declaring war
on all other pcp
related discord
oh my god I repeat
the mud puddle is going to war
on all other pcp related
discord
the mud puddle
okay hang on
oh fuck
sorry I paused it
so this is the captain D the official representative
of the mud puddle discord
your personal discord give
that's my personal discord
alright I guess the joke is
there seems to be like a large
the people in my discord
seem to be mostly german
at least the people who like
they're gonna do fuckin blitzkrieg bro
literally like
is that who all these collars are
are these all german? is that what this accent is?
I mean I don't know all of their voices
but you know maybe
so is this your doing
are you the secret puppet master
leading blitzkrieg against?
I ain't saying anything
alright let's let him finish his point here
please take contact
on the usual routes
this was the mud puddle discord
representative captain D speaking
good day and remember
to kill all whites
hahahaha
the fourth one right cause a little bit
different story than I remember
different flavor
I like it though it's spicy it's new
well I've gotta weaponize
everybody in BGE's ticket to enlightenment
my patron discord
rev up your artillery
rev up the anti air cannons
everybody in the poddyskord
you know
prep the guns
I am games discord
I am games
oh my god just weaponizing
the ratty fuckers cop killers though
is going to be now that's an
experienced warfare in culture
we need to we need to make some sort
of event some sort of event where
representatives from each of the discords can
beat the shit out of each other in live action
it's a good idea it's a good idea in real life
boxing gloves
well until we figure that out
next call is from
Steve I'm saved saint
who I think we've heard from before
who was in tough times
let's see how he's doing
hey PCP I think a thank you's
in order because not only have you provided
a great podcast for me to listen to
you also
exercised my house from benton saint
oh right the digi's advice
and it worked I breaded all my meat
and that's one food you can't steal
and uh
pipa was the real man the real MVP
I scheduled everything in my house and not only did I
schedule it but just in case
he was on time one in a million
I made sure I was early to everything
so well there's absolutely no fucking way he could
do anything so
just wanted to say thanks to you guys and I guess
I'll ask a real question this time since
I've been memeing a lot
Mr. Bessman since you're a god among
men and will definitely be alive to see starfleet
what's the first thing you're going to do
when we achieve that
alright thanks guys
I'm going to head on over to
patreon.com
the procrastinators
and so should you
I got to say it was really nice to finally
hear just a down home American white guy voice
for once on this
yup
yup last guy killed all the whites but
Steve I'm saved saint brings them right back
like the cockroaches they are
um
he sounded kind of southern right
a little bit
next one here is from
Ryan Harper
shit no play almost type pray
haha hashtag atheism
oh shit I don't know
if I sent the last
voicemail or if I
fucked it up
but I wanted to tell you guys
Mr. PCP
that I love y'all
you guys
do a pretty good podcast
it's
my 21st birthday
hey that explains a lot
like that all
before
I had my second beer
ever today
sooo
Nooo
hahaha
oh yeah I'm like
I think like 10
10 drinks and
something along those lines
beer
wine and shots I don't know what to split we gotta get this guy to start
watching I am games but you're right I've got a suggestion to you guys okay you
guys should give mage a button that when she presses it and it's everyone else
in that way she can say things and she's she's the most relatable and
important person really in the PCP you all should respect her more he relates to
like scrapping in the streets of Lithuania with like angry squirrels or
whatever her story was like he relates to this like amorphous color-based
creature with no definable characteristics how you know you're drunk
you relate to mage well that was sweet nonetheless well we'll try to give old
mage you know give her give her a roll give mage a solo podcast we'll leave
and let her the legendary solo PCP podcast will just be one problem because
major solo podcast you just dream about it and that'd be it oh that's true that's
true oh okay next one two more people this is from the anti-procrastinator is
here oh shit are getting shit done man let's see what he's got all right news
our solutions are pretty cool so just one little problem with them that's sad
everyone waits till fucking January to start on what the fuck are you doing stop
procrastinating starting girls right the fuck now he's got a good point he's got
a great point personally though I try to wrap everything up before the end of the
year so that I have a clean slate to do the new thing you know that yeah well my
favorite thing to do is to get rid of obligations by January yeah yeah that's
good that's good for me it's like I usually I really like the idea of
thinking of things in terms of years just like I like having clear cutoffs the
way I do my job is always like what do I have to get done by the end of this month
you know yeah so like I always have that mentality of like okay everything has to
be clear by the time the next increment starts so that we can you know we can
hit the ground running and just do the whole new plan you know yeah it's it's
a lot more difficult like even if you have a good plan if you're still supposed
to be doing other things while your new plan is supposed to be implemented you
like I guess like I should do the thing I said I would do but I still got to do
this oh geez and then you you die I've never really been a big news resolution
guy which I guess is probably weird for me but I don't know it just like I mean
I guess I don't want to just like pretend like I'm so glad like well I just do
everything immediately I'm so good just for whatever reason the whole new
year's resolution thing I think it's the same thing for me right it's with
holidays I just don't even like the end of the year doesn't even register to me
I'll be like somebody yeah like oh my god it's the next year you know I just set
all of my I kind of wish I did my new year's resolutions are just like a
reasonably doable but kind of extreme goal for that year so like make a hundred
thousand dollars this year it's like there's a chance it could happen there's
a chance it won't happen it's good to move in on how things go but like that's
this is where I'm trying to be you know if I fail I just make the same thing the
next year until it works I make sense yeah but if I would have like a new year's
resolution I don't often do but like I've been thinking 2019 is gonna be the
year of music where I finally get around to all the music stuff to do so I will
make albums I will make attempts to learn how to produce myself properly and
record myself well and get better at certain instruments I'm okay at drums
but I just need to get a little better before I can you know lay down some sick
beats and all that maybe I'll even pick up FL studio again even though I hate it
and I don't like it and it sucks and I would rather hit things with my drum
sticks than click buttons to make the same thing happen much easier yeah but
yeah that that's the year of music if it's the year if it's a whole year of
like one thing then if I don't know what I'm doing or I finished a project and I
don't know what to do next I know at least that it's the year of music I can
do I can work on the next just like the year of Luigi that's our Nintendo yeah
yeah the year of Sanji the year of my maybe I'll maybe I'll make an effort to
kind of get into it more this year like I'm thinking of just making red to a into
a thing where like I run every day for that year and then I like track my
progress and like see what's changed over that time you gain 365 pounds in
yeah exactly exactly I don't know and that's not that's not the currency this
time and I've got I mean I've got some some big events happening in my life
coming up hopefully relatively soon but I don't know I'll think about it I'll
think about it as I go anyway let's get to our next fucking call here oh this is
our last one too from oblivion fall not mad just passionate is the full I don't
know okay let's oblivion go we can spend an age discussing the multitude of
reasons why going to college for art is a waste of time no already art degree is
worthless the only thing that matters is your portfolio and connections and
college is really not necessary for that this is especially true if you are
already an artist with an established presence I went no we don't need this
anymore this is done this interesting course I was the top of my class and
the only thanks I got was a worthless degree and $20,000 worth of debt but I
am against a munchy going to college if munchy wants to go to college he could
do great because I'm doing great I am only 23 years old yet despite college
holding me back for two years I managed to emigrate from New Zealand to the
United States of America I have a green card I am now happily married to a
beautiful wife I am earning four thousand dollars a month working two dream
jobs doing animation and animation directing on YouTube the products of
which have earned over 250 million views that is more than all of your
channels including side channels combined if I can do it anyone can fucking do
it certainly munchy can do it he's a talented kid he's got a bright future
ahead of him stop filling his head with doom and gloom he's going to be fine
have faith in him interesting is that the fact that we had faith in him the
reason we didn't want him to go to college well there's an maybe so I
noticed one thing in that story that stands out as strange to me so his whole
point is that you can you know like do just fine go into college and then be an
artist whatever but but he frames it as you can overcome the setback that is
going to college why so why encourage college if it's a setback why would you
do that it isn't it's hired I was funny I gotta think that the funny thing for me
is that like college is great it opens up all these opportunities I have 250
million views on YouTube yeah YouTube well to be fair to be fair I think he's
talking about like obviously he wasn't the only person working on these
projects so is it really fair to say that he obtained every one of those views
himself I don't think that was a point I think the point was saying that the
product is working on is successful and that's great I mean God yeah yeah yeah
exactly is this still a part of the same call that was okay I have nothing
further to say on that but oblivion way to just never talk about is an interesting
guy ever again yeah yeah we don't need to talk about oblivion oblivion fall is a
cool guy he he he he snuck PCP references into a lot of big animation
yeah he didn't whoa where can I find these there was there was like a
cuphead music video animation the music that the song sucks the song's really
bad but he put like but chugger and face yeah and hippo tries not to die the
video game yep he did and he's cool and he famous you would be way into this
didgy he made you know that like come song that this guy made with all the
PCP imagery you know you don't talking about people yeah I think like whatever
whatever that is is like actually that that video I heard oblivion talking about
this it's like obtaining strangely renewed popularity now and it's just full
of like PCP imagery for no reason wait what is there's no connection what do you
what is it's a song about come yeah it's about like I need to hear this song I
haven't heard this before God I wish I do I did we play it I don't remember what
it's called okay let's definitely put in the show notes we can definitely find
it before then so everybody go check that out I don't know I guess that's it
oblivion's interesting and I like to hear his perspectives on this is a great
voice sounds like he's been to the most speech therapy out of anyone ever probably
turned out all the kings well I guess that's it like 23 oh yeah cuz he had the
one New Zealand accent I don't think I won't catch your one slip up you fake
American accent man I posted the brother is brothers and arms cuphead song that's
what it's called right that's the one with with the PCB memes you got to look
close but they're there but they're there in the background um all right well
that's it that's it everybody I guess that's it that's that's it patreon.com
slash the procrastinators wow 20 bonus episode people five dollars and you get
them all one dollar and you're in the discord you can talk about stuff that's
fun that sounds good shouts out to Victor for Bastard indeed rest in peace
yeah I'm gonna go listen to his radio after this. Pray for our boy Victor Victor's a good boy
you wouldn't hurt a fly. Yeah Victor I knew watching his video he did not
intend for it to be insulting to anybody it's just that he's a sensitive young
man yeah all right well follow us at TP Crass news on Twitter speak pipe link in
the description give us some more voicemail still respond to people keep
them coming that's good shit he needed his apology video so what god damn it oh
I wanted at least yeah I want to listen to that damn it Victor well like a lot
of people like all the comments on it were like you don't need to apologize
what the fuck are you talking about so maybe he just went this is gay and he
pulled it maybe the only evidence will exist in this podcast where we discuss
everything there is all right well anyway we'll see you guys next week have a
wonderful time oh and I won't be here by the way because I'm gonna be away so I
won't be here to record so that'll be that'll be pretty pretty kooky guys
pretty kooky squad all right anyway rest in peace see you later bye-bye
welcome to the cum zone that's the one
I am a stupid I got a deadline don't want to do it