I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's Ben Saint and it's Gibbontake.
You sound like you literally are recording while in bed, like on your side.
I wish, I feel, I'm a little, I don't know, this has been a week of like, totally, totally fucked up my sleep schedule.
I mean, the last two days, like I went to bed at like 5pm, and then I woke up at midnight, and then I worked until like 6am, and then I went to sleep again until like 4pm, and then I woke up, and it's been like that.
Weird and wacky.
It's been weird and wacky, and I just took a 4 hour nap, and then I woke up, and it's 10, 20am.
It feels so bad. Like when that happens, sort of like the concept of days starts to blur, and you're like, what a, ugh.
Part of me enjoys feeling like there's no outside world, and I'm just in floating in space, and I just like, whenever I feel tired, is it light out? Is it dark out? I don't know.
Whenever I feel like it, I'll just go to bed for as long as my body feels like sleeping, and then I'll wake up and be awake for a while. What day is it? I don't know.
Part of me enjoys that feeling.
I feel uncomfortable when that happens. I like a structure that I can reliably be like, yes, today is this day, tomorrow will be tomorrow.
Well, physically I feel pretty bad right now. I'm also very, ugh, I'm sick and I'm sick and because I just had a, just right now, the reason why I'm like 10 minutes late is that I was, ugh.
My roommates are like, who's going to take over the gas bill? Ben, do you want to be the one to take over the gas bill? No, I don't. I really don't want to do it.
But somebody's got to, and I'm going to get bullied into it. I have a bad feeling I'm going to get bullied.
Uh-oh.
I know, so, I mean, somebody's got to do it. Ugh, makes me sick. But, hey, speaking of being in space, I've been playing Outer Wilds.
Ah, pug, what do you think?
It is pug. It's great. It's awesome. It's like if Spore was good.
If Spore, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can see that a little bit.
I mean, it doesn't have the creature creator, but it's got planetary exploration and all that.
Yeah.
This is a bit spoilery, but I have managed to land on the quantum moon.
Nice.
And I think I know, I've learned all three quantum lessons, so I think I know what I need to do when I go back there next time.
I'm not sure, but I'm not going to look it up. Admittedly, I did have to look up, I had to look up the solution to one of the quantum puzzles.
Uh, failed.
A little bit fail. A little bit fail. But I don't feel bad, because I never ever would have figured out that you have to use your probe scout to, like, observe the arch to keep it from moving.
That simply never occurred to me.
I believe, I believe in one of the temples. It teaches you that lesson.
Yeah, but I was just not getting it.
You didn't get it? I thought, like, you had to, like, use your probe in that place.
Yes, yes, and I didn't, and yes, and I could not think to do, I never thought to do it.
Lamau.
Yeah, I was, I was fucking around and I was like, Supernova is coming. I've spent my whole, I've spent this whole run fucking around in this temple.
And I, like, I can't catch this fucking arch, so I had to Google it and it was like, use your scouter.
Like, oh, fucking duh. But I never would have thought of it, because I never, I never used the scout.
Oh, the scout's very useful.
Yeah, I, I slept on the scout.
Like, just for like, if you're in a cave, just shooting it on the walls, you can see what the hell's going on.
Yeah, I would basically never use it unless I got, like, a Ghost Matter warning, or I'm, I'm, I'm kicking myself because I never thought to shoot it into the dark bramble seeds.
And so, like, now I have, first of all, I fucking, I hate the dark bramble. I hate the dark bramble so much.
I'm so glad. By the way, I think, I think, I think we should, like, like, this is a spoiler for outer worlds.
Put that before, because I want.
I think I said that, didn't I?
You did, but like, we didn't really make a big deal of it, and people probably weren't.
It's important that you don't know anything about outer worlds, like mechanics before you play it.
Yeah, a lot of it is, a lot of the joys in figuring it out. I haven't, that was like the one thing that I looked up was like, what do I do in this fucking temple?
And I don't feel bad about it.
I remember there being, like, a log or a thing on the wall that says, like, an image of a quantum thing is the same as looking at it.
And if you look away, it changes where it is.
So I was like, yep, it definitely did hit, yep, it definitely gave me those hints and I just didn't get it.
I just did not pick up on it. So that's, that's what happened there.
Talk about Dark Bramble, because I, it is the scariest worst place in the world.
Honestly, it's not as bad as I thought, like, what happens when you go into the Dark Bramble is basically the scariest thing I can imagine ever.
It's like literally the sort of thing that I'm scared to go to sleep because what if I have a nightmare about that?
And yet, you know, the first time it happened, it wasn't that bad.
I was just kind of like, whoa, okay.
Yeah, you just sort of like resigned just, okay, I'm being eaten.
Yeah, yeah, I saw the light, I saw it moving.
I was like, oh, it's moving. Oh, is it attached to something?
And then the fish showed up and I'm like, oh boy, there it is.
And only afterwards that I process, like, that was really scary, actually.
Yeah.
It's just, it's the anticipation really, like when you actually see the fish, it's not like so bad.
But like, when you're waiting for it, it's like, I'm going to cry.
I don't know how much of things you've learned.
So I'm trying not to like bring things up, but please keep telling me about your adventure.
What did you, what did you find out first?
You want me to talk about the Dark Bramble?
Yeah, just talk about everything. Talk about anything.
I've beaten the game, so I know what you could...
I think I'm like pretty far in.
I definitely have more stuff that I haven't found in the Bramble.
I mean, I found the guy playing his harmonica inside of the skeleton.
I've found the escape pod and the graveyard.
Oh, and that's the really annoying thing is that I realized later that I did not think to throw a scouter into the little Bramble hole.
So I have to go back and I have to find the graveyard again and throw my scouter in.
Yeah.
Because I forgot, I didn't, at the time I had not realized you could do that.
So I have to find that again.
I found the big jellyfish frozen inside of the Bramble somewhere.
So how did you find, what's his face, the harmonica?
How did I find him?
Yeah.
I did use my scouter.
The audio?
Oh, no, the scouter.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I followed the signal.
Yeah.
I followed the...
I forget.
That was another thing.
I have started using it more, but for a while I just never used the signal locator.
I was just winging it.
I was just like, eh, I'll just blast off and just go wherever.
That's a great thing though.
You fly around and merely observing how things work is knowledge that you gain that you can use later.
Yeah.
When I started using the, it's not called the oscilloscope, whatever.
The one that gives you a little radar signal and it tells you which direction some signal is coming in.
When I started using that, that was how suddenly I figured out the quantum stones.
I started finding the quantum stones and, oh wait, the other thing I had...
Actually, no, I had to look up both things about the quantum stones.
I'm so stupid, but I would never have figured it out.
I would never, ever have figured out that you have to turn the lights off and the quantum stone changes location because you cease to observe it.
I never would have figured that out.
Did you get to the underground place that you learned that?
Yes.
But you didn't figure out to turn the light off?
No.
I found that cave and I was looking around in it and I was just like, okay.
Yeah, I found that cave and I found the stone and then I just left.
I was like, well, I found the stone and there was nothing there.
Wasn't there writing to look?
Yes, I found the writing and I read it and maybe somewhere in the writing it suggests like, oh yeah, I turned my lights off and the stone disappeared.
But I just didn't get it.
I just didn't think to turn my flashlight off because why would you ever turn your flashlight off?
It is unintuitive, but like I've found that like paying close attention to the things you read is it does give you enough clues to figure out what to do next.
Yeah.
Except for one part, but I don't know if you've got there yet.
Do you want to give me a hint for what the part is and I'll tell you?
It's to do with the white hole transporters.
Oh, do you mean the tower?
The towers?
Yeah, the tower that falls through the black hole.
Oh no, that's different.
Then no, I don't think I have seen what you're talking about.
White hole transporters?
I don't even know what that is.
Okay.
That's fine.
I guess there's more to find then.
There is more.
So much.
What have I found?
I've seen the ash twin become completely naked and I figured out that it's some sort of hourglass that counts down to the supernova.
What else is there?
I think I've found most everything there is to find in the dark bramble.
I did all the quantum stuff and I think I know everything I need to know about the quantum moon.
I just haven't done it yet.
I know the shrine on the quantum moon needs to be on the north pole.
I don't know how to get it there, but I think I have an idea.
I found the guy on the Adlerock.
I've delved into all the old ruins, all the escape.
I found the Sunless City, but I didn't get to fully explore it because the sand rose too fast.
That's a tricky one to get down quickly.
You sort of have to remember based on landmarks where you're supposed to land your ship to get there as fast as possible.
Yeah, that one's a little...
Shit on the Ember Twin is a little annoying because once the sand's too high, it's like, well, nothing else to do.
Did you get crushed by the rising sand?
Oh, several times, several times, yeah.
It makes a little squishy sound at the very end.
Yeah, they're like...
Poor gross, a little gross.
Well, I actually find the Giant's Deep is almost as scary as the Bramble.
Is there something about the Giant's Deep?
When I fall in the water, I'm scared to look down.
Oh, yeah, I was like that the first time.
I crash landed on it and I'm like, oh my god, it's water.
Oh my god, if I go underneath, is it going to be like Subnautica?
Are the big demons going to come and grab me?
I held my breath and I forced myself to look down and it seems like it's just jellyfish, so it seems like it's fine,
but it's still like, when I'm in the water, I'm just like...
Yeah.
I first landed on Giant's Deep.
It was big, it was green, I just flew there.
I fell there by accident the first time and I'm like, oh shit, what the fuck?
I can't even jump because there's double gravity.
Double gravity is such a big planet, but I landed on one of the islands
and I was just sort of looking around being like, okay, I don't know really what I'm doing,
just finding things, and then I just sort of, I was in space.
Oh yes, the like, I haven't quite figured out what's going on with that.
Is it like a tornado passes by and like, inside the eye of the tornado, there's no water and no atmosphere?
Is that what that is?
It's quite funny.
I don't know whether to just explain it to you.
Up to you.
I mean, if you think it's like a big spoiler that I...
It's not a big spoiler, it's just sort of like something that when you notice it, you're like, what?
No, you can tell me because like, I've noticed it and I've been curious about it, but like...
Okay.
I'm sure there's something going on.
I just, I haven't...
So...
Yeah, just tell me, just tell me.
Yeah.
The islands on Giant's Deep move around on the surface and the tornadoes also move around.
And when an island connects to a tornado, the tornado...
Would it throw it into space?
It throws it into space.
Oh my god.
And then you're floating for half a second and then the gravity of Giant's Deep brings it back down.
And the first time I happened, I had no idea what was happening.
I thought I was going to die.
It was the scariest thing that ever happened to me because I had no idea why I was in space and why there was no gravity.
And I looked around, I'm like, what?
I'm going to...
My ship's down there.
I'm going to die.
And then I fell back down.
Yeah.
Okay.
And it's funny because like if you leave your ship on an island, sometimes you can see like your ship's like location.
If the island that it's on gets blasted up, you can just see like, oh, it's like six kilometers away now.
Oh, and it's falling.
That is...
Yeah, that makes sense.
I was talking to...
I don't remember any of the astronauts' names, but I was talking to the astronaut on that planet.
I think that's Gabbro on that one.
That sounds right.
Yeah, I was talking to Gabbro and it had happened before.
So like I knew that sometimes I just ended up in space and I didn't understand why.
But I was talking to Gabbro and I hear like a rushing sound start and I'm like, oh shit, it's coming.
And then it happens and it's like, and suddenly I'm in space and Gabbro just like floats off of his hammock.
Yeah.
And he's just floats and then I'm like, I can't talk to him anymore.
He's too far away, but I don't want to like jump because I'll like, I'll end up in space.
Yeah.
And a couple seconds later, it like crashes down and he fell back into the hammock and I'm like, okay, we can proceed as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he doesn't even remark upon it.
Yeah, he's just like, he's very used to it.
All the astronauts are so...
I know this is kind of the point, but they're all just like so comfortable in these like fucking unnerving and like scary situations.
They're all just hanging out, playing harmonica.
All of these planets and places are like extremely beautiful and like the sound design is really immersive,
especially with all the like, you know, when you put your helmet on, you can hear yourself breathing when you're in space.
You can only hear yourself breathing and stuff like that.
And it makes it extremely scary when you're going into the unknown and you don't know what's happening.
And then there's the familiar like, oh, you can roast a marshmallow around a little campfire every so often.
It's really nice.
Haven't roasted a marshmallow since like the very first time I booted the game up.
I've only did that once.
I gotta say I was pretty disappointed the first time I like jumped in my ship and like chased down that blue thing.
You know what I mean?
That the rocket, the rocket blows up and it throws that little blue thing.
Oh, yes.
I found it and I'm like, yes, I found it.
Oh, like the whole game, every time you start, you see this rocket explode and this blue thing fires out and I'm like, well, I gotta catch it.
And it's quite hard to find it because you can't like, you can't autopilot lock onto it.
So I really had to finesse it, but I finally got it.
And then I'm just like, oh, it doesn't do anything.
I don't know what it is.
It's interesting because I've always seen that and I always thought like it's probably going way too fast and I can't click on it.
I can't like track it.
Well, it is going fast.
So I didn't even try.
I didn't even try to find them.
Well, sometimes I noticed that sometimes it shoots out with a trajectory that brings it closer to shit.
What's the home planet called?
Timberhearth?
Timberhearth, yeah.
Well, sometimes it fires out and it like kind of passes near Timberhearth and it looks bigger.
And I'm like, no, it's a thing in space.
Like you can, I think I could catch it theoretically and yeah, you can, but it just doesn't really do anything.
It's very easy.
It's very easy to overshoot it.
Oh man, to me at this moment, the ultimate boss of the game is landing on the fucking sun station.
I tried like seven or eight times to land on the sun station and it's hard.
That, yeah.
I'd never tried it that way.
I'm sure it can be done.
I'm sure it can as well.
It is just, it's a little toasty over there.
It's a little toasty and like you can't get that close to the sun without it pulling you in.
So like in theory, you need to one shot it and I think it would work out fine if you like,
if you sort of got near ish to the sun and sort of started accelerating towards it and you kind of like move to the side and you sort of built up like
side angular momentum.
So you were sort of orbiting the sun at kind of the same rate that the station was.
I think that would make it easier.
It's just, it's very hard to do that because the way that the controls work,
to match the speed of the sun, it kind of automatically kills your angular momentum.
Yes, it's to match the speed of the sun orbiting around itself.
So you just sort of step and start being pulled towards it.
Yeah, you can.
You have to do it totally manually if you want to do that.
Yeah, you have to do it totally manually.
And I try to do it and it's either I like lose my angular momentum and I just fall into the sun or I like go too far in sort of trying to build up angular momentum.
And I end up sort of like shooting past the sun and sort of like a comet like, you know, my orbit goes way wide to one side and then I have to like get close again.
So I have not managed to land on the goddamn sun station.
I'm sure I will have to go there at some point, but it's really hard.
Yeah, I think you can go everywhere.
I think I don't think there's anywhere that's like impossible to get to.
Yeah, some places are difficult to get to if you wait too long.
Yeah, because the, I mean, on Ember Twin, you mean on Ember Twin, I think there's one or trying to say there's a few things.
Okay, okay.
I still have no idea what's going on, unlike the inside of Ash Twin.
I thought that the supernova was coming from Ash Twin.
Like I thought that like when the ash all drains off, whatever was down at the bottom of Ash Twin is what is like exploding.
But no, it's the it's the sun going supernova.
And when the ash all drains off, I can see it's funny.
In the minds on Timber Hearth, you can read notes about how they're mining the ore to, you know, build the shell around whatever is on Ash Twin.
Yeah.
And it's made of the same like starry looking rock.
And it's like, oh yeah, they really did it.
So yeah, it drains off and it's just like some kind of rock shell around whatever it is.
And like, I don't know. I don't know what's going on with that.
And there must be a way to get inside, but I don't know what it is.
Yeah, been on the quantum moon.
I think what I have to do is I have to go back to the quantum moon and I have to turn the lights off and let that move the station around or something.
Gotta do something with that.
Assume that will bring me to the eye of the universe, whatever that is.
So that's that's probably next on next on my to-do list.
What have you seen about Brittle Hollow?
Oh, Brittle Hollow.
Oh, well, I've been to the Hanging City.
Actually, that was one of the last things that I found the last time I played was, yeah, I had to wait until the tower fell through the black hole and then find it out in space near the white hole.
And that happens right at the end.
Once it goes through, you have like a minute to go and find the tower and learn the last quantum lesson or whatever.
I know there's the Hanging City.
I've been there a little bit.
I think I have more to explore there.
I've jumped through some of the rings that like teleport you through the tractor beams.
Other than that, I found the guy.
I found the astronaut on Brittle Hollow.
I think I haven't really explored Brittle Hollow very thoroughly, to be honest.
I think I need to get there like early and find some stuff there before it falls through the hole.
It's interesting that I've noticed the meteors from the little moon.
Yeah, the Hollow Lantern.
They destroy things kind of randomly.
So like sometimes a bridge that's useful to get to the Hanging City will fall immediately and you have to find the long way around.
But other times it will fall much later.
Yeah, I know that pieces of Brittle Hollow just kind of fall into the black hole.
I did notice that the lantern kind of throws meteors down onto it.
I thought there might be some connection like the meteors break pieces off, but I wasn't sure.
If you shoot your probe onto a piece of land, it'll tell you how close it is to falling.
Yeah, the structural integrity or something.
I did do that with the tower and I saw that structural integrity was getting lower and lower as it got closer to falling.
That's annoying.
That's annoying that pieces just fall.
Oh, it was on Ember Twin that I went and I found the, I think it's called the Gravity Cannon, the thing that shoots the probe out.
Gravity Cannon?
Yeah, it's like a big mesh tube looking structure.
Oh, right, like a launch pad thing.
Yeah, like I went down there just to see what it was about and I was like, okay, it does a little probe thing and it shoots the probe thing out.
Okay, gotcha.
And then right behind it, there's like a sign that's like Sunless City this way, but there's just like a cactus in the way.
And it's like, I cannot, it's an impassable obstacle.
Unfortunately, the Sunless City is blocked by a cactus, so.
Gotta go the long way around.
Oh well.
I'm trying to think, I'm trying to think what else I've discovered.
Oh, I mean, I found the dark bramble seed on Timber Hearth.
It took me many times visiting it before I had, you know what, I think it was while I was reading how do I solve the frickin' quantum puzzle.
I think something in there jogged me to try shooting the probe into the dark bramble seed and then I'm like, oh, okay, gotcha, gotcha.
So now I have to go back and I have to try that again in the, what are the aliens called?
Like the old?
The Nomai.
The Nomai grave.
I have to go back and I have to try it at the dark bramble seed at the Nomai grave.
Because I know there's like a bunch of different seeds that have the same.
Well that seed on Timber Hearth has the harmonica sounds coming out of it.
Because I guess it connects to a place near where, what's his name is playing, the harmonica.
And there's some other sound coming out of the seed that the Nomai grave is around.
And I guess it's because it's near their ship, like it connects to a seed that landed near their ship.
So I have to investigate that.
Oh, I went to, like the first thing I did, I think like the very first thing I did was I landed on the interloper.
Oh, the comet?
Yeah, because I saw the comet was going by and I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, there's a comet?
Like that's weird.
All these planets look boring.
You can check out this comet.
I should like maybe go back and investigate it again because yeah, that was the first thing I landed on.
And I found, oh, I found the ship like frozen on the far side of it.
And I don't really remember, I remember there was cryptic messages.
I don't really remember what they said.
Later, I think it's on the quantum moon?
No, in one of the gravity cannons, either there's one on Timber Hearth and one on Brittle Hollow.
In one of them, you can like recall that probe from the interloper.
Yes, and then you can go inside.
Yes, and I did that.
So I found it on the interloper and then later I used the gravity cannon and I summoned it.
And I don't know, I don't think I found anything else on the interloper, but maybe I should check it out again.
What a game.
I'm glad you like it.
I like it a lot.
Yeah, it's really cool.
How'd you rate the space travel?
Space travel is, it can be a little annoying, but when it's annoying, it's usually like my own fault.
Like it's my fault that I decided to spend a long time trying and failing to land on the sun station.
It's my fault that I spend a long time trying to catch up to that stupid little blue thing.
Game didn't make me do that, so I can't hold it against the game.
But oh my God, I think like there was one time I crashed into something.
I think it might have been like pieces around the white hole.
And it disabled my autopilot and it disabled some of my thrusters.
So like I was no longer able to like fly straight.
And that sucks so bad.
Have you ever tried to like get out of your ship in the middle of space and like repair it and then get back in?
Yes, I think that is what I ended up doing that time.
It's very annoying.
Sometimes I'll like get out and then I'll have to like be like, shit, I can't find where I'm supposed to repair.
And then I have to go inside, sit down at the cockpit, look at the like ship diagram to see like where is the damage.
Then like, okay, I'm gonna go back outside.
You know what I haven't tried to do? I have not tried to leave the ship in like an inhospitable environment without my suit on.
I assume I would die.
I haven't tried to do it.
I mean you'd die if you can't breathe, if there's no oxygen.
If I like went out in space and I didn't put my suit on and I opened the hatch, would I like die instantly? Would I get sucked out?
You wouldn't get sucked out. I think you would. I've seen it happen.
Actually, I don't, I think I must have done it once because I was getting frustrated with this thing like, oh, fucking.
I think it was probably in between trying to get into the city quickly and I'm like, okay, go, go, go, go, go, land, land, land, land, get out.
Oh, I didn't put my suit on. You just sort of walk around for a bit and you can hear him like struggling to breathe and then his eyes close.
I assume it varies based on which planet you're on. Maybe some of them you die faster than others.
Maybe. I wouldn't want to try it because it's so morbid.
Yeah, it's funny. So many of the planets have trees that give you oxygen.
Most of them have at least some place where like trees have successfully grown and there's oxygen that you can breathe, which is surprising.
But it's okay. I can suspend my disbelief about that.
Yeah, it's just sort of like an easy respite sort of moment.
Yeah, because sometimes like you're traveling on a planet and you have to be away from your ship for a long time, there's no oxygen.
So you will just run out unless there's a little place where you can rest and get some more.
Yeah, when I was finding, I was following the Nomai like writing towards the Sunless City and there's the little like part where they're like, there's trees over here.
Like you can go refill your air over here, but like be quick about it because like the sand is falling and it's like, yeah, it's true.
I'm trying to think. I know that like the Nomai all really want, they want to find the eye of the universe.
I don't know why. I don't know like what it's supposed to do, just that like they all, they seem to want it.
Yeah, there's hints around in some things that it's just sort of like they're a very curious race.
And they found this amazingly impossible thing. So like, we got to find this and sort of like I get it.
A parallel to you as the player being an explorer.
Yeah, and I know, and I know, yeah, I know the Quantum Moon goes there. It's the sixth location.
I made myself Sapa playing it for a little while because I wanted to work on my stupid video some more.
So that's why I have unexplored territory.
No, it's a great game. I'm glad you recommended it to me. It's really awesome.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
When you finish it, I'd love to talk a little more in-depth about like things because I'm holding my breath and being like, ah, ah, I can't say anything.
So I assume the end is when I reach the eye of the universe. I guess I'll know when I, you seem to know like there's a definitive end.
So I assume I will also eventually know what the end is.
There's technically like three or four endings, but they're not like obvious as endings.
They're just sort of like, when you find the ending, it's very obvious that it's the end.
Yeah, okay.
Now, I definitely haven't noticed that.
Yeah, the whole like, it's surprisingly, you know, it's nice that they give you a little, you know, a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit
They give you autopilot options and they give you the like match speed options.
Without those, it would be so annoying.
The match speed is what I like using the autopilot I found doesn't know when to start slowing down properly.
If like the if the thing is like, if if I'm clicking on dark brown below something and it's like going away from me or if it's coming towards me, it'll be sort of the autopilot would like stop at the same time every time.
And so it wouldn't always work.
Yeah, just do manual.
I kind of like how it controls manually.
It's sort of an enjoyable experience.
And if everything's going all like tits up, I just press the A button until I'm like in lockstep with the thing going around the sun.
I like and get my bearings.
The match speed button is basically the like if you're on a planet, it's basically like the stop moving button.
Yeah, like if you're if I don't know if you're getting tossed around like a rag doll or something.
Match speed is like just slow down, make everything stop spinning.
Yeah, autopilot can fuck you over.
Like I did end up falling into the sun a couple of times because the autopilot because the sun just happened to be between me and whatever I was.
Yes, yes.
That's the sort of thing it does.
It's like a mile.
Oh, the thing you want to get to is straight through the suns as crow flies as the space crow.
It can it can it can it can just put you in the sun.
It can.
Yeah, it can sort of undercompensate for like the fact that like the thing is already coming at you.
If it can it sort of fails to account for like like like like the twins are orbiting each other.
So like you'll match one, but like the other one will still be kind of like spinning around.
It'll be spinning around like like bonk you on the head.
Yeah, yeah.
I use the autopilot if I'm like really far away from something.
Like I think I was out by like the white hole and I'm like, okay, well, I want to go to Brittle Hollow and like, okay, well, it's right there.
So I don't want to like fly there myself.
So I use the autopilot and I went and I took a pee.
I was mostly there by the time I came back.
Yes.
So sometimes it works.
Uh, yeah, but when you when you described it, I thought there was like a lot of like, okay, you really got to like align your trajectories and like not really the the game.
The game pretty much gives you the option to there's basically an align trajectories button, which just makes it pretty painless.
So it's a lot of fun though.
It is I I've I think without like all of the cool gravity stuff and the space flight, it would it would be a little more like run of the mill.
Yeah, something or other all of the all of the cool space, you know, the quantum stuff and the the gravity and the sort of the spherical planets that you can just walk along and you can just it feels weird that
the sun is so big and feels so close, but you actually fly there and it's a lot further away, even though it's not as far away as it really should be.
Yeah.
But it's like it's it's it's like you can just sit on the on a planet and just watch stuff happening.
And it's like, wow.
Yeah, you just watch you can just watch the Adler rock like go between you and the sun.
And it's like, oh, yeah, the shadow on you as it flies past.
Yeah, you can you can win like.
When like, yeah, you can see like it goes from day to night because like the planet occludes the sun.
It's like, oh, yeah.
Hmm.
Celestial phenomena.
There they go.
So cool.
Made me I don't know.
I saw a an article on I think it was on Twitter about how like I guess they proved.
Oh, they proved some quantum shit recently.
They proved what is it that like the universe is not quote unquote locally real.
Now that sounds interesting.
What does that mean?
It I I was very frustrated because the article explaining it only let me read the first bit and then it was pay walled.
So I didn't get I didn't get to read the full explanation near as I can tell it.
I think they like they prove they experimentally confirmed Bell's theorem and it's something about quantum entanglement and like basically like the the fact that like a wave form is not collapsed until it is observed and something something quantum entanglement like there were predictions made based on that and they have like experimentally verified like yes, the predictions were accurate.
Entanglement is real.
The wave form fucking weird.
Yeah.
It's like like I obviously have not looked into quantum physics any with any like real depth.
Just the the the you know the sentence something doesn't really exist in any like like measure like unless it's observed isn't really exist or yeah you can't it doesn't act the way it would unless you're looking at it.
Well, what?
Yeah, my mind but I mean but I mean it's only it's only at like it's only at quantum scales that that is like ever really true though.
It's just so funny like it seems like magic that if you if there's an eyeball on it it's doing something different as soon as you look away.
Well, it's you know it sounds really spooky and like it would be spooky if it were if it were like acting that way at like macroscopic scales like on like everyday objects that we experience but like.
The fact that it only the fact that like quantum phenomena is only happening at like you know angstrom scale things of that size 10 to the negative 10 meters meters wide it's like.
What's what's even going on with that shit anyway you know like stuff stuff that size is like so far out of our experience that like oh it acts weird like oh it acts spooky like well.
What else is new I don't know it's it's all it's already like fucking fucking bizarre.
You know sure you know it's just it's just I don't know what observing how that acts on something to make it.
Yeah different yeah there's um I was always a little confused about that like what like what counts as observing.
Like you take a picture of it or you get video like some sort of interference that you can measure in some way.
Like oh like waveforms you can see this or that.
I think I tried to I think I tried to ask a professor or to this about this in college and I never really got.
I mean I'm not sure if I never got a satisfactory explanation or maybe I just never understood the explanation properly but like.
It's it's it's a yeah like like like okay does it's not it's not about like human understanding right it's not the fact that like a human understands.
The state of a of a of a of a pot particle that like collapses its waveform.
I think it's about like its interactions with other things like if it if it passes through like a wire loop and it creates an electric current by doing so like that is the sort of event that like collapses its waveform and like confirms what state it was in.
I think I think it's like it's only after the fact do you know what it was doing.
Something yeah well it was well it was not doing it was not it was neither doing that nor not doing it before it was in a superposition of doing it and not doing it until it happens and then an observable effect occurs you know it it creates the current.
And then it's like okay.
But you know it just sort of it makes me feel like it's on some level existence is like as a personality and it just decides certain yeah it.
I don't know if I don't know because to me I guess what I always wondered was like hang on.
If it's just about like if like if a particle can have an interaction with like other particles.
Or it can have an interaction with its environment and it's that interaction that like causes it to collapse its waveform.
Then like surely it's interacting with with its environment all the time right like every particle with mass is having a gravitational effect.
Or any particle with charge is having an electromagnetic effect and they're like shouldn't ever isn't every particle constantly interacting with every other particle by like these.
These forces so like why why isn't everything's waveform collapsing all the time because like to charge particles are constantly you know affecting one another's trajectories.
So I never I never quite got it.
Yeah commenter commenter commenters please explain the quantum quantum entanglement to me is it like this was a question I never I never quite understood how this worked.
Is it like they don't exist in the same way in time that we experience like time linearly.
Do you know about them.
Oh fuck.
Shit what are they called.
Hang on.
Like it's very obviously different from Schrodinger's cat like always the cat alive or dead.
Well the cat is alive or dead.
It's just that we don't know the quantum is like it was neither or is neither until you look at it.
It could be both.
Damn it fuck what are the I'm okay the double slit experiment.
Yeah the double slit experiment is the experiment.
They shoot electrons through and they can they observe it being in two places at once.
Well it was photons.
It was photons first and then was it was it the bell.
Basically yeah you shoot the photons through the double slit experiment and they give a pattern the result of photons going through the double slit gives a wave pattern that but that was expected because we knew that wave the photons and light had a wave formation.
The spooky thing was then they tried it with electrons and they found the same wave form and it's like well what the fuck why is that happening.
And the reason why is because the electrons are also waves but they're waves of probability.
And it's it's it's not it's not like like the light the light has a wave pattern of amplitudes that was constructively and destructively interfering with itself.
The electrons had the same thing but it's not about their amplitude and like their intensity or whatever it's about their the probability of where they are which was like the what what the fuck is that.
I just don't get it.
I mean it's it's it's elementary it's simple it's it's literally just this it's literally just that a particle does not have a location.
What it has instead is a wave in space and that wave represents where it is likely to be and when you measure its location it will be somewhere and that wave defines where it is likely to be.
But it's but it but until it's measured it exists across the entire wave.
So it's like it's like a big old cloud of electron but when you take a picture of it it's just a tiny dot on one part of the image.
Yes yes yes yes it becomes the dot after you take the picture but before that it was smeared it was smeared across space in a probability distribution.
See what that implies to me is that like it is not like traveling through time the same way like it like it's at any one amount of time or whatever it's in all places.
Why is it why is a measure and a measurement is just a single number.
It's like it's not it's not all places it is it's in a superposition of all places you fool completely different.
Well hey whatever at least I didn't need to look up the quantum stuff in outer while the Davison it was the Davison experiment I think is what they called when they fire the electrons at the double slit and no young's was young's experiment that was like.
They observed oh the same sort of wave phenomena as a photon but with electrons.
Shit I was gonna say something I was oh you ever seen.
You ever seen okay you know about you know Adams they draw them with like oh it looks like a solar system there's the nucleus at the middle and then there's the orbiting electrons around but you know that's not really what they look like.
Yeah that's the illustration for the explanation.
But the the the electron is just sort of like like a big C cloud of charge and it's and like the reason why you know you look at those those you look at those freaking like graphs and they have all these like weird crazy like lumpy shapes you know what I mean.
Hang on hang on I think they're called valence clouds I think I saw a YouTube video trying to explain why orbital electrons do that.
They have I mean something like this like fucking my internet is being weird again there yeah yeah yeah.
Yes I think I did see like a YouTube video trying to like express these things in like 3D modeling to make it more understandable I don't remember who did that and I can't think it made sense to me but well I've seen these before.
Okay you ever all right you know how if you hold a rope at two ends and you shake it you can get it to like do you know what I'm talking about if I say like a harmonic.
Like well you know what you're well you know about music you know about like how a how a string and you know about how it can vibrate a different harmonics right like it can vibrate.
Is that different from frequencies.
It's related.
Like I know that on a single guitar string there are like different sounds that make up a single note.
Yes like I think harmonics.
Yes well you can you can have well you can you can shake the same string you can shake it at different frequencies but only at a limited number of frequencies and that represents like the different.
It's the same note at different octaves.
Look at look at look at this image behold behold this image you know what I'm looking yes you can shake a string.
And you can you can you can shake the string and you can shake it so that it like the wave in the string is like fat in one spot or two spots or three spots.
Why not for.
Well you could do for to but the point is you can't you can't have a fraction right you can't have you can't have two and a half you can't have one and a half.
It has to be like a whole number has to end at the same spot.
Yes yes yes yes that it yeah okay well all right so like that's that's true of like waves on a string it's also true of like electron position probability waves.
So this is this this image right here this is like the theoretically most simplistic model for what's for solving the Schrodinger equation is imagine you had an electron that could only exist in one dimension like in a straight line and you put it in a box with infinite potential energy on both sides.
And it could only travel like in one direction up and down in the straight line inside of this box and it can't go outside these these walls.
And if you put an elective theoretically if you put an electron in that situation it has to bounce between these walls and it bounces in in these harmonics like it has like depending on how much energy you give it it has these same wave patterns it has like one one wave or two or two wave or three wave and it has to have a whole number.
Just like waves on a string and that wave is like its position it's the superposition of its of where it might be if you measure its position.
And it and it the reason why the electron cloud around these hydrogen wave functions these atomic orbitals the reason why an atom looks all weird and lumpy like these hydrogen waves is because.
I mean if you take that box and you just make it a sphere you make it a spherical well.
It just when you when you solve for those wave shapes and you put it in a spherical well as in the case of an electron orbiting around a an atom that it is electromagnetically attracted to just when you solve for the wave shapes they look like this they look like these weird like.
Curvy lumpy lines and that's why atoms are all weird and lumpy looking that's why they have weird clouds around them.
I I so you see it I mean I mean just imagine this okay you you you pluck a string and it and it shakes and it has waves in it right.
Well now take that string and instead of being a straight line curve it around so it's a loop.
And then a ring yes and then imagine imagine like twanging it so it's vibrating.
And now the and now the waves are like going around the loop in a circular pattern.
And then now imagine you okay well instead of just a one dimensional string around a circle make it three dimensional make it a spherical membrane and then you like twang it and it vibrates right and now the waves are in 3D but they still have to like.
They have to follow you know the shape of the membrane and I mean that's basically what's going on with electrons orbiting.
Yes basically I mean more or less yeah I mean well then I'm stuck on like imagining twanging a spherical objects that waves like where does it start and end.
Well did you ever in gym class did you ever play with like that big like parachute.
Yeah I mean you can imagine I mean it's hard to it would be difficult to like solve the wave function but you can imagine like a three dimensional or a two dimensional membrane like kind of wiggling and vibrating right in sort of the same way as a string does.
Like if I take a ruler and I held it at both ends and you know like a plastic ruler and I can bend it down and up that's like a wave form.
Right you I'm trying to imagine it because I can't I can't do it in 3D.
I mean I mean yeah you can't it's hard to like really get like a clear image of like exactly what it looks like because it you know wave form goes up and down.
And there are two like on this diagram here with the ends there are two ends to it but on a sphere where do the ends go.
Well I mean what's what's the beginning and the end of the wave does it all just shrink and grow like it just vibrates up and like the entire thing gets smaller and bigger.
I think it probably looks something like I mean you know when you're blowing bubbles right.
You ever make like a big bubble and like you form the bubble and it's kind of like wiggling.
Sure yeah yeah I mean I think it would probably look like that.
Okay the surface of the bubble is just kind of wiggling.
Is this what it was like being taught by Ben St.
I guess.
I guess so probably that's why I got fired.
Mr. St. I'm fucking I hate science I don't get it.
Just just imagine just picture the wiggling bubble just just think just picture the form the bubble in your mind now make the surface wiggle now solve Schrodinger's equation.
Everybody get out your bubble blowing equipment.
That would have been a cool thing if a science teacher came out it's like all right here's an atom he blows a bubble and everyone was like oh look at that.
I mean I mean I never had it explained to me that way I'm just I'm just trying to think like how I think about it and I mean that seems like a.
When I that makes sense to me to explain it that way I mean it's the reality is more complicated because in addition because what do you say.
The electron does not actually exist in a two dimensional spherical membrane it can also move in and out so it's actually like a three dimensional cloud shape right.
But I mean you imagine going from a one dimensional string to a two dimensional spherical membrane and it's like OK that's one step and then if you wanted to make it even more complicated then you would.
Excess not exacerbate not elaborate extrapolate you know extrapolate than one more dimension into a three dimensional spherical well.
Three dimensional I thought the bubble is three dimensional.
Yeah I mean it is because it's in.
OK OK but that's curved yeah but imagine if.
When I say three dimensional like.
OK but but if you're imagining the bubble the bubble then it's only a 2D or it's a flat plane even though it's curved.
But I mean the the the atom the electron is not limited to just traveling along you know a spherical surface it can also go in and out.
You ever see.
You ever see like a like a.
Like a picture of space and then there and it's like a grid and you put like.
An object.
Yeah and it forms like a like a pit like it falls into a hole.
You know what I mean yeah.
Like a black hole.
Gravity.
Yeah curves space time around itself.
Yeah well I mean that's just that's like a two dimensional representation.
But like actually the gravity is not in 2D it's in 3D.
Like the curve is more complicated than just the flat plane.
So it's like that it's like there's there's we're representing it in 2D.
But actually there's a third dimension.
But it's just it's just hard it's like too hard to visualize.
Nods.
Nods to self.
Outer wilds.
Outer wilds baby.
So what I'm saying so what I'm saying is that if you stand on top of an electron and you turn your flashlight off.
When you turn it back on you'll be somewhere else.
You'll be on the other side of the atom.
True.
Yeah I.
I think I think I've made a lot of product.
I think I played it for about a week.
I've been playing it on and off for about a week and change.
And I haven't played it in a few days because I've been crunching on my stupid video.
But as soon as the video is done I'll probably jump back into that and finish up.
Some more stuff.
Can't wait.
Yeah.
I should have had the video done by now.
But it's becoming it's becoming more and more torturous to work on it.
I hate it more and more every time.
So I'm dealing with that.
You know what's the worst part about it is the audio levels.
Because I was talking into the microphone.
So there is times when I'm not talking as directly into the microphone and I.
I've been going through the clips and I try to adjust the audio a bit here and there to like make the quiet parts louder and the loud parts quieter and just try and.
Keep it as even as I can.
And there's parts where it gets really finicky and like I have to make adjustments like every few seconds.
Parts weren't that like compressing the audio.
Compressing helped.
Compressing helped but it didn't like.
There's still I mean imagine me standing in front of a whiteboard and I'm talking at the camera and I'm speaking into the microphone.
And then I turn around to look at the board and now I'm not speaking into the mic anymore.
And now it's like quiet and muted.
And then I turn back around and I start speaking to the mic again and then back and I look away and then back and I look towards it.
And there's parts where like I'm doing that for a while and every time that happens like I try to like OK I'm going to try and boost the.
Boost the quiet part boost the quiet part and I'll have to cut it up into pieces.
I don't know maybe there's a more efficient way to do it.
But I'm like I did compress and normalize the audio and it did help and it made it more listenable.
But there's still parts that like benefit from a little manual boosting here and there.
It's just tedious.
Yeah.
I think.
You know when you're doing a long video.
Like that.
Yeah.
I mean this is just me.
But I would just I would do as little touching up as I could.
If my if I'm literally unintelligible then I should I would go in.
Maybe like add text if it's like the mic just cut out or just really just can't hear me.
But like going through like a multi hour thing micromanaging the levels.
Yeah.
That's a lot.
There's there's debt there's definitely diminishing returns and I'm trying I'm trying not to get too hung up on it because like no matter.
Yeah.
No matter how long I spend on it it'll it'll never be perfect.
But at the same time like when I hear a part that like oh I'm like noticeably choir at this quieter at this part.
I'm like I don't want I don't want that.
Yeah.
I've been I've been I don't know I've been sinking time into doing that.
Also there's.
Damn there's like there's there's parts where I'm like OK I want to show something on screen.
But like again there's diminishing returns there's like if I wanted to I could I could be putting up like images on screen like all the time I could be like constantly showing something and taking it off.
And I've read I think yesterday I was like.
I gotta stop like I gotta I gotta not I don't need I don't need to show some every time I mentioned something it's OK to just show it one time.
And then just leave it.
I was thinking about like putting up screenshots of the of the of well I don't want to say what I almost I almost spoiled it.
But I was thinking about putting up screenshots of some particular thing and lots and lots of examples of this particular thing.
And I know I can't I can't let myself do it.
It would be if I if I if I did that I would have to do more.
So I gotta I gotta call it at some point.
I gotta call it like no that's enough.
I have yeah I have I passed the six hour mark of like edited completed stuff yesterday.
Yeah I have six hours that are basically done.
Like I'll need to like give it a final listen through and like see if I have anything that's like fucked up and needs tweaking.
But theoretically six hours of it are done and there are like a little less than two hours left to go.
I had to add a bit big three or four minute like explanation of something.
So I keep adding little bits of explanation that are making it a little bit longer and a little bit longer.
It's not looking like it's going to hit eight hours.
I would be over I would be happy if it hit eight hours but I don't think it will.
I feel terrible.
I mean six hours of edited content.
Yeah it's a lot of work.
You're getting through it.
It's taken me more than a month now.
I didn't I didn't anticipate spending more than a month just on the editing but I have and you know what it's OK.
It's fine.
You know what without.
I don't I don't want to say it.
I don't want to say it because it'll spoil it.
I guess I'll just say I realized the thing that the lecture is about.
There's not too long before I think it will have a little bit of a resurgence.
I have there's there's reason to believe that like in the not too distant future this thing is going to see coverage mainstream media coverage.
And I think about that and I'm like wouldn't it be amazing if the video did well.
And then there's like a big like media sort of surge around it and that and it's positioned at that time to get like a ton more views based on that and like I could see that happening.
And that is like I got I got to keep going.
I got I got to push through.
I got to have the video out the sooner I have the video out the more likely that is to happen.
And I want to have the video out then the longer you will have to never work on it.
That's true.
There's two good reasons one the sooner it's out the sooner it can start accumulating views and the more views it will have by the day.
The time that it stands to maybe gain a little bit of mainstream media reflected limelight so to speak.
So like getting it out sooner is is strategically optimal for that reason.
Also I just want it to be done.
I want the nightmare to end.
So you know there's two excellent reasons.
Two excellent reasons.
I've definitely slowed down.
I've definitely been struggling to like continue to force myself to look at it just on an emotional level.
It's becoming harder and harder to keep going.
I'm trying to fight through it.
I get my week was yeah my week was not very productive at all.
I had a bit of a at a bit of a depression moment and I sort of didn't do anything.
But more recently like last few days I think it's it's the difficulty of like giving myself praise for the things that I do well.
I saw you tweet something about like praising yourself through gritted teeth.
Yeah like like when I do something well it's it's never like oh good it's like about time you did that you took too long.
Like that's my first thought.
And when I do something bad it's like oh that's expected because you suck.
It's just sort of like negative one way or the other.
If you do down if you don't sort of thing.
I've mentioned it before but I had that I had that thermodynamics professor who was like a Buddhist and he told us like when you solve a physics problem you know take the time.
Feel good about it.
Let yourself feel good about it.
Yeah it's it's it's a very important thing.
I've been trying to like give myself praise for like the small things that I managed to do.
And it's really hard.
So I hope you do that.
I hope you feel good about what you are accomplishing.
I you know the fact that it has been more and more of a struggle has made it been like the slower progress goes.
The more like I can look back and be like I accomplished more a week ago than last week than I did this week.
You know.
It looks worse and worse in comparison the slower it goes so it's becoming harder and harder to feel good about it because like the first week I'm like oh yeah.
I did it like three hours of it.
That's like almost half done and then two weeks later I'm like oh it took me like almost three weeks to get another three hours.
You know.
I do know but I also know that it's it's probably not helping things to to to increase like the negative feelings you have towards yourself and it the longer it goes.
Yeah I am.
I'm a little concerned actually that like part of the reason it has gone slower and slower is maybe I've what if I've become more and more like stringent about like.
What audio blips I need to correct and like how much.
Visual info I need to add and therefore I will get slower and slower as I'm doing it and then I will be like OK done now to go back and give it a final listen and then I'll realize oh the the early part.
I didn't do as much work on as the later part and now the early part feels sloppy and I need to.
Correct some more.
To just to make it that go I think you gotta let that go just because of the extreme length of the video that's always going to happen.
Yeah it's like like an artist drawing a comic the early pages are going to look worse than the most recent ones that's.
Are they going to go back and redo everything every time they increase increase in skill.
Yeah.
Or learn a different way of doing things.
No I think I think that's probably true.
It's OK if it's not completely like buttery smooth consistent all the way through.
There have there have definitely been points recently where I've needed to add like kind of a lot of like additional info but I think there's a reason for that.
I think I think it's I think it's justifiable based on the material that I'm talking about that's not like.
My standards change that's like OK no this this part requires further elaboration in a way that previous parts did not so like I'm OK with that.
Yeah.
Working.
Working working just working.
Just working.
Maybe this week I know I sound like a broken record but maybe this week it'll be done.
I say that every week.
Is it is a catchphrase.
My old catchphrase was end of the month.
That was when I was talking about what I used to do like endless war coding stuff I would always say oh yeah this feature will be done by the end of the month.
That was a bit of a meme.
I have no idea when things I used to have that with like.
I mean it's just making a deadline and being like I could probably do that and then realizing you can't and then feeling bad about.
And it's a yeah sucks.
I don't have much to say on it really well.
It's just hard to know exactly like what is what is the perfect deadline.
Is it a good or a bad thing to expect yourself to get something done by a certain point or not.
Is it is it motivational or is it purely destructive.
I think if you have no deadlines at all you'll never you'll never get anything done.
I think it's probably OK to have it's probably better to have deadlines and fail to meet them because most of the time at least in pursuing that deadline even if you fail to meet it.
Usually you'll at least have done something that the deadline will have made something happen.
If not then I mean that's bad.
Yeah I mean for me the thing with the giving myself praise is like it's sort of like a way to get out of like because if if I let myself feel bad for long enough it will come down to like well you're certain years old and you could have been so much more if you had only started when you were 12.
And it's sort of like well I can't do anything about that you know sort of like the deadline the feeling of deadline the feeling of having missed the deadline and be feeling bad about it can sort of fully encompass you and make you paralyzed.
I'm like giving yourself praise for like having done something is like a good I don't know like a bit of a boost to continue making progress.
Sure yeah I hope that I get better at stuff and I know that you know things I've made already are good.
But I was just last this this last week just like really critical and then what I just stopped what were you being critical of if you don't mind me asking.
I think it was partly work related like oh I'm so slow some some sort of thing reminded me of feelings of like super inadequacy of being you know I'm too old to be only just now getting stuff done super inadequacy.
Damn that's so that's so much better than my inadequacy.
Yeah give me five seconds to grab a sparkling water.
Okay I'm back.
I forgot exactly.
To you were saying feelings of oh I'm too old to not be.
Yeah yeah like it's something like I've had feelings like that before us like I'm too old.
And I've missed my chance to be good at anything and I was making good progress last week and something tip me I can't really even remember what my mind was doing.
But I just sort of fell into like a depression spiral was like yeah you know what fuck it everything sucks.
And I don't know I think what was most frustrating this time was that I felt like I had the tools necessary to get out of it and I couldn't do it.
It was difficult.
It was like I mean you know what you should be doing in order to not like be falling into that.
Yeah cuz like yeah cuz like I have the therapist down I talked to them you know about once a week and like I had felt better since then and then I was like you know what I think I am capable I think I am capable of getting myself out of these these these moods with tools and like mantras and like helpful little things to remember.
And then it just it collapsed and I just couldn't do it and I'm like what I thought I knew what I was doing.
I thought I had it I thought I was smart now but it was it was not the case.
Well I mean that's just it's always like what does that make me think of like everybody you can even even if you're really good at something.
You can still like sometimes like forget to apply the fundamentals and then you'll fuck up right and everybody happens to everybody.
Yeah I mean I was feeling bad back then right now I'm a little better I'm like yeah I get what my problem was it will happen again it's just sort of like trying to deal with the outcome better.
It's like they say like it certain things just never get better but you get better at dealing with them.
So I'm just sort of hoping that that it's true that I can I can get I can get away from depression faster and faster.
Yeah each time but yeah I don't really have like those are some more personal things in there I don't really want to get into.
Okay that was part of it but yeah it turns out I didn't do anything last week work wise.
I did like one drawing and I put it on my not safe work Twitter and I was like oh that was good.
I did it I did something you're talking about that you're talking about this past week since the last podcast this past week yeah yeah.
I mean yeah you win some you lose some I guess.
I'm trying to think I'm trying to think that I do anything besides fuss over my stupid video avoided avoided my roommates tried to try to avoid becoming responsible for the gas bill.
Oh you know what we could talk about what's that to get away from the depression stuff.
I generated imagery let's have a topic let's have a topic about this.
Yeah I'll say it I don't like how some people talk about it I think there I've seen some bad arguments against it.
And I'm not a fan of it or anything but I've definitely seen some arguments against it that I think are dumb.
Like what like one of mine.
You will you retweeted one that I that I kind of I didn't like disagree with it.
It was it was that Sean tweet Sean said something about.
Oh yeah I thought that was good.
I didn't like it.
I didn't like it because it felt like the argument is that like oh AI makes it too easy and things should be hard and things that are hard are good.
And it felt like it felt like Calvin's dad saying like like struggling builds character.
It wasn't that it was that there are benefits to doing the work like that the the act of making art is fulfilling in and of itself it doesn't like the end product is hyper focused on for the AI quote unquote artist.
They don't care about like the creativity and the fun of creating art they just like when a thing is you know made.
I mean sure and they're missing out is this what I got from that is that the to do AI art is to miss out on most of what makes art fun and good.
I it's I don't even disagree but couldn't you say the same thing about shoveling the walk.
Wouldn't Calvin's dad say the same thing about shoveling the walk though.
Shoveling the walk like the sidewalk.
Well you know that's that's the thing in in in Calvin and Hobbes.
Yeah.
The dad always didn't know I shovel the walk.
Don't remember that turn of phrase.
No well I don't think it's like a it's a building character argument.
Well I think it's just like it's a shame.
It's not it's not the main reason I dislike AI art.
I dislike AI art because the people who do it are shit.
Yeah I don't like it's the bigger deal is that like the AI is made to basically just like.
Thieve data from existing or like you know that guy I for that that artist just died like this past week and like immediately.
Yes we're AI generating stuff that like was like mimicking his his work.
They train an AI by feeding it images from a certain artist.
Yeah so they can then create in the style of the artist more or less.
I mean sometimes it doesn't work but for some artists it really does.
You can steal an artist's entire style and put it into an AI thing.
Yeah and then type their name and then generate things that look just like what they could draw.
I mean I think it I think it's like OK as long as like everybody's clear on like that's what we're doing.
Like like as long as it's like.
Yeah I feel like since the technology exists and it can only get better from here.
It's not like we can stop it existing.
Yeah but like it's the the the people behind doing shitty things are the the thing that make me upset.
Yeah it's the it's people profiteering off of off of it.
It's people that didn't people that didn't actually create anything like someone who just like took that AI.
And maybe they did a little bit of work you know training it on these images or whatever I'm sure that took some effort but then it's like oh yeah now I.
Own this like infinite machine for generating plagiarism of this of infinitely recombining and recombining the work of this artist that just died.
And like whatever I guess if someone wants to do that it's OK.
It's it's what it's like if someone were profiteering off of it that I'd be like that's gross that's horrible stop it.
Yeah it's like I've said on previous weeks it's just the fact that you need money to live and the fact that this can take potential money.
Away from artists is like that that part of it is why it's more horrible than just sort of like cheap like this guy is not the real artist but he makes some some AI generated things but the fact that.
It really can be like a thing that makes people lose money because they can't get commissioned.
I mean it's still hypothetical I haven't actually heard of a situation where that has happened but it's hard to to like pinpoint like an exact amount of lost money.
You can just see it happening like people would if they can if the AI is good and the the artist they steal from is usually expensive they can make whatever they want.
I don't know whether people would pay anyway.
I feel like people would still pay artists just to support them.
You can but it's like if there's an art there's a hypothetical like it will just happen less and that's gross.
I don't know I mean you can you can post like you can pick and choose like AI generated images that like oh this looks good.
Like this this looks kind of like something this someone made or this looks is like a nice image but like.
You can't at least where the technology is now you can't like generate that at will you know what I mean like you can't make you can't make the image you want.
You can make an image that looks good and looks like something that someone might want but getting like the exact thing you want is like.
Hard to impossible unless you're like unless what you want is like I just want something that looks like so and so drew it.
And that's it.
That's the yeah I think that's the most annoying part is the the the prevalence and the sort of common accepted notion among AI artists that to get the best results you really should put somebody somebody's name in there like buy this this artist or buy that artist alongside all of your descriptive things because I've I've I've dabbled just for fun to see what it could do.
And if you don't put an artist in it is a nightmare most of the time because it's drawing from like the entire Internet Google images like photographs like it needs to narrow itself down.
And so it's sort of like that's the way to do the the ones that look good is to like just steal from a good artist so that it's not like pulling from every possible thing that a word could be referring to.
What do you think about when people say like oh well real like like artists copy other artists like like artists artists can like oh yeah I drew this in the style of so and so right like is that is that.
Is that is that is that theft in the same way that like oh I trained this AI on on the art of so and so and it drew it generated an image in the style of him.
I think like legally would only become theft if you portray yourself as being the artist that you're copying and then it would be like a like a litigation thing if you if an AI artist trains an AI to make something that looks like an artist work.
It's it's not illegal.
I don't know but it's a new technology and it's sort of weird I feel like I feel like the technology is just combining elements of isn't isn't isn't that basically just sort of like taking his that person's work.
I don't know I feel like the AI is like directly combining stuff that someone else made into a new thing whereas like if a human being is like interpreting someone's art and trying to recreate it there's like more of a.
You mean recreate it or like use the same style.
I mean like try and try and draw something like create a recreate a style recreate someone's style.
Like this is my this is I'm drawing a new drawing but it's in the style of so and so it's my take on their style.
That's the thing that people do.
I think the difference I would say is that the AI does not need nearly as much time to create an image than it does for a person to draw generally speaking.
So like it's like they're equivalent in a lot of ways but I just don't like the I don't know.
Like if the machine can do it better than the real person.
Yeah like faster and more efficiently they can overtake that person.
I don't know if an artist could like overtake another artist by copying their style.
I guess it's I think I think it's just when it's like a one off thing like oh I did thing in style but if you do like many many many images in another person's style they might feel like you're copying their style and like cramp in their style.
You should maybe stop but that's sort of like a disagreement thing.
It's not really a I don't know.
I don't know how I feel about that usually.
I generally think it's better for anyone to like find their own style.
Yeah not because it's it's not because like for any legal reason it's just sort of like it's lame.
I think it's lame to be copying somebody.
I mean I think that it's probably it's a thing that already happens that like an artist with a popular style a like small like cottage industry might crop up of people like sort of doing art in their style.
Like oh it looks like this.
Oh this is like something that so and so would draw.
I don't know.
I think I think that's already a thing.
I just here's kind of bugs me.
I don't know.
I think that there's a little vein of like effort is good in and of itself.
I think there's a little bit of like labor fetishization going on when people say like oh the AI makes it too easy.
I think that I don't really care too much about that.
I think that if an artist.
I think that if let's let's take considerations of like art theft and plagiarism out of it.
Let's say that that was not a concern if if an artist if someone you could call them an artist or not could take the AI and generate exactly the image that they had in their head just by pressing a button.
I think that that was good.
I would be like it's OK.
It's fine that you didn't have to do any work to make it.
Sure.
Yeah.
Like it's an interesting tool.
It's definitely useful for spitballing ideas for concept art or like coming up with like I wonder how it would look if I did this sort of a thing and then you make some images and you're like yeah this gives me an idea and then you go and make it yourself.
Or even if you don't if you're not an artist you just want to make some cool things.
I think the tool is fine.
I think it has potential to be misused and I think a lot of people are like have no scruples whatsoever and will misuse it as as much as they possibly can for as much gain as they possibly can without consideration for anything.
And they will just go ahead and do that because there's no laws against it.
There's no like restrictions.
Yeah.
So they're just going ham and it sucks because I because I know those people are those those people suck.
I mean I'm pretty much fine with anything that anyone wants to do with it up until it becomes like IP theft.
And then it's at that point it's I'm not exactly sure where that line is.
Yeah.
But there's definitely there's cases that are definitely over it.
And those are bad.
And I don't know exactly how you would like define where that starts exactly.
But it's definitely bad.
You know the worst thing about it is that I tried to make a big booby risk image and you just couldn't do it.
I typed in big boobies huge breasts doesn't work.
All those prompts that have those like Victorian era.
Shit.
Like they have those prompts.
Yeah.
And it's like filled with like a very embarrassing but very funny like a lot of like booby booba beautiful.
Oil painting looking oil painting Renaissance highly realistic anime like they're just a bunch of words.
And I tried doing that because like I'm not going to like pretend I'm an artist for doing it.
What if I can make a really good risk image.
Can it be done.
I wanted to see and I couldn't.
I guess I needed to steal from more specific artists.
I didn't put any artists in.
Look at look at this one.
Jess posted this in my discord and it's really funny.
It's loading.
I looked at this and I didn't realize a spork pointed out that.
Okay what it did here is it confused the boobs for legs.
Oh it did.
Yeah.
If you get rid of the shirt it looks normal.
It looks it kind of looks like legs if you yeah if you crop it out.
And that's actually really interesting.
That's actually like a really interesting trick that the AI played on itself there.
It is like it's very funny when it's like almost good and then it's like freaky.
Wait I want to whenever they have like hands there's always like three fingers or seven fingers.
Look at look at this that Maryweather posted.
This is horrible.
This one's actually really upsetting.
I don't.
Is it is it doing the same thing?
Is it think the boobs are legs?
I don't think so.
No I think it just sort of there's like a crease and I thought there was a belly button.
Yeah.
But then why would they make boobs after that?
I don't.
I don't know.
It's the funniest thing to me is the enemy face looks exactly like things I've seen before.
The face looks totally normal.
Nothing wrong with the face.
And like the legs look totally normal.
The face looks completely normal.
The shoulder is a little weird and it's just the torso just has an extra set of boobs in it.
It's like two rib cages.
That's freaky.
Yeah that one's actually kind of kind of unsettling.
See like the tool is fun.
The tool I mean when everyone was going nuts over like the dolly too.
It's like yeah you can make a weird freaky thing.
Yeah.
It's just this current trend of like certain people trying to sound and be considered more like.
What's the word like official like it's that they're more.
Yeah.
That one that one guy said that it's like AI art is real art because like I had to spend an hour and a half typing prompts into the machine before it made me this picture.
Like great.
It's just sort of an embarrassing like mindset.
It reminds me a lot of NFT artists.
It reminds me a lot of crypto bros.
They're just sort of.
Yeah.
They fetishize.
Them being very smart and good.
They only want to do it through the most easiest possible means.
Yeah.
I mean.
That stuff is really frustrating.
It's not that like doing things in a difficult way.
It makes it more valid.
It's just that it's annoying that I am reminded of these sorts of people.
If something is easier, there exists the temptation for some people to be like, OK, well, now I can take this.
I can take this shortcut.
I can do this thing and it makes me.
I mean.
If if if if something like this if an AI generator like makes it really easy to make art, like I think that's OK.
But I mean, it does mean that, you know, it is a less skilled job.
Like it's true that like if if you can just type a bunch of prompts into a generator and it will generate an image that looks great.
And it's exactly what you want.
Like I don't think it's wrong to do that.
But it's true that like, you know, that that Sean Tweet, he said, like, yeah, the artist will, you know, he will gain skill by doing the work.
He gains skill at the task.
If you don't need to be skilled to do the task because the AI will do it for you, like, well, maybe you just don't need to be that skilled to do it anymore.
But like that's OK, because that just means that technology has made work easier and that's good actually when that happens.
It's good if technology makes stuff more accessible and makes it easier to do things.
We should like that.
You do you do miss out.
You don't get as skilled.
You don't develop as much skill at this thing.
And I mean, that might be negative in its own way.
There might be cases where, boy, I really wish that like I was more skilled as a draftsman so I could just I could create the image that I have in my head.
Because AI is it's not possible with AI for whatever reason.
It's it's it's not a.
I think but it's it's not it's not an evil in and of itself that like.
You can do something that like something becomes possible without.
As much work or skill required.
I agree.
OK, I agree that the tool existing is not a net negative society.
With that strong tweet, I very much focus more on like the.
The like the enjoyment of like the fulfilling nature of creating art by hand.
Yeah, like I or with with like more with more purpose, I suppose.
I feel like I would get like with my limited experience working with AI stuff.
I feel more than anything like frustrated at the computer for not understanding what I'm trying to say.
And like, OK, let me do it.
And then I would draw a little sketch and it wouldn't be as like beautiful and as like detailed and perfectly rendered as a lot of these images that the from artists they're stealing from that these things can generate.
But it is more like true to what I'm looking for.
I feel like it's.
Yeah.
The path of least resistance for me like mentally is to do it myself.
But that's yeah, maybe just because I'm used to that.
Well, that's I mean, that's what is when you're looking at AI stuff.
You can see lots of images that are specific that like look good, but those aren't if you're setting out with a very particular image in mind.
I think it's like.
I don't know if any AI can do that like ever.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe in the future right now it is good for like like spitball and concepts like you want to think of like.
Instead of going to Google search and typing in that sorts of things that you need like inspiration for.
You can generate an image from Google images with those like key words and you can get some like mishmash things and be like, ah, yes.
Like that that's the sort of thing I'm looking for or like no, that's too much like this.
But I'd like this one part of it.
Like it's good for for coming up with ideas.
Is it right now?
I don't get it.
Well, because like if you're finding what I mean is like telling the AI to generate the image, surely you already have kind of you already know like the sort of thing you're looking for.
But you don't know what the AI will come up with because the keywords are always going to be more vague.
Like that.
That's what I mean.
When you have a very specific idea in mind, going to AI and typing prompts in will not get you the image you want perfectly.
It'll be like sort of weird and sort of wrong and sort of like you got to fuck around with the prompts a lot and it'll never be exactly what you're looking for.
It'll be sort of maybe in the ballpark.
But that's that's the benefit of the thing is that if you don't exactly know what you want, but you have some sort of general themes, you can throw those at the AI and they can give you a ballpark estimate of what it might look like.
And you'd be like, yes or no, like you can you can skip the the lengthy process of looking up a bunch of images and seeing if anything grabs your fancy.
That's what I think is the benefit of it.
It's not to create a specific image.
It's to like throw shit at the wall and see if anything's good.
I think it's good for like, I mean, like for something that doesn't require a lot of specificity like a background like like man like manga backgrounds.
I think I think it's like, that's the the most obvious use that comes to my mind, like sort of a lot of time it sort of doesn't matter, like exactly what they look like but like maybe you just need something to and it's like
there's there's there's there's there's artistic applications.
There's there's times when specificity is important and there's times when it's not and in times when specificity is not important.
I feel like AI is probably good and you might as well just fucking generate any old thing.
There's times where that's could be appropriate.
It's so stressful.
Well, just thinking about it.
Yeah.
Time marches on.
It's almost sort of unsettling to think that like it's like a new thing that like might really like change the landscape of anything.
I don't like it.
I don't like landscape changes.
Like I can hypothesize about like how industries might change how art art as a skill will be like, I don't know more difficult to get into or get money from like I don't know.
I feel like it's not quite good enough to like you couldn't animate an entire show with AI.
No.
A lot of skill like you some illustration work you can do but it is still like mostly stealing is the reason why I can do that.
Yeah.
And and you can trace them to the artist that they're stealing from quite easily which is not good.
I feel like at the end of the day, you know, art is still about, you know, an artist expressing a vision that they have.
And like an AI can never have a vision.
It can only borrow and assemble from other stuff.
So like there will never be.
I don't I don't.
I'm I don't like I'm sure that AI will become more and more able to perform more and more tasks.
But there will never be a world where like AI just makes all the art because there will always be.
People need to come up with the ideas right AI can't have ideas.
Not yet.
I'm trying to do I think it will.
I don't know if I don't know.
I don't know if it will ever be able to have ideas in the way that like a human does.
I mean, I don't know enough about the technology of neural networks to, you know, to say with any confidence whether or not it can't do that in the future.
I know it can't right now.
It's very much like it's still gathering data from people like general like AIs of many types rely heavily on on human input.
There's to like learn things.
We're not even we're not even like close.
We're not even anywhere in the ballpark of like an AI that like thinks like a human does.
And I don't know if it's it's it's like an open question whether such a thing is even like possible.
I think it could be possible just because I can't disprove it yet.
I mean, sure.
Meet me either.
But like we're not there's like there's no there's there's no even like theoretical framework for like how such a thing would come to be.
So it's not it's not at all.
What I'm saying is it's not at all clear that like it's a foregone conclusion that eventually AI will become human like in its capability for generating thoughts and stuff.
You know, I guess you'd have to come down to like a human being learns by observing and the five, six senses or whatever they get data from the moment they're born.
And they don't know what the fuck they're doing.
But like over years and years they figure stuff out.
But it's not just that because they have instincts as well.
So like a pre program set of like things like when they're hungry, they cry, they don't know why they do that.
But like, um, like, I don't think in any short time frame, something could be approached.
But like, I think hypothetically, if an AI is like left to to grow and learn through many, many generations to the extent that it's like mimicking the human civilization from like when we crawled out of the sea.
Like that because I've seen I've seen some they're not like about AI and I says, well, they are, I guess.
But like, um, like learning algorithms where they have like a funny stick with legs and the goal is to make a goal to get to make a walk and over thousands and thousands and thousands of generations.
The ones that get furthest are passed on and the genes that don't do that are deleted and slowly it evolves to become good at walking, even though no instructions were given on how to do that.
So like, hypothetically, that system applies to learning algorithms might make it more able to come up with unique thoughts.
I just don't know what time frame or how like how difficult that would be to actually do.
I mean, that's you're talking about performing a very specific limited task of like move from A to B.
Yeah, that's the thing. It's like there is no.
We'd have to come up with its own instincts. We'd have to program its DNA and the goals it has.
Like for humans, the goal is like survive, procreate, because that's how we got here.
And that's just sort of what we want to do.
And all of the other things are related to surviving so that we can procreate.
We feel good when we are full and we like to drink water. It feels nice.
We have emotions because they help us decide what to do.
No other reason.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
No, that's it. Yeah, yeah.
I think generally that's where it comes from, right?
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah, sure.
Sure, sure.
Honestly, I hate this stuff.
I hate thinking about it.
But oh well.
Robots are going to shoot you in the brain.
Well, somebody has to.
They're going to come up to you and say, I'm the Terminator or something.
Live with me if you want to come.
That's okay. Wait a minute.
Okay.
I stole that from someone.
I was going to say you must have stolen it.
Don't think I'm smart.
I don't have it somewhere, but like it did catch me off guard.
So, I mean, good job.
Do you want to go to voicemails?
Yes, I think I've said all my things.
You said before we started, you said you had nothing to talk about.
And I said, I don't have anything to talk about either.
But maybe we can just do a short episode.
And I guess we've done kind of a normal episode.
So, good for us.
We always find something.
It was fun to talk about Outer Wilds.
I wish...
I would keep talking about it.
I just don't know what else to say about it.
You've got new things to explore.
That's the joy of it.
It's like thinking about what to do next.
You look at your little computer on your ship.
What have I not understood?
Well, I have a little bit...
I'm a little bit dreading.
I thought I was done with the Dark Bramble until I realized I got to go back
and I got to throw my fucking Scouter into that seed near the...
What are they called?
Bramble Seeds?
No, no, the Aliens.
The Nomai Grave.
I got to throw my...
I just got to go back, got to deal with it one more time
and throw my goddamn Scouter into the goddamn Nomai Grave.
Actually, I think I have to do that with...
not Gabbro, whatever the astronaut...
A Feltspar?
Yeah, I got to do that.
There's a seed near Feltspar too.
I got to do it with him too.
Just got to throw my freaking Scouter into some stuff
and, you know, just got to do that.
The third guy, I can't remember what his name is,
but I keep thinking it's Cheems.
Cheems?
There's another astronaut.
The small one?
There's like a fat one?
There's like a big one in Brittle Hollow.
Yeah, that's who I think Cheems is.
I can't remember his real name.
I know they're all named...
Oh, Chert. Chert.
I know they're all named after stones.
Stones that I know from Dwarf Fortress.
Gabbro.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, Gabbro, Chert, Feltspar.
I'm trying to think with it.
I know about Gabbro.
I mean, Dwarf Fortress, I'm always...
I'm always mine in Gabbro.
I'm always striking Gabbro.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, rocks.
Do you want to...
Okay.
Thespeakpipe.com slash PCB voicemail.
It looks like the newest one we've got is called...
The oldest new one is called Store Run.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
What's up, guys? I'm headed to the store.
Do you need anything?
Yeah, give me a pack of cigarettes.
Give me a pack of smokes, please.
Get me a...
A little chocolate bar.
I don't know what they have where you are.
Do they have a crunchy?
Give me a crunchy bar.
No, I want to...
I haven't...
Last night, I was really like...
I want to order some food from a restaurant.
I want to order some...
What do you call it?
What's the...
Middle Eastern food?
Kebabs?
Yeah, I want to order some kebab.
But it was too late.
It was like past midnight.
So it was like maybe in the morning.
I mean, it's good that I didn't,
because I would pay like $45 for the fucking wrap.
And that's bad.
So give me a kebab, please.
If you're going by something like that.
Next one is called Mike Ermentrout.
Three, two, one, go.
Welcome.
Would you take away Walter?
I'm not necessarily right now, Walter.
What?
It's a...
Put his phone up next to a meme of Mike Ermentrout
not actually speaking about
fucking Walter White or something.
Fucking Walter White, huh?
I heard it before.
Fantastic.
Spectacular.
Uh...
I don't know what else to say about it.
Next one is called...
Well, it's an Imgur link called
NFT Hypothetical Screenshots.
Okay, I'm going to listen to it.
Three, two, one, go.
Real quick, Ben doubted the story
about an artist being approached
to make an NFT,
so here's the screenshots of it.
They created about $36,000.
What?
I doubted the story of an artist
being approached to create an NFT.
No, I didn't.
Do you know what he's talking about?
I don't remember.
Maybe you were saying it probably
doesn't happen that much.
You misinterpreted it as you denying
that some specific thing didn't happen.
See, some people have noticed
I sold one of my posts in NFT.
Someone emailed me offering to...
This is dumb.
I feel like, obviously,
I didn't mean that it never happens.
I feel insulted that this...
Do you think that I meant that it had
never happened to anyone ever?
Of course it happened to one person.
Of course that happened.
Maybe we were talking about this.
I vaguely remember.
I donated 10 times the highest
credible estimate to the carbon cost
of climate change-related charities.
I don't care.
I don't care if it happened once.
It's irrelevant.
Whatever.
Yeah, whatever.
Stupid.
Next one is called...
Well, it's a Vinnie, I think.
3, 2, 1, go.
Cat face.
Okay.
Alright, I'm drooling.
Trixie is a golden witch.
There she is.
The lace in your dress
tangles my neck.
That's what you say.
I say that all the time.
I'm always saying this.
In case you wanted to look at that one picture
of Trixie a little longer, yeah.
My stand, Uwupati and platformer M.K.
Ray woman having a soda pop together.
Yep.
There's me.
Okay, me and Uwupati doing poses
from Baki the Grappler.
Cool.
NFTs become currency?
No.
I would say that.
Then crying like that Chopper meme
going around right now.
And then a Virgin Chad meme, you're the best kid.
Virgin Saint doesn't know how to dress
like a cool goth, spends hours
stalking his ex Trixie the Golden Witch.
Has to move out of Slumlord's apartment
to chicken to kill his landlord
and become the new landlord is
being hunted for his treachery
against the Kawasaki clan.
Yeah.
Nice unicorn power shirt.
Twice your height.
You're so huge.
Virgin Chad mean they're like the same height.
Is cute.
Is like so cute.
Like, oh my God.
Has made so much character development
and helps her friends and viewers with it.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Dude, I've made so much character development.
People are proud of her and her accomplishments.
Oh, that's so, no, that's great.
Oh, that's so good.
I'm so glad.
Inspires me who is writing this.
I hate, I hate you Vinny.
I fucking hate you so much.
Has overcome.
Stop saying the same thing over and over and over again.
How many times can you say had character development?
Fuck off.
Doesn't like the bottom one doesn't
outshine her co-hosts for their sake.
What the fuck does that mean?
Shut up.
Makes hilarious funnies that brighten your day.
No, she doesn't.
She sucks actually.
So true.
Thank you Vinny.
False.
Here's a.
Prove it.
You can't.
I like this drawing of me as well.
That's fine.
It's okay.
Next one is called cheesy owned epic style.
Three, two, one, go.
Wait, wait.
There's one more image on this.
Oh, was there?
Yeah.
Is it?
Oh.
Is another Trixie thing.
Oh, yes.
Trixie, the golden witch.
Her outfit is one of her boyfriend's shirts.
Trixie tape.
Carpenter.
Yeah.
Yeah, like a potato sack.
Trixie taping her office computer chair
to her witch broom for the comfort,
for comfort when flying.
That's kind of funny.
Stand whichever wand.
Her manifested which one to communicate her feelings.
The offense and defense varies depending on Trixie's understanding
or awareness of the situation she is in.
Hmm.
Same.
The ones variability is its greatest strength when utilized properly,
but really has to be worked up to be shown.
Shown.
I don't know what that last bit means.
This.
This is my superpower.
My superpower does things when I understand what's happening,
but it does not do anything when I don't know what's going on.
So true.
Shit.
Where was I?
Cheesy.
Cheesy owned epic style.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Cheesy man, Fredo.
I'm like cheesy.
Man's gay though.
Yeah.
True.
I don't want to keep saying true, but these keep being true.
These ones.
Man's gay though.
Do you get it?
No.
Oh, let me explain it to you.
See, it sounds like it's saying the man is gay though.
No, it doesn't sound like that.
It sounds like cheesy man Fredo.
That's the joke.
Yeah, but also he's gay though.
Like pizza dough?
No.
Like what's like African American vernacular English like dough instead of though.
Oh, like currency.
No.
Like just the way you would say the word.
I can't.
Listen, picture it like it's a bubble.
Let's get two dimensional membrane.
Yeah.
Make it vibrate in your mind though.
Rotate it.
Rotate.
Gay bubbles.
Rotate it in your mind.
Rotate the key.
The concept of the bubble of gayness.
Gayness.
And then pop it because God doesn't like it.
Pop and lock it.
Next one is called no SIM card, no service.
True.
Yes.
Next one is called what do you think of the Mario movie trailer?
I looked at it.
Looked all right.
It looked, it looks, you know, like a 3D animated film.
Yeah.
You know what was odd to me was like people when they heard Illumination Studios was working on it.
They were like, oh no, because they made minions.
Those are like, the minions movies are not like bad movies.
They're just sort of for children.
I mean, I've never seen one, so I don't even know.
I've caught one once.
I assume that they've made other things beside the minion movies.
So it wasn't like I thought like, oh, it's going to be just like the minions.
They did Despicable Me and then a minions like Despicable Me 1 and 2 and then a minions like standalone thing.
And like a prequel and like, I don't know, but like.
So you're actually like just proving that you're actually kind of making me think, oh, maybe that is all they've done.
Well, it might be.
I don't know, but like, like they're well animated, goofy, silly family movies that children love and mom's love for some reason.
I just so it's just sort of like people.
I don't think people really understood.
I heard people saying that they thought like the goombas would be like the minions.
Yeah, like I'm sure they I'm sure they don't write just one sort of thing.
Like the studio being used means that it's going to look like the animation is going to be like similar in quality.
The writing is different because they're working with Nintendo to write it.
So like, why would they think it would be the same thing?
I don't know.
Yeah, that seems a little silly.
No, I didn't.
I didn't think that.
Chris Pratt's voice is pretty boring.
Yeah, a little bit lame.
I think I think it's OK for him not to have an Italian accent like I'm fine with that.
Because I mean, he's always been a plumber from Brooklyn.
He doesn't sound like he's from Brooklyn.
He has a he has a slight Brooklyn accent.
Yeah, it's not it's not much.
It's it's pretty underwhelming.
The fucking Hotel Mario CD I Mario voice is better.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I agree.
But I'm just saying like no Italian.
I think some people think Mario needs to have an Italian accent.
I think it's OK if he doesn't have an Italian accent, but I still think Chris Pratt's voice is boring.
Sure.
I mean, yeah, it's always a thing with animated movies where.
The budget goes big and they get like famous people who are not known for voice acting to do like to bring star power.
Yeah, because voice actors don't have star power, even though they're better at their job generally.
Yeah.
But what are you going to do?
Change the whole fucking industry?
Yeah, it's stupid.
Next one's called Happy Birthday, Ben.
Thanks.
Next one after that's called ASMR with Ben St.
Three, two, one, go.
Breathe in and out.
I don't get it.
Do is it saying that I sound like this?
No, that was like a recording of you when you were asleep.
Oh, that's how you breathe.
Wow.
That's terrible.
I should stop breathing.
Next one is called.
Wait, did I download that one?
Yes.
Next one is called a win is a win.
Three, two, one, go.
What's up, baby?
Baby voice.
I called you guys back in August to say that I was going to be 22 soon.
And that was bummed out because I listened to the Nate's Virginia Republican story back when I was like 16.
And I still had not had sex, but in this time I have in fact had sex.
And it wasn't good, but it was sex.
That's crazy.
Hey, congratulations.
Progress Nate is forever.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Congrats on the bad sex.
That rules.
Character development.
We're all developing over here.
I'm amused.
Hey, I'm glad you gave me the update.
Thank you for the update.
Yeah.
A win is a win.
Yes, it's true.
Next one is called love you guys.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Maybe it is in fact say it wasn't good.
No.
It was just kind of awkward because it was.
It was the first time.
Yeah.
And it was gay sex.
Oh, well, that's that's never good.
But a win is a win.
That's no good.
No, I think as a win.
You can't have can't have gay sex.
That's evil.
No.
It's evil.
No, you must die.
No, you're evil.
No, God says you are bad.
What the fuck does God know about the progress Nate's podcast?
God.
Okay.
This is the least godly place.
God is like an AI so advanced that he could draw any.
And he could draw boobs that are any size.
I was there.
Are there boobs?
Is God.
Wait, because there.
Can you imagine that God boobs so big that even God cannot draw them?
Is it like that God has boobs so big that even God cannot draw them or is it that God can do anything?
No.
And there's no such thing as a big that God can't try it.
I'm talking.
No, I'm thinking of other.
You zoom out on the universe and it's just a big booby shape.
No, they're so big that they can.
Where's the nipple of the universe?
That's what the Nomai are really looking for.
Well, I'm glad they died instead of finding it.
The next one is called I'm a hungry.
What should I eat today?
You should eat some kebab.
Kebab.
I say it kebab.
I'm not sure if that's like a stupid way to say it.
It always sounded stupid because it's kebab, but it's like an American thing to say kebab.
Yeah, I think Americans say kebab.
But even though it's not spelled that way.
But anyway, that's what I'm hungry for.
So this guy should be hungry for it.
Yeah.
Eat dirt.
Eat gruel.
Sure.
He gruel gruel is good.
It is.
It's like porridge kind of oatmeal.
This is sort of like a gruel in a sense.
Next one is called funny man.
Where are you?
Yeah.
Kyle and funny man.
Right?
That's what it was, right?
Kyle.
Kyle and the funny man.
The saga.
They ended, right?
They had their grand finale.
I don't remember what happened.
I remember there was a grand finale.
I couldn't tell you the details of it.
Those were the days though.
You know, that does make me nostalgic for Kyle and funny man.
Where is he?
He's off being funny somewhere, you know?
Just as we all knew he would one day.
And Kyle was just being Kyle.
Kyle's just not Kyle died, unfortunately.
Kyle got pancreatic cancer and he didn't make it.
Sorry.
He was good material for the funny man's like stand up routine.
He's working on it.
He's building his repertoire.
He's making his tight five.
Next one is called today is Tuesday, three, two, one, go.
Oh.
It's me again.
Shit.
Oh, how are you?
I see how you are.
You are on the way.
I like how you are.
You are intelligent.
Can you understand?
No.
Why?
Jesus.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Thank you.
Shit.
That should not have gotten a laugh out of me.
That sucks.
That just makes me think of today is Friday in California.
You know that?
I don't.
There's a gimmick account on Twitter that posts it every Friday and it's like some Japanese
movie and it's like a guy.
He's like he's on an operating table.
I think he's like a corpse, but he like sits up and he's alive.
And he says today is Friday in California.
And the like a cop goes like, huh?
And the corpse like shoots him with a gun.
And that's the clip.
And I don't know the context.
It's like a cool like 80s one liner, but very strange one.
Yeah.
That's not on purpose.
Next one is called and three, two, one, go.
Oh my God.
No.
That's enough.
Enough, enough, enough.
Couldn't get a single word out.
Appreciate the thought.
Next one is called L for Ben St.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
Thanks for the voicemails.
Next one is called uplifting true facts.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, Dick Masterson got swatted.
That's pretty good.
Wait, really?
Swatted for what?
Like was it legitimate or like swatted as in like he was streaming and then they said.
I think when you get swatted, that's not, that's bad.
I mean, I know when a SWAT team comes around is bad, but like the act of swatting someone
streaming live who has done nothing just to harass them.
That is what I imagine this means.
I mean, that's pretty bad.
That's pretty bad.
I don't know, even though I don't like Dick Masterson, I don't know if I can, I don't
know if I can condone such a thing.
However, if a SWAT team had a reason to go there and they found something that would
be very juicy, but I suspect that's not what this is.
Yeah, I wouldn't, I don't know.
I'm going to assume that it was just some guy randomly swatted him and like, I've got
a, I've got a tut tut.
I've got a tut tut that that's, that's rough.
But oh well, bad things happen all the time and I'm not going to worry about it.
Uh, next one is called PCP fans costumes for Halloween, like how Homestar does.
I don't know what that is referencing.
I know Homestar Runner.
I just haven't seen it.
Every, I mean, every Halloween they have like a, you know, all the characters have a costume.
Like every show?
Uh, no, there'll usually be like, there'll be a Halloween special and everyone, you know,
everyone's got a costume that year.
Or there'll be like a special menu or something and you can like, yeah, like hover your mouse
over everyone and see like, oh, what are they dressed up as this year?
Oh, it's like a website.
I thought it was a like video show.
Well, it's both.
It's a website with video cartoons.
What?
That's crazy.
Are you just not, are you not familiar?
I'm not familiar at all.
I just know that it was a thing.
Uh, yeah.
Well, it was flash based.
So there were like interactive things as well as cartoons.
I think that why would, why would fans costumes like fans aren't typically featured in a thing?
I think he means, do you mean like, we are we going to do costumes?
I don't want to do.
I hate it.
I'm going to get a costume.
I know.
When I said last time, I was going to get a costume.
I didn't really know what I wanted.
I thought you were lying.
I thought you were lying to me.
But damn, you're telling me you were serious?
Damn.
I'm serious.
I'm going to get a costume and it's going to be normal goth girl.
And it's going to be, uh, that's what I'm going to be.
Not even a Halloween thing really.
Yeah.
That's, that's not really much of a costume.
That's just.
Yes.
That's, that's the, that's the joke.
It was not a joke.
It's the serious secret tactic where I say I'm going to get a Halloween costume and
then I just become a goth and wear it every day.
Hmm.
That's a good trick.
It's a good life hack.
I need to go, I need to go clothes shopping for goth, for goth girl shit.
Yeah.
Uh, next one is called PCP.
No, it's called specifically PCP related ones.
Oh.
To costumes.
Oh, are you asking like, if you're asking for like PCP related costume ideas?
I mean, God, I don't know.
Like fuckers.
The samurai.
Dress up as Kyle and funny man.
You should go as Kyle and funny man for Halloween.
Everyone will know exactly what you're talking about.
Yeah.
Or, or you could be the PCP mascot guy who's just got his mouth open and he's like.
From a manga.
You could be a Riddle My Ass Batman.
Or just the Riddler.
It's just the same.
Looks the same as the Riddler, but you'll know that you're not the real Riddler.
You're the PCP version.
That's a good costume.
Next, next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder.
Play Delta Bruin chapter two.
Okay.
Then Ben's Weekly Reminder.
Catch it to one piece.
Okay.
Then there's some YouTube links that you know what, I'm not even going to check them.
I'm not even going to check them.
We never check them.
If there's no information involved, then there's no reason to click.
Then there is happy birthday Ben.
Okay.
Then there's I miss the old PCP.
Wait a minute.
There's one second of audio.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
They cuffed.
It's just a cough.
If you miss the old PCP, you can go listen to it over on the procrastinators.com.
No, you can't.
Or on the YouTube.
You're banned.
Oh.
Well, you could go listen to, you could become a patron and listen to the old bonus episodes.
That's true.
Years and years and years and years of those.
It was like 60.
It's almost 60.
There will be 60 bonus episodes one day soon, I think.
Next one is called NB Parents, Maddie, Mappa, Dama, Nori, Nibi, Nody.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I have no idea what he's talking about.
I guess these are words you could call your non-binary parents and like, sure.
Oh.
I could make up any fucking combination of syllables that I want and say, why don't we call non-binary parents?
Why don't we call them, why don't we call them Dimbuses?
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
I have two binary, non-binary parents.
There's Dimbus and there's Migmog.
Sure.
No, no, no.
They're combining like things like Maddie's mom and daddy.
Mappa is like Mampa.
Mappa, Dama.
What does Nibi mean?
Nori, Nibi and Nody.
Is that supposed to be like a gender neutral, like no, like a negation?
I think you could teach a baby to say Nibi or Nori.
I guess.
Problem solved.
Sure.
You could just call them whatever you want and that's true.
Next one is called Sweetness in Mains.
Loud equals funny at gibmail.com.
This is going to be shit, isn't it?
Three, two, one, go.
Ain't it all just food?
The courses are arbitrary.
You can eat three bowls of ice cream at 2 p.m.
You can eat a steak at 7 a.m.
You can eat wings and fries whenever you want.
I just can't bring myself to think X isn't suitable for this course.
I just like the food sensations in my bard.
I don't want arbitrary dish tyranny ruining any of that.
You're a dictator gib.
Totalitarian.
You're killing me.
What is he talking about?
He was talking about how I can't handle a sweet flavor in a main course or a starter
as opposed to the dessert.
Because I always bookend, not bookend, but I end a meal if I have a dessert.
It's a sweet thing.
And so it just feels wrong to have sweetness before the dessert.
And that's just a me thing.
I wasn't dictating what you should do.
I just feel like if I'm having a thing,
I want it to be non-sweet unless it's dessert.
I mean, there's not there's not very many sweet foods that I would eat as like a main course.
I think the thing I brought up was like certain curries have dates in them.
They're sort of sweetened and savory at the same time.
But I just don't like it.
Don't do it to me.
You can do it.
But that's you.
I mean, I think I'm not.
I think I wouldn't care.
Yeah, I think I need a sweet entree.
I'll eat a peanut butter and fluff sandwich.
Yeah.
I don't give a shit.
It's just a me thing.
It's not prescriptive.
All right.
Gotcha.
No.
I got no.
I got no scruples about anything.
Next one.
I think this is the last one.
It's called Herder Carbon Offsets Are Scam.
Three, two, one, go.
What do you mean carbon offsets are a scam?
Like, yeah, there are some shit ones like pay this login company not to cut down the forest that they were never going to cut down.
But there's a whole spectrum of them.
There are better ones that replace equipment and infrastructure in poor countries so that their people can go through their activities generating less carbon.
And yeah, from some senior companies, these estimates can be off by 300 or 400%.
But some companies do better testing to make sure that the offsetting methods they provide are accurately measured so that they don't fuck over their customers.
And if you don't trust anyone, there's still the ultra reliable method of direct carbon capture.
This is way overpriced compared to every other method of dealing with climate change.
But it's also way easier to measure, making it more reliable.
And guess what?
The ass I was talking about who offset his NFT this way bought credits for 10 times more carbon than the relevant transactions emitted.
And within that mix, he bought some from a company that does direct carbon capture.
Carbon offsets can be fucked up, but good companies exist.
And if you overpay 10 times, as some people such as the YouTube channel jet lag do, then you can truthfully and reliably offset your carbon offset.
I guess I would agree that there are good carbon offsets.
But like, I think the use of carbon offsets to excuse NFTs is not good enough.
I would rather you don't do any of that and you only do the carbon offsets.
You don't buy the NFT at all.
Leave that alone.
It's just bad.
I mean, yeah, so carbon offsets are something that a company can do to reduce carbon emissions, right?
Reduce carbon emissions or like he was saying, like take carbon out of the atmosphere.
There's there's things you can do.
There's things that are possible to do.
But like, well, in the case of NFTs, I don't like, yeah, they're bad for the environment.
That's not like specifically why I think they're bad.
They're bad for all kinds of reasons.
So I don't know the fact that they can be carbon offset doesn't really help my opinion of them.
I'm not sure if that was this guy's goal was to be pro NFT on the basis of carbon neutrality.
I mean, I think you thought we were just completely uninformed about the fact that carbon offsetting can work.
Yeah.
Well, I just I'm sure I'm sure it can work.
I'm sure it can work.
But like what does my reservation my reservation of like citing carbon offsets with regards to stupid things like NFTs is that it feels like an excuse.
It feels like it could be very easily manipulated and like like used to like, I don't know, bolster the credibility of things that suck.
This yeah, like this guy says like it can be fucked up and it can be like dishonest and it can be ineffective.
So yeah, probably is a lot of the time with something with something with something scammy like like NFT companies, I think are probably even more prone to that.
Like if there if there was, I don't know, a very strict like pipeline of like that you could easily look at to see to prove that they are saying that they are actually offsetting the right amount of carbon and that they're not fucking around and that the companies are all above board and stuff.
That would be one thing.
I still wouldn't like NFTs anymore if they did that if they if they can offset if they can offset the carbon from, let's say, an NFT.
Why don't they offset even more carbon?
Why don't they just keep why don't they just keep offsetting carbon?
Why do they why would must they stop when I think why must they stop at net zero?
Why can't we go into the negatives?
The I think they just don't want to spend more money offsetting the carbon than they have to.
Can we just I mean this is kind of a separate thing but like hmm I mean if we can just do that, can we like subsidize like more of that?
Can we like pay more tax money to like offset even more carbon emissions?
Can we just do that?
Is that a thing?
I mean we could just do that but the government doesn't want to because it's expensive and not as popular as it needs to be for that to be like a it should be more popular.
It sounds good.
There's enough people who don't like saving the planet.
It sounds like it's something that would probably be worth some money.
It's sort of like COVID like if the if the situation is dire enough the government can get a lot more done than it usually does.
If it actually wants to like it can it can fund the creation of a vaccine much faster than the bureaucracy normally would allow it and the funding that would take a lot longer to get you know given to the people who need it to do the work.
If the situation is fucked up enough.
I feel like with climate emergency the situation is clearly it's fucked up.
I feel but it's like it's not immediate enough for the people to actually do as much as they really should be.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's okay.
We just it's we just got to get it really bad.
We just got to bring we got a brinks minute.
We got to acceleration it.
We should just get it as bad as possible as fast as possible so we can get to the point where we were someone will do something.
That's all.
Yes, let's burn down every tree and become the Lorax.
Exactly.
Well, that was the last that was the last voicemail.
Thank God I've had enough.
Let's go back to outer wilds.
That was more fun.
Yeah, but I've said everything.
Yeah, it's it's it's a little tricky.
I don't want to accidentally give you the solution to something.
Yeah, that's fair.
Well, I don't know.
I feel like I'm getting getting somewhere with it.
So I might have finished it by the end of this week.
Perhaps maybe I could see it happening.
We'll see.
I gotta pee.
I gotta pee really bad.
The episode's almost over.
So we should probably just end the episode so I can go do that.
Okay.
Well, patreon.com.
So step procrastinators if you want to listen to a bazillion bonus episodes from all the way back years and years ago and also today.
The time capsule from many different times.
You might say.
Pete speak up dot com slash PCB voicemail.
If you want to send us something that we will maybe listen to if it doesn't take our boxes for things that need to be skipped and ignored.
We're very, we're very picky.
We're very, very picky.
We're very, very scrupulous about what we will allow into our content.
And I guess that's it.
Anything else?
No.
I'm hungry.
I want a kebab but I've had enough.
I ate like a lot last night and I've used up all my calories for the day.
Well, now what am I going to do?
You're going to eat more calories, Ben saying.
I should just get a fucking kebab.
Fuck it.
Yeah, if you're hungry, you should eat.
That's normal.
I just want one.
I just haven't had real food in a while.
I mean, now I want one.
Yeah, that's what I want.
Order something from Mr. Shawarma.
I'll probably do that later.
All right.
That's the episode for the week.
Tune in next time for more Outer Wilds Talk probably.
And nothing else.
Yeah.
I will try to get Clarissa Gunspoke done quick.
Based.
I want to get it made.
I want to make it a day.
I'm going to do it.
Based.
I'll try to get my video done.
Maybe my video will be done this week.
Maybe.
It could happen.
It's getting there.
Only two more hours to go.
All right.
Bye.