Donald J. Trump is now president of the United States.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy in the motherfucking game.
And I'm here once again with all your favorite internet shenanigan boys.
Here's Hippocrit.
Everybody is a human being.
But some are gayer than others.
Mumkey Jones is here.
I just saw the Japanese film Your Name in theaters, and then I went and watched The
Pleeve and the Weep episode, and I thought it was very funny and well-edited.
Oh, well, go on to, uh...
It's only we knew the name of the genius who edited those episodes.
Who could have?
It's only he had a Patreon.com slash Endless Jess that we should know about.
You have co-opped this intro segment.
It's garbage now.
Endless Jess is here as well, as you heard.
I'm wearing slippers.
Nice.
Tom Oliver.
Sup?
Uh, yeah.
I'm here.
He's not on the podcast.
I'm just asking him what's up.
I got nothing.
He's in the room.
I'm eating my blue pills.
Is he saying he's eating his blue pills?
What on earth else could he be eating?
That's a good question.
I'm hoarding those blue pills.
You son of a bitch.
Leave some for me.
I'm eating my blue pills.
Oh my god.
In that new Rick and Morty episode, is that what they were feeling?
What on earth else could he be eating?
That's a good question.
Are we feeding everyone?
Is that the pills that everyone was surviving on?
Oh my god.
And Ben St.
The most blue pill man the world is here.
That's right.
I'm here to show y'all how it's done.
Because today's topic is SJWs.
Uh-oh.
It's a spicy topic.
It's a heated topic.
It's gonna get crazy.
This will be the end of the PCP.
Most likely it'll terrace in Twayne and will never be whole again.
Today's special episode has not one, but two,
urban dictionary definitions that we're reading,
which means you have to go to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators and double your Patreon amount.
I find the term urban is totally rad, so keep going.
I thought you were gonna say racist as a SJW.
Way to explain the joke, Nate.
I fucked it up.
Well, rad is a very white word as far as I'm concerned.
Read your fucking definition.
Here is what he's the definition of SJW.
Social justice warrior, a pejorative term for an individual
who repeatedly and vehemently engages in arguments
on social justice on the internet,
often in a shallow or not well thought out way
for the purpose of raising their own personal reputation.
And that's the important part.
And here's the special bonus definition today,
because I thought it behooved us to define specifically
social justice itself, to be a little clear
as to what we're talking about here.
So here is the urban dictionary definition
for social justice, promoting tolerance, freedom,
and equality for all people regardless of race, sex,
orientation, national origin, handicap, et cetera,
except for white straight cisgendered males.
Fuck those guys, they're overprivileged no matter what.
That's true.
That's the deal, that's where we're starting.
I wanna start off by saying I don't agree
with that definition of social justice.
It's a meme.
It's a joke.
Yeah, so everything except the fuck white guys.
Ben does agree with that, though.
He's like, yeah, that's me, that's me, right, Ben?
As a cis white male, I know that I deserve no rights
and no consideration.
Good, good, good, good.
Yes.
You there, boy, what day is it?
Why is Mon Luther King Day, sir?
Mon Luther King Day, bring me some social justice.
Here's a tuppence, my lord.
For the sake of organization,
I think we should start off
when everybody goes around the horn and says,
you know, what's your stance on social justice warriors?
That's a good way to start.
Probably evolve a debate from that.
That's probably a good call.
Monkey, why don't you start us off?
Well, I think it's no secret that I'm not a fan.
Yeah, okay, I'm a racist, it's fine.
I'm also a sexist, a misogynist.
Just anyist that's negative, you can say I am.
So I'm pretty much against the idea of,
the social justice warrior who like innate definitions,
who was very loud and obnoxious,
but in a way where it's hypocritical,
not in the good hippo way,
but how are the good gibbon way, I should say,
but in the way where they want equality in quotes
and their version of equality
is special treatment for people like me
and disregard the issues of others.
That's what I think the modern day
social justice warrior is.
Can I insert my little definition in there?
I was reading about it ahead of time
just to make sure I was sort of up to snuff
on sort of the more accurate definition.
And it's kind of this Leninist, Communist sort of idea
in terms of society where there is,
the goal is an equality of outcome for all
in terms of society, as opposed to eliminating the barriers.
No, it is equality of outcome.
That's what it's about.
Equality of outcome in terms of society
in a social context, which necessitates
a large degree of control on people
to force the people above down
and lift the people below up to get the same right.
Okay, so that's-
Social Marxism as the buzzword is.
Yeah, yeah.
I like Leninist though,
because it makes me sound smart.
It does sound cooler, I'll give you that.
Okay, monkey, have any further?
I have a lot more to say, but I'll save it for later.
Okay.
How about you, Munchy?
What are you, where are you at, brother?
You're Californian, so you're gay, right?
I'm a Californian.
One time, Bernie Sanders actually ate my poop.
He actually came into my house
and he actually ate my poop,
so that changed my fucking life.
Were you that bird that landed on his podium that one time?
Was that you?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
If we're gonna be serious about Bernie,
I actually shook that man's hand.
It was an honorable moment in my life.
Really?
What was that?
He came to my college.
What?
I stopped trying to call it my social movement, Munchy.
Anyway, I think, while their efforts are noble,
they're debatably noble.
No, they're fucking noble, they're great.
However, they're also bad.
Well, they are mean, and I don't like that part of it.
So you think that they got their hearts in the right place,
but their tactics are mistaken?
Their tactics are that of a fucking boy.
I hate boys.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, that's a no-no.
How about Tom?
What do you think about all this?
I think my opinion is probably pretty close
to what Munchy was talking about.
I'm really not a huge fan of the hypocrisy of the movement
and the people in general.
There seems to be a lot of, instead of raising people up,
it's trying to push people at the top down.
Right.
And just like, I think this way about one thing,
but not about the other thing,
and I'm sure I can probably get into specifics
as the debate will continue.
I'm not a huge fan of social justice warriors.
It's interesting, back in 2012, 2013,
I was more on board with it
because I just kind of heard the service arguments
and it seemed to make sense,
but the more I digged into it,
the more I realized that a lot of it was bullshit
and based on false arguments.
So now I'm definitely more on the red pill side of things,
but I'm not super invested in any of it.
It's just kind of what I hear and stuff.
Yeah, so it's done.
Jesse, what are you saying?
Well, the PCP has slowly morphed over the years
or the last year into more and more
of the Jesse is Right podcast.
And I think this episode is going to be the most
Jesse is Right episode in quite some time.
Because everybody's wrong about social justice warriors.
Everybody's wrong about what a social justice warrior is.
Everybody has an idea in their head
of what a social justice warrior is.
And most of us picture the militant left,
but I say the term needs to be expanded
in people's minds to encompass people
on both sides of the extremist fucking spectrum.
Because I think if you're the kind of person
who is up in arms about social justice warriors,
then you are yourself a social justice warrior.
You're all the same.
You're all polarized, you're all politicized,
and you're all a fucking militant, tribalistic,
primitive cancer on this earth
that is holding us back as a species.
And every single one of you, all of you people,
all of you social justice warriors on the left,
all of you social justice warriors on the right,
you all need to be fucking terminated
and executed immediately.
Because you're destroying everything.
You're choking the empathy out of the human race,
and you all need to be fucking dealt with.
All right, Jess, no time out.
Jess, you just said if you're against social justice warriors,
then you are one, and then you say
they should all be exterminated.
So does that make you a social justice warrior?
It makes me the one true social justice warrior.
The only one in the world, everyone else is doing it wrong.
There's one social justice warrior in us, me,
because I'm the only one who really cares about justice
and social progress for both sides, for all people.
I'm the only one who's not sitting
in my own little fucking corner saying,
you know, rah-rah for the home team, fuck the other guys.
I'm the only intelligent person,
the only one standing against this wave of retardation
that is just drowning the entire world.
I'm the only smart one,
and more people need to listen to me,
and no one else, fuck all of you.
The end.
I think more positively about the kind of,
what's the word I'm looking for, benevolent despot,
you know, that seems more and more appealing to me.
But okay, got it.
Note real quick, I should factor into my ideology
that I also find the opposite, well, yeah, as Jesse said,
just the same people on the right side,
almost more infuriating to me specifically.
I mean, like, what is really the difference
between this group of people who, you know,
everyone who disagrees with me is a Nazi?
What's the difference between that
and everyone who disagrees with me is a cock?
They're exactly the fucking same mentality.
I see what you're saying.
I think that they sort of have come from the same place.
More, in recent history, it manifested more.
It's the same sense of sort of, you know,
fighting back against the ideology
that you feel is becoming too entrenched.
It's all, it's just, it's fighting fire with fire,
because like the social justice movement
hit the mainstream, it got a lot of attention,
and like, you know, you have like governments
and companies kind of capitulating to that ideology,
and you have people who are against it,
basically saying like, okay, if you wanna be tribalist,
we're gonna be a tribe and fight you with tribalism,
which is kind of like the natural reaction,
but not the one that's very well thought out.
So like, they're both, they're both operating
using the same tactics, but with different ideologies
and different value systems.
So they're both wrong in their execution,
despite having different kind of motivations for doing, so.
If you're talking about like, yeah,
these kind of political activists,
SJWs on both sides, then yeah, you're totally right.
So Hippo, what do you think, dude?
I think the clue is-
As the only non-American, I'm curious
what you have to say.
I mean, it's the same over here
because the internet's everywhere, but-
What?
The clue.
You guys have the internet?
Yeah, dude.
Whoa, okay.
Fuck that joke, it's stupid.
All right.
I think that the clue is in the name.
Social justice warriors, they fight in wars with weapons
and they're brutal and they're clan based
and they attack people.
And social justice, I think, is a neat idea
that warriors have taken and used
to bludgeon people to death with.
It's just sort of, if you're fighting for a cause,
it's an okay cause, it shouldn't be ignored.
It's not the biggest problem in the world, social justice,
but it shouldn't be ignored, it's real.
And it's good to have more representation and stuff
and their quality and all that, people being good.
And then we've got all these warriors and a war
and it's like everything that's called a war.
It's like everyone gets hurt and nobody's happy
and everything's shit.
So I think the warriors is the main part
that sucks about it all.
That's my stance.
Okay, I'll say mine before we get to Ben's
because I think his might be the most different.
I agree with most of you guys.
I don't care for a lot of the tech.
I mean, if we're talking about not people
promoting these kinds of ideas,
but specifically the SJW people.
Yeah, not a fan of what seems to be,
I see this happen on both sides a lot,
the kind of willing to ignore facts.
Like the goal is to promote the ideology
as opposed to intellectually honestly pursue
what appears to be correct and then operate based on that.
That's where I really, that's where I get my most annoyance.
When I see things like, just to bring up one big example.
Just monks, then it might be better.
That's true, that's true.
Like one thing that infuriates me that gets brought up
is the way that the gender pay gap
gets brought up repeatedly.
And it's not inaccurate to say that men overall
earn more than women overall,
but it's in the nuance of that point
where either deception or the actual truth lies
because the truth is that,
they say 77 cents on the dollar.
It is that men overall, in total,
all people, all men in America make like 100 cents
compared to the average woman's 77 cents,
but that's during net earnings for a year.
So it's just that women are in different jobs
and there may be a small pay gap,
but it is not the massive,
like almost 25% people talk about.
And it's when people bring up that idea,
like Obama himself did it.
And I'm sure people have heard this a thousand times,
but like Obama said sense,
we have to pay women the full amount that men get paid.
It's just not fair.
It's me, President Barack Obama, this is how I am.
It's in the way that he presented that point,
which made it look like your average business
gives a woman 77 cents and a man doing the same job,
one dollar, which is factually inaccurate.
And it is by saying things like that,
that people are deceived and you create this kind of outrage
about things that aren't real.
So like when you've got people who are outraged
by things that aren't true,
fighting people who are aware of the truth,
like I don't really blame the people getting mad.
They've just been filled false information
and they're confronted with conflicting information.
Of course there's gonna be a conflict.
Like what else could you expect in a situation like that?
So it comes like the responsibility is on everyone
to be truthful and honest and accurate.
But people aren't capable of pursuing
that responsibility or holding to it.
People are, they're not looking for nuance.
They're looking for an excuse
to justify their own bitterness
and everything that they do.
It's all that people care about because like,
you should be able to say,
any intelligent person should be able to say,
well, obviously the wage gap is not a real thing
because I work with women and they don't make,
you know, more or less than me, you know.
Everyone should be able to, but people can't,
people have this like conflation they do where like,
if one thing supports their side,
then everything must support their side,
even if it doesn't.
Well, the wage gap isn't true and that's bullshit.
So, you know, everyone who believes in that is dumb.
Yeah, okay.
It's not true and it's dumb.
And also this stuff about, you know,
how women might sometimes like get harassed in the workplace.
That's also not true because the wage gap, like, what?
No, you can have both.
You can have a brain and have empathy,
except you can't, only I can.
Going back to what you were talking about.
That's why everyone hates me.
The left hates me because I have a brain
and the right hates me because I have empathy.
Well, it just goes back to what you were saying earlier
about how both sides are dumb.
It's because there seems to be no room in people's heads
or this discussion in general, you're aside for nuance.
You know what the problem is?
The problem is, I think, I see this all the time.
And God, I see this with guys like Sargon.
They just like block out things that look like they're correct
and they're just not focused.
There's this problem of focus where people just do not
emphasize the things that are true,
but don't help their argument.
It's not like you're lying, but this is the whole problem,
that it's so hard to be intellectually honest
and accurate with your information.
And there's this additional problem
that I think people have such a hard time
relating to things that don't,
and I don't blame them at all.
I'm like this too, everyone's like this.
People have such a hard time processing macro issues
as opposed to specific issues in their life.
Like if you have a job and the women there
aren't sexually harassed, it is your experience in life
that women never get sexually harassed ever.
So you're like, why is this a problem?
It never happens.
Look at my life.
This has never happened to me.
Like I understand why that guy would think that way.
It's, that's right.
It's when you live in a bubble, when you live in a bubble
and you've never seen discrimination
or you've never seen what you considered re-discrimination
and you've never seen inequality,
it's easy to tell yourself that it doesn't exist.
That's why people talk about white privilege
and the thing about white privilege
is that white people can deny that it exists
because they don't have to deal
with the ramifications of not having it.
And what they say is that if you don't,
like only if you don't have white privilege
do you need to acknowledge it, you know?
Like if you've got white privilege,
the part of that privilege is the privilege
to pretend that there is no white privilege.
And to take it one step further,
I would say that like,
I'm talking kind of about that bubble as well,
but about like a bubble that is unavoidable for anyone.
And that is that like we observe the world
through our individual perception as one human being.
But like the most accurate way to like deal with this problem
is to look at things like mass gathered statistics.
It's like the only way to accurately assess like,
okay, how much of a problem is like workplace sexual harassment?
Like no one's individual account
is going to help us solve that problem particularly much.
You have to aggregate like all the information.
And it's so easy to just look at that and be like,
ah, fuck it, I don't care.
I don't care about that.
Even if you aggregate like the statistics,
you then have, well, okay, but what is the actual like cost
of that?
Like how like, like, like no two,
no two harassments are like the same.
You can't put like a dollar amount on them.
Yeah, yeah, that's another problem.
Experiences are the same, no two people.
That's why the whole privileged, you know,
genre of arguments in general is fucking goofy and retarded.
Well, I think like the whole thing is that you can have,
like I don't think there's like people who say
there's no such thing as like racism or discrimination
or like white privileges and the thing.
I think that's stupid.
Of course there is, you know,
there are people out there going to think that my problem
is when you have social justice worries saying
that all of this is systemic,
which I don't think there's really any basis
for saying there's systemic.
Can you define systemic for everybody?
Cause that seems to get fucked up a lot.
Well, I mean, as far as I can understand systemic,
when social justice refers to something as systemic racism
or systemic privilege and stuff like that,
it's talking about a concept that is pervasive
throughout all of society
or is like ingrained in law somehow.
Yeah, does it necessarily imply that it's baked
into law specifically or can like?
Sometimes it sounds like that's what they're,
I mean, again, like I'm not a social justice warrior.
I think the problem here is that it's a little bit too vague
and like we can, we can have different meanings.
The interesting thing with the social justice argument
is that it kind of like points at a boogeyman sometimes.
It's like, okay, cause like you have people saying like,
we need to end, we need to end white privilege.
It's like, okay.
Does anyone really think,
does anyone who knows what white privilege is
and understand what it actually means,
does anyone like that actually think we can just end it?
Well, that's the whole thing.
It's like, what do you, why,
that's what they want to do.
They want this equality of outcome.
And they want, we can't, we can't just end.
Okay, good.
Can't we just all get along?
No, well, can't we all just Pokemon go to the polls?
I mean, yes, queen.
That's the solution to all of our problems.
It's her time.
Hi, here's my second Hillary song.
What up, wow, Hillary.
You make my ass whole flame, Hillary.
I got AIDS, thank you, Hillary.
Wow.
Hillary Clinton, widespread AIDS support.
Hillary Clinton, everybody, she'll be here all week.
Yeah, all right, thank you, Hillary, thank you.
No, it's Hillary fan 306.
Oh my God.
I was gonna say Hillary fan 666, she's the devil.
She's my queen, I worship the devil.
But anyway, so we didn't get to Ben.
So Ben, why don't you tell us your stance on this?
I need to get in the bra, what's up?
Well, I really believe, I really believe in all the ideals
that I think the SJW movement is, like, wants.
Like, everything that they want, I think would be great.
You know, equality, representation, egalitarianism,
everyone gets a fair shake.
But like, okay, I don't believe that equality of outcome,
like, to bring about equality of outcome,
you would just have to take away everyone's freedom.
Like, you would just have to dictate
exactly what everyone gets and make sure
everyone gets the same thing.
State-enforced communism is what that amounts
to all times.
Yeah, that's what it would be.
State-enforced homosexuality.
It's coming, dude, it's coming.
So like, I'm all about equality and SJW bullshit
and all that crap that sucks, but I stop short
of being willing to like call for like...
Equality for everyone but Pokemon.
They're not people, they're not people.
Yeah, but like, yeah, I also don't believe
in telling people what to do.
Like, I kind of think that like, if an employer is racist
and hates Mexicans, like, if he starts his business
and is like, well, I'm not gonna hire any Mexicans,
I mean, that sucks, but I kind of think
that's his prerogative in a way.
Yeah, you would think like, really,
ideally the free market would just be like,
well, fuck that guy, we're not gonna, you know,
if you can deal with that.
Like, one of the things that, one of the stories
in a couple, in recent years that really got to me
was for this issue, like, there was a baker
who was asked to make a cake for a gay wedding
and they're religious, I hate all religious people,
by the way, but they didn't want to
because of their religion and, you know,
because they're Christ fags or whatever.
And so they didn't want to.
And then later on, like, they were sort of,
they were forced to do it, like, they were sued
or whatever and they were forced to do it.
Well, that's some bullshit.
That's where I hit a fucking, that's where I get mad
because to say that you're not allowed to, like,
hurt people, totally on board, makes sense to me,
but to force people to do things
that they don't want to do, that's, like,
that's a whole nother ballgame, to impel action
at, like, otherwise you'll go to jail or whatever.
Yeah, like, saying, like, if these people were straight,
you would have done this, therefore, you have to do it.
Yeah, right, that's not.
I think a lot of the social justice,
there's like this, they don't understand that
even if, like, people hate people, like groups of people,
they all, even if race wasn't a thing,
we would hate each other based on what town we came from
or, you know, what street you came from,
like, various things we would divide ourselves up into
and say, well, I don't like those people,
they're from the next town over.
If it wasn't race, it would be something else.
So you can't ever end, like, subjugation of a group.
Yeah, it's never, it's impossible to do.
That's an interesting point,
because I think that a large,
I think a lot of it comes from, like,
a base-level ideological difference between,
between, like, more, I guess, conservative is the word to use,
conservative versus, like, SJW people,
which is that SJW people, in general, or, like, the left,
seems to have their mind, have in their mind,
and I kind of agree with this,
that people will be able, like, humans as a species,
will be able to overcome, like,
our generic kind of prejudices,
and we will be able to solve these kind of issues
as time goes on.
And so they're kind of working towards that,
whereas conservative people more accept
that that's a reality, that they can't change,
and are sort of comfortable trying to just deal with that
as far away as possible.
I would like it if people didn't care so much about race,
but I understand that there's always gonna be groups
dividing people up, you know,
even if we finally end, like, racism of skin color,
it's gonna be something else.
And I don't, I don't think, you know,
we're all ever gonna be on the same page ever
as a species.
I don't quite agree, but that's interesting,
that's interesting.
Well, I mean, you know, there's always,
I'm thinking about Starfleet Dog,
I'm thinking about Starfleet.
There's too many people to get, like, on the same page.
I disagree.
Well, you know what, you know what's a great example of this?
I think the ending of Watchmen is a really cool
example of this sort of issue,
because at the end of Watchmen,
like, the world is about to be destroyed by these,
these kind of like, you know,
country-based divisions between, you know,
like, it's the Cold War,
it's a Russian America in the 80s,
and like they are on,
they are one minute from midnight,
which means like a nuclear war is like about to happen.
And so, Vite, or Ozymandias,
like the quote-unquote villain,
like he staged this whole operation
to basically trick humanity into not destroying itself
by uniting it against an interdimensional alien race
that they, that he like,
sets the situation up as invading Earth.
We don't have any of those.
And almost immediately, well, that he made one up,
he invented a false one,
and that at least temporarily solved the problem
of like humanity about to destroy itself.
And I sort of think that for just for one crazy example,
if we had something like, you know,
space travel and relationships with other alien life forms,
all of humanity would look at each other
and be like, you know what?
I guess we are pretty similar compared to these guys.
They're a bunch of weirdos that we don't understand,
but we, you know what I'm saying?
I think that perspective-
I think that perspective, like if we had that,
would definitely help.
But I mean, the whole thing is that like,
for example, like we still hate people.
Like, even-
Of course.
I hate Ben Stain, for example.
You just said you hate all religious people.
Well, Nate, you just said you hate all religious people,
you know?
I do.
I do, I want to say that.
Like you thought it was a joke,
like you still, there's still some disdain
for religious people.
They're holding us back,
and I, oh my God, you totally got me.
You're absolutely right.
So, I'm a total hypocrite.
It's just like, we're always gonna have like prejudices.
And like, the thing is that like these prejudices,
they don't always come into play, you know?
Like, it's, I think it's less about our thoughts-
I like to think that this is a very
parental brain.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Go ahead.
You can dislike somebody,
but as long as you don't let that,
like affect your day-to-day interactions,
that's what true tolerance is.
It's not about like loving everything.
It's just about like, you know,
letting bygones be bygones.
Like, you know?
Yeah, the best case scenario for the future
is that when somebody is like racist or whatever,
or dislikes a whole group of people,
they would just, they would channel it into apathy.
They would just be like,
oh, fuck that guy, I don't care, whatever.
It does, because it tends to not affect you directly.
Most of the time.
You know what this reminds me of?
This reminds me of my award-winning video on T-Bap.
Keg reviews, putting your hoof down.
The world-famous My Little Pony episode.
Speaking of people I hate, fuck Bronies.
They're the worst.
It's just, Fluttershy is this cute little pony,
but in that episode, we learn that deep down,
she has a burning hatred for everyone in her life.
But what makes her the fitting element of kindness
is that she is able to suppress that rage.
Is that she looks past her friends,
horrible inadequacies.
Yes, that's right.
And she pretends to like them anyway.
And that's why she's the best guy ever.
She is the best.
Yeah.
Oh, I like that one.
I'm gonna put that in my book.
It's funny that you bring up My Little Pony,
because, and this sounds like a non sequadar,
but I'm gonna make it make sense.
Recently, they released on YouTube the teaser
for the My Little Pony movie.
Is this the real one with the actual ponies now?
Oh, that's exciting.
What are you talking about?
Well, you know, as opposed to like the humans,
as opposed to equestria girls.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's the real.
That's not the movie.
But the teaser on YouTube has like mostly thumbs down.
And at first I'm like,
why the fuck does this teaser have so many thumbs down?
And then I realized, oh,
it's because people still hate bronies.
And like, this is like putting bronies
in the forefront again, I guess.
And it's like, yeah, and it's like,
how can people still be invested in like not,
like how can people still give a shit
about bronies like existing?
And it's the same thing with social justice.
Like when I hear people complaining
about social justice warriors now,
I just roll my eyes like,
how the fuck can you still care?
That you've been, you people have been circle jerking
about this supposed problem with social justice warriors
that's gonna destroy society for fucking like,
like almost 10 years now.
And you just, it's never gonna stop.
It's just gonna go in circles forever and ever.
And both sides are gonna continue destroying society
in tandem because they're never gonna stop
fucking throwing shit at each other.
And everyone in the middle is going to get rained on
by all this fucking poo punch from the sky forever.
How can you still fucking care?
That's the problem.
It's people caring too much about stupid bullshit
that doesn't matter.
People care too much about the president.
They care too much about, you know,
whatever goofy social issue scandal of the day is going on.
People posting on Facebook,
arguing with their friends and family members
about everything.
Everyone's a fucking social justice warrior now
about something.
Everyone's got a fucking hill to die on about something
and fucking argue with everyone about something.
And it's just like, you know what the problem is?
It's that people are fucking empty and bitter
and sad and pathetic.
They hate their lives.
They hate themselves and they can't admit it.
And they've never fucking loved anyone.
That's what the problem is.
I think if you've ever just cared about another human being,
then you would have some kind of fucking empathy
or compassion inside you.
And you would realize that all of this fucking
tribalistic shit is fucking goofy, man.
It's that the problem, people are stupid.
They have no lives.
They don't love each other.
No one has ever fucking loved anyone.
No one loves themselves anymore.
They're all cancer.
Everything is cancer.
Everything is bad and nothing is good.
The world is irreparably broken.
And I'm the only one who fucking sees it.
No one else can see it.
You know what you remind me of, Jesse?
You know that comic of XKCD about all the people on the bus
having the same thought about how they're the only
smart one in the world.
Yes, and I'm all the people on the bus
and nobody else is on my bus.
Exactly.
That's right.
Hey, Jesse, you know who you were on me of?
Have you ever seen a little show called
Bojack Horseman, bro?
LOL.
You're like that one.
You know, I think, I understand why it's gone like this.
It's because the internet is based mostly in text.
And through text, you can't ascertain someone's
like real mood or the way they're saying something.
And we've seen it in our chat.
Like sometimes we'll be arguing and we won't actually
be as mad as we seem like we are.
And then on the internet, people,
they see these things on Twitter,
they argue over forums and Facebook and stuff.
And they come away thinking that these other people
are way angrier than they actually are.
And that's sort of like, it's gone in circles
and cycles and cycles and circles.
And to the point where people themselves
are in general being angrier.
There's a great communication is on the internet.
It's just people accusing each other of being mad
over and over again in a circle.
There's this great little flash game on Newgrounds
called You Become What You Behold.
Oh yeah.
And it's like a bunch of little stick figures
running around a room and you have like a camera.
And you can take pictures of things
and they show up on the TV screen in the middle of a room
and all the stick figures look at it and they react to it.
And basically what the point of the game is that
like they only care, like the stick figures only care
if you photograph something like bad happening.
So you'll photograph people that like bump into each other
and fight each other like a square and a circle
because they have different shaped heads.
Like a square and a circle will get mad at each other.
You photograph that and you put it on the screen
and then more like squares and circles
get mad at each other.
And you just like take more and more pictures
of like the people being mad at each other
because it keeps happening until everyone's mad
at each other and then it erupts.
And it creates this like sort of racist thing going on
between the squares and circles.
Yeah, everything was fine before.
Everything was fine before but because the racial tension
was so like brought to the forefront of media,
everyone like perceived it to be a bigger deal
than it was and then it got worse as a result.
Yeah, and the thing I really like about that
is that once it starts getting bad
and you try taking pictures of nice things happening,
it doesn't help, it just always continues to be worse.
Yeah, that's so, that's, that is an absolutely brilliant
representation.
It's true, I retweet wholesome memes every day
and the world still isn't fixed.
You're doing your part too.
You're doing, so, Jess, I don't want to misinterpret
your argument before I go against it.
So are you saying we shouldn't be talking about SJWs
in the first place because they aren't causing
any real harm?
No, I think that they are causing harm,
but I think that, you know, if you give a shit, fuck you.
So what harm, what harm would you say that they're causing?
I don't understand a question.
You literally just said they're causing harm,
so what harm are they causing?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Maybe you can give an example.
Okay, sure.
Job lynch mobs, that's an entirely SJW run thing.
People losing their jobs for having the wrong opinion
for saying the wrong word.
These SJWs are dangerous because they'll go after
these people online, they'll contact their employer,
they'll contact their family, their friends,
do whatever they can to ruin their lives.
Just because they have the wrong opinion politically,
or they say a word out of context or something.
So that's an example of how SJWs cause harm.
You're ascribing a philosophy to behavior,
but the behavior is done by people with all manner
of political and social stances.
I mean, it's not just social justice warriors
harassing people or setting out to fuck with people
or ruin each other's lives.
Everyone does that.
I mean, are you gonna tell me that?
Are you gonna tell me that polox don't go around?
Not polox the country, I mean like 4chan kids.
Are you gonna tell me that people on the right
don't do the same thing?
Yes, you've already defined for all of us
that social justice warriors are both into the spectrum.
So let's say I automatically agree with you.
If I'm saying social justice warriors
means angry idiots who care too much about stupid shit
and fight each other, then they, yeah, they just.
Oh yeah, well then that's definitely the,
yeah, that's the problem,
but the way to fight that problem
is not by caring more in response.
I think the way to solve it,
not that I would know,
but I think is just to be a nicer person in real life
and leave the internet alone a bit more.
Yeah, I think the problem in general
is just to leave the internet.
Everyone, okay, the thing is we can't leave the internet
because that is real life now.
The internet is like the essential highway
through which everything important is done now.
You can't just, you know, ignore it.
You can't ignore it, but you can't listen it,
you can't like forget about Facebook.
Even if you, okay, I mean like if everyone did this,
then okay, that would make a difference,
but not everyone is going to be able to do this.
And currently, if I write a story saying, you know,
PewDiePie is a Nazi,
here are a bunch of screenshots that prove that,
no one knows.
I mean, immediately, they will first of all,
just see the headline and that will already,
like a billion people see it if I'm someone important,
like the fucking Wall Street Journal or whatever,
that will already make people flip out.
And it's just the reaction to that
without looking into the details,
which were 100% false in this case about PewDiePie.
It was just a bunch of stuff that were,
I mean, you could call it bad jokes,
but at no point was he ever advocating
for any of this stuff.
It was all just, in fact,
much of the time he was making fun of Nazis.
That is true, I mean.
Nonetheless, it's the response that is inevitable
in the day and times that we live in right now,
that people will flip out and corporations are forced,
as money-making machines, to react to it,
no matter what the actual truth is,
just if people are mad, they have to act
if they want to keep their problems up.
Well, on the PewDiePie thing, I mean,
I think we all agree that it's trumped up charges
and it's fucking ridiculous and false claims
and it's retarded. Of course, it's been proven many times.
You know, it's just people lying for clicks
and they should all be hung.
But it's not as though the people on that side
or whatever don't have a point at all,
because the idea that a guy with PewDiePie,
with all this reach and this young audience,
this impressionable audience,
the idea that joking about Nazis and stuff
and joking about rightist ideas, right ideas,
is seeping into young, impressionable minds
and making them who might not be as in tune
with satire or the memory behind it all,
that they might grow to honestly believe it.
I mean, that's obviously true.
That does happen.
I mean, that's what memes are.
Memes are just thought control.
It's just the way that people spread their message
in a humorous way.
It is impressioning minds to feel a certain way.
I mean, I don't think that that's
the entertainer's responsibility at all
to give a shit about that,
but I mean, it is a valid point in some small way.
You know, I kind of do think it is,
I sort of agree actually on the,
I do think that you have a responsibility as PewDiePie,
like legally you're not going to be held
to any kind of standard, like, oh, you have to,
you know, make people smart or whatever,
but there's definitely a responsibility
if you're reaching millions of people every single day
with the things you say to not be a monster,
which he's not, but like the worst thing he did,
the objectively worst thing he did was make a joke
about like, wow, will these guys on Fiverr
actually write a sign that says death to all Jews
or like kill all Jews or whatever it was,
even though it was that followed by subscribe to Keemstar.
I mean, I definitely think that like PewDiePie
was like the wrong target to make that point with
because all he does is make silly jokes.
But any story about PewDiePie gets views,
so that's the perfect one to do it about.
I mean, like, if they were saying that like,
that like, Sargon of Akkad is the problem,
then maybe they'd have more of a case.
I, I, okay.
I don't really watch him,
but I assume it's, he's basically the amazing atheist,
but different slightly.
What does he talk about?
Sargon has transformed.
I admit, I watch Sargon and he has,
he has transformed over views.
He just talks about social justice issues,
just like, you know, free speech and shit like that, you know?
Yeah, that's true.
He was speaking to Brexit because he's in England.
Yeah.
That was the thing that we talked about.
I think, well, we tend to bash Sargon.
He's very, he's very evidence-based.
I mean, he definitely has his agenda
in that he has his opinions and, you know,
presents them where appropriate.
We tend to bash Sargon a lot on this show,
but it's mostly because I can't think of any other names
that are in that genre.
Yeah, like, I have famously feuded on Twitter
with Sargon of a kind.
Yes.
Earning Ben swaths of Patreon bucks, right?
It's not that I think that Sargon is the worst of his kind.
It's that, it's that I hate his whole kind
and he's just the one that comes to mind the easiest.
He's just the first, he's just the first name I think of
when I think of like right-leaning internet pundits.
I, yeah, I hear what you're saying.
I do think, just, I don't know,
this is even appropriate to say now.
It's just that I do think that he's gotten more concerned
about providing factual like reasoning
behind what he's saying and he does a lot of reading
and presents like, oh, well, I read this book, you know,
fucking The Republic by Plato or whatever
and it has this idea.
I'm applying that to this thing I see happening.
So I don't know why I'm defending the guy.
Yeah, I mean, and obviously if there was like a,
like a left-leaning pundit that I could equally think of
to name and shit on him that I would, you know.
Anita.
Anita's the one.
I hate that, I hate the fact that
in order to shit on someone,
you have to find someone on the opposite end of the spectrum
to also shit on or else everyone's going to accuse you
of being on that side.
That's, yeah, that's true.
That's where we're at.
Well, it's the cultural binary.
It's always been there, that's bullshit.
You're right on.
There's a guy I found recently called Quinton Reviews
who he made, he's made a couple of drama videos about,
but he, and a few reviews and stuff.
And he seems like really nuanced.
Like he's like exactly in the middle
in terms of being a totally reasonable human being.
And I kind of really love that because he's like,
he's actually kind of, he's got a hundred thousand subs
and he's like doing decently well
and he's not crazy on one side or the other.
Like he did a review of Ghostbusters
and he actually talked about, you know,
the new one.
Mofeminism, Mofeminism!
But he actually like went into it like,
like as a normal person, like a real human being.
And he said, well, you know, it's just an okay movie
and all this and that.
And then he explained what it was, you know,
cause like every other video about Ghostbusters
that I had seen was like, oh my God,
I can't believe everyone likes it
or I can't believe anyone hates it.
It's like, whatever.
I mean, I'm not trying-
And his video is really nice.
I mean, I'm not trying to say that like it's impossible
to examine these issues from an unbiased
or at least from a nuanced perspective
or that like, you know, opinions are just bad
and nobody should say anything about any social issue.
I just, I'm just so like wary of people who care too much.
I don't trust them.
When I feel like someone gives too much of a shit
about these issues, they just come off like they're just like,
they must be like an empty, bitter weirdo to me.
I mean, I think-
I guess there's just people who are into politics
and social issues.
I think that's what makes an SJW
is someone that cares too much about it.
Yeah.
To an unhealthy level.
And I think we should bring back you, Mad Bro.
That should really like grow.
I don't know about that.
That's the equivalent of get good.
It's a discussion ending.
It's like they are mad and they'll be like,
I'm not mad and then they'll feel stupid for being mad
and then they'll try and be normal.
I suppose that's true.
Yeah, you can tell a gamer goes into an old spaghetti factory
and breaks all the dishes.
What are you gonna do about liberals?
He, that munchie really leveled up.
No!
Oh God.
Guys, Gamergate.
Gamergate was cool, right?
Remember that?
Guys, look at how fucking Gamergate.
Well, I don't know what there is to say.
Gamergate was a bunch-
No, no, it was a joke, Nate.
It was a joke.
No, actually, don't actually start talking about it.
Okay, abort, abort.
Okay, DeVoo, you know, here's something
that's interesting.
DeVoo, I see this-
Wait, have we done a PCP on Gamergate yet?
We told you!
We have!
No!
At least we are firmly post Gamergate
so we can kind of assess it.
Gamergate PCP, it'll be a bonus episode.
I'm gonna kick that bonus episode.
Gamergate, what's the problem?
The next bonus episode, Gamergate,
starring only Munchie.
You know what, that could be plain everyone else.
We should do it as a bonus episode.
That would be pretty funny.
It would be a fucking bad idea.
The only reason I don't want to do it
is because I had never looked into any of it
and I don't care so much.
I, that's the exact right perspective.
It was, I feel like, not until months after it ended.
Did I even begin to understand what Gamergate referred to?
I was very invested in it for like the first three days of it
and then it went on for like seven more months
and I'm like, what is wrong with you people?
What's going on?
Why do you care?
Hey, you know, I wanna talk about...
It's because that slut Zoey Quinn
slept her way to the top of the video game
and I am insane!
I'm a Gamer!
I pricked my bones!
I, man, I know a lot of shit about her that I read.
But anyway, so Davoo mentioned something else.
In the chat, he just said like,
the Young Turks was all the time posted.
Yeah, that's an example of like a left-leaning pundit
on YouTube.
The interesting thing about the Young Turks is that,
I'm coming out.
I'm going like the Young Turks.
I'm coming out of the closet.
I watch the Young Turks all the fucking time.
All the time, I watch the Young Turks.
Among the most politically invested among us.
I mean, I think Monkey might also be, but...
That's possibly true.
Here's the thing about the Young Turks though.
Cenk Yuger, the main guy.
I fucking love Cenk Yuger as a person.
He is like the most fun and the most goofy and silly
and I love everything he says until he starts talking
about his SJW shit when I want to kill myself.
Like the left-leaning Alex Jones a little bit.
Oh, he would get so mad.
I was thinking that same thing the other day.
He would flip his shit because he hates Alex Jones.
Did you ever see that video where they fought?
It was great.
Of course, of course.
It was nuts.
Have you ever watched Karen Strone or whatever?
Strone?
The fucking Gourds, what?
The short haired lady.
She's like an anti-feminist talker
and she's very articulate and, you know,
among the least retarded ones, I think.
But she was on there, like that guy was just yelling at it
like, shut up!
Yes, you are oppressed, you fucking idiot!
You stupid idiot!
You so oppressed!
Shut up!
That blows my mind.
It's so weird to see a fucking straight,
almost white male telling a woman how oppressed she is
when she's arguing against that.
It's just, I mean, I get what's going on here.
He might as well be hitting on himself.
And I gotta say, one of the things,
the biggest problem for me with Cenk in general
is that he has this fucking retarded feud
with one of my favorite people on the internet right now,
Sam Harris.
He has been fucking, just the other day,
I'm watching the show,
I'm watching the stream on like Friday or something.
He just, he brings in a little joke
just to shit on like Sam Harris out of nowhere
because he just fucking hates the guy
after he's the one who took all his arguments out of context
and just doesn't understand what it is he's being.
It's so fucking weird that he still is doubling down
on that after Sam Harris fucking destroyed him
for like an hour.
I get it, he doesn't like it.
Like now they're just fighting,
now they just hate each other.
But he got to that place,
there's such a fucking retarded clusterfuck
of his own circular, I'm sorry, I'm going on a rant.
It sounds like you care a lot about it.
I'm invested in that.
And that means you're social justice,
you're social justice warrior.
I can't watch these fucks.
And that means you need to Pokemon go to the polls
to cleanse yourself.
I need to vote for Hillary like 20 times
to cleanse myself of this.
That's my ablution.
Memes are cool, I like the jokes,
but I don't like the political ones.
Hey, you know who doesn't like jokes?
SJWs, those are offensive.
Hey, let's talk about cultural appropriations.
Let me talk about what I want to talk about.
I go on YouTube and I go to my subscriptions
and I have like, oh, there's another tab, trending.
Let me reconnect with my fellow humans.
What do they think is popular right now?
It's all like anti-Donald Trump shit
and I always watch it.
Oh God, I hate the trending hashtags so fucking much.
It's the worst, it's the worst.
You guys don't like that shit?
I almost always agree.
And yeah, I basically always agree.
I watched Donald Trump's stuff
and I wanna know why is there not stuff
like this for the right,
because I want to watch every political opinion
and then forward afterwards.
I think we know why.
They don't want you to see that shit.
They are controlling it.
There's no, all they have to do is add one tag
about whatever to flag things as offensive
and it won't, you know,
because they control the system.
They control it, right.
You know, there's no doubt in my mind.
I have been enjoying like Razorfists' rants
about Donald Trump, people who hate him.
Cause Razor, you know, what is the rageaholic guy?
Yeah, Razorfists is great.
Yeah, right, right.
I like the fact that he's quick with his videos.
So I don't have to sit
through a 40 minute lecture or a podcast.
That's kind of the problem with a lot of the alternative media,
quote unquote, is they tend to be very long-winded
because they're exhaustive in their points and stuff.
Yeah, Saigon of a card.
I think I've watched one video of Saigon's
and it was just him sentence by sentence
reacting to someone's video
and it was like a 40 minute video.
And I can't imagine unless I was already invested
in his content that anyone would like
I think that's kind of the problem
with the alternative media and what's kind of happening.
Like a great, a great channel
if you want something that's like really unbiased
for that is the Rubin report.
I don't know if you guys ever, you've been heard about it.
Oh yeah, I'm familiar with him.
But he just interviews people from like all sides of.
You know what they say, never rub another man's Rubin.
He is gay.
That's true.
He would rub his own Rubin.
I don't get it.
But I think the problem is that
when you have someone like a Saigon of a card
and guys like that, is that because it's become their job
they have to kind of keep placating to their audience.
So I think that's a real thing.
That's a real thing.
Oh man, even if they don't realize it, that happens.
That fucking steams me up.
That fucking, yeah, because like,
because their commenters are all people
that agree with them and are in their fucking echo chamber
and they, and because they're surrounded by people
that like love them and believe in what they're doing,
they're like, yes, what I'm doing is good.
I'm making a positive contribution to this world
because all my followers and fans think so.
And I don't want to have to stress.
I don't mean to.
Now they're trapped, they're trapped in the cycle
where the way that they make money and be popular
is by hating on the other.
And they're like, they couldn't,
like they have no motivation to do anything else.
They have a monetary incentive not to change their mind.
Yeah, yes.
It doesn't have to be necessarily malicious.
That's so fucking much.
Like imagine a situation if you're any of these guys
and you have two stories to talk about,
one that is like a vindication of Hillary in some way
or one that's about her fucking up in another way.
Like what do you think your audience
is going to want to hear more?
Like that's all it comes down to.
That's like the big problem.
And I mean, it's hard to put the blame squarely on them
just because like, again, like that's how they make their money
and they can't control their audience.
It's not like when your audience is whipped up
into a frenzy, how is it like, you know, like that's,
I agree with the fact that they should be unbiased,
but I never, I've always gotten upset
when people have blamed them for like,
your audience is just circle jerking in the comments.
How dare you?
It's like, well, there you don't control
what the comments are, you know?
It's not something that they do, but unfortunately,
like it's interesting.
There's a guy who does this kind of videos.
His name's Harmful Opinions.
And he-
Yep, I know him.
That guy is a fucking maniac.
He's pretty, he like went against the whole grain
and people have been giving him shit for it,
but he's slowly starting to get people back to his side
because like, there was that app, that candid app,
that everyone was like, this is like a free speech app,
and it wasn't, and he was the only one talking about it,
but everyone else was under contract.
He seemed to be right in the end.
He seemed right.
So, I don't know.
I know way too much about all these people.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Well, you know, it's drama.
It's interesting.
You can't help but admit that, you know,
you click on it because, ooh, what's all this about?
Actually, I wasn't subscribed to drama with these guys
until like three days ago,
and I just unsubbed from everyone.
So I was like, I have more important things to do
than watch all this stuff,
even though like, I'm kind of invested in like,
the whole like social kind of game going on right now,
because I just find it interesting.
Well, see, that gets back to kind of Jesse's point
about like, you know,
should you really concern yourself with it too much?
And like, I say, you know, I don't quite agree.
I don't quite agree.
I think that, I am concerned about like,
yeah, I am concerned about the future
and the way things are going.
And like, this back and forth, sorry to just interrupt,
but I mean, my whole thing is like this,
this cultural back and forth is just perpetuating itself
because everyone's fighting fire with fire, you know,
they're fighting the extremism with more extremism.
Everyone, I mean, I guess your instinct is to think
that the way to combat all these people being wrong
is to be right, but it doesn't matter.
You're not gonna affect anything.
All you're gonna do is make more people go back and forth.
The only way to solve what you do.
The only real solution is to find the people in your life
that you care about and just hang out with them
and be nice and be normal and take yourself out
of this fucking insane war zone of shit-flinging.
Just take yourself out of it.
Oh yeah, see, what if I haven't got any friends?
Then you should die.
Oh no.
Yeah, I think you're right though.
And I can easily see like all these,
oh yeah, all these things,
these people like pawning each other
and coming out with videos,
like whoever you're already on the team of,
you're just gonna get more polarized.
There is not a lot of course correction
so much as deepening of adherence
to one side of the other.
This whole meta-narrative could be solved
if there was just compromise.
Compromise, if both ends of the extremes
could just sit down and just give a little ground,
get a little ground and just like, okay.
You don't have to do that.
But there's no incentive to do that.
Yeah, you know what, there's no financial incentive,
there's no cultural incentive.
Because that's the whole problem
with having this all broadcast on social media
is that shitting on the other person
gets you more attention than trying to solve the problem.
Like does anybody on either side invested
in solving the problem anymore?
Yeah.
Well, I've noticed this, I mean,
it's this kind of like this neutrality shaming again
to get back on that old fucking topic.
Oh dude, yes.
Yeah, it's because, you know, like Centrist
has been made into like a dirty world now.
And it's like, you never see people
just like coming down from like their extreme.
If you see anyone change their mind at all,
it's always I was one extreme and now I'm the other.
I see articles all the time of like,
I was on the alt-right and now I'm fixed
because I'm on this side or I was a social justice ward
and now I'm fixed because I'm on the other side.
And it's like, no, you're not fixed.
You just look like to another cancer.
You just treated one cancer for another.
Dude, it's that horseshoe theory, dude.
It's that horseshoe theory that you offer
the size of the spectrum resembling.
It all comes back to drowning in horseshoes,
the greatest YouTube channel video thing of all time.
It all comes back to that.
Horseshoe will never finally be solved.
The most fucking prophetic, brilliant,
artistic vision ever created by mankind.
There's this thing that if you're a centrist,
then what you are to the left is too far right and a racist.
Or if you're a centrist to the left,
then you're a fucking Nazi.
It's almost as if like the horseshoe is endless.
I'm a bitch!
The war is finally coming together.
We finally are cracking the code.
But yeah, it's like, because I mean,
if you're a centrist, then you're both sides' worst enemy.
You're everything to everybody that they,
you're every villain they want to paint you as.
Because I mean, I make a lot of opinion-based videos,
not because I particularly care about my opinion,
but because it's like a launching pad for comedy for me.
But you know, I can't help but have opinions.
I can't help but say stuff.
I fucking say things.
But because I am more towards the center,
I guess, on most things.
It's like, you know, I'm hated by everyone in the world.
That's why people fucking hate me so much.
I've been called a social justice warrior.
More times than I can count,
I've been called a fucking whatever the opposite-
You said that being puppy cat comic.
That was pretty-
I've been called an alt-right, like a Nazi.
More times than I can.
I've been called everything by both sides.
Yeah, fucking, I've been called the social justice word
because I did a video complaining
that there was a page bent in my being puppy cat comic.
You're a monster!
Like half the comments were like,
Oh, you read that fucking SDW trash unsubscribed.
What the fuck is this?
It's a comic about a girl with a cat.
I just wanted to read it.
It's because, all right, that's the thing.
That's what happens to all conversations.
They boil down to like the most like drama-y issue
about that thing.
Like what do we, what do you think of when you think of like-
Nobody is talking about the real issues,
which is that I was sold a comic
with a fucking weird bent page in it.
That when I unbent it,
it was like longer than the other pages.
How did it even get printed that way?
I don't know.
It's a mystery.
This is a thing that's very much on my mind these days.
Like the new Ghost in the Shell movie came out recently.
Like all anyone ever fucking talked about
was that Scarlett Johansson was cast as Motoko Kusanagi
or as the major whatever.
Like that drives me up the fucking wall
because the intellectual content of Ghost in the Shell
is the most interesting thing in the world.
And all anyone's fucking talking about
is the race of the main character.
You're missing the entire fucking point of the thing.
I do think it's saying-
It really fucking sucks and makes me mad
that they made them all white, but whatever.
That's not important.
Well, I just think it's far, far more important
to talk about transhumanism.
I would kind of find it hilarious.
Her name's fucking Kusanagi.
Why the fuck is she white?
Never mind.
Look, I'll tell you all about it.
Shut up, I will say something.
Yeah, okay.
That fucking once you're training, it's paying off.
Yes, yes, yes.
Breathe in, son.
All right, I was gonna say it was just a joke,
but I was gonna say it would be legitimately hilarious
and I would love it if they went too far with the thing
and they made the entire Avengers,
but everyone's a black guy or everyone's a black woman.
And it would just be like-
Dude, give Marvel the Avengers,
they're working on this to comics.
Yeah, they can make a Ghostbusters remake with all the women.
Oh, God, that would never work.
That wouldn't make any sense.
It's a man's story about a man's business
and a man finding a place in the world.
Women have no place in the workforce.
That movie would never work.
Yeah, you know, really?
I would just plain the legend of Zelda.
You may have heard of it
and when you said that, the controller dropped out of my hand.
What do you think you're talking about?
But games.
I am the most blue-pilled.
Ghostbusters, the remake is my favorite movie.
Coming soon, the Avengers, the Spike Lee joint.
What do you think about the whole thing
where if you've got a team of dudes, it is now-
Whoa, whoa, whoa, that's a real problematic premise
for a movie.
That doesn't pass the Bec Del Test,
even one little bit, buddy.
I didn't even mean all men, I just meant people.
I just used the word dudes.
Well, that's problematic too.
I know that's problematic.
So if you've got a bunch of people in any group or whatever,
it's now expected that the ratios will be like,
okay, you can have one white guy,
and then you want one of each race.
Yeah, tokenism.
Right, tokenism, but the thing is,
well, what I'm talking about, tokenism is one issue,
but I'm just saying, the fact of the matter is,
like white people are roughly 60% of America right now,
so you'd expect there to be
roughly 60% representation in whatever.
But that doesn't seem to be acceptable anymore.
You know what I'm saying?
This gets to the heart of the issue of representation,
which is like, I think that it would be pretty swell
if everyone was more or less equally represented,
but I also think that it sucks when people are like,
let's have our cast of characters, they're all white.
We gotta make some black ones.
We gotta make some gay ones.
We gotta do that.
Like, I hate that, and it's terrible.
I hate when those decisions are made for a good reason
that isn't artistic.
Everyone thinks that everyone, yeah.
Everyone, no, no, no, wait, wait, let's talk, let's talk.
Let me see, let me see.
I'm just saying, I hate it that the playing field is skewed,
but I think that the measures taken
to deliberately unskiew it are skeevy and almost worse.
It just seems like everyone thinks the way to empower
one group is to disenfranchise or tear down another.
Could Tom repeat a statement,
because that's like my favorite thing.
Can you say that again, Tom?
I forgot what I said.
Well, you just said like, you hate that any decision
is made for a good reason.
Oh, any decision and anything is made for any reason
other than artistic reasons.
And that's, you know what?
It almost, it's almost like this makes me
almost like approaching racists sometimes.
That sounds terrible, but let me explain.
When they take something, you know,
like when they recast a character
and make always a black guy now,
or they just have like a black guy in like something
or any sort of like non-white person.
Now, because like social justice is everywhere
and I know about and I can't get out of my head,
I always have to think, was this an artistic decision
or are they playing the fucking SJW card?
Yeah, that sucks because sometimes.
And I can't appreciate their performance anymore.
I just want to appreciate art.
Fuck you for making you have to even think that shit.
I know you're gonna say it.
I want to say it.
Let me say it.
I'm gonna say the exact same thing you're gonna say.
Fine.
Thank you.
Okay, there are some times we're fucking like,
oh, like, oh, I'm a corporate exec.
I have money in my pockets.
Let's go do it.
Put the black people there.
Well, most of the time I would argue
is that that's what the guy, he wants it to do.
Like, I like black people.
I'll put a black guy here.
Yeah, sometimes it's good.
Sometimes it's good, but the times.
Because that's what Hillary wants.
Sometimes it's good, but then like,
there's the other times when like,
it's clearly tokenism and that makes it all bad.
But Jesse, let me break up an example.
Let me break up an example real quick.
And it's one Jesse told me about.
So in the Dark Tower movie they're making,
like they're making the main character dude
played by a black guy, but in the original,
and so I guess they're making a change artistically.
And that's not a big deal in and of itself,
but like, there are issues
where there is a black female character
that has very specific race-based relations
with the main character that are now fucked.
Like what is the, the entire arc of like the third book
is Dettel Walker and Odetta Holmes.
She's like, she's two people.
She's a split personality.
But like the whole arc of her character
in the third book is her, you know,
kind of getting over her prejudice and racism
because she grew up in fucking like segregated
60s world against Roland, this old white ass
Clint Eastwood looking motherfucker gunslinger.
And like that's her arc.
I mean, I don't even know if she's gonna be in the movie,
but it's-
Wait, the black person has to get over their racism
towards the white person?
Yeah, we can't have that.
That doesn't make sense.
Guys, the obvious answer is we're just gonna make
the black girl a white girl
and then it'll be exactly as good.
Whoa, whoa, no, no, no, no, no.
You cannot have a white woman or any white character
ever upset with the race of another person.
That's not allowed.
It's not allowed.
What I hate about the, like the race-baiting
in like Hollywood casting,
because I see it a lot and it's not just that they do it,
but like the dishonesty and the like outright lies
from everyone involved, like you'll have like,
like when they cast Hermione as a black chick in the-
I was just gonna bring that up.
Yeah, like-
Like J.K. Rowling being like,
well I never said she wasn't black.
Like, yes you fucking did!
You literally slid the buck.
Yeah, it hurts you really?
I think she tweeted.
I think she tweeted like, you know,
it never says she's not black.
Yeah, but you know, because she's,
all it says is like she's got frizzy hair.
Shut up, J.K. Rowling.
Like, there's other characters in the book,
like Blaise Zambini and that guy who fucking,
the Gryffindor who reads the fucking announcements
at the Quidditch, that's explicitly called them black.
If Hermione was black, you would have said black,
because you said that about other characters.
Don't fucking lie to me.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, and I kind of should be raising my thing for you.
She did the same thing with Dumbledore.
She did the same fucking thing with Dumbledore,
pretending that he was gay all along.
No, he fucking wasn't.
You don't even know what being gay means, J.K. Rowling,
because Dumbledore is clearly asexual,
and he had a crush on a guy one time like 70 years ago,
and you're like, oh yeah, he's gay.
He's always been gay.
J.K. Rowling, you-
That's just so they can check the gay character box.
That's what they want to do.
Exactly, that's what they want.
You fucking cuck.
Don't pretend like this was your grand plan.
You, ooh, I love your work, but I hate you so much.
Hey, guys, I'm excited to meet you.
Can I just bring up one more example?
Wait, it's kind of, it's kind of gone.
That kind of reminds me of a, of a, of a-
Fuck, kill me.
I feel so Caucasian.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Homestuck's important.
Homestuck, right?
Like, fan art, I've seen like, like every single character
in every single color.
And at first I was like, ah, that's, I thought,
mm, I didn't, mm, I guess that, ooh.
It's like, I wasn't sure about it,
and they hadn't been explicit,
because like, all the characters are like,
literally like, ff, ff, ff, ff, ff, white.
Right, right.
Because that's just the, the style of the thing.
But then the-
They're supposed to pay respects, ff, ff.
But then there are the, yeah,
then there are the trolls, which are like gray,
so they have a skin color.
Right, right.
And then is, are all the other characters white?
And some people say, well, it's up to interpretation.
And then it's like, I guess.
Hussey says like, yeah, you know,
I never said they're white,
like it's open to interpretation.
And the response, like the shitty response to that is like,
oh yeah, but they're white-coded.
And then, and then that gets into like,
okay, well what is white-coding?
Like, what is a white person supposed to be?
What behaviors signal a white person to you?
And like-
Oh, you know, I'm a superior intellect.
It's just that I remember that it sort of,
it sort of rubbed me, rubbed me the wrong way initially,
but now I'm totally cool with it.
Like, if I see like, somebody does a fan out of sands
or something, and he's like, he's a human sands,
and he's like, you know,
he's got all these weird tumbler things.
Oh, are you talking about human tail?
Yes, that's a similar sort of thing,
where people tumbler things,
they love attributing characters for things,
making them human, and then giving them a bunch of shit,
and it's like-
You know what fucking grinds my gears anymore?
About human tail, what grinds my fucking gears
is how they do this thing where they're like,
assigning sexualities to each character,
where like, that's not evident in their,
like, okay, like-
Well, here's the thing, here's the thing with that.
Pretty clearly gay, or bi, or something.
But like, we don't know that Frisk
is a weird pansexual demi-
Demi-boy.
That's not evident.
Yeah.
My point is that it used to rub me the wrong way,
but I realized they're just having fun,
so I don't really care.
So I just let them have their fun.
Yeah, I mean, to that extent, yeah.
Real quick, I'm rereading it as we speak,
and the only character so far
that has been canonically white has been Bro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, he's been stated that he's been white.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
That does happen.
So, Dave-
From that, we know that his genes were given to both,
you know, Roxy and-
Spoilers.
Oh, yeah.
Homestuck, guys.
Welcome to the Homestuck PCP.
So we know that Dave and Rose are both at least half white.
This is what we know.
What the fuck is homestuck?
No one knows, dude.
Can I just bring up-
Good.
Let me bring up just one more example
that always bothered me, and then we can move on.
And it was just in The Witcher 3,
The Witcher 3, I'm a Pollock.
I'm a Pollock.
My people are from that land.
It's a story made by Polish people about Polish lore,
and there aren't, I mean, in the 16th century
or whatever the fuck,
there were not a lot of non-Polish people,
non-white people,
and when people see that game,
so imagine you're playing this game,
you play through it,
and all you see are white people,
and imagine getting mad that this game
did not have people who don't belong here historically?
This leads in directly to what I wanted to say.
You know what fucking pisses me off
and what I hate about people?
SJW or otherwise.
I hate, fucking hate, how for some reason,
some people have to be like,
I can't relate to anything unless they look like me.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Yeah, I know you're 100%.
Those people need to be beaten up badly.
I don't know if I agree.
I mean, yeah, I think you probably,
I mean, I think you should be able to identify-
Ben!
Let me finish, let me finish.
I think you should be able to identify
with a protagonist of any race.
But I think if you lived in a world
where like all the movies you watched,
like everyone was Asian and you were a white guy,
like even if there were other white guys around-
I watch fucking anime.
I think you would feel, well, that's different.
I think you would feel weird.
I think it, I really think it would affect
how you saw yourself.
You know what, okay, here's the thing.
I don't know if people might get mad at me about this.
Well, it's related.
It's that I think, yeah, I think you should be able
to relate to a protagonist of any race in theory,
but it's like when it's systemic
and when it's like, when there's broad trends,
like broad trends affect in this sort of thing,
affect how people feel and think.
Okay, well-
So you're saying it's okay for them to get mad
at something that's historically accurate?
What?
No.
I'm talking like the Witcher 3, like the Witchers, yeah.
Cause it's like the Bechdel test, right?
Like the fact that a movie does not pass the Bechdel test,
does not in and of itself make it a bad movie,
it's the fact that like so few movies
pass the Bechdel test.
That means that none of these individual movies
are necessarily damned and like a bad movie
because they don't pass it,
but it's the fact that this widespread trend
is like speaks to like a systemic problem.
Well, all right.
Same with like, and same with the overwhelming whiteness
of like protagonists in movies, that's what I'm saying.
Okay, but like, all right, with Witcher 3 specifically,
would you say that the solution to that anger
is to let them be angry and not change it
or to change the game and add different races in
even though they wouldn't make sense?
No, you should let them be angry
because in that case it makes sense
that everyone would be white.
Yeah, okay.
Right, right.
Well, here's the thing.
I don't know if I'm gonna get in trouble with saying this,
but like I sort of agree with Ben in at least a sense
because I mean, just one way I think about this
is I watch movies about, you know,
people who are from different cultures than me
and like I definitely can relate to it less
than I do to like a middle American, you know, story
or whatever, and as well as like,
I've moved to a mostly black neighborhood now
and like it's just like a sort of a different culture
around like, I grew up around like 99% white people.
Yeah, I'm a little white boy.
And like the neighborhood I live in now is just different
and it's not that the people are necessarily different,
it's just like when I'm in this neighborhood now
and if I see a black person, I just,
I know that they're like, or I don't know,
but like it's an indicator
because I'm a visual oriented creature as a human being,
it makes me think like, okay,
this person is from like a different culture than me
because this place I live now is different.
They're not the same sort of thing
that I've known my whole life.
So like there, and I'm, yeah, like I'm assuming
because I don't actually know this person,
but it's just sort of a hint
that there's a difference here.
And yeah, that's probably not, you know,
I hope I don't sound horrible here, but it's just a fact.
Like, you know, I agree.
Like, like, I'm like, I don't really feel,
I don't really feel like I'm racist at all,
but like, with it, when I feel a cultural,
well, like it's not about how people look,
it's about when I feel a cultural difference.
Like if they're speaking in a way
that is like not how I'm used to speaking,
then I'm like, well, that's different.
I don't know how to relate to that as well, you know?
I don't think there's anything,
is there anything wrong with that though?
I don't, there really is, I don't think so.
Like, I know it's probably, I think it's good,
it's good to be multicultural.
It's good to be multicultural, but like if you're not,
like, I don't think you're a bad person.
Yeah, Ben, what's the point you're trying to make?
Are you saying we, like, I agree with Tom.
I was just agreeing with Nate
that I feel that same way about cultures.
If I agree with Tom and that the artist is always the one
who should decide what the races are, we shouldn't,
like, do you want us to force more races?
He already said no, he already said no.
I said no to that.
Well, then what's the point?
I feel like, what are we even talking about?
Wait a minute, so we're talking about
having more representation in media,
and I think the point right now is that if there's,
but like, my point is that I think that no change
to be made that isn't done for artistic purpose.
And if for whatever reason, all these creators are just like,
this is how we think about it.
I don't think it should be arbitrarily changed
because, well, we need more black people.
I would, I don't, I'm not disagreeing with you
saying that like more, like, diverse cast
would necessarily be a bad thing.
All I'm saying is I want to be done
for natural organic reasons and not to check boxes off.
Here's what I think, I, this is, this is,
this is my opinion on this issue,
and this applies, this applies.
Hippo's been trying to say something, Ben.
What?
Let him say, let Hippo say something,
he's been trying to again.
I mean, it's like too late now, almost,
but I wanted to bring up the fact again,
like you said at the beginning,
I'm the only English guy in this American-centric podcast,
and that the whole thing of like things being unrelatable,
the vast majority of media that I've ever consumed
has been from America and with American things
like peanut butter and jelly sandwiches,
like that, I don't know what the fuck that is.
Taco Bell, we don't have that.
You don't have Taco Bell?
Oh, God.
You poor bastard.
I'm never moving there.
You know, that's Munchie's dad.
Munchie's dad is Taco Bell.
It's like all these American things that have been in like,
you know, every cartoon I've ever watched,
like Rugrats, I don't understand most of the things in that.
I mean, they're babies and they're weird,
but like there's, there's American things in there.
There's American references in all things that I've seen
to the point where I don't find it like,
I don't find it that I can't relate so much
if something is a different culture
because it's just, it's just one of many cultures
that I can relate to in, in that I know that they're different.
I don't really know what like not being,
it not relating to me.
I don't know what that does.
I don't know whether, like if I watch an anime
and it's got Japanese buildings and stuff,
like what does that mean if I can't relate to that thing?
I know, if I see enough anime,
I will be able to relate to it.
If I see enough American things,
I will be able to relate to it, you know, through that.
And then I don't even know what it means
to not relate to something.
What does it even do?
Yeah, Ben, could you,
could you maybe speak to like the damage you see being done
by there being a lack of representation?
Like is it just the level of comfort or something?
No, it's not the, it's not the level of comfort.
I think, I think that if when there's not enough,
when there's not diverse representation,
then it just contributes to an othering effect wherein,
wherein the inside group and the outside group
see themselves as distinct and opposed to one another.
So, okay.
I think that more, I think that,
I think that when media, if media was more inclusive,
then it would mean, it would, it would lessen,
it would lessen that like in and out group psychology.
So how do we do this, Ben?
Do you want, do you want like a government forced diversity
in your TV show or what?
No, here's, here's the best thing.
Here's the best solution I come up with.
No, I wouldn't, I don't think anyone should be,
compelled to do anything or make art any way
that they don't want to.
I think that the only viable solution to this at all,
and it's not great, but it's the best I can come up with is,
I just think that people should try to have,
should try to view novelty like positively
in a way that like, you know, like if you've got two,
I don't know, movies you wanna watch,
and one is like an American film,
and one is like a Pakistani film,
and you've never seen a Pakistani film before
or a film with like, with like a Pakistani director.
Maybe you could be like, oh, well that's neat.
You know, I just think, I think we should look,
I just think, I wish we just looked positively on that,
and I think if societally, we looked positively
on things that come from like diverse cultures,
and a novelty, and a novelty in that way, then I-
Only white movies win Oscars, like Moonlight,
that was an all white movie, just won the best picture.
Well that was like, it's like one dude, it's like one.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Look through the Oscar list of the last 50 fucking years, dude.
I think that should mostly be due to the fact
that the Oscars are bullshit,
and nobody should care about it.
Are you making an argument that they're just,
I'm just wondering, that there is
proportional representation in the Oscars for-
I'm not saying, I'm not saying-
Not you, I'm asking monkey.
Okay, are you saying that society on a whole
doesn't like things that are different,
and I just proved them wrong with the Oscars, I guess.
Well, you didn't actually present anything to say that.
What do you mean, what do you mean,
what is the trend in the Oscars that you're talking about?
I mean, the idea is that if society
doesn't like things that are different,
then the very white Oscar voting people
would only vote for the white movies,
so clearly they do have some-
So, hang on, are you saying that because Moonlight won,
that alone proves that there is no problem?
No, it's an example that shows that Ben
isn't entirely right in what he said.
I think-
I don't think that's true,
because a very small number of people actually decide
who win, and those are big lip cucks,
so first of all, they don't represent America in general,
and that doesn't solve any kind of problems.
It's not just about whiteness,
it's not just about blackness.
I don't know what movies won the Oscars
for the last 50 years,
but I'm betting that there's some noticeable trends
in what kinds of movies win Oscars.
I think-
For instance, they're all self-important and awful.
People like things that are familiar,
like in general, like on a human level,
I don't think you can ever change the entire universe.
And that's not a crime.
Yeah.
Well, I think it should be.
They're gonna like, I mean, yeah,
you can have ideals that we should all be introduced,
mixing and trying out new things,
but the fact of the matter is,
people generally don't care to do that,
and it's hard to try and convince them,
and I don't even know what the problem is anymore.
Okay, Beth, I have a question for you,
since you're kind of a social justice guy,
I wanna kind of satisfy you, okay?
Cause, no, because maybe you'll be on board with me on this
and thinking this is stupid,
because you're saying right now,
people should definitely try and experience more culture,
and go look at other stuff outside of their sphere
and bubble that they're familiar with.
Yeah, it would be nice.
Why is it that the same people who talk about that
also say that cultural appropriation
is the worst thing ever,
and you should stay inside your bubble
and never touch anything?
Cultural appropriation is the best thing ever.
Yeah.
Because it doesn't make any sense
that to get back to social justice worries in general,
I guess, is that, again,
they want all this more representation
of people to understand things outside their culture,
but then as soon as you touch anything else,
they're just like, that's mine, you can't have it.
They're just like, well, you're just raising the barriers
and bitching that there are barriers.
So what the fuck?
Yeah, I hate that.
I think we should all culturally appropriate all the time.
It would be, I wish I culturally appropriated more.
Sometimes I feel bad.
Sometimes I feel bad, like just how fucking white
me and my upbringing and my culture is.
But then I think about branching out,
and I'm like, that sounds hard,
and not doing that is easy.
I would really like more toast in my movies.
You want the government to force people to eat toast?
No, I just think that societally,
we should agree to give toast more money in the box office.
Hey, you know, I had an uncle Phil, right?
And he was white, because, you know,
my family's white, I'm a white boy.
Unfortunately.
Yeah, but I had an uncle Phil,
and that means that I could technically be
a white Will Smith in the Fresh Prince of White Bel Air.
Could I, would it be cool?
Imagine a reboot of Fresh Prince of Bel Air.
Yeah, would it be like cool?
Well, it would not be allowed.
What do you mean it wouldn't be allowed?
My whole thing is like, I don't think that's cool or uncool.
It should just be a thing that happens.
It should be completely neutral.
There should be no, it's just like, whatever.
The thing about that is that the point of Fresh Prince of Bel Air
is that they're an upscale black family
living in a white neighborhood.
Okay, well, for the audience,
but if you switched it,
then it's like a poor white family
moves to a rich black neighborhood.
Is that, that's not a thing.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe nowadays it's a little different,
and maybe it could happen.
That was just being a stupid joke, sir.
Well, I'm fucking, well, I'm taking it way too seriously.
You're welcome.
I do find Carlton a fascinating character though,
because God, one of the best scenes
is when him and Will got pulled over one day
when they were just driving down the road.
And you know, Carlton's been sheltered his whole life,
so he doesn't know about the shit.
And like they were pulled over for driving like too slow
on the side of the highway and like got arrested
and some real shit went down.
And then afterward, like Carlton's just like, Will,
like we were, like, of course the police pulled us over.
Like we were acting suspicious.
And Will's like, dude, if we were white,
never would have fucking happened.
And Carlton, Carlton just does not understand.
Like it's not in his worldview
that the police are discriminating against
in a particular race.
And that is a very interesting phenomenon.
Cause to Will, this is just life.
This is every single day, you know,
he just thinks that that's just how he thinks about shit.
Cops are out to get him.
And Carlton does not process, like his dad's a judge.
So, you know, probably has a more favorable view
of the law system in general.
Cause he, cause Carlton's,
Carlton's got fucking privilege, man.
He's got privilege and he's been sheltered.
And his privilege allows him to,
his privilege allows him to ignore and deny
that privilege exists.
I'm just saying, I would sure like it
if everyone could was in a position with Carlton,
with like, yeah, this doesn't happen.
It would be great if we all could ignore
fucking societal bullshit.
I wish we were all like Carlton.
I wanna, everyone in the world should be like Carlton.
We'd have the best dance moves.
You're that big of a Michael Jackson.
That's true.
That one commercial.
Did Michael Jackson get more privilege
when he turned white?
Did that happen?
No, he actually got more privilege when he turned rich.
Got way less.
I mean, hey, that's how it happens.
Where were you when Michael Jackson died?
I was doing 9-11.
That's a good one.
Uh-huh.
I actually do remember where I was,
but I don't remember when I was.
If anything disproves the concept of white privilege,
it's that, I mean, Michael Jackson,
he was black and he was successful.
He turns white.
Next thing you know, he's fraying for pedophilia.
He's being assassinated by Sony.
You know, all this horrible stuff is happening.
His legacy is tarnished forever.
Oh, because he was white.
Michael Jackson, yeah.
He had the audacity to turn white.
You know what the real problem with that guy was?
He fucked with Paul McCartney.
He bought a lot of the Beatles music
that Paul wanted.
He was not still alive.
He said he was the Beatles hit squad.
Wait, he bought the Beatles music?
Like he just purchased the albums?
He bought the rights to a lot of the album records music.
And he was like, I don't know,
but I read about it the other day.
And I know that him and Paul McCartney
were not such good friends after that.
But they made a song together.
That was beforehand.
Say, say, say, what the fuck?
Do, do, do, oh, yeah, you're a black man.
I'm black.
Da-boo-dee, da-boo-dah.
I'm black if I was white.
I'd have privilege if I was white.
We should make a remix.
So listen up.
Here's a story about a little bitch who fucks with a bitch.
Hey, Nate, do we have any Twitter questions this week?
No, no, no, no, I know.
I have a closing statement.
I want to, I want to, I have a closing statement.
The closing statement of this is,
just know that whatever side you fall on,
there is no, in the words of my personal savior,
Jan Rynkowski, a.k.a. actor of Parkour, dude 91,
there are no anime villains controlling everything.
And everything is, every movement is not a result
of one person maniacally cackling.
They, there's just people reacting
to what they see in the world,
maybe immaturally or maybe materially.
But it is all, it is all people just like you
making decisions to act the way they do.
I just want to say, as a final statement
on the matter of SJWs, that I agree with everyone
and everyone is bad also.
Those are two things, not necessarily conflicting.
And I think in general, people should take themselves
out of it and not give a shit.
But I also think that maybe, and this is something
that I almost wish that I was more capable of doing,
is just go with it, man.
If all your friends are libtard cucks, be a libtard cock.
If all your friends are fucking alt-right,
be an alt-right, doesn't matter.
None of this really truly matters.
Just be what your friends are.
That's all that matters.
And if I could get a baby, fine.
But that's what got us all into this situation
to begin with.
If I could give a final, final statement.
Tonight, we talked a lot about why we shouldn't talk
about SJWs, we had a lot of derailing.
So look forward tomorrow to me and Tom
having a real podcast about SJWs.
What name is it for, Jack?
I want to say, as a final name, this coffin here.
Oh my, I'm with the king day.
Wait a minute, what made this not necessarily
a real conversation on the topic of SJWs?
I think we covered a lot of ground.
I did my level best, Mumki.
I did the best that I could with what I had at the time.
I think it was very early derailed into why
we shouldn't talk about SJWs and how now suddenly everybody
uses the SJW.
I was hoping to get a little bit of nitpicking
into what it actually is, but me and Tom can do it later.
It's been the whole time talking about what it is.
An SJW is like a work of pornography.
You can't define it, but you know it when you see it.
I agree, I agree.
Okay, let's go to the questions.
Okay, what do we got here?
Okay, here's one, just a fast-filler
until I find a good one.
I think Mumki's a little sad that this didn't turn out
to be the echo chamber he particularly wanted.
I just thought we'd have multiple perspectives
represented in, you know.
I think we certainly have multiple perspectives.
We're too intellectually honest,
and we understand each other too well
that we don't devolve into a bunch of shouting and bullshit.
Like, what would you, what would you want to talk about?
This podcast has already been derailed.
We'll do it another time.
The rage, the quietly simmering rage of Mumki.
I don't have time for a three-hour podcast.
I have a date tonight.
Well, congratulations, Destin.
Do you have a time for a two-hour podcast?
It's only been going for like an hour and a half.
Yeah, I'll save it for later, it's fine.
All right, there we go.
Let's go to the fucking questions.
All right, Jesus Christ.
Okay, here's one.
Edwin at Edwin Jart asks,
hey, TB Crasnayers, you become God for exactly 45 seconds.
What do you do?
Make racism legal.
Who else has a good idea? Come on.
Sex isn't legal.
Makes sense.
I remake Evan Almighty and make it good this time.
That's, yeah.
Why are you guys fucking around with laws?
You became God, not like the president.
That's not a law.
Black political.
I would buy up all the land in Missouri and then nuke it.
Oh, you know what I do?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Why in Missouri?
What did they do?
I don't know.
I was just thinking of a state.
I don't know what states are.
I'd go for Rhode Island.
Liquid?
I would probably like share.
I would probably like fucking share the secrets of like faster than light travel with humanity
or something.
I was just going to say, what I would do is I would have an alien race like the Vulcans.
I would instruct them to visit Earth because that's what started Starfleet in like the
original.
Right as humans did their first warp drive test.
The Vulcans happened to see them and then they became best friends and everything started
from there.
I think I'd give myself abs.
What hippo were you saying?
I was going to say, if you ask God, your plan was to tell people about the light speed travel.
What if, as God, you realize that it's completely impossible?
Do you tell them?
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
Tell them that their dreams are crushed.
Yeah.
I would prove it to them that it's impossible so that they would stop working on it.
I would do that.
It would be great.
Some include things like wormholes though because wormholes aren't really travel.
They're just kind of jumps between pockets.
Whatever steps were necessary to make it happen, I would share them if there were some and
if there weren't, I would let them all know.
Excellent.
Good.
You know, actually I retract all my statements.
I would ask God, I would go around the world and make geography, I would get rid of all
the weird geography related things like Portugal, that should be all Spain, it would look better
on a map, basically, I would get rid of all the small countries because they look bad
on maps.
That's true.
And we'd just simulate them in the bigger countries.
Fuck Luxembourg.
Yeah, exactly.
Like what the fuck?
Luxembourg sounds like some fucking, like a Power Rangers knockoff.
Like the Beetleborgs.
The big bad Luxembourg.
The bad Luxembourg.
To make racism real.
I thought it was pronounced Luxembourg.
It's fucking Luxembourg.
Get out of here.
The original character Luxembourg.
The cool new character Luxembourg.
Here he comes.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
I thought it was pronounced Luxembourg.
Yeah, but I think Luxembourg.
Lord, naked, you hit me with another.
Yes, okay, here you go.
Let me slang this one for you.
Fuck where'd it go?
Oh, here it is.
At Swagdude.
Yeah, at Swagdude.
Oh, it's Swagdude.
Yeah, I know him.
What's your favorite soda?
And I just want to quote Anthony Fantano and say, soda's piss water is bliss.
Don't drink it.
It's garbage.
Poisons your body.
I hate soda.
True that poisons your body, but it tastes very good sometimes.
If monster counts as soda, then monster.
But only the zero calorie.
It doesn't.
It's an energy.
Okay, then Coke zero.
It's clearly lead.
Hey, that's a great, you know, topic for this podcast because we were talking about SJ
Doubles at CWs.
You know, it would solve all the social ills of the world right now is a nice cool bottle
of Pepsi, you know.
Topical.
Give me that Pepsi.
I'm CEO of Pepsi.
I'm a baby.
I have millions of dollars.
I'm your Pepsi.
Yeah.
That's what the riot control police say when you bring them a Pepsi and, you know, they're
beating on the blacks and they're beating on the everyone.
I hate blacks.
But I kill people until I get my Pepsi.
Someone give me a Pepsi and cut this hatred out of me and wash my hatred away in an ocean
of Pepsi inside my body.
We made a terrible mistake.
What we should have done at the beginning of this podcast was so that we know how important
everyone's points are, is compare ourselves on the, what is it, the progressive stack?
On the Pepsi scale, which we are.
Yeah, that's what I wanted.
I wanted us to be ranked, but it'll never fucking happen.
That's a number bonus episode.
Yeah.
Five dollars, motherfuckers.
I'm going to say that I think the number one would have to go to Munchy because he's
the most non-white.
So that puts it up pretty high.
But he's also the least gay.
So that's pretty, that's pretty serious.
You know, Ben, I think I might be the least autistic.
Yeah, well, somebody's got to.
Just maybe, just maybe.
Okay, what do we got here?
Oh, wait, no, no, no.
I have to say my favorite sodas because I'm a soda enthusiast.
I like to try, I'm very cultured.
I like to try a bunch of different sodas.
I always compare tastes.
I'm very into suicides.
Like as in like mixing drinks, not as in killing yourself, which I am staunchly against.
What the fuck is this?
I don't know.
What?
The sodas?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm way into that.
That sounds cool.
That's when you mix all of them like at McDonald's.
Yeah.
Oh, all right.
And I say, I say that the best, the best soda in the world is as follows.
All right, 60% Dr. Pepper, 30% fucking root beer, and the rest Sprite.
Hmm.
It's pretty good.
Did you know that if you mix Coke and Sprite, you get ginger ale?
How would I have any way to test that, Jerry?
I'm fucking gay.
Kill me.
I'm gay.
I want to die.
Oh my god.
I know they said it on Seinfeld.
That's why I know it.
What of it?
Yeah.
I'm Seinfeld.
And there's George, too.
I lie, I'm a Jew.
And there's George.
Okay.
Wow.
He's not a Cuban, Homer Simpson, just Undertale.
Nice.
Did you guys, did you guys, wait, are you guys talking about Simpsons Meet Undertale?
Yep, I am.
Yep, yep.
Is that a real thing?
Is that real?
It's the worst.
Oh my god.
It's so bad.
It's fucking dumb.
I'm ashamed, I'm ashamed that we've mentioned it on the hallowed halls of the PCP.
It's wrong.
Just tell me what meat, is it a video?
Is that what it is?
It's just like a little like one minute shitty animation.
Okay.
It's fucking amazing.
Oh shit.
I'm subscribing.
So Monkey Away at Monkey Away asks, is watching shit in a theater ever worth it?
That's an interesting question.
I would have to say yes.
Totally.
Because I enjoyed my time in a theater just the other day.
Yeah.
If you're with friends.
I was alone.
I'm always alone.
I guess it could be.
It's not a joke.
I wouldn't do it alone, but I guess it could be fun.
I mean, you should definitely go at least once to get the experience of a huge screen
with a loud speaker in a big old dark room.
Dude, if you wait a couple of weeks, so there's no one else in the theater, it's the best
possible way to watch a movie.
That is totally true.
I agree.
I think the percentage of worth it your theater experiences is directly proportional to how
good or shitty your TV setup at home is.
I agree.
I like the emcee of the theater.
I like movie dogs.
I like watching people, like with people around.
I like watching, you know, I like having, it's a full ritual.
They've ruined, like, 80% of the movies.
Here's what I would say.
Yeah, I'm kind of a solitary watcher myself.
The optimal, like, movie going experience.
Like, unless it's like something that you want to page engine to and like analyze and
it's like, oh, it's a really heady fucking, like Scooby-Doo or something.
Like, you want to watch that alone and get the bullshit.
But if it's just some bullshit like Ghost in the Shell, you can go with your friends.
And if we live in a perfect world, then I think the perfect place would be like a movie theater,
but only you and your friends are allowed.
So you can like scream and like make fun of the movie for bullshit.
But you still get all the comfort and like the movie dogs and like the blackness.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, I don't ever do anything with my friends.
The theater experience can also sort of revitalize an old favorite.
You know, if you have one of those movie theaters that play old movies in your town, you know,
like you can go in there, you can watch like The Room, or you can watch like The Pals.
Yeah, that's the one.
Me and Nate went with some people to a screening of The Room one time.
And it was fucking great.
That was fucking downtown Boston.
It was the best atmosphere.
At the Coolidge.
I had the most fun.
At Coolidge Corner.
Yeah.
And we fucking, we threw spoons at the screen.
That was so much fun.
It was great.
I loved every second of it.
It's like one of those Rocky Heart Picture Show things.
Yeah, it was so much fun.
Everyone there was into it ruled.
Ruled.
Yeah.
Give me another one, Nate.
Okay, here's an appropriate question for now.
I'm your commentator.
I eat questions and comments.
At Cloudy Chain asks, are you planning on ending the PCP anytime soon?
Yes, I know.
I've been fucking begging.
People don't even know.
I've been like bringing this up every week begging.
Please guys, can we vote for it to end?
Please, let it end.
The Patriot has only just begun.
We have to keep going forever.
All artistic integrity has to be sacrificed.
It should be our last Patreon goal at the end of the PCP.
Just when I...
We should set that like a hundred grand.
Yeah.
Just when I thought I was out, they started the Patreon and now I'm still here for them.
The PCP is voluntary, Jesse.
That's the only reason we're here.
The fans of the Skriller are too important to me.
He's...
What a hero.
I'm a true martyr for this fucking podcast.
Okay, the rest of these questions are shit.
At JerJot...
Wait, JerJerRod asks,
Best Gavra, do you recommend the can of beans lunch diet?
Absolutely.
It's fucking awesome.
Just eat a can of beans.
That's the worst.
That is the worst.
This is coming from me.
This is coming from me who will eat anything.
I would never eat a can of...
I would never eat a can of uncooked kidney beans.
That is the grossest thing I can imagine.
It sounds awesome.
Nate, I have a can of black beans for lunch on the regular.
Pretty awesome.
Good.
You gotta have representation for those black beans.
Yeah.
Baked beans are good with tomato sauce.
Baked beans are good, but they got sugar and shit in them.
We're talking about un-topped, undressed, straight out of the can with nothing.
That's right.
Stop turning the camera around.
In the perfect world, we'd all eat for survival and nothing else.
This whole eating for pleasure...
I disagree.
We're gonna have to bring that into the food cast though.
Oh my God.
I'm very much a pro food.
I didn't even get to talk about how much I fucking hate fat people.
God damn it.
That's the biggest thing.
That's true.
I'm also pro hating fat people.
It's very complicated.
Yeah, so fucking fix your diets people.
Okay, well, that's it.
All the other questions are garbage.
Thanks for watching everybody.
I am an SJW.
I take all the blue pills, but I've also taken red pills.
I'm dying inside.
There's an internal conflict within me.
Thanks for watching everybody.
Everybody sing.
I need my blue pills.
Bye.
I need your pro pills.
Oh my God.
No, we can go for days.
You can leave your kids.
I can't...
I can't do the Loudspeakers anymore.
Hilary?
I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick I'm jerking
Myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't wanna do it