Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever. And we've got Tom Oliver. I'm here, the Pokemon master forever. That's
me. Indeed, we got Mage. I lied, I'm here again, still this year. Hello. Oh yeah, that's
right. How unfortunate. Gibbontake is right around the corner here. Oh, it's not Gibbontake,
it's me, Endless Jess. I'm back from popular demand. Oh, finally. Our shitty commenters
will be so happy. I'm so fucking cool. Speaking of shitty commenters, there's Ben Saint everywhere.
Communists, the communists. You know that song? It's a good song. I do, Neutral Milk. Good old
Neutral Milk. Did you see that Endless Jess met ICP? Yes, on Instagram. I saw that picture
of the uploaded. The man. I don't know the situation, like what leading up to it. I really
would like him to be online at all so we could talk about it, because it's really cool. Yeah,
I would love to hear the story behind that. I mean, he probably just went to a show where
they were and then, you know, they're not like A-list celebrities, so they probably mingle
a little bit. Apparently you had like a bunch of his raps on like a thing and he gave it
to them. Oh yeah, that's it. I hope they collab in an epic way. God, can you imagine the world
would implode? Because it's just too good. I still remember. I'm sure everyone remembers
this, but the legendary video, oh shit, what's the name? Violent J, the big fat one. Mike,
Mad Mike, I can't remember. Mike Matta, I think that's it. That guy did with his daughter Who's
a Furry, that video about what was like Snake Catchers or Snake Wranglers, because someone
had produced a shittily, a shittily produced fursuit that his daughter bought. I thought
Violent J was the big guy. I could be wrong. That might be Violent J. Is this a sweet bro
and hella Jeff situation where I thought sweet bro was the guy in red the whole time? Or
no, the grand mother? That was very confusing for a while. In any case, they made this video,
I'm sure we can find it, where he and his daughter made a video together. His daughter
is a Furry and had it in fursuit the entire time and was talking shit about a fursuit
manufacturer who sent them a fursuit of dubious quality.
Yeah, I remember seeing that. That was, it was adorable. It is adorable. Don't fuck with
my daughter or he didn't say fuck. Don't fuck my daughter. It's just sort of like standing
up for his girl. This is really cute. I vaguely remember that. That was a while ago,
wasn't it? I mean, that was years ago that was made, but it keeps popping up recently.
That's an evergreen content for sure. My mind is very much at end of the decade, like what
are the pinnacle moments? What are the hinges upon which the decade turned? And I think the
release of that video was absolutely one of them. There was a big change in the world
when that happened. The Furry's and the Juggle is united and there was no stopping them
once they combined their forces. Indeed. The lowest dregs of society, finally combining
their power, becoming a force we can no longer ignore.
Hey, watch it. Those aren't the lowest. We can go lower. We can go lower.
As the decade progressed, we learned that, but at the time, we thought we'd hit the
bottom of the barrel. Guys, please, you're worse than this. This
is above you. You can do worse, I believe it. So speaking of worse, are you guys feeling
much Christmas spirit yet? Are you feeling getting gifts and whatnot?
Oh, I haven't got anything for anyone. I'm so poor. Christmas just causes me stress.
I'm just like, am I a bad friend or am I a broke friend? I guess I'm going to find out too.
Why not both? Yeah, you know. I mean, once I know the rules.
You are an art friend, so you can do art for people instead.
Yeah. The tragic reality is, I mean, Ben and I had this agreement from a long time ago
that we wouldn't buy to the gifts just to cancel it out, which is fine, and I stand by.
But unfortunately, Michelle went ahead and bought things for Ben, so I mean, I don't
know if we count as one individual or not, but...
Fucking it all up. Yeah, she's really fucked it. Although I did buy something recent,
I think I might give it to Grace because I didn't realize it had already been gotten
for Ben, but I did find something very nice that I think would be very enjoyable for someone,
some lucky boy or girl out of the Crimson Street. I still want to buy a Christmas tree
for my apartment here. You still haven't bought one? Hurry Nate,
stand's running out. No, I don't believe it. Today might be the
day. We're going to go out shopping after we record those to do some...
Send pictures. Sure, sure, if we get that set up. Although,
the one thing I'm worried about is Sessho destroying it and ripping it to shreds.
Yeah, that's always good. We might need to buy a table or something
to put it on so we can't reach it. Just the other day, he somehow reached a loaf of bread
on a table that he is not tall enough to reach, so it must be he was dangling over the side
or something, and that loaf was no more when he got his hands on it, and I'll never forgive
him for that. Oh, I thought you meant Sessho was no more.
Oh, yes. As a result of his betrayal. Don't touch my bread.
Speaking of Christmas trees, I want to show you guys my friend's Christmas tree. She found
like some light bulbs, like ancient lights in her parents' house, I think, or something
like that, or aunt's house, and she plugged it in, and this is how her room looked.
Whoa, that's a powerful light. That is magecore.
Yeah, she said she's not going to use the lights because it blinded her, but I was like,
What a coward.
If only she could give it to me because I want those lights.
I like it. I like it.
You know, the glow is like 90% or like 99% of the Christmas spirit is just seeing things
illuminated by colored light rather than white light.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Like I have some blue lights in the dining room, and it just changes the atmosphere so
much. It's like cool blue lights twinkling, twinkling.
I want twinkling twangly lights. I want glittery lights. I want glitter. I want, I want, I
like Christmas. It's so pretty.
I also love it. Driving down the street now and just seeing the Christmas lights on houses
and trees out front, it does a lot to bolster my spirit.
It's fairly epic.
My neighbors are decorating their balconies with twinkly lights, and they have put their
Christmas trees on their balconies, and it's just so pretty.
And I'm like, Oh, look at that. Oh, a new one. Hey, better look, a new one.
You know, I think there's a thing. As a young man, I never understood this, but I think that,
like, OK, engaging in these kind of cultural activities does take more than zero effort.
But the benefit is that it just gives you a stat buff of intelligence and wisdom and
dexterity.
Does it?
Yes.
I think so.
Well, it's worth it.
It's a peer pressure buff.
Like, it's not like you can put up Christmas decorations any time of the year and get the
same feeling. You have to be one with many.
So I should expend a few bucks, get that tree, buy a couple of ornaments, set it up, and it'll
just make life nicer for me. I've got, it's 10 days till Christmas or so, so that's, and
now I'm sure we'll have it up for a while afterward. I was even thinking of there's
like a railing up to my apartment. I was thinking of buying a set of Christmas lights and just
winding it around the railing up there. Oh, I bet that'd be nice. Maybe I'll do that.
How much is a Christmas light set? Like less than $10? That's worth like less than $10 to
do something like that.
I don't know. I've always just used whatever lights we have from many, many years ago.
Oh, I remember the lights from my family Christmas tree. They haven't been used in a while, I
don't think, because mom always comes over to the UK. So I think for grandma, they set
up like a mini Christmas tree nowadays. I wonder, yeah, yeah, they give you all the,
you know, you know, it used to, in Lithuania at least, they used to have like, not like the
ornaments for the Christmas tree. They're now like round balls nowadays, but like, they
used to be like very different shapes. Like I remember there was like a squirrel and like
a pine cone and like, like a little Santa Claus, stuff like that. They're really, really
detailed and really pretty ones and really colorful ones. I'm really, I'm really sad.
They all standardized to just make round balls. I mean, it's easier now, but I kind of miss
those decorations.
Yeah, that's fair. My parents have got like a bunch of old fashioned, like, you know, like
pine cones and like gold snowflakes with glitter and ornaments, like a tiny wooden train on a
string, all that sort of stuff. Ye old chisel Santa Claus, back when he didn't have a computer.
We, I remember finally the setting up the Christmas tree in my house with my folks. And I'm
looking forward to going to going to spend a couple of days around Christmas at the fam's
place. It's going to be nice. I haven't seen those guys in a while. It's probably been, I
guess not a full year since I was last home, but, but it's good. It's always enjoyable. And for my
main Christmas present that I asked for my parents, I just asked guys, please just help me
pay for my ticket because I don't care about anything. I just want to not lose as much money
every month as I have been.
I need to justify seeing you all financially. So just pay for the trips. I don't have to be
burdened with coming to see you. Yeah. And plus me being there, sharing my sparkling
personality with them is the gift that they really want anyway. Exactly, mage. Well said.
Any, anything exciting happening around Christmas? Anybody doing anything exciting?
Absolutely not. Yeah. You know, I was, I was going to say like the whole Christmas spirit thing.
I've been feeling it less and less every year. There was a few years ago where I was like, oh,
no, I'm jaded and I'm not like giddy about the idea of stuff. But I think it's like,
I don't worry about that so much anymore. Like, yeah, it's just fine. It's just, it's just another
day, another month in the year, but it's just a little, you know, you do a little thing. It's
like, it's not a big deal, but I've gotten over the fact that it's no longer a big deal.
Yes. I feel more or less similarly. I, for me, I just like visiting my family since I don't see
them very often. And, and this year, this year, I'm super excited because I'm actually getting
like a really good gift for my, for my dad. And I'm really excited to see my dad happy
because my dad is very, very stoic and he did like rarely smiles or just, just like talks
so much or anything. So like, I want to share with us what it is. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So like,
so I got a new computer, but my old computer is still fine. And my dad's computer is ass. So I,
I, I, I delivered to my sister, my old computer. And before I delivered it, I, I, you know, I
completely wiped my computer and I installed a very, very, very legal steam not required
like a copy of doom because, because I think I told you before that me and my dad bonded over
doom when I was so, so I got him that. And yeah. And it's shipped over. And like his old computer
can't run any games. Like it's just so ass. Like, like the way he has, he has to turn on the computer
is to connect two wires together. That's how bad the computer is. This is like a fucking Apple
two or something. Jesus Christ. It's just, it's awful. So I'm really excited to get him like a
really good computer. Like, because my old computer, it was still good, but the thing is,
because I used it so much, it would sometimes crash for me. And it had some other problems
here and there, but I don't think my dad will face these issues. No, no, no, they will. I don't
think he will face those issues because he actually doesn't play that many games. All he
uses this computer to watch movies. And my computer is fine when I'm just watching stuff. And, you
know, see, yeah, I mean, just as Gib was saying, I think as you get older, we're all adults now
and we're running our own lives mostly. Now that we're older, it's, it's not about getting the
stuff anymore. Now it's just about the experience of spending time with folks, not worrying about
shit. And yeah, that's what I'm just happy. I'm finally able to give gifts this year.
That is nice. I'm prepared. Like my family was like, oh, you know what, we decided not to give
gifts. I'm like, yeah, okay, sure. And I'm sending gifts. It's like, surprise. I don't want anything
from them. I don't really need anything from them. I just, I just, I just want to give gifts and see
them happy again. You know, I don't know if you guys feel, I assume, I get the vibe that most of
you guys feel similarly, but like, I have a very set, I have a very select set of rules as to who
I'm required to give gifts to every season. And anyone outside that bubble, like all you guys,
you're getting nothing. I don't give a fuck. I don't care. My friends get nothing. My obligatory
family members, I'm forced to buy them things. And I'm almost, I almost appreciate being forced
to give them something because then it's like, you know, whatever, we all feel happy giving
gifts is nice, et cetera, et cetera. But I will, I'll, I'll never go like outside of the people I
have to give gifts to, which is weird. Cause like Michelle, for example, she just like gives gifts
to friends. And every time she bought, I'm like, this is so baffling to me that you would choose
to engage in commerce for no purpose other than to give that thing away to someone else.
Well, some people have these weird things called feelings and don't understand it at all,
make them do things that seem on the surface irrational, but aren't actually,
there's got to be a game being played here. She gets a dose of what's it dopamine?
It's a dopamine spike. Yeah. Yeah, it's also just, yeah, that's it.
Pretty much, pretty much. Well, it's degeneracy and I don't condone it.
If I had actual disposable income, I would get gifts for people.
Back in the day when I had a decent amount of money, I got my family and like some of my friends
like fucking stacked gifts. I'm just like, yeah, I got money. Let's do it. Let's get some actual
dope shit. And it felt like I was a God because I, I, I engendered, I engendered favors, you know,
subtly, subtly, because it's just like, I've done this great thing and you did not meet my level.
So now you feel obligated to return the favor at some point in the future.
That was not why I did it, but it is a convenient side effect.
Indeed, it is. And that is a good thing to do. But I mean, the best situation of all is when
you can get like a meaningful or really good gift that still isn't worth a lot of money.
Like I think this was actually for my dad's birthday years ago. I think it was my idea.
It might have been my mom's, but in any case, I think that me and like, I think Ben and Grace
and also my mom, maybe like split this with me. What we got was just like a ticket for my dad
to go to like a, like a racetrack and race like a Maserati or like a Ferrari or something.
And he would just like get to drive it around a track for a couple of laps or something.
It was like an event that like people were doing. And he was, he, he very much enjoyed that one.
So that, uh, like by breaking it down so that I think we all paid for a piece of this, it wasn't
that bad. Yeah. Me and my dad, uh, from her, uh, from his mother, uh, received one year tickets
to the play cats. And that was a cool experience. I really liked it. I really enjoyed it. I
haven't been to a play. Was that performed by me by any chance and my high school performance
of cats? Is that the one? No, no, it was, it was like in London or something. Yeah, I was in London.
It was really cool. It was great. I loved it. And I, and I, and I said, we should, we should go
again to a different place sometime. And we never went since. Dogs. Yes, dogs. The much maligned
sequel. Uh, yeah, but that, that, that also, because I saw the, the play now I'm sort of like
excited, sort of scared for that movie coming out, the cats movie. Have you? Well, I mean,
it looks terrible. It looks very weird. Yes. But I mean, maybe the songs are good.
The songs are good. They're always good, but they are the same songs from the musical that
we've all heard a thousand times. Memory. All alone in the moonlight. Yeah, I heard it. I've
heard that song. Enough movie. Enough. Never enough of that song. I don't want any more memories
of the song. Thank you very much. Back to Christmas though. I, yeah, I usually just give gifts to,
to my parents and like, maybe I draw something for my friends. If I have the time sadly this year,
I don't have much of a time, but it's not like they give me gifts back anyway. So, you know, it's
fine. I'm not obligated, but there's this one friend that I really desperately wish I could
give a gift. And the only gift I really want to give her is a switch, because I would buy her a
game, but her laptop absolutely sucks and she can't play many games on it. And we, the way we
met with this friend, it was, we kind of bonded over Pokemon and she, she can't get Pokemon,
you know, this gen Pokemon, even though she kind of wants to. And I doubt she'll get a switch
anytime soon or just like ever because of her income. You know, she's also like one of the,
like her only income is art. And she's a really good artist. She's so much, so much more talented
than I will ever be. But like, she doesn't earn enough to afford a switch or to justify a switch
until like it goes on sale, which will be never. So I just like, I really wish I could afford to
get her switch, even a switch like just something for her to play Pokemon on just just because
just I want her to be happy and play Pokemon. That's all I want.
Just a thought, is it possible to perhaps split the cost with other like-minded friends who might
want to invest? We don't really have, I guess we have one friend in common, but I don't think it's
possible. The other friend we have in common, she kind of has a family and a child and stuff,
so I don't really feel good about asking her to spend a lot of money on a thing.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Well, no Christmas for them, I guess. They don't get anything.
Fair off the hook.
I'm tempted to just like send her some money for her savings at least.
Well, that's not the worst thing in the world. You could even say like for the switch fund or
something. I don't know, things like that. I remember, I think a couple Christmases ago-
You should get her just the game and no switch.
Pressure her.
Pressure her, so enforce her to spend her own money.
Here's Pokemon. Wouldn't it be great if you could play it with me?
Yeah. Nudge, nudge, asshole.
Here's Pokemon to play and you see here like sewing like little dresses to put around the
cartridge of like Pokemon Sun and Moon, like little tea sets where she can set up her little cards.
Oh no, I sold my switch to buy you this Pokemon game.
No.
What do we do?
Well, all right, that's it. Christmas is canceling.
There's no winning, Christmas. There's just no way to succeed.
So what else is on people's minds? This has pretty much been dominating my thoughts as I'm
trying to crank out some videos and buy-
I'm trying not to think about it.
Gifts. Yeah.
I've been playing Slime Rancher. Thanks, Ben.
I also, wait, did we talk about this on the last episode?
No, no, I didn't. So on the stream, on the-
Oh, it was on Shackles for Hackles. Yeah, no, I've been playing Slime Rancher.
I've been getting my fucking drone set up. They're so good.
I got the advanced drones now.
Oh, that's great.
Like, I haven't gone for this yet.
Speaking of the stream though, for this Christmas, give the gift that really matters.
Pledge for your friend to be able to play the PCP Minecraft server for only $5 a month.
You could just give us a down payment of like $100 and we'll just keep that going for a while.
That would be-
How many months is that?
We're not going to do that, actually.
That is just months.
Pokemon or Pixelmon is really fun.
The stream is really fun.
How many, how often do we do them?
At least once a month.
Right now we're doing about once a month, but-
We should do twice a month. I think that'd be cool.
I think the community has asked and I will deliver like next year, by next year, I mean January.
They want to have like sort of like a champion of the server.
So have like a Pokemon battle and decide who's the champion.
And they get to keep the title for a week and then people can challenge them for the title.
And once they win, they get the title for the week and stuff.
That's a cool, excellent idea.
So I was thinking of having the tournament and during the time we're streaming,
so people can see the tournament if that's okay.
Oh, that's a great idea.
And I know that I hadn't seen the construction, but I know some of the people are building like
an Elite Force Stadium somewhere or like an Indigo Plateau for the purposes of this.
So that would be fucking sick.
Gotta go, gotta go build my team.
Also, also a similar title for like just PvP.
And I might have to build a PvP arena in the nether.
But yeah, so like those two titles are gonna happen on January.
How excited.
Get it here first, folks.
That's the perfect chance.
All these things you could be experiencing firsthand.
Give us your money.
For only the low, low price of $5 per month.
Patreon.com slash PCB Minecraft, everybody.
I mean, the stream was like fucking yesterday or the day before or whatever.
And it was a great time.
If you want to give us a Christmas present, give us the present of your patronage.
Very true.
Actually, I stuck around for like several hours afterwards streaming on my Twitch.
Just grinding out levels and leveling up my...
Or did you use the crewhouse?
Yeah, I did.
That guy was all blissies.
So good.
It was amazing.
Oh yeah, yeah, blissies, yeah.
Yeah.
Speaking of which, speaking of streams and Pokemon, the official Pokemon heart gold BGE Nuzlocke
has begun, everybody.
That's all I'm just saying.
Oh yeah, let's get to Pokemon.
Let's discuss it endlessly.
I'm just saying that Nuzlocke is going.
Tuesdays and Saturdays, 7 p.m. Eastern Standard Time.
It's great.
Name Pokemon.
Donate to me money.
I mean, what's the downside here?
The spirit of giving money all the time in every way possible.
Giving money to me.
Spirit of shilling, the spirit of shit.
You heard it.
Speaking of shilling, Davoo has a new game out.
I don't know whether you talked about it last week.
Oh yeah.
I was amazed.
I think I'm going to play that on Twitch tonight.
It's quite a short game, but it's very brain teaser-y.
Sounds cool.
Brain teaser.
You know, I had one issue.
I was wondering if you guys had this.
When I first loaded up the game, by the way, what's the name of it?
Chamber of Hex.
I can't remember.
That's right.
Chamber of Hex.
When I was playing H.E.X., that's correct.
I had an issue with a driver.
I was missing something.
I had to download whatever, DLL or something, whatever I fixed that.
But then when I was playing it, I just wasn't getting any music.
So I just stopped.
I was like, I got to fix this problem before I play this game,
because the music is one of the major features.
And I couldn't do it.
So I just decided I'd play it later.
Anybody else have that issue of playing it?
No.
I don't know.
I haven't played it so long.
Just me, I guess.
Okay.
Well, in any case, I did really like it and I wanted to play more.
So I'm going to fix that as soon as possible and then finish it.
Because I got to be happy to eat it.
Very cool art.
I have a question.
It's like, you changed your profile picture to that Digimon I linked it.
It's always a Digimon?
Yeah, I really like it.
It was a Digimon.
I thought it looked like a fucking like baby form Digimon, but I wasn't sure.
Yeah, you say, you give me Botomon.
Okay.
You give me Botomon?
You give me Botomon.
Right now, I have it as on both my screens of my desktop wallpaper stretched to fill.
So it's such a big happy face looking at me at all times.
Digimon is sick and ironically great.
I'm trying to see what it digivolves into.
I've been playing a mobile game of Digimon, an official one.
Oh yeah, that came out a while, not a super long time ago, a little while ago.
It's considered a species of Botomon.
Right.
Before we go off on nothing, just to mention, go check out Chamber of Hicks.
It's free.
It's a video game.
It's good.
It's short and it's got the same as Chiaros, Skrull, music that Davoo's worked with on his
previous game, really good musician man as well.
It's good.
Have a fun time with it.
Ah, good.
Okay, I see Mage posted a thing about the digivolve forms, by the way.
But I've got to say, it looks like it can digivolve into this beautiful creature known
as Poncho Mon, to one of its digivolusions.
Amazing.
As far as I'm considered concerned, that's a win.
That's a win.
God.
Reminds me of the base character, King Tacos, from One Piece.
What a legendary character that guy is.
Digimon is so good.
God damn.
I like the idea of Digimon.
I like how there's no rhyme or reason between the digivolvations.
And it can digivolve into them.
I'm not a fan of that, as it happens.
Seems pretty arbitrary and dumb.
Like they're not thinking about it.
No, no, no.
But it makes sense because you see their data and you can shape data in whatever which way
and you can involve into very different things.
That's true.
I mean, Pokemon are also data, essentially.
I mean, I know in lore, yeah, sure.
I don't even disagree that Digimon are crazy and random.
Basically, every Digimon's like Eevee.
They're just completely malleable.
Well, plus there's like a thing in, I forget.
It's like there's, with Digimon, there's like a vaccine, virus, and like data or whatever.
There's three main types.
And they can like change between them or something.
So there's like some kind of system for how they-
And they also have like elemental attacks as well.
So there's a bit of play between these things.
So sneak.
Has anyone played a good Digimon game in the last 10 years?
The DS ones are pretty good.
Yeah.
The new ones for like PS4, PS Vita.
Cyber Sleuth or Cyber Stalker.
Yeah, good things about them.
I've not played it.
They're also available on the Switch now.
The shows are quite well designed.
They're available on the Switch now.
So just letting you know you can-
Another game your friend can't play.
The Digimon like show series and stuff.
I remember watching like episode one to three because I had that on VHS and seeing some other
episodes on TV.
And then Pokemon was the obvious comparison.
Pokemon was so much easier to get into after the fact.
Because Digimon didn't have like a clear,
this is what the character wants and this is what he was going to try and do.
And then he goes and tries to do it.
It's just a bunch of kids who suddenly get magic powers and digital monsters and
they want to go back home.
Well, they want to go back home.
I mean, the whole premise of the original show is that they get transported into the digital world.
Isakai.
They get, it's yeah, it's basically an Isakai.
And the whole, like the thing that made Digimon difficult to watch,
like just kind of get into as a kid is because it was one of the few shows I was airing
in those time slots that had a single continuous story.
Yeah, that's it.
Like each episode directly continued from the last.
Whereas in Pokemon, it was like an episode of the week kind of thing.
Where it's like a simple one hour, half an hour conflict.
Even though it would not be difficult at all to get into Digimon, the anime,
I feel like this general sense of like apprehension to even thinking about it.
But I could easily just go watch Pokemon all over again.
Because that's simple.
I feel differently.
Watch Digimon, especially Tamers.
Tamer season three is fucking choice.
It has nothing to do with the previous two seasons,
it's its own self-contained story.
So you can just watch that.
It is great.
It is a 10 out of 10, unironically fantastic.
Go watch it.
It's sad that they completely dropped the ball with the enemies,
like starting with season four and downhill from there.
Season four was just barely tolerable, just barely.
And everything after that is just pants.
Wait, in Pokemon?
Digimon.
I heard people like Frontier, but I never watched it.
I've only watched the first three seasons.
The idea, it's a hit or miss.
If you like the idea of people becoming Digimon, then I guess.
That's why I didn't watch it.
Yeah.
I liked it when I was younger and when it was in German.
I recently, me and Bayer, tried to watch it like the dubbed one.
And we laughed about how stupid it was.
Like the dub was awful.
Everyone had like some sort of accent.
The dub of Digimon is, if you go on with the right mindset, it is such a joy.
Because the awful jokes that they add into the dub are incredible.
Incredible.
It is.
We compared some scenes.
There's this one scene where like Lee, the evil Digimon are sort of like coming,
like they're following the good people, like the main characters.
And they keep switching back and forth,
showing how like the antagonists are coming closer.
And like in the sub, it's kind of silent and ominous.
And you're just like, they're sort of getting closer.
But like in the dub, it's just like, there's this one guy with like a really stupid accent
going just a little further.
And then this other guy just like, shut up.
There's dialogue constantly.
It's like the guiding mantra of the dubs is like, we can't have silence ever.
And there's just like constant ad-libbing jokes and bad.
Was this a four kids production by Nathan?
It was not.
I don't remember.
But I think it was Saban by Saban.
I believe they did it possibly.
I could be wrong.
It was a good laugh, I'll say that much.
But like as much of a story or endearing character is like not at all.
One through three are good.
Three being the best.
One being the second best.
Two being good, but not great.
Go watch them.
Better than the rest.
They're good.
Better than the other ones.
Fourth one is just like just entertaining enough.
And the fifth one, I think it was like the one with like a lullamon.
Those cross wars, right?
No, that was the weird one with the different art style where the first episode is just a
regular guy punches a digimon in the face with his bare hands.
Like the fucking manliest man who ever lived.
There's a giant abumon who becomes his best bro.
That's all I remember about it.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
That's the one.
I hated that one for one reason is because like there's this kid.
He grew up in the Digimon world and he has a partner that's an owl and the owl's very
eloquent that they had a mom fridge humon and she's also eloquent in English.
But he himself, in the dub at least, he himself talks like a stupid child.
It's just like, he just goes, I mean, oh, like you.
Oh, God, oh, God, you grew up around people who are eloquent.
Well, Digimon who are eloquent.
Why are you talking like this?
Some just have retarded brains.
Yeah, you know, some people just have mental problems,
mate.
You don't have to fucking drag them like that.
Cognitive diversity should be embraced, not criticized.
Diversity is our strength.
Because his design is like, you know, like a wild child or whatever.
I guess in the dub, they thought it's like appropriate for him to talk like that.
But it makes no sense.
That's not like these dub copies work.
Because Nico Robin wore a cowboy hat in her first appearance,
they just gave her like a Southern Belle voice actor
for like her entire four kids dub lifetime.
And it was, I mean, it was so, it's kind of charming actually.
But like, that's not, just because she's wearing a cowboy hat.
Well, hang on.
She's not actually a cowboy.
How do you know that that isn't what Elder intended?
I guess I don't give, you know what?
Got him.
I'd like to think that it was, maybe she had like a weird like Osaka accent
or however the fuck those jabs do that shit over there.
Can you tell that in written dialogue?
Probably, probably, I don't know.
Anyway, yes.
It's, I mean, there'll be like a guy who's like wearing one of those Russian hats
who they just give like a Russian accent to,
even though it's just like a character.
I don't know.
Is Osaka like, like it's usually depicted in dubs as like a Texas accent
to like differentiate it from normal voice actor accents
from normal America or whatever.
Is it?
It's Osaka, Texas.
Well, like what does it actually sound like?
Is it like, that's gonna be a major gomenasai for me?
Well, like is that how they actually talk?
There's no easy translation in English or anything,
but they are, I think the gist is that they are thought to talk
in a more like lackadaisical way, which is somewhat analogous to like the Texas drawl.
Like they have different ways of saying things.
And it is to the south, like Kyoto and...
Oh, Hayao Kazai, my ass.
Osaka to the south.
So I guess it kind of works.
I mean, I mean, I love Osaka, the character from Ozamangadayo
with her silly like Southern accent.
It is extremely adorable.
So it totally works as like a correlate, but is it 100% accurate?
I mean, no, no, no, it is not.
It could be.
But that's one of those like a dub adaptation things that I actually appreciate.
They're putting some thought into how to adapt it.
I guess really it's a localization question as to how to capture the spirit
of like a character who whose trait is that they talk weird
compared to the other Japanese contemporaries
and giving them the Osaka dialect converted to Texas shit.
Makes sense.
Osaka from...
What a great show.
I like, yeah.
Ozamangadayo.
We did, I think, yeah, we did do a Chibi Baka's episode,
me and Munchy on Ozamangadayo.
Munchy hated it.
I liked it.
He hated it.
Did he, did you guys watch the dub?
I think I watched the dub.
I don't remember, actually.
I usually try to watch one or the other just to see,
like on the first episode, which is better.
We should do more of those fucking Chibi Baka's.
I have one recorded when Munchy came over, but I haven't edited it yet.
We watched Akira and we were like, what the fuck?
Oh, well, that's a great one.
People would love to hear your thoughts, I think.
Akira's pretty dope.
Akira's pretty dope, but I've, I don't know,
I've been recording lots of like little things here and there and being like,
but why would I put it out?
Why would I make anything?
Why would I make a video on this day and age?
I mean, you know, I think...
It gives just like, you know what?
I'm not sorry I haven't made a video in a while.
Proceeds to not make videos.
And literally, I'm not sorry.
The effort that go into editing it and putting it out, it's like,
you know what?
I'm just happy that I did it.
I don't really care.
You know, I get that.
That sounds like you have a healthy relationship to content creation.
You can't do that on this day and age.
Well, not if he's not getting it out any...
I mean, I think that releasing it is an important component of creating content.
Well, I mean, creating content.
I have like recorded the footage.
I would need to edit it and put it into a thing and see that it's okay.
So there's a hurt.
So there's something to do.
Okay, fair enough.
Right, you're absolutely right about that.
But I would encourage you that the good news is,
because you've self-avowedly not...
You're not a video man at this juncture in time or whatever.
There's very low expectation.
So anything you do release is just a bonus for everybody, including me.
So I'd very much like to see it.
I mean, yeah, it's a bonus.
I'm still waiting for Kingdom Hearts 2.
G-R-P-J, when?
When will it be released to the world?
I don't know, maybe never.
Probably never.
When Kingdom Hearts 4 comes out.
Alas.
Ooh, that'll be fun.
The thing though is like, I feel like putting...
Due to just the nature of what everyone else experiences on YouTube with other YouTubers,
is if anybody takes a break, whether they've completely retired
or they're just having a few days off,
there's this expectation of when they come back, it's got to be big.
It's got to be a big thing.
So that it's not like a limp sort of like, back onto the platform.
Like they've been waiting for years and then like if I...
Like the other day or the other week, or just whenever,
I upload something onto the Gibbentech channel
and it's just some like four second, four minute, silly thing.
I can't help but feel in the back of my mind that somebody's like,
yeah, like they see that they forgot about me because I hadn't been doing anything
and then they're reminded of me and it's not interesting.
And they're just sort of like, what a shame.
On that similar vein though, so one, you may have heard of him,
Digi Brony MLP uploaded a new video today
that is top 50 TV anime of the decade, one of two.
And upon watch, I watched the whole thing, I gotta say,
I loved that video because it was so quintessential,
like it's the best stuff Digi makes, things like this basically.
It's like none of this bullshit face cam,
get that content bullshit out of my face.
You're part of quarantine.
It's just I want the edited Anna cat's trash, don't watch it.
Each has their place, but this was like prime Digi,
just the reason that people subscribed to him years ago
and it just feels right, like exactly what...
Like I mean, just not to show you Digi, I love you,
but just looking at his channel, he's got like his last videos on the channel,
some art so far, it's a whirling dervish, a Pansu party podcasting over PSB, fine.
This retarded worst video I've ever seen,
the wife is the little sister, where he was obviously just high
and not thinking clearly, because I could explain to you in two seconds
why the wife is not the little sister Digi.
I just saw that thumbnail, I just let out a deep sigh
and then moved on with my life.
And then like this music review thing that I had some interest in,
but I'm not a big music guy for his strange ways here we come,
wherever the fuck that was.
And then this like classic Digi Bro video,
and like I just feel in myself like, ah, at last, relief,
the thing I've been looking for is here.
And that really makes me reflect on like my own content.
I was about to say Nate, I can't wait to feel that way
when my perception of this turned on myself.
I'm still waiting.
People didn't sign up when they signed up,
when they first subscribed or whatever,
for Mia Maffova or Weagawa or any other, even the Smash videos.
They didn't sign up for those.
They signed up for best enemy ever,
Ghost, the Gurrenlogging and Ghost in the Shell
and maybe Galco to some degree.
And God, it just, it really makes me think like,
I really should be giving people like as fast as possible
the stuff they really want, which is part of the plan of course,
but not fast enough for my taste.
Well, it's weird, right?
Because you feel like you have to do like weekly content
or just like keep the algorithm fed.
But then at the same time, it's like you, Nate, the person,
are doing weekly podcasts here.
You're doing weekly content on content.
It's like, why can't your channel just be some tentpole pieces
that you can promote from other sources?
Well, I mean, I gotta tell you, Tom,
that's really where my mind is heading these days,
but that seems like the reasonable way to go.
I don't know.
Yeah, the way it's always felt is like, for you and for Digi,
they have, you both have your big tightly written
analytical pieces that are really in-depth and great.
And Digi is just good at analysis generally,
so he can make a list, but he does the scripts well
and he doesn't quick.
And so something like this sort of list
is very exhaustive and very well-informed
and it's really useful and cool.
I bet he loved making it too, just watching it.
So like it's good.
Like I've seen some things I'd never seen anywhere else,
even on Digi's channel.
I was like, huh, that's interesting.
Yeah, and it's almost like for us as viewers,
we get kind of the most out of these videos out of anything.
And then there's like the second tier of goodness of content
where you've got the We Agua and Digi has vlogs
of various description where he rambles on about a topic
and you also ramble on with talking points in your heads,
but it's not as tight and it's not as edited or impactful.
It's pretty good.
Nobody really would complain that a video like that
is coming out all the time.
It's just sort of like in the back of your mind,
you're wishing for something else, something more intense.
There's some, you know, I know Digi.
Digi goes to a lot of, he'll explain a lot of this stuff.
He'll rationalize these things.
And I love the guy, I do it too about We Aguas and whatnot,
but there's just something.
There's something that's just part of this edited,
I don't know, like in our cases,
like these anime discussion things with like a script
and fancier editing and music in the background.
The fancy editing is less important
than the tightly written scripts.
And because usually when you're writing a script,
you come up to like, you get to the part where you're saying things,
writing things down that you would say just off the cuff
and then you realize, well, this bit's less interesting.
I can cut that and then I can go more in depth
into this more interesting thing.
And then it sort of naturally becomes
a more interesting video through that process.
So like, when I made the Konosuba,
like the YMS ripoff video I made on my channel recently,
I mean, yeah, I mean, even you, Gib, who's,
I mean, you're not much of an anime guy necessarily
compared to some of the other folks,
but you really enjoy that.
And when I was making that, I was really trying to embrace,
honestly, the Digi example of when I made a script
and then I was like, okay, I know this would be better
if it was shorter.
So I'm going to really dig deep and try to cut things.
It was the first video I've really tried to cut content from
in a way just to make it cleaner and better.
And even I was shocked, I still got complaints
that it was still too long and like wasting people's time,
even though I put so much work.
I guess I'm not perfect at this yet
about cutting unnecessary stuff,
but it's like eight minutes long.
I thought the whole thing was pretty great.
And just like, if that's all the videos on my channel,
I just feel like if I replaced Weagua's with things like that,
just everybody would be happier, including me.
I don't know, it took more time to make.
And it's, I mean, yeah, you're absolutely right.
I mean, I don't, we don't have to go on this
for too much longer, but like the new year's coming,
I'm feeling like it might be a time for a fresh start
on what I've been doing.
I've been trying what I've been doing for a while.
So I don't know, we'll see what happens.
If you're interested at all in Nate's channel,
known as Best Guy Ever on YouTube.com, maybe you've heard of it.
This has been a public service announcement.
The content channel that you and Digi do
is also feels like secondary content.
Like it's, it's good filler background noise,
but like it's not, you wouldn't go to that
and then discover Digi bro or Nate the best man you would.
Yes, I agree.
Although, you know, one of the conceits
behind the channel was that like,
Actually, maybe you would because it is more relevant anime.
So I don't know.
Yeah, see, that's the one strength I think it has
that like Digi and I, both of this thing where I don't know,
we were like, we talked to Victor, here's what I was going to say,
that like there was a conversation Digi told me about
with Victor and I think about this a lot
as inspiration for content.
And it's that like Victor told Digi that like he begs him to make
like fast videos about currently airing seasonal anime
because Victor just wants to hear about them
and because no one besides like Jeff and his contemporaries
are making those videos about those shows,
that's who he goes to watch.
And I think content is a few rungs in terms of like quality beneath,
like frankly, like, you know, a mother's basement scripted edited video.
You know, I don't hate Jeff or anything.
The type 10 content on YouTube came up with Digi bro first.
And then some strange thing called content media,
which is not content.
So I mean, to be fair, the channel is only like a month and a half old,
you know, it's still, it's still getting its legs.
It is a baby.
And actually even the content that's on there is basically like an alpha
or like a beta version of the content that we one day hope to have,
that'd be more like red letter media-esque on the channel.
So, you know, right now I think we're, I mean,
me and Digi already know we can talk about pretty much anything for a while.
We're both have the gift of gab and whatnot.
So hopefully we'll make some money, be able to finance some,
some upgraded equipment and whatnot, do this thing in person, possibly,
at some point, at some point.
The biggest episodes at the moment are
cautious hero and Pokemon Sword and Shield does it suck.
Like 11, 12 and 13 in K views each.
Which interestingly-
Martin's a good thumbnail choice for anything, you know.
Indeed.
Gotta get those fucking genders.
This must be a coincidence that those are like the most popular things
that we discussed.
That's probably just random.
Well, Pokemon, I feel like that's way more popular in general than anime.
So that would get more attention.
Well, that's true.
That breaks outside the little anime bubble.
I have no idea what cautious hero, how that caught on.
It's just a popular isekai.
Yeah, it's a currently airing-
It's a quality show.
Okay.
I thought Beastars was huge, but the-
I think it's kind of launched away in-
Well, you know, I guess I know nothing because I don't,
I don't like any of these circles.
I think the people who like it just really like it.
So I think they're just loud on social media.
I sort of get that feeling too.
And it is really good.
I know because I'm one of them.
Watch Beastars, you fucking peasants.
Yes, it's good.
Yes, yes.
But I mean, mostly me and Digi have been talking about the most popular shows.
Everything that we've watched, I think is worth people watching.
That we talked about on content so far, if they've got the time to burn.
Probably Beastars, Blade of the Immortal and Cautious Hero are the best ones.
I am curious, as someone who's been observing content, as from the very beginning,
what was the decision or the thought behind doing every four episodes
instead of doing a weekly show where you just covered all the stuff?
Would it just-
Time saving?
That's a very-
Like this weekend animatic reasoning.
I mean, it's kind of a middle ground between-
First of all, we wanted to do like two episodes a week.
Because we're not prepared to spend all our time on this as it exists right now,
for the paltry amount it's earning as it is.
We wanted a middle ground between reviewing every episode as it comes out,
which is the way that Digi and I traditionally had done our Aromanga Sensei
and our Rick and Morty stuff and those kinds of shows.
And not also having to wait until the end of a season to talk about anything at all.
So it was Digi's idea, but I think it works out pretty well
that it's just- it's a decent chunk of the show.
It's not that we- we can avoid the semi-pitfall of like,
when you discuss just one episode of a show at a time,
you could be like very critical and very nitpicky about like,
oh, this episode didn't make me feel happy in my pants as I wanted to,
because the girls weren't sexy enough.
This episode, well, Nate, that's because next episode, they're extremely sexy.
So that's what you have to wait for.
So, you know, it just- that's part of it I think at least for me as to why.
I was interested because like, you're doing the four-episode block thing,
but then you're also doing the potty cast, which is every chapter.
So you're-
Well, that's a separate venture, you know.
Digi's no one-piece expert, so that's- that exists to serve a particular demographic.
I mean, plus like, potty cast exists to serve exactly one thing,
which is the one-piece manga, whereas contents for whatever is due of discussion at that particular time.
If there was like a really hype one-piece arc, if Digi was read up to it,
we probably would talk about it like on content or something,
but I don't think he'll be catching up any time soon.
Probably not.
So there you go, that's- that's my thoughts.
And if Digi ever wanted to show up to one of these episodes, he could tell you about it too.
Yeah, Digi also roasted-
Has been not in the chat or online to- to talk with anyone ever.
He has been busy.
I just would like to know what Digi and Jesse are up to.
I know more about what Davoo's doing right now.
I mean, I could tell you, Digi's just busy with getting his videos for the end of the year and-
I suppose.
I mean, yeah, talk at content and stuff.
It's just sort of like, yeah, he is my friend, I wouldn't like to see him.
Yeah, understandable.
If you add him, he'll just probably show up eventually.
He's a hard man to read.
I'll slap him.
I'll attack him.
He has said before that like the only Discord groups he's in, like, is like the PCP and like maybe one of two others,
like, I guess the content, the one that he and I have, and that's it, because he only gives a shit.
Those of us in this group have to say to him on Discord.
So if you added me, probably.
Yeah.
Although I did add him yesterday demanding his W9 forum for tax purposes in the PCP,
which he has not gotten to me after six months, and we need it from him, you, Ben, and Jesse as well, who actually did respond.
I thought, okay, the last time we talked about it, you were like,
well, actually, maybe I have, maybe I messed it up. Don't worry about it. I'll tell you about it later.
Okay, that's absolutely true. You are correct, but I couldn't figure it out.
Later is now, and now I need it.
So now it has become later.
Ben, Ben, you sedated right now. What's going on?
Did you roll out of bed?
I am pretty hungover, so I'm not technically sedated, but I wish I was.
You might as well be.
Did you get Big Drunk on the RCK stream?
I got Big Drunk on the RCK stream.
I got, well, I got Fairly Drunk on the RCK stream, but it was nothing compared to what was to come later.
How many doors did you knock on this week?
Is this the new Ben segment, the weekly inebriation where each week?
What substance will Ben abuse this week?
Actually, we did. Me and one of my roommates did go across the street and knock on the door,
but it was at an appropriate time this time because there was a party going on,
and we were like, let's go over there and bring some alcohol and just be like,
hey, what's up? Let's hang out. But they didn't answer.
Oh, that's cool.
Wait, so the party was going on inside?
We could hear, there was stuff going on.
We went and knocked on the door to see if they wanted to, I don't know,
let us in on it or whatever.
Yeah, sure.
That's good.
But it was upstairs and the door was downstairs, so maybe they just genuinely didn't hear it.
And we just...
Should have thrown rocks at the window.
Should have thrown bricks through the window.
I've got, we had some.
I got two.
Indeed.
I locked myself, well, me and my other roommate, a different roommate,
locked ourselves on the porch the other day and because the handle to the door is broken,
the handle came off and I accidentally left the handle inside and then he closed the door
without realizing I had left it there.
So what I tried to do...
So you weren't like trapped outside, you were trapped in this space of the porch.
I was on this porch.
Yeah.
So what I tried, yeah, specifically on this porch, couldn't leave it.
So I tried to take two bricks and put them around the like door handle like bit,
like the bit sticking out of the handle is supposed to attach to and turn.
I tried using bricks to like squeeze the handle or squeeze the knob,
what's what remained of the knob and like turn it.
And guess what, it didn't work.
Any luck.
We just had to bang on the door for a really loud and make everyone upset.
And they rubbed them together, started a fire.
Smokescreen burned the house down and escaped.
But I managed to avoid putting them through the window to get back in.
So that's a win for me.
That's good.
I mean, that's what I've been up to.
That's my week.
That's a hell of a take.
A hell of a story.
A hell of a time.
All slime and punishment is almost done.
Just like it's been almost done for years now.
Oh yeah, that's true.
How exciting.
Maybe another two dozen images left to go or something like that.
And then I've been thinking about the epilogue.
I don't want to say too much about it,
but I've been considering various forms that the epilogue might take.
And it might get pretty ambitious with it.
We'll see.
That's not the climax.
The climax I know is going to be a video.
The epilogue will be something else.
You can get some ghost writers to fanfic write the epilogue just like Homestuck.
Yeah, get the Lord of Ghostwriters in there.
Lord of Ghostwriters.
Mix it up.
Hey, what's the status of the Kickstarter?
I want my damn comics and pins.
Well, a bunch of people are still working on their chapters,
and a couple people haven't even gotten their scripts from me yet.
Oh, here's a question.
I was just curious.
Will the digital copies of the updated stuff like that be available,
or will I have to wait for a physical copy?
I don't care either way.
I'm just curious if it'll be available online before the end.
At some point, yes, but not for a while.
Okay.
All right, Gib, explain yourself now.
Why are you delaying and fucking this up for everyone?
I mean, I have had the script for a few weeks.
I was busy doing other things and had a cold, and I just was lazy.
For the beginning of December,
I just was lazy playing video game.
But I finished the video game.
Singular video game.
Yeah, literally.
I beat the entire video game, and now I'm serious,
and I opened up Photoshop today, and I was sketching the page,
and I hated it, and I was not sure how to do it.
It was just one of those annoying things,
where I know the size of the page.
It's about the panels and the order they come in,
life to write, you know, normal Western comic ideals.
And I'm trying to fit, like, it's just a lot of thinking.
The panel layout is the most difficult part of any comic.
Drawing it is easy.
Once you know where the panels are, what shape they are,
and where the speech bubbles go, then everything's great,
and then you can just line it and draw it, and it's easy.
But...
Panel layout is a whole art in and of itself.
And when you read a fucking sick manga,
where the panel layout just blows your mind,
you're like, how did they come up with this?
Yeah.
The way I do it, which is not the right way to do it,
is I draw a rectangle, and I draw what's in the rectangle,
and then I realize, well, I think, okay,
so this takes up this much of the page,
there's this much to the right of it left,
so I can put one panel there, and then underneath it...
Do not thumbnail your pages first.
You don't thumbnail your pages first.
What does thumbnail mean?
It's like when you do a tiny little sketch version of it,
really loosely, just kind of lay it out
before you start doing...
I mean, that's kind of what I am doing.
Like, I'm not drawing the finished panels,
I'm just sort of drawing boxes and seeing...
Like, I want this action to be going from left to right.
He's holding a thing, he goes this way,
we need to zoom in on this, zoom in on that,
and then, oh, turn the page,
and then we see the next thing on the next page,
that's when you see the next thing.
I thought you meant you were just like,
you just did one panel at a time, like final art,
and I'm like, you brave motherfucker, that's some crazy shit.
That's the stupidest thing you could ever do.
Right, which is why I was like, damn.
I'm just stuck on this, I've got one page sort of good,
and I'm trying to figure out the second page,
and it's just not clicking, I don't really...
And when something's not clicking,
it's very easy to do your text returns, or, you know...
That's the real reason why I'm doing it, sure.
I can relate, I can relate.
I mean, what I like to do is,
I like to bust open my favorite comics,
and read them intentionally,
and pay attention to the panel layouts a bit.
And then I kind of put them under my paper,
and trace over them,
and I just get really good results with that.
Yeah, yeah, exactly, exactly.
I think one thing I always have difficulty with
is understanding how small I can draw something.
Like, when I see a panel, I think,
okay, the face has to go in this panel,
and I make it fill the panel,
but you don't have to do that,
and you also don't have to have the full face in the panel.
You could have it really zoomed in.
It's just a lot of...
That's true.
It's a lot of decisions that I'm not good at making yet.
Do you have that...
I don't know much about comics or anything,
but I have read a lot of One Piece.
One Piece is a big inspiration,
because those panels are very simple,
but the things in them are great, and very rarely...
I've collected the group shot that you made the thumbnail
of the body cast.
Yeah, I'm just curious.
I don't know if you've ever seen this,
but I'm going to link something for you,
because I use this all the time,
and I was making comics.
It's the Wally Woods 22 comic panels that always work.
It's pretty cool.
Oh, that sounds useful.
It's just like a reference of different kinds of comic panels
and way to lay things out
that just gets the nog and jog,
and you can start thinking about it.
It's pretty cool.
I'll have a look right now.
So, on this front, Ben, are there any other holdouts,
any other moral degenerates
who we should perhaps throw, you know,
who we should either kink shame
or throw bricks through windows of
to spur them along on their quest?
The only one who is done is Cheezy.
Munchy's working on his.
Hippo's working on his,
and then I haven't fucking done anything
for Jade Murrow or Nexus Mania.
Or am I forgetting someone?
In Kazzy, I haven't given her the script either.
I'll fucking...
I don't want to talk about it.
No, talk about it.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone, you boys.
Are you a Kickstarter hell right now?
You're a Kickstarter purgatory burning away your sins.
Dude, writing is easy.
That's where I am, yeah.
You just imagine that you are the character,
and then you say the most embarrassing things possible,
and then you write it down.
That's right.
Just for...
Yeah.
I always assumed the Vapors was just a biography, so...
Just remember, it's supposed to be bad.
I just got to do what I do with Slime and Punishment,
and think this is supposed to be bad,
and it would be off-brand if it were good.
Oh, that's very helpful there.
That's not healthy reverse psychology.
That's the secret.
That's the secret right there.
I assume you guys are similarly,
but I spend a lot of time,
or maybe I don't spend a lot of time directly thinking about it,
but I really feel imposed upon in a helpful way by the rules.
Like, my existence and the things I do change
based on whatever I perceive the rules of the game to be at that time.
It's like, right now, it's like, I need to make videos,
got to make a weekly Weagua video or something,
but if I formally change...
If I make an announcement
that I'm changing the rules of the game now,
then I feel perfect permission to do things,
or I don't know, do whatever.
But if I don't announce it,
I feel like the eyes of the public enforcing those rules upon me,
and it's...
I don't know, maybe this is more of a normal thing.
It's just people have expectations,
and then you live up to them or not.
I used to feel like that.
Now I feel the opposite.
I feel like the best way to do things
is just to subtly make changes,
and just do it by degree so nobody notices,
because I feel like if you make an announcement saying
you're changing,
you're just going to generate controversy in the backlight.
Because we know people don't like change.
They don't want to hear about it.
Exactly.
If you just do it, then it'll probably go over better.
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
You just got to do it subtly,
and before they know it, that's the new normal,
and they're just like, you've conditioned them subconsciously
without anyone realizing it's happening.
I definitely agree that that's a better way to do it,
although the one thing is that if...
Let's just say, for example,
you have a Patreon with very clear, explicit deliverables
that you are expected to deliver,
and if you were to want to change that in some capacity,
it seems like the only honest thing to do is to inspect.
I'm going to change my Patreon.
I'm going to start delivering nothing.
How do you...
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, I feel like...
I'm still sad that...
I feel like if you...
You can talk openly to your patrons,
because they're the ones who are the most hardcore.
So whatever you do, they're there for...
You're going to be in your court,
unless you royally fuck up.
Although literally...
I would say,
Include and deliver nothing.
Communicate with your patrons,
because I talk to my patrons.
Every week I do a Patreon podcast,
and whenever I have any thoughts
about my creative process or things I want to change,
I'll talk to them,
because they're the ones who are actually paying for it.
As far as I'm concerned,
they're the board of the directors.
And so I'll keep them in the know,
but the public can just get what they get.
They don't need to know.
Because I feel like the public are the ones
that are on the fence about you,
and they're the ones that will bitch the most about anything.
So I'm just like,
well, I might as well just keep controversy to the minimum,
just do what I want to do,
and deal with,
put out fires as they come,
as opposed to lighting the match myself.
That makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, that's a good point.
That's a good point.
And I was going to say,
I'm still disappointed that Ben's idea of the Ben St.
is creating a Patreon,
and that idea of just support me
as I create this Patreon page.
This Patreon is my magnum opus.
This will be my legacy.
Help me create.
Help me create the greatest Patreon of all time.
It was just too big brain of an idea.
It was too smart for the people to latch on to.
They couldn't comprehend the magic.
Before it's time, unfortunately,
Jake Paul will get around to it like in 2022,
and it'll do gang clusters,
and then we'll all be able to sue.
And it'll be big.
They'll call him a genius.
Oh, it's like Tesla.
It's like the world couldn't handle Tesla
making more than one world-changing idea at a time.
It was too big.
The Vapors, the champion,
these were already too advanced.
He was already celebrated,
but when he attempted to do this,
it was just a bridge too far.
The people couldn't handle it.
As he exposed capitalism
for the farce that it truly is.
It could have been great if only.
Man, it was such a golden idea.
I don't understand how it didn't take off.
It's bizarre.
It just needed better marketing.
That's all it needed.
Incomprehensible.
Yeah, yeah.
It word of mouth.
If I just got,
if I could just have gotten one Super Bowl ad
for my Patreon,
it would have been different.
Like when Patreon was relatively new,
like one dude created like a Patreon,
like he asked for like $5 to like make a lasagna,
to like buy, and he ended up making like tens of thousands of dollars
because people just thought it was funny.
Potatoes.
No.
And it wasn't Patreon, it was like Kickstarter.
It was Kickstarter, yeah.
Okay, a similar idea though,
but yes, fair point, fair point.
Well, Ben should have started a Patreon for potato salad.
Clearly, that was the missing ingredient.
It's not Keto though.
Maybe this would have gone over better.
But people didn't think of it as a recurring donation.
They thought of it as like,
what if you made a Kickstarter,
Ben State is creating a Kickstarter,
which is this Kickstarter.
You know, please help me support me in mine.
Oh, so for the Vapors Volume 3,
you're going to have a Patreon to fund the Kickstarter
for the Vapors.
Then we're going to have the Indiegogo
to fund the Patreon creation,
to fund the Kickstarter.
We're just going to go like multiple levels deep.
Going to go deep, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, boys and girls,
I'm ready to go to the voicemails if you are.
Boys and girls, boys and girls lined up.
I know.
We don't have to, we don't have to now.
Much like Nate's content,
maybe we should just trim the fat and...
Maybe, maybe.
I mean, it's going to,
like people are going to hear this
on the 22nd, I think.
No, no, no, no, no, 20th.
No, the 20th.
Yeah, 20th.
That's right, 20th.
But this will be the last episode
before Christmas, everybody.
Maybe they have shit to do.
So...
So yeah, we'll assume they're busy.
It's okay though,
because we've got,
we've got some choice of voicemails lined up today.
Yeah, they might actually take two hours.
Won't waste too much of your time.
You can go back to your families eventually,
I guess.
You want to do that, gross.
Precisely, precisely.
Ah, shit.
Where the fuck did I put the SoundCloud link?
Okay, there it is.
Found it, found it.
All right, all right.
Let me pull up the...
Okay, sounds like we're all fine with going to the voicemails.
Yeah, okay.
All right, so let me just preface it
by saying, of course, ladies and gentlemen,
go click the link down below
and leave us your voicemails,
which we will be delighted to hear
and to separate the wheat from the chaff.
And if they are good,
if they are quality,
if they are supremely glorious,
we will play them on the show
as we do as you're about to hear.
So, okay, we've got our first one here.
This is from Centerpoint.
And it's called...
Oh, actually, it's untitled from Centerpoint.
Let's just get us started off
in the right direction
with whatever he has to say.
Take it away, CP.
I don't want a lot for Christmas
There is just one thing I need
And I don't care about the Riddler
Or the weird ass dating sim
I don't need to wait for Radcon
Non-existent quick draw streams
My craft stuff won't make me happy
Or bonus apps on Christmas Day
I just want for you to know
Should've happened a long ago
Make my wish come true
All I want for Christmas is...
Then, huckstable, to join the PCB already.
Damn it.
Why don't we have a pie, Pels?
Why doesn't this guy have one?
Yeah, he deserves it more than us.
I mean, great work, Centerpoint.
Zend's a great guy.
What can I say?
Maybe we'll make your Christmas wish come true.
Who can say?
All right, never.
No, fuck that guy.
No, he's can't.
We're canceling each other.
That's all there is to it.
That's my plan for the holidays.
All right, let's move on.
We've got another one.
Oh, this is called Yes, I Am Sick.
That's Why My Voice Sucks.
Let's see if the prophecy is true.
Hey, fuckheads.
I'm asking for a dick tip.
So, as soon as you have spent the past couple of months
bashing in the Chad lifestyle,
getting confident and charismatic in the whole shebang,
and has realized how shitty every single person on this earth is,
how exactly do I go about finding the coveted GF?
But what I understand,
all you guys found your significant others by making content
but as someone who is both a high school sophomore
and has absolutely no creative energies whatsoever,
where exactly do I go to seek out my fellow autists?
All my communities are great and all,
but I'd hate to find the apple of my eye
just to find out that she lives in fucking Wyoming or something.
You're in fucking school, dude.
That's where you fucking do it, you nerd.
You go to school with a group of your peers.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the answer.
That's the answer.
That's the basket to draw from.
I mean, okay, he's saying like I don't have...
He wants like a gamer girlfriend, you know?
He wants like a fellow interested...
You said that?
He said something like that.
He said he wanted a fellow autist.
Right.
There you go.
So he's looking for...
Maybe he goes to school with a bunch of Stacey's,
a bunch of Veronica's.
We'll just go to Anime Club with Carl Ackersenville and his brother.
True.
I mean, okay, look, he says the thing in here
about like, you guys will guide it through making content.
Okay, okay.
It's the wrong lens to think that like,
oh, the PCB made a podcast and got girlfriends.
I mean, for some of us, that's true.
For me, that is true.
But like, it's not that simple.
It's what did I actually do in order to like get a girlfriend?
I did whatever the fuck I wanted to do.
I slowly acquired skills at it over years,
and I encountered various people while doing so.
So it's not about being a content creator.
It's about doing stuff that you want to do
and like being open to meeting people while doing so.
It's about having some skill that is impressive.
It doesn't have to be a podcast.
Even if that skill...
I would even argue that doing a podcast
is probably on the lower end of the bell curve
in terms of impressive skills.
It's one of the worst ways.
It's the opposite of what you should do.
Because exactly as you said, it's like,
oh, you'll meet a girl from like a million,
my girlfriend was from Hawaii.
We had to like date for a while and then decide to move.
So like that was, you know, like ideally,
the thing to do is meet people around you.
This whole idea of meeting people online from far away
is so retarded.
Leave the house and go talk to people in real life.
That first of all,
that's how you meet people directly around you.
So you don't have to do all that bullshit.
And it's how you like acquire socialization skills anyway.
So it's just obviously, okay, you're in school,
like nut up and talk to the girls in your class.
Because this other thing he says about like,
ah, I want to meet a gamer girl.
I want to meet a girl who's like me.
Like they're probably our girls in your school,
in your class who, oh my God,
could you imagine a girl liking anime,
but not talking about it excessively
or like wearing anime shirts to school every day.
So like you have to kind of get to know her first
in order to find that out.
No, it could possibly be true.
So, you know, just like talk to people
and meet them and get to know them.
Talk to people and improve yourself
in whatever way you can.
Just go up to all the girls in the school and say,
hey, do you like anime?
Unironically, yes, unironically.
Or pull the Spider-Man, put the hand on shoulder,
sexual assault and say, hey, that's the way.
It worked for, it worked for-
This is not related to anything,
but I just, for the first time,
I've seen what Vivzi Pop looks like.
Just, I don't know what she looks like.
She looks like exact, she is the,
the platonic ideal of a white girl who fucks dogs.
What?
She looks exactly like that.
I need proof.
If you don't remember who this is, everybody.
That's a big claim, Ben.
The big claim.
She may have been a hotel.
Yes, yes, yes.
Other things too.
Among other things.
Ben, I'm waiting for this image.
Law and animation.
I guess I'll screenshot it.
Yes, please do.
We will pause and wait for this update.
Here we go.
There she is.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know.
You can picture it, right?
I sure can.
Absolutely.
No, just think about it.
Just really rattle that one around in the old brain dome.
Speaking of Vivzi Pop, right before the podcast,
she was tweeting, had a big tweet thread about complaining
about how people give her shit.
Vivzi Pop, stop.
Stop publicly acknowledging it.
It just makes it worse.
You're just drawing attention to yourself.
It kind of makes you look like a fucking idiot.
Tweets like that are a lightning rod for controversy.
Just don't acknowledge it.
I know it feels good to have people by the thousands
flooding your replies saying how good you are.
But your long term, you're just making the problem worse.
Please just make more content
and focus on the people who resonate with it.
You're absolutely right, Tom.
Although it's the wrong thing.
I mean, she said in there,
I don't usually talk about personal stuff on her Twitter.
I don't know if I totally believe that.
Seems like she talks about some personal stuff on there
pretty frequently.
But, I mean, oh my God, I saw, okay,
you know what, I won't even get into it.
But I understand the desire to vent
on a social media platform
where people can respond to you in real time.
My God, what a technological wonderland we live in.
But it's-
You don't vent in public.
Vent to your friends.
Vent in your discord with your friends.
You are correct.
I saw-
Keep it out of the public eye.
I saw Patricia Taksin on Twitter just being like,
guys, I'm so depressed.
I hate myself.
And I just was like, ugh, bad luck.
You know, I just-
On a larger scale, this like depression meme-
Love, love, love her stuff, like her videos.
But I saw that Twitter and I was like, man,
I almost want to say like, please stop.
But I feel like it would be perceived as an attack
and I don't want to be that guy.
It would.
It certainly would.
You need to leave that to the meme boys.
I mean, the person making a tweet like that
is clearly already in a troubled headspace
and so they're probably not the most open
to constructive criticism at that point.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
But you know, the thing is not to be an asshole about it,
but like, isn't this just a cry for attention
at the end of the day?
Well, that's the whole thing, right?
Is that like that?
Because even if it's not,
even if you're legitimately just frustrated
and trying to just like vent,
people, the people who you are complaining about
will see that tweet as a plea for attention
and double down on their negative opinion of you.
So you're doing yourself no favors.
This is why you got to play things close to the chest, people.
Don't let them know what you're thinking.
Don't let them feel, I mean, see.
Don't let them see that you are sad.
Talk less, smile more, don't let them know
what you're against or what you're full of.
I was literally going to say Aaron Burr
is the good role model for these things.
Oh, don't let them see.
Oh, you know, just about Visipop in general, though.
You know, I haven't been following it too much,
but it sounds like with Hasman Hotel,
if I understand it correctly,
I think she's getting shit on mostly from people
who like find her jokes like distasteful
or not politically correct.
Is that true?
That is some of that, yeah.
Isn't that true?
There's a lot of people
trashing her for her past since, so to speak,
but like she's apologized for those, I think, and she made up.
Don't apologize, you don't owe me an apology.
Sometimes you do things that should be apologized for.
Well, if she doesn't stand by her statements anymore,
like those statements were made like seven years ago
and she says that she doesn't stand by them anymore,
so I don't know why people keep giving her shit.
She used to say, stay strong, sister.
I don't like potatoes and all the potato fags came out.
The problem.
All the Irish were real pissed at that one.
Visipop is at the point now where she is popular enough
that people are gonna take pride in punching up at her.
This controversy is never going to go away.
You are never going to be forgiven
by this contingent and this kind of person.
So just stop acknowledging it.
You're big enough now that you have a huge amount of people
who genuinely like your work.
Focus on that.
There is no reason to get bogged down in minor controversy.
You're absolutely right.
When you get to a certain point, you'll always have haters.
This will never stop being a thing
and you can't apologize it away or whatever.
I haven't followed her career very closely,
but it seems like what the release of Has been,
she kind of was like, again, to give her credit,
I know she worked really hard on it,
but it's like a poor guy who wins the lottery
and is suddenly rich and is now surrounded by people
who want a piece or want to tear him down.
I mean, this isn't her first big project.
I mean, it's the biggest project she's done,
but it's not the first thing she's done
that's garnered a lot of attention.
Like back in 2013, 2014, that Kesha animation she did,
did gangbusters, had millions of views.
So she's no stranger to a successful project.
I see.
Well, you know what?
On that front, it might be more of maybe
a semi-cultural divide sort of thing,
because not to get into the issue or anything.
Here's my thing.
Just not to cut you off,
but I think the problem is that we already know
that this is a personal project for her.
50 million views on that thing.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
But the thing is this has her OCs in it,
this is her personal project.
So I'm sure every detraction stings a lot more than like,
oh, you didn't like my Kesha animation, whatever.
Clearly, this is a much more like a personal stemming
from the heart kind of thing,
but that doesn't change the fact
that you're still doing yourself no favors
by complaining about it.
You're pragmatically speaking, you're absolutely right.
But it just reminds me of like, for example,
and again, not to open up the can of worms,
I just want to say that on the substance of the issue,
like when Vic Minyana was having his court case
and was being called a predator and all those things,
again, I don't care if it's true or not, not the issue.
But the point is that when the depositions were happening
and they asked Vic, the thing is,
Vic had made no public statements whatsoever
about all these accusations that he was like,
I mean, some people called him a pedophile, a rapist,
and even though those things are definitely exaggerated,
but it was the fact that he's definitely over 50.
He's of an older generation.
His approach was like, I'm just not going to talk about it.
Like, I will talk to my lawyer.
I'll let them sort this thing out.
Whereas nowadays, I think with our generation
and beyond and stuff, our instinct is like,
I'm just going to go to Twitter and get the people on my side.
Yeah, and I just don't think that's always the best move.
Yeah, but there's really no winning
because a lot of people say, oh,
then this person kept silent.
Why would you be silent?
Sounds suspicious.
Well, that's exactly my point.
Well, that's my entire point.
That's what Pro Jarrod did, and it worked out for him.
Eventually, with his...
Yeah, I mean, for a while, everyone was like,
oh, he's not saying anything.
He's guilty of non-crimes.
He had a statement, but then people ripped it apart
and he didn't follow it up.
He made a pretty shit statement.
Yeah, but he just...
That's true.
He talked to his lawyer.
He literally said, with style and brakes,
you don't give yourself any rope to hang yourself with.
He literally said in that statement,
I hope, first, to exit this marriage with style and grace,
which is a funky, a lanky con quote,
which I assume was unintentional.
I don't think he said style and grace.
I'm telling you, Ben, he said style and grace.
That's the word to use.
No, he did not say style and grace.
That's insanity.
It's impossible.
Someone verified.
Someone in the comments will tell us who's wrong, who's right.
And to think, we got onto the full tangent
by acknowledging style and flair, just like the nanny.
Not like lanky con at all.
Very distinct.
And to think that we got onto this whole tangent
by acknowledging the reality
that Vizipop does, in fact, fuck dogs.
Yeah, well, you know.
Fascinating.
It's a fascinating term.
Just look at her.
You know she can see it in her eyes.
You know, bro.
That's so nice.
You can see it in her eyes and in her...
Yes, it's not a value judgment.
It's neutral.
It's not bad or good that Vizipop obviously
is a white girl who fucks Donna.
All cultures are equally beautiful.
It's just a fact.
All right.
Well, anyway, let's move on to our next voicemail, shall we?
This one is from...
Let me see.
Oh, it's a Coomers Rise Up is our title.
Let's hear what they have to say for themselves.
Go.
There was this guy last week talking
about how he has so much willpower
because he did know not November.
Well, I was a proud Coomer.
I just want to say that I have coomed
every fucking day of my life
because I'm not a little bitch.
I have so much willpower
that I'm constantly cooming nonstop.
I have a hashtag not never, never
because I'm never not nutty.
You're a little bitch and a little bitch.
And as Endless Jess would say, a little bitch.
He would say that.
He would.
Well...
You do your people a service.
What do we make of this?
With your advocacy.
Makes sense to me.
I'm convinced.
You can support.
I guess.
Yeah.
Hard support.
It's, it's...
Coomer's...
Proud of, proud of your boy.
I'm so proud of my Coomer boy.
All right.
Well, obviously he's won us all over.
Voice Grail, we'll come back to that later.
All right.
Let's go to our next one, which is the Muppet Hater.
Right.
Okay.
The Muppet Hater is calling in.
What do you have to say?
Let's find out.
Brothers, I have one question to ask you.
When you guide your thumbs down the queues
of your selection of YouTube videos
that you can spend your time watching
in the most skillful and masterful and expert way possible.
Right.
That's it.
How do we keep falling for Arlo fucking videos?
How many times am I going to let this blue motherfucker tell me
that I want more Paper Mario?
When ain't no more Paper Mario coming down the fucking pipeline
and tell me how he's won.
But Pikmin 4, when ain't no goddamn Pikmin 4
in a billion years.
How long are we going to put up with this bullshit?
It's been since 2013.
How long are we going to let this blue puppet dictate our lives?
Rise up.
Get away with it.
Well, listen, the problem, the problem is you hit the three buttons,
the three dots, and then say, don't recommend this channel.
And then it goes away.
Arlo, it's the only way.
Arlo called me a great Keto pizza crust recipe.
So I can't hate it.
I can't hate him.
It's I can't do it.
Well, I have no choice but to stand.
You know, I think I might just figure out how to make a puppet puppet of my own.
But Red Man.
So Red Man will fight Arlo as being the red guy.
And he'll be like, oh, I like video games.
Duh.
Fuck you, idiot.
I hate video games.
I unironically endorse this opinion.
Can you please make a YouTube channel for Red Man?
Red Man has to review video games.
Red Man has a channel where he reviews video games.
He reviewed Pokemon Let's Go Pikachu.
Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god.
Can you get the link to that?
Because I forget about that.
I think I type in Red Man into Google.
Can Red Man review the classic Showa Tokusatsu series called Red Man?
Um.
That does sound like a winner.
Yeah, maybe.
Wait, there is a channel called Red Man who has a video called Pokemon Facts,
OSM Fact Galaxy, Red Fact One, Factor Red Man.
How many fucking facts?
I don't know what that is, but that sounds awesome as well.
Link that back.
Guys, look at this.
What the fuck is this?
This is incredible.
Okay, I love this.
Post the damn.
Okay, here it is.
Like Pokemon, like actually watch this.
Actually watch this fucking video.
Holy shit.
Oh god.
Oh, that's not English.
Not a fan.
Definitely not.
Oh my god.
I got a collab.
We got a collab, by the way.
You have to collab.
This is this is Red Red Man reviews Pokemon Let's Go.
Okay.
Excellent.
That legendary icon I haven't seen in so long.
I forgot about this.
These facts do not have anything to do with Pokemon, by the way.
Why is there a guy with a pin stuck in his collar,
like pointing directly at his jugular vein?
What is the fact?
Why are these red facts?
Is this like a blood fact or something?
What is this?
Oh god.
This makes me so happy.
Okay.
Okay, please collab the two Red Men.
I don't appreciate it very much.
Sorry, I've never made a video.
All right, go watch these incredible videos, everybody.
Red Man's so funny.
You won't regret it.
Is he just gradually getting wide?
It's the simple things.
All right, let's next voicemail.
Let's go.
We got a couple more.
All right, guys, I'm proud to announce that people at home watch.
I mean, definitely watch Red Reviews,
but also please watch Red Facts with Pokemon Facts with Red Man,
Red Fact 1, OSM Fact Galaxy.
Wait, wait, look at the description.
Red Man, some sort of Arabic or whatever.
Welcome to Red Man Channel, also Red Man here.
Red Scribe here.
You got to Red Scribe, everybody.
Everyone at Red Scribe, and he links to a channel that does not exist.
Damn.
This was posted like a month ago.
This is like new.
Oh my god, is it based on the lore?
Is it based?
Oh, it's based on the lore.
It's based for no doubt.
Oh, it has one like?
Well, guess what?
Now it's got two, baby.
Let's see how high we can get that.
Let's encourage him to make more.
All right, voicemail.
As I was saying, I'm happy to announce the end of an arc, guys.
It is the voicemail god final voicemail.
At long last, we can wrap this up and move on with our lives.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Go.
Hey, what's up, PCP?
It's your voicemail god here to explain myself.
So basically the whole premise of this thing,
it wasn't just to randomly, oh, guess who I am?
I was supposed to give you hints each week.
That was the plan, at least.
Maybe you guys forgot or whatever.
It's fine.
Doesn't matter.
Anyways, by the time you listen to this,
Nate will know who the voicemail god is.
So I figured I would get the cat out of the bag.
Voicemail god is me.
It's Sean, S-E-A-N.
Nate, obviously, I think you know me by now.
Of course, everyone's favorite.
Ben, I always show up to your screens
and ask how today's episode of PCP was.
And maybe you can hit the bell.
What a revelation.
I know this guy.
You know, pretty epic.
Yeah.
Anyways, I figured.
See, that's the thing.
He's a viewer.
What better way to send this shit out?
A real viewer?
I'm all my voicemails over the past 23 episodes.
Sounds good.
So, I hope you're ready.
Here we go.
On Ironic Gang, we guide the OG.
Zoomer Don.
Idea man, woman, or creator man, woman.
Rad Lectures.
Retard and Hermit Frogman.
Megalo Smash.
PCPSOS.
Calling on BG.
Greylers and Jailers.
Dictator Nate.
How the fuck you pronounce?
PCP Shoutout, Cup and Master.
Pick the number.
Pression on it, Shrager.
On Ironic Gang, we guide part one, part two.
Five in a row, baby.
PCPie.
PCPromise.
Proving voicemail god is real once and for all.
PC Purgatory Application.
119.
Part one slash two.
Fate Chip.
Calling on Ben St.
Voicemail Introduction.
On Ironic Gang, we guide you.
Eager of voicemail god redemption.
And hopefully this voicemail.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's a lot of voicemails.
He did it.
That's a lot of great memories made over these 23 weeks.
It's sad to see the finale, but everyone, I'm happy to announce.
By donating.
Oh, Ben, you didn't see it.
Yesterday, there was an intense bidding war in the Nuzlocke for the name of my rival,
the Ben St. Socialism Boys.
We're going hard to try to get the rival named Ben St.
But alas, capitalism went out.
By donating over 100 of his own dollars, the voicemail god has become the rival in the heart gold.
Fuck you, buddy.
He went ham, man.
He's so gay.
That's fucking gay as hell.
And I'm not going to take it anymore.
Oh, but you'll be happy to know, Ben, that because you were the next donation down,
Ben St. has become a lowly hoot-hoot who will almost surely be boxed instantly.
That's so bad and dumb, and it would have been way better for me to be the rival.
And I hate you, Sean.
Don't ever fucking come around here anymore.
Don't underestimate hoot-hoots, though.
They can, like, hypnosis.
They can toot-toot.
That's true.
Oh, they can, dude, every time.
Yeah, he can hypnosis.
Dude, have Ben St. the hoot-hoot use hypnosis to fucking cheese your way through every battle.
Perhaps I will.
Just keep doing it until he dies.
Just go hard.
That's okay.
We've got the endorsement, kill Ben St. the hoot-hoot understood.
We'll do.
Do not switch him out under any circumstances.
Let me see.
We've got another one here.
Ah, this one's in keeping with the season as well.
This is a very procrastinated Christmas.
Oh, I'm excited.
Okay, and go.
It's 2018 Christmas.
Okay, before I start, Ben, you're going to have to leave the room.
Trust me on this.
It's for your own good.
Should I actually?
Of course.
Uh, no.
Okay.
Pretend that you did.
Okay, guys, Christmas is right around the corner,
and we all got to talk about Ben's gift.
So what's going to happen is tomorrow we're going to do the Communist Revolution.
We're going to keep it way on the down low so Ben doesn't find out.
And then on Christmas morning, we'll be doing our usual Christmas tradition,
you know, watching End of A. Vangelion and our PJs and drinking our eggnog flavor fuel,
keto cinnamon rolls.
This time when the song is playing,
well, I'll turn to Ben and did you say,
hey, Ben, you know what else came tumbling down over the weekend?
And Ben'll be all confused and go like, what?
And then Nate, smiling big, will say,
capitalism, bro.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Ben's saying.
Shade of black.
Hey, Ben, you're good to come back in now.
God bless us.
Okay, well then later, guys.
Let's make this a good one.
Happy holidays.
Happy Christmas.
Happy Kwanzaa.
I won't tell anyone that I heard it all.
I'm just going to be sitting there on Christmas morning.
I'm just going to be like smugly looking at the chimney like, oh yeah, I totally don't know.
There's an extra present waiting for me.
It's the fucking end of fight club out the window right now.
I was going to say, yeah, we open the door and the financial institutions are collapsing one by one.
What a wonderful, heartwarming time that'll be.
I can't wait for Karl Marx to come down our chimney in his traditional red.
Oh, it's going to be beautiful.
Yeah, yeah, that's pretty much what it would be like.
That's pretty much it.
Sweet Communist, the Communist daughter.
Who knew that Santa Claus was Karl Marx the whole time?
I suspected it, but I never had the courage.
We all in our hearts, we knew all along.
He does take from no one and gives to everyone.
According to their needs.
According to their $1,000 dividend.
Yeah, yeah, according to Yum.
All right, I would like to start a potential new segment of the PCP.
This is a trial run.
Okay.
It's called the cool drawing that I post on Twitter this week.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh, I saw this.
I like this.
It was looking excellent.
Pump is particularly aesthetic and I dig it.
Yes.
Oh, I like the last one.
What's the Cowboy's name, the girl?
Clarissa.
She's going to explain it all via bullets.
That's going to be great.
What's the last one?
Oh, that's a dead guy.
My favorite.
It gives me like Samurai Jack vibes.
I like it.
Yeah, he's very much one of those kinds.
His leg looks a lot like that.
I was just sort of doodling and it was like,
hey, you know what?
I can doodle now.
It's like a skill I have and it's good.
Hmm.
I mentioned pump is very vulnerable to that rain.
So keep that hood on, sis.
Don't want to die yet again.
An alley-oop with that football.
She's going to alley-oop that.
Definitely for the touchdown.
Can't wait.
It looks like a big smile, but I know it's not.
It's like it's the thing with the helmet, right?
Oh, it's like a weird big smile with big thick lips.
Oh, don't make me think about that.
Don't make me consider that possibility.
All right, next voicemail.
I thought that was the end of the voicemails.
I was going to do the segment afterwards.
We have two more as it happens.
This one is, what is this?
Oh, okay.
So this guy, this is the true chronicles of an American hero.
And this is a good one.
He had left three, but I thought this was the best one,
episode one.
And you could leave one next time,
but three in a row would be too many for one episode.
So feel free to leave more, but only one this time.
Okay, two chronicles of an American hero, episode one, commence.
It's Friday night.
I'm chilling upstairs in my man cave
as the red-pilled mctaug icon I am.
Listening to my favorite group of sexy twinks
talking their alt-right podcast, the PCP.
Suddenly I hear a noise, like the screams of two Palestinian
children as Gal Gadot stands over their broken thoughts.
I zoom down the stairs and find a masked man
dressed somewhere in between a pimp and a civil war reenactor
led pipe in hand.
He's broken through my door and is coming for me,
but I have a trick up my sleeve.
I pull out my trusty slap bracelet.
I keep in my underwear at all times and slice open his neck,
the blood covering the entire neighborhood.
While I'm going through his wallet after I absorbed his experience
points of cocaine, I find his address.
I put those crack perk points in the stealth
and bomb over to his house where his mom is waiting.
She tries to seduce me when she sees my striking masculine form,
but I say the gamer word of power in the entire house
is wiped out of existence.
Reduce the rubble that smells like a mixture of sweat and broccoli,
because then I return home and finish my podcast
like a true American hero.
All right.
A true text of heroism.
And that's America in a nutshell.
That's a way to go, dude.
That's a proud of your boy.
The only thing that would have made that better
is if he donated to the patron.com slash PCP,
I mean, the procrastination.
Hey, once that American podcast is done,
why not sit back with some good old fashioned Minecraft?
Indeed, patron.com slash PCP Minecraft, everybody.
We can accommodate that need.
Naturally, naturally.
Well, leave more because that was great,
but make them good or I will not play them.
Okay, anyway, we've got one more.
Now, okay.
Now, this may sound redundant to everybody.
So this is from a guy named Tom.
This is from Tom.
That's pretty redundant.
I don't think we need another one.
It's pretty redundant.
Yeah, one's enough.
So this is a longer than normal voicemail that was sent to me.
He actually sent a link through the speak pipe.
The email address or his name was a link to the full file.
So you can do that too, by the way.
It actually worked out well, but it's several minutes long.
And I'll stop it short if you want,
but I'm happy to play the full thing if everybody likes it.
So if we wanted to stop it, just let me know and I'll cut it off.
But I think you'll enjoy it.
So here we go.
This is from Tom.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
Hey, procrastinators, this is Tom.
There's been something I've been meaning to get off my chest
for quite some time now.
So I think it's about time I say it.
And the only way I know how,
through Vocaloid Parody Song, enjoy.
Yes.
Oh, I want to sit down and relax.
I'll put on the PZP.
I don't want to hear that bullshit.
That face be on MTV.
There is just one problem though.
There's one member with no soul.
I think we all know who the one I hate is.
No, I thought I was going to say that.
No, no more.
Best guy's brother is Van Saint.
Horror images of a man.
These are just some serfless flaws.
I can't just move past them all.
He's worse than Jeff Lou.
He's the same thing as J.W. Lou.
All right, there's more.
Let me tell you all the ways that Van Saint is a little bitch.
Every PZP episode is his personal sales pitch.
I know, but he first all makes sick J's.
He is worse than the third drive.
You only hear his stupid bitching through his shitty USB.
Oh, my God.
This is the whole song.
It's the whole song.
And we'll bring the apocalypse.
It was a clear hello cost.
Humanity ever lost.
Ben's not who he seems to be.
He's eight and secretly.
Before he evolves, someone kill him quickly.
Antichrist is not slain while he looks like a man child.
He will be too late for us all.
Our innocent defile his patriotism.
To wake his evil with him.
The end doesn't involve you.
Kill Ben Saint before me.
Yes, yes.
He kills you.
Kill Ben Saint before he kills you.
Best guy, kill Ben Saint before he kills you.
Jesse, kill Ben Saint before he kills you.
Kill Ben Saint before he kills you.
More, more, more, more.
I can't get enough.
All right.
We're fading.
Wow, I'm feeling the holiday spirit now.
Tom, why was that so epic?
It sounded more flatter than I was.
How did they do that?
He made it with a Vocaloid or something.
That sounded so good.
Vocaloid, not like a Utau or Utau.
He said a Vocaloid.
By the way, this guy's name is Tom.
He asked us to kindly link his YouTube channel with 117 subs.
I watch, he makes memes.
He is a funny guy.
Go check this guy out, link in the description or something.
Incredible.
He put so much work into that.
Is that song a video? Can I like tweet that or something?
It actually, I looked, it's not a video on his channel,
but you should make a video out of it, Tom,
as soon as you hear this.
So we can put it in the description.
Why does Ben have two songs of high quality about him now?
It's so bad.
What is it about Ben that inspires such creativity?
It's the rage.
It's the fierce hatred.
It's, you know, I'm a divisive figure, right?
Everyone's got to have a take on Ben saying.
You'd rather, what is it?
It's better to be hated than not to be remembered at all, you know?
Something like that.
That's what I'm going for.
And also, I said, that's two parodies of Mariah Carey's
All I Want for Christmas, this very fucking episode,
but it is the quintessential Christmas song,
and Christmas is in a few short days,
so I guess we'll leave it at that.
Next PCP that people will be hearing.
Not the one we will be hearing, but people will be hearing,
will be the last PCP of the year.
Yes, yes.
I will not be present, sadly, for real this time.
Oh, okay.
Tickets are bought.
I will not be present.
But yeah, so people who are going to send in voicemails,
just know your voicemail will be on the last PCP of the year,
so make it good.
Make it amazing.
Make it all Mariah Carey parodies.
And you know what?
This is actually very useful.
Okay, so it's hard for people,
like a couple people actually center point,
send me his on-disc or whatever, don't do that.
Put a link to it on SpeakPipe,
like from a SoundCloud,
or you can put the URL exactly the way Tom did.
He's pioneering new smart things.
His actual voicemail was like a,
hey, just Nate, so you know this is a link,
so you can click on this link and get the audio.
Like that works perfectly. Do that.
That was convenient and easy to do.
It was great. It was great.
So keep the quality coming everybody.
Incredible work Tom, incredible work every center point.
We appreciate your song as well.
Everybody else, good stuff.
Quality voicemails today.
I was enjoying most of them.
And so SpeakPipe, link down below
to leave your voicemails.
And of course, yeah, yeah.
All those Mariah Carey, all that one for Christmases,
reminds me of this one video,
which I would have linked in the show notes
for people to listen to,
a TF2 parody of all I want for Christmas.
And it's really funny.
I listen to it every year.
I hear it.
I'm going to play this for the fam on Christmas Day
as we all jam out.
Oh, this is great. I love it.
So there you go, everybody. Get in the Christmas spirit.
I am.
I'm going for sure.
Or your holiday denomination of choice,
whatever it may be.
Right, why not begin the true giving spirit
and go to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators,
support the show, and we will give you a gift
of bonus episodes.
There's 32, 33 will be out pretty soon.
We already know what's going to be recording it soon.
And it's going to be a great time.
You can follow us at tbcrastinators on Twitter
for updates and whatnot.
And anything else?
No, just give us more money.
That's really the long and short of it.
Play Minecraft with us, patreon.com.spz
Minecraft for the streams, et cetera, et cetera.
Alright, thanks for being here, everybody.
See you after Christmas.
Have a great week, have a great time,
and have fun.
And don't kill me before I kill you, everyone.
You better do it, like the song says.
See you then.
Bye!