I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch, son of a bitch, son of a bitch, son of a bitch, son of a bitch.
Okay welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast I guess we're going, I guess we're live, I
guess we're not live, this is pre-recorded.
The pre-recorded Colin show, there was a bit, you know, there was a bit on the, you know,
There was a bit on Mr. Show called The Pre-Recorded Colin Show, which was about, it was David
Cross was the host of a show and like, just the whole show was just confusion over like
people calling in and leaving effectively voicemails thinking that the show was live.
And so it's just a big like, people thinking they're talking live but he's responding
to them and it's just a series of responding to voicemails that like have not understood
the nature of the show and that's pretty much our voicemail segment.
So you know, I feel like that was ahead of its time.
That sounds pretty good.
I like Mr. Show.
Well it had its moments.
It's actually kind of, a lot of it sucks in hindsight.
But that's comedy.
That's comedy.
I'm here Ben St. Gibbentake and Cheesy Manfredo is back.
Hey, I'm back.
With a vengeance.
Oh, I'm like, I'm feeling an acute sense of like tiredness that like makes me want to
sneeze.
Like I woke, like I just got out of bed and like I want to be back in bed and that makes
my face feel like pinched up like I'm gonna, like I'm gonna sneeze, like my eyes are stinging.
You just got out of bed?
Yeah.
That's so interesting because I just got out of bed too right now.
Oh my God, we were in bed together.
We were in bed together.
We were homosexual.
Were you here to hear first folks?
We was homosexual.
Okay.
Yeah.
So how was it with me?
What the gay sex we do?
Yes.
Yeah.
It was pretty all right.
The problem was that your dick was just too massive for me.
Uh-oh.
It didn't fit in my mouth.
It was gonna say the same thing about you.
So neither of you could do anything.
We were, yeah, we couldn't.
Yeah, we couldn't.
Our dicks were so big we couldn't have gay sex.
So it's like, damn, I guess we got to go back to fucking women in the bud.
Like God intended.
Isn't there a show, I think Michelle tweeted something.
Were they fucking women in the bud?
No.
Ew.
There's a show that's called My Husband's Too Big or My Husband Won't Fit.
Is that real?
I think, yeah.
Is that TLC?
I think it's Chinese.
There's like a Netflix show that's called My Husband Won't Fit.
Maybe it's Korean.
There's a, like, My Husband Won't Fit.
This sounds right up my alley.
And I haven't watched it, but I highly recommend it to anyone.
Won't, not a waste of your time.
I promise.
Kimiko and Kenichi meeting college, build a happy marriage together, but over time an
unusual problem fended to the server relationship.
Oh, it's a drama.
Give.
Save us.
Yes.
My big announcement that even if you already know that my secret project was revealed to
be Pumpkin Alley, the fucking video game I'm making, wow.
I knew about it.
I knew about it because I am a patron at patreon.com slash give and take also probably because
we're on the show together, but both, both reasons.
When did you first start talking about the secret project?
Give.
Do you remember?
Because it feels like forever.
It has been a while.
You've been working on it for a year, but I don't remember when you started, like, talking
about it.
I don't remember when I started talking about it.
Maybe it was initially, well, the project started in January 2021, and I was like, it's
time to start, like, making a video game.
And I was like, that's what I'm going to do this year.
And like the initial idea was to make some sort of demo by the end of the year.
Or well, I think that became the goal because I didn't know how long anything would take.
And it seemed like it was possible.
It wasn't quite possible, but then early this year, it was finally ready to be revealed.
So it's been, yeah, literally a year and a month or two since I started working on it.
There was a bunch of months in the middle of last year where I was sick and unable to
work.
We're both game devs now.
That's true.
We're all game dev people.
I guess this isn't Digi's anime podcast anymore.
This is Digi's podcast.
This is now video.
I was trying to call you Gibb and take, but I pronounced it video game.
That's my new name.
I'm changing my name.
To give and take is now a dead name.
I'm called video game now.
That's my new name.
No, it's still spelled Gibb and take, but the G is pronounced as a V and the B is pronounced
as a D and etc.
And the T is pronounced as a G and so on in that order.
We're Gibb and takes video game podcast now.
Yes.
You heard of Neo pronouns.
Here are Neo dead names.
My pronouns are video slash gay.
Yes.
So, yeah, if you have not heard and this is your first time, go to link in the description
pumpkinali on itch.io.
Free demo.
Right.
Link in the description.
It's a free demo to play.
I would like everyone to play it in the world.
I don't think I'm going to do that later today.
I have a question at the top of my mind, seeing the trailer for a pumpkin alley.
Do I have to have red bell jade to get this game?
No, this, this is the, the origin story of the friendship between punk and alley.
They are two characters, they meet each other.
That's the story of the game that I have roughly lined out.
Right.
So, so it's a, it's a prequel.
It's a prequel.
I saw you.
I posted a drawing of a Tiki on Twitter.
Is Tiki going to be in the game?
No, probably not.
No, because they need Tiki and bell jade.
So, no, I wouldn't make any sense.
I just felt like drawing her because it's been a while.
Yeah.
The, the, the adventure of punk going out into the world, finding alley-oop and becoming
friends on an adventure.
I have it.
Details to be determined and also I don't want to spoil anything.
Well, okay.
Yeah.
I mean, don't...
About the story at least.
I could talk about some things.
Don't answer if it's spoilers, but what's up with fairy bits?
Why fairy, why are they fairy bits?
Because that's, that's what you collect in the, in the game, by the way.
Yeah, it's kind of gay.
It's kind of...
Yeah.
What?
Why, why gay though?
Well, it's an allegory.
You see, they're gay.
Fascinating.
No, it's initially the, the, when I was writing up like the, the story and the, I was thinking
of the locations, the enemies, what you do physically and then also the story that carries
you through.
Initially, I wasn't sure about what collectibles there would be and we decided fairy bits.
So there is lore, but I'm not sure how it fits into the lore I already had planned for
like the enemies.
Very...
There's lore for that.
Okay.
Now tell me, tell me if I'm completely off base.
I was, I strongly, I got the feeling that pumps, pumps health bar looks like fairy
bits and I, and I was so much that like when I took damage, I thought collecting fairy
bits was going to restore her health.
It didn't.
I don't know.
Are those, are those connected?
Is there a reason?
Is that bad game?
Is that bad game design?
It is, it's definitely bad game design.
Definitely.
Bad games.
Well, the thing with the demo, right?
Yeah.
Everything could change when the final game is released.
So if, like, there was no particular reason they're the same color, it was just sort of
like, that's a cool color.
I'm a lore guy.
Like that for her health.
I'm always looking for lore connections.
When it comes to like the actual thing, lore connections will be considered with every
design element.
Yeah.
We just sort of like, initially the, we were like, I wasn't sure how fast things could
be done, but my brother, Charlie, he's a programmer.
He went to Game Dev University School.
He went to Gaming High School.
He went to Gaming High School, became a big gamer.
Lucky.
And he's just sort of always interested in programming things, so he's very good at
that.
And so like the first month of working on it, we got quite a lot like of the assets and
stuff working.
Things that took a long time were like the camera and movement and a bit of the animation.
The fairy bits were like one of the first things he made.
Just like, I'll make this little code.
So when you go near them, they jump up and then swoop around to you.
And it's like, it's really nice looking.
Yeah.
So there wasn't much design into like, like from my end, like what they're supposed to
look like yet.
So you know, who knows.
That's pretty epic.
You just made them look.
You did, well, he did some art and you did, but you did like most of the art.
I think the credits list him as doing like textures.
Shelley makes most of the models and things like the trees and like the floor, like cubes
that you can like copy paste and make different shapes with.
Yeah.
He drew the textures for that while he was muddling them because it was easier than me
like getting a UV map sent to me and then painting something on.
Yeah.
So so those and they're pretty good.
And I did like the textures for the bush and the flame particle things and the health bar.
And I mean, you can tell, I think, well, things that I've drawn.
Yeah.
And then I animated punk with my 3D animation knowledge.
So this is a demo, right?
And this is like how long is this demo?
It took me it took me maybe an hour to like it took me less than an hour to like
basically explore the whole thing.
But then it took me like another hour to find all 250 fairy bits.
How long do you imagine the full game to begin?
I'm hoping it'll be like.
Because you can't like aim so high that you need like a 10 years or like to hire a whole studio.
I don't really prepare to do all that stuff.
So it's going to be like a sort of small ish game, maybe five hours.
That's not small for an indie game.
Like for the sort of game you want, that's like pretty good, I think.
OK, when is the animated series going to come out?
That's what I'm wondering where the real money is at.
Moichan dicing.
Well, Chen dies.
Well, I mean, when can I go into a when can I go into a hot topic
and buy my own punk marriage?
That's what I'm wondering.
Well, actually, I was I forgot I had notes.
I had some I had I had a couple of notes to complain for the for the devs.
I said, like, hey, I got so I got a bone to pick with whoever designed this piece of shit.
Oh, yeah, I. All right.
So I gave I was first complaint.
There's no gay sex.
Where is all the gay sex?
Give OK, it's family friendly.
Obviously, I can't do that.
I can't do that. Such a such a product.
OK, well, I guess I won't be playing it.
I guess I won't be playing it then.
I'm not it. You can figure it out.
It's violence. It's violence against me.
All right. Yeah.
I I missed I'm I guess at some point in this,
I will probably have to say like what the places were that I found stuff.
So if you don't want to like if you want to find everything in the game,
I guess don't don't listen to play.
Play the game right now.
It is a unsubscribe from the PCP.
Go play the game.
The game is very easy and fun and good.
And there's a few little glitches.
But yeah, the main glitch that I found was well, actually,
it was it was when I was fucking around.
I spent a lot of time after I got to basically the end.
And OK, OK, here was here was my play experience.
I progressed more or less.
OK, I kind of was just like went past the big area
with the big like hollow tree with the mushroom stairs.
That's sort of like one of the main areas.
But I kind of just like accidentally like missed it and kind of went by it.
And I sort of progressed directly to what I guess would be the last area,
the area with like the angry mushroom that throws mushrooms at you.
And I got there and then I collected all the fairy bits.
And I was like, OK, there's definitely I definitely missed an area.
But while I'm here, I saw up on the cliff, there's a doorway.
You know what I'm talking about?
Like up high, there's like an alley grotto doorway.
Yes, little caves that you can go into.
And I was like, oh, hmm, how do we get up there?
And maybe and maybe this is on me.
But I spent I spent a not inconsiderable amount of time
trying to find ways to jump up the sides of the mountain
to jump around on the up like
mountaintops sort of ringing around the area in order to jump up
and get up to that like high up door zone.
And I did it. I did it.
The main glitch that I found in the game was when I was jumping around
in areas when I wasn't supposed to be, I would slide down
certain parts of the mountain and I would be caught in the geometry.
Yeah, sort of in between two slopes where I would just be falling forever.
And I would have to use the restart command.
Yeah, it's it's funny.
There's lots of people who have jumped around on on like
not technically out of bounds.
Like I've never liked games that have invisible walls.
But because of that, I think because of the lack of invisible walls,
people thought you should go to places that you shouldn't.
And.
When it comes to like the slipping down.
It's it's determined we're going to redo a lot of things like that.
Because like from the ground up, they're just sort of fundamentally
not not good.
But like it you land and then it checks the angle of the polygon
you're standing on.
And if it's certainly if it's a certain height, you know, slip.
But there's like a little grace period where you can sort of jump
because some some other thing was interacting with that.
And we needed it to jump sometimes it's a bit messy.
So, uh, mm-hmm, there's work to do in like understanding level design
to like make it clear to the player where you should be going
and where is no go please.
And also just making it harder to do it.
I yeah, I was able to get up on the side mountains and jump around.
And I actually got up to before I even found
well, it turned out I wasn't really supposed to go up there
because I got up to that higher up doorway
and you can't actually go into it.
And I was like darn.
But then I was like, well, that's kind of on me
because I hadn't collected all the bits yet.
I shouldn't be trying to get up to like secret areas.
So I went back and I collected the other bits
and then I came and I explore the area some more.
And I found down below there's the actual entrance
where you're supposed to go in and then there's bits in there.
And then you go through it and there's the exit
and you come out, you come out that upper door
and then you you drop down and Pump is waiting there for you.
So I was like, OK, got it.
And then, yeah, I went back and I explored and I had
and I had all but 12 fairy bits.
I had 238 fairy bits and I'm like, there's 12 left.
And I went back to all the previous areas
and I and I roamed around and I was like, damn it, I can't find them.
I'm sure there's there's a I was sure
that I was looking for an an alley cave, a grotto, I called them.
So I'm jumping around and I'm looking and I'm looking for caves
and I can't find any.
And the way that I ended up finding it was I was jumping around up.
I was I was again, I was like, I can't find anything here.
Maybe if I get if I get a higher vantage point.
So I was jumping around on mountains
that I definitely wasn't supposed to be on.
And just by happenstance through from above,
near the starting area, I saw a little crack in between like the rocks.
I saw the glimpse after like an hour.
I saw the glimpse of a fairy bit and I jumped down
and I fell down into a little not a not an alley grotto,
but a little side cave.
And I realized there was like in the beginning area, there's a little
sort of like a little crack in the rock that you can go through to a little
a little secret area that has some cool like unique flowers and stuff in them.
And I was like, got it.
So so I had missed that on my first go
and I found it sort of in the wrong way by jumping around,
jumping around on rocks.
But that was fun.
It worked. It worked out what you're saying.
So what you're saying is this game was built wrong.
I would say it's built different.
It's just built different. That's all different.
Not wrong. Not wrong. Just different.
But while I was hunting those last 12 bits, I found
what I call the surprise lizards because I found I found four of them.
And I know there's a fifth one that I didn't find.
Steel Viper on Twitter posted there's a red lizard that I didn't find.
But I found a green one, yellow and blue and purple one.
I found four of five, maybe more of these lizards that when you take their picture,
they make a little they make what sounds to me like the little metal gear
alert sound. Oh, yeah.
That's why that's what it sounded like.
And I was OK. Oh, they're like surprised.
It's like a startle. It's a surprise lizard, a surprised lizard,
surprise lizard, a video, a video game reference in my video game.
No, no way.
It wasn't a reference, I guess it's just a coincidence.
Yeah, as a reference.
I think it's a reference.
I'm going to put that down as an Easter egg.
Yeah. Put that down in the week.
Yeah, the week is going to be like, you know,
these lizards sound is taken from metal gear solid.
The first the first one was, I think,
the the yellow one who's on the back of a rock.
And I was like, oh, that's neat.
Many people found that one.
Yeah, I was like, oh, that's neat.
And I took a picture and it made a little boing sound.
And I was like, oh, oh, oh, now we're cooking.
All right. Yeah.
How many are there? I got it.
I got to know how many there are.
Tell us all the tips and tricks for us.
I actually, I actually forget.
I think there's six.
Shit. Shit.
They're secret lizards.
You should make.
Collect them all.
It's been fun seeing, seeing how, like,
people have varying levels of, like.
Like varying degrees of finding the secrets.
People who find the one lizard, usually the one behind the rock,
they're like, oh, I found the lizard.
Yeah.
And they don't know those other ones.
I think the second one I saw was in the per,
because there's, I think there's three
alley grottos and in the one that's purple, I remembered,
I think I remembered when I found that yellow one,
I remembered that I had, I was looking everywhere
for, I was looking everywhere for the last 12 bits.
And I went back into the alley grotto that's all purple
and I remembered, wait a minute,
I think I remember seeing something on the ceiling here
and I looked up and sure enough was like, yes, I was right.
There is another lizard up on the ceiling.
And I took another picture of it and it made the sound.
I was like, yes.
My exploration has been rewarded.
Intrinsically rewarded.
I mean, it didn't, didn't give me anything, but that's OK.
It was the joy of discovery.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, the biggest problem is that no Xbox achievement
was awarded for finding each lizard.
That's my big complaint, too.
The little achievements don't show up.
You haven't even played it.
I'm playing it right now.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm playing it right now.
You're not playing it.
Oh, no, I'll play it, I'll play it.
Just like I'll eventually play the booze game
and just like eventually I'll play Ben's game, you know,
it's going to eventually happen.
Well, unlike unlike the booze game and Ben's game,
my game is in three dimensions.
That's a little too much from my eyes.
I can't play anything.
Yeah, I already live in a three dimensional world.
Why don't I look into another three dimensional world?
It's it's too much effort, really, you ask me.
Fortunately, fortunately, Phantom's Revenge.
The Phantom's Revenge is is is better.
It might lack the third dimension, but it's it's not a demo.
It's a finish. It's it's it's it.
There's no no more potential.
There's no more nothing else to summon.
You've you've completely wrung it dry.
I have wrung it dry.
It's actually it's very frustrating.
I'm very frustrating because you beat me as I
as it has been looking increasingly likely that you were going to.
And it makes me really mad because Phantom's Revenge is done.
It has been done for weeks, maybe more than a month now.
And I'm just and I'm just drawing panels.
This week I am drawing just last night I was drawing.
I'm drawing the final scene, not not not the end scene, not the ending,
but the the final scene of Simon punishment that I had envisioned in my head.
I'm drawing that and it feels weird to finally be drawing it after I imagined it for so long.
But I'm drawing that.
And so I'm like, I just
I'm so close to being able to post it, but I can't post it.
I can't post it until it's all done.
How does it feel getting feel like your wife?
All the video game play as gay sex.
I'll tell you that much.
They'll never play another video game.
Elden Rings out.
You beat Elden Ring.
Oh, my God.
And now I'm going to be behind Elden Ring.
And now everybody's talking about Elden Ring.
You'll play you'll play you'll beat Elden Ring in a day.
Didn't it just come out?
No, I made Elden Ring.
Yeah, that's that's an alley was the demo for Elden.
That's a lie, maybe.
That's maybe a lie.
I don't know.
I don't I don't play.
I never Elden Elden Ring.
I haven't even played Demon Souls.
I can't I can't really play that one.
I can't jump right into the franchise.
Elden Ring looks pretty cool, I guess it looks.
I never played I never played Breath of the Wild, but I really do.
I think that the whole open world, the way that Breath of the Wild
does the open world stuff is pretty neat.
And I think it's probably cool because I've heard that the Elden Ring
is like Dark Souls, but in a Breath of the Wild open world.
Which is pretty cool, cool idea there, which is so funny because I thought
Breath of the Wild was like the Dark Soul of Legend of Zelda.
I mean, it kind of is.
It's a little bit of a circle.
Is it?
I swear I heard someone say that.
Yeah, I haven't heard or something like that.
That Breath of the Wild is the Dark Souls of Zelda.
Wait, I didn't Dark Souls.
Wait, I didn't Dark Souls start the whole like, oh, you can just walk up
to the final boss if you want to.
I mean, not exactly.
Not really, no.
I think the connection is that people used to say that Dark Souls
is like Legend of Zelda, but realistic.
Yeah, Dark Souls, like the most direct lineage of Dark Souls combat
is to like Ocarina of Time, like Lock on Z targeting.
Like, Dark Souls is like a direct ancestor of that anyway.
OK, so basically Dark Souls is the Dark Souls of Zelda, I would say
it would be a more accurate comparison.
Is it like a bad game or take to say that, like, this is probably going
to get a lot of people mad with it.
And the people who hate me are going to hate me more after I say this.
But you don't want to offend those people.
I especially don't want to offend those, I don't want to offend the hate
fandom that big Twitter artist has.
But yeah, all these all these like from soft games
look like the same to me.
Is that is that is that bad to say?
They all just look this.
No, I agree.
I the the the yeah.
You're talking like I mean that I could ring.
A round and ring looks like Dark Souls.
Yeah, like exactly the same thing that I haven't played it.
So all these games have this kind of like
gray, kind of like, I want to say edgy filters.
It has like some sort of filter over them.
Like all the games seem to have this filter.
You might even call it a style or something.
It's it's supposed to be like Dour and Depressing.
Yeah, like things are fucked.
Here's a sword.
Like that's the idea of like of all the the Souls series is like things are
fucked. Here's a sword.
Also, you're probably decrepit and is like it's really sad.
You're going to die.
You're going to die one day in that day is today.
Isn't like every so like it makes sense that there'd be a lot of grays.
But I'd like it to be like a pink one.
Yeah, why is there going to be a pink one?
He is like my favorite color.
I keep saying I keep saying they need to make they make armored corps.
They should make a Souls like where you're a mech.
They should make armored bore.
Oh, my God.
They should make one about being mechs.
And instead of like weapons and armor, you're equipping fucking mech mech parts,
treads and rocket launchers.
I don't know.
It could be pretty cool if you ask me.
Instead of sorceries and wood and pyromancy, you got guns.
I don't know.
Why not?
I want like the I want like Dark Soul, which I never played to have
like a Dragon Quest aesthetic, which I never played.
That's that's what I want.
I aesthetically, they do look pretty similar.
And I'm not like I'm not super into like the way they look.
They look fine.
I can tell Dark Souls to a part because Dark Souls to looks worse.
Yeah.
Dark Souls to looks like Goofy air.
That's that's funny.
There's a few nice places in Dark Souls to it's not like overall.
Yeah, overall.
I don't know exactly.
It's just no, it's the models.
Different feelings.
Something about the like the character model
and maybe the enemy models just looks.
So I feel like maybe it looks cartoonier.
And so I don't know.
I don't ever heard that that's before game, but that sounds interesting.
Yeah, I remember thinking when you put when you have like a lightning weapon,
the way that in Dark Souls to like when you apply lightning
or something to your weapon, it just it doesn't just have like a lightning bolt
effect like an electrified effect.
It glows.
It turns like a stupid like bright primary color like, oh, it's yellow now.
It's like, I hate that.
I feel like all of them do that a little bit.
No, Dark Souls one, maybe I mean, I didn't play I haven't played three.
Dark Souls one, it doesn't turn your sword like yellow
when you make it when you use a, you know, gold pine resin on it or whatever.
It gives it like a little thunderbolts coming off.
Yeah, yeah, I haven't noticed that.
Stood out to me, not in a great way.
Anyway, who cares about Elden Ring?
Yeah, if you got any more game development thoughts on that,
I have many things to say because it's been like, I don't know.
Yeah, that I've been like talking about it, but not talking about it.
Yeah, have people found everything in the game that you like have set up
or there's some more secrets that are that lay in the game
that people haven't stumbled into yet.
I haven't seen anybody who's found all the lizards
and aside from that, there is something that nobody has figured out yet.
Really? OK.
There's an aspect of the game that nobody has figured out yet.
Can you and it's a little obscure.
So that's all I'm telling you about that one.
It's going to be funny.
It's going to be cool if anyone finds it.
Can you? OK, I don't.
Can you be any more specific than aspect?
Uh, is it like a I don't know.
Is it like a little scrambler?
Well, is a scrambler going to show up?
It's all right. Here's here's what it's not.
It's not like a physical location in the game that's hard to reach.
It's nothing like that. Is it like, I don't know.
My mind goes to like, is there is the mechanic?
Is there like, is there like a backwards long jump?
No, it's not like a movement thing, either.
That would be funny if we made like movement controls
that didn't like was so hard to figure out that nobody would ever use this.
Oh, I got it. There's a there's a what do you call them?
Coupes, there's QPUs. There's QPUs.
You can you can QPU misalign yourself in parallel world.
That's right.
If you get stuck when you're in the full animation, you stay there.
You go parallel universe.
You build up speed.
You build up speed for 12 hours until you you warp to the next world down below.
People have made that joke.
It does kind of look like you could build up speed.
Yeah, because because because you're continually falling.
You're stuck in the falling animation. I did.
I almost got.
Well, I was jumping around in mountains
and I got pumped stuck in the between two ledges, infinite falling.
And Ali looked normal and I wanted to get Ali
to take a picture of pump in that state.
But I think Ali was also considered to be falling.
So I couldn't get her to go into the the take a picture.
Did she have her arms up?
Was she a falling animation?
She didn't know she looked normal.
She no, I remember thinking she did not look like she was falling,
but she could not take her phone out either.
So it didn't work out.
If you can control Ali, you can walk around.
You should be able to use the phone.
Um, I think I could maneuver her a little bit.
But she was she was also stuck in the left.
Yeah, she didn't.
But I could sort of move her.
She could sort of like, well, that makes sense.
Wiggle her a bit from left to right.
She's got a thing.
She's got a thing where, like, if she's moving too fast or.
Or something, she'll you'll be forced out of the phone mode.
Or I think I haven't tried this.
I think it's you you throw Ali up.
No, no, that wouldn't work.
There's something something to do with, like, no, when you.
Yeah, you can pick up and if you didn't know, if you didn't know,
you can pick up and throw Ali open.
She bounces like a bouncy ball against objects and it's funny.
But, like, if she's using her phone and she gets thrown,
but she wouldn't be.
You wouldn't break her phone and then you can't use that for no more.
She she's forced out of the phone mode for various little reasons
like that, I think.
It's just the main thing I I don't know.
I don't know if this is an intentional bit of like, developer comedy.
Or or just bad conveyance.
But it's probably the second different thing.
I'm talking about the first Ali grotto that I found.
There's a sign right outside of it
that says you can return to pump at any time by pressing.
I think it is shift I didn't try it, but I came back later and when you when Ali goes into the grotto
No, you cannot you can't you can't actually can't do it while you're while she's in the cave
Only when she's out in the overall which makes sense
And I get why you wouldn't want because if you could do that then you would become pump again
And you would be stuck without Ali. She'd be back in the in the cave
Yeah, the the the reason we did that was because when Ali is way away from punk
She'll teleport to her if you're playing as punk. Yeah, and it was like confusing and difficult to like account for
Ali being in the cave and if you accidentally switch back to punk and then suddenly Ali like teleports to you as punk
You'll lose every all progress you had in the cave and we didn't want that so we have like cave zones where
Ali is unable to switch back. Yeah, he has a little moment and then she gets out
we might rework that because
I
Mean funny, I guess that you are immediately told you can switch back. Don't worry about it and you actually I think it's fine
You're in there. It didn't like I mean
if I
It would not it would not have frustrated me. I would have been like. Oh, well, whatever lol now. I get it
It's fine. I'll just go back out this door. Okay
See ya
Yeah, people said Ali. It's a little too slow. I think we're gonna increase her speed
It's not so much of a slot. She's pretty slow. I didn't I didn't find it too frustrating
Yeah, but like
Obviously things like this is
We wanted to have like a slice of like all the different aspects of game development game
Mechanics that you could interact with and Ali going into little caves
Not all of them are planned to be like that size
Some of them might be a bit longer more involved
Or there might be like a puzzle involved where you have to be Ali and punk and switch between them or something
so
the
things about like
Playing as the character need to be fun. We're thinking of giving Ali a little jump as well
Not like a big jump, but just something so the tiny little
Things on the floor don't get an array. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
Yeah, she can't move
Just can't move at all
So, but I mean that's that's that's character design. What is um when is shovel night gonna show up in the game?
This is an indie game after all right, we're gonna
We're gonna have a shovel where and night he comes in he's like hey
Do you want some cheap shit and you buy hey?
Do you want to buy a Chippendales rescue Rangers on the Game Boy Advance like where you want to play shitty games?
I
Says that and then Ali it's like yeah, I got a GBA adapter on my phone
And then you can play Chippendale in in and pumpkin alley. That's a intended feature that is definitely not been just made
Yeah, you the game the game the game comes with an emulator
You can you can play any any like Super Nintendo or NES emulator you can play it in the game
In yeah on on elliops in elliops phone mode like far away from the screen like in vertical
Yeah, like terrible resolution
In in like low low lower colors can converted to like cyan cyan and pink and yellow
Yeah, good pretty epic. See him. See I see him like a bee
That's pretty epic
It was pretty epic any any more gamer questions you got forget those are all those are all my notes
Those are all my complaints
I'm trying to think if there was any
I what did you like about it? What did I like about it?
Um, I liked running around like Spyro the dragon. I like Spyro the dragon. You know what? Yeah, you know
You know what I didn't like actually here's a good one. I think that I think that that what did you like about it?
Nothing. Here's some stuff that sucks. Um, I think the the
The plants burning burning the plants was a little bit. I didn't like realize they were burning until they weren't like later
I feel like the difference could be like more dramatic. I don't know. It took me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I
Had to kind of be like are these what did I do anything by that? Um, yeah
I
Don't know. That's it. My minor minor gripe
Yes, it's it's to do with them. There's like a layer
for the thorns and the grass
Where like I had to make a layer of a gradient and
The color of the gradient determines what order it gets like burned away
in the and sort of like
Like if you burn a thorn bush, it'll like shrink and then there'll be like embery bits
Yeah, and it'll it'll follow that that mat or whatever you call it
Yeah, but for the grass I kind of fucked up the gradient a little bit
And so it sort of doesn't do much at first and then then quite quickly goes to nothing. Yeah, okay
So it looks like nothing's happening, but yeah, we're gonna redo the grass. Yeah
What's a little I mean the grass doesn't even like do anything so like whatever it doesn't even matter if it's there or not
Yeah, people like burning it. Yeah, some people were saying
Why isn't there rupees in this? Why isn't there stuff in this?
and I think we were thinking of doing that, but it was just sort of like
quite late in
Like we wanted to get the demo out
There's lots of little bits that we could have like spent maybe another few days on a few, you know a week or two
to iron it out perfectly, which is why there's so many glitches and stuff, but
That's the the idea is just to make it real get people hype was there and then you know, yeah all that was there
was there something in there that like
You didn't have to add
But you were like I want to add this and like it ended up being like
Oh, but that was like way more trouble than it was worth like I spent like we spent like a month adding this stupid thing and like well
I think I think most things that we ended up spending a lot of time on
Are worth because people like them. Yeah, they're just sort of like
Maybe arguably like time investment to enjoyment gained is like skewed. I think I'm Ali Oop's phone and her camera
Considering maybe not doing that, but it was funny
Just to be able to take a selfie even if the selfie camera is quite like you couldn't really angle it in a way
So you could see things. Yeah, but it was it's funny that you can do it at all. It is funny
It would be I mean, I mean, it's it's just yeah, it's just it's just funny and like
What's flight flavorful? I guess thematic character building that it's in the game. Yeah at all. Yeah
I think I've said this before but this was a lot of a lot of my
experience with the phantom's revenge is
Being like hey, I got a little funny idea for something I can add. Haha wouldn't it? Yeah, whatever
Hey, I'll just do this thing and then it takes me like several weeks and I'm like
Regretting it and I'm like, why did I do this? Like why did I decide why did I decide to add floor reflections?
Why did I decide to add like, you know a dynamic blood splatter on like the walls and stuff?
Yeah
Yeah, there's definitely moments where I'm like, ah, how about this and I say to Charlie
What would it be like a big load of hassle and terrible coding nightmares if we did this tiny little thing?
And he goes, yeah, ah
Yes, it would and I'm like, okay, we don't need to do it and we'll we'll not do it you
You poached you poached Charlie from me give I
Did yeah, you gave you gave me told him you wanted you gave me Charlie and then you took him back for me
How could you Indian give her how could you poach? How could you poach your own brother?
Well, yeah, I'm taking it been taken. Oh my god. It was oh my god
I
Remember I remember that
Charlie cuz he was like, you know, he made a runaway from snakes
Yeah, and he was like working on little projects here and there and I was like, okay Tom
Does game development work?
Maybe you should talk to Tom and like do things and that never really happened because Tom wants to be in control of his thing
And they didn't really talk so it's like yeah, whatever. Yeah, but Ben you were talking about making a game
Hey Charlie go talk to Ben about this thing. Yeah, you know, you know, it's thing
Yeah, and then apparently you didn't get back to him. So it's just like I don't know what to do
Yeah, I was a bit anything else happening. Yeah, I was a bit of a dick
I didn't get back to him for a while because I think I've said this before I
Sort of told him what this is when I had not even really started working on the game
But I was like, I think I think this was this was when I was working on the s revert animation
I was like, but I know I'm gonna make the game and I was talking to
Charlie and I was I told him like what the game was
Kind of gonna be I kind of said like here's my idea for it
It was pretty rough at the time and he he was like hey, I prototyped this thing like what do you think and it was
Not it was not
Exactly what I had envisioned it was something a little different. It wasn't because it wasn't like a straight-up ghosted him after that
I
Did eventually get back to him. It was it was I didn't I didn't know what to say because it was like
This is this is good and all but it's not what I was
picturing and like
What do I do I?
Should I just say like no or should I just be like hey change it or should I and I think I
Just wasn't sure what I wanted to do. I think eventually I decided like I kind of I kind of just want to make it myself
I thought I was fucking do it myself
Then so yeah, I hope yeah, I hope I hope I guess it all worked out
Yeah, yeah, I mean it's really just a thing of
Communication it's harder to communicate through discord messages and stuff. Yeah, yeah, yeah
It's for me to just go up and talk to him like when we're developing the game
We're in the same room. He's coding things and I'm like either drawing or like fucking around thinking
Yes, and then we like have discussions about how do you think this should work? I'm like, okay, let's think um
conveyance
in an in an alternate in an alternate universe where I had been like I
Had jumped on it and I had been like, okay, Charlie. No, no, you got to rework this here
You got to make you got to make it like this. You got to you got to do like this
You got to add this you got to add that I
Yeah, I imagine the process of like
get him him
Making changes to the prototype sending them back to me me be I'm like, okay change this this this and that and then like
Sending it back waiting for him to do that getting it back. I imagine that would have been
painstaking
So a little bit. Yeah, maybe it's probably fine
I
Must it is must be nice to have a to have a code guy though must be nice to have a brother
Must be yeah
Yeah, must be nice. Oh well
He doesn't know that feeling at all, right Ben
Not it not anymore
Although I mean, I don't regret I don't regret learning I don't regret learning GML I
Feel like I learned I feel like I learned a lot of code
Working on it. Yeah, but I can keep using in the future. I don't need a code guy. I'll never need a code guy again
Coding is easy. Yeah, coding is easy by the way
It's literally it's literally just looking up how to just you literally just Google
How do I do this and there's someone wrote it's like you type this and you go okay?
Yeah, I think I've seen a car kind of you just Google how to fix a car and then they should just tell you right there
I mean unironically unironically
Coding is like fixing a car only
Nothing happens if you fuck it up and you can just keep trying until it works. So yeah, basically the easiest thing
Okay, that's I'll learn to code right now, but for me. Yeah coding. Yeah, coding is like it's interesting
but it's like
The the skill floor like you need to like get a ladder to get to that floor
Before you're like actually able to
creatively solve problems with like idea like knowledge of like, okay, this kind of code would work
If this and that so I'll just make a thing and then I'll experiment like it would take a long time for me to get to the
experimental phase of being a programmer
Which is the fun part and copy pasting stuff only works if someone else has done it
And if you're trying to make something specific, it's sometimes not
Easy to find that you know at least not a good teacher, you know, I'm thinking about it
And I'm realizing that I am a genius because again yet again
I'm coming to I'm how many how many times must I have the same revelation over and over again of what a genius I am
How many different fields? How many different mountains must I conquer before I'm finally finished already?
The the it was just like in in vapors. I had never made a comic and I was like, well, I guess I guess I'll just do it
I guess I'll just start working on it and I'll figure it out as I went along and that was and then I did and
Then same with phantom's revenge coding. I'm just like, well, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna start making it like I don't know
What I'm doing, but I fuck it. I'll just figure it out and I did
And yeah, and and I just just keep chiseled just keep hammering away at it until it's how you want it
And in the process you discover how to do those things and then you're like well
It is definitely possible or it would have been definitely possible for me to make pump canali myself by myself
All right, probably it just would have taken like four years instead of right like nine months, right?
Yeah, four to five to six years. It would take a long time
I guess Charlie has been learning to code for a long time or are you pretty long time?
He went to uni for three years for it and also he's just been like extra curricular like coding all the time
He loves I don't think he loves coding, but he loves making games and being interested in like trying to find out how to do things
Yeah, yeah once a coding university and you went to PCP University and finally a brought both talents together
To fuse and make this ultimate product for the masses
Yes
PCP is is only game. It's only game game people now damn
It's can't watch it no more. I can't relate. Yeah, can't can relate no more
tech bro
Once you become a game developer all of your comics. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, they're swept away in the tide. It's the source for us lost. Where is she she's gone?
Yeah, true. It's it's just like it's just like toy store, you know everyone nobody wants to play with cowboy toys anymore
Everyone want now everyone wants space toys as soon as Sputnik went up, you know everything changed
Is it's kind of like when I switched over from short films to comics my short film side doesn't exist anymore?
They just they just
They just melt it away
Yeah, you like dismantle them and use the skill points to put into new. Oh, I actually
I actually am currently doing that exact same thing you just described right now
They melt it away like something melting away
No, I mean they melt it away like something
I won't specify in the scene that I'm drawing in in slime and punishment right now because it would be a spoiler for the end
For the end my god
Does phantom horn get melted into a skeleton of horn like if you lose the game?
That definitely phantom horn shoot like buckets of cum and it looks like it's like it's like melting in their hand
That happens
I'm not gonna answer any I can't answer that
Cuz it's true. I can't answer that specific question
Yeah, you can't you can't give any direction on that question cuz if you if you had asked anything else
I could tell you no, but unfortunately
I can't answer that specific query either positively or not actually um
It's like the idea that you do the whole phantoms revenge like slime and punishment comic and right at the end
It becomes extremely explicit 18 plus poor and that's how villain versus gonna end and then
And that's the reward for getting to the end
There's instead of like it's like instead of like a confirm
Are you over the age of 18 before you see it instead?
I have you beat a video game cuz I'm like only a heart only a hardcore gamer could see this pornography
That'll show there they're mature, you know ages just a number right ages just a number and you just gotta you gotta prove
It's your epic gaming skill is more important than like what's on your driver's license if you want to read my porn or be my girlfriend
I didn't I shouldn't say that on a podcast. It's really about that'll be quoted
It's really about mental maturity
People think I'm serious, you know in and gaming and gaming skill is
The best indicator science has yet found it's better than IQ
It's you have to be quite mature. I have no video game
Especially one that's like a have to be spin off of a spin off of a based on
Another bullshit that Benzane is doing
That's right. That's right. Um, yes
Wait, that's the big difference in the games is that mine has this market appeal because it's just two characters
Yeah, man, that's the formula, you know, there's um, there's punk and Ali and there's bongo and Luna. That's that's the two
It's always the two
Phantom always to handsome and horn Phantom and Phantom and who?
Phantom and who? There's no one there. Yeah, Phantom's got a sidekick. Phantom's got his little his little pet
He can he's got he's also got platinum
You know his trusty sidekick platinum the sword who he can marry now in the game if you so choose
Can you kiss the sword and cut your lip you can kiss the sword it doesn't cut your lip though because phantom's very he's pretty good
He knows how to handle knows how to think he's an experience. He's an experienced love knows how to use his tongue
Right, you know, so if you know the amateur tongue kisser, of course, you'll cut your your lip
But unlike phantom horn lots of experience
I mean, I mean if you're if you're cutting your lip when you kiss your sword, you know
You're your gaming skill level is not high enough for you to be getting married in my sort of mental disorder
If you cut your lip while kissing a sword really that's my opinion. It's my take of the day
And you it shouldn't be happening if you're a gamer. True. Let's just let's just let's just put it that way
Shit, I feel I was gonna was I gonna mention? Oh, oh, I do have one
Yeah, I had one thing to mention. It's not exactly relevant
Should I should I say it? Well, if it's I'm just gonna know you go first
the the pumpkin early thing
to wrap up
Play that game
In terms of in terms of like what's gonna happen in the future
Yeah, we're gonna be working on it
I think in March and just just working just like doing some things maybe have a little hot fix patch for some of the
The more obvious and easy to fix problems, right?
Not gonna be an overhaul or anything, but we may once my Lord of Ghost Kickstarter is all squared away and done
We may be doing a Kickstarter to raise funds for paying for the making of the whole thing
Yeah, I was wondering about so stay tuned for for potential that I'm not entirely sure how long it's gonna take and stuff
We'll have to like figure out costs and and things
Yeah, but that's the general idea because it seems like that it seems like lots of people want that
It's the sort of normal thing that an indie game studio could do. Yeah, and I think it would work pretty well
Really release a demo and then kickstart development on the full game. Yeah makes it makes sense to me
Do you I?
guess do you
Have anything you are
You're like we're for sure gonna add this that you want to mention
And well for sure
Uh
There's there's dialogue things
That we couldn't get done for the demo
Obviously, there's gonna be NPCs and and things there's lots of different zones wait wait
Yes, I had a complaint there was at least one time when a signs dialogue box would not advance
I like mashed the F key or I like mashed the key for a while before that damn
Dialogue box advance. Yes, the dialogue box event was a little bit weird. Yeah
I just remembered that just nice
Quality of life upgrades not really upgrades, but just sort of like fixes
Like that. We're we're we're tallying them up. We're gonna go through the wall. Okay fix them. Okay
if anybody has like
Thoughts complaints go to the pumpkin alley itch.io community tab and leave like a a post
Detailing everything because when we're going to like check everything
It's the easiest place to go and like double-check what people thought
What the criticisms were?
So we can like look at them all at the in one place. Yeah. Yeah, so
Anyway, you were saying you were saying
You were you were enumerating things you were going to add which I'm curious about. Oh, yeah
So there's there's boss battles. Yeah, and lots of enemies
I kind of what the design philosophy for for combat is that I don't want it to be like God of War
It's not like a combat heavy game. Yeah, and when you do fight an enemy. I want it to be
More of a puzzle than just running at something and setting in the moon fire. Yeah
Maybe there could be some easier enemies like that, but that would feel like padding but maybe
But like generally they'll be like, oh this enemy has some sort of shield that you need to like
Knock off before you can burn them or this enemy. Yeah is made of a material that can't be burned
Unless you change something in the environment that makes them burnable, you know, that's the sort of idea for the buses and
And and enemies. Yeah, so that's gonna be expanded a lot that the mushroom was is pretty good
I think it explains that yeah, the most that is a puzzle. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, the mushroom is I
He kind of jump-scared me a little bit when he like the idea
Yeah, when he first yeah when he first yells and like the music changes. I was like, oh my god. What the fuck?
Yeah, I didn't because there had not I didn't think there were any enemies in the game. So I was like
Yeah, it gotcha. Yeah, it got me it got me a little bit
Uh, whatever. There's there's there's a dialogue system. There's like
I'm not entirely sure how we're gonna do this. I had this idea
Initially that like you could press a button to like chat with the other character
So like you could just say something and and the dialogue that they have would be like
Contextual contextual to like the the room or like the general zone that you're in
And there would be like pulling from a pool of like possible chat options. Yes
And if there's like a puzzle room you could press the button
And punk would say what do you think and ali would say? I don't fucking know like you just have like a little
Maybe it could be a helpful thing. Wait a second. I don't know how easy that would be to program though for like every room to have a little
little potential dialogue, but that's uh, it's an idea
I mean, that's not
It it could be I mean, I mean
Phantom's revenge has a little uh has a little you know not not to brag or anything
But Phantom's revenge has a little contextual dialogue where in every room you can examine every enemy and you can examine the room
And you can examine everything and depending on where you are you'll get a little different different dialogue boxes
so there it's it's it's like um the the issue is like
One if a dialogue box appears on screen, are you still able to move and will that halt the flow of platforming?
And if it doesn't halt the flow
Will it get in the way of like visually because they don't speak English they go
They're gonna have like a animal crossing or okami or banjo banjo kazooie is the one that jumps to my hand
Um, they're gonna talk like that. So it's gonna have to be in text and
I don't know how that's gonna fit with like
gameplay
unnecessarily
um
But there's definitely gonna be like dialogue scenes where like you there's like a threshold and it's a kind of a cut scene
Where they talk about the story or whatever and they talk to an mpc or something like that
Does ali talk in bell jpe?
Um in bell jpe there there's like a few moments where they speak but like there's no like quotes
Yeah in in the text the text underneath each image is like the narrator saying what's happening
Um, or like if you are a punk you do this and you do that and you say to ali that's fucking sick
um
But like they don't have like speech bubbles and there's no like quotes at the bottom to to to be able to tell
But there is at least one place. I remember where like
um
ali and pump have
Reunited after run away from snakes the game and panel
And they're saying something about stuff and ali has her phone back
Excellent, so they speak do I gotta me spare gotta play run away from snakes before I get into this
Yeah, yeah, you have to play run away from snakes or the game won't make any sense
You got you got to read bell jpe and play the the run away from snakes panel
Which is a video game panel that is a is a panel of the comic and also a video game
It's an endless runner. It's fun. It's hard, but it's it's it's a lord
There was is there still a leaderboard for that?
I think that broke. Um
That part of the thing was so confusing and terrible idea
um
When it broke, we were like, no, we'll leave it. No, you know, it's fine. It's fine. Yeah
I mean, it was fun. It was fun to fuck around with while it was while it was uh happening though
Yeah
Oh, I had um
Yeah, the thing I was gonna say was I had a
I had a
An idea for the the eventual
Book form for slime and punishment, which by the way
I guess I'll be curious to know when you wanted when you're gonna do
Uh, a kickstarter for that because I am I'm gonna kickstart the book
And I don't want to run our kick starters at the same time. So, um, yeah, sure. I mean, um
It will depend
On first I think march is gonna be my love ghosts kickstarter
Backer reward like finally finish all of that stuff send them off
And then it'll be either during march or in april
Figuring out the kickstarter and then maybe launching it sometime in april. I guess
Yeah, but I don't know yet. It'll maybe it'll depend on how long it takes for me to do all the the lord of ghosts stuff
Yeah, well, I mean I want to hmm. I mean, I guess I'd see no reason
I guess I'm gonna try and run the
Slime and punishment kickstarter as soon as I I can
So maybe I mean I might kind of like finish the comic and then basically immediately try to
You know figure out how I'm gonna print it and yeah, and it'll it'll just depend on how long it takes me to settle on like
Okay, this is the final design of the book. These are the printers. I'm going with
Okay
Yeah, so that's that's what uh
That's what that depends on
but anyway
I I had thought right I had envisioned
Slime and punishment as being like
The problem sleuth books. I haven't read the homestuck books
So I don't know if they're the same but the problem sleuth books generally have four panels on a page and then at the bottom
um
Andrew hussey has a running commentary where every page he has little uh
Little notes about the panels and I was gonna do that
but I think
A lot of panels like a lot of pages I could but I don't know if I have something to say on every page
So I think it actually might be better and maybe also funnier
I think the way I might actually end up doing it
Is to have like an index section at the end with footnotes
Like infinite jest, you know infinite jest has like the whole book is full of like little
Asterisks that lead to the back and there's a whole like there's like
Several chapters worth of like
Notes and indexes and like little side stories that relate to uh, whatever
So I think I'm gonna have an index section where I will have little asterisks that will direct you to a part where I
explain like
This is this is why I
This was the context that made me add this to the story or oh, yeah the the the the player
Avatars that are depicted on these pages are are these people
Or does the homesick books do that? I thought they did do that, right?
That they would have the little commentary. I don't know it
They do they do I have some of them word. They have a little they have a little index
They have an index section not an index. No, they have the the comments right on the page, right?
Right on the page at the bottom. Yeah, I just I just explained that my original idea was going to be that
But I think I want to have it in a I want to have
I want to have foot I want to have foot footnotes in their own section like annotated almost, right?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes, because it definitely needs it. It definitely needs that for certain things
that might be a little confusing or
something like
in the
In the index section is probably where I would put
For instance, there are some panels that there are some pages of it that are me
Recreating or like pseudo recreating
Drawings that chris chan did and I would probably like have a little
asterisk that would direct you to a page in the index where I'd be like
Yeah, here are the original images that these
Panels were were based on a referencing or something like that
Because I couldn't I couldn't fit that in a I couldn't fit that in us in a foot. You should um
You should do it that every time you mentioned chris chan
You write another like little mention right next to chris chan's name saying yeah, yeah, I know I know they're in jail
Yeah, I know about the several things he did and
But I've got every time in a book in a book in a book. I leave a little footnote
That's like, yeah, please don't comment telling me uh about the chris chan being in jail. I I know
Please and then at the end of the book. I should put please like comment and subscribe
Uh, ring the bell. Yeah, and then you should um, yeah, you should just yeah
You should drop off the book at a random bookstore and then people be like what the fuck is this what the
What the niche hell shit bullshit internet bullshit is this?
That's the brand I
Yeah, I guess that is the brand. I guess that is the brand. Um, I'm just allergic to mass market appeal
I I I would be
You know what if anybody actually likes if anyone actually liked my game
I would be disappointed in myself. I would hate them. I would if you like my game. Fuck you
You're an idiot. I made that game specifically to attract the kind of people I hate
So if you like it that means I fucking hate you
I made that game specifically to be
I made the game specifically to be fun on its own
In a way that people that had not read the comic could enjoy anyway
But in a way that is also sort of very strongly gesturing towards
Hey, hey, hey, check the comic out. Hey
You should read the comic if you want additional context on like what's going on in this game
You don't have to read the comic, but like you should you should read you should read the comic though
Please, please read the comic
Please please read the comic
And please watch this this this t-bat plays. Let's play. It's very important to understand. No, that's not things
Are gonna make sense even
Even I even I would not
Even I would not expect someone to watch t-bap in order to understand the the context there
All you need to know is that he is a
he is a
mlp youtube reviewer
Cartoon
Cartoon avatar in the side of the in the side of the video avatar, that's all you need to know
And you don't you don't actually have to go and like experience it just really it's self-evident everything
I mean
You can just see it. You can just see it in his face
It's like
He's got that youtuber in the corner of face. He does right? That's me in the corner
That's my mlp sonar ranting about episodes of my little pony. I
I I'm drawing his
Losing my subscribers
I'm drawing his fight basically his final scene
Right now and it's it's making me uncomfortable. It's very uncomfortable to draw, but I have to do it. I think
I don't know. I think I talked about this before. I don't know how people will react. First of all
I don't know if anyone cares. I don't know if anyone reads the comic a few like I know I know that a handful of people do
I don't know if the catch-up
Uh, yeah, I am at least I mean I
So after you drop off after you drop the little animation for what I
I thought at the time was the finale. I was like, oh, well no more
Simon punishment. I guess and I like oh wait still going on, huh?
I called it the finale
Even though I sort of knew at the time that I knew I was going to make the game even then so I don't know why I
Yeah, I and then I thought oh the game must be like the extended and I might be the finale part too, but not really
It's interesting
No, no the game was the game was always going to be the true ending. Um, but uh
I'm drawing
The finale I'm drawing the final scene
And it's very uncomfortable and if anyone cares. I wonder I wonder if they'll
I'm I think on another episode
I said like it might feel very different to a reader than it feels to me a reader might just read something
And just be like oh lol that happened
um, and me I might like feel it differently and I might be like
I don't know. I think it might be different and to me. I'm drawing it and I feel
Discomfort I feel disquieted I feel
I don't I would you I would you being like really
I would even I would even say I would I would even say horrified. I would say I would say silence you feel the platform
You feel like like the libs have come after you they've taken everything away from you
Well, what well what I'm getting at is it's an uncomfortable scene and I wonder if people will dislike it and be like
I don't like the ending because it's uncomfortable
Or I wonder if
Nobody will
Mind I don't know because if someone complained about it
If someone was like wow that ending was was like why did you do why did it end that way?
I would understand why they felt that way and I wouldn't disagree with them
I I would merely tell them
That it's what my heart. I followed my heart. My heart told me to do it
The muse the music it was literally it literally was not my choice
The muses spoke through me and they told me to do that and I and I just had to do it
And it and that's and that's not even an exact. That's not even exaggeration
I'm sort of thinking like is it like a gory like he gets
He's slowly like close up of him falling into a wood chipper and you see in all the glory detail
I'm not going to say what it better not be
No, I can I can neither confirm nor deny that specific
That's specific thing that one there's gonna be some fourth wall
Breaking bullshit where it cuts to Ben St. Drawing the comic and he's like I think I'll just stop or some
deep
That's that would be very uncomfortable. It's a
It's a it's a Stephen King
Dark tower the ending just loops back to the beginning
Infinite I don't want to read this comic again
Yeah, well you have to you just have to keep reading it. You just have to keep reading and reading and replaying and replaying it
That's how bonga luna
That's how bonga luna was supposed to end. It was supposed to just restart back to the beginning loop forever
Is that true? Is it is that no, that's not true. I mean that up. Oh, okay
well
So I guess that's all just to say that I'm curious what people will
Feel about the ending and I guess
For the month I kind of just hope I hope I hope people feel anything at all about it. Even if they're mad
disgusted
Infuriated disappointed
That's all that's all good
That's that's all a net positive if everyone's just like
Oh, whatever. I kind of just didn't even notice. Oh, I didn't even read it
Yeah, that would be that's that's that's the worst-case scenario
Uh me going around being like, hey, hey guys, you read the end of the slime and punishment. What are you? Who?
Slime and what?
Who are you? Why are you talking to me?
This is a this is a school. This is a school zone. You're not allowed within 500 feet. Oh my god. I have this uh
Oh my god. Oh, okay
Is the ending that dark that you're not allowed out of school zone after it's happened?
Yeah, we read the end of slime and punishment and we've decided you're no longer allowed you're no longer allowed within 500 feet of a school
Yeah, and um
Slime and punishment cuts to phantom horn in bed and he's all like and that's my story and it and it's like another pony
It's like one of the one of the toddler ponies is like wow, that's crazy
The end of slime and punishment is a is just phantom horn turning to the camera and and
As speaking as me he delivers a direct apology and a list of people that he that he is that the author has groomed
And he's sorry and he's really sorry though. Give him another chance
Yeah, that's how that's how villain versions two
Oh, we all got to do it. Yeah, we all gotta do it now. You have to do it too. Give that's how punk and aliens
Yeah, yeah, yeah, give you gotta do it. Yeah punk turns to the camera just list off all the people
Sorry, I groomed
Uh, this dog I groomed the rex. I groomed alex. I groomed chachi. I groomed
Um tico all all poodles that live in my neighborhood
So, uh, anyway, uh, that's I guess that's I guess that's all I guess that's all that's that's pretty epic
I think so what I I want to I want to talk to you
Ben and give you could you could participate you could you could be a part in this too
Oh god, I think I mean, I didn't I didn't think I mean I invited you on there. I didn't think we'd have to talk to you
Cheesy you're just here for diversity hiring really
Wait, yeah one one second
You try and escape is please try to escape
I'm
Back with a new bottle of sparkling water. Okay, go. Um, how come you didn't have a black guest on for black history month, huh?
kind of fucked up
Wait, do you guys wait? Do you guys know black people?
Uh, no, I know zen huckstable
I guess kind of who where is he? I kind of disappeared a little
I saw him
not
Maybe if you
Maybe a month or two ago, uh, I think
You should um, you should see him
I see him every once in a while because he lives he lives sort of nearby
She got him on the on the podcast and get the zen update because that guy's like a ghost now
Yeah, I don't know if he would want to be on because he's he's kind of gone ghosts
He's he's kind of gone in the real world. He has a band or something. He isn't he isn't a band. He isn't a band
It is cool. I saw them. I saw them live. Uh, they're they were great. That's epic. That's cool. Oh never mind, dude
Fuck podcasting
I yeah, exactly. Yeah, it's either you got in a band or you do a podcast. You kind of have both
That's too much
But I want to I chose wrong
Ben on the wrong horse like you always do Ben
um, but
Yeah, phantom horn. Yeah, exactly
I want the the inferior the inferior brother the dandy de Vito to keg standards. Arnold Schwarzenegger
Where the fuck is keg standard? Where's keg standard? That's what I kept saying every time reading slamming punishment
Like when is keg standard gonna pop in and save the day?
Uh keg standard is in slamming punishment keg standard does in fact make a cameo
I drew that uh, actually, I'll be I'll probably be posting that
in a few days
Yeah
I asked
I asked I thought I thought keg should make a cameo at least once
And so I asked this was this was like this was like a year ago
Which is how fucked up time is
like a year ago
I asked nate
Hey, what would you like?
Do you have any input on like what keg's cameo should be and he did?
and
This is actually pretty funny. He did he was like, hey, what if keg did this and I was like, okay cool
And I didn't I didn't depict it exactly the way he described
but I incorporated the joke that he that he suggested and
I and I posted those pages in my my patron discord channel and
A bunch of people were like
Is this like a like I don't get it like is this a reference to something like what like what it why does he
What is this and I was just like lol nah
Nate just said keg should say that
Because it's funny and everyone was like why is he's saying
It may it was funnier in my opinion. I was like good
uh, there's there's it's
It's good. I think it was I think I think it may at least to me it made it funnier
also keg kegs the kegs the pony
That um that says all the people he groomed right that is that the funny thing Nate wanted you to put
it
I'm not gonna say it's just a little it's just a little weird keg moment
keg moment
Yeah, it's just just it's just a little weird quirky keg moment. That's just a little bit like, huh?
What?
Oh, no, I think I think it was I think it was crack said
Like cracks said someone asked like why is why is keg saying this and I was like, I don't know lol
And Nate Nate said to and and crack was like, oh, I thought you were making fun of him
You're telling me Nate told you to to have this like oh, okay
Uh, I was like, yes base phantom horn beats beats keg to death
And the the whales whales and pain from all the fucking kicks that he's getting
Yeah, he's like, hey, what if keg? Hey, what if can't just beat the shit out of phantom?
Well, yeah, that would be yeah, that would be pretty funny. Okay, bro
Yeah, he has it coming. He's been on his high horse for too long
He is on his high. He's on he's on virginia
Hey, he's a little high slime wood
Hey, oh
got him
But um, I wanted to talk to you uh bent about because I I I finally I I did my first convention this uh past weekend
Yeah, I saw that's why you couldn't be on last week, right?
Because you were doing that uh that con I saw you tweet that picture of you at the con table
And you look great. Thank you. Your hair looks amazing. Thank you
Thank you king. Thank you. I um, yeah, it was interesting doing a con
um
And I I've sold I sold like half of my inventory
When I was uh, yeah, yeah, it was like I I still have not done a full con. I've only done that that mini mice
Like pseudo con table outdoor thing. Are you gonna just not quite the same?
Are you gonna apply for the full one once the registrations are open for that or?
Oh god, I didn't even think about that
Yeah, I want to do it again
It's probably too late shit
Fuck
Wait, I gotta google. It's probably it might be too late to do that. Uh uh mice uh convention
Uh mice 2021
No, okay, it looks like they have not scheduled one for mice for 2022
Okay, uh, so okay, it's it's fine. No, okay. I'm not you should uh check on the website. See if like applications
and just
Well, I don't think so because they haven't yeah, they haven't even announced one for 2022 yet
So because yeah in previous the last year
I wanted to do it, but like
Uh table space was booked like like immediately
So I missed my opportunity
so I
I wouldn't have even been surprised if I had gone and like it was already too late
Uh, but it's not
um
Okay, anyway, uh
Yeah, so you tabled. What was that? What was the convention?
It was called the rocket con and it was here in san diego and um
It was um it might
This probably this con was not necessarily perfect for comics because
When I first stepped into it and I went into like the bigger halls where they had like the the vendors booths
I realized that wait a second. This is a toy convention
Because it was just nothing but toys
Like toy convention, huh? Like it was all the bigger booths were selling just walls of funko
and everything else was like
Everything else was like the older toys like retro toys or like the the newer stuff that's trying to look like retro toys
Right, which isn't bad. Like no, that's like necessarily bad stuff. But like
Yes, it was mostly for collectors and I should have known that this was going to be the case
Because um this convention was hosted by a local comic book store called
um
TC rockets and actually I don't even know if I want to call them a comic book store because they
They sell comics, but they're in a small like alley section of their of their store
the rest of the store is just nothing but like toys
and a section for uh tabletop games and um
And that was just kind of obvious stepping in because like there was only two people there
selling um independent comics. It was me and uh a guy who was like two booths next to me
Right and it seemed like people were spending people were way more interested in like just getting toys there than um
Getting comics, which makes sense
Right. Yeah, also. Yeah fair enough. Yeah, also
But what was kind of annoying was that the I was in the artist alley with my partner and um
it was
The room for the artist alley was kind of like
It felt almost like conjoined
The the convention didn't really do a good job of like making like
Making the way people walk into the convention seemed natural
because um the entrance of the convention was actually like the exit even though it was like at the front of the of the like
Like um event center and they had to make people like walk around
Right and then our art section of the artist alley was kind of like it was right next to the hall, but you had to like
I don't know like it it doesn't
incentivize you to like walk into the artist alley
You kind of have to go out of your way to get to the artist alley
Right and there was only like a handful. Yeah, there was only a handful of us there
and it was um
I mean, we probably could have sold more if if this convention was more focused on comics
and um, but
I mean that them's them's the beans
But um a couple as they say them's the beans, but um, I I
Fuck I didn't even break even
I sold half of my input. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. What do you mean you didn't break even? Okay
So, what was your did it cost money to table? Oh, yeah, I did it cost money. It was like um
Oh, you didn't you didn't you didn't uh, you didn't cover the cost of tabling that sucks. Well
It technically everything I sold was more than like like I did like break even
But then when I started adding the numbers how much money I spent on like merchandise
And um, it it it all kind of just tallyed together and I realized wait, I didn't break even
You know, so it wasn't like it wasn't like I didn't cover table cost
It's just I didn't cover like my merch costs like I didn't sell it
Enough. What do you mean?
What do you mean you didn't okay, but you still got the merch left over. Yeah, I still got merch left over
Okay, so
Yeah, I mean, I guess if the goal if the goal in my head was um, I guess the goal in my head was kind of like to sell everything
Um, I didn't reach get it out there at least that goal. Yeah. Yeah. Um, I sure I printed a bunch of uh
I printed like 60 like villain versus chick tracks
Which cost me like yeah, I have one. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I was gonna send you more but um, I ran I ran out at the convention
Send me more. Oh, shit. Yeah. Yeah. Did you just give those out for free? Yes, and it cost me like
Hmm
It cost me like now that I know the thing about it cost me like 45 bucks to print all those out and it was like 60 of them
Because uh, yeah, yeah, because to print out like 20
Was like 15 bucks
Which doesn't seem too bad, but like when you print out more and more it just it's kind of annoying and originally I
Printed out like half of them through my home printer
but um
But like ink cartridges like cost fucking too much
So I invested in those um, those little like inks ink syringes that you like
Just refill the ink
And it worked. Uh, yeah, you know what I'm talking about. Yeah, so those work pretty well
Until like I over like I think I reached the limit of how many times I could inject my like ink into my ink cartridge because it's like
It's like so I've never used those
Yeah, they're they're pretty they're pretty cool. Like, um, they do work
But there's like a limit to how many times you could inject your little cartridge with ink. I heard it's like around like
30 times you could do it
but um
Is that cheaper than buying new cartridges it is cheaper
But like if you don't do it right you could like just fuck up the cartridge and then you have to kind of bite the bullet and buy like
Just just an actual cartridge store. It's so annoying
Um, I wish they brought back those like ink subscriptions that used to have
Well, I think that's and you know what I think there is ink subscriptions, but my printer is like so old they don't do it for
For that like printer anymore
And that's got you. Yep. That's frustrating
But yeah, if you if you tell me the cost of how much it's spent on the merch
Um, the little chick tracks my stickers. I did not
Break even and that was kind of very frustrating
after after the convention because like it felt like
Um, I also did like little like um ink commissions like I would draw like just someone's character in my sketchbook for like
25 bucks and that did pretty well. I got like three of them. There was actually yeah, there was actually this older gentleman who um
Who was going around to every booth that did uh commissions that he would pay for a commission
And um what he specifically wanted he wanted mermaids. He wanted everyone to like draw him a mermaid
Right, but yeah, but the thing is that what he did was that he came up to my booth
And he gave me like a printed picture of a of a like a model in a japanese school
Like a japanese girl school uniform
And she was like tied up like she had um
That those type of like bondage those like rope bondages. You know what i'm talking about
Yeah, you mean like yeah, yeah, I think so. Yeah, like the the medium
Like the japanese kind of beat us and like rope played thing they do
Um, so we showed you a japanese school girl in rope bondage
It and said draw this as a mermaid. Yes. Yes, exactly
And and it wasn't it wasn't hard because like the way the picture was like her like pose was like, okay
It looks like she's being strung up like on a fish net almost, right?
So all I had to do was just like not draw her legs and just put a mermaid tail under her skirt, right?
And um, yeah
Yeah, and the and the guy like I told him like, okay
I'll have it done in under two hours and he just waited for a while and they told me like, you know what?
I'm gonna be here the next day for the convention. Just give me a then and I'm like, all right
So I finished it. Yeah, he came by the next day
And I showed him the picture like here you go and he's like, okay good
And then he like walked away after he got his picture like he already paid me the day before and everything
And then I see him go to the other booths to get like their commissions
but like
But like I I see that after they he gets his art. He's like still talking to them
Right and I'm like, what is he? What is he telling them?
And then I kind of like eavesdropped a little on like my next door, uh, my neighboring booth
And it sounded like he was giving them like criticism almost
Right. Like like did they not draw the mermaid, right? Did they nice?
Nice alpha alpha move alpha alpha move establish establish expertise
Right because like he just like oh draw this girl as a mermaid. Okay, so I literally just drew the girl as a mermaid
I don't know what these people did
Or or maybe he was really complimented them. Maybe I wasn't hearing correctly. Maybe I did a garbage job
And he didn't want to say anything
You know
Yeah, who knows? Yeah, who knows? Yeah, who knows? I mean I could DM those
neighboring booth people because I do have like their contacts now, but
Yeah, who wants to do all that? Who wants to do all that homework?
You know
Life's too short already right and too difficult and painful life's too short to know if you did a good job
Right, exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fuck. It's better. It's better not to know. It's better not to know
He already paid me anyway. I really don't give a fuck
You know how you know how many commissions I have asked that people like
Look at and be like, whoa, this is great. Thanks. And I'm like, oh, you're welcome. You're welcome gamer
some people
some some people are
it's just more
Some people have very specific
Tastes and some people are just happy to see their
To see whatever it is. He yeah, he didn't draw their mermaid tail fishy enough. It's like this looks more like a manateed
Tail
Exactly
Um, another funny thing is that the other
So the other guy who was selling his own independent comic was like to boost down from mine
And I I over here and this guy like during the whole weekend was just like
Um, I I kept rehearing his elevator pitch for his comic
Like over and over again because he was telling everybody and I mean I was doing that too, right with my comic
When like people came by right?
But um, but the first time I hear this guy's like pitch
He was like basically like so in my story all the characters are immortal and then I'm like, oh, that sounds kind of familiar
And then and then he's uh, and then he said like and there's also no heroes in my story and it's and I'm like wait a second
Wait a second
I'm thinking like is he describing villain versus these people. Is this is crook? Uh, you know crook
Crook crook crook crook dimension crook. Uh, yeah the crook cronies the crook company
Is but um
But no, he was just describing his own because then after that he's all like also in this universe. No one like
Uh regenerates back their organs if they're like, um rip the part or something
And it's like, okay
He's describing something completely different because that doesn't happen in my story
And he he had a his comic is called like a mortal era
And it was like about yeah, it was about like some sort of like thing happens where everyone becomes immortal
But it's kind of like the immortality where so it's so it's 17
The best comic ever made right but this looks more like
um
It seems like this guy's goal is to kind of like get some sort of netflix deal or something because this feels like something that would
Oh good. Well good luck, buddy
Okay, this seems like something that would eventually become like a netflix deal or something and apparently
One of his first artists he did the issue with because this guy isn't the artist
He's just the writer and he he pays like several people to draw the comic
and they and they have that kind of like, um
I don't want to call it like the the marvel or dc house style, but like it's a very like
Um, they they wanted to look as realistic as paul you ever like seen those comics that like wanted to look really like super realistic and it's um
And it's almost like
These could be like celebrities playing these characters almost, you know
There's a lot of yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I can imagine
Yeah, there's like a lot of comics in the wild that are like comics that were like intended to be pitches for shows, you know
And this this kind of yeah, this kind of feels like it
um
Hmm the the guy seemed cool
I was I was talking to him but um his comic wasn't something I was super interested in he didn't sound super interested in villain verse
So I guess the feeling was like mutual so
Yeah, that's fair. I guess
um, hmm
uh
If you hmm
I mean, I you know, I mean, I'm never I was thinking about this
I've I've I've never made anything with an eye to like, oh, maybe someone will adapt it. Oh, maybe someone will pick this up
I've I've never even thought about it in my life
uh
Is that like, I don't know. I mean some some some how I I mean I I managed to
I I guess I would call my comics have been
profitable more or less. I mean I not like your comics are anti-netflix if you will
Oh, I mean, I I had like uh dreams of like, oh if I make if I write down an idea for a video game then
Then nintendo or sony I I could go to them and they would make it because like
You know, I'm yeah, I had I had those ideas
Give them a give them a shot. Yeah
Give them a show just make a video game. It's a pretty good idea actually five-year-old
Oh, me me me a me a monosan. It'll it'll cost us 900 million dollars to develop this game. Oh
You you've forgotten the joy of childhood. Look at this. This child is innocent
from the minds of babes
A bad video game is forever a rushed video game is forever bad make it
Do it it watch us on it's like that bangs gavel
It's like that episode of uh, it's like the episode of the simpsons where like mel Gibson hires homer to write his next film
Is that a real episode? Yeah
I yeah, yeah, it's mel Gibson
I forget why because mel Gibson like is like tired of his successful like movie franchise
And he's all like I can't believe he's like really does everyone like this and then he finds homers
The sole person who doesn't like this franchise and he and he hires homer to like
re kind of like
rewrite the whole
The whole kind of like a movie
It's the one episode that ends with like the dog the dog that's looking like sideways like kind of like dog with a shift
Yeah, that was shift the eyes. Yeah, you remember that wait
That's the episode with the with the shift the eyed dog because that was homer's idea. He said like at the end of the movie
I don't remember that. I remember the dog. I don't remember that episode at all
I don't remember that plot even a little bit because they they go to hollywood. I think yeah takes place
All I guess mel Gibson like hires homer
They go to hollywood and homers don't want to says like and the villain at the end of the movie
The real villain is going to be revealed as this dog who's going to look very shifty looking back and forth
And that's how the audience is going to know they're the bad guy
Uh
And then they shoot it down, but then there's a real then at the end of the episode. Yeah, the real shifty eye dog shows up
Yeah, I only remember that gag
I remember the
Gag that I liked from that. I don't know why I like it so much
It's like mel Gibson comes to the simpsons house
It rings the doorbell. He opens it. He says, hey, you're homer simpson
I need you to come to the thing and homer says. Oh, you had me at hello
And mel gibbons says I didn't say
Yeah, because he didn't yeah, and I just like
I don't know. Oh, yeah. Yeah, why that stuck with me. Hey, uh, that's great. That's great
Oh, so anyway, good. That's a good joke
Always simpsons always gets me a chuckle always gets me a laugh a gaffa out of me
um
I wanted to ask ask you ben um
How do you feel about uh, if
Because um what I'm gonna do in my because I got two more conventions lined up because I like doing
Inventions for the these next conventions. I'm gonna make sure I break even and not like
Spend a crazy amount of money
um, yeah
But how would you love do you want to do like
A trade ben where um
If I send you some copies of villain versus you send me copies of vapor
I will sell them at my booth and I'll give you a percentage
Do you think that's something to be interested in?
No
No, no, no, not really not not really. I'm not gonna sell villain versus
You're not gonna sell you don't think you can sell villain versus. You don't think you'll be like, yeah
There's a bunch of kooky little space aliens
uh
I don't even have a con that I'm like planning on going to anytime soon
Is is cons is conning something that you so you're not super interested in conning and going to no, I am
No, I am it's just uh, there aren't
Like the only one that I'm aware of around here is mice and uh, that one is not scheduled yet
Uh, I don't know. I'm out of I'm out of I'm out of vapor's one. I need to reprint vapor's one
I have no copies of it left or have like two copies of it left
um
and um
Yeah, I don't know. I just I think if I'm tabling
I'm gonna sell my own stuff like I I got I got 30 seconds
I got I got seconds to pitch to someone who's wandering by my table, right and they're like
here
What what do you got and I'm gonna tell them like here's my comic
I don't have time. I don't have time to be like, oh and here's this other comic by some other guy
And let me tell you about that, right?
I mean my thing is that if I have like a variety of comics that kind of incentivizes people to like
Stay a bit longer, right? And also
Like I like the idea that like, oh, there's cop. There's being there's copies of Villainverse being sold in other parts of this country
Right. I do have I have a I have a friend who like lives in
I think um in mass chusas also, um another another person who I talked about this and they said they're down
They're gonna send me a couple copies of their they're just gonna send me like three and I'm gonna sell them three and it's like, okay, like, you know
You don't have to like you don't have to like push this on people but it's like
If people ask about it
You know, you know what, you know what, you know what if uh
Look, it's up to you. It's up. It's up to you. Like you don't gotta say yes
Is there something I wouldn't want to worry about I wouldn't want to worry about like a percentage or anything
If we just do just trade we just trade copies, right?
Uh, you know, I mean
I guess if I was gonna table like I gotta fill table space with something right
Uh, yeah, you know, I mean there's um when it may you know what maybe when I reprint when I reprint vapors one
Yeah, yeah, maybe I could maybe I could just also give you like I don't know like
10 copies of each I guess or something and then 10 might you give me 10 might be too much
You give me like five copies of each
Okay, I mean yeah
What what what I do what what I gonna do is just send out like issues once and then in the back
It just tells you how to get an issue too
because um
That that's kind of something I learned from other people
Like who are kind of smaller is that they don't really like
Do the other issues?
um
Yeah, because then it's kind of harder to sell the other like if you do like a bunch of like if you
If you print out like a bunch of issue too
But like no one really has an idea of like issue one. Yeah, right? So I mean sometimes like like I
I do have a bunch of spare issues to Streets and Fours and I'm thinking like
For the next time I'm gonna find a better way to display all those
So you sell issue one and then in issue issue one, there's like ordering information for the other issues right in the back
Yeah, got it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I need to make sense. I yeah, I need to update mine because it says that oh
You get them off gumroad and I'm actually took them off of gumroad recently
Uh, I think well after I after I put uh after I restock
I think I'll put uh vapers one and vapers two just up on my my store page
Like I'll probably maybe I'll sell them for like 20 bucks
Maybe I'll sell them for like 20 bucks on the store page and then like they're 15 if you get them through
A Kickstarter or something
Uh
Or I don't know. I'm not sure
I'm not sure if there would be any
I mean, maybe once in a maybe once in a while. Maybe like once a month. I could see somebody some random person being like, hey
I'll buy one
Okay, I like, you know people buy
the the the the
People buy during a Kickstarter because it's like, oh, this is an event like this is this is a thing
This is this is a one-time thing. It's happening right now. I have to buy this comic right now
Right. I feel like even if I did list them on my store page
I don't think it would vastly increase
Sales or anything, but I probably should do it anyway. Why not?
What's what's the downside? You know, um, if if like sending comics doesn't sound super interesting to you you could like, um
One of my buddies I got a friend of mine. His name is nick
Um, I forget I forget his twitter handle, but I'll look it up right now and tell you guys
But um, he made these little postcards for villain verse and he gives them out at his booth
And it's like like the like check it out looking at them
Little postcards. Yeah, there's little postcards. So it has like the cover
This is a new cover that I read. I drew a new cover for the prologue
And in the back it has the the the chick track comic
So you just give these out to people, you know
Yeah
I don't know. I guess I'm
When you're sitting there when you're sitting there at your little booth or whatever
People at least this was my experience at mice and I feel like it's
What I feel like I've seen it happen at other cons too
Like people are there and they're asking you about your comic, right? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, they want to know
about that
uh, and like that's
Mainly what I want to be talking about is like I want to tell them what I do and what I'm doing here
Because if they're here to talk to me about my stuff
I'm gonna pitch I'm gonna I'm gonna pitch him on my stuff. No, I got you. You know what I mean? I got you
Yeah, that's my buddy, uh, Nick's art corner. Um, he's the guy who made these postcards. He's pretty cool to check out his comic
as well
But uh, it looks he's art looks pretty good, right?
but um
What I was gonna say is that the strategy that like I I saw was kind of like
I was kind of doing like a car salesman strategy
Almost or like you ever been to like a shopping center and they have those little kiosks boost
Booth where it's like a guy like and he has that like
Product that cleans your shoes and when he sees you looking at his booth
He calls you over to come to him. You don't want to talk about this is a very specific thing
Uh, and then he and then he accidentally like drops a bunch of like
A bunch of like diarrhea on your shoes and he's like, oh, let me get that out for you, sir
I have just the thing basically that's kind of what I was doing because at first um
To kind of attract people to my booth was if anyone walked by I told them like here. Here's the chick track. It's free
Right, and I just give I give everyone a chick track and I ran out of chick tracks like the first day
Which was kind of dumb what I should have done was um
If people ask if I had a business card, I should have just given the chick track
Because that's kind of a little more memorable is to get a little comic than like a business card
um, I was
Because I was at uh, I was at uh
anthra new england last weekend and
Yeah, one thing that I thought of was like I should make business cards or I should make something
Uh like that
um
Yeah, it's it's helpful might not be might not might not be black. I think a black business
Might be black like my soul. You see much much like my soul much much like that in a similar
Yeah, um the second day everyone kept asking me for business cards, but I ran out of like the chick track
so what I did was I just kind of like
I um, I just took like one of my I took my lint my luna sticker inventory
And I just wrote my my handle on the back and I wrote villain verse and I just gave it out to anyone who asked for like a business card
um, yeah
but um
But people um what I noticed what I did was that um
I would kind of just use like uh like free stuff to entice people to come to my booth like my friend nick
Also gave me some postcards for his comic and I would give those out. I'd be like hey man
I'd be anyone's walking by like walking by be like hey, man. Uh here this is free
Right and and I'm like this is my buddy's comic. You should check it out
That's like all I say about the postcard and then after I say that I say like and this is my comic and I pull out the villain verse
That's on display and I tell them to like you know flip you can flip through that if you want to check check it out, right?
Uh, you got it. You got a sucker. You got a sucker punch him right exactly
So I I pulled them in and I just gave them the quick I gave them the quick uh like just elevator pitch of how it goes
Um, I point out things in the comic like in the pro level like yeah
This guy right here this guy's like evilest guy in the universe
He's so evil the devil shows up to fight him in the prologue
And
Yeah, yeah, that's the kind of thing you want you want people to be like it
And that's also kind of like how you can tell if they sound interested in it
Because like if you say like oh, yeah, the devil shows up and they're like what?
What?
No way not not not old bls above right exactly, but if they don't that old scratch himself
If they if they don't say anything during that part you they're not interested
If you yeah, so so so depending on their reaction if they sound interested
I keep going and like and I try to sell it more on the book
But if they sound uninterested I just kind of cut the pitch short and just say like
I I go I go to my other things a lot of people kind of just like supporting local artists, right?
So you got to mention like yeah, yeah, you got to mention like that you make the you made the book all by yourself
And that's your local that's your local artist because people just like
They might not like really dig the story, but they might like the idea of just supporting local artists, right?
and um, I think a bunch of people that bought books for me at mice were just like
They were kind of yeah, they were kind of just there to buy everything they were kind of just there to
Support everybody there just whatever anyone's got like yeah, I'll take one. I'll check it out later. Maybe but like I'm here to
I'm here to spread money around and the
local indie scene
Yeah, that's that's that's epic. That's that's epic of them
Um, I also thought of another strategy that was kind of too late to do because I already had my price on my on my shelf
How much everything cost but um my strategy was to
I said I'm selling the book for 17 bucks, but um
Yeah, I mean it's it's a it's a hefty
It's a hefty ish book, right? Right. Yeah. Yeah, it's like 42 pages
But but what I should have done was sold the book for 20 bucks and as I'm going for the elevator pitch
I tell them like, you know what dude? I'm down to sell this to you for 17 bucks like you don't gotta pay the 20
To make it seem like they're getting a deal right do the do the car the car salesman singing dance, right?
Yeah, I mean, why not? It's a it's a nice little uh, I think probably some people
I think probably some there might be a few people who'd be like, uh, well if it's oh, he's giving me a discount. Ah, well
Right, exactly. Yeah
I guess I guess I can't
I can't not I can't not do I think you know, I think I sold
I think if I remember correctly at mini mice I sold my books for less
I think I was selling them for 10
Each, uh, which is less than than I was selling them for in Kickstarter. Right, uh, which is okay
I mean, they were it's still a profit, but like
Yeah, I sold them for I sold them for cheap. I sold them for cheap there
Uh, just just because I wanted people to buy them just so that I wanted to move
Um product and I get and I guess it worked more or less another thing
that like
Should have been kind of obvious
From the get-go like this is the most obvious thing ever
When it comes to like selling at a convention
Is that people are attracted to the things they already like, you know, so
Um, for example, there was a guy next to us
Who who does this kind of like?
um
He does like
He he draw he recreates like images of characters from like video games or anime
But he uses like an ink brush to to do the art, right?
And it's literally just like it literally just looks like he printed out these images
And he just like just clicked on the ink brush filter on like photoshop or something
But he sells like he sells these like huge like look, I'm gonna I'll show you a picture of this guy
But he was like right next to us and I don't even know if I want to call it like uh
I don't even know if I want to call it like an art style
It's more like an art filter that this guy is doing these like pieces with because look at that
That just looks like the that just looks like the official art, but he just recreated in ink brushes, right?
He doesn't like with physical ink. Well, I think he says he does
I I didn't really talk. I didn't really talk to him because I wasn't like
I was on the other side of the table and I wasn't that close like next to him
But it just looks like it looks like official art, but he just
Ink brushed. Yeah, right
If he's doing it with like it doesn't look very difficult to do something like this
Yeah, I
I guess if he's doing it with like physical ink
On like parchment or something. I guess I can appreciate why someone would buy it because it's like, oh, yeah
It's this image, but it's like in a in a in a new meat. It's been transferred to a new medium. It's a physical piece
Whatever if he's just doing this with like with like photo filters or whatever then like
I guess I could under I guess I could still understand someone buying it
But I I'm pretty sure like this is what I think he does like he I think he probably
I think he on prints out the image and he paints over it because that's what it looks like it just looks like he's like
If he's physically print if he's physically like using actual ink and like actually brushing it on to the canvas then I
I respect the
I respect the yet. He's like crafting something
Right and like and I was thinking like this is like so like this is like so basic, you know
This is like so like normie core, you know, it's like the average
Yeah, the average nerd, right? But then I saw I mean, that's how you sell shit, right? And I'd be in
Yeah, and then I saw him like have a picture of devil man and I was like, oh, it looks pretty badass
And I was like dammit. He got me. He got me
Because like he just froze out this like wide net of like just
Everything that people likes and he probably does gang clusters
His his booth was like super popular. I could see it. I could see it selling. Yeah
It's definitely the sort of thing. This is this is the kind of thing that really bores doing it myself
but like it's
Yeah, uh, specifically what he's doing is just like tracing or like copying
existing art
I would like
I would prefer to draw it myself
If I'm going to draw a bunch of popular characters, but like even that
Is like, uh, but I want to draw my thing though
This is time I could spend doing my thing and then I nobody pays. I mean like I was like, uh, I guess because if I were to like
Buy a piece of art like if someone like um if ben saint drew popular character mario
I want I want that ben saint kind of like flavor because that's why I would come to ben saint to draw like mario
Right, I wouldn't want to just draw like here's the brawl render and I just drew over it
right
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, right. Yeah. I mean I I agree. Well, I agree
but uh, you know
That's not like nothing against this guy like nothing against this guy. He he probably
Potentially, I'm pretty sure makes more money than me doing this
I think I think that that's a different
What you're describing is a different kind of thing. These are not like
This is not a commission. This is a this is a
This is a print, but it's got a sort of a different
I don't know. It's got you got the ink brush filter and people people love that a different medium
It looks edgy. It looks cool. You know, you put that on get it
Yeah, I mean nintendo wouldn't be selling like a mario that looks like that
And if you wanted that on your wall, where else are you gonna? Yeah, I want him to do exactly if he did joker
I'd put that on my wall
You got heat. You got heath ledger's joker. Yeah, I got
I want to get Joaquin Phoenix joker on the wall. Joaquin Phoenix joker
Who would win in a fight Joaquin Phoenix joker or Heath Ledger joker?
Yeah, I know I already I knew the answer as I was asking it, but I had to finish the question
um
What I was gonna see yeah
Yeah, what I was gonna say is that like you need like you unironically need something like this at your booth
You want to draw attention?
Because I saw a bunch of other people doing it too where they have like little prints of like
Just like popular characters that like people like right
And you would sell those right or you were just enticed people with those like yeah, here's my
Here's the stuff based on popular franchise, but here's like my original stuff, you know
I saw a tweet this week
It was a screenshot of a tumblr post. It was two posts by the same guy and and i'm gonna try to remember and paraphrase it
it was like
It was something like
I know this guy who
Always gets girls. He's always getting girls to come to come to his house to come over to his house
by say by saying by saying
Oh, can't oh, I'm so glad I have stew at home like mm. Can't wait to go home and eat some of that stew
and then
And the worst part is
And the yeah, and the worst part is I was um when I'm I'm there at his house and I'm eating stew and I'm like damn
It worked on me too
So this this this these ink prints are this guy's stew, you know, everybody everybody loves stew
Why wouldn't you why wouldn't you want to have some stew? He's the stew maker. He's the stew artist
Exactly, right right instead of calling himself shame
Shane sarr
He should call himself stew art
It's like that's like the name of this guy's like uh stuff
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So I think well, I'm glad glad he's working. Yeah, he's fill it. He's filling it. He's filling the demand
I guess yeah, I think for my next convention. I'm gonna try to like I have this like little sketchbook
And I think I'm just gonna just fill it up with like
drawings of characters popular characters people like
I mean, I like a lot of popular characters. So I that was just throwing a couple of throwing like a lot of people I like
In that I drew Gino once I drew Gino once I should make prints of that one time. I drew Gino does it does it look good
Yeah, it was pretty good. Oh, can I see it? Where is it? Where can I see it?
Oh god, uh, if you let's see, uh, if you search twitter, let me try and find it on twitter
It's all so ugly
Gino
Okay, I put yeah, I posted it on twitter somewhere. Okay, you post your Gino, but um
Um
Mecha Godzilla was also at the convention here. Check it out. No shit. Mecha. Yeah, he's right there. There he is. There he is
That's mecha Godzilla. You fucking shut up
Holy, I thought he was holding the chainsaw game
Crap. No, that's a chainsaw man cosplayer. Oh, this is good Ben. Yeah, you should make prints of this
I think yeah, I think this is pretty good
I think the piggies will slop this up if you make pictures of it. They will
They would eat this up. They'll be like Gino
And I want and I want their slop. I want them to slop all over me
There's gonna be a all over me for Gino, baby
There's gonna be a guy in like the the triforce the green triforce shirt with the with the like khaki shorts who comes up to you
And he's like, oh Gino for smash. Am I right, bro? And you're gonna be like, yeah, yeah
I'll be like, uh, yeah, who's your man, bro? And he'll be like
And he'll be like it's in a roar
And and I'll be like
You can't and I'll be like
My my products are not for you sir. I'm gonna have to ask you to leave stay. It's get to leave my establishment
Fuck away from the asshole
Oh, yeah, also, um at the con there was this there was this uh, oh shulk or like shulk. Fuck you
Yeah, yeah, that's a that's a smash guy, right? Yeah, I find the thing with shulk shulk shulk. Sorry
Oh, I'm thinking sorry. There's a manga called shulk
Isn't that so there isn't that what they do to clams like when they open them and they like take out the meat
They shelf them or they shuck them. Yeah, they shulk it right out of there. They shuck them
Wait, shuck them good. They shulk. No. No, it's help. No, they shuck them
No, it's help is the manga
The infamous oyster shucking manga draw some help help is help is the manga help is the manga about the
About the mortal the one mortal guy the big fucking Hercules mortal guy who goes to the demon world
To compete in the demon olympics to choose the new demon president
Uh, and everyone loves him. I remember that because he because he's the human who runs on the i hate humans platform
And all the demons are like hell. Yeah, bro. We hate humans too
We're gonna we're gonna build the wall keep all the humans out from our own keep all those filthy humans out exactly
We're gonna build the ceiling. We're gonna make the humans pay for it
Um, yeah
So, um, also at this convention. There was this a rubin s gentleman dressed up like a frappy from my hero academia
You know the the fraud girl
Yeah, yeah, so he was dressed up like like her and this guy like he came by my booth and we talked
And he gave me this sticker that he made
Of this this guy is like the antagonist of his like comic, but he never told me where to find his comic
So if anyone knows like I love this sticker, by the way
This reminds me of I don't know remember one time, um
I think I talked about it on one one episode
So I wouldn't blame me if you didn't know what i'm talking about but crack gave me a like
scrawled
drawing on like a piece of brown paper bag
That he got from like a
Artist's convention for like mentally challenged people or something like outsider artists with like who were like from like an
They're like institutionalized
Oh, some guy drew his like edgy sona his edgy like shadow the hedgehog guy
Complaining about some dude. He knew who who didn't bail him out of jail one time
Yeah, that that's what this this looks like that sounds like art right that that sounds so fucking cool
I should like it was so cool. I should it is I have it here in my
Well, it's not hanging up. I should hang it up. I don't know why I didn't hang it up
It's on my shelf. I should commission like some x con to draw like a cover for villain verse because it'd be kind of cool
Like oh at x con cover
right
Yeah
Yeah, that's an angle. Yeah, that's a gimmick. I need um
But I think I was I need to like make my booth kind of stand out a little bit more
Um, I all the other booths had like this whole giant like there there was a booth next to us
that had this whole like
these these rates had these like
Metal grates around their like booth with all their like images like it was like um display images for all the prints they sell
Right and like that's like easy and identifiable. Like if you see it across the room
You see your favorite anime character, right?
And I and and the thing is like I don't necessarily draw popular stuff
I always want to push my original stuff, right? But yeah, but if you had like
Let's say you're um, let's say the stuff you made had like a popular character on it
And if you could find a way to kind of display it
Out there that could attract like like people, you know
um
You know what you should have you should like 3d print or otherwise try to find a way to like create that
Golden skull medallion necklace thing. Oh, yeah. Oh, actually
At the 99 cent store, um, there was like a plastic like
Skull like chain that was like a skull with the crossbones like that looked very similar to that
And I was like, oh, I should buy this and like use like gold spray paint
To like make it and then like make a bunch of fake jewels and put it on it, you know
Because that'd be pretty fucking good
A guy who was selling video games
At uh, anthra new england from whom I purchased did I meant
Did I say what I bought a copy of well neither of you guys were on last episode?
So you don't know what uh, yeah, I purchased a copy of bart's nightmare for the super nintendo
Uh for 30 dollars, which is a reasonable price
Uh, I
I looked on amazon to make sure that I wasn't being ripped off
Uh, it was not
Bought a copy of bart's nightmare. He had uh, anyway, he had uh, he had 3d printed uh stuff there. He was selling some 3d printed
Pokemon stuff. He had 3d printed cubone skulls. He had 3d printed porygons shiny and non shiny
He had a couple of different things. I forget there were more there wasn't all pokemon
But yeah, he just had a bunch of junk that he 3d printed it. It's like hell
Hell yeah
For the for the porygon it worked perfectly like it looked digital and like
Yeah, looks like a porygon
That's that's pretty bad for the didn't look bad for the cubone skull either. It was it. I was like damn
Look at all this shit
It looks neat looks kind of neat actually
I'm thinking about um getting one of those big like cardboard like you know how people could just print anything on a cardboard stand
Right
Yeah, like we did with uh, gino at uh
At the rad con for rad con four. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so I was thinking I was trying to think which number it was
I want to like do this into a 3d stand and put it uh to put it on my boof
But looking at this image right now
Yeah, what will we have on the paper? Oh villain verse
Read read villain verse. No, I cut it out
So I can make it a stand that he's like holding villain verse copies so people can just like grab them and check them out
Right, that would work really well actually. Yeah. Yeah, that's that's that's really funny. That's really funny
Um, I might just I might just recreate it. Maybe make it everybody would be talking
Everybody would be talking about did you see the Kanye boof? Did you see that guy with the Kanye standee?
Yeah, I'm thinking I might get like maybe negative attention if I use just Kanye there
But um, uh, isn't isn't this like a meme? I think it'll
Meme value, right? It's still it's still black. It's still black history month. So you can still use them after that
You're not allowed. Yeah. Yeah, you're right. You're right. But um, I'm thinking maybe like, um
Boss of the clown and like it's it is like a little stand where I put my comics
Because um, hopefully by the next convention that I'm doing which is gonna be like in april
um, there is another comic I want to like
Make because I think it might get like
A lot of eyes on me. That's kind of like a meme, you know, like I'm thinking like
um, I need to do my own like
Mr. Boo eyes on me final fantasy 8
If I if I were gonna talk about the Kanye song eyes on me
No, which is final fantasy final fantasy 8. That's yeah
That's the song that plays when they're in space and they have the romantic
See squall they save someone save someone from dying in space
And then they're like, oh now we're in a spaceship. Oh, we were gonna die. We didn't die
And they sing a little song. Okay. Okay, shut up. Okay. There is shut up
Shut up and keep talking. There isn't a Kanye song called all eyes on me. There's a song called all eyes on yay
Which is what he calls himself now, but um, totally. I know I'm trying to make my own mr
My own mr. Boop my own tails gets trolled
Right. Oh god, which is basically. Yeah, basically just like oh get pre-existing characters and they're doing something hilarious guys. Oh
Yeah, yeah, sure. I mean, I guess it's I guess it's a tried and true formula, right
But oh, it's your own scoob and shag my own scoob and shag. Uh, check out. Yeah
Check out my new podcast main character syndrome where we talk about scoob and shag for like
Five minutes, even though that's like the title of the podcast is scoob and shag sucks
Um, is that a real is that a real pod? Yeah. Yeah, I mean character syndrome. Yeah main character syndrome. That's my new my new podcast
Is it on it's on the cheesy manfredo channel
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. All right. So so
Check it out. Um, first episode I got tectonic improv and a king protus
Remember those guys. Yeah. Yeah. This guy's pretty cool. This guy's pretty baller
Those guys are pretty they're pretty quirked up white boys with a little bit of swag both of them. Yeah
But um, what are you saying is yeah, I'm gonna I've told other people about this
But what I want to do is I want to do
a comic book adaptation
Of the opera of paglacci, right?
But I want to replace all the characters with a ronald mcdonald the characters
Because I think I think that would be pretty stubborn
And I don't know the story of paliachi. Oh, well, you know, um, you seen like all the parodies, right?
Where it's like a clown like doing opera, right?
Sure
Yeah, the paglacci story is very simple. It's very short and there's only two acts and it all happens in a span of a day
Um, but basically this this clown this clown
gets cucked
This this actually happens. He gets cucked, of course
And then um, and then the second act becomes like a this meta this meta kind of thing about him getting cucked
And it ends in tragedy. So he gets cucked the whole time
He he finds out he's been getting cucked
Oh
Yeah, he finds out he's been getting cucked and then after he finds out he's been getting cucked
He sings that iconic opera song
That that's all about like the song is basically like, oh, you got it. You got to laugh paglacci
You got to laugh because the show has to go on even though you're sad even though your heart is broken
You got to laugh inside my heart is breaking
My makeup may be flaking, but my smile
Still stays on right on ironically
Of course, unironically. Yes. That is what that song is
and um
And because like the thing is that he's like a he's like a he has a comedy troupe and they go from town to town
And he's considered like the king of the clowns, right?
and um
And he comes into this this town and like everyone's happy and but then he finds out that his like his um,
Bright to be is actually has a secret lover in this town, right?
Right. Yeah, and then he goes to the doctor and he says doctor. I'm depressed and the doctor says
Hey, polyaches in town. Hey, that that scene doesn't I actually don't know where that's from that scene is not famous
Famous scene from the opera like doctor
doctor, I'm depressed, uh
This might cheer you up. There's like webcom. They call the villain verse. Um, it's pretty funny doctor
I am
No, but but but doctor. I fucking hate
The villain verse
Sucks
No, no twist no twist like but doctor that webcomic blows. Oh, sorry. Well, no, no joke doctor
But I rather read slime in punishment. They read villain verse
Oh god, no
But um, yeah, so the second after he finds out he gets cooked and he sings the the iconic song
Um, the second act is like his comedy troupe performing
And it's basically a skit about a guy getting cooked. So that's the meta part
Is that the second half is like a whole skit of like a guy getting cut
But the the guy getting cut cut in the skit is like paglacci playing a person getting cut
And and the the kind of thing that happens is that over the course of the skit
He starts to become serious about it. Like he starts to like really like
Like asking like who who did who did you sleep me slip sleep with who who was what's the name of your lover, right?
and
And at the very end the audience doesn't know if it's serious or not they keep laughing because they think like ha this is funny
Right. They're like ha ha. This is a pretty funny bit. I like how serious they're taking it
It's man. Then he pulls out a gun. What a juxtaposition. This clown is asking these these hard-hitting questions
right exactly and then at the very end like, um
Paglacci is gonna like stab his wife to be
Because she won't tell him the name of her of her lover, right? He's like, oh, you better tell me. I'm gonna like murder you
Right, it's like it's like Othello, but with a clown right exactly
And then like as he's about as he's as he's as he's froze his arm ready to stab her like it's gonna go in
It's gonna plunge. She screams her last words. She screams out the name of her lover as she dies, right?
And and then it's yeah, and then her lover shows up and then Paglacci like stabs him too, right?
And everyone in the eyes are like, oh fuck. This is real and they run out
Right and there's Paglacci like alone in the in the tent and there's I think there's other people there
Like of the comedy trooper just looking at him and then he looked then Paglacci turns to the audience and says
The comedy is over and then the curtains come down and that's the end of the play
Hmm, so imagine that is Ronald McDonald. I think it'd be pretty funny
Yeah, yeah
Would it be I think I feel like you would need to like
Fuss food in eyes the cooking so there's not like a person
It's just so like you stole the the ingredients for my chicken nuggets. He's like my secret crabby patty for
Yeah, maybe instead instead of a play. It's like a commercial like it's in a commercial or something
I might
I might do that the thing is that the reason why I chose the Ronald McDonald cast is because like they each
Each like main core member of the Ronald McDonald can play a role in this
right like um like Ronald is Paglacci and uh
I forget the name of uh of his bride, but it's but she could be like yeah early. Yeah birdie
And and then the guy who the guy who cucks ronald could be the hamburger, right?
Yeah, I think so. Yeah, I think so and and also grimace grimace could play a role too because there's actually another character who's this kind of like
This kind of like I don't know if I don't want to say he's a hunchback or something
But he has like some sort of deformity that doesn't make him attractive
Right. Yeah, and this guy this guy actually wants to sleep with Paglacci's like wife of Paglacci's wife
Is kind of like ew no gross stay away from me. Everybody wants right everybody wants to sleep with Paglacci's way
And um and basically um this guy is kind of like guy who who wants to sleep with Paglacci's wife
It's kind of like he kind of like tries to push Paglacci to the whole like murder angle
Right because like oh if she won't if she won't have something with me. I will manipulate Paglacci to murder you in a way
Right. Oh, yeah. Yeah, and that guy could be played by grimace
Hmm. Yeah
Uh, I think it's a funny idea
I mean would it be
I mean how much
How how how how many pages do you how many pages? I'm gonna think maybe
32 I'm pretty sure I can tell the story and maybe under
Oh, that's under 35 pages. Yeah. Yeah, because the play isn't long like 10 pages a day
Yeah, the play isn't long because um, and if I mean I'm gonna cut out all the songs
Yeah, right. I'm just gonna just play out the general gist
It's gonna be played pretty straight and you know, it's actually perfect about the Paglacci play is that at the start of the play
Uh, one of the characters goes up on stage and explains to the audience that this isn't real
Like it's they say that it's based on real events, but this play isn't like these are just actors by the way
So if you get too invested just letting you know they're actors
Right, so
Yes, so what I was thinking is I would have grimace appear at the start of the story and say this isn't like real
This is just a parody. These are these are just the the mcdonald mcdonald character. This isn't this is not the real ronald mcdonald
Right, exactly. Yeah
Honestly, I I like this idea. I think it's good. Yeah, I think you I think it's very funny, right?
I could see you so I could see you getting I could see this being a hit
No, I yeah, I agree
I had this like in the back of my mind for a while now because I'm really I really like the idea of going to a con
And I have like a little poster for it of like a sad ronald mcdonald and it just says mcplaglacci on it
And people would be like what the fuck is that?
I like it. I like it a lot. You sold me. Thank you. All right, perfect completely sold completely
Perfect. I'm gonna try to have that done before this next con and then I'll sell it there and make a gang busters
Hopefully what's the next con?
What's um, it's called comic fest in san diego
I'm actually on a wait list because um originally I thought I couldn't get in but then um
One of our boof neighbors told us that um, oh you could you could still apply
And they'll just put you on a wait list because apparently people just drop all the time which makes sense because at this con
Um, there was like there was like two empty booths in our little section because they just didn't show up
So i'm like, okay, so i'm just hoping that
People just start dropping off the closer we get to it and then they they'll pull us in
and um
Yeah, and I think I think i'm gonna like email them again to sell them like
Hey letting you know i'm on the wait list, but i'm i am like a local artist who makes comics and just
just to see if like
That gets their attention more than like look you don't need another person selling like anime prints there
You know you can just have someone locally right like me
You know maybe yeah, maybe yeah could could help. Yeah, that's the goal
and I also
And I also have a secret project much like you guys
Have been talking about
Now now it's cheesy's turn for the secret project and this might be announced sooner than anyone thinks but um
I think I I think I cracked the code for the next hit
um
I'm going back to making slice of life comics. I'm making bongo and luna 2.0
But it's not bongo and luna bongo and tuna. Yeah bongo and tuna
Oh, like was it um, I forget my friends have like a parody name for the fake bongo luna
A bingo or tango. I can't forget camera. Okay, but but basically I'm doing it's not bongo luna 2
But it's it's gonna be kind of like a refined bongo luna. It's also gonna be gayer, right?
Um, and and dare I say dare I say this is gonna this is gonna make a merry weather a run for his money
I'm gonna tell you that right now
This is gonna this I call this one the merry weather killer
It's just the title of the thing. Yeah, which which which merry weather like uh
I mean is it because
I mean there's a cuz there's an internet explorer in it
Yeah, I was gonna say is it because it's like
Can you can you say what about it makes it a merry weather? I'll tell you
Okay, so I'm gonna tell you the only merry weather comic. I think I read all the way through
Was um, he did one called of my sucky best girlfriend, right?
Yeah, and so so my comic is gonna be in that vein of like oh my whatever whatever whatever
Right, gotcha. And I
I'll tell you guys afterward like done recording what it is like really quickly, but I'm just letting you know
It's gonna be it's gonna be slice of life. It's gonna be gayer
Then bongo luna. You thought bongo luna was gay. This is this is beyond gay. I'm in this comic, right?
Fascinating. Yeah, exactly. I'm I'm I'm hooked. I'm hooked beyond gay. It's gay isn't good enough anymore in 2020
We have to be beyond gay for everyone for everyone who thought for everyone who was like why doesn't bongo luna date?
This is gonna be the comic for you. I'm gonna tell you that right now. That's gonna be the
Uh, the homosexual clown comic. I see. Oh, I'm not I won't say no
I won't say anything. I won't say anything, but this is gonna this is gonna hopefully come out
Maybe in April. I'm gonna see if I could go back to making like a weekly comic. I'm pretty sure I can now
I've learned like so much more new things
To just pump out like yeah pump out shit faster. But yeah, this is just gonna be
Yeah
I feel I feel like I was just gonna say I also feel like you know
I've been drawing slime in punishment for feels like ages now
But I do I do feel like now I could do
I could draw faster I could make comics faster than I used to if I went
If say, I don't know I made a vapors for or something, right? If I ever did that
Ben you should make your own merry weather killer
My my uh, what kind of girlfriend would it be my my dog is my girlfriend
My mom is my girlfriend. She's also a goth male. My mom is my girlfriend
Now there's now there's a comic my mom is my girlfriend, but I'm also her dad
I saw that hazel video
About that one manga. Do you ever watch hazel? Yeah, I love I love hazel. He's was pretty good. Um
I don't want one about the kid the kid who's in love with his mom
Yeah, because he's like secretly like the reincarnated like husband or something or some shit like that
He's some sort of like genetic memory flashback thing going on. Yeah
I don't know just thought that video was really funny. Yeah after watching that video
I thought like oh man, you know, but I feel less bad about drinking off the incest more now
Somebody else does it trans people do it too. So it's
Progressive, I don't know
People want to fuck their mom that's what Ben's saying
That is what I said
Oh christian did no
Yeah, whoo brought it back circle at 180 degrees. We we brought it full circle
All right, so just letting you know if if if pcp is too problematic for you now
Um, you could always watch main character syndrome or as I like to call it the pc the pcp killer is gonna
This is the name of my new podcast
It's gonna destroy
I'm gonna finish with yeah go on to call to call to call something a pcp killer is to imply
Like the pcp is like you could you could be so it's so frail has so few hit points
It's it's just the slightest the slightest gusts the slightest gusts
I'm gonna
I'm we're like we're like mr. Burnt
We're like mr. Burns with so many diseases that we we are not dying of any of them yet
But even the slightest breeze could uh
It would destroy everything. Yeah, it's um, I'm gonna finish what tricks he started
Please
Finally
um
Okay, uh
Well, I don't want to rush anyone, but I we've been going for two and a half hours and I feel like voicemails are
Coming soon. Yeah, I agree. I'm um, what do you what do you think gib?
Yes
I don't really have too much else to say
Because I have the topic the topic, but I could leave it for next time
No, you could go ahead and say it if you want to say it
This week well, it's just about the I've been playing a video game. I've been playing animal crossing pocket camp, but like
It's not really that interesting wait. Um
I don't know what pocket. It's the it's the mobile the mobile version of animal crossing, which is basically exactly the same
Is it new? It's fun
It's been out for a while. I think you played the old animal crossings, right like before new leaf
Or no before new horizons
I've never played a single animal. Oh, okay. Haha. So so uh pocket pocket dimension. What did you call it?
Animal crossing pocket camp is so pocket camp is identity. You're saying it's very much like
Ah
Well from from from my understanding you gather things you shake trees you fish and you catch bugs
And then you give it to animals and they say wow, thanks
Yeah, and then you become friends with them and then you invite them to your campsite and you can craft furniture that they like and then
They're like you put a microphone down. They sing at it. It's cute. It's been consuming my life
It's this all I have to say about it really
It must be it must have some differences from new horizons, right?
I would yeah, I mean new horizons you have an island and you can like sculpt it. Yeah in in pocket camp you have
like a grid based
campsite and
You can put tents down
Uh two different like amenities and then a bunch of like furniture in this large area
And then you can invite like 10 animals
10 I think animals at a time can just be in there just hanging out and talking
Chatting and like eating the food nice and you get like little quests to get like oh, I need like
A fucking stick insect you got any of those and I do and I give it to them and they say wow
It's great
Whoa, I love it. And there's a little that
There's a little garden to the side where you can like
Make flowers and like cross pollinate them to get special seeds sure
Oh
It's fun
You know what didn't um
Didn't just a couple of like hours ago the new pokemons got announced for the next gen
The next generation of pokemons. Oh, but they just but they just released a new pokeman
They they um, I think well, they said that's that's pokemon legends arcades. So I guess it's like, uh,
This is like the next one. No, this is like the next installment after sort of starting shield
Marin said they just announced pokemon rowdy and pokemon killer. I thought he was lying
Uh, it's kind of that it's scarlet and violet. Yeah, it's a red and purple. I am
Scarlet and violet, huh? Have you seen the news new starters for it? I'm just seeing them right now and uh
Is it is it just me?
But didn't we are like when I first saw those I thought like they were like fan pokemon or something
But then when I find out they're all pokemon look like fan pokemon these days
um
Right, but like to me they they look like pokemons that we that already exist like
Don't we don't these pokemons already exist in the game?
The they okay the the duck looks exactly like ducklet
Right. Yeah, that that one looks like one that already exists for sure. Um, and the cat
I know that ducks sometimes have like the funny afro
And I see it and I like haha that's funny, but like it is just a duck
It's they've done that already
I didn't isn't the cat looks like a lot like the other cat starter. Uh, the one that eventually comes
Yeah, yeah, like it looks it does kind of look like it just looks like green litten and it's like uh
It looks a bit like yeah
And then the uh, the middle guy the fire starter
Um looks like an apple. Yeah, he's like a sliced in half apple. He looks like he looks like the little dinosaurs from bubble bobble
Yeah
They just feel like pokemon. We already got
Whatever they do a little bit. I mean, isn't there like literally a pokemon that is just an apple
Oh, there's appleton appleton and uh
Yeah, there were some gen six or seven. There were some gen seven pokemon that are just apple apple dragons
Yeah, yeah
Um, there's yet another apple looking guy. I I
I guess I'm I don't know if I guess I'm curious like why the fire guy is a is a plant
That's that's unusual, but like sure whatever
Um, yeah, I know the new game takes place in some sort of like spanish inspired like country or something
um
So maybe something to do
I'm gonna do it there. I mean, I don't know. I haven't played a pokemon game since
soul silver
I haven't played a pokemon game since sun and moon. I haven't yeah, I haven't played one since
Haven't played one since sun and moon. Haven't played a good one since black two
Uh, or white two
I might I might
I played I played black and and then I and then I played white two
Uh, yeah
I might I might play uh with platinum
I kind of want to play platinum at some point. Uh, I might do that in the future
Uh, so I probably won't play these unless everyone says like holy shit. They revolutionized it
I was I mean people people say that about arceus
Yeah, they they love that game, but like yeah
See seeing people really like our arceus made me a little bit like
Kind of kind of want to try it because like it's it seems like
People liked it a lot and it did look a little bit different and like yeah, that's kind of what I
It's kind of what I was hoping for in a pokemon game. So I don't know
But I don't know to switch. So like whatever
What am I gonna do nothing? It's it's
Like I know pokemon goes like the pokemon game on mobile and I guess they have a few other like mini game games, but like
I feel like it wouldn't be very difficult to make
An a 3ds style pokemon game for mobile
You know like like like x and y sort of level of 3d
I just would not buy a switch because it's a fucking thing I have to get
But the the reason I get animal crossing pocket camp is because I just download it
I was like, I wonder if there's an animal crossing game that I can play on my phone right now and there is and it was great
Everything should be on phones. I am a fucking mobile gamer
You know, I'll I'll say
I'll
These these pokemon these these starters. They don't really look like pokemon
They have the bit of like look like digimon syndrome to me or they look like they look like uh
I mean whatever
That's that's fine. That's not that bad. They look I like them better than
Uh groovy sobble and uh score bunny for sure
I yeah, I remember we had a very similar problem to those designs. Their silhouettes look too familiar
They look yeah, they really all look like they're like the same base creature. That's just like different color
Yeah, yeah, that I I hated that. Yeah here at least it's like
Um, like one's like a four-layed creature one is like two the other one is two
But it has like longer arms
And the head shape is different. Yeah, there's there's more variety in their silhouettes, which I like
But the but the little kind of I don't know they
I don't know like what I think like what's the point if I can play about pokemon. I don't play the games
Yeah, um people already there's already like 10 million fan art for all these characters
I saw I saw way more. I had to scroll past a silhouette fan art before I found the official images
I'm looking I'm looking at this
Okay, here's here's my problem. Um
Um
The the new trainers uh their hat uh way worse than the hat that the sword and shield trainer
Was there look uh, they look too young
The what is the the the the girl is supposed to be 10 I may
The girl in sword and shield was wearing
The girl in sword and shield was wearing that like flat green, uh, scottish hat the like the clod clod hopper or something
It's called you know what I mean that was way cuter. What is this fucking?
Cowboy hat
Too much like uh like school children
Uh, they are dressed. They are dressed like school the school uniform. I'm gonna I'm gonna post I guess in recent years
It's been a bit ambiguous the age like it's always been
Initially it's like oh when you're 10 you go out and you do your pokemon adventure. You just don't know
playing the game
The protagonist is around that age
You just don't understand spanish culture. Everybody dresses like this
I'm gonna adult like this all the time
Get uh get james, whatever he calls him. So now on the podcast give his take about this spanish culture oriented pokemon game
James
I think james used to go by lemon. Yeah used to go by. Yeah, lemon tart. Oh
Or or tarty art. I think they like to be right, right?
Firmly tarty art. Yeah, I remember now
Um, yeah, he'll he'll tell you this is just what he wears every day. So yeah
Um, but was he gonna say yeah, I'm gonna post this picture of the new trainers on twitter and caption it like
Oh, man. I am not looking forward to the porn for these guys
No, yeah, that sounds like a post you would make
Hey, they're a little too young for me. That's what I'm saying the other one
Yeah, the um, I mean they're all they're all kids I guess
claud hopper girl
claud hopper girl was kind of like
She still makes the rounds. I I see you could sort of you could sort of imagine. She was any age really like she's
You know, she's an anime character. She doesn't look
She's not she's not dressed like a little kid like yeah, these kind of are. Yeah, I see I see what you mean
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so um
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I can't wait till they start dropping the gym leaders to see which one is going to be the the porn gym leader
Which one was the porn gym leader in gen seven or gen eight rather?
um, and um,
The last one was
If I haven't seen if I have not seen any fan art at all of any of like the the characters from arceus
Really, no nobody cares about well, I I seen a lot of fan art of like the what is it the rival girl with the red hair
There's a lot of art of her
There's a lot of art of uh, I haven't never seen it
Really, well, I guess I guess I'm not really like
Yeah, I guess you guys aren't on the nsfw side of the car. Yeah
probably not probably
I have seen like a lot a lot of um
Of that I retweeted every time um
Oh, yeah, so uh, I guess another news um go go to my nsfw account, which is a
creamy pasta tc
I have I have a patreon for that. I'm selling some new luna stickers
um, I think I think
I think you guys
I think you guys would dig it if you guys seen the previous ones where she's like
She has like hard eyes and she's doing the the p symbol and the uh, the hi-ya go face
Um, I'm not sure if I've seen that sticker specifically. Well, well good. Don't don't don't those are old
That's old. Okay. This is the new one. This is the sticker you're gonna want
Damn the gradient
Yeah, exactly smash
Exactly. Yeah graveyard smash is is the name of the of the luna porn comic series. I've been doing
Oh, I saw her
Fucking a werewolf. Yeah, she fucks a werewolf in the first one
Sorry spoilers. I saw spoilers. I saw I saw that I saw that I did
Yeah, she fucks a werewolf in and in the second one she fucks a ghost girl with a penis
For all you all you ghost girl penis lovers out there
That's me. Yeah, exactly. And um
Depending how depending if I want more money, I'll make another installment
Um in the future. I'm thinking about depending on if I want more money
Yeah, exactly. Yeah
True. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So just check it out. Um,
Yeah, I I mostly just do porn commissions nowadays
um
You should uh, you should everyone out there should uh follow me on the creamy pasta tca commissioned me
I am currently
About to be laid on my rent and also, um, I mean, I guess I'll make this a quick story before we go into the
Into the questions, but um, yeah, yeah, I so
Guess who owes like a shitload of debt because uh, one of my roommates just disappeared
They just disappeared in November rents. Yes. He bailed on rent, but then we find out that he actually
Since the start of the lease
He has not been paying rent
And uh, you got to take him to court
Yeah, exactly. And that's that costs money, but he avoids us like he actively just doesn't like want to come in contact with us
Yeah, no shit. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, of course. Yeah
So the the game plan right now is that like, I mean the landlord says like, oh, you got to pay all that off
um before the lease is up
and um
And it looks like each each roommate here is going to have to pay over like 900
Um to cover for it, but um, we we got a couple of
You got a you got a you got to hold him responsible for that by any means necessary
No, I I agree. I think um, well, I mean the plan now is to
Cover just cover that the debt we owe and then sue him afterward none
And just just to fucking make sure and then he and then he'll give us the money we spent and plus more hopefully what
Hold on, uh
How how has it?
I mean, you've been living there. How long you've been living there? Um
Since I think the start of I think the end of june, maybe
How how have how has how has the landlord
Not said anything. That's another
That's another fucked up thing. That's the landlord told us like hella late
The landlord told us like six months in basically
That this has been going on and it's very
It's not good. We don't like I don't I didn't feel like
I don't know that yeah, that does seem fucked up like
I feel like she should
Like how how are you supposed to know?
Like yeah, I I have to like double check our like lease and just see like what's
Distipulations for her not telling us cuz I feel like she should not be able to
Just be like hey by the way
Yeah, one of you didn't pay rent for six months and the rest of you got to pay it now
Like I don't think she should be able to do that. That doesn't seem legal
No, no, I mean I I agree. Um, yeah, and uh, we've been talking about that with the other roommates
um
And it's I I don't know I have not taken the time to look at the lease and like
Yeah, I feel like you should be able to like just refuse
To pay for because that you're not responsible for that there's
Well, it's all there's all of our names on the lease like we all signed it together
So that's that's the thing we all owe it
I just don't uh, I'm confused how he was able to just not pay rent for six months
Like how like how does that just happen? I'm fucking surprised. I mean maybe like because it seemed like
I don't know this this landlord like
Is lenient
But like also like this leniency has like
Like she's let like too much terrible shit like slipped by you know negligent is the word. Yeah. Yeah
You're right negligent right because the thing is that we were like
We were like late on rent for a couple of months
And then she and then after like two months she dms. I was like, yo, what's up?
And um
And then we tell her like oh, we'll get you we'll pay it all back by the end of like january and we did
Um, I did start that one and go fund me
To like pay like the my late rent
But then around that time is when she told us that like oh this guy
This guy who the thing is this guy disappeared like at the end of like no like in the middle of november
This guy just disappears. We don't see him
For all of december. We don't know what's going on. Well me and my partner don't know what's going on
um
and then suddenly like um, she tells us this and it's
It's very garbage very garbage that she like waited this long to tell us this is bullshit
and
And apparently this guy just owes a shitload at that at other places too
Because he apparently can't pay his car
It's just so much
Yeah, it's fucking frustrating
Damn what a what is what a scam though like just move into a new place
Don't pay a rent for six months and then when and then just bail as soon as the landlord's like, hey, uh
What about rent for the last six months? Oh, he's gone already. It's just so genius. It's genius
I was was fucking annoying is that I know for a fact other landlords would like if you're like a couple days late
The dm you like yeah, what's up?
my my landlord uh when I was
I was uh a little I was I was like three weeks late on rent
And she and and she called me and was like you're late on rent and I was like lull. Sorry
And uh, yeah, well, uh tough tough titties bitch, and then you leave
Basically, yeah
Yeah, three three weeks free three weeks for rent. I'm out. Bye. Yeah
Uh, oh my god, exactly
Epic. Yeah, I gotta uh, but there's well you're in you're in california, right? So
I don't know. I know the massachusetts is very uh legal legally
Massachusetts gives renters a lot of protections which is pretty based
In massachusetts in massachusetts it is illegal for a landlord to charge
Did I I might have told this already? I won't go into it that long, but
She was she said like hey your rent is rent is late
You got to pay me two hundred and fifty dollars extra because your rent is late
Which is like so that's so that's a totally unreasonable. That's a huge amount of money. That's way more than is is reasonable
um, and it's also
It's just illegal for her to charge me anything late at all
Uh, because in massachusetts, it's specifically not allowed to like find a renter for a late payment
Unless they are more than a month late, and I was not more than a month late. So it was a complete like
Not not only was the number would not hold up in court, but just she's it would it's just can't do that
You just can't do that. Um, and I know that now. Um, so, uh, you know, I don't know
Renting shit renters laws
It's good to know if you're renting. It's good to know and look into and learn all the laws and shit because uh,
There might be some shit in there that your landlord you can you can kill him
You'd be like well, mr. Landlord sir, you violated
You violated code 17 146 and now I am the owner of the elder wand actually
And your spells will not affect me sir
I gotta yeah, this landlord has been kind of doing us some screwy shit
I mean she's led like a lot of shit slide, but then she's also like yeah
Like I remember she my deposit from the previous place
She tried to like give me less and I'm like no no I my deposit was this and I had like
I had like the receipt like on venmo for it and I
Screenshot and I shut it to her and she stopped arguing with me and she just like
Sent me the actual amount
I saw you my my um, I had a
Roommate here for a few months. He moved out and then just actually just by coincidence this last weekend
I ran into him. I ran into him on the the tea
And I'm like, oh, hey, man. What's going on? What's up? And he talked about stuff
We talked about this place and he said
He had told me previously that someone else that lived here told him
Don't even don't even worry about like forget about your your deposit
Like you're never getting it back the landlord won't give it back and this guy
He said well, you know, I moved out
Uh, she said he said the landlord gave him half of his deposit back
Because he agreed to like like give the keys
In a timely fashion
So he should have got the whole thing
But like he because of like some key shit he uh, she he was able to uh
She oh, she gave him half she gave him a half of what he of what he she owed him. So that's great
Is that legal to just give him half of the deposit back yet? Like no, of course not
Of course, I mean she could claim she could claim that there was some reason why she could claim that there was some damage to the room or something
Which like obviously there wasn't
um, so I'm
My goal
My goal is to I'm gonna try and be
As late on my rent as possible
for for the next
I'm gonna try and be as late on my rent as possible for until the end of my lease and then
I'm gonna not pay my last month's rent
This is my plan and then I'm gonna until you know, maybe maybe three months later. I'll pay it
Or maybe three weeks like three weeks later
um, and uh, I just I'll just I'll just like not pay the last one
And then my my and then if she asks me like hey, where's last month's rent?
I'll tell you like well, you have my security deposit, you know taking that
That's pretty good
I think it might work. I think there's a chance it might work
um
So, yeah, that's my that's my plan to try and not let her screw me
On my deposit because I know because I know she wants to I know this lady's fucking evil
Jesus Christ
Yeah, so I gotta I like your situation sounds pretty fucked up though. Yeah, I gotta I gotta look up
I need to look up like what are the
Our landlords really supposed to tell us if someone else is late on the rent
That something is not something is not kosher about that situation right exactly because like if that's the case
Like oh, yeah that landlord has to tell you right away when someone's like late on the rent
Then it's kind of like okay. Well, she hasn't told us in like six months
Right, so yeah, it doesn't it doesn't seem so if we can like if we can like use that against her
Also, this place was like a kind of a shithole before we moved in and luckily one of our roommates
Recorded everything that was like bad like everything that was bad in the place before they all moved in
So we all have that
um
It's just it's just annoying
And I think I've been too much on the sideline in this whole situation
I've mostly been letting my partner and other roommates kind of handle this
And maybe uh, maybe it's time to man up. I mean it's time to grow a pair and take my t-shots
Wow
Cheesy Manfredo, uh
What's the word?
Ark redemption ark redemption ark
Cheesy Manfredo doesn't gotta pay their late roommate ass fees ark
Oh god, uh
All right, we we we're at three hours. It's time to it's time to blast through these stupid voicemails
All right, let's go as fast as we possibly can. Yeah
uh
Apologies to the audience for this uh segment that I
Choose to do that. I could stop at any time, but I won't
um
First before a smell
Is an image
Let's check it out
What do we got?
Um, oh, it's comparison of things
Oh, it's uh, it's one piece versus uh
Uh rank and bass rank and bass, uh, yeah
Like stop motion
Yeah
Yeah, I guess cool cool
Good good good good stuff. Thanks. Oh, they had a they had a whale and there was a whale in one piece. Oh, what?
pro
They disney totally ripped off the ideal for their whale movie off of hiyao Miyazaki's
A famous whale manga from the 80s
Uh
Next yeah next voicemail is called
And another thing there it is
Three two one go
Also, anybody knows of any connections between the ranking best movies and one piece that I didn't call
I didn't watch all of those movies and then you read the all four please. I don't know. Whatever
If anybody knows more, I'm really interested in this. So let's go comment
Um, or tell me I would appreciate
Actually the usap one. I don't get it all like Pinocchio. Maybe
Uh, oh, yeah
Sure, uh next voicemail is uh
I think I think that I think those last two connections are kind of they're kind of a stretch like oh monster
Oh, these are monsters just like in a thriller bark. I'm like, yeah, but that's like
You might as well just put universal monsters. Yeah than the rank and bass. Yeah, because it's kind of like
Yeah, it's kind of like whatever. No, that's stupid. Oh wait. Wait a fire guy and a nice guy like oh, that's just like
The misers that's just like uh brothers. That's just that's just like world industries. Uh flame boy and wet willy
You know who i'm talking about. Yeah. Yeah, I know who you're talking about the guys are on the shirts flame boy wet
I got I got a I got a post a reference image for uh
For anyone who doesn't know what i'm talking about. Yeah, i'm a big i'm a big flame boy and wet willy fan
Uh, yeah, here we go flame flame boy and wet willy world industries. Uh, every everybody loves them
You put this on the charm, man
These should have been these should be starter pokemon
um, true
Uh, all right next one is called
The sorry a message for ben three two one go
Hey, ben say make more let's reads
Uh, I guess I could
That one that I made didn't do that well. I guess it was fine
Uh, I maybe make it patron exclusive
Uh, I need a bit. I need it. I'm I'm disappointed with like the video quality in that
I didn't like how I looked and I think the bat my bad camera and my kind of mediocre microphone didn't really help
um
It's yeah, I could do more of those I should get a
She should get a better camera
That one sucks that one sucks really bad. That's I'm kind of disappointed in how that one looks
Uh, next one is called a message for gib. Gib is is gib uh
Here i'm here. I'm just munching on some marmite toast
you
what
Marmite is that marmite is that australian stuff right no no that's vegemite
Marmite is the english one
But it's okay, but it's similar though
I can't confirm, but I've heard it similar. It's like it's like a it's like a brown or deny
It's like a brown like kind of tangy like fermented paste
mm-hmm
Uh, well, I tried vegemite and I didn't love it. Uh, I don't know. I guess I've never had marmite
But I'm gonna make fun of you for being british
Anyway, okay
Um, okay message for gib three two one go
I request more pictures of gib's face
Because my one big takeaway from the rad con 2 documentary is that gib smile is so freaking
Precious, and I really want to see more of it. I really really do please give me more gib face, please
Uh gib uh
unfortunately
I can't smile on command
If I try to smile for a picture, I'm like
Yeah, and it looks like a disgusting thing like I
You got to do it candid you got to have like you got to have a
A secret journalist paparazzi
Candid photo is the only way you'll get that
Because just pay her like everyone else does
Yeah, come on
Go to my only fans and I'll smile for real
Right exactly like if it's so precious then that means it should be worth your precious dollars that you have in your pockets right now
Yeah, don't don't beg put the put your money where your mouth is put your money where her mouth is
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I want to see these pearly whites. You got to have a cough off the cash
You gotta see these pearly whites. You got a you got a
Pearl necklace. No, that's not fun
That's disgusting. That's disgusting
You got to polish off that that credit card and start pumping in the cash. You got to start churning, don't we?
You got to start churning. You know, I'm gonna put okay
I'll put I'll put a thousand down on a gib smile
But it's okay because this is all working towards my $250 sign-up bonus. I'm a new uh
us bank uh
Business cash card, so uh, I can't afford not to do it
You gotta collect all those fairy bits and present at the gib
You have pump out them smiles. Yeah
Yeah, I'll smile if you play pumpkin alley. Yeah, complete it
And you and so will you because it's a fun video game
Okay, next one is another image, uh
Doing my part by telling the truth
Oh
PCP or two pcps ago
What what did you think of this video heartwarming enjoyable life changing calming useful inspiring informative and other five stars
Ben uh ben saint talking about his never changing fear of getting his head smashed by a train truly is light life chaining
I think they meant to say life changing
Thank you
He's life chained
Is is this youtube like asking people is it bringing back the five star rating to get like an accurate
Is this good?
Yeah, I think so. I've been seeing people say that youtube has been asking them has been
Making them answer questions lately
That's so weird. Yeah, I don't know. I suppose I suppose the whole like publicly
viewable
Rating system does encourage people to like performatively make the number go big or small
Depending on like the community
Does youtube rather than their actual
Interests like does youtube want the number to go big? Do they care?
If like people rate videos well
I I don't know probably just so like did you like it?
Hmm, would you recommend youtube would you recommend youtube to friends and family?
No, but the thing is like people will always joke
Like this and then like people who are typing in heartwarming video will get the pcp
Inspiring
Epic uh, all right next one is called
No, no, thank you with zeros. Uh, three two one go
Hello, I'm no. Thank you. Wow. You may know me as that one guy from the 100 geck's remix album
Yes, I do I alleged I think I have
Multiple songs on spotify with over a million plays or something
My point is I have clout. Let me on the podcast, please
Please I was
I have history with the show. I know the name racist forest gump remember that
It was the bail jpeh song. I was the halloween special song
I have clout and I have a history with the show. I'm the perfect guest and
We can reminisce on old times like that remember when you guys were like
Hey, jesse your video is a yellow and jesse was like, no, they're not yellow
But they were totally yellow, but they were totally yellow. So like, you know
I don't know how to get on the podcast, but this is I want can I
Yeah
Yeah, I remember hearing about like maybe like no, thank you was like a commenter that I'd seen before and then
Like not too long ago. I'd learned they were only evolved with 100 geck's which is pretty cool
That's kind of wild. I I recognize the screen name
I didn't know they uh, I didn't know they were racist far
Okay, yeah, maybe yeah
Not that jesse ain't here. You can't defend himself when we totally say that video was yellow
You fucking idiot. Check your eyes. I mean we said it then too. We said it was fucking yellow because it was fucking yellow
Obviously any idiot could see that it was yellow
um
Yeah, yeah
I'll
I said it that and I'll say it again
Uh, that's neat. Uh, yeah, okay. Maybe we can get no. Thank you in the in the fucking
guest discord. I guess
Probably, uh, I'm on the spot. Uh
Why what you're on the spot about?
I mean, I don't know. I don't I guess I don't know too much about them
But like uh, why not?
Yeah, sure. Okay
Now now I hope now we're gonna have a flood now
It's gonna be thousands and thousands of thousands of people who are involved with 100 geck's saying oh, I have a plot too
Yeah, yeah, all right
Okay, next whatever next next voicemail is called, uh
No, here it is long huang long huang dong
three two one go
Long chun is obviously just a bad riff on samurai sama. Yes, except where samurai sama. It's an actual character
Long chun is just a bad stereotype
Yeah, and being half chinese have bitten me. This partially offends me
Like that's not even a chinese accent. All your chinese half is offended
I say throw the fucker in voice jail. I would oh and also throw the on an iranic crypto bro there too
Yeah, bye
I think there is a voicemail. Well, uh, um
What was wang wang chang? What's his name?
Something he's got a voicemail coming up and last week he said big big things next week
So let's let's see what is let's see what his final his final plea
For his life and his freedom is before we before we put him in the slammer. All right
He's he's on trial this week. Yeah, so he better impress us
Next
Oh, yeah, uh next one is uh a youtube video
Yeah, and it is a link to okay. I watched this
Okay, i'm actually glad this person sent this video in this is a guy
CJ makes videos he made or he is making a uh
Like a retrospective series
About uh the pcp
Ha and this is his
first
Video about it. I think I think has he made any more since then?
No, he made this video three weeks ago
um
Okay, and
It's really funny. This is the story of this is the first bit it talks about like basically the the formation of the horse cast
but
Hilariously and and I appreciate it. It's does not start with digi. It starts with tbap. It's it's like, uh,
This guy basically, uh, he he diagnoses it as like tbap is the like, uh,
The central point around which the horse cast
uh
formed
And uh, I think it's I don't know. I just thought that was interesting
I'm not sure if I wonder what their argument is about that because it well, I
Yeah
It was definitely like it very initially
A jesse digi thing
And then I was in there
I guess maybe maybe if you want to say like, okay, but that wasn't it wasn't really like the pcp until
Kagan phantom. I don't know. Yeah, you two definitely had like a
A good mix with the rest of us to make her like a group dynamic that was fun
Yeah, I remember some of the earlier horse cast was extremely awkward
Where it was just me and the other two
This guy it's funny. This guy doesn't even like mention digi brony
Like he mentions digi brony as sort of a like, oh, yeah, and then one time, uh, tbap mentioned this other guy digi brony
And that kind of started a whole thing
Uh, I feel like if I were, uh, to
He does not mention to me to me the moments that kick started like hey
Maybe we should all be friends and make a podcast was, uh, when he doesn't mention when you made the the weekly roundup videos and you included, uh
You know, you would have include our videos in your in
Right. Yeah. Yeah, whatever
He doesn't mention those
Yeah, anyway, uh, this was a pretty good analysis assemblage. I came up with a yes
analysis assemblage, uh
Anyway, I like this video and I recommend people to watch it and I hope
It's good. And I hope uh, I hope he makes I hope he keeps going with it. Uh, I like it
um
Next voicemail is called. Uh, sorry. Where did or did they put it?
Um
No, I gotta go to
Oh, it's from son of marowak
posting it in the chat right
there
Okay, three two one go
So I've recently been reacquainted with twilight sparkles secret ship Vic folder and I've really been itching to make
Horseshoe crew style cards. I have ideas for goals ship cards and pony cards inspired off of the horseshoe crew
and
probably just general pcp lore talking about the horseshoe crew a lot today
I would make a digi bro card a princess
Unicorn well, it should be digi brony
and
I would have funny effects like
Uh, the meme that tom will never die
He could be a card that you can like take from the discard pile and put back on put back into the game whenever you want
Uh, I would uh, there would be goal cards like
For instance, it could be called rad con
And the goal of that
A card would get all the crew together ship
Uh, at least six like the lens of exodia horseshoe crew keywords so to speak and you get that goal
Uh, if you guys don't know the game like the ins and outs
I think it's a really fun game
If I know you've heard about it because you've talked about it
but
I'm really itching to make a expansion deck and if you guys
Would like to lend me your
Your voice and your opinions. Let me know
Yeah, I uh
I've never played the game. I'm I'm vaguely familiar with it. I'm I've seen it played
I understand sort of how it works. I've never played it. I don't really know
I I always assumed it was like
A pony version of cars against humanity. I'd never really looked into it at all. No, it's it's not like that exactly
I know you have to
You sort of build
Like a sort of like grid
You sort you sort of build like out in like chains
You chain like chain cards together through like shipping them together or something and you you're building towards some sort of like
goal
With it and I don't know that's probably uh wrong
But it's it's something like that
Uh, yeah, I don't really know how it's played. I know chris chan makes uh or was used to make uh, uh
Like she made uh, she made the slime city, uh new new los angeles city uh expansion deck
Which would be a funny thing to play with
um
Yeah, you could i'm sure you could make uh, you could make uh stuff out of lots of pcp memes
Uh, uh, yeah, you could definitely do it. Uh, I don't know if I have any like specific ideas off the top of my head
Uh
milking uh former members
for
For this new this new content. It's just all
uh, uh
If you make it about make it about the horseshoe crew and then we don't have to worry about the fact that nobody in the pcp is still here
Uh
Because the p the horseshoe crew is preserved in amber in the past
Along with everything else
Uh, next voicemail is called mario movie three two one go
I had this dream where I saw the mario movie
And instead it was a loop on the third movie or loop on the gang
brain, uh
Fucking made a movie set for chris batten all those other losers in the movie
And it was like that one episode where they took the old nazi and make them think he's in a world war two
In world war two in a movie set
But it's like kind of like that
Fucked up
So like the the real
Like a roger rabbit situation where everyone's loop on the third
But there's a live action chris pratt and they're they're trying to film him being mario
It's it's okay. No, it's a cartoon loop on the third they're cartoons
And live action chris pratt
Shows up and he's like hey guys, uh, so who's which one of you?
Am I going to be the voice of and they're all like no leave us alone live action chris pratt
Stop here get out of here. We don't want your damn voice
We want the original we want the original japanese voice actors
Dubbed not subbed not dubbed die chris pratt and then uh and then jeegan shoots him
Jeegan's the guy with the gun, right?
Uh
Yes, I believe so the beard. I forget what jeegan is the guy with the gun. I forget what the samurai
Guy's name is samurai on going. Yeah going. Is it going on?
Yeah, it's going on. Yeah, pretty sure
Uh and and fucco obviously dude. What what do you get?
What do you get when a rodent falls into the mcdonald's french fry?
Uh french fry
Oil, what do you get?
When what falls into it when I when a rodent falls into the mcdonald's french fry oil third degree burns
No, you get chris pratt
Okay, you know what?
Yeah, it's actually yeah, okay
next voicemail is uh
Okay, it's a suspicious link. I don't know I guess I'll click it
Fuck it. Don't moe. Where does it go? Where does it lead? Okay? It's a never mind. It's a flak file
Um, that is that an audiophile? It is an audiophile a very high fidelity
It stands for a fucking lit lit
Audio cassette. That's what it stands for. Well, I mean, I don't want to open. I mean, I already have audacity open to record in
so
Yeah, it's not gonna work. Yeah, I'm just I'm just not gonna not gonna listen to it wait unless
Marin maron pan said he left a voicemail
Oh, that's true
Could this be could this be what could this be marin's voicemail?
I'm just gonna assume. I'm just gonna assume it is. Let's okay. Scroll up
And let's let's listen to uh that okay three two one go
The procrastinators my craft server's doing really well though
It's been some months since the last trench. We probably couldn't tell we've got awesome builds in the pc pokemon league
There's that picture from magements a munchie and even
Tom and Gibbs are underway
Jesse's have a plan come see your people's buildings from luck
How come to japan just five bucks for all this and more by all those creators at patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Also last week then misrepresented my intentions with a philite scent regarding rowdy killer relations
I was making sure the full picture was being understood
Anyway come see our minecraft server cuz it's fucking good
Okay
So so we have we have no that was great. That was great. I can't believe he wrote a whole song for it
All right, first of all, yeah, it's been a really long time. So we look at the minecraft server
We should look at the minecraft server. We should definitely do that. Yeah, we should definitely do that
Definitely do that
um
So, yeah
I'll join the patreon to uh become a patreon
supporter to join the minecraft server, obviously
Uh, second of all, I did not misrepresent your intentions
Meron Meron Meron sent me a dm about this before and I said, uh
He said he said that I was I was narcing. He was like, hey, I didn't I wasn't narcing and I was like
I didn't think you were narcing. I understand that you just wanted to inform me. That's what I said
I said you want you you messaged me. I don't know. I just I don't think I misrepresented whatever
Let's check out the might we'll be
Check out the minecraft server soon
Uh, okay. Good song though. I can't believe you wrote that whole stupid thing for the stupid
voicemail
Yeah, okay, uh, I'll be right back. Yeah, okay continue with the voice. Okay. Okay. We're we're moving right along here
Uh, the next the next voicemail is a Japanese
It's it's title is in Japanese and google translate tells me that this means defecation
Uh in japanese, so uh, that's pretty cool
Um, anyway, uh three two one go
The pro krastinators podcast why this name who came up with it and what is a krastinator? Come on
That's that's like the top of the iceberg
Come on come on
bro
Come on. All right next uh next who came up with it. Uh, I don't even know I don't remember was it nate
I think mage may have come up with it, but I'm not sure. Yeah
Yeah, somebody said it and everyone was like ha ha that's really funny because we don't work
Sometimes it wasn't it wasn't me for sure
I don't actually don't remember who I think actually it must have been because
It must have been mage must have been who mage
I think so. Why do you say that?
Because it was sort of a disparaging remark and I remember her being involved in the naming of the group somehow
Obviously the podcast is just named after the group and that came first. It's like what should we call ourselves?
We're not the horseshoe crew anymore
Actually it was a disparaging remark, you know
It was like ha ha like we're pro crest and aiding all the time
But I actually can't remember if it was major or not. I know mage had the discord server or something
The the skype group mage started the skype group
She yes, okay. Well, I don't know
And then she and then she also I mean then she also started the discord server when we decided to migrate to discord
um
Yeah, okay, uh, something like that
Um, I don't remember next one is a question. Ben. Have you played delta ruin chapter two yet? Uh, shamefully no
You shamefully I I was gonna I was gonna do it on stream and then I just never did it do it off stream
Yeah
Maybe that's what a gamer would say
I just don't want to do it. I don't want to do anything until slime and punishment is done
I can't justify anything. Well, that's fair. So maybe after that maybe
Uh
Next one is will jeff ever get cancelled for being on this podcast. Uh, I'm gonna say probably not
Who cares? No. Yeah
uh
Next one is uh
Message for crack on the episode 300
opening
Here posting a message for crack on the 300 episode opening three two one go
Hey crack. Um, first I want to say, uh, fuck you and second of all I want to say no
I genuinely want that to be opening for every episode. So, uh, yeah, you're wrong
And uh, fuck you again. Okay. Uh, well, yeah. Oh, I see crack assumed something
He I I did watch the last episode. Yeah, this this guy said make the opening for the 300 the opening for every episode
Crack said I think what this guy actually means is just that he likes
The episode that opening
But not that he would not that it would actually make a good
Opening for every episode, which I also don't think it would make a good opening for every episode
But apparently this guy's serious. Okay, that's fine
You know
That's that's okay
Anyway, next voicemail
Is called
Here it is wang chan is sorry
wang chan is sorry
Uh, here it is. Here's his final statement before we throw him in the slammer
three two one go
Wang chan is running behind kajua
Wang chan very sorry
In the meantime, how are you?
Okay, well next time
So so it's not even your big thing
Uh voice jail
Took too long voice. Yeah. No, I
He's got something. He's cooking up something. It's bad. Yeah, you're you should he's just a
He's got nothing to it. He's gotten I don't I don't believe he's got anything coming
It's probably gonna be bad. Yeah
It's probably gonna it's not gonna be good
It's not gonna be good, but I'm more I guess I'm curious. I don't know like maybe it's something
Well, if it if it appears you can still play it. I guess okay. It's definitely in jail right now
You know what? All right. I'll agree to that. I'll agree to that
We can get him out on uh on um parole for uh for a for a new hearing. Oh, this is this is like a
It's changed up from it's changed everything. He was going he was going somewhere with it the whole time
It was an ironic commentary on um
Anyway, next voicemail
It's uh next voicemail is a youtube link. Uh, let me post it here for you
All right
Yes, it's a link to the new uh the new void gazers podcast
That oh, oh, I I love this thumbnail. What's going on? I love this
This thumbnail is like fucking
The new adventures of batman thumbnail. Yeah
Uh, it's uh, you know, whatever
So I saw
I saw someone asking in a in a comment. No, there's one there's one comment on this video. That's really funny
It's a guy says uh great episode
Too bad no one's gonna see it because of this channel's limited reach
Uh
Boy, this is actually riley. I thought it was like a joke. No like channel
No, this is actually riley. What's happening? I thought riley left. I'm not up to speed with
Oh, okay. No riley, um
I mean who we can only speculate as to why but uh riley quit yig
And he cancelled void gazers
but he
But I guess he I think he just didn't want to edit it anymore
I think it probably was like
It's just not worth it and like I guess I who can blame him
Uh, so they're not doing so he cancelled void gazers, but then they started the new void gazers podcast
Which is like, I don't know, you know
Because they're not going to be traveling anymore, right? They're not going to like be doing road trips and seeing each other because that's expensive
Uh, so instead of doing that riley, trixie, mint and birds. It's just the same people
Yes, it's just the same it's just the same people
But only but it's only instead of seeing each other in person. They're just uh, I don't know
talking about how
much how revolutionary the donda stem player is
uh, yeah
so, uh
What else what else do I have to say about this? Um, did you watch this whole podcast episode?
No, some people in the discord in my discord
We were talking about it and I know riley is like really into the donda stem player for some reason
Uh, uh, he's trying to he's trying to get sucked up. He's sucking up to cotton. Yeah, he's trying to he's trying to get
He's trying to get that in with the a
right
What else what else is there to say about this? Um, I feel like there was maybe
um
I don't know nothing everything everything
Everything everything trixie tried to do with her channel was eventually
Fail a failure and just had to be had to be shunted off to some side channel never to be seen again
Void gaze is just no different. LeMau
Damn
She should go back to her anime podcast. She should go back to her anime podcast. Um
Anime videos are also not doing well. They're barely they're not even the new one got like 3000 views
LeMau
She should copy hazel again
Uh, I think she tried I think the new one is another attempt to be do copy hazel
But it didn't work
Yeah
Oh god, the next one is also called, uh
Void gazers lives on
All right
Three two void gazers three two one go
It's not dead. It's not dead
whoo
Hell void it should be they should have renamed the podcast the void gazers right on
Then it'd be ironic because they don't travel no more. Yeah
Uh, the void gazers, uh live live from detroit
It's
Okay, next force mail is called, uh, vacation time, baby three two one go
Hello comrades
Nikolai would like to apologize for waiting Ukraine
Nikolai would stop Nikolai on vacation right now drinking vodka. Yeah, not I know you I know you would never
I know you would never do such a thing. Nikola. Oh, is it is it is it unfair?
Is it unfair for us to uh, it's for us to, uh, hate Wong Chung, but uh, we're cool with Nikolai's, uh
shitty russian impression. Are we being are we every double standard?
I think it's mostly because russian isn't like a race. It's fine because in my head, um
In my head, I imagine that he's white passing. So it's okay
I think russians are white
They named a whole drink after it. Aren't they asian?
They're the same continent as asia, right
But they're you're right. Because they're such a white asian. What?
um, um
Yeah, we didn't even oh, yeah, we didn't even talk about uh
Uh, Ukraine this week. I don't think we have to I don't yeah, I don't really have any uh,
Trenching insights about it war war is bad
War war never changes
yeah
it's uh
Yeah, I
A lot of better people better equipped to talk about the situation I'm talking about yeah, and a lot of and a lot of
Worse equipped people too
Oh, yeah, especially I guess they see that one guy. Did you see that one guy who was encouraging?
Uh, uh, ukrainian civilians to throw paint balloons at russian tanks
Yeah, that was
No, I didn't see I mean that's it
What would have that done? Well, he was saying that like you can disable their cameras by hitting them with a paint balloon
Oh, see see oh, yeah
So yeah, yeah, so just just just go close to it go close to the invading army with their tanks and their infantry
And uh, real home throw paintball a long time. Shit
Real home. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we must uh, we must adopt the strategies of makaulik hulkin and home alone to repel
Yeah, you get a bunch of fucking grease on the road like oh
It drops where it was a couple of marbles on the ground and put in walks by and trips on them
Like oh, he flings up in the air before he lands on the ground
Uh, if only if only an frank had just hung a paint can from a string on the staircase leading up to the attic
Uh, that would have repelled the the invader
Uh, the nazis coming in right right and and I think ukraine can learn a thing or two as well
um
Yeah, so uh
ukraine
War is bad
Maybe maybe I'll explain it to the to the people in a way. They'll understand you see
Putin is emperor palpatine
And uh, russia is the empire
He he kind of is he kind of is like an insane
He is this crazy old fuck right now to get the fuck out. I mean, I guess he always was
um
You see ukraine are the rebels they're much like harry potter. You see and
Oh god, you uh ukraine is like
Uh, oh wait, you victor crates from in the in the in the uh, try no in the uh in the quidditch
I was gonna say the quidditch the quidditch world cup was the was what I was looking for
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah
Ukraine is a kim kardashian while russia's kanya. Have you seen the
the
Have you seen the the president of ukraine is just hanging out on the streets in Kiev while it's I've seen people
Like he's he's like vlogging from there like yeah, fuck really. I ain't going anywhere. Wow. Yeah
Like a big hard ass. It's just like it's just like out in broad daylight
Then there's like that's awesome to be like expected to happen. He's like we will not stand down to you bullies you motherfuckers
We're cool. That's like coming. You know, that's pretty cool. He's probably he's gonna die if you know, I hadn't seen that
I have seen people uh being pretty uh positive on zolensky. I have seen people talking about how he's a comedian turn president
Oh, yeah, yeah, I've heard that. It's pretty funny. So he's got he's got a he's got a I guess a neck for dramatic
That's very funny. What he's doing is is yeah, wait a second and it's really good for morale apparently because like
A lot of the russians who are being sent in are like teenagers who are forced to go and they were like tricked into
Like going yeah, I've seen
And they didn't even realize they were supposed to be killing people and they surrendered
It doesn't really yeah from what I've been seeing like a lot of russians don't like the war either
It's it's just like a which is good. Um, wait a second is it's it's really just a putin
That's what I'm sick. Yeah, like insanity thing and it's really
That he's has that power still
did wait a second in zolensky the
Wait, the ukrainian president the ukrainian president cranium wasn't he
Wasn't he the president who was who before became president?
He was in a comedic series about a comedian who becomes president and then when the series was over
He actually ran for president and won. Is that true?
I'm trying to look it up. I remember that I heard that like a year back or so. I'm like uh, phil the franco
I mean that would be that would be really funny. Okay. Yeah, so let's keep in 2015
Zolensky played the star of the television series servant of the people where he played the role of president of ukraine
You
The ukrainian president used to be a comedian and he's fucking he's like a mean
He's unironically more of a mean president than donald trump and he's like out there on the streets
Like with the fucking troops and everything. Holy shit
Amazing
He's what a basement. Yeah base. Um, he might he might suck. He might suck in other ways
He might but like I mean if you're getting invaded
Be like being being like showing solidarity with your people as they're being invaded is pretty cool
No, don't get me. Don't get me wrong. I hate your policies. Maybe I hate all hierarchies
You know, like a good little like a good little anarcho boy. I am but um, even even even an archo cheesy could say, uh,
Based I love presidents. I love I love liberal democracy. I love the free market
I love you. I love nato nato. Marry me. Have my babies. Uh, okay
I love nato charlie. I love nato
Uh, he he loved uh, i'm trying to think what's the end of the end of 1984 is like he love he loved nato
Winston Winston loved nato
uh
Okay, next voicemail is uh from overwatch
1984 is a good book. I like it. You know, you know, I think um
Damn, I don't know. I I'm gonna I'm gonna start. I want to start reading books. Uh, I should read books
Uh, I think I might go to the library. Maybe after maybe after phantom's revenge. I might go to the library and just pick up
Some books I never read before and read them
I don't know what to read. Wow. Make sure you take a selfie while you're down. So people
Books are for suckers bad read more comics
Here's the thing
Books books are for suckers, but I feel like I don't know. I think I
I think I want
To maybe start like writing stuff and I think that starting to read stuff might be a good
First step, you know what I mean? Okay, I got you. Yeah, I got you
Okay, but if you read enough comics, eventually you would have read the same amount of a regular book and that way
Uh, comics are for babies comics are for little babies that need pictures. I'm
Want to be in the realms of pure ideas pure thought
Damn Ben read read more dead clouds. That's
That's that will feel that'll stimulate you. I did stimulate your underside your your brain will tickle your brain
I did really like uh, fuck. What was the name of the one you gave me? Uh
It's david boring. Yeah
Yeah, david boring. I did I did like david boring a lot read. Um, you should read a
You should read a defray next because that's kind of like david boring, but there's like a superhero angle to it
I should I should read some more. Yeah, that's that's fair
All right, that'll stimulate your other side right there, buddy. Let's let's do the next one the next one wait
I post I posted the wrong one here. This is
What wait, um
No, no, I didn't the next one is called local print shop quote quandary 3 2 1 go
Hey last episode ben mentioned that his local print shop wouldn't give him the formula to determine prices and he had to
Bespokely ask them for every permutation. He was interested in yeah
And I wanted to mention that this is not just your local print shop. My local print shop is the same way
I expect it's uh every local print shop in america
And I think uh, I it doesn't make any business sense why they would do that. I think it's just not their bread and butter and uh
maybe like when
Companies want something printed. They already know what they have in mind
And maybe they're less price sensitive, but I don't know
If someone works in a print shop, it could be interesting to figure out why I figure they're
They're just not focused on it. They're stuck in the past
Model of uh, you call somebody up and you ask for quotes or something
Anyhow, just wanted to let you know that you weren't alone and it's a problem everywhere and it's aggravating. I mean
Seems like there's a really simple solution
Just tell me the fucking formula you fucking hacks like
Crap, I was giving me the crappy patty formula, please
the
The the mixam
Was the company I used for the lot of ghosts and they have a really good online like quote
You don't have to like give them your specifications. They don't email you later. You just type in the like
Like whether you want it to be hardback or like
Glossy I specifically mentioned how many pages
Uh, what page thickness and then they just give you exactly how much that would come
I specifically mentioned mixam last episode as one that I found while I was looking around for alternatives
Because uh, maybe you probably didn't catch it. Oh, no, you did. You said you did listen
I
Yeah, they were quoting me like they were quoting me like 30 dollars plus on like per copy
At my local print shop and I'm just not that's just not a uh, manageable
Threshold
So that's full color. How many pages is slime and punishment? It would be uh, it
It kind of depends. It would probably be somewhere around like 150 to 180
Ish
Okay, so not insubstantial. Yeah, it's not insubstantial
um
it
just so
Yeah, I print stuff through mixam too and I really fucking they get back to you quick too. Something's like wrong with your like
You know printing
Cheesy did they send you a sample pack because I I tried to get them to send me a sample
Pack of like different papers and they said it's like not available in my country
Which is very disappointing. They didn't send me a sample pack
Okay, who said that mixam
Mix it. Yeah, that uk based. That's why
Shifting is quite easy for me. Yeah, I just want to I just like trust them
There were there were a few there were a couple alternatives that I was looking at too though
So I may go with mixam or I may go with someone else, but uh, yeah
Okay, uh next one is called how do bicycles
Stay up three two one go
Hey crack if c is so good then how come endless war isn't written in c
endless war. Yeah crack endless war is written in python
Uh, and I don't know why I don't know if there's a good reason for that
I just I just started writing it in python. I think you know, I think it might be
Shit is it written in python just
Because I was learning no because I was learning python specifically to make endless war
And someone recommended python to me. I think I'm probably asked crack
And he recommended python as the language to do it in
But I don't remember why so yeah, you would have to ask him why it's and why it's not in c. I don't know
Uh, well crack was earlier in the call before I've been stepped in
He did he was here before we started and he and he spewed a bunch of like racial slurs
Yeah, yeah, I I believe you
Yeah, it's crazy. So I don't know. Do you have crack of
A characteristic behavior for him honestly. Yeah, just DM crack
Yeah, also there was a period where I would follow crack on twitter and he never followed me back. So I unfollowed him
Just want to throw that out there. That's uh, it's valid. That's a character character exposed
Exposed, you know, you know me. I check everyone who follows or unfollows me. That's my that's the strat
Next next voicemail is called a ramble three two one go
Okay, so I'm just calling into vent. I have no idea what's going on in the episode
But for some reason things weren't working well on my speak type on desktop
And it just wasn't picking up my audio even though when I did it on my mobile phone
It picked up things just fine
And I didn't know it was wrong given the fact that I could pick up my microphone fine on discord
But it turns out if I go into my audio settings
I didn't have my microphone set correctly
So make sure that you set your microphone correctly in your audio setting so that make sure that people can hear your voice
You guys understand that also give a good job with the game. I'm glad to see that you were able to make that
And I hope you can make more in the future. Yay. Thank you
Yeah, this is uh, this is a good buddy of mine deaf alchemist. Yeah. Yeah, it was an obvious. Yeah deaf alchemist
It to me it sound like he was about to start rapping
Uh, check check your microphone settings everyone
And yeah, good good job on the game
Hey Mike check
Good job good job on the game gamer. Good job on the game. Good job on the game. Uh next uh next
Next voicemail is called pain three two one go
Yeah, thank you for thank you for that sound effect. I will use it in the game
That guy sounds like they were in pain
Uh, he could be next one is called pcp revolution three two one go
Remember when jesse during raccoon four was like
Man, it'd be great if the there's a pcp revolution where everyone was against each other
They'll hate each other the pcp breaks up and all that she needs like I would love that
And look what happened now that basically happened. I don't remember jesse's dream came true
pcp revolution forever
We should change the name of the of the show to pcp revolutions
Uh, I don't that sounds like something he would say I don't specifically remember
him saying that but that it's
It must have been in a video or something. It must have been in a video
Um, who you tracks about everything that guy says anyway, not me
exactly
uh next next one is called
Uh, ben saint doesn't care about pcp listeners three two one go
Minder to all pcp listeners that ben saint does not care about us
it is
8am
on
Sunday, February 27th, and there's still no podcast on any of the podcast platforms other than youtube god
Fuck you ben saint listen. I'm coming for that but listen
tom
Tom has traditionally uploads the episodes and he just
Didn't and he just hasn't been doing the podcast stuff and I don't know where he is
I don't know why he didn't answer when I asked him about it. Uh, I don't know how to do it
You're you're I'm so fucking generous. I don't even have it's not my job
It's not my department, but I uploaded the dang video all by myself. It was so hard. It was so it took me took me all night
Slave and over a hot stove
You're welcome. That's how much I care
next voicemail is called
slime times weekend update number three three two one go
Good day slime city. Good. Welcome back to the slime times weekend update
This week features some spectral news an old state ad by the name of taco a living taco from outer space
Has made their return to the slimy streets and the sewers
in addition
This week marks the one year anniversary of state ad auger don refusing to revive as state ads tend to do
auger don is in my lord of ghost comic cap and metalheads animal fact segment
Which has been going daily for what has to be over a literal year. Yes approaching its 700th installment
The skeleton-based fellow has reported on regular fauna and slime based life forms alike
And we're excited to see what special info he brings us during the anniversary
Finally, there seems to be a contest going on for people regaling others about their epic back stories
Word on the street is the new los angeles literary community is getting especially excited about it
curious
That's it for this week. We hope to see you next time and remember the slime time is the best time
Thank you. It really is the best time. Thank you, uh prince isolation
the uh, yeah, I remember in the last contest judging a bunch of people were talking about
Captain metal heads animal facts segment, uh, which I thought at first was in an anamorphon time
Reference because they have an animal facts segment on that show, but I guess not it's just independently
independent
convergent evolution
700 insolence
Wow, um
and then
uh
Oh, yeah the uh, yeah the backstory contest the the theme for the next. This was my idea. I thought it would be pretty good
Uh, the theme for the next contest is like people it's like tell your backstory. What is your
What is your your oc? What's there? What's their deal? What's their what's their backstory?
What's yeah, what's going on there? Yeah, because because everyone's got because everyone's got like some weird stupid
avatar, right? Everyone is like a sentient like
piece of bread or like a like a you know a fish
A fish with a gun coming out of its mouth or something everyone's some dumb thing
Everyone's like what where what's your what's your what's what are you right? Like what like why are you here?
Well, how did you end up in slime city, right?
Everyone's a blimbo everyone's a squimbo
Everyone is scrimblified. We're extremely scrimblified over in
The scrimblified population you should be able to you you can pick your race
You should be able to uh, you should be able to spec into scrimblow
That would be pretty good. That would that's a mechanic that endless war could use and would use
I am I called my the style of characters that aren't going versus us scrimblows. They're uh, grimblows
Oh
Good wouldn't want them to be wouldn't want them to to to be uh,
Too similar or anything. No, I don't want them to be scrimblows. I gotta be grimblows. You know just edgy or scrimblows
Much much better much better with angry eyes
I guess all your eyes is a grim blow and and sharp teeth. Everyone has sharp teeth
Next voicemail is uh, what is it called base? It's just called base three. We're almost done. But we have three more
three two one go
Hello, Ben
Hello, yep. Hello. Hello any potential guests. I just want to look you
You're all
Yay, thank you. Thank you. You too and you too and you too voicemailer
Yeah, you too. I didn't hear that. I didn't hear that last part but you too
they
He said he said, uh, we're based here and you're not he said any potential guests are based except for cheesy manfredo
Damn, he said that really quickly. I know it's really messed up
Yeah, I hear that from my mom every single day. She's like, yeah, he's pretty based after when cheesy's on but i'm like, but mom i'm cheesy
Uh, she she said, uh, whatever happened to the pizza party podcast. I never liked him on that either
Yeah
That boy that boy. He's just uh, he's a he's toxic for podcasts. He's
poisoned
He's fucking problematic
problematic
Uh, next next voicemail is called. It's ya boy three two one go
Hey guys, it's your boy here. Just letting you know that yix studio is officially dead boy gazers is no longer on yix studio anymore
Fuck trixie. Fuck you. Fuck everyone on there. Fuck you. We saw we saw that uh,
shunt it off
I I
I don't get why though
What do you mean?
But why is it different if all the same people are doing it?
Well, it's a different. Yeah. Well, it's a different show
Because in the sense that it's uh, it's no longer like video. It's just it's just audio
That's why it's the podcast now
They it's funny they
Riley called void. He he used to consistently call void gazers a podcast even though it's obviously not one
It's obviously like a vlog
Slash like
I guess you maybe could call we could generously call it like a variety show like a variety comedy show the times they would
do like
Live like, you know, it's like question people about stuff on the street or whatever
um
So it was definitely not a podcast, but he always called it one
But now it's the pot. It's the new void gazers podcast, which is an actual podcast, which is just them talking
Uh
So I
So, I mean, yeah
I get I I think I think that's why because there's no more there's no more video component or uh, or riley just doesn't want to edit video anymore
Uh, so now it's
Now it's the podcast now it's on his channel and that's what he wants. He wants that content
Now he's got it
I'm good for him
All right
One more voicemail
Is uh, Nate is back
three two one go
I'm reaching back today. Thank you boys. That's good
Yeah
Wow, you're excited. Yeah
I love voicemails
Okay, well, that's it we listen to them all
Oh good
Somehow I had big nice. We did it. Yeah. Yeah
And only under four hours. Excellent. Uh, god, are we under four?
We're just yeah, we we we kept it under four
Shit, I had somewhere to I had somewhere to be at four actually. So that's a little fucked up. That's why I had to uh
Oh, well
Oh, well, uh, anyway any final thoughts before we conclude today's episode
Play pumpkin alley
Free demo you don't even have to pay, but it's nice if you do but you don't have to and
Leave feedback and look forward to
Kickstarter and other things in relation to it. So I was
Ish I was kind of curious actually I wanted to ask and I don't know if you'd be comfortable talking about this
But I was wondering if you like made any money in donations
Because I'm all I'm also hoping that people will donate to my to my game when it's out
We got a few donations. Yeah
Yeah, I think I got a big one from crack actually. That was nice
Oh, wow
Uh, can I like how many people donated? Uh, I don't have the
The numbers it's like maybe 10 people
It's something it's not it's not nothing. So it's pretty good
Uh, well, I mean, uh, I don't hopefully more will trickle in
I mean the the the point of the demo is not to make money is just to show people
To have something to show people when we're trying to like actually fund it and make the real thing. Yeah
Yeah, sure. Sure. Um, it's also a good thing. We can like bring to like a games convention and say, hey, we're working on a game
Any journalists want to write an article about it?
Yeah, I uh
You should have pushed the diversity angle. Here's a game made by a trans creator
I guess I guess I could throw that in there if it will work
For a thing or two, but I don't really care. But then for then wait, wait a minute. Wait a minute
Wait a minute a a trans gender game developer. Are you are you are you serious?
Are you
Unfathomable
Yeah, um, I don't know. I said gamer. I know trans people. So I don't think I'm gonna
Partake in this. Well, well, well gamers and game developers are like natural enemies
They're like lions and hyenas. They hate each other and they always will true true
True. It's uh, it's it's a abusive relationship. They share
Quite toxic to one another. Mm-hmm. I want the game to stand on its own. Um
First and foremost, I get you if I need if it could help I'll just say, um, yeah, can I have a table at this con?
Sorry, we're booked. Well, I am trans. Sorry, please. No, sorry
No, no, no, no cis people allowed at this convention. Yeah, no sissies at this convention
I'll I'll weaponize my minority status if I need to
But like I don't I don't care. Put that put that sound bite sound bite
I'll bludgeon people
Yeah, just just as you apply to convention. Just letting you know, I am trans. They're like, um, this is a transformers convention
It's not the same thing. Just letting letting you know. I'm trans. Uh, uh, sorry, uh, don't care that much
And it just smacks your own head with a hammer and I'm disabled now
Plus ratio plus
Yeah, yes, it's it's like the like a version of like, uh, do you know who I am? I'm making youtube videos. Um
Yeah, I have the I have so much social cloud. I could make you take a big L if you don't let me in
I could make or break you. I was on I was on uh, excuse me, uh, I don't know if you know who I am
I was on a brony con, uh panel
In 2019
In the sun room might I add?
Yeah, was it really 2019? Who?
No, I I wasn't it was 2015 or 14
Oh, was that was that when we did the first cast live was like early 2010s
Yeah, you
I think it might have been 2015
I can't wait till they do pcp live just ben and give and they're gonna be like, where's Nicky?
Where is he?
People people come people come live. Yeah
Well, we're gonna we're gonna fill that we're gonna fill that sun room again one of these days
These days and help people be back, baby. We we we peaked we peaked in the sun room. We have we have to go back
All right, I just wanted I wanted to ask I wanted to ask about uh, I wanted to ask about money
Because I love money so much. Let me just ching ching
Okay, now it's my turn mom says it's my turn to show
Okay, so I I have
Read everyone read Villainverse everyone
If you have not read Villainverse, please read Villainverse. It's actually good. It's free to read or not
Actually, um, if you and you remember back in that shonen contest where everyone was posting their comic on medibang
Yes
You remember that
Oh, you mean um this the show the jump the one that give entered Clarissa in
Yeah, yeah that one right so
Villainverse is on medibang
And I looked at kind of like the ranking for like I guess I guess medibang just shows you kind of like western comics or anything
That's like in english instead of like
The popular stuff in japan, right?
And it got me and I saw like kind of like how popular kind of like western stuff is in medibang
And like it only gets a handful of likes
and and I and I see that um
I see that I tend to have like a bigger following than a lot of these other like western comics guys
So I'm like if anyone out there is a fan of Villainverse and you have a medibang account
Um, go to medibang. I mean just look at Villainverse
Go yeah, look at Villainverse on medibang and just give it a couple likes
And I'm pretty sure I could get pushed to the top of the ranking just with a handful of likes
Yeah
Yeah, dog and I'm yeah, I'm still cheesy manfredo on medibang
Uh, check them out. Check out. Check out cheesy manfredo on medibang. So is that where is that the only place the comic you can you can get
Is on medibang or is there the Villainverse? You you can read it on medibang. You can read it on tumblr
There's actually a discord this villainverse discord where it has a chat that just has the whole comic right there
And people can read it by the box by the books. They're all on itch. Also. I have new books
If anyone remembers luna from bongo luna, I have made two porn comics
And those are on itch. They're called graveyard smash
Yeah, and I yeah, they're pretty good. Um, she bangs a werewolf then she bangs a ghost and
I don't know what she's gonna. I don't know what she's gonna bang the third book
But it's not gonna be a ghost or a werewolf
Yes, yes toby fox crossover
Uh, I was gonna say a revenant, but those are those are just zombies basically those are just zombies. I can talk
So that sucks
She needs to bang someone with a vagina in the third book. We already have like two penises in a row. We need a vagina
I would say succubus then a fuck you. Yes
Herm Herm I might go with that angle
So I got that going on for me and the nsfw account is a creamy pasta tc on twitter
And I post a lot of uh, I'm actually doing reduces have vaginas
Everybody knows that everybody knows
Medusa has vagina. I checked. I looked at her vagina not her face
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was uh, it was a perfect plan
Work her work perfect. If you look at her vagina, you become unstowned. Oh, no
She saw her own face reflected in her vagina and turned herself to stone
Fuck
Excellent. So yeah, I got
She was she was so horny that's like she she her vagina juices drip down her legs and formed a slick
Shiny pool at her feet and she looked down and saw her own face
No
tragic
But who hasn't been there am I right ladies who hasn't slipped am I right ladies who hasn't slipped on your own pussy juices
Where you're walking down the stairs and snap your own neck
It's just you know
It's just like when when you're playing a handheld video game and then the screen turns off and you're you're there and you're looking down
And like you got double chins because you're looking down and like you look you're old and you look like shit
It's like that when you when you're so horny that you just piss pussy juice out into a big slippery puddle on the ground
And you look down and you see your own face and you go
How do they get so old and stupid?
Oh, you know, it's just it's just hashtag just medusa things
Medusa's historically they have snakes for hair and they have an incredibly heavy flow
All right, an incredibly heavy flow
Vaginal flow is what i'm referring to
I I love all this new
Squirters allure big squirters
I love all this new medusa lura lura squirt squirt is peach discovering right now
But yeah, anyway follow a creamy pasta tc. I don't draw medusa's yet, but I might eventually
Mostly drawing like big titty clowns. They could commission me to draw more big titty clowns because that's pretty great
I even have a patreon for that with a sticker coming out soon
Do you give do you give a do you give a um?
Do you give a discount if someone commissions you for a big titty clown?
Uh, they're a patron
Oh, okay, because because some people are like, yeah, I'll uh, like oh well
I I'll give you a discount if you if you'll commission something with my oc's
Yeah, I do I I do that. Yeah. Um, yeah
Yeah
So if anyone like commissions like, you know bongo or luna or all the other clown girls that I've created for the NSFw account
You get like a five dollar off
Right. Oh, yeah, who's this yellow?
Pac-man. Oh, that's a that's a pac-man. That's a pac-man girl designed by a buddy of mine super spo
She's very cute
I need to update this
It does I do comics now. I could do like porn comics, although I charge way more for that. Of course. Yeah
Yep, of course. So yeah, cheesy manfredo is doing porn now gamers and you can get in you can get in on these on the sick
Sweet deals that I'm doing
Okay, just for you
Good. Yes. I condone everything that was just said
Uh, but I gotta get going actually. I'm late for an engagement. So we gotta wrap this up. Uh, all I gotta say. Yeah play
Uh, check out. Uh, check out cheesy manfredo read villain verse and definitely play
Pumpkin alley. Uh, it's on itch. Uh, link in the description
Okay, that's it. Good night. That's it. Good. Good. Good. Bye. Patreon.com slash the progress data and all that other stuff, you know
Cheesy manfredo. Yeah for some stuff. There's some stuff there, too
Okay