Well, we did it everybody. We made it back to The Pro Crastinators Podcast for another week of content.
They said it couldn't be done. They said it shouldn't be done.
They said, they said, my god, an all guest episode. The PCP has degraded. It has lost. It has lost. It's a vital Chouadevive.
Ever since Geoff left, it's all been downhill and there's been nothing good. It's just been a series of escalating humiliations wrought upon themselves.
And they said this was the final straw. But guess what? We can go lower, baby.
There's more dirt under the barrel and under the bottom of the barrel to dig down into if we put our minds to it.
And here we are to do just that.
That's the new goal of the podcast is to be as embarrassing as possible.
My goal, I'll tell you what my goal with the PCP is, is I want to divide the audience as much as possible.
I want to make controversial decisions that some people will think is great and some people will hate it.
And the goal here is that I divide the audience enough that the split audience hates each other more than they hate us.
And we can escape. We can escape notice. We can throw it on a smoke bomb and run out the back door.
I mean, I feel like that's already a thing.
We've got the types of fans who are invested enough to come on the All Guests episode.
And we've got all the cowards who said, nah.
That's what it is, a pure cowardice not being on the Oops All Guests episode.
Damn cringe.
You think that's the divide people who were on and people who weren't?
Yeah, I mean, that's the difference.
Sure.
Alright, a big announcement.
I fucking did the manga.
I made a whole 50 page manga chapter for a contest.
The Tezuka Awards, I submitted it and I'm gonna win.
Can't fucking believe you.
I didn't think it was possible like in week two.
I was like, there's no way I am going to be able to get all of these pages done.
It's the worst thing that could have ever happened to me and I kept going, dude. I did it.
Okay, I have, I was following along at the beginning.
I sort of fell off following your progress later in the month.
So, so tell me, you said that you're the...
Whoa.
Okay, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Sorry.
Did you fall and you nearly fall off the cliff?
No, I was, I did. I did earlier today.
I was trying to sleep and I straight up had the, it was the strongest sensation of I'm about to fall asleep
and I'm going to fall off the cliff and I would, I jolt awake like, ah, I'm falling.
But no, that's, that's not, that's not what's happening.
The point, okay, the point is, you said that like your actual manuscript was like 80 pages or something
and you had to like split it, right? To qualify.
Yeah.
You ended up doing that?
I, first week, I was like, let's, I got a basic story in my head.
I haven't written down the dialogue or like scene direction, like close up of this white shot of that.
Like I did with Lord of Ghosts.
I was just flying off the seat of my pants, basically.
And I was like, let's just try and sketch as much as I fucking can.
First week, I got 55 pages sketched, I think.
And I realized-
So many fucking pages to sketch.
It's a lot of pages to sketch.
Not all the pages are as good as other ones, but you know, you know, they work.
They all serve the function that they are intended for.
Dialogue scenes are harder to make interesting.
But, um, I got to, yeah, page 55 and I was like, okay,
I, this is past the limit.
Wait, can I interrupt you for a sec?
Do you have it scripted out before you sketched it?
No.
Okay.
I was sort of figuring out, okay, well, what could I put on this panel?
I knew basic story beats, like Clarissa comes to town, altercation with bandits.
Town sees her, kill the guys and be cool and they ask her to help.
She says, okay, she goes, you know, she finds bandits, you know.
Okay.
Yeah, that's how I do it too.
I don't, I don't script in advance.
Yeah.
And it worked, it worked fairly well.
It's just that the time pressure was like, I have no idea how long it's going to take me to line like the ink, all of these.
So I have to like cut it off at some point, whether or not the sketch is good enough.
And I was just like, ah, I just move on like all the time.
I was just like, ah, fuck, it sucks.
Got to move on though.
So first week, getting all the sketches done, I realized that there's too long.
The story that I have drawn, some of the panels may be too big.
It doesn't fit in the allotted 55 maximum page limit, this one story.
So I had to split it.
And I decided on page 50 is a decent enough place that you could feasibly imagine the ending being.
It's just a really bad ending.
Yeah.
So for the contest, it sucks because it's not really finished.
But I think it tells enough of a story.
So did you finish the whole thing or did you just finish the part you're submitting?
I finished the part I'm submitting.
I think I might stream in September as well to finish Clarissa like chapter two or like part two.
And then once it's all finished, I'm going to put it on my site.
And that's that's my plan for the moment.
But yeah, it was it was eight and a half hours of work every day, every weekday that is for all of August.
First week sketches, then I had like a depressing like depressive episode and like Monday of the next week where I was like, oh God, I'm not I'm not fast enough at drawing.
I'm bad at this.
Oh, I'm so bad at drawing.
And I was like, there's no way I can do this fast and good enough.
And then I got over it by the next day is like, yeah, I'll just do it.
And then I did.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's how you do it.
No, I actually I actually will simply do it simply.
I will just do it.
And I will just try to do as much as I can.
And after the first after the second week, I was like, OK, the rate at which I can line like ink pages.
If I keep up a pace of fully inking four of these sketched pages every day, I will have enough time to add, you know, speech bubbles and dialogue and tweak it and clean it and then submit it by the end of the month.
So I was like, once I had that plan, it was just like, go, go, go, go, go.
And I did it.
I was I just kept going and it was cool.
And it was so many people came in the chat and they subscribed and they made all that they made so many bits fly all over the screen.
Everyone was so hype.
Everyone who came to the stream was great.
And there was like a slowly like the last one or just in general, just in general, just over the course of the week, like the people saying it's inspiring and it's cool and it's epic and it's based.
Yeah.
I mean, they're not wrong.
And I think I forget when this started, but people started drawing fan art, mostly jokingly, like specifically lewd Clarissa fan art because I said, don't do that.
And so they did it.
And it was a trick because I actually wanted it.
Haha, you fucking idiot.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, by the end of the month, the stream was just covered in fan art.
Yeah.
And as the policy I came up with, if you draw a fan art and submit, like just give it to me, I will put it on screen for the entire rest of the month.
And by the last stream, there was so much that you could barely see what I was drawing.
Perfect.
So yeah, very successful in all aspects.
I love everybody who came to see and cheer me on and just watch and it's just like, wow.
Wow.
So yeah.
And then I submitted it live on Saturday, the 29th.
I saw the link to the media bang page that it was posted on or whatever.
You know what I'm talking about?
Medibang, yeah.
Medibang.
Yeah, what is that?
Because I saw it there.
It was posted there.
It had a couple thousand views or something.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Is that where you have to host it for the contest?
That site is where the contest is submitted.
It's a Japanese website made for mangaka to post their internet manga and illustrations and you post your comic and whatever.
And when you're submitting a comic, you can add it to an ongoing contest.
And I selected the Tezuka Awards while I submitted and then it was locked in.
I submitted it and it was in the awards.
And also it's just on the site for people to read.
And I looked through the submission things.
There was this pay button.
And I was like, excuse me.
You can have people pay to read your stuff?
Is it like a band camp thing?
It's like pay what you want?
Sort of deal?
No, I think you can give people a preview and then you have a set price.
So if you want the whole thing, you have to pay 420 yen to see the whole 50 pages.
But I have zero yen.
You just have to go to Japan then, won't you?
And I have to go in the rice fields and grind some of that rice.
That's how you get yen.
Yeah, okay.
So yeah, 420 yen.
And I think like two or three people have purchased that.
420, nice.
Yeah, it's like $3.99.
And yeah, I didn't intend to get money from posting it.
But I thought if it's on there and some of the fucking submissions to this contest
get an unbelievable amount of views.
There's this shitty one, this awful six page one piece ripoff called Two Piece.
Okay.
And it is just like Gear 5, Gear 7, Luffy versus Blackbeard at Raftel.
And it's just a bunch of traced images, no story, no nothing.
What the fuck?
Okay, yeah.
And it got like 80,000 views because it was posted right at the beginning of the contest.
And I saw it and I was so angry that this could happen.
But it means that there's a lot of eyeballs on Medibang apparently.
I guess a lot of non-English speaking countries including Japan use it to look at things.
And so Clarissa has got like 6,000 views or something.
It had like 2,000 when I looked and that was like right after you posted the link or it felt like it anyway.
Yeah, I was like there's no way that this could be just my fans.
Because when it was on stream, there was 30 viewers in the stream and it had jumped up to like 280.
It was like whoa.
So have you made any money off it?
Has anyone like bought it?
Yeah, like two or three people.
Okay, alright.
So you know, it was like a little pocket change just for the thing.
Okay, now the other submissions, are they like, do they all like look like anime?
Or are there a bunch of like not strictly anime looking shit?
I see the vast majority are going for a sort of anime manga style trying to look as professional as one of those mangas as possible.
The very most popular one does look like that.
And it's very, the story sucks.
I read a little bit of it and it's just like.
What is it?
There's a boy who is like in a world with constant conflict and dragons.
There's angels and devils.
There's angels and dragons?
Tell me more.
There's like angel people and devil people.
The angels fight the devils.
But there's this boy who has an angel and he becomes an angel with black wings.
He could be your angel or your devil?
No, just the angel.
Sorry.
Okay.
But he's got black wings and it's like oh wow.
You ever, you ever read Helc?
Like milk?
Yes.
No.
Oh.
Helc?
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know if I want to go on it.
It's not, it's not relevant at all.
It just reminds me of Helc and I really like Helc.
And sometimes I just want to talk about Helc.
Helc?
Helc is the, is a manga about, I haven't read all of it, but like it starts off either in the demon world and like the demon world is trying to choose a new king.
And the way that they choose a new king is they have a tournament, right?
Of like various contests.
It's battling, but it's also like various like tests of skill and like long jumping and shit like that.
And all these demons are competing in this tournament to be the new king.
And demons hate humans, right?
That's like the thing.
The demons like they live away from humans because they think humans are gross.
Humans are like terrible colonizers.
They're evil.
They're shit.
They're embarrassing.
They hate everything.
They're disgusting.
Is this human named Helc?
He's this giant fucking hulking guy.
And everyone's like, why is a human competing in the demon tournament?
And why does everyone love him so much?
And this reporter goes up to me and he's like, excuse me, Mr. Helc, why are you competing to become the demon king?
And he's just like, hmm, it turns to the crowd.
Humans suck.
And the whole crowd's like, yeah, Helc, we love you, Helc.
And the conflict later is like humans are bad.
Humans are the human kingdom is really bad in Helc.
But like the humans discover a way to like reach the next stage of human evolution, which makes them like grow angel wings.
So they're like humans like are angels in that.
And oh, and they they figure out like a way to use like white magic to like revive themselves.
They're basically immortal.
Like these fucking priests can just like bring people back from the dead.
So it's like impossible to kill the humans.
They're like the biggest fucking problem.
They're like it's terrible scourge on the planet because they're just like, yeah, we're just going to take everything.
And now we got wings and we can never die.
So, you know, everyone's fucked.
Pretty, pretty good.
Okay.
I'll never talk about Hulk again.
I'm sorry.
Is it like Hel Hulk?
It is the.
Okay.
His name is like he had like a partner or a brother or something who was killed by I think by the humans.
I think like it was executed as a traitor or something.
And the two of them were named like Helc and like Achles or something.
And it's like their names together are supposed to be like Japanese for hercules.
So he's like the hell and the other one is the the Culeys or whatever.
That's what the name is supposed to mean.
I see.
So like RL like herk, but Helc.
Yes.
Like, like how Boruto is supposed to be bolt.
Why?
I had no idea.
Yeah.
So wait.
Boruto.
And Naruto is like Naut.
Well, no.
Naruto's name is not a pun.
Naruto's name is just a reference to those like spiral.
Oh yes.
Yes.
The funny thing that I don't know what it is still.
It's a fish.
It's a fish cake.
He's a fish boy.
It's a fish.
No, he's a spiral boy.
The fish part's not relevant.
Anyway, so you said you were saying that the top one is this like fucking Angel Demon
Dragon.
It's it's Angel Demon Dragon fantasy world.
Like I couldn't get invested sort of story, but sure.
It's extremely popular.
800,000 views on that one.
And it's like that.
That's that's that's going to get a poggers.
That's a PogChamp moment.
And it's like, if this, I mean, this popularity is not the way to win you.
Things are just submitted to the site as like a, you know, a comic website.
Contests are one judged by judges.
And so it doesn't matter how popular you are.
As long as you're in the contest, you have a chance.
But it's interesting to see that there's that much like viewer base,
even potential for something.
So I think I might upload Lord of Ghosts on there as well.
Cause why not?
Would you submit Lord of Ghosts?
Or I guess it's too long.
It's too long for the contest, but like, I mean, there are other contests.
The site has loads of contests all the time, but this one is like the big one
that is like in association with Shueisha Inc. or whatever that has shown on Jump.
Well, shit.
Maybe I should get in on it.
Maybe, maybe I'll just fucking upload some shit on there too.
I don't know why not?
Why the fuck not?
I never really thought of much of it as like a site that you can like get noticed,
but apparently, apparently there's a lot of eyeballs.
But are there, are there other ones that like do not look like anime manga?
I skimmed them.
I only really looked at the covers so I couldn't tell,
but there were a few that had like a different art style, like a western-ish.
The ones that were submitted are either from,
this is the international portion of the contest.
The Japanese one is completely separate.
So we weren't, in this thing, I'm not competing with any Japanese people,
which is good for me.
But I am competing with Chinese and Korean people.
So, you know, but I think Clarissa stands out among like the ones that I saw in terms of it being extremely simple art style,
you know, with thick lines compared to a lot of the other things,
which are either anime-inspired, very heavily manga-inspired,
or sort of painterly or scratchy,
not really going for the cutesy sort of look quite as much.
Wait, are you saying that yours is cutesy?
I think Clarissa, like, looks sort of cute,
like the thick black lines and the sort of bloobly character designs.
Bloobly.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm very proud of what I made.
I think it's good.
I think it could obviously be improved.
I kind of was rushed to get it done.
So like, the first few pages are a bit like, oh.
But I, you know, there's a few pages in there that I'm genuinely like,
this is some of the best work I've ever made.
I'm so happy about it.
Well, that's, I agree.
Yeah, I do think, I mean, I haven't, I haven't read the whole thing through.
I've just seen like the parts you were sketching.
Yeah, I thought some of the stuff I saw you drawing there,
I also was like, this is some of the best work you've ever done.
Good stuff.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I guess, I guess on the subject of comics, let's see.
I ordered my fucking, I ordered Vapors 2 to be printed.
Oh, shit.
I paid for the order.
I'm looking at the invoice for it now.
I paid $2084.51 to have that printed on August 21st, 2020.
Here we are.
It is August 30th.
It has not been printed yet.
It has not been shipped, but I'll guess I'll give it another week or two.
Because these things, I think these things are delayed due to COVID, lol.
The last, that was a test copy that I ordered took almost exactly two weeks to be printed
and shipped to me.
I assume that a big load, the mother load will take as long or longer than that.
I'm waiting on fucking tenor hooks over here to get those, but they're coming, presumably.
Very exciting.
I have all my envelopes.
I have all my white ink pens for addressing them.
It's going to be, it's going to be, it's good that it's coming soon because I'm kind
of like I finished the Simon punishment finale and now I'm like, well, I got some stuff I
could work on.
But what I would really like to do is just kind of not, just kind of zone out and just
do a bunch of busy work for a while, just addressing envelopes.
Honestly, I could, I could really get into doing that for a little bit.
Like sorting pins by sorting pins.
Man, they're, they, they give me the fucking, the pin manufacturer is like, oh, the coin
design.
You want the hard enamel or the soft enamel.
And, and by the way, soft enamel looks bad.
So I'm like, no, hard enamel.
And they're like, okay, well, we recommend the soft enamel because the hard enamel, like
the coin design has so many small lines that like during the polishing process, the lines
might all run together and it might not work.
And I'm like, the other pins had small lines on them.
The other pins had lines just as small and it looked fine.
Totally fine.
Why are you fucking with me like this?
Why are you, why are you doing this?
You mean the challenge coin or is that some other thing?
Yeah.
The challenge coin, which is, so the pin people were going to also do that.
Yes.
The pat, the patches were made by a different company.
The pin people were also going to make the coin using basically the same process.
And they are going to do it.
Eventually, she was all like, oh, I don't know, you know, the, the polishing process,
the lines could mesh together.
Finally, I just had to be like, I don't care.
Just, just fucking do it.
Just fucking go ahead and do it.
And if I have to just redo it from scratch and it looks like shit, then so be it.
You know, fine, whatever.
We got to get the show on the road.
So you're getting the test of the coin.
See how it looks.
I am getting the full order of most of the pins and I'm getting a test, like a color,
like two more color tests of the cop killer pin because I wasn't quite happy with the color.
I was a little too pink for my tastes.
And I should be getting a test copy of the coin as well in hard enamel in a lighter green
and soft enamel in a darker green.
And I will be comparing them and being like, which one looks better in, in person?
Hmm.
And yeah, very exciting.
Very exciting.
Been spending a lot of money on this stuff, but you know what?
It's okay.
That's what the Kickstarter was for.
And now I get 2% cash back.
Get 2% cash back on my city double cash credit card, baby.
That's the power of a good credit score.
Epic.
Very, very epic.
I've been thinking about like, uh, kickstarting.
Not the Clarissa thing.
Well, obviously I want that to be finished before I even consider kickstarting, but like,
I've got so many things I could, I could make books of.
Beljape, I think is like the next project.
I think once that Clarissa is done, I'm going to like make Beljape a physical book PDF.
However, that is supposed to be done.
I have no idea really.
And I'm going to see, like I looked into book, like payment things, how much, how many pages
it would be.
And like, approximating because I need to like turn the video game and the animation
and the gifts into multiple little images.
It's a whole Homestuck problem.
And yeah, I mean, Beljape, right?
Hey guys, what do you think about Beljape?
Would you buy a little Beljape book?
Am I right or am I right?
Yeah, I don't know how much money.
I kind of completely forgot all the fact of the statistics that I came up with.
I will buy a Beljape book assuming it's not like a hundred dollars.
No, no, no, nothing like that.
It would be like the sort of price for something of that size that you would find in a bookstore.
Like, oh, what is this?
It's kind of hefty.
It's kind of hefty this thing.
Imagine what?
It'd probably be like 30 bucks?
30?
Yeah, I'm hoping.
More and I don't know.
Might be more, but I'm going to try and get it down as low as possible.
I just don't want it to look like shit.
That's the only thing.
There's no reason to make it if it's going to look like shit.
I've been thinking about, I was thinking about doing a Kickstarter
for like a physical slime and punishment book, which I'm not going to do that.
Because even though the finale came out, but the finale is not the end,
there actually is a little bit more that's going to come after the finale.
So the slime and punishment is not technically done, so I'm not going to think about that yet.
But even so, I'm definitely not going to do any more of that until the pin Kickstarter
and the Vapors 2 Kickstarter are completely fulfilled.
Yeah.
And I will probably even wait a little while after that because I will be relieved.
I'll be so relieved when I have those done and taken care of.
It's been like the better part of a year since the Vapors 2 Kickstarter wrapped up,
which is terrible.
It's so embarrassing.
I can't wait for this nightmare to be over.
Next time I kickstart anything, I am not going to jump the gun.
I am going to have the whole thing done.
The whole thing will be done and ready to immediately go to print when the Kickstarter is finished.
I promise this to myself.
I will not put myself through this again.
It's not to say that it's not worth it, but it could have been so much easier if I'd just done it later.
Oh, yeah.
I was thinking about if I did make a bail shape book, I could have bailed J-Pets.
I could get artists to make little bail shape comics.
Yeah.
Just don't put off and procrastinate writing them like I did.
I don't even know what they would be.
It's such a weird history of like, oh, Pumpkin Alley, how do they meet?
I could write that.
Actually, I could write that.
A bail shape is such a self-contained story, though.
Yeah.
A bail shape side story could be literally anything.
It really could, which is why it's so hard to think of what it could be.
Yeah.
Pumpkin and the Gango to Space.
I don't know.
I mean, bail shape ends with like, who knows what sort of wacky adventures will follow?
Sort of note, right?
Yeah.
So it could be who fucking knows.
They all just burn in the lava.
They die.
Yeah, actually, a whole world of possibilities.
There's a fucking hole in our...
What is it?
Is it a raft?
It's a rock.
It's like cooled magma because the jewel of splish is like consistently emanating like
a coolness sphere.
Like a...
Not a wet sphere.
I don't know.
Pumpkin isn't dead, so it's definitely not like making things watery.
It's just like making the magma turn to rock and be not going to kill them.
Yes.
Excellent.
Beautiful.
Oh, but it sprung a leak though.
Ah, fuck.
Ah, darn.
Perished.
Yeah, have me write the bail shape...
The bail shape at where they all just die immediately afterwards and make a cannon.
Yeah, why not?
There's a different timeline.
That's the alpha timeline.
Ben, do you want to talk about Chris Chan's response to Slam and Punishment finale or
is that secret?
No, that's not secret.
Oh, wait, you mean the stuff that she messaged me personally?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't mind.
Do you have the screenshots that I said?
I didn't show them to everyone.
I posted them in the...
They're just up here in the PCP chat.
They're so wacky.
Should I go through them?
Should I like read them?
Yeah.
This is...
Okay, I'm going to say the thing about these...
Chris's strategy is to try...
Is to like rewrite history and be like,
No, no, no, here's why that didn't happen.
And she gives like three different...
She tries like three different get out of jail free cards and they all like contradict each other.
It's total nonsense.
Okay.
So, right.
Slam and Punishment comes out.
You know, Lockecom goes from the beta timeline to the alpha timeline and returns with all the
spoilers.
The Grand Canyon is full of slime again.
The city falls on Chris Chan's sonichu, presumably crushing her, presumably to death.
I don't know.
I mean, never found a body, but you know, let's see what it looked like was happening.
So I...
So I message Chris and I basically say,
Hey, Christine, sorry, I've got bad news.
But, you know, Lockecom's back in the alpha timeline and they're real mad.
They're real mad about the Soda Rain Holocaust and they're going to war.
You know, the war has been declared.
The war is on.
I'm sorry.
Quickville is under attack.
And Christine says,
I got news for you, Ben.
What you said there did not take place in the C197 of this timeline at all.
By the way, she has tweeted before specifically referencing this taking place in C197.
So this is contradicting herself.
This is nonsense.
See, that happened in an alt timeline from this one, right here.
That affected the alpha timeline, but not here.
The Omega timeline.
You picked up on one of the many, many self counterparts from your Chris Chan Sonichu of this dimension.
You may call it C197 alpha, but it was actually dimension C194.
Sister dimension of reality, 1214.
And do you know how I...
Do you know what any of these...
Are these made up new things?
These are just completely made up.
These have never been referenced before.
There has never been a C194 or a 1214.
These are just like, I don't know, let me think of a different number.
No, no, no, it was actually this other number.
I promise.
So, first she claims that, no, no, that's not the alpha timeline, it's the Omega timeline.
Then she claims, not only is it not the right timeline, it's actually a completely separate dimension entirely.
So it doesn't even matter.
This Omega timeline thing is totally irrelevant.
And why would it matter even if it were true?
It's just like a different Greek letter.
And do you know how I know that, Ben?
Because the Chris Chan talking with you right now came from that very dimension.
So the conversation you're having with this Chris Chan is from C194?
That's what she says.
That's what she says, but I don't buy it.
I was there while that cop fucker had me in his slimy, mutated grasp.
But as that beta plane landed on him, I literally teleported out of there in an instant, at least to all of you.
I am literally faster than time.
So not only does she claim, no, no, no, that wasn't the alpha timeline, that was the Omega timeline.
And also, no, no, no, that wasn't C197, that was C194.
And also, no, no, no, no, it also didn't kill me because I teleported out of there really fast.
So, you know.
This is multiple layers of redundancy.
Yeah. There's all on every possible level.
This is not what it appears.
She continues,
I can what you call time stop at any moment.
All I had to do was hit that pause, clear my mind, teleport out of his grip, and mox speed dash far away from the impact zone.
I was in the next date over, and then some upon that impact.
Your beta time liners ended up falling at the hands of their alpha self counterparts.
Not even slime could protect any of them.
Quickville remained very much safe and sound.
Wait, what does she mean by your beta timelines ended up falling at the hands of their alpha self counterparts?
What it seems to me to be suggesting is that the slimed people from the beta prime timeline came to the alpha timeline.
You know, the city fell...
Okay, here she's contradicting herself again, because first she says that no, this was the omega timeline,
but now she's saying, okay, yes, the beta timeline people did come to the alpha timeline,
but then they were killed by the alpha timelines.
So, like, what is the so-called omega have to do with it? Answer nothing. It's a fiction.
Unlike everything else, which is real.
But she seems to be suggesting that the de-slimed alpha timeline people killed the beta people that came there,
even though all the alpha people would be dead, because the city fell on top of them and crushed the alpha timelines version of Mlachikam.
So it's just destroyed.
And B, the beta time liners have slime, which makes them invincible compared to someone who don't have slime.
We saw Phantom Horn, he just easily dispatches everyone from the alpha timeline.
He just butchers them without a second thought.
Because without slime, what can they possibly do? Nothing.
So it's ridiculous. It's totally, totally absurd on its face.
Anyway, Chris continues,
Quickville remained very much safe and sound, and all remaining slime was nullified as well.
Nice try, though.
But you know that a deity is not one to be trifled with that easily.
Okay, so that's all bullshit.
And then here, and then here we go.
You might like to know, also, that back in my timeline, Michael Jackson lived a few more years beyond yours.
He put out two additional albums of inspiration and uplift, as he counted from his experience of falling in golden years into elderly ages.
But his fate was the same as yours.
He OD'd.
He didn't want to feel that old when he felt so young.
Like Sonichu going back in time within your Chris Chans to undo your COVID virus.
I came back in time to see your fate play out.
I will be personally talking with you again, face to face, very soon, with my body and my Magi Chan.
See you then, Ben.
Lightning Bolt, Blue Heart, Lightning Bolt.
So.
I don't know if this is a threat.
Wait.
You just had to tell me.
You know, I know we're talking about timelines and realities and the nature of the universe and stuff,
but let me tell you a little bit about Michael Jackson.
He got older, and he made some new albums.
And then he OD'd.
He didn't like being old, so we OD'd and he died.
What does it mean his fate was the same as yours?
Is Chris Chan predicting your death?
I think Chris is implying that I, I mean, I think it's that like I,
the implication is that I am like OD'ing on the slime or something like the slime is corrupting me.
I think that's an illusion to that.
I see.
That's the best thing I can come up with.
So then like Sonichu's going back in time within your Chris Chans,
possessive Chris Chans to undo your COVID virus.
So she's saying that Sonichu went back in time in the C197 timeline,
or I don't know what timeline she's talking about.
I don't know what dimension she's talking about, but in some dimension,
Sonichu went back in time and undid COVID,
which is I appreciate a lot.
That's pretty cool.
I want to read that.
Yeah, I want to read.
Me too.
I wish I wish he was a little more specific about it.
Anyway, this is all complete nonsense.
Like I have seen reports from C197 that the war is raging.
The war is raging right now.
You know, there's photographic evidence.
It can't be denied.
Chris doesn't want to see, doesn't want to acknowledge that it's true,
you know, but it is.
Quickville is under attack.
It is being besieged.
And you know, the people of New Los Angeles City will not be satisfied with anything less than total surrender.
So, you know, sad, but true.
I'm glad I'm glad we went into that.
Yeah.
So if you want more, Michael Jackson, go to fucking, I don't know.
C194 or the old mega time?
Which one?
Which one are we in?
We, I mean, we right now are in 1218.
We are we are in 1218.
Sonichu and Endless War take place in C197.
Wait a minute.
If C197 is the cartooniverse that corresponds to 1218.
Why is C194 the one that corresponds to 1214?
What's the logic there?
Okay.
Numbers, numbers, numbers.
What, what, whatever, whatever.
So.
Omega timeline.
Ridiculous.
Absolutely ridiculous.
Give me a fucking break.
Okay.
So anyway, I guess I'll be seeing her soon.
I guess she will be visiting me bodily.
Whatever that means.
It means you're going to meet up again.
There's no more brony cons to go to, but you know.
I, I just, she's, she's going to have to come to me if that's going to happen.
And I kind of think, I kind of, my, my reading of this is that she intends to do it via some kind of astral projection or teleportation.
I don't think she's going to like get a train up to Boston.
E?
Yeah.
I guess she'll be visiting me in my nightmares, but physically, physically.
Physically, in reality.
But she doesn't say what dimension that'll be happening in.
So.
It's probably happening right now.
Just right behind me.
I mean, um.
Maybe she, she, she was the one who like created that, that dream, that puzzle dream you had.
Ooh.
She, oh, she's the one that set up all the puzzles or magic, maybe Magi Chan did.
Yeah.
Magi Chan Smiler.
And because you didn't solve the riddles.
You didn't solve it quickly enough.
And then you woke up the, the, the, then that means slime is sucks.
We couldn't unlock the secrets of the slime and it stayed trapped in the dream realm.
Oh fuck.
That made me think of something.
What was it?
Oh, oh, I was, I was going to say, I mean,
Uh,
Magi Chan did bottle, make a, make a physical appearance in the Sonichu 102 lecture.
So, I mean, I guess anything is possible.
Oh shit.
Do you remember that?
I, I do.
I didn't see it.
I couldn't see it.
Like, I didn't see it, but like, no, I've been going over the footage and I think it's, it's undeniable.
I think an entity, an entity from C, from C197 appeared.
And I think it was Magi Chan.
I don't know.
I can't prove it, but, uh, all the evidence points to it.
So it was very, I mean, I'll be releasing that and you'll, people can, you'll be able to judge for yourself.
Uh, uh, uh, was it, was it only a dream?
Or was it, or was it reality?
Hmm.
Think about it.
Think.
Think about what you're trying to do to me.
Uh, uh, and, and as we all know, uh, Aretha Franklin's think is the,
is the anthem of Quickville.
Uh, so, you know, think, do it.
Okay.
Uh, excellent.
Uh, beautiful.
Well, I think we've, I think we've covered everything there is to cover about that.
Um, well, uh, I guess I could like, uh, I could talk a bit more about, um, girl shit.
Like, like, like girl shit.
Like, like female, like, huh?
Um, so last two, two episodes ago, I explained that I'm like gender something still don't really know.
Gay.
Gender gay.
Um, trying out female pronouns.
I was trying to do voice, uh, like feminization to be like high pitch, but I was like, I don't
know, whatever it's, it's hard and I keep forgetting to do it.
I'll figure it out eventually if I ever do that.
Um, but you know, um, uh, dude, dude, uh, I'm going to go to Amazon.com and buy a skirt
and it's going to arrive and I'm going to put it on.
And that's all I've got to say about it.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm going to buy a skirt.
Uh, yeah, I mean, makes, makes sense again.
I got nothing to say about it really.
It's just, I'm just continuing to be a gender freak, a cool person that is better than everyone else
based and dab.
Oh God.
Oh God, our views.
Oh God, our views are plummeting.
Oh God, our audience.
They're hemorrhaging audience.
They weren't here already.
They left.
They're splitting.
No, no, keep going.
Split the audience.
Make them hate each other.
Divide them against one another for our mutual gain.
They saw that Nate still wasn't here and they said, no, and they left a little comment
about it.
I can't wait till Nate comes back, but he's trans.
I can't fucking, I can't wait for Nate to come back for everybody's trans and more
trans than the, than everyone else.
She's more trans.
Haha.
Oh, here.
Yeah.
The, I know it's like, it's, it's, it's embarrassing to talk about.
All right, I get it.
Like I can't, I can't like get the words out because it's like, woo, woo.
You know all that stupid shit.
it. Everyone's always saying like, oh, you were, well, wow.
Oh, well, well, that was stupid. Yeah.
Girls, huh?
What?
You don't look like one. You don't sound like one. I know.
Die. Die. Okay.
But I've been shaving my legs to get rid of that hair that, that I have on them.
Right.
And the, I think I told like, when I shave, when I show up, shave my legs.
Didn't you say you shaved them at Radcon? You hated it.
Because it like hurt, right?
Yeah, at Radcon four, I shaved them for the OVA, which is in production.
Oh, I don't keep, I don't, we probably shouldn't say too much,
but I do want to say that you posted a thing.
You posted an update on the OVA.
Yes. And I thought it looked sick as fuck.
Yes, I was kind of, I was kind of like, I'd sort of been dreading it.
I'd sort of been feeling like, I feel like it's stagnated.
I feel like like nothing has happened on it.
I feel like I don't know if it's going to like be what I wanted it to be.
I don't know how many like compromises we're going to have to make
and how is this going to disappoint me?
And you posted the thing and I was like, no, it's fine.
It's going to be good. It's actually going to be cool.
Which is so, what a fucking, what a relief, actually.
But yes. Yes.
OK. And I won't, I won't go into any specifics about it.
Yeah. What was I?
Oh, yes, I shaved my as much of my body as I could for that.
But I'd never done it before, ever.
Like my legs had never been shaven.
My arms had never been shaven.
When I did it, it was like, oh, wow, I feel like a completely different person.
But also I did it wrong.
I did it the worst possible way.
I used like a fucking cheap razor.
I think I told the store in the PCP.
I used a cheap razor and I dry shaved my whole body
because it didn't feel, it didn't hurt.
Yeah. And I thought that would hurt really bad.
Yeah. Like I was just, I was just sort of like amazed
at seeing the hair like not be there anymore, that I didn't realize
that I should probably think about this before I continued to do it.
And I just did this and I was like, yeah, this feels good.
Next day.
Extreme pain.
But like, you know, we got a thing to film.
So I filmed the thing.
We all did the stuff.
And yeah, it just hurt like shit for ages
because I cut my leg a million times.
Million microscopic death, death by a thousand thousand cuts.
But now I've researched how to do it.
And I've learned that there's a you just need to be not an idiot.
And you shave it the same way you would shave your face.
Use water. Yeah.
Use shaving foam and you make sure that it is warm and wet
and clean. You ever you ever use you shave in the bath?
That's what I've been doing.
You ever see a device called an epilator?
I think I saw it when I was looking around when I.
I used I used to I used to like try like shaving my chest and stuff.
Be like, well, this look good. And no, it doesn't.
I don't I don't do it. It's stupid. It was dumb.
But for a while there, I was like, I don't know, maybe I should do that.
And I and I did it and this was in like college.
And my my girlfriend at the time had, you know,
she had an epilator that she used on her legs.
And I was like, what is this?
And if you don't know an epilator, it sort of looks like a razor
that you might take to shave, but it doesn't shave you.
What it has in it are these like rolling pins or like bar.
I don't know how to describe them.
They're these like these rolling things.
It's sort of like never seen like them toss an animal carcass
into like a meat grinder.
And it like gets like it's no, it gets like rolled in
and like I have not squished in in between like the these rolling things.
An epilator is like that.
And what you do is you pass it over your body
and these rolling things like grab the hairs and rip them out by the roots.
So it hurts really bad, but you get really fucking smooth.
It's smoother than a shave because there's no stubble
or like it takes a while for the stubble to grow back in.
So and I mean, for me, I'm a very hairy guy.
So it was like a real nightmare.
Did you do it? Did you do it somewhere?
A couple of times, a couple of times I did it just to see
before I was like, I think I'm going to stop doing this.
There's no point to it.
It's done. How quick did it regrow?
It takes maybe a week for it to start being stubble again.
OK, I mean, I feel like just generally shaving does the same amount.
Like it's it's stubble.
Well, when you shave, like you start to get stubble like immediately.
Yeah. Oh, you're saying that there's absolutely nothing until a week passes.
I'm saying when you when you when you epilate,
yeah, you don't have like any if you if you do it all at once,
you don't have like any stubble for like at least a few days
because it's like under the skin
and it doesn't like the root doesn't regrow out the skin for a little while.
It's you're not cutting cutting it at the skin layer.
You're pulling it out from from deeper in.
Hmm. Hmm.
So I don't know.
Yeah, I heard of epilator.
I heard of like this this other thing that's like like lasers.
They use lasers to like burn the the the follicle so that it never goes back.
Is a thing.
I think sometimes it can grow back eventually, like some of it.
There's so many fucking hairs on a leg.
I saw the amount of power that the laser would need over the whole leg.
I mean, too much.
It's too much of a problem to really like I don't think is that is that the problem?
No, that laser would have to be too powerful.
I don't understand like how would it work?
Like how does a laser shoot?
Do they pull their hair out and then shoot the laser down the hair hole?
No, not down there.
I think it's more like because the skin is like semi
translucent, so they can it's like a cancer treatment in the same way
that you have two lasers and where they meet it burns, but everywhere else, it doesn't.
So they probably have two lasers and they pinpoint it at the specific point
and just do that a million billion times.
You know, I didn't know that's how it works, but it makes sense.
So well, I don't know how that that's how the hair removal works,
but that's how cancer treatment works, because if they shot you with the
the whatever it is thing, the gamma rays, I don't exactly know.
Yeah, but if they shot you with just that,
all of your cells would be affected the same way.
They need to pinpoint where the cancer is,
which is why it's really important to get it early, because then it's not all over the place
and you don't need to do that much chemo.
Right.
So they can just figure out where it is, shoot from a different angles
to pinpoint an area and then it burns that the fucking thing and it's gone.
Making me this is making me super nervous, because sometimes I haven't
I haven't been to a doctor.
I haven't had a checkup in like two years and I'm like sometimes I think about it
and I'm like, maybe I should get one.
And then I'm like, oh, God, but what if what if it's bad news?
I mean, what if I go in and they're like, well, you got cancer
and you've had cancer for almost exactly two years and it's too late.
Yeah, but like you ever think about that?
I mean, I don't really.
OK, I feel like I feel like.
I don't think I shouldn't go to the doctor
because I'm scared that it will be bad news.
I mean, yeah, I mean, sure.
Obviously, obviously, I'm not being rational about this
because like if you feel like there could be something bad,
it would be one a relief to now know that there is nothing wrong.
I don't feel like to catch it early if there is something wrong and potentially live.
I don't feel like there's anything wrong.
But I feel like sometimes you just go to the doctor
and you think everything's fine and they're like, actually, you're going to die.
Did they say that to you every time?
No, not to me.
Well, then what's the problem then?
I'm saying, what if I go and I'm like, yeah, you know,
I'm just coming in to get, you know, just test me for.
Yeah, whatever.
Just give me a prostate exam or whatever, you know, the standard.
And I'll just be on my way and they're like, oh, no, no, no, no, no,
your blood work came in and your blood is full of poison.
Excuse me. What?
Full of poison.
You could drink your own blood, you'd die.
Yeah, exactly.
But like, I don't know, you know, sometimes you feel fine,
but you're actually on death's door.
Well, I mean, I guess I guess the the potential, like,
worry, like needless worry of like knowing that you're going to die,
but having nothing you can do about it would like make the rest of your life suck.
But I mean, worrying about it surely also makes the rest like it's the same thing.
Worrying about the potential that you could be dying.
Yeah, is about the same as like knowing that you're going to die.
Well, not the same, but like it impacts your life in the same way negatively.
So just if you go to just go to a doctor and they say,
you just have to be really nervous and say, oh, is there anything else?
Do you think I have anything else?
And they just say, no, just go, go away.
You're fine.
You stupid piece of shit.
I hope you die.
That's what they should say.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, OK, this is me.
I should fucking I should get an appointment.
Yeah, get an appointment.
Get one right now.
Go to appointments.com.
Get the doctor app.
Need a dentist appointments, too.
I got a couple cavities.
I got a couple cavities that need to be dwelled and filled.
Dwelled and filled. Drill them and fill them.
And that's what they say about me.
That's what I do when I have sex.
I thought you didn't have sex.
I thought you were an abstainence.
I lied.
I'm sorry.
I went on Twitter and I can't believe.
I told a lie for attention and likes and I got them.
And everyone said, yay, I love Ben.
He's a virgin like me.
It's funny.
It's funny that it got like attention and likes
because everybody knew that it wasn't true.
It's like it's like my most popular tweet
in like weeks or months.
It's like completely nothing about it is interesting.
There's just like, I don't know.
Hey, guys, I don't know what.
I'm pretending to hate sex.
Ha, ha, that's a funny joke.
I like.
And everyone's like, I love this.
I want more of this.
I want to encourage this kind of behavior.
I mean, it's not terrible.
It's just sort of like whatever.
It's no, it's just baffling.
It's just baffling.
I don't know why I made it.
And I was like, why are people like it?
It did seem to me like a lull so random sort of tweet.
Yeah.
That's exactly what it was precisely.
Um, I guess people are into that.
I've been, I've been getting, I mean, I do those.
I do those all the time.
I know, I'm no better.
I don't know why my attention to my Twitter
has picked up a little bit.
I was just like hemorrhaging followers
and I still kind of am,
but now I've started gaining a few to replace them.
And I don't know why.
Maybe it's because of slime and punishment.
I don't fucking know.
Twitter sucks.
I'm terrible at Twitter.
My follower count has been in like slow decline
for a long time.
It's kind of a bummer actually.
I honestly can't, I can't believe
that anyone pays attention to their follower number.
I mean, I just noticed it every once in a while
to be like, oh, yep, went down a few more.
Okay.
The only thing is, is like,
I see when somebody follows,
but I don't see a button like a notification
when someone unfollows.
So I just assume it's constantly going up.
No, mine is, I've lost like maybe a hundred
over the last like year or so.
Maybe maybe only six months.
Oh, a year, six months.
That's, that's not so bad.
I think it's just people who followed me
like a while ago and like forgot
and they're just finally getting around to like,
I don't even remember who this guy is anymore.
He's changed his name so many times.
He got so many funny things in the name.
Mm.
Ugh.
Yeah.
I have discovered a Twitter breakthrough,
which is like, it's not,
it's not something that is new.
It's just something I've just realized
because I've been stupid this whole time
is that you don't follow people you know
and want to keep up with.
You follow people who retweets shit all the time.
Specific shit.
I found this guy and he's an artist.
And I was like, oh, what is his art?
And I was looking for his art
because I saw he was an artist.
I was like, where's your art?
All it was, it was retweets of other artists.
I was like, where's your fucking art?
I can't believe all you do is retweet.
Oh, there's one of them.
So I found one of his hearts,
but like 98% of what he does
is retweet cool art from other people.
And then I realized that he is a good artist
who is curating Twitter for me.
I should just follow him.
And then I followed him
and now my feed is filled with great retweets of cool shit.
And that's all I see.
It's the best.
Because each individual artist would like post their art
and then sometimes something else or some other thing.
But this guy only retweets the cool shit that he sees.
So it's like I'm cutting out the annoyance
of following somebody who only posts about their art
some of the time.
And it's the best.
Yeah, I guess so.
I don't really follow Twitter for art that much, honestly.
I actually use Twitter more as a news feed.
I think I've talked about this before.
I mostly go to Twitter to like read
like what's fucking happening in like the news and stuff.
I don't, I've got it all.
I've got it all Arabic.
Like I can't read it.
Really?
Yeah, I changed my location
so I can't read what's trending.
And it's always like just some letters.
I feel like I said this before.
I maybe, but I forgot.
That's very funny.
The person I follow is at Chibi Changa 12,
but we'll put a little thing there
so in case anybody wants to see cool art all the time.
I don't think anybody wants to see that.
Me.
Okay, I'm gonna look at this picture.
So this person does do their own art.
Yes, very rarely do they post it.
But, you know.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's quite good.
It's like, you know, it's a professional looking.
I mean, the thing I like about it.
I see a lot of retweets from,
I see a lot of retweets from Cheesy Manfredo.
That guy is like always retweeting
people's cool art and stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Honestly, that's probably the most art I see on Twitter
is from Cheesy Retweeting.
Well.
You know, speaking of art and Twitter,
I was thinking of making like a new Twitter account
for not safe for work art.
And I would draw like a big booby mummy milker.
Or two per day.
That's what I'm thinking of doing.
Okay.
Judge Jury Executioner, you can try to kill me,
but I'm too quick.
I can run away from you.
Well, okay.
I mean, I don't know, follow your bliss.
Follow your bliss.
Follow my bliss?
Okay, sure.
Okay.
Well, I look forward to that.
Should I follow it?
Should I follow it or will you be embarrassed?
No, people can follow it.
I'm probably not going to like hide it and be secretive
because it doesn't matter who cares.
People already know that I like sex
and things of that nature.
And I think, you know,
everybody's got a not safe work account these days.
What does it matter if I have one as well?
I made an OnlyFans and that was funny
and epic and everyone liked it.
Are there still updates on that?
Is that updating or?
No, I just sort of forgot to,
I mean, this month has been like mostly the comic
that I've been drawing and nothing else.
But I don't know, I feel like OnlyFans
takes such a large cut that it's not really worth doing it.
Like it was funny from meme and for a bit of cash, but like...
Hey, what's the only,
what's Pump's OnlyFans account called?
Pumpk911.
Well, Pumpk911, OnlyFans.
I'm gonna look this out.
Here we go.
Pumpk911.
So, I don't know how to read a fucking OnlyFans.
Can you like see how many followers a person has?
I don't know.
I see up in the top left, I see nine posts and 22 likes
and that's all I can see.
Oh well.
Yeah, I've received 22 likes.
Do you have any subscribers?
Probably, why is it not loading?
I clicked on the thing.
It's not loading the page, whatever.
Sometimes I'll see like,
up here where it says how many posts and likes,
sometimes there's more info
and there will be like a little like
stick figure with a heart next to it and a number
and I think that's the number of subscribers,
but I don't know.
It doesn't actually say what it means.
I think all of my subscribers have left
because I stopped updating.
But I don't know.
I feel like it's probably
worth my time to just build up
like some sort of a public following
and then say, hey, here's my specific
not safe for work Patreon
or whatever I end up deciding to do
if I ever go that far with it beyond hobbyist.
Indeed, indeed.
Yeah.
It really is not loading whatsoever.
I'm seeing what I'll go right now.
Only fans, it's like a really slow
and like loads really badly like consistently
when I go to it, which I never do.
I would never, I would never support sex workers.
So yeah, but it's always like takes forever
to fucking get off the page where the only fans logo
is just floating there.
Bad website.
Yes, sucks.
Oh, should we talk about Munchie?
Oh, what about him?
Munchie leave.
Munchie leave a disserver.
Did he post a thing?
All of this.
All a disserver.
In RFCK.
Did he, he left all, did he leave this server?
No, he's still here.
He's just, well, I feel like
he would probably not want me to butcher his statement,
but I will say-
I haven't actually read his statement in-
The statement is basically he's,
wants to focus on being a real person
outside of an online personality.
So the things he did as an online personality,
such as podcasts and things, streams,
he's abandoning, not abandoning,
but he's leaving indefinitely
and may one day return,
but it's not like a sure thing in any way.
Did he post that in the auditorium?
He didn't.
He posted that in Detention Set-O.
Oh.
He also posted it in Quick Draw.
Oh, shit.
Okay, well, whatever.
I haven't read it,
but I think he's like told me as much before.
I am like, okay.
Yeah, all right.
If you want to like, you know, school starting,
you want to focus on school or whatever.
That's fine.
Whatever.
I don't think,
I don't mean to be dismissive,
but I do think it's sort of weird
and I don't really get it to be like,
I'm going to be off the internet
to focus on being a real person.
Well, I don't think you use those exact words.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, all right.
I shouldn't, all right.
You're paraphrasing.
I don't know.
That's fine.
Yeah, I just feel like,
I mean, Munchie has been on the PCP in a while anyway.
So it's not really an announcement
that he's left the PCP, but like.
I don't see why it has to be so black and white
either or like I'm on the internet
or I'm not on the internet,
but at the end of the day,
like whatever he wants to do.
Well, it's not like,
I feel like it's not like the internet.
I feel like it's more of the internet personality,
Munchie wears tiny hats.
Like the things people expect
of Munchie wears tiny hats.
The appearances of Radcon, I assume.
Making content at all.
It's just like he wants to stop the expectations
that he will continue to do that forever.
Which is like, fairly respectable
and I don't really mind
that he still exists, obviously.
And I'm his friend, so I can talk to him.
I mean, Munchie doesn't really,
you know, I mean, Munchie doesn't really make content.
Like I have not been expecting Munchie content for a while.
No, but like.
The lecture came out and I was fine.
Yeah.
He got his things, all affairs all in order.
But like, I think not doing RCK episodes
and streams and endless world stuff was like a big thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, if you, okay.
I'm looking at the statement right now.
Okay, yeah, sure.
I mean, I guess it's like, Munchie was already,
like yeah, he might've been,
I don't know exactly how much time
he was spending on Endless War.
I mean, if he wants to pull back from that, fair enough.
It kind of seemed like he was mostly,
like he was already mostly disengaged.
Like he wasn't being on the PCP.
He wasn't like making his own videos or anything.
He wasn't like working on any art projects
that were like people were anticipating.
He had already like pulled back most of the way.
Yeah.
I think this is, he said he was like doing all that
to see how it felt not doing any of this stuff.
And it was fine.
It's just whatever you want to do.
It's just whatever anybody wants to do.
I don't know.
I'm just like.
Where's investigative?
Yeah.
I'm just like,
being doing stuff,
doing the stuff that I do on the internet
does not in any way prohibit me
from doing other things in real life.
So, it's.
I don't think it's, it's like,
it feels like it prohibits him from doing other things.
I think it's just sort of a cloud over one's head
to like be switched on.
I mean, you know how he always like,
when you turn a camera to Munchy,
like he always does the funny thing.
Like I feel like that he's got that sort of like
the pressure to be a certain,
you know, he wouldn't like live stream him
just sitting around.
He's not that sort of person.
So, like the, any obligation that he has
to like be someone internet personality wise,
I think is what he was like
trying to distance himself from.
And I feel like you maybe are a little different
where you just feel like it's the same.
Real life in the internet is the same
and you're just doing whatever.
I do.
I do feel like real life in the internet is the same.
Like I guess on like a show or whatever,
I guess I do put on like a little bit of like,
I'll like bring my energy level up or whatever.
Or I'll, you know, I do like behave in a deliberate way
to like, you know, get good responses.
But like I do that normally in real life
when I'm just with people.
I'm like, if I'm like hanging out with someone,
I'll like, you know, try and like be funny or whatever
or try and be like, I don't know, entertaining
in the exact same way that I do, like on the internet,
it's the same to me, to me anyway.
When I'm in real life, I don't do anything.
I just sort of like float through an experience.
And when somebody says something to me, I go, huh?
What?
Yep, that's true.
That's true.
I heard it.
Yeah, just just mentioning to people who may have like
heard rumors of munchy and then this is,
that is just a explanation.
Well, okay, I feel like, I feel like I have now explained
how I, why this is like different
from how I would characterize these things.
But like I respect it, it's fine.
It's okay.
Yeah, same.
Yeah, dirt.
But I am a little upset because it's like,
cause I don't know if we're gonna finish our slime monopoly.
Ooh.
We're not gonna be able to finish slime monopoly.
Slime monopoly was so fun.
It was the funnest I've had in a long time.
Even when munchy fucking squatters rights me.
Even that.
It was so intense.
Yeah.
And the board was so cool.
I wish I could have stayed there for even longer.
You know, I thought it was probably about time
to quit playing that when you left anyway.
So I was like, I kind of think this is good
that we have a reason to be like, all right, call it here.
We gotta judge the contest.
Well, heck.
I landed on the fucking get all of the money
spot thing, didn't I?
Piece of shit.
You landed on, was it community service?
Yeah, I got a community service or,
yeah, I said collect all the money from the thing.
No, no, no, no, I landed on the board.
Wait, I can't remember.
Yeah, you landed, yeah, you rolled a five.
You were like, if I roll a five,
I'm gonna land on community service.
And you did.
And you got like $800 from it.
Yeah.
I don't think it's called community service.
Like the community chest, money.
Kings ransom or something.
Oh, Kingpin's coffers.
That's the one.
Kingpin's coffers, that's right.
I got everything.
I could buy so many hotels.
That sucks.
That sucks so bad.
Yeah, we're fucked.
But I don't know, if Munchy wanted to come back.
That's the real reason Munchy is not coming back
because he doesn't want to have to face me.
If Munchy wanted to come back for a guest spot
on a slime monopoly episode two, I would love that.
But I don't know, I guess we'll see.
I guess we'll see.
Anyone that didn't, that didn't see,
if you want to go to twitch.tv slash
rowdyfricker's cop killers and watch.
I don't think, it's not the latest video.
It's the second the latest video
because I highlighted them in like a weird order.
But it was the slime fest, it's eight hours long,
but the first like half of it is us playing slime monopoly.
It's a custom monopoly board that Smirg made
with the help of like input from other people
in the RFCK community.
It looks so good.
It's like so custom, it's got like a new custom rule set
that there's like new cards and there's new like
mechanics added on to it.
There's like a slimeoid mechanic
that I don't think any of us ever got to really use,
but it's in there.
Even just having- The pieces are like pretty modeled
and they're so good.
They're so great.
I love the little Lord of Ghost model with the,
like you can look underneath like upskirt Lord of Ghost
and you can see that Smirg has models like the eyes.
I never did that.
I never, you were saying that,
but I never got around to peeking.
I wanted to, I was curious next time
if there is a next time.
I hope there'll be a next time.
I would like to finish that game.
Cause like, yeah.
Cause everyone says monopoly is like a terrible game
and like a boring game that just makes everyone mad.
And it's kind of true.
And yet it was like so tense that I was enthralled.
I was on the edge of my seat.
It makes everyone mad,
but people play it with their family
and you don't want to be mad at your family.
When you have like a rival, a friendly rival
in like rowdy fucker cop killer sort of situation,
then it's fun.
Cause friends don't play monopoly,
only families do, which is always wrong.
When Munchy squatters writes me,
I was legitimately upset and could not,
like I could not talk for a while
cause I was like too mad.
You were like switched off.
I was seething.
And we were like, oh my God.
What is it?
He can't even speak.
And you just said, like, I'm looking up the rules.
Yeah, so it was like so dead.
He fucking got me.
I mean, it was, it was like cheap.
It was really cheap.
But like he didn't say that he was moving,
but it's technically not against the rules.
You don't technically have to say what you're doing.
And he fucking robbed me of like 50 bucks
that should have been mine.
But hey, that's capitalism, I guess.
Lamal.
Good times.
I don't know.
You want to go to voicemails?
Yeah, we've been going for an hour and a half.
Hour and hour 15.
Do you have anything else to say about stuff?
This now would be the time to do it.
No, no, I'm just like,
I'm really over.
I'm really over not having delivered on my kick starters.
And I'm really impatient for those fucking books to get here.
So I can fucking do that.
You should do an unboxing video of getting the books.
Oh, maybe I could.
Maybe I could, you know what I really want to do?
I keep thinking about this and every time I think of it,
I'm like, yeah, that is a good idea.
I want to do like cooking videos.
I want to do like a series of like.
I would love to see how how Ben makes like the gummies
and keto pizza and all of these weird things that you've come up with
and you talk about, but like, I want to see it.
Yeah, I feel like.
Yeah, like my the pepperoni crust is like a it's like a Ben invention.
Nobody else does it, but it works great.
And it's and it's all and it's all me.
I invented it and why not make a video being like,
here's how I here's how I do it, lol.
The worm.
I mean, the worms is such like a strange thing
that like no human being does.
I feel like, yeah, that probably deserves to be documented in some form.
But I would have to clean my kitchen because my kitchen, my my kitchen,
my kitchen is filthy, but I but I can handle it.
Yeah, I don't know.
I keep I keep thinking about that.
Probably when I have some free time and nothing better to do,
I will I will do that because because why the fuck not?
Oh, I haven't got nothing to say.
Let's do voicemails. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, let me get this side up.
That's a fuck. What is it?
Is it big pipe dot com slash?
T. P. Crescinators.
Is it the procrastinators?
I will look it up on the procrastinators podcast dot com.
It is speak it.
No, no, speak pipe dot com slash PCP voicemail.
Lol, is how you send us a frigging voicemail for us.
Keep getting it wrong.
I do too, because I keep thinking it's like the Twitter.
It's T. P. Crescinators.
But no, PCP voicemail, PCP voicemail.
Oh.
Do you see that?
I think the first one is voicemail Lord Tards.
You ready?
Uh huh. OK, three, two, one, go.
Two episodes ago, some guy called in
autistically screeching about, quote, unquote, the voicemail god
submitting his persona five voicemails.
You frigging idiot.
That's tiny Timmy.
Don't you fucking remember the whole arc
of giving him a name and shit, bro?
Come on. Of course we don't.
Because I don't know.
I don't know who either of those people are.
I've never heard. I don't know.
Lore, we have lore now.
Very confusing.
Yeah, you know what?
I'm going to give you lore and I'm going to forget it immediately.
You are dumb.
Dead, die, crushed.
Um, OK, next up.
Cringe conjurer three, two, one, go.
Somebody was asking about recognizing your own cringe
so that you can do based and it reminded me of an amazing story.
I think you guys would appreciate.
So I would go to Friday Night Magic, which is when you go to your
comic shop to play Magic the Gathering with other losers.
And we were playing one day and there is a table of people playing Pokemon
and this one guy walks in and he was, I swear,
the star football player of our high school and he walked in
with a Pokemon shirt and his little deck box of Pokemon cards
and the shopkeeper was like, hey, what's up, state champ?
And everybody was like, oh, yeah, this guy's the fucking state
champion of Pokemon, bro.
Oh, he's so good.
He made eye contact with me and my fucking nerdy friends
from the same school and it looked like he saw a ghost.
It was hilarious.
He pulled us outside and fucking freaked out
and was like begging us and like he would offer to buy us packs
if we didn't tell anybody.
That's so lame.
So, yeah, you got to own your own cringe because if you don't,
that's the cringiest thing of all.
That's so lame to be like, please don't tell anyone.
Please don't tell my friends.
So that's so sad.
I missed.
So you said baseball champion at school or something?
Some story.
I don't think he mentioned which sport it was.
Yeah. So sports kid, alpha Chad kid.
Exposed for liking and Pokemon and being good at it as well.
Being state champ.
State champ.
That's that's like that's like a big deal.
I think that's straight out of like a like a sitcom.
That's situation that is.
That's like it's like light Yagami walked into my card store
and say, hey, what's up?
You're going to make you finally made it to nationals
in fucking Magic the Gathering.
Uh, it's like, um, yeah, it is.
That's very, that's very sitcom.
I was pleased.
That's that is cringe.
That I should have been like, like, oh, my God,
this guy has really good sports.
He's also really good at Pokemon.
That just means he would get more popular
with all the kids who like Pokemon.
I thought I thought it was going to be.
I didn't think we were going to go in the like, oh, and he was like,
oh, no, please don't tell anyone.
Like that seems, honestly, I'm not sure I believe it.
That's that's trans my credulity.
Imagine being because like what if you're like fucking
star quarterback or whatever, if you're Alpha Chad, why would you be
so insecure about like being state champ at Pokemon cards?
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe maybe like they get pressure from the like dad to be the sports kid.
And they're like, OK, dad, I'll do what you wanted to do, but couldn't.
OK, I'll do it.
Sports kid. They did.
Yeah, yeah, they did it because they like, but maybe they don't like it.
Maybe they hate it, but they're just that, you know, pressure to do it.
They secretly want to be a Pokemon kid.
You can't you can't be star quarterback and hate it that much.
Right. I mean, maybe.
I don't know. I've never played an entire sport.
But yes, own it.
Not owning your cringe is the cringiest thing of all.
Yeah, I think we can all agree that that's true.
Mm hmm.
Um, OK, next one, men and women.
Huh? What? What?
I was just going to say, he should have like seeing his friends.
He should have just given him a wink.
It's like, yeah, you know, oh, see, I mean, seeing these nerds
at the table, seeing these nerds that he recognizes from his school,
he should have just like winked like, yeah, I mean, yeah,
that would have been a cooler thing to do with his hair bangs.
It would have been more based, but unfortunately,
but, you know, that's not the world we live in.
Uh, OK, men and women, three, two, one.
Oh, right. Let me get the record straight.
Uh, men are like,
and when we're like, do you understand it now?
I go, OK.
What? What?
What I have only before understood on a sort of emotional visceral level
now has been put into words for me to be communicated.
I mean, like, true.
Fuck, yeah.
It's true. It's always been the case.
Mm hmm. That's that's just biology.
That's just science.
Um, uh, uh, oh, I want to say,
going going back to the Chris Chan's weird DMs in in the.
In the Chris was arguing with Endless War
and it's really weird to me that she called Endless War on Twitter, Ben,
as though, like, Endless War is not a separate entity.
Like, I don't know why she would think that, like, Endless War is Ben.
Like, I don't like just like, you know, she is Chris Chan Sonichu
and like a nightstar is like a separate entity from that, you know?
So I don't know why she wouldn't like they call Endless War Endless War,
because that's his name.
So that's confusing to whatever.
But there's the part where she's claiming that, like, oh, no, it was the Omega timeline.
She made some replies.
I didn't read them.
But so the Omega timeline and, you know, Endless, not me, Endless War,
like posts a picture of the of the timeline from Slime and Punishment.
And he's like, you know, the diet, it's clearly labeled.
This is the alpha timeline.
You know, I'm sorry, but the science just checks out on this one.
And a couple of people like that and thought it was pretty funny.
And I was like, yeah, that's pretty endless war.
That's a good, good one.
I like that. Endless War, like, uses Twitter.
He's got like no hands.
How does he do it?
Endless War. Yeah. Endless War uses Twitter.
And like until now, he mostly just retweets like cool slime.
Like he mostly just like will just retweet anything that like is like, oh,
yeah, that's pretty slimy. Oh, yeah, that's green. I like that.
But, you know, now the war is on.
So I think he might he might get a little more active snarky.
You might. Yeah, a little bit.
You might have a little more.
He might have some some opinions to share at Endless War.
I think it's at Endless War.
I think it's his handle on Twitter.
Follow him. He's good. He's a good boy.
OK, next one.
It's cringe, but it's sincere.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
Just wanted to say thanks for all the content you put out over the years.
Been watching some of your vids since the pony days,
but only got into the podcast back in 2017
when I got my cushy programming job.
I binge listen to it a lot, especially when things were quieter than usual
in the office, made the days a lot less monotonous.
And I also went to the dentist for surgery the other day.
It wasn't fun.
More so since I had to wear full PPE because of the rona.
But I was able to sneak in my phone and earphones.
And I listened to one of your older episodes,
which made the experience less terrible overall.
So, yeah, thanks for the podcast, the videos, the comics,
the music and the games that you all have put out.
Really good stuff.
Oh, and special thanks to Ben, Tom and Gibb for holding down the fort,
so to speak for a while.
Hope the others are OK.
That's all. Bye.
That's really nice.
Yeah, thank you.
I got I got nothing to say other than cool.
Sorry about the surgery.
I myself am terrified of dentistry
and surgery in specific.
So I will have to think of something to I will have to find something
to listen to to help me deal with that shit.
Just just record your own voice,
saying things that aren't related to dentistry and listen to that.
Boy, I don't want to think about it.
I don't think about it.
OK, next.
Anyway, thanks. Thank you.
We're doing our best.
Doing our best.
Next up is several discontent fish.
Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa. God damn it.
I am Osamurai.
This fucking asshole.
I'm a sensei of Benno Cento, sir.
And clearly, very much a dedicated to this joke.
Benno, son, you said the cranno no longer need you for we have
a miscellaneous tea, son, sura pricey.
It was a note on Mr.
Teal, but to me, haha, epic to roll.
This is a one of the two.
Each in Osamurai revenge scheme.
On the table, Benno, son,
for a pale, yellow boy, you pussy for Shinobi penis.
Whoa, OK, until you next time.
Sayonara. So this has taken a turn.
I mean, up until now, I thought he wanted me to come home.
But now he's I think he's just like, nah, we're going to rape you.
You took too long. That's what happened.
I just I didn't I wanted to be.
I wanted to learn ninjutsu.
I wanted to learn ninjutsu because I saw Naruto and I was like, yeah, that.
And I couldn't I couldn't be I couldn't I couldn't continue my samurai training.
You know, it would be illegal.
It would be illegal to do both.
You know, I made I made my choice.
And I guess, you know, there's consequences to every action.
It's the it's equal equal and opposite.
Newton's Third Law or whatever, supply and demand, equivalent exchange,
all these things, the world is a fuck to bazillion dead cops.
I like I like that the Mr. T was actually him doing a voice.
And he got you.
He must have used some sort of he must have used some sort of genjutsu
to become Mr. T.
Typical.
Well, that's distressing.
But just like the dentist, probably best just not to think about it.
Next up, we got another one from from Margar,
who was who was a shouted down and mocked mercilessly last episode
by all by all of our esteemed guests.
So let's hear his response to that three to one.
Margar here, I was regretfully unable to attend the last episode of the PCP
due to my confinement in voice jail.
It's still bad in here.
There are still rampaging bandits and marauders sent by presumably Ben St.
But we're doing the best we can here.
I'm starting to make friends, starting to make plays.
Maybe I'll rise up in the ranks and we'll see what happens.
The violent revolution did not go according to plan.
I need more supporters.
We're we're trying.
Also, the PCP, good luck with the whole having 50 people in one episode thing.
Let's see how that works out for you.
I'm not sure of the plan or the idea, but maybe it'll work out.
Good luck. No, it worked out.
You you were the only victim.
They they the the people, you know, we've split the audience.
And that segment of the audience is very much very much pro state,
you know, pro fascist police state,
you know, anti anti liberation.
You know, they do not support our prisoners rights.
So, you know, I'm sorry, that must be very distressing for you.
But it is what it is.
And sad, give what do you say to Margarh here?
Get on the ground.
That's what I said on the ground.
Yeah, give me drop and give me 50.
Drop and give me 100.
Good, good, good luck in there.
Drop and give me a hundred dollars.
I will send some more fucking ruffians to rough you up some more.
If you if you would like, I can I can do I can send more of those
or I can send the same amount of it's let let me know.
Let me know your choice.
Next up, quick scoper champion of PCP Minecraft.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, could you please play more Minecraft service kind of that out here
with no players online for what feels like months?
It would be much appreciated if you streamed more frequently
since that last stream was kind of let down for it had been a three months
wait with the channel takedown and they just disappearing from the podcast
without word.
I really want to serve to succeed as MeronPen,
the only admin online on the server right now have been working hard
on adding more facilities like Pokemon centers, gyms and even more trainers
to battle. Also, it would be pretty cool if you could advertise the server
more by either mentioning it or just playing on it.
Well, I guess this is the way I say goodbye.
Oh, God, fucking Arceus is going to rape me.
No, please.
Is that what Arceus sounds like?
I suppose so.
Well, sad.
What do you think about Minecraft server?
I guess we should advertise it more.
But like the way we advertise it.
Yeah.
The way we advertise it is mostly through the streams there, right?
Which one was it?
When did we do the last one?
It wasn't that long ago.
Was it? Maybe it was.
It was. I think it might have been.
I mean, let me let me let me let me let me let me let me let me.
The Procrastinators podcast.
I'm going to check it was we streamed it.
One week ago, maybe it was two weeks.
It was less than two weeks ago.
So I don't know.
Yeah, we went for a while without streaming.
OK, we went for a while without streaming
because we weren't using the channel because of the hack.
I do intend to stream checkers for heckles more now.
Maybe we could try.
Maybe we should have like a meeting and see if we schedule
like a like a regular like bi weekly thing or something.
Yeah, something like that.
I don't want to be the guy who streams again, though.
How come?
Because it's so laggy and terrible.
Like, I feel like it was unwatchable.
Hmm. I don't know.
I mean, I I personally hate responsibility.
But so. But I mean, if nobody else wants to do it,
I could do I could be streamer man.
I'm willing to I'm willing to step up and do that.
So, yeah, let's do that.
Let's do that soon.
Oh, I don't know.
I'll see. I'll say something in the chat later
and see what the interest level is and when we can maybe
when we can maybe get that fucking going.
Yeah, all right. OK.
Message received.
OK, next up, I'm just being cool.
parentheses proven.
So let's let's see what his proof is.
All right, three, two, one, go.
Hey, the PCP, I recently found in real life
in the wild an example of the I'm just being cool
crap where if you say something enough,
it suddenly becomes true, right?
Two rights make a real.
Yeah. And it comes in the form of this podcast,
as a local podcast, W-A-T-P.
Who are these podcasts?
W-A-T-P in the morning, everybody.
That podcast has a bit at the end where, you know,
basic conceit in case you're not familiar.
If they review podcasts, they review podcasts each week.
And basically, I've heard of the show kind of.
And they do this thing at the end of the week
or at the end of the show where it's the teaser for next week.
Right. So they play like they play this drop.
They play this like 10 or 20 second drop
and then a couple of seconds from the show they were reviewing next week.
And the joke is that the host, Carl, says to every guest who comes on,
you know, explains it to them in great detail,
as if everyone doesn't already know what a teaser is.
And then proclaims insistently that this is the best part.
Everyone looks forward to this.
This is their favorite part, and he gets, you know, voice mails.
And over the course of listening to this podcast,
it just got funnier and funnier until it just.
I love the teaser.
And ironically, next week's teaser, I love.
He made it. He made it true.
Next week's teaser. It's great.
OK, folks, see you later.
Yeah, you just you just insist hard enough for long enough.
And it becomes funny to do it.
And if you do it ironically, you'll start to do it unironically.
This is this is this is.
Yeah, this is this is the theory behind I'm just being cool.
It's it's it works.
It works in every it works in literally every situation.
It's it's it's the secret, you know.
I should start saying that in real life.
I'm just being cool.
Yeah.
I don't, you know, I would say it in real life,
but I rarely have the opportunity to.
I know, it's the sort of thing where, like, you have to be caught
doing something that people like, hey, what are you doing?
And then you rip up with, hey, I'm just being cool.
I mean, no, I guess I feel like I would say that if someone
criticized me, I guess I just don't get criticized enough.
And that's a big problem.
That means I'm not pushing the envelope.
Well, maybe maybe the trick is is not to wait until they say something
because people try to be nice.
They don't want to say they'll give you a weird look and they'll think something,
but they won't like say anything.
So you just need to like, as soon as anyone walks in the room,
you just insist that I'm being cool before they even have a chance to
like, like, like think anything.
It's like they walk in the room and you're like, hey, hey, I'm just being cool.
And it like it would seem like, why is he saying that?
It seems suspicious.
But you do it long enough and people will be like, yeah, he's just being cool.
You know, you know, I got the, you know, actually.
Got a little I got a little I got a little drunk the other day.
I got a little sauce hanging out with some friends, got a little silly,
got a little stupid.
Honestly, that would have been a great time for me to bust out the, hey, guys,
I'm just being cool.
But I didn't.
I don't think I did, but it would have been super funny.
So I'm going to have to keep that in mind.
I'm going to keep that in mind for next time.
Next time I'm next time I act to the fool.
I will, in fact, I'm just throwing sand.
I'm just being cool.
And that's all you need to know.
Stop thinking about it, you idiot.
Yeah, it's a great line.
If you, hey, viewers, listeners, if you have ever,
if you have ever been criticized and just said, no, no, no, I'm just being cool.
Let us know how it worked, because I'm sure that it will.
I guarantee it'll get you out of it.
It'll get you out of a jam.
They'll go, oh, I see.
I apologize.
Excuse me.
You go to a protest and you say to the police, no, no, I'm just being cool.
I'm being cool.
They're like, oh, I guess he's being cool.
Damn, well, I don't want to be uncool.
You know, trans rights.
That's what they'll say.
Um, yeah.
So anyway, being cool base, not being cool cringe.
Next up, centrist voicemail three, two, one, go.
If the establishment, right, labor unions, corporations,
inter trade established black lists, you know what I mean?
Like if they all agree on something and they want to enforce their will
upon the workers of America, for example, they won't give you a job.
If you don't take the COVID-19 vaccine
already happening on Australia, already talking about it,
they might as well be like a form of government
because they own the means of production.
And if you can't get a job, you can't produce anything.
So you can't create value, which is required to live.
So in conclusion, we need to control the private corporations
and keep them from infringing upon our First Amendment rights
and our body autonomy.
Yeah. I mean, I agree.
I agree with that.
Um, is that centrist or is that a joke?
It's, um, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if I would characterize it as centrist.
That seems like it's an anti-capitalist thing to say.
That's like your anti, you want to limit the power of big business.
You want to regulate them.
That seems like, I mean, it's liberal.
It's it's like, you know, it's still like, OK, well, we're pro
business, just we can't we can't let them do these specific things.
I don't know. Um, I mean, yeah, people people give like,
you know, like you're an Ann Cap or whatever, you're a fucking
you're a fucking Libertarian or whatever.
You're like, uh, companies are not the government.
You know, companies are not bound by the Constitution.
Company like a corporation, you know, it's they're a private enterprise.
They can run their business however they want.
And like on some level, I guess that makes sense, but on a practical level,
like what if you what if you live in a society just for example, where the
government is relatively weak and private corporations are relatively strong
in terms of like influence they have over people's lives and the like the
practical effect of the way that they run their businesses is that, you know,
people are in effect having their freedoms limited, right?
Like people are, I mean, I think people probably should take the vaccine
if they if they if it works.
But like, you know, if the if a corporation is basically
basically making it impossible for someone not to do something that only
affects them and should be up to them, but they can't do it because they live
in a world that's controlled by fucking private interests and private
interests are wielding their power to, to, you know, influence society
in all these unjust ways, then you what is the what is the difference
between that and living under a tyrannical government?
Like there basically is none, you know, like maybe they don't control
the police, but if the police exist to protect their interests, which they do
to a greater degree than they protect anyone else's interests, then effectively
they have the private industry has police on their side and other people don't.
And that's been the way it's been for a long time, you know, police will like
police have been employed to, you know, break up, break up strikes and like,
yeah, like fucking bust skulls of like unions and stuff and like, you know,
get people working, declare strikes illegal and then like, you know,
attack protesters or whatever. This happens.
This is the world we live in.
So I yeah, I guess I would agree.
And I don't think that your voicemail is all that centrist.
And I can't tell I can tell that you're joking to some degree,
but I don't know if it's just the native of what you were saying,
or if it was just the name of the voicemail.
I don't know how much of it was a joke and I apologize.
OK, any anything to say about that?
Yeah, I generally agree.
I don't really know how like I would
like my exact stance on this this issue.
But like when I see big company, I say I hate you.
So that's that's my stance.
I mean, everybody big company.
I'm like, you should be smaller than that.
You shouldn't have that power.
Every everybody agrees that like monopolies are bad.
Everybody will agree to that on paper, but then they'll be like, oh, well,
you know, you can't like you can't like nationalize Amazon.
You can't like buy out Amazon.
You can't split that up.
You can't like bust that trust.
Everybody loves Teddy Roosevelt.
He was a trust buster.
He was a monopoly breaker.
Everybody thinks that was great.
But you suggest doing that today and the end caps like, no, you just want to
you just want to take Jeff Bezos's money.
He earned that you just want to steal people's money and give it to people
that don't work, like, shut up.
You know, even just saying that like you want to steal
somebody who works his money and give it to people who don't work as if
like Jeff Bezos is working like 10 billion times.
Not even that. Not even that.
It's it's it's it's as if like, like, I don't know, working is
tantamount to deserving to exist.
Right. Some people like can't work as much.
I don't know.
Like, should you kill a disabled person just because they can't work?
I mean, they're not contributing to the economy.
Yeah, I mean, that's the argument.
It's frankly, it's unethical for you to expect us not to kill them
when they're a drain on everyone else's resources.
That's a joke, by the way.
This is this is this is this is my straw man.
Uh, you know, I'm just fine.
Final thought about this.
I think about this a lot.
It's like, OK, you kind of like people, people like libertarians and caps.
They're like, oh, you know, socialism bad because socialism is totalitarianism.
You have to give the government all this power to do all this stuff.
And if the government has that much power, they'll be authoritarian.
It'll be tyranny and like, OK, in theory, I understand that concern.
But if you if you like what you basically have, you have to balance
the power of like private industry versus the government.
And I understand that a government can become tyrannical,
but at least the government in theory, at least in theory of the way
we construct it these days has some sort of check and balance
in the form of like people can be voted into and out of office.
And you know, that's a little blurry now because money
because like money is so involved in politics that like, you know,
that it's kind of you can sort of buy an election and that's bad.
Don't get me wrong.
That is bad.
But in theory, if it wasn't wasn't like that, if it were harder to just buy
an election, then it would probably be better if the government had power
versus had more power than private industry, because private industry
has no checks and balances, whatever, just some guy owns it
or some people own it and they can just do whatever they want.
They're not beholden to anyone except their shareholders versus at least
in theory, the government is like, okay, well, if they're bad,
we can unelect them.
That's how it should be, you know, so there.
I mean, a private company is basically it's basically just a little
a little like monarchy.
It's just a little like fucking tiny or not even it's just an isolated
little pocket of like feudalism where like one guy owns everyone below them,
you know, for eight hours a day, five days a week or whatever.
That's that's what a private company is.
Most of the time you live in a feudal a feudal
place.
I don't can't think of the words that you would use to describe
what it is that we us surfdom of Hamlet do radical base.
Yes.
Yes, surfdom, dudes.
Okay.
All right.
I spent a long time on that one, but you know what?
It was worth it.
Next one, if we're ready for it is called bring Nate back and I can't wait.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys, is it just me or is Nate hella cute?
Haha.
No homo though.
Why does Nate have the cutest laugh on the PCP law?
I don't know.
I just I do like it.
I do like it when I can make Nate laugh like uproariously.
Yeah.
I mean, I like it when I can make anyone laugh, but it is funny.
Hmm.
Uh, sure.
I mean, yeah, I guess I can't really disagree with this guy's point.
He's got that little like like like when he's trying when he's trying not like
I can't fucking do what I'm thinking if you listen to it.
It's like when he's trying like if I'm saying something funny or like
he's listening to something funny and he's starting he's starting to laugh,
but he's not letting himself like explode yet and he's got the he and then he
starts when I think when I think of Nate's when I think of Nate's laugh.
I think of like when he's like sort of he's laughing and he's genuinely laughing,
but he's sort of like he's sort of like putting on a little bit of a an air
about it.
He's sort of like sort of making a joke out of the laugh by sort of turning
it into a cackle where he goes like or something.
That's not a real laugh.
It's the real the real I usually get the impression that there is genuine
mirth there, but it's also he is affecting it a little bit like for a bit.
Uh, that that's more of like a aha.
Yes, I I see that was a joke sort of laugh.
Hmm.
Yes, indeed.
That's that's that the same sort of energy.
Perhaps perhaps.
Um, cutie though, major, major cutie pie that Nate Bestman.
Right.
Frankly, a huge audience straw.
And you know, without him, just, you know, property values of tanking.
Uh, I even stock market crash.
And I think it's because Nate hasn't been on the PCP in a while.
Where's Nate Giggling?
We need Nate Giggling on the PCP.
Yes, please.
Um, next one is from not a vampire.
Who, um, I should mention, I'll, I'll put a link in the description.
Not a vampire made a video about me called the emotional genius of Ben
Saint, which is a little embarrassing because I feel like self aggrandizing
to say that out loud, but it weren't, wasn't my words.
It was their words.
And so I liked that video.
It was very, um, uh, explain a, you know, a very analysis.
At first when I saw it, I was like, Oh, well, someone is praising me.
Excellent.
And I retweeted it, but I didn't watch it because I was like, I'm too embarrassed.
I'm too embarrassed to watch this video and hear what they're actually
saying about me.
I'm just going to assume that it's fine and put it out there and not watch it.
But I, I, I eventually was, I got curious.
I cracked, I did watch it and I was like, Oh, wow.
Oh, it's actually pretty nice.
Not that embarrassing.
I guess I, you know, I, am I allowed to say I agree with the points made?
Uh, I thought it was good.
It was, it was well, well written.
Yeah.
It was very, it was very personal, but like, um, the analysis was like easy
to understand from that perspective, why they think these things.
I'm like, yeah, I kind of feel that way too about Magda and stuff.
Yeah.
It made sense.
Uh, so anyway, link in the description.
Go check that out, but let's hear the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
This question is for Ben.
So a couple of us, let's go in the personal finance podcast.
You said that to you gender was just language.
So by that definition, do you consider yourself a gender by default?
Hmm.
Um, well, depends on what you mean by default.
I would get, well, you, you grow up in a world that it says boys and girls do
this and that, and you just sort of go with what you're told.
And then you continue on in that way without thinking.
So like kind of, I guess it depends on your upbringing.
Yeah.
I would, yeah, I wouldn't say it's automatic.
I would say generally most people will find themselves kind of slotted
into a group and just kind of go with that and that'll be their gender.
So that's sort of by default.
Um, I think no, I like, if our language was constructed
differently and like it wasn't required to refer to someone in a gendered way
with pronouns, like if pronouns just didn't work the way they do, I think
maybe gender would not be automatic and, and, um, people would be, and people
would maybe be more gender neutral by default because I, I do think that
it is mostly just about the language used.
Um, and so the way our language is constructed, you know, affects it.
Yeah.
Like, like even just titles like boy and girl, like you're necessarily, I mean,
when you're young, you certainly don't need to be split up because you're kids.
You don't know anything, but like, uh, there's, there's definitely arguments
to be made for like the separation for like teenage years.
It's a bit weird.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Um, sure.
But it's, uh, oh, there was this guy in my Twitch chat at one point who was arguing.
Um, he was arguing about like, uh, it was something about like free the
nipple, like girls should be able.
I saw, I saw some screenshots of this guy.
Oh yeah.
Um, and Kazi showed me Kazi.
Yeah.
Um, she was in there and arguing with him and it was like, I saw what he was going
for, but he was just sort of arguing from a point of like, like status quo is
what is like, like a circular logic, sort of the status quo is this.
Therefore, this is the status quo that I like, and I don't want it to change.
And he wouldn't like accept that maybe it could be better if it were to be changed.
And he's like, but no, it's that I don't like it because this is how it is.
And it should stay this way.
And you just wouldn't like, he wouldn't concede that potentially there is benefit
in changing how the, how the, you know, the current system.
I feel like most people have that sort of viewpoint where like they imagine that
if, you know, people talking about changing society in certain ways
would be like a snap of the fingers and then suddenly everything is different
and everything they knew was a lie.
Yeah.
And you'll go to jail and you'll go to jail if you don't agree with it.
And it's like, it's sort of like, oh my God, I don't want anything to change
because stuff could bad happen to me.
And it's like, it's not, it's not really about like it happening right now.
It's about like, could you consider a future in which, you know, hypothetically,
this is the system.
You don't have to live in it.
But like, could you accept that there may be benefits?
Yeah.
Like maybe we could try to go in that.
Like it's, it's one thing to be like, there's a real lack of imagination
going around.
A lot of people are just, yeah, it's no imagination.
Visceral, like negative reactions to things are like understandable.
Like we all understand that if you grow up in a society that says this,
then this other thing that is completely new and alien to you is going to like
be the wrong way.
You're going to be like freaked out and scared by it because the unknown is scary.
So it's like, I get it.
But like, you got to look past that at some point and understand that you're
always going to be scared of stuff.
You don't know what it is and you can't know for sure that any certain thing
anything like is like certain bad or good until you think about it.
And if you never think about it, you just like, oh, I what man turned into woman?
That's gross.
Yes.
It grosses me out.
It's yucky.
It's yucky and they dye their hair and I don't, and I think that's stupid.
Um, I feel like I feel like I could say more about that.
It's like, um, it's it's like that that guy was saying like, um, the nipple should
be not free because it's because I would get aroused by seeing female nipples
and I don't want that and that's not fair.
That's like, it's violent against me for like women to show their nipples
because it will cause this something to happen to me that I do not want to
happen.
Well, yeah, it's it's his argument was that he would make people feel
uncomfortable if people walked around naked half naked and it's like true.
You know, if they did it right now, if people lived up, grew up in a world
where, you know, um, that the the the chair, like a bare chest of a person
is not inherently scary.
Like a human person, a man can have a bare chest and you don't really think
about it.
You're just like, oh, it's must be a hot day.
You know, he's taking a shirt off.
Um, and a woman doing that is completely different, but it isn't completely
different.
It's just society has taught us that is it is completely different and because
it's completely different, it's different.
It's strange.
It's new.
It's fearful.
You get scared of the idea.
I mean, the argument he was putting forth was, you know, Boner City, which
I was like, why, why was that be a bad thing?
But like, I understand that some people don't don't want that.
Right.
So like uncomfortableness.
It's it's like an inevitability of a society where it would be uncomfortable
to do a thing, but you got to think of the inheritance.
Like what is inherently wrong with that?
What, why is it uncomfortable?
And you got to think of like similar things that are not a problem.
And why are they not a problem is because society has put that in there.
Like, oh, we, you know, somebody doesn't wear a hat.
Well, that's normal.
We used to all wear hats.
It used to be like seen as like stupid to not wear a hat.
Yeah.
And it's like society can change.
It's just we don't inherently need hats.
We don't inherently need to wear things on our chests when it's hot.
I mean, this guy, if this guy were a frickin if this guy were a frickin Muslim,
would he be in this chat being like it's it's wrong for women not to like wear
the hijab because it's like it's like it's too tempting.
Like it's too tempting for men.
They'll get boners seeing like pretty girl faces and that's violence.
That's violence against me.
It's the same argument.
It's literally the same.
I think he was like saying Muslims have the right idea at some point.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Cool.
But I don't know.
I don't know how much he was joking about that because I wasn't really paying
too much attention.
Sure.
I was busy drawing.
I don't want to shit on that guy, by the way.
He's I don't think he's like like a terrible person.
I just think he's not thinking about this very hard.
Well, I, Cassie was annoyed about it and she was complaining about it to me
and I was like, hmm, sounds pretty annoying.
It was pretty annoying.
I mean, sure.
Sure.
I mean, people are allowed to have bad opinions.
I think that's a pretty bad opinion, but you know, whatever.
Yeah, whatever.
It's fine.
No, no biggie.
Um, well, fuck.
We're at the end.
That's all the voice mails.
We made it.
Well, thanks for, thanks for listening to another low energy to man to two
man, to person, to person.
Lol.
It's very strange.
Man turned into woman.
That's gross.
Disgusting.
I've turned into woman.
I'd just be strange.
I'd be halfway there.
I'd be halfway.
I'd be non-binary and I'm on my way and I'm feeling, feeling, feeling real gay.
Um, that's, uh, that's the show, everybody.
Yeah.
Go, go to, uh, before PCP, go to give and take dot site where I might, but by this
point, I may have the, no, wait, I may, I don't know.
Go to, go to medibang.com, read the Clarissa, buy it if you want.
How do they, how do they find it on medibang?
Um, link in the description.
Link in, link in the description.
I think if you go to medibang and you look for the Tezca contest, you can just
look at the submissions and then I'm, I think I'm on page two, uh, of the most
recent submissions because there's been a lot already.
Like, so there's the last few days.
So it's like a, everyone's submitting right at the late, the end.
Right.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
Um, there's like all these voicemails come in and like the last 24 hours before
the show, haha.
Uh, it's, it's, uh, it's crunch time.
It's crunch time, baby.
All right.
Cool.
Um, well, hey, bonus episodes.
Oh God, we didn't do a bonus episode this month.
Did we?
Did we not?
I don't remember.
I don't remember either.
We'll figure it out.
Uh, bonnet, but there's like, um, there's like fucking 30 plus bonus episodes for
your enjoyment on, uh, patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Is it the procrastinators?
Is it TP procrastinators?
No, it's the procrastinators on Patreon.
The procrastinators, uh, for only $5, you can get in on that.
It is cheap as free almost.
Uh, it is cheap as free except for the money.
Except for the little bit of money that has to change hands in order to make that
happen.
Um, yeah, send us a voicemail, scrap on Patreon, uh, join the Minecraft server.
Link in the description to the Minecraft server, which we will, we will stream
again.
Uh, I'll, I'll say definitely, definitely we will do it during the month of
September, uh, for sure.
May hope I would like to do it twice during the month of September.
Yeah, twice.
It should be easy.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let's, let's, let's, let's soft commit to that.
Um, all right.
And thanks for listening, everyone.
And I'll see you, uh, in the next one.
Uh, uh, peace and love.
Bye.
Goodbye.