I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Okay, without further ado, hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, episode 305.
Ben Saint, Gibbontake, and Oblivionfall is here.
Welcome back, been a little while.
Uh, I get it, alright, everyone shut up, everyone shut up.
Okay, thanks, I just gotta start with the announcement.
This week, Phantom's Revenge, Phantom's Revenge is out, by the time you're listening to this,
Slime and Punishment is done, Phantom's Revenge is out, link in the description to the comic and the game if you just want to play the game.
I'm hitting my head, stayed up all night last night.
The last three days, let me just tell you what I've been doing this last week.
I finished drawing the ending, and I was like, it's done.
And then I was like, okay, I just gotta end it.
And then I'm like, I don't know how to end it.
I don't know what do I want the actual last panel to be.
And I've just kind of been sort of like, sitting around and like staring at it and trying to think of like, the story's done.
Just like, what do I want to put right before I have a big thing that says the end?
And I've just been like, uh...
You have Phantom Horn transports back in time and it's episode one of T-Bap.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
You spoiled it, again.
Oh, sorry, I'm just so media literate.
I couldn't help it.
I've just been trying to decide on something because I don't want to do a thing, right?
The story's over. It's time to end it.
So I've just been thinking like, what do I do that's not that hard?
I don't want to go on a thing, but what would be appropriate?
What would wrap things up?
I was like, I don't know.
Nothing fancy.
A thematic.
Doesn't have to be too fancy.
An icon.
Just like, there it is.
It's like, oh, that's the Phantom Horn's favorite Beyblade.
Remember all those times?
Like laying on the ground, like a close-up of it.
Like laying on the table and you think about like, yeah, I remember the whole Beyblade
like subplot that he had around like chapter six or seven.
Like, that was my favorite.
Yeah, I should just go back.
I should just make the ending panel just the end with like a picture of a Beyblade.
If you don't listen to this episode of the podcast, you won't get it.
And you still won't get it, even if you do.
Anyway, I've settled on something that I think is like fine.
So I'm just, I'm like mostly done with it.
And like, I'll probably finish it like tonight.
Yeah, so this week, it's over.
The nightmare is over.
That's it.
And maybe next week, maybe next week, we can talk about it since it will have been out
and hopefully maybe you'll have played it or something.
I will definitely stream it when it comes out.
Hell yeah.
Oh, that'll be fun.
Oh, that'll be really fun.
And I'll be like, what do I do?
And people will be in chat, like patrons of yours, they'll be like, I know.
I really want to, let me know when you're doing that because I would like to observe some of it.
I think that would be really funny.
Probably like, probably only like a dozen or so people have played it so far.
Maybe a dozen in my Patreon Discord server that's had access to it.
I actually made some, I might have mentioned this, I made some minor changes to the final version.
The final version has the damage numbers like have like a visual shake effect on them when like,
when you do lots of damage, the number gets really big and it like jostles around.
And like, that's it.
But other than that, it's the same game.
Looks pretty cool.
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
So it's literally done and like, there couldn't be like a complication that would mean that this is incorrect what you're saying right now.
I would have to fail to draw like one small image for like an entire week.
And like, I don't think I'm going to fail to do that.
I don't know.
It's still not literally technically complete.
Yeah, well.
What if it's too hard to say goodbye and you don't want to finish it?
That's how I feel.
That is how I feel.
But I'm going to do it anyway.
It's actually going to, I was thinking about the index that I want to put in the book, like the end of the book.
I think I mentioned this before.
I want to have like a, an infinite jest style like index section with like footnotes so that like every time there's a reference in the in the comic.
I have a little footnote and then you can, if you want, you can flip back to the index section and read and it'll I'll be like, oh yeah, this character is this guy or like the reason this shot looks like this is because it's a parody of this or whatever.
And I'm just thinking about that.
And like, that's going to be huge.
It's actually going to be like really extensive.
I could see that being like maybe a quarter of the whole book will just be like notes about like, why is it like this?
The more I think about it, the more I realize that being like hard to understand and inscrutable and perplexing is sort of the whole mission statement of it.
And so it's like fine.
It's not, it's not a, it's not a problem.
It's not a flaw.
It's, it's the, it's the work functioning as intended.
If you don't understand it, but if, but if you want the, the joy of discovery to understand it, the index in the book will hopefully be a fun read for people.
I'm looking, I'm looking forward.
I'm really looking forward to putting that together.
That's going to be fun.
That's nice.
I mean, that I have felt like it's usually in regards to like YouTube as like a platform.
I think of like how it, it didn't always used to be like a career path.
And now it is almost entirely a career path.
If you're not making a popular video, why would you make anything?
And, and that's like a mindset lots of people have.
I certainly have felt it where it's like, yeah, but I know that I could be making bank if I just did something different.
Yeah.
Oh, what the fuck?
Why, like all art has to be extremely successful.
It doesn't actually need to be that way, but like there's a lot of pressure.
There's not, there's a lot of pressure to like make it appealing and to a large audience and all that.
And it's, it's cool that you have, you've stuck it out to make the most obscure thing possible.
I think, yeah, like, I don't know, I'm just, it's just, it's just what I was going to do anyway.
And I'm just like, well, it is what it is.
And I just got to lean as far into it, whatever it is as possible.
And I don't know, maybe hopefully the people that like it will really appreciate it and all buy books and all have some money.
Yeah.
Maybe my next thing will be a little more, a little more universal.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to do after this.
Maybe I'll go back and finish Beast Capades.
Beast Capades.
Beast Capades had that twist ending that I had in mind since the very beginning and that I would really like to show people at some point.
So maybe that's what I'll do.
I like Beast Capades.
I remember reading it the first time through and it's like how he goes on his little Beast Capade.
Right.
It's a beast and it's like, oh, the stuff happened.
Whoa.
And then he spoiler.
Whoops.
Bleep that.
Eliza.
Oh, that's okay.
But it's sort of like, it doesn't go much into what happens next.
And I'm like, oh, there's like hints at cool lore.
And I just don't really have enough.
I don't have enough yet to even ask questions.
Yeah.
There was, I mean, I had some, I won't say what they were, but like some, some of the stuff in there.
Was, um, I kind of just, well, there's a, there's a mix.
Some things I put in Beast Capades.
I, like, I know exactly where they're going and I know what they mean.
And I'm just not going to say it yet.
Some of it was just like stuff that I threw in randomly.
And maybe sometimes I would sort of, uh, sort of suggest that it is important without really
any idea of that it would ever be important.
So it's kind of like a mix of the two things and, uh, I don't know.
I thought, uh, that was a fun way to, to go about it.
Like I've said, I know, I know where it ends and I know some of the steps along the way.
I think the, I think the most, uh, uh, or a problem or an annoyance that I might face getting back into
Beast Capades that I would have to, I would have to reread all of it just to like figure out,
okay, where was I and like what, what was the like micro step of the adventure that we were on
and how was I intending to resolve it?
Cause I kind of forget.
I forget exactly what was happening, uh, at the end and like what the immediate goal was.
I, I, I only had the broad strokes, like really, like really, really fleshed out in my head.
I'm sure there will be beasts and escapades.
Probably.
Yeah.
Most likely.
Uh, now you know, God, this is a scary thought.
But Beast Capades is the kind of story that I could, one could really imagine someone going ahead
and making like a tie-in video game for.
Uh-oh.
I hope I don't, I hope that doesn't happen.
Uh, yeah.
It's like the opposite of Pokemon.
Right.
You're making the manga first.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Um, it's kind of embarrassing how many of my projects are like heavily homestuck based.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, mine are as well.
Bailjack is, is just that thing.
Yeah.
It's more like problem sleuth, I guess, cause there's no like dialogue, but it's that thing.
It's that like just fuck around and, uh, cool shit happens.
Right.
Oh, that's homestuck.
If you fuck around and cool shit happens, it's probably homestuck.
It's just homestuck.
Uh, I mean, there's a lot of, there's a lot of homestuck in, uh, in slime and punishment.
I just, I took, took the, the mask just fell off when I named the video S-Rivert.
I was just like, ah, fuck it.
I don't care.
Yeah.
It doesn't even make sense that it's called that.
I mean, I did that for, I feel like there's just sort of a lot of homestuck stuff in,
uh, Endless War.
I mean, I made that, uh, what was it?
S-Descend or like Negus Slime Descend?
Yeah.
You know what that, you know what that is probably why, I don't know if I like consciously
was like, I have to keep the, the naming conventions consistent between those two videos, but I think
maybe on like a semi-conscious level, that is why I called it S-Rivert.
Yeah.
And we could always say the S stands for slime.
Absolutely.
Of course.
What else?
Uh, Oblivion.
Yo.
Since you're here, I wanted to ask how your project is coming.
My project is going pretty good.
I finished another shot, which, uh, I guess I can share it with you, but I don't know if
I can show the audience because it's Patreon exclusive still.
Right.
Sure.
But I've been changing up, I've been changing up my animation process.
Um, cause, oh man, it was, it was slow before.
Um, I guess to summarize how I started the project, I would do a sketch and then in flash
Adobe anime, I would like trace over it with the line tool and I would just use my mouse
to very carefully move vector lines around.
Um, and that was my method of animating.
And it's really, really fucking slow.
Yeah.
But it looks.
Drawing with vectors sounds like a very special sort of hell.
I know.
But, but it does give me like a lot of like really, really, really fine control over the
movement.
Like I can get the easing and everything exactly right.
From what I've seen, they, they, uh, it's just like incredibly smooth.
You don't, do you not like have a rough sketch of like the keyframes before?
Um, I sort of, yeah, I do have a rough sketch of the keyframes first.
Um, and that's what I did for the first loop of my character, uh, dancing around.
Uh, okay.
And then the new method I tried was like, I'm going to try doing puppet animation where
I just draw a bunch of pieces and I move them around with tweens.
So I did that for an animation of my character shaking her butt around.
And that looked all right.
Um, but it was kind of robotic.
And for this next shot, I kind of did half and half.
And I was able to get it done in one week, which is pretty good.
And it looks really good.
And I will send it to you both if I can remember how to DM people on discord.
Okay.
Clarify this for me.
Uh, cause I'm dumb.
Yes.
You draw with, you were drawing with vectors.
Were you doing frame by frame animation that was drawn with vectors?
Or were you like tweening the vectors to create the motion?
Uh, now that's one of the things that changed.
So before it was frame by frame, I drew the first frame, I drew the last frame.
And then I kind of like, cause that seems like the advantage of drawing with vectors is
that you could just transform the vectors directly.
Yeah.
And silly me, I didn't do that the first time.
Ah, I see.
Um, I would like manually like find the halfway point and then I would like break it down
and increments to more and more like halfway points until, you know, it moves smoothly
from one to the other.
Um, what I did this time is I used a lot of shape tweens, which are usually the fucking
devil in flash.
Um, if you try to shape tween something, it'll look just fucking awful.
Um, I wonder if I have.
I wonder if I can find it a good example.
If I just Google shape tween, give flash and see if there's like, we can see how fucked
up these things look.
I mean, a shape tween is a, is a transformation of one shape into another.
Yeah, it's like, it's sort of.
Does it take individual points on the shape and then map them to the other shape?
Yeah, sort of.
The problem is the way it does that is completely like fucked up.
It doesn't know which points should be mapped to which points.
So like part of your character's ear will turn into the foot.
Um, and like part of like their left finger will become like the fucking belly button
or some shit.
And so like the, like between the first and last frame, like the, like you'll have a,
the first frame is like a normal character and then you just have a whole bunch of fucking
gobbledygook and then it turns into the same character again at a very similar pose.
Just everything got fucked up in the meantime.
Um, but.
Yeah, it's weird.
I remember like in flesh doing that and being like, why, and how does it choose what points
of the vector like go in a straight line to the net to the end point?
It just sort of flips over itself and like just becomes a mush of like weird lines and
shape all connected.
And then it just sort of flattens out and becomes the, the final key frame.
I don't know how it chooses that.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
You were just like, pick a random point.
You have to, you have to ask a, you'd have to ask crack or someone who knows like how
computers calculate stuff.
Like you would think it would be like, oh, the, the closest point would go to the, you
know, the straightest line, shortest distance or whatever, but they just seem to go all
over the place.
Yeah.
Trying to, to interpolate something and they don't know where to go.
Let me export a GIF.
I just like made one right now.
Hell yeah.
Let's do it.
We don't need, we don't need a lot of colors in here.
Transparency required.
No transparency required.
I, I say, uh, as a HR, HR director of Amazon corporation.
All right.
I'm going to drop Ben saint.gif into the, uh, the chat right now.
I hope it doesn't look extra fucked up because of how discord handles gifts.
Yeah.
Like why do that?
Where do they decide these things come from?
Um, I guess.
Why are points from the, the right side of the screen going all the way down to the left
side?
All right.
So I know a little bit about this just from fucking around a bit a lot.
So what I'm doing when I do this stuff is I'm not using like solid vectors.
I'm actually using the line tool, which is like a single vector that, that doesn't have
a fill and you just give it a width.
Um, and those have very few vector points.
Um, and I think what it is, is some kind of vector point hierarchy.
Um, it looks at the order that the vector points were drawn and like numbers them and
it tries to match like the same number to the numbers in the next shot.
So if I draw the leg first and then I draw the head first in the next shot, it'll probably
like put parts of a leg, leg to the head or something.
Maybe.
That's just how I assume it works on a small scale.
Cause when I'm doing this, um, one of the things that I did to make the shape tweens
behave is I did everything in pieces.
Like the arm is a separate layer.
Um, the hand is a separate layer of the, um, you know, the shoulders, the eyes, the hair,
everything is like different layers, um, that are all tweened individually.
Um, and, and then the gift that I sent you, um, you know, in DMs, like one example, you
know, cause I have my character lift up her arm.
Um, what I actually did is I shaped tween to her arm in place.
Um, from like, I drew the beginning frame, I drew the ending frame and then I moved
the ending frame on top of where the beginning frame was.
I shaped tween it in place and then I put that animation in a symbol and then had it rotate
that way the rotation wasn't part of the shape tween.
That was like me just moving the object afterwards.
Uh, cause shape tweens also don't handle rotation as well.
Um, instead of, instead of a thing spinning around, it'll just kind of like stretch, uh,
weirdly.
Um, and I can probably show an easy example of how that works.
I'm going to draw a fucking funny looking axe.
You mean her, her, her front, her front forearm and her hand, that was shaped tween?
Um, yeah, her, the front, like the front part of her forearm was shaped tween.
Also, her hand was also like, so I, yeah, the hand was also shaped tween.
Um, and each finger was actually shaped tween individually.
Um, so I know it was, it was painful.
It took, it took a couple hours, but it resulted in, it ended up behaving a lot better.
I mean, it looks, I mean, it looks pretty good.
It's a, it's a, it's a pretty natural looking motion.
Yeah.
Um, and it's not to say that like it was all tweens, like, uh, I think the pinky finger
on the right side, uh, it curls and shaped tweens don't know how to fucking handle rotation.
So, um, I actually had the break that down into like steps, uh, and then like shaped tween,
like for steps.
Um, and even then, like, I just kind of, a lot of the time.
For the curling of one pinky finger.
Um, oh my gosh.
It's not even worse than I imagined.
Sorry.
I just shaped tweened an axe.
It's rotating.
An axe?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just wanted like some kind of recognizable shape.
Um, I don't know.
Let me say this as a gift and put that in chat as well.
So many gifts for Eleazar to put in the episode.
Yeah.
This is how it handles and objects like rotating.
Perfect.
Swing, swing.
I like, this is so unusual.
It's such a very specific, like vector based, uh, like issue that I would actually kind
of like to see like an animation that uses that.
It's, uh, like deliberately.
As it's like a stylistic choice, there is, there fucking is.
Um, let me grab an animation by Junie.
This guy, um, uses like flash fuckery for like stylistic effect and it's really fucking,
really fucking cool stuff.
I just need to remember what the video is called.
Just squishes into a puddle.
I must remember, he didn't, he, he didn't use shape tweens.
He used the, uh, straighten slash some move effect and flash, which is famous for slash.
Yeah.
There's a, well, these two effects in flash, like that'll, there's the smooth effect and
there's the straighten effect and both of them just make your drawings look completely fucked up.
Oh, you're talking about when it's all like black and white.
Yeah.
During the black and white section, every frame he just hits a smooth button and it fucks
up, but it actually stylistically looks cool.
This, look at, look at this, uh, yeah, this, this frame.
It looks really good in motion, uh, but, uh, freeze frame.
It's like, why does it look like that?
Neat.
Cause you said right click shape, smooth.
Actually, I think it's a modified shape.
Smooth.
It looked at its head and he was like, yeah, that's a square.
Yeah, I was going to approximate that to a square for you.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
I just, I just, uh, put the effect on the axe, for example, in the first frame and it
looks like that.
It like, uh, looks very, um, uh, what's the word?
Maybe like, uh, just sort of removing data, like, like, uh, curved lines become straight
lines, like trying to think where the points would be.
Cause you can, you can kind of see like where the vector points are.
Yeah.
Like it kind of, basically what both of those effects do is they just delete vector points,
um, because that actually makes the file less laggy and run faster.
Um, the less vector points for our, for more cleanly, everything runs for less chances
of something glitching.
Um, so it'll find that point vector points that are very close together and it will delete
some of them and try to approximate the shape afterwards.
Um, which is basically how it works.
There's also how the brush smoothing algorithm that's built into flash used to work.
Uh, it's a little bit more sophisticated these days because I've updated the brush a bunch
of times in the last few years.
Um, but flash was famous for having a really terrible brush, um, because a lot of things,
you would draw like a good shape and then the second you let go of the mouse, the shape
goes and like straightens out.
Yeah, it becomes like weird polygon.
Yeah.
Uh, the flash brush has gotten a lot better, uh, at not doing that, but if you, but the,
the smooth, the shape smooth and the shape straighten effects basically work like the
old brush.
So you can still get that look if you want.
Um, uh, the way I work where I use the line tool specifically, so I don't use the brush,
I use the line tool, um, results in very, very few vector points anyway.
So my files tend not to be laggy at all.
Um, and I guess, um, I'm going to, um, I'm going to put a cropped picture of my animation
in chat that Eleazar can use earlier in the episode for when I'm talking about the hands
and shakes.
I realize it's going to be really confusing for people who can't see.
Yeah.
Perhaps.
Just a little cropped version.
If you want to see the uncropped, patreon.com slash oblivionfall, which, oh no.
Oh no.
What's this?
I'm Richard and Ben Saint now.
Oh, I better pledge to Ben Saint at patreon.com.
How have, how have you, how has this happened?
You haven't posted anything.
Um, people just show up to my patreon, I guess.
I guess there's people who just see the link in the description of the cum zone and they're
like, they just wander in.
Um, yeah.
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah.
I haven't advertised it.
Booby is very powerful, uh, like a, like a magnet.
It jumped up because I opened my, uh, I, I finally like announced, oh yeah, I have like
a patreon discord server now and there's like extra stuff in there that you can get
early and then a bunch of people up there pledged like instantly and I was like, oh
shit, I wasn't expecting that.
And I jumped above 400 just this morning.
I'm like, damn, time to fulfill my obligations to Ben Saint and give him money on patreon,
because now I'm the big creator.
Oh, uh, did you, did you say you were going to say that?
Did you say you were going to do that?
Yeah.
You, you suggested it, Ben.
Uh, well good.
I'm glad I did.
You were like, oh, um, yeah.
Like giving each other money on patreon at the same time is dumb because then we're both
just losing money and fees.
I'll pledge, like the bigger person should pledge to a smaller person and that was the,
that was the plan.
Uh, okay.
But did I actually pledge to you?
I'm not sure that I did.
Actually, I don't know if you did.
I don't see what you did.
I don't, I don't think, I don't think I actually did.
Darren, you get nothing then.
Oh, I fucked up.
I fucked up really bad.
Uh, damn.
No.
Okay.
Well, I would have if I knew, if I knew that, uh, you, that you believed my lie.
Uh, oh well.
I believed it.
I believed in Ben Saint.
What a tragic mistake.
You're first, you're first in your last mistake.
Yeah.
Actually, it works out for me because my tier at the time was free dollars and your lowest
tier is five.
So actually I would have been, um, I would have lost in that transaction.
So it works out.
Absolutely.
Wait.
Now I gotta check.
Let me go check if I'm, let me make absolutely sure.
Yeah.
Do check.
Well, now you know Ben Saint, that if you want to win this war, uh, you're going to
have to turn bescapades into sexcapades.
Yes.
Yeah.
I always knew deep down.
I think, uh, uh, who are posts from my creators?
No, I'm not subscribed.
I'm not pledged to oblivion fall.
Damn.
Uh, shit.
You could, you could have had it all.
You could have, you could have made back two dollars extra from whatever you were,
who would have been giving me.
Yeah.
Well, I didn't just like Bitcoin.
I didn't get in on the ground floor.
Uh, I'm pledged to cheesy Manfredo, Gibb and take and Shaddock.
Uh, I'm also pledged to Gabriel the star man, but I think his, his Patreon is inactive.
So that doesn't count.
Uh, yeah.
That's, that's me.
That's all I have to say about that.
Uh, Patreon.
Patreon.
Uh, maybe some people will like the video game that I made and pledge me some money for
that.
Uh, or maybe not.
Uh, if anyone, if anyone were to pledge right now, they would get their name in the, in
the credits for the game.
Anyone who pledges up until I post it gets, I've had to add a couple of last minute additions.
Well, when they listen to this, will it be too late?
It will be too late.
Yes.
Fuck.
Fuck them.
Yeah.
I gotta, I gotta, I gotta fucking, uh, I gotta fucking put the, no, I said, I said the
game will be out.
I said the game will be out by now and it's true.
Uh, it'll probably, I'm not sure if I should wait till Friday to post it or just go ahead
and post it whenever it's done.
No, just post it.
Yeah.
Just post it.
Probably like middle of this week sometime.
Uh, that's what I'll do.
Uh, that's all I can, uh, even think about.
Uh, I got nothing else to say.
Wow.
Well, um.
Good thing I have a podcast.
I have, um, been dealing with, uh, the lore of ghosts, uh, Kickstarter, Becker, rewards,
mailing, delivery stuff.
Yeah.
And, uh, it really got me down.
Um, but I'm okay now.
You seemed agitated.
You seemed agitated about it.
I did.
Um, I think there's a couple of problems.
One of them is that it's too hard.
Uh, the other one.
That's a big one.
The other one is that I had too high of expectations of my own abilities and because I didn't meet
like that high bar, um, I felt like I was worthless and I got me all depressed.
Do you mean your ability to do it in a certain time period?
Yeah.
It was like last week, um, like, uh, I don't know, Monday I had something happening, but
like it was going to be this week, I'm going to start buying the rest of the, uh, postage
and packaging and that's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to be packaging this week.
Right.
Um, because the demo is out and I have the time to do it and work on it, focus on it.
And then I immediately ran into like confusing things, uh, customs things that I needed to,
I didn't have data, um, on enough of like the, the money that I was going to spend.
And there was a lot of like questions of, do I have the money to, to pay for all of this
custom stuff?
How do I do it?
And I, I, I couldn't pack anything.
I, I had to like do like some more research.
But because I had said it to myself, I'm going to be packing today.
And the fact that by the end of the day, I was still like struggling to understand a
bunch of like numbers stuff.
Um, I felt like I had failed utterly and that I was pathetic and terrible and worthless.
And that was like the main problem was not that it was too difficult.
It was that I thought I could do it and, um, I beat myself up for not being able to do
it.
And so that's, that's more of like an ongoing problem, which I have now identified correctly
that I beat myself up, I treat myself like shit.
Like I am my own boss and I treat myself like a shit.
Like I treat myself badly.
I'm a bad, uh, employer and I don't give myself a break.
And, uh, that's not good.
That's a cause of a lot of problems.
Uh, well, we got it.
We got to, uh, just, we got to destroy the business owners.
So you're going, you're going down.
I'm going down.
I'm going to, I'm going to be scared to see me in the alleyway at night.
Um, because I'm going to kill myself, but not like that.
I'm going to kill, I'm going to kill the bad part of myself.
Right, right, right.
But yeah, that, that, that was just like, that was my, my saga.
I've, I've, I've since calmed down and then realized that I, I'm giving myself too much shit.
I got to like allow myself to be not perfect and be kind of dumb or like just accept that
things are difficult and that it's okay that I didn't figure it out so quickly.
Um, and, uh, now I, uh, I've bought some label stuff and I've figured out where,
where money is going, which, uh, things I'm, I'm sending it through and mostly through
Royal Mail for like most of the world.
And then Transglobal Express is good for the US cause they have like a connection to USPS,
which makes it very cheap and good.
So it should be good.
It should be fine and not a problem.
And I checked all of the numbers and I have enough from the Kickstarter to reimburse anyone
who will have to pay customs.
That's just the easiest way to deal with it is to have the person receive the item,
pay customs to receive it, and then I will reimburse them, uh, the full amount of whatever it is.
It won't be more than like 10 pounds or something.
Is that, um, to like for, is that for all like international mail?
Yeah, most, I mean, especially with Brexit now that like you have to do it just to send to Europe,
which is, uh, didn't used to be the case.
Oh, jeez.
All right.
I remember I have to like make a little customs sheet declaring what it is and print that on a label,
stick that on along with the, the mailing address label.
And then they receive it and they have to pay like customs to receive it like a customs tax thing,
VAT, handling whatever it is, just a bunch of little fees that add up to like maybe 10 pounds,
sometimes like six pounds.
And then I'm just going to like message everyone say I can reimburse you whatever it was.
Yeah, I remember sending packet, it was the, uh, the, the RFCK pins.
When I had to send a package of them to the UK, they would, uh, it was only the UK that ever did this.
It was like, Oh, the, the person receiving the package has to pay some like customs fee for it or some nonsense.
Which is weird because I had to pay for postage and then it arrives and then they also have to pay more.
It's like, just charge me it.
I was looking into it and there's like, if you have, at least for the UK and sending to Europe or most international places,
if you have a business or you can declare yourself a business and get like an iOSS number,
which is like a one stop shop, like, um, export number thingy,
then I can do a special thing where it's like delivered taxes paid or duty paid.
So that I pay the fee ahead of time and then the customer just receives the thing,
which is I think what most businesses do, I hope.
I mean, it feels like that because like a lot of, you know, I order stuff.
I don't have to pay customs.
I also didn't have to pay customs when I received the vapors.
Any of those or like the Cato anthology or any of that stuff.
Yeah.
So I don't really know what the, the deal is.
I think it was just when I sent places versus others.
I think it was just when I sent like a box, when I sent the, like the, the box of pins.
That was when, that was when it was laid over as a custom.
It was, it was a package instead of an envelope.
That might have been the, that might have been it.
So yeah, I feel like I've learned a lot.
I'm glad you didn't go into the red.
Yes, I'm not going into the red.
I actually like when I made the Kickstarter, I was very scared about all this stuff
and I made sure the goals were a little higher than was like absolutely necessary,
at least what I understood at the time.
Yeah.
And then I ended up like undercharging for the delivery cost for everything.
Cause like sending something to Canada is like 18 pounds.
Jesus.
And, and that's like,
It's like 25 bucks or 30 bucks or something.
Something like that.
And it's like the, the, the delivery costs I was asking for, for Canada,
I think was like five pounds.
Oh yeah.
No.
Almost four times as expensive for most of the places.
Yeah.
Europe.
Europe is all right.
Cause it's close by.
Yeah.
But like it's big delivery cost, but I had accounted for it and I think I will have enough.
I may even make a profit at the end.
Very nice.
So it's all, it's all sorted out and it will just take a little time and then it will be done.
Yeah.
So I'm glad that that's over and I'm glad also that I recognize.
Is it over?
You finished it?
Well, I got to draw the doodles.
That's the next thing.
That's the next like big, big scary thing is like, oh no, what if I deface this comic and
it's, this is a doodle sucks.
I've ruined it for them.
Yeah.
I don't have that many extra copies.
Oh shit.
And that, you know, that'll be a thing, but like whatever.
I can, I dealt with like a fucking doodle anxiety or like commission anxiety before.
Uh-huh.
Where people pay for a thing and I'm like, oh God, my art style varies in quality like
wildly from day to day and hour to hour.
I don't know if they're going to be happy with this one, but they usually are.
So no problem.
No, I don't think, nobody's going to be like, what, but that guy's was better.
You put a better doodle in that guy's book.
What the fuck?
That one had more lines.
That one had 50% more lines.
That one took up 25% more page space than mine.
It required 30% more ink and I demand satisfaction.
Everyone's got to meet up together.
Everyone who had a book is going to meet up and like compare pages and make a new book.
Make a new book with just those pages.
Take it out.
Okay, they're all going to tear the covers off and then I'm going to put the drawings in
and then they're going to tear them all into a number of equal pieces and then distribute
the pieces among each other.
So they all have equal quality distributed socialism.
And when they come together, they can put them together like a secret map that's being
reforged.
Yes.
And then they'd be like, oh, I always remember you, person who also pledged to the pluge to
the Lord of Ghost kicks out.
I'm going to next time I do a Kickstarter, I'm using that pluge again.
We're going to be pluging from the very start.
That's an evergreen.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I said that.
You did it.
You invented it for some reason.
I don't remember what the context was.
Was it during a stream or something?
Yeah.
It was right at the end.
You were playing a video game.
Call of night.
Call of night, I think, yeah.
I beat Call of night, steal, solo run.
That was great.
You beat it with like 45 minutes before the Kickstarter ended or some shit, right?
No, it was like within like five minutes or something.
Oh, yeah.
It was very close.
It was super close.
I thought you weren't going to make it.
Yeah.
I thought I was going to die.
That was the most epic type.
Yeah, I saw you make like a couple of errors against the Hollow Knight and I'm like, oh,
God, she's going to, she's, nah, she's fucked.
Nah, she can't do it.
There's no way.
Yeah, rule.
My favorite gaming moment of all time, probably.
Yeah.
Shit, was I going to say?
Yeah, Pluging.
Yeah, Pluging is coming back in a big way.
I was looking into, I mentioned that my printer, my local printer was giving me like some bullshit.
They were giving me bullshit quotes on their books.
I was looking at Mixam, which I think is a UK based printer.
And I think I can get the price down to under 20 a copy through them, which is okay.
Like it's manageable.
That's, that's for 100 copies.
If I were to sell more than 100, I could get the price down even lower.
Under 20 is like fine.
I have a couple more options I want to look at to maybe save even more or something.
But we'll see.
I could bring it down even lower if I went, if I made the book small.
Like if I made the book like six by nine, I could get it down to like, like under like, like 12.
But that's like six by nine inches.
But that's, yeah, but that's, that's a bit, that's a little smaller than I think I am willing to accept it being.
It's not sad.
I don't know.
I'll have to like look at it in real life.
Maybe I'll just use a ruler.
Print out on a piece of paper and cut it to the size it would be.
Yeah.
Just to have a look at how legible everything is.
I was envisioning something that's like eight by 12, but that might be too big.
That might be like unwieldily large.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Eight by 12.
That's a little bit bigger than a.
That's like, that's bigger than like a peanuts anthology.
That's bigger than, than a fucking.
What is, I think that's larger than a Homestuck book, actually.
I think, I think it might be because that's what it's like nine by nine.
The Homestuck books are almost square.
Yes.
Mine, my book would need to be, I think I want it to be about like, like three to two ratio.
You know, like longer than it or wider than it is tall.
Because, you know, it's, it was Twitter images and that's the roughly like the Twitter image ratio size.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm shopping around, but I was glad to see that like, no, these, these prices that fucking Fleming
printing is quoting me are not reasonable.
It is unacceptable.
They will pay for, for what they've done.
They lost themselves like customers.
They have lost themselves a damn customer.
Those mutants.
I thought we had something Renee.
I thought we had, I thought we had rapport.
But no, but instead you thought I was poor.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here's, here's something funny that happened this, this week.
So I recorded a podcast.
I was on a podcast, a cheesy Manfredo invited me onto a podcast.
His new podcast, which is called, uh, main character syndrome is what it's called.
Yes.
And he invited me onto an episode with, maybe you've heard of this guy, uh, uh, the Yolo swag studios.
Uh,
They might be unbelievable.
Are they an animator?
They are a cartoonist.
They draw funny little comics on Twitter.
Okay.
Maybe I'm not sure.
I feel like I may have seen him before.
Um, they're, you know, moderately big on Twitter.
Uh, so that was cool.
Got to talk to that guy.
Um, but then after that we recorded, that's, I think he said that's going to come out like
end of the month or something.
Uh, but then after we recorded that, I was talking to him and, and, uh, he mentioned that he
had a comic idea that he was not planning to draw, but he wanted to, um, he wanted to
have this other artist to draw it.
This other artist called, uh, Mimi Yori, who, uh, went kind of viral on Twitter a few weeks
ago or maybe longer than that.
I don't know because she made, uh, Among Us Girl, which is like, people loved Among Us
Girl.
I love Among Us Girl.
She's very specific.
Among Us Girl.
Yes.
Um, yes.
It is very specific.
Let me, uh, I like Fall Guys Girl too.
Fall Guys Girl.
Yeah.
Her, her, her bitter rival, Fall Guys Girl.
Uh, she looks like she had commie names and that's good.
Uh, I bet Gib would like, I bet Gib would like, uh, uh, Fall Guys Girl actually.
This could be the type.
Here.
This is, this is, this is, this is Among Us Girl.
Oh, I have not seen this.
Everybody loves Among Us Girl.
Uh, I don't know.
She says, Sus.
Sus.
Ah, crewmate.
I love you crewmate.
Um, anyway.
So, so, uh, anyway, Cheesy wanted, uh, Mimi Yori to draw this, uh, comic idea that he
had.
Uh, but it was like, they were trying to, uh, they were trying to work out like who, uh,
they wanted to like pay her an artist fee, but they were going to do like, okay, when
you draw it, then I'll try to sell it and I'm not going to pay you upfront, but like,
I'll pay you out of the sales and like, you'll get the first cut of like the fee and that'll
be it.
But it was like, okay, but because it's like not a guaranteed, uh, uh, return, it's like,
okay, she's like, she couldn't like do it.
She had like prioritized other things.
Uh, so I, uh, a genius that I am.
Oh, yes.
There's, there's, there's Fall Guys girl.
Uh, I was just like, here, well, why don't I, why don't I just pay for it?
I'll just give you, I'll just give you money.
I'll just give you some money.
Oh, I definitely like Fall Guys girl.
Yeah.
I knew it.
She's a bully.
She'll bully you just like you are.
Is she a bully or does she just look like that?
She just, she's got that, uh, that, um, uh, well, it's like Rose Lalonde and Mandy from
Billy and Mandy and Pacific Northwest sort of vibe.
Yeah.
Very, very Pacifica.
Um, I like her little tote bag with the Fall Guys face on it.
It's great.
Uh, but anyway, I said, uh, here, I'll just, I'll just pay for it.
Here's some money.
Anyway, the point is now I have, now I'm executive producer of, uh, of this thing.
Cause I paid for it.
And I think that's pretty funny.
Your producer of Among Us girl comic?
Not of Among Us girl.
It's Cheezy's specific, uh, uh, story, which is called Extra Souls.
Uh, I won't say anything more about it cause it would be a spoiler, but, uh, so she's,
she's drawing it.
He, he wrote the script.
He wrote it and came up with the idea.
She's drawing it and I'm executive producer.
Cool.
Yeah.
I think that's pretty cool.
Uh, and maybe, and maybe I'll get my money back if, uh, people buy it.
Lemau.
I just realized what this, this comic is.
Maybe I'll buy chicken for dinner.
They both grab for chicken.
Among Us girl, full guys girl.
What are they going to do?
There's more than one thing of chicken there.
So there's not even like, they have to fight over it.
It's true.
Uh, but no, they want.
They're just going to kill each other.
They just, uh, I think the problem is not that there's not enough chicken to go around.
It's that now they've seen each other and that's.
It's time to throw down.
I'm not even sure what happens.
Full guys girl is going to fall onto her and Among Us girl is going to try and vent to get away.
Um, yeah.
You should get stuck in the vent because it's a real fucking vent and it's like, oh no, it's not meant for humans to go through.
So anyway, I'm a page, I'm a patron of the arts.
I'm a, I'm a, I'm an executive producer now.
I'm moving on up in the world and I just wanted it to let everyone know that I would have,
what a, what a cool, what a big shot I am.
Yeah.
It's funny.
No, cause it's like, it is kind of cool, but it's also like.
It, it's, it's like, uh, it's executive producers, the sort of thing you see when you're young and it's like, wow, I wonder what that means.
Yeah.
Um, must be important cause they're always like right at the end, but it's really, it's really literally just, they paid for it.
Yes.
That's right.
And they get to put their name important.
Like, well, I paid, so can I have like my big name, big, right?
Really big in the credits and like, yeah, okay.
Can you put me in the video description?
Just my name.
What?
Cause it's just paying for that.
You know, I always thought it was like super lame when patrons were like, oh, if you pledge this amount of money, we'll put your name at the end.
Um, but no, that's what people pay, people pay millions of dollars for that in movies.
So.
Yeah.
You know, it's executively produced by all my patrons.
Uh, well, you know, uh, being an executive producer, the challenge, the challenge is, uh, is you got to recognize the talent.
You got to have an eye for talent.
The, the, the, the hard part is not, uh, giving someone some money.
The hard part is, uh, is scouting out like who is worthy of your investment.
And I think cheesy is a, is a real go getter.
Cheesy's a moxie.
And, uh, I think Mimi Ori is pretty good at, uh, drawing stuff.
So it's like, yeah, I think, I think this is, I think we're doing this.
I think, I think, I think it's time to throw down, uh, it's time to invest, to take all my money out of Bitcoin and put it into, uh, comic executive producer credits.
Uh, getting in on the ground floor.
Uh, it's going to the moon.
Uh, yeah.
Anyway, that's what I did.
Left the call.
I didn't, I didn't leave the call.
I was delivered food that I didn't know was happening.
Uh, I have a steak here.
Um, well, I can't eat a steak in the middle of a podcast.
I mean, can I?
Well, here, how, how about this?
You won't have to, because I'll kill your appetite by telling you about the other thing that happened to me this week.
I think.
Did you diarrhea?
Well, that goes, that goes without saying.
But, um, the, no, I think I had a tonsil stone.
I think I got one.
Do you know what those are?
Uh, I, I know the tonsils are the back of your mouth.
Yeah.
I don't know what a stone of that would be.
It's like a buildup.
Oblivion, yes.
Oblivion, do you know what a tonsil stone is?
It's like, it's like a weird growth sort of thing.
I don't know.
It's not a growth.
It's like in the, okay.
I'm not sure if it's what it is, but like, I think so.
Uh, in the tonsil, in like the crevices of the tonsil, uh, fucking, I don't know, stuff just gets caught in there.
And, um, sometimes it just accumulates.
Yeah, sure.
Pissed crystals.
It accumulates into like a, a lump, a white lump.
And, uh, you know, it just lives there in your tonsil until it eventually, if you're lucky, falls out.
Or maybe it is extracted if it's like, whatever.
Uh, anyway, all, all I know is I was eating something.
Or I had just eaten something and then like, I like spat something out and there was like just a white sort of like ball.
And I was like, what is this?
Like this does not look like what I was eating.
And I was like, I get, maybe it was a tonsil stone.
I've never had one before.
Although they say the tonsil stones smell really bad.
And this, this thing did not smell that bad.
It didn't smell like much of anything.
So I don't know.
Maybe that's not what it was.
Maybe it was just some food.
I don't know.
It was like smooth and sort of roundish sort of pea size, small pea size.
I hadn't noticed any like white blobs in my tonsil.
If you go on YouTube and you look up tonsil stone extraction, you can see inside the mouth.
You can see people's tonsils just, uh, just absolutely laden with a big white lumps of stuff.
And then they go in with like a hook and they like jostle them around and they squeeze them out and they just fall out.
It's disgusting.
Anyway, I hope that's killed Gibbs appetite.
So she won't have to eat that steak on.
Yeah, I'll make sure to talk about piss crystals some more.
Yeah.
I'm going to go to rant about a kitty litter and why it's, why it's bad.
Let me hear it.
So they used to be a really good brand.
It was like this, um, it was like this paper litter that flushes.
You can flush it, which is handy.
Wait, like you line the, like you line like the box with.
It's like, you know, it's like these little blue pellets that are apparently made out of paper, but the, the like little blue pellets that are like squishy, like foam almost.
Oh, but you can.
So it's flush, but it's flushable.
Yeah, it's flushable.
So like, um, interesting.
It's very good at like sticking to all the, the trash that your, your cats are dropping.
It's really good at solidifying and clumping as well.
And you can just flush it down the toilet, which is really handy because we had the litter box in the toilet.
And then they stopped making it for some reason or at least I stopped selling it here around the time COVID started.
So like, you know, mid early 2020, we couldn't get it anymore.
So then we had to try other types of litter and there are so many just terrible, terrible types of kitty litter, but I don't know why anyone would ever use them.
Um, the first one we found was like these like hard, like brown pellets that didn't clump.
They didn't do anything.
Um, and it would just turn to mush at the bottom where all that pee is and that's no good.
Um, and so that, that show was terrible.
And also it's like really sharp.
If it like, if the cats kick it out of the box and you stop on it, it'll like hurt your foot.
Um, and then we tried because we kept seeing like, oh, crystal kitty litter.
Like, and I'm like, huh, um, that seems weird.
But you know, like, we might as well try it since like, we've been trying a bunch of different things because and none of them are really that good.
So we tried, I'll get a, I'll show you a picture of us.
You know, it's like these hard, like, um, delicious transparent crystals.
And we thought maybe this will be okay.
I'm gonna crush that up and snort it.
If you know what I'm saying, all I have to say is the smell minty.
It smells minty.
It does.
Nice.
This is the worst imaginable though.
This is actually the worst.
Like having this is the worst experience I've ever had.
Uh, this is like everything bad.
Like a good litter.
You know, we'll cancel out the odor.
It'll clump.
You know, the liquids will cause it to clumps.
You can easily scoop out those parts.
It's not too heavy, which means that like, you know, like it, when you put it in a bag,
doesn't make the trash bag weigh a ton.
Um, and it also like clings to poop and stuff correctly and all that.
So that way like that, that, that those are the things you want.
This checks none of those boxes.
Um, and also it's fucking sharp.
Um, like walking into the bathroom is cut yourself on it.
Never cut myself, but like it is painful as stepping on glass could be without
bleeding is what it felt like.
Oh, like on your months.
Um, and the worst fucking stuff is that, you know, cause you're just like kind of,
you mostly like scoop stuff off the top.
Uh, what I didn't realize is that the bottom of the litter box, like every,
all the crystals had turned.
No, I hope, I hope Kim's not listening while she's eating.
This is the worst part.
I hope she is.
No, no.
Guys, this takes so good.
Fuck you.
It's so good.
Even the most grossest things could not dissuade me from eating.
All right.
So what kind of steak?
What cut?
I want to know what, I want to know what cut you're eating.
Um, it's, uh, from a cow.
Damn it.
What?
I don't know.
It's a, it's like a steak the size of a, well, I don't know where it came from.
It's good.
It's got like, uh, there's like, there's like sauteed little potatoes and like a tomato
sauce thing.
It's good.
Damn.
Fine.
I hope you enjoy it.
I'm going to get to the gross part of the story now.
Yeah.
So, um, yeah, so they don't really, these, the shit doesn't really absorb liquid.
It just changes color.
Um, so at the bottom of the litter box, well, like after a while, I'm like, I've been cleaning
stuff up at the top.
I should probably like do a full on clean scrub the box out as you, you know, should do it
every couple months at least.
Um, because instead of just emptying it, um, the bottom of the thing was the most disgusting
looking and smelly thing I'd ever seen.
The crystals had absorbed so much pee, but they weren't just yellow.
They were like dark orange, almost brown with pee.
That's how you know you're getting your money's worth.
But they were like, but like when I, when I scraped it with the scraper thing, like,
you know, a little, little shovel, like liquid would still like leak from the crystal, like
pile at the bottom.
And amazing.
The weirdest shit is I could look, I, it somehow was like, was getting into the air.
I was breathing in piss crystals.
I could feel them coating my lungs.
Um, just being near it.
Um, very nice.
It was the worst experience ever.
Um, and after that, I just, me and, me and Kai were just like, fuck this, never buying
this shit again.
This is like the worst litter imaginable.
Um, and then we found, um, then we switched because we couldn't get the, we couldn't get
the fucking blue paper pallet stuff anymore.
Cause again, they didn't sell it.
We eventually found, uh, it's like, it's like powdered like wood shavings or something.
Um, that's like scented and it's pretty good.
It's the next best thing.
Um, because it's still pretty lightweight.
You can't flush it, but aside from that, it's just as good as the blue paper litter
pallets.
So there's no, there's no alternative.
There's no like similar off brand alternative to the blue paper pallets.
There's no like similar off brand alternative to the old kinds you used to get.
Um, you can't like order it online or something.
Um, you really, we tried, we tried it.
We just couldn't find it.
Um, blows, but yeah, the, the, the wood, it's like, it's like sawdust sort of like litter
or whatever.
Um, and like it's scented like tree or some shit.
I don't know.
That stuff's all right.
Uh, it's a lot better than everything else we were trying at the time.
We couldn't.
Yeah.
Sounds, sounds pretty bad.
Uh, I don't, I'm not a cat owner.
You know, I could, I could, I could care less about animal husbandry.
Uh, our cats are wonderful and their best friends.
Is it possible for the cats to like learn how to go outside?
Um, like where you live?
No, it's not a good.
It's not how, that's just not how cats.
I mean, uh, we don't, we don't, uh, we keep our cats as indoor cats.
Yeah.
There's indoor cats and there's outdoor cats.
I mean, I guess so, but like, man, no, that's, that is true.
Some cats are very want to stay inside all the time.
My cat, um, regularly goes out on little expeditions.
We never needed a, a little trade for her.
That's awesome.
Yeah, rules.
Our cat, Labris, and I, I will put a picture of her in chat.
She.
Labris?
Labris, named after the character from persona free.
And our character, I guess, is also named after character from persona free.
Oh, I, I know who I guess is.
Yeah.
Um, that's Labris.
She's our, when we got her, she was apparently six months old, but she looked like she was
free months old.
She's tiny.
She's a ball of fluff and we've had her for two years and she's still tiny.
I worry that if, uh, she ever went outside, she would just never come back.
She would just wander off.
Yeah.
Um, she, she's very, she's very silly.
I don't think she knows where she is ever.
I used to live, I used to live with a cat, a horrible cat, a disgusting little creature
who, uh, who would scratch you, who would like swipe at anyone who came near all the time.
And, uh, if you let it out, it could, it would always, it would attempt to, it would attempt
to bolt out of any door that was opened.
You had to like watch your back and make sure the cat was not around.
And if it was around, you had to like really carefully block its way from getting out the
door because it would try as hard as it could to get out.
And once it was out, you had to chase it around in order to get it to come back in.
No G's.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, a nasty little goblin thing that should have been put down.
Uh, but it was allowed to live, unfortunately.
Uh, unfortunately.
Okay.
You know, the weird thing is when we, um, got, when we got, uh, labris, it was actually
I'm not talking about Digi, uh, uh, Trixie's old cat, uh, not, not talking about, uh, what's
my lala by that?
Lala was a good cat.
All right.
So anyway.
Anyway.
Yeah.
So we, we, we got labris because our overcat we had, I guess I'll put a picture of her in
chat.
She, um, uh, so it's I guess she's holding a little yellow fluffy ball in her mouth.
Um, she,
Whoa.
Umbreon.
Did she kill Umbreon?
Yeah.
She pulled off.
It's, it's yellow.
Exactly.
Um, she was, so, so we had two cats we had, um,
Well, but how did her attack stat, her stats must be insane.
Umbreon is such an incredible wall.
Like it's got such bulk.
Like how did she do that?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
She used, uh, she used a track.
She's cute.
Look what a, what a cute Pokemon moves.
She, she toxic stalled it.
Well, with her horrible poisonous, uh, poisonous kitty litter crystals, P crystals.
It's true.
So, um, we had, we got I guess, and we had a cat called Artemis living with us that we
gave to my mother-in-law after a while.
But, um, I guess was very, was, was very much trying to like acting in motherly ways towards
our other cat who was older.
She was always trying to clean her.
Um, the other cat didn't like it.
She didn't like being cleaned.
Uh, and she would try to fight her.
Yeah.
Artemis didn't like being clean.
She would fight off.
A lot.
And I guess would just end up like sitting on blankets and just licking the blankets
and licking towels and just licking things all the time.
And we thought she, we need to get her a friend.
Um, that she can, she can, we need to get a kitten so that she can dot upon them.
Um, and so we got, we went to a shelter and we thought, well, let's get a boy cat this
time.
And we, we, there was a little black kitten and we were going to call it Mona, uh, named
after the fucking cat from persona five.
I guess.
After Lisa.
I didn't know you were such a persona head.
Um, I like, I like the persona games.
I've never played them, but I watched my husband play them and I think they're good.
Um, I've also, I've never played a, I've never played a persona.
They're pretty good.
Um, but yeah, so we got this black cat called Mona.
Um, and they're really cute.
And we grabbed them because when we're at the, at the shelter, it just, it just liked
me.
It was just hugging my leg.
It was just wrapping its paws around my leg and wouldn't let go.
And we were like, we'll take this one.
And it was a mistake.
It was a big mistake.
Mona was, we got, we got Mona home and Mona had the sharpest claws of any cat I've ever
fucking encountered.
Its claws were out pretty much 24 seven.
It would just constantly like scratch and scratch like, and it, it wasn't like aggressive.
It just did it because it just felt like it.
It would just scratch everything.
And the other cats were terrified of him and we had to like shut him in the, oh, he would
even scratch the other cats.
Yeah.
He would, he would scratch the cats.
He would scratch us.
He would scratch everything.
And he, he's just playing.
He's just doing it cause he thinks it's funny.
Um, he's not even mad.
That sucks.
That's the toxic cat behavior.
Yeah.
Toxic cat behavior.
And so we had to shut them like in the bathroom, like in the master like bathroom by our bedroom.
Cause we couldn't let him out at night cause he would cause too much trouble.
And we were like, this sucks.
We hate, we hate that we have to keep him separated from them.
And every time we'd go in there, he would just be like asleep in the sink.
He'd be filling up the sink and he was really cute.
But then like, if we went to the pen and he would just reach out his paw and just fucking
slice our skin open, like nothing, never had a cat that would do that to that extent.
Um, after like two weeks, we were just like, I think we have to try and take him back.
And it was a really hard decision.
We were like, we really didn't want to, we really tried sticking it out.
And then like, even after having that fault, we kept him for like another week and then
it was just so bad and we were like, we just have to, um, and the, the original shelter
wouldn't take him back.
Um, we had to, we had to fucking drive around to like four different shelters and eventually
we found one that, that took him in cause we're not going to fucking abandon him on
the side of a road or some shit.
Um, and then when we got home, we're like, okay, I guess we'll try to find another cat
because that one just did not mesh.
It was not good.
Um, and then we saw a picture of the cat that was, you know, Labyrinth's who I put
posted earlier.
Um, we saw a picture of her on the shelter website, um, and we're like, she's beautiful.
She's beautiful, fluffy, fluffy thing.
She basically looks like our cat, I guess, just way fluffier.
Um, but another family had already like, um, said we're picking her up.
Um, so like we called the place, we're like, we want to get this cat and they're like,
oh, well, there's actually another family, um, who's already like said that they want
her and they're going to come around and pick her up.
But if they don't show up, then you can have her and we're like, oh, shit, there's no way
they're not going to show up.
And then they didn't, um, that other family just never can, they just, for like, for
like five, like five days after the, that they have a family was supposed to pick up
the cat.
Apparently they tried calling that family.
They just couldn't get to them.
They were like, okay, I guess you can have her.
Um, and then we brought her home and immediately.
The complete opposite of Mona, they, they became best friends.
Um, like I guess we didn't need to clean the blanket anymore.
I guess just like within like five minutes of them saying hello to each other.
I guess was cleaning her and being all sweet and then they were cuddling.
Um, it was wonderful and unlike fucking scratched up everything.
Labris has never scratched me once.
Every time I've interacted with her, she never, she always has her claws retracted.
Every time she bats at me or swipes at me, it's just soft little whiffle things.
There's, there's her claws are never out.
Um, and we've had, it's been, we've had her for about two years now and she's
been the nicest, uh, sweetest thing.
She is just a little bit retarded.
Um, and all cats are to be fair, but she's like, she, she has certain spots around
the house where she'll just sit and look at the ceiling and scream.
Um, and it's always the same free location.
She'll just sit there and scream at the walls and I don't know why.
Um, but aside from that, probably a problem with the walls.
Yeah, you know, cat, cat's no.
Yeah.
She's always making crazy faces to, uh, putting a GIF in chat.
You can see you in the background, her head's just spinning all over the place.
That's what she does.
Uh, she's very silly, um, but very sweet.
I really like that when, when, when, when a cat is like play fighting with you,
they're friends, the friends, like, uh, cause, uh, my cat Luna, uh, she sometimes
gets the claws out, but not to like fight.
She'll like have the claws out, but not like scrape them.
She'd be like, Bap me when I'm like tickling her in an annoying way.
And she's like, protect, she gets her mouth around my finger, but she doesn't bite
down.
She just sort of like, yeah, imitates like, this is what I would do if I were to bite
you, but I love you actually.
Yeah, she's like that.
That's pretty nice.
That's pretty nice cat behavior.
It's too bad all cats aren't like that.
Yeah.
What a shame.
Well, oh, well, well, oh, well, oh, well, like I always say, I don't know what I
always say.
Okay, nevermind, sorry.
I always, I always find difficult to find the words and that's what I always say.
Oh, speaking of, I'd better do that fucking wordle.
I haven't done it today.
Oh, I got it.
I lost.
Oh, yeah, I had my first I had my first lose on wordle.
My streak of 100 percent success has been ruined.
I lost one because I actually forgot to do wordle that day, but I saw your tweet
about it.
Do you do you guys do any any wordle alternatives?
I do wordle, which is yeah, which is it shows the silhouette of a country or
province or something.
And and they you have to guess where on earth it is.
And for the last few days, though, it's been very difficult.
I think the last one I did was like a an island that has nothing on it, which is
like a few kilometers like north of Antarctica, which is owned by Denmark.
And it's like my first guess was a country near the bottom of Africa, which is
the closest I got.
And I'm like, it's the same shape as like Lesotho, which is like a little
country, I think, within South Africa.
Yeah, I'm like, that was my first guess.
It was wrong.
Go south.
And I'm like, it's the south point of Africa.
The hell is south of that?
So sometimes it's just so obscure, you'd never get it.
But it's so fun because like you can be like, I don't feel like stupid for not
knowing that very obscure island that has nothing on it.
I I tried to do I tried to do hurdle.
You tried hurdle where you've heard sheep.
I know I hate it.
It's it's about identifying a song and it'll have like, oh, it'll have it'll
play you like the first like second of a song.
And then you try to get it has like a list.
Like every time it generates a list of like some amount of songs that it could be.
So it's not like you just you're just guessing from every song in existence.
You're guessing from a list, but it's like a big list.
Like you can't like look at the entire list, but there is like a limited
list of things it could be.
And you got to try to guess it.
And then if you don't get which one, then it plays you a little more of the
song and then you do it again.
I it sucked.
I didn't like it.
And I was completely listen.
I don't listen to music that other people listen to.
So I would never know.
Yeah, it was completely hopeless at it.
So and I was like, this is not the kind of thing I'd be good at.
No, my favorite might by far my favorite word alternative is Squirtle.
You've played Squirtle.
I haven't played that one.
No, Squirtle.
It's it's a guessing Pokemon.
And oh, well, well, yeah.
You guess you guess they're they're well, you guess a Pokemon and then it will
tell you like their generation.
Is it did you get the right generation or is it a higher generation, lower
generation, their types?
Did you get their types right and then and then their height, their height and
weight, like is it is it taller or shorter and is it heavier or lighter?
And you get eight guesses to get the correct mon.
And I've done it a few times now.
You start with nothing.
Then you just put in a Pokemon and they'll tell you whether
you're on the right track on some things or other.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, hold on.
Today, I guess I guess.
Well, what if I want to play it?
Or no, no, no.
OK, yesterday, yesterday, I guess I guess shinks and it was like.
And it was like, no, that's not not the generation lower or whatever.
And then, you know, it's like, no, neither of the types were right.
OK, and it's bigger and it's heavier.
And then you just go.
It's a good it's a great one.
I like it a lot.
I want to try that one.
That sounds fun.
Yeah.
But like the thing I don't like about Wordle
is the reason I lost was like the nightmare scenario where
I knew four of the five letters very early on.
And then because I was playing hard mode, I can't narrow it down.
OK, yeah. Subsequent guesses on hard one.
You can get completely fucked like that.
Yeah, like I my first guess was torch and it was like C.H.
To the end was like, OK, how about hatch because there was a T.
And it was like, OK, hatch is a T C H.
So OK, hatch latch.
No, batch catch match.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It was watch and I lost.
I was like, that's that was that blows.
I wasn't stupid.
The game's bad.
And then I will never play it again ever.
That's a that's a.
That's like one of those mind sweeper situations, right?
When it's like, OK, there's like an equal.
You get down to the last couple of choices
and there's like an equal chance that the mind is in like one or the other.
Yeah. And you just you just got to guess.
Like it could be any of those consonants.
There's too many words that end like that.
Yeah, there's there's one where I forget that happened like a few weeks ago.
But I was lucky enough to get it.
But like the word that I had four of the letters.
Correct. I was just missing one letter and it turned out
there were like seven words it could be just by changing the one letter.
If you're if you're not on hard mode, you can you can just you can just guess
like another word that has those letters in them to eliminate them.
But if you are playing on hard mode, there's just nothing you can do.
I'm not playing on hard mode, but I treat it like hard mode.
I I always like everybody does that.
And I don't know why.
Just play on hard mode.
If you're going to because I'm you might as well get that star.
I feel like I'm oh, yeah, you're right.
I should just play on hard mode.
I don't know how to switch to hard mode.
There's a little thing at the top.
Let's say there you go.
I turned it on.
Hell, yeah.
I just realized that I had lost like I hadn't lost before.
And my my score was like 100 percent success rate.
But I had missed my streak one or two days.
So I really should have like once I realized that it was probably I was going to lose.
I should just not done it for that day.
And then my my my my my my my statistics would have been perfect forever.
But what's the because now that it says it says 98 percent.
And I'm like, there's no way I can get it back to 100.
This game is permanently tarnished.
You have you have to you have to play.
You have to win a hundred and ninety nine times so that the ninety nine
point five percent rounds up to a hundred.
It's the only way.
I wonder if that actually does work.
I don't know.
I don't know. Nobody knows.
Some there's some.
Yeah, sometimes they don't round up to a hundred unless it's actually a hundred.
They'll never give you that last percentage unless it's everything.
That's how video.
The New York completion is a New York Times is going to stiff you like that.
I bet the New York Times is going to buy your game for a million dollars.
I fucking hate New York.
New York.
Fuck New York.
I wear a shirt that says I like like upside down heart New York.
A spades of love spades.
You got to go with spades.
New York.
Yeah, I'm Kaleigh Kalyganis.
What was wrong with the old?
What was wrong with the old York?
Small, I guess.
You're asking me this.
It's town in the UK.
It's just like this is nice.
Yeah, good enough space for giant buildings, though.
Kalyganis is like it's like you hate each other, but you also like respect
one another as like rivals.
So yeah, yeah, it's a bit it's a bit different, I guess.
Oh, well, that's the best I got.
Damn, I start New York.
Let's see if I have anything else on my stupid topic list.
Oh, I bought the Ukraine bundle for from itch.
Honestly, honestly, just just because of the value, incredible value.
I was I was I saw.
Kingdom two, I saw that it had Kingdom two on it.
Oh, yeah, I played Kingdom.
I liked the original Kingdom and I didn't even know there was a sequel,
but I saw oh, there's a Kingdom two.
Oh, and it's on the Ukraine bundle.
Oh, and it normally costs $15, but the entire Ukraine bundle costs 10.
Well, what else am I going to do?
So I was like, well, obviously, I have to buy the Ukraine bundle.
So you're losing money by not doing it, basically.
And, you know, obviously, and, you know, obviously,
I support Russia's right to self-determination
and I support their their action against the imperialist United States and NATO.
But, you know, that bundle, though, but that bundle, though,
I had to I had to sell out to sell out Putin, my man, Putin.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
Yeah, did you see the the video?
A guy was filming out his window at a tank and the tank, like,
shot at the guy filming and it exploded right in front of his face.
And oh, God, I I did see that.
I did not. No, I didn't see it.
It wasn't like right in front of his face, but like right below the window.
You see the tank coming up, facing him.
And then the thing, the barrel goes up a bit and it shoots.
And I think in that, it's like it bounces off of the ground.
So it wasn't shooting up at the guy in the window, but it bounces off the ground.
People say it bounces off the ground.
I think they're mis-free in the video.
It's actually just clipping of the branch on a tree
because you see the branch actually
starting to fall when the bullet like slices through.
Maybe it's a different one we're thinking of.
I distinctly remember seeing like a thing where it like it it ricochets off
and then hits the building in front of the guy in the window.
And he keeps filming.
He doesn't move out the way entirely.
No, we're trying the same video because I saw Vosh were acting
and he was saying, oh, look, you see it bounce.
And I looked at it and I'm like, no, it's actually slicing through the tree.
Oh, God.
Oh, we just zoomed out casually.
That would be so terrifying, you know, having seen an explosion happen
and the dust is there and you don't know whether they're about to like fire
right at you because you can't see anything.
I'm going to come back for more.
Oh, I guess you reminded me that I'm mad about I'm mad at Vosh.
I really fucking hate Vosh this week.
I really think his I really think his stupid J.K.
Rowling thing was like really embarrassing.
What was embarrassing?
Why is it embarrassing?
Because because he looked because J.K.
Rowling is a devil and but he looks like a bad guy.
He looks like the bad guy because he's like.
He said women shut up.
She she she retweeted the reason why she retweeted him was
because he had already made himself look like the bad guy.
And he was an easy dunk and it worked.
And I just have I just like what is the point?
What is the point of a debate, bro?
Who makes our side look bad and embarrasses us?
You know, like, like, is this that's not what we pay you for?
That's not what you're supposed to do.
You fucked up.
I'm really really it actually really irritates me.
I don't agree because it's just a tweet that like when you when you tweet out
a dumb joke like that and people
all over the left make those sorts of jokes all the time.
You don't know that J.K.
Rowling was going to retweet it ahead of time.
Like if he'd known that was going to be the case, he probably wouldn't have done that.
It's not like he.
I am well, I guess and then made the joke.
It just kind of I mean, and also I know he didn't.
I know he didn't know she would retweet it, but.
And also I don't know it's all the other things
that people bring up with Vosh is like nothing compared to everything else,
in my opinion.
So I did.
I did see his like response to the backlash of that.
And he's he's he's he's just doubling down on it.
Like, it's bad.
Like, I think he's handling it wrong.
He had a point in the like.
Like, oh, God, trying to remember what he said, because it was like, it was like,
yeah, I guess I can see where you're coming from that like.
She.
Fuck, God, it was a good point.
And I kind of agreed with it.
I can't remember what he said.
I, you know, it's like he he he he made like a a sexist comment.
And I think no, no, I can't remember it.
I can't remember it.
So it's not like a good idea for me to try and like paraphrase.
I'm just like, fuck, you know, like, like, like my mom, my mom is a big Harry Potter fan,
does not have certainly does not have like a nuanced take on like trans people or whatever,
unlike, you know, gender ideology.
I imagine someone like her seeing J.K. Rowling pointing at Vosh and being like,
this this guy thinks women should shut up.
And it's just like, it looks bad, you've failed, you fucking failed to do what you're supposed to do.
And and it bugs me and I'm upset.
I wish he hadn't done it.
It's not like it's not like.
I guess it's it's hard to know how how much it like.
It actually hurts trans rights, I guess, like the the idea is like moderate people who like,
they know who J.K. Rowling is and they don't really know what trends rights are.
They wouldn't immediately understand that what she says is like transphobic or bigoted.
No, but they will definitely see that what Vosh said is is is mean and like sexist.
Right.
It's like, I guess they would feel that way.
I just don't know, God, why do I hate that I don't remember?
I don't want to go watch his video right now to figure it out.
Yeah, whatever.
I noticed stupid.
I noticed people on the left, like when and I got this reaction from Spork and then later
saw other people memeing about it, that if if he had said white women shut up,
then people on the left wouldn't be man.
But I feel like people on the right would just be like, oh, well, now it's also racist, too.
I guess, like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I guess the only the only solution is to just never make those kinds of jokes at all
because you might get screen shot at, I suppose.
No, I think it's I think it's like, I kind of I kind of I kind of don't think it was
like a comment that was made in very good taste.
Like, I don't think it was very funny.
I don't think it's I don't think it's a good joke.
Just be like women should shut up.
Ha, isn't it funny that I said that?
Like, not really.
Well, you said shut up challenge.
It sounds like a YouTube title.
And no, oh, he said the joke was because it was International Women's Day
and J.K. Rowling was making like transphobic tweets at the time.
Like I said, you know, women like not trans people, that sort of stuff.
Um, and Vosh was like doing the opposite of like the the the phrase.
It's like, listen to women.
Um, it was like, it was like women speak up and he's like, how more like
women, shut up.
La Mal, women shut up.
If, you know, and then he went on to be like, uh, you're crying about this
when you're a billionaire trying to remove the rights of trans people.
Yeah, I know.
And and it's all like.
Yeah.
I can see, I can see there's two sides to it.
And I forget what he said.
I mean, obviously, I mean, obviously I agree with Vosh's position.
I just think rhetorically he made a big error.
He made a big, he made a big costly error and he isn't even sorry about it.
And that makes me mad.
Okay, I'm upset.
And what are you going to do about it?
No, you're trying to fight me about it and I'm going to fight you back.
Ah, whatever.
I'm only just throw down for Valhush.
Yeah.
I'll figure it out.
I'll figure out what he said.
And because it was something about like how optics, like if you, if you
constantly care so much about optics, then something is bad.
But I forget why.
I don't really know exactly what he said.
I'm mad at him because I, I see, I see people over the place making those sorts
of jokes all the time and we laugh at them and we think they're funny when.
I don't know if I do.
I don't really think that his joke was very funny.
So I don't, I don't know.
I just, it doesn't get.
I mean, do you think it's not funny because of the potential?
I'm not, I'm not offended.
I'm not offended about it and I'm not like, oh, if you say this, people are
going to, people are going to, I don't know.
It's just, it's just not, it's just not very compelling.
Just be like, oh, well, you see, I said that.
Yes, I did say women should shut up.
But you see the joke was that I, I don't actually mean it.
I mean, I don't, I just said it when I don't mean it.
Oops.
Well, it wasn't as simplistic.
That's why I said it was like, I don't want to see, when I see the phrase
for women, when I say a woman shut up challenge, that just immediately
reads to me as like, it's obviously a joke, like directed at her specific.
I know that because I know who Vosh is even not knowing who Vosh is.
Like the word challenge being in there just makes it sound like some dumb,
like free AM YouTube challenge, like title thing.
Like it's, it's clearly.
Just anyone who's, you know, my, my, my, my mom's not, my mom's not going to think that.
I.
I guess, would she, would she understand any of the other points Vosh made?
No, regardless.
No.
And if Vosh hadn't said that, it wouldn't have been screen-shotted and
never would have even happened anyway.
And she would have found some random trans person.
Well, it kind of just seems to me like.
Well, it kind of seems to me like Vosh making, you know, he's, he's just
making these deliberately inflammatory comments kind of being, you know, just,
just a little bit shitty, just a, just a touch little shitty, just, just for fun,
just for fun and profit.
And then, you know, and then, you know, J.K.
can see, can see him doing this and be like, aha, I'll make an example of him.
I'll show how my enemies are so evil and cruel.
I think part of his thing was like, she would have done that to anyone.
Because she's looking for someone to like scapegoat as like, this is why
trans people don't deserve rights.
Look at this annoying mean person who was mean to me.
They hate women.
Because people say that to her all the time because they hate her, because of
course they do.
And I think his justification for that is that he can take, like, people getting
mad at him because of this.
And he's not a small creator that would be like bullied by J.K.
But, but that's not a good example.
That's not a good, like, I guess it's not a good argument for doing it in the
first place.
I don't care what happens to Vosch.
I just think it was, I just think it's embarrassing.
I feel, I feel embarrassed.
That's, that's it.
I, I don't.
But then again, I've heard so many worse jokes on the PCP itself.
Maybe not recently, but.
Well, it's, it's.
The point, the point is that it, the point is that it's, it's when J.K.
Rowling says it, people listen, you know, that's, that's the difference that
people will hear it and see it.
Uh, this is a, she, like what she says is important as much as I wish that
weren't the case.
I mean, that's true.
I just feel like I'm not sure how, like, this is like a tipping point for
anything in particular.
I feel people who follow J.K.
Rowling on this topic, um, are already transphobic anyway, because they've
already been listening to it.
I don't, I don't know if that's true.
I feel like there's a swath of people who just don't have a nuance take on
this issue and they could, and they like J.K.
because they don't understand.
And maybe they could be persuaded and that's not what happened.
The opposite of that occurred.
This time.
The people who, it's, it's, I really hate the concern trolling aspect of
from like J.K., like, because it's the biggest annoyance is it's like, oh, no,
I love trans people.
I love them.
I support them.
I just think that don't do, I think it's a little bit.
I support, I support that you want children to have healthcare.
Isn't that groomer behavior?
I support them as long as they don't get anything and, and, and they, and I
would rather them kill themselves.
I'd rather these men, these men stay out of our spaces.
I'm going to call them men constantly and deny them healthcare.
And, you know, maybe it's okay that in America, like, um, there are certain areas
where like they're going to check your genitals if you're a kid to, to make sure
that you're the right gender because we don't like pedophilia.
That's where we're going to touch children.
We don't like pedophiles, we definitely don't like pedophiles here.
Uh, but, uh, yeah.
We'll support legislation that allows adults to, to, we have, we have, we have to,
we have to, we need, we need to have, we need to have teachers, uh, patting down
our kids in schools before they use the restroom.
We need to have them checking their genitals on the regular to stamp out pedophilia.
Of course.
Yeah, I think it's just my, my takeaway from that whole thing is that it's a net
like neutral.
I don't think the world has ended because of Vorsch.
I didn't say the world has ended.
I just think it was embarrassing.
Sure.
I don't, I don't, all right.
I will not speak so exaggeratingly, but like, I feel like it's a net neutral.
I feel like it's just sort of like, yeah, whatever.
I think it was bad.
It's kind of amusing that it happened to Vorsch and that he got on fucking,
like news articles written about him.
Well, I don't like it.
I don't like it because I see it as, I see it as a, I see it as him acting out
and being rewarded for bad behavior.
That's what it, that's what it seems like to me.
Ah, sure.
I mean, it was, it was, it was a dumb tweet, I guess.
I just don't, I don't care.
Fine.
All right.
Well, that was what was grinding my gears this week.
And that's the last thing on my stupid list of topics.
My, my gears are neither grinded or they're just, they're just still.
They're neither ground nor on ground.
They're perfectly clean, unused.
They're, they're unfunctioning.
No one ever switched for power on.
I, I have like only like one topic.
I mean, I've been wanting to come on for like a couple of weeks to talk about something.
Because things kept delaying me, I forgot what it was.
So instead I'm going to ask, I'm going to, this was a meme like a few days ago.
Maybe it's already died down.
Maybe you've already had this conversation and if not, we'll just skip it.
But are there more doors or wheels in the world, in your opinion?
Are there more doors or wheels?
Doors.
Why do you say, I think it's wheels.
I would say doors because a single building can have many doors inside.
And I feel like there are more buildings than there are cars,
even though there are a lot of cars.
But it's not because some places don't have cars and like in a big city,
like a skyscraper would have maybe even thousands of doors in it.
And like how many cars take up that real estate on the ground?
I mean, cars have cars have cars have cars have doors.
But, but here's the thing.
They do also have doors.
Sometimes they have as many doors as they have wheels.
Ah, but.
Or maybe even more.
They could have five because there's the boot.
Yeah, but there's usually a spare tire in there too, though.
So, yeah, you got it.
You don't forget about the spare tire.
I'm on team wheels because see, my argument was the same as yours at first
until my husband, Kai, won me over.
He explained, well, yes, but there's like wheels and a lot of things.
You're sitting on a chair.
How many wheels does your chair have?
My chair has five wheels, for example.
An office building, a big tall skyscraper probably has hundreds of office chairs
that have five wheels each.
So, that's that building might actually have more wheels.
A grocery store, so many shopping carts, that's full of wheels.
So, okay.
A hospital, hospital beds.
Yeah, a building can potentially contain like so many different things that have wheels.
Yeah, a wheel has to be, you know, circular, spins around,
and it can roll on the ground like transport something.
Okay, does it have to roll on the ground because that makes a difference?
See, that's an intention because like if it doesn't have to roll along the ground,
then if you have like a chest of drawers, those have wheels in them as well.
Yeah.
So, like my dresser has five drawers and each drawer has four wheels.
Me and my husband counted up my bedroom and we realized that there's like 50 wheels in that one
room.
A piece of machinery, like yeah, like that.
It's not a wheel for rolling a thing around, but it is a wheel.
Yeah, it really is.
We're not interested to count those like influence the answer, but I think wheels went either way.
Okay, but what is a door then?
How would you define door?
A thing with hinges that opens?
It doesn't have to have hinges, sliding doors or a thing.
I think it's like an archway that humans can pass through that can also close and like seal itself.
Okay, so that's very much like more restrictive than the wheel definition, I feel like.
Because if wheels can include like the things inside drawers, then I feel like doors should
be able to include latches and hatches and little openable things.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I think it has to have a hinge.
I think having a hinge is required.
But then sliding doors on a hinge.
But then sliding doors, those are definitely doors.
So like this is more complicated than-
A portal for which you can put human through and close.
But why human?
Is a doggy door a door?
True, actually you're right.
Doggy door should be a door.
Why are the doors on a cupboard not a door, you know?
I guess, I mean, some people do count cupboards.
I feel like if you're counting like the wheels in a drawer, you should count cupboards as well.
But then it's like, I don't know, like I try to like restrict wheels to be like things that
have to like roll on the ground.
Okay, so all right.
But then you can count hot wheels and there's half a billion of O's made a year,
that's two billion wheels every year.
Yeah.
All right, I'm team door for no other reason than to be an alternative on this podcast.
I think the more I think about it, the more just like things that have wheels,
there actually are when you really just get right down to it.
I would posit this definition for door, all right?
A flat plane which can be moved in order to access the other side of a thing.
So like an open door way is not a door?
No, it needs the flat plane like a doorway, like an arch that then you could like count
the arches underneath a bridge, they're not doors, they're just arches.
I think a door would be if you put a flat plane on the bottom of a bridge archway and then you
could move it around to open it and close it.
Is a gate the door?
I think a door is a more architecturally like complicated object than a wheel,
just that it's baseline.
I feel like it's it's that they're harder to produce.
And therefore, sociologically speaking, there must therefore be fewer of them.
Although I think now that I'm saying that a lid is different from a door,
but it's also a flat plane that you can move to access the inside of something.
And our CD's wheels are our hard drive disc wheels.
We go with no because while they do rotate, they don't roll.
They rotate, but they don't roll.
Oh my god, what's the difference between those two things?
They have to roll as the function of the like you can put a circular thing around
an axle.
You're not going to call a coin a wheel because it rolls.
It has to like roll on an axle.
On an axle for the purpose of like bearing loads or transportation.
I'd just say transportation.
Okay, I see.
So to to roll, okay, rolling is a rotation that causes motion with contact with a thing with
friction to move something.
Yeah, either a draw outwards along like a floor, which is like the inside little
metal thing of the of the draw.
That's the floor of that wheel.
That's and that's rolling along that that track.
A train has wheels.
They roll along a track.
That's obvious.
A shopping trolley.
The wheels on an office chair, they roll the chair back and forth.
That counts, I think.
But what about the door to the mind?
What about the door to the mind?
You know what?
I've forgotten.
What if something can like really open your eye?
Open your.
How fool is it?
Wait, are eyelids doors?
Are eyelids doors come on?
Just think about this.
Wait, no, no.
Your eyes, they roll.
They roll in their sockets.
They're wheels.
No, those are the eyeballs.
The eyelids, those are different.
You could have ball shaped wheels.
It's happened.
Some animals have two sets of eyelids.
So that's four doors per iguana.
Per.
Is your mouth a door?
Is your.
Are you into four?
When someone is gatekeeping, does that imply the existence of another gate and therefore a door?
Yeah, it's to stop something going through.
Wait.
It's a barrier.
So a door is a barrier that can be removed and replaced, usually a flat plane.
Maybe a curved plane.
It's a bread box, a door.
Does that have a door?
An oven has a door.
A refrigerator has a door.
It could be like a garage door is a door.
Garage door, yeah.
That's like it can bend.
It can, it can, it can, it has like sheets that like bend at a, at a, what do you call it, a thingy.
An aperture, a large sized aperture can function as a door,
but you also have those in like your camera, you know?
Yeah.
So, so, so a thing that is made to block, this is, this is fun.
So like a wheel is defined as something that rolls along a surface
for purposes of like bearing a load.
It's, it's to move something, it's to move something other than itself.
Because yeah, like a coin can roll, a rock can roll, but they just roll around.
They don't, they're not a wheel.
So I think the wheel has to move something else by rolling.
And so a door is a barrier that can be removed and replaced
in some fashion and it's to stop things getting through.
Wait a minute.
No, I'm so stupid.
So an anus could be a door.
I was going to say, wait a minute.
No, the anus is a window.
The anus is a window.
What's the difference between those things?
Look, I could, when God, when God closes one, he opens the other.
That's the difference.
I think windows could be doors.
I think they really could.
You can classify a window as a door.
I almost said, wait a minute, bread rolls.
Oh shit.
So is bread a wheel?
Well, it isn't, it isn't, it transports itself, but it doesn't transport other things.
Unless you put something inside the bread roll.
Unless you put butter.
So it's transporting butter.
Okay, now we're talking.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Even with this limitation, I still think the wheels on a Hot Wheels car count as wheels.
They still do their job.
They're just small.
Wait, but a Hot Wheels car has doors.
The doors don't open.
Some of them.
The doors are like painted on, but they don't actually open.
Yeah, those aren't mazed to be removed and replaced.
I think that, oh, what was it?
I was going to say something.
Bicycles, roller skates.
Pockets, pockets of doors.
When they have like a little thing you can close.
We have a zip.
A zip tie pocket.
A pocket is a bag or bags doors, I don't know.
Okay, hold on.
If you have a school bag, you can zip that up.
I feel like it's funny because you could have like a tarp with a zip for a tent.
And that's a door to the tent, but it is a zip thing.
So you're not in a bag that's sized for a human.
You're in a tent and it has a door.
All right, so I think bags could have doors to the inside of the bag.
As you can see, according to Google Trends, interest over time in doors is consistently higher.
There are more searches.
Yeah, there's 93 searches a day for doors and only in the 60s for wheels.
So Google Trends, they're both on the rise, by the way, as of recently.
So I think this is a strong indicator in Dora's favor.
They're just more popular.
And that means there must be more of them.
They're on people's minds.
Counterargument.
What is this?
In the U.S., this person estimates that 700 million doors are produced per year versus
like Hot Wheels alone, 2 billion wheels per year.
That's a pretty big difference.
Yeah, but I don't know his definition of door.
He's probably thinking you have to have a human walk through it.
True, they're probably thinking like doors for houses.
Hold on.
Where does he get his information on the U.S. door market?
You know, this guy's got Rudolf in his name and that makes me not trust him.
That sounds like someone who's a bad.
Like Bernie Rudolf, uh, Madoff.
Yeah.
That's what they call them.
Nathan Rudolf, Nathan Adolf.
He just removed some letters.
I was going to say Madoff, like Enron, 2008 market crash.
But yeah, sure.
What about virtual doors?
What about doors in a video game in Zelda?
You know, Minecraft has zero wheels, but it has no wheels at all.
So many doors.
But you can make an infinite amount of doors with that game.
How many villages are in a Minecraft world?
Does a mine cart not have wheels?
Oh, it does.
I mean, but that's four.
There's a boat.
There's a boat in a mine cart.
Mine carts just float on the track.
We don't actually have wheels that are like, you can see.
No way.
Is that true?
It's just a square.
Like there are no wheels.
I don't even think they're really painted on.
I mean, is a square wheel still a wheel?
I have to confirm this.
If it rolls and it moves something, yeah, I would say.
Oh, yeah.
No, there's no wheel.
There's no wheel on the mine cart.
Holy shit.
This changes everything.
So there's definitely more doors than mine.
There's sort of an implication of wheels in the sprite, but the 3D model.
No.
Yeah.
If you count wheels, I mean, they appear in mine shafts, but there's like villages.
Actually, okay.
I actually, I mean, this is the one you can solve with math because let's just assume
that a mine cart has four wheels.
If I do naturally generate sometimes they're just rare, but they have more wheels per
mine cart than a regular door.
If someone booted up a Minecraft world scanned like, you know, like 10 million
chunks out and counted all the doors and all the wheels and naturally generate,
which would win.
That's actually a good question.
Someone could do that.
I think definitely the doors would win just because of the fact that villages have
more than one building and all the buildings have doors.
Yeah.
I feel like villages are about as rare as mine shafts.
It's true.
Mine shafts only have a couple of mine carts here and there.
And this fits other wheels in Minecraft.
I'm not thinking of.
Sometimes there's a mine shaft that's huge.
It doesn't have any mine carts.
That's true.
Oh, wait, no, they have mine carts inside chests, don't they?
Oh, yeah.
I mean.
They never have them spawn randomly outside.
At least I've never seen that.
No, there are mine carts with chests that are just sitting around,
like as entities that are just mine cart chests.
So it's a mine cart with a chest inside.
You see those around.
Wow.
I see on the wiki that you can make one of those.
Fascinating.
Oh, you can put a furnace in your mine cart?
You can put a hopper?
You never tried that?
No.
You can make a little train.
You can have like a, this is something I used to do way back
where I would have like my base and then I-
What the hell is the word in?
What the fuck?
I think that's a new thing.
It's a new, extremely scary mob that's coming in the game.
I don't think it's in the game yet.
It looks insane.
It's in the game in the experimental snapshot
that they released two weeks ago.
I summoned one just on the overworld.
It wasn't even in a cave and it was actually really scary.
I was really scared because when he's around,
your vision goes fucking down.
You can barely see anything.
That must be why it's a popular page right now because it's new.
So freaky looking.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
You can make like a little furnace mine cart.
You can put like a bunch of mine carts ahead of it
and fill it with the chest with the stuff.
And then you put coal in the furnace
and then it'll go choo-choo and it'll push the other mine carts
along the track.
Yeah.
So you can like have a little train
deliver your stuff to your base
while you're doing the other things.
Yeah.
That's kind of cool.
Powered rails are more reliable though.
I've heard furnace mine carts are not.
Sure.
I mean this is like before powered rails were even a thing.
That was the way to do it.
What about high speed rail?
What about China?
High speed rail, trash.
Clearly we need the hyperloop from Elon Musk.
It's totally not a scam.
He's totally not going to go to jail
when his investors find out he's been selling vaporware
for the past 10 years.
I agree because car dependency is good
because the price of gas is so reliable.
It's so much clearly it's more economically efficient
for instead of having a train like one engine
that carries like a hundred people
to have a hundred engines that carry one person each.
Clearly that's more efficient.
Economies have scaled bad wrong.
Let's move in the opposite direction.
Elon Musk is clearly correct.
They just keep hiring new like brain trustees
you know fresh out of Ivy Leagues or whatever
to be like hey guys think of a new way.
Think of a new way to transport people efficiently.
And they just can't stop reinventing buses and trains.
They just can't do it any better.
They're desperate but they'll never stop.
And they're just going to keep doing it and doing it
because they've got to keep pulling in that salary.
They've got to keep pretending they had a new idea.
I thought of it a window right is a type of door
that you can also see through.
So not all doors are windows but all windows are doors.
I feel like if you're not meant to go through the window
then it's a window and not a door.
What if it's fun to do that though.
No fun is no there's no room for fun.
We're here on a fact-finding mission.
But you're not supposed to go into a cupboard when you open that.
Would that be a window.
If it's got if it's made of glass.
What if you have a glass cupboard.
Shit I do feel I feel like covered doors.
I feel like I feel like wardrobes and cabinets have doors.
Actually no not all windows are doors.
If you can't open the window then it's not a door.
Yes but many windows can be doors because you can open them.
I think we.
Game Fury. Game Fury needs to make a video about this clearly.
Is a sandwich a door because it's like an open and close it.
Yeah yeah.
Do you just want to go to voicemails.
I think we can all agree the sandwiches are not wheels.
I think we can all.
So very for they must be doors.
Weak.
They're either one or the other.
It's either on the one I mean wheels and doors.
They're all they're all in a spectrum right.
And if you're not one you must be closer to being the other.
Are humans doors or wheels.
Wait a minute.
Every door is on the hinges and a hinge rotates and is a wheel inside the door.
Doors contain wheels within them.
Wheels within wheels.
I would disagree.
I would say that it is not rolling along a surface.
It is just rolling in place.
It is rotating.
If you take a single wheel and mathematically and you define every radius from its center
geometrically speaking you can divide every wheel into an infinite number of wheels.
Every wheel is composed of an infinite number of infinitely thin geometrically defined wheels.
You know sliding doors are operated by wheels and you might be saying the wheel is rotating
in place and it's moving the door.
Well if you believe in the theory of relativity and you use the door as a reference frame
the door is standing still.
The wheel is rolling along the door carrying the universe with it.
100% I'm on board with this idea.
Yes but not all doors are sliding doors and also you could extrapolate
every possible angle a door could be open at as a different door.
I mean like a phantom door just like you could with a phantom wheels.
All 360 degrees of rotation are possible wheel states.
Does okay I forget whether or not relativity holds true between rotating frames of reference.
So I'm just going to assume it does and therefore say that based on your frame of reference
there's nothing in the universe that can be ruled out.
Are orbits wheels.
You can't say anything isn't rotating definitively therefore
everything is a wheel in one.
No I think at least one reference frame.
I think you could say that no no no no no no.
Orbits are not wheels.
Planets could be wheels because they are rolling through space.
Spacetime.
Consider the planetary system is a wheel and in that case.
Consider every molecule every atom with its orbiting electrons just you know in a solid
crystal matrix obviously obviously the the atoms are not wheels because they're all fixed in place
relative to one another but in a liquid or a gas the wheel they're all sloshing over one another
they're rolling they're rolling around at the speed of sound.
This conversation is literally wheel spinning right now.
My fucking god.
Liquid is door okay here's why.
Yeah I'm listening I'm ready to hear you out on this.
The door a door is is is too is it's a blockage it's it stops something going through but it
can be removed and replaced every single particle you can't phase through a particle it'd be pushed
out of the way so each particle going past another particle pushing it out of the way is a door
opening and closing behind another particle so every single thing in the universe is a door.
So we've decided that every every thing every discrete object every discrete
particle in the universe is both a wheel and a door.
Yeah yeah that's good I think that's that works I'm satisfied which if they're all if they're
all doors and wheels when they cancel out and then the none of them are other than only one
matters are like what like composites of objects.
When everyone's a door no one will be.
Oh god you're right.
Post it post in the comments here your interesting arguments for what a door and what is a wheel.
I want to see as many creative ideas as possible.
I really think I really think Bosch was being a door with that comment of his and Rowling was
being a real wheel by say having an opinion about wheelie bad optics in Ben's but I think
this opens doors for his notoriety now we can do he can say.
I don't want to talk about this anymore I shouldn't have said it like Bush adorable you know I hate
you thank you finally somebody had to say it
voicemails yeah okay okay okay okay I'm gonna do it I'm gonna do it right now
let's see pulling them up we got the first one is called why image voicemails suck let me find
it here we go this is why image 528 hertz didn't change my dna of the image lied that's why
uh oh sorry about that okay here we go three two one go
I get it I get it that's funny is it is it quiet is it silent is that the joke
I mean usually when people send images I assume they like don't even actually like send a voicemail
it's just like half a second of silence or whatever a lot of a time right it's yeah it's
zero seconds that's probably the joke I don't know if I get it maybe image voicemails are good
image voicemails suck because they don't contain audio voice I mean they they don't need it it's
it's just another way of like just sending an image to react to like the voicemail
like service provides multiple functions you can send a voicemail and you can send other
shit too okay then the next one is is an audio an image voicemail and it's this this map of a
u n generally assembly resolution on combating the glorification of nazism neo nazism contemporary
forms of racism racial discrimination this is uh how how uh how this country's voted or something
wait a combating combating the glorification okay that's weird against how come wait a minute
I think I saw this before but I don't know wait is this saying that it was only the united states
and and ukraine the voted against yeah I mean it wouldn't surprise me too much but I don't know
what this is about more I saw I saw uh statistics that showed uh ukraine as being uh particularly
accepting of jews among eastern european states yeah it's it's hard to know which things are what
um yeah it was basically like what the question that was like do you think jews should be allowed
or should they be kicked out or whatever oh yeah should they be would you accept them as citizens
yeah like they should should they be allowed to be citizens and ukraine like five percent said no
but in like russia 15 percent said no and it was like yeah ukraine was like the most accepting of
all of the surrounding countries yeah um but the way this graph is kind of if this is true this is
kind of weird though like even new zealand like abstained that's weird I feel like I've seen the
same graph before and I I don't remember it looking like this I don't remember it being just
ukraine yeah I remember Australia I thought Australia and New Zealand like where I wonder if I can find
it I don't know and like if you think New Zealand would be green though they're pretty progressive I
don't know uh I don't know maybe but also also I sure Africa is all green there's a guy I forget
which country in Africa there's the guy there's a guy called Adolf Hitler who's like in charge
somewhere in there yeah I don't know I don't know how much we can really glean from this graph
I don't know seems fake I'm just gonna say it's fake nah nah it didn't happen uh did you go to
find something I'm I'm just seeing if I can like google to find what the this is from if you if you
change your name to get boob a take that's one extra wheel in your name that what where's the wheel
it's just like circles the letter O is a wheel if you think about it no no we just decided that
it has to roll along the surface boo like a coin a coin isn't a wheel but all the atoms that make
up but it could yeah the coin itself is definitely not yeah it's true okay oh you know what you're
right actually I was getting I was getting ahead of myself um okay next next voicemail is uh what is
this one 290 it is called uh at killer prints 930 uh three two one go have you guys read roof girl
no read girl right now roof girl like on the ceiling like she's on the roof what's girl
apparently apparently this is a location in Adelaide when I research it I get a it's a I think
it's a business yeah it's a business in Adelaide where is that in Canada where is Adelaide is that
Australia where the fuck is Ali I don't know okay I have found whatever the point is I can't
like it yeah it's Australia it's Australia I was right okay I have found the United Nations thing
this is talking about combating glorification of Nazism neo-Nazis and other practices that
contribute to the fueling contemporary forms of racism racial discriminations and infobia and
related intolerance and uh there's a bunch of the things and the two nos are indeed Ukraine and
the United States well that's weird so that is weird I did not I have not had a moment to read
like the full thing if I can that is pretty weird but I don't know what to make up to this I don't
know what to make of that information yeah it's weird I mean I know that there are like neo-nazis
in Ukraine but like the fact that the country you voted for it is odd because like the this was in
2020 I think Zelensky was already like the leader at that point well like surely the graph that was
posted in the image says 2018 that's weird maybe they did it multiple times I feel like this is
the one because it's like all the yes I don't know maybe my guy same maybe I should go and
un-un-pledge my uh my support from that Ukraine bundle oh no I can't no I can't
oh but the value though no the value oh kingdom two oh yeah five dollars off kingdom two I mean
this has been brought up sometimes it's like uh how could you support x because there are bad
people over there and it was the same with the Palestine relief like Hamas is benefiting from
support of of the people with like aid to like civilians running from being killed
and it's like true but like I think it's fine because people are being displaced by war and
they need help so like whatever it's not like I it's not like the charity is give guns to Nazis
the charity it's like food water shelter um relocation of of of like refugees it's like
that's where the money's going I mean one hopes I mean one would expect one would hope one would
hope even the majority of it would do that is like at it whatever yeah uh okay whatever I can't uh
I can't draw any conclusions from this graph really conclusion I can draw reading that
thing is it says n for no but also nuke crane uh these guys boy I hope they don't do that I hope
they don't just saying uh don't do it don't no okay next one is called scrub quoting wordle
three two one go I'm here to bitch about the March 8th wordle sweet is the worst type of word
that can be a wordle it has a double vowel so you're not going to get that set up just get good
shut up I just get good maybe I got a quick um it has an interchangeable uh the Dark Souls is too
hard because uh the boss attacks too fast you can't dodge it could be you know sweet like it is it
could be sweet it could be sheet it could be ski it could probably be something else I'm not thinking
yeah yeah and I'm just very fucking mad it ruined my like 30 days treat your wordle
I'm this is the reason that mr wordle the person who made wordle sort so I've gotta hold on um I have
to deal with the liability of this exact moment I gotta I gotta find the one that that was ruined
me that would be coming this way he's going to pay with blood I'm going to fucking kill mr wordle
okay it was it's definitely just that wordle is a kind of a flawed game because of the moments
like that where it's like even if you are smart you'll just lose because of unlucky letter choices
oh the one that I lost on was uh January 31st might might that's the one that uh I couldn't do
oh did you get it and then it was like yeah well I got I got it on my fifth guess so
yeah fifth guess was fight fourth guess or six guess was might wait and the actual one was
uh it was light yeah it was light so it was it was kind of the sims yeah yeah that one almost
got me yeah it got me oh yeah there's like four words I can do that yeah I turned over the one that
was like six words I don't remember right now yeah what uh watch right watch match batch
maybe yeah yeah latch latch catch that one's that one's super bad yeah
hatch latch what catch watch damn that's like five at least yeah patch uh patch yes no
all right next one is all right here we go next one is kylan funny man episode six uh it's a
vocaru and it's uh it's it's five minutes long so uh we're in for it uh here here we go
oh jeez like the files are too powerful all right week me and I'll post it because I
have discord nitro oh thank you thank you very much uh here you here you go I will use my
nitro for good I know a bunch of people were um I saw some people on twitter who were mad at
discord for twitter links not embedding properly and making it harder to post nsfw stuff and they were
considering dropping their nitro but I use it too often to send files because my work is
through discord a lot of the time I have seen uh I have seen had twitter image twitter post not
embed correctly that's but I don't have nitro so no no nitro doesn't fix that issue it's just um
yeah some of the do if on the one hand twitter doesn't want images embedding because they don't
want people not using the platform um and discord simultaneously is also like being
restricting nsfw stuff more like they can like they're trying to make it so you can't post it
anywhere unless the channel is marked as nsfw which is a little annoying um but trying to send
stuff to people in dms who you're friends with uh of artists and stuff but oh anyway so it's a file
I see okay uh well here we go kyle and funny man episode six three
three two one go
funner than before kyle and funny man will never make you snore kyle and funny man look who's at
the door kyle and funny man in space
oh my god funny man can you believe that we're back oh yes kyle finally after all this time back to
status quo exactly a wise man once said old good new bad as well as
goodness of the status quo and we're back to the status quo which was the old con funner
man not the new one where there was dramatics happening you're so correct every single time
you speak kyle you are so correct so kyle's just like me let's go on a crazy adventure funny man
we haven't done that in a while true true let me put the uh the show makes me think what if I had
a friend like funny man into the computer beep beep beep beep beep beep all right we're traveling to
a different planet now hell yeah I believe him what do we do in the meantime the meeting pickles
by the way i'm snacking nice dude ah pickle rick's no yes remember the yellow argument
yes remember tommy jay yes remember rad con yes remember dry dumps
yes remember when we referenced dry dumps in episode two yes remember ben saint no i don't
what remember ben saint yes remember riddle my ass batman
yes remember samurai sama yes remember lectures yes remember keep and take
yes remember voice grail yes remember when ben said forgot to put kyle and funny man on the
voice grail document along with other voice grail recipients such as doid gazers what the
fuck are you even talking about remember Nate bestman who remember tricksy who could forget
dude remember the pcp yes this is this is just like me and my friends yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
scooby-doo skipity-dee go and climb up a tree making games ribbity woo these are things that
give to
yes i drink cum and love it too then i go and swim and poo i eat hay
and i'm gay these are things that ben st
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes....
its so groovy
never shows up, never dies
furry character, fake in the pie
broken back, never come
Yeah!
Yes!
D.C.P.
You're gonna be funny man, remember this was the kind of funny man episode?
Yeah, that was a pretty fun time. Now it's this, I guess.
Yeah, you know what they say, a wise person once said that if you don't know how to end
an episode, just end it in a wall next to your random papa, you know?
Every time you open your mouth, just pure gold. Just pure gold.
You don't suck alcohol coming out of your sweet little bubble.
Oh, thank you for your time. I'm glad we are friends and discuss things here on the station.
I want to kill myself.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't.
Well, if you do, I sure would be laughing.
No, he meant like, if he met himself, he would kill himself, but not in like that way.
Like, he would like shoot and kill the evil part of himself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was great. It was a little musical.
It didn't even feel like five minutes.
No, that flew by and some part of that's got to be the theme song.
Oh, of course.
Oh, hell yeah.
Some section.
Play the whole.
Honestly, yeah.
Well, that was great.
Should I put the link to the Vokaroo file in the descriptions?
You can hear it if you want.
Without us jabbering over it, I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
Lol.
Okay, they should be in the voice gray elephant already.
They should, yeah.
Definitely after that.
Who did they say we forgot to put in there?
Doid gazers.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe someone else too.
I'm not sure.
They probably are other people.
Okay.
All right.
That was great.
Let's see who's next.
The next voicemail is from...
Well, it's called Jelly Beaner.
Where's the...
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Well, here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Riddle me this PCP.
I'm loud and obnoxious.
I like music that rhymes.
I'm a fraction of the population.
But commit half the crime.
Yeah.
Who am I?
Jelly Beaner.
You're Trixie.
You wrote your name right on the voicemail.
Yeah.
What were you thinking?
I can't believe you commit half the crime.
That's insane.
Yeah, congratulations.
Okay.
Next one is...
It's called Woof.
Next one's called Woof.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you think you got it rough?
Just imagine being Ben St.
Woof.
True.
You know, true words were never spoken.
I think about that every time I'm in a bad place.
I was like, well, imagine if I was Ben St.
It could be so much worse.
Oh, God.
No.
No, it's great.
No, I got so much space for my bags of sparkling water bottles.
It's luxurious in here.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I got so many...
Did you just say bags filled with sparkling water?
Well, yeah.
Well, the bottles.
Yeah, but yes.
Sparkling water bottles are doors.
I got space.
I have a nice little parking lot outside.
You know, this is not too many rats.
It's good.
Just enough rats.
The right amount.
The amount you're looking for.
Okay.
Next one is an image thing.
There it is.
This guy.
Oh, it's Destiny.
There he is.
Well, I guess...
He's looking like a...
He's looking like a Doctor Who.
I guess we're gonna fuck because Destiny fucks and...
for fucking...
No.
He does look pretty good here.
But if anyone slapped my ass, I'd be like, what?
Huh?
Wait, is that him?
Did they like Photoshop his face onto this guy?
That's not his actual face, right?
It was not his actual body.
Probably.
I mean, I guess it could be.
I thought it was Photoshop.
Okay, whatever.
Nice, nice coat, asshole.
Next one is Ben's weekly reminder.
Play Deltarune Chapter 2.
Okay.
There's no voicemail with that.
The next one is, okay.
There's a...
There is a thing.
Oh, okay.
There's a link that goes along.
It's the link to MangaHelk gets anime adaptation.
Let's hear the thing.
Hold on.
Where is it?
It's 2, 9, 7.
Here we go.
Bam.
Post it.
Okay.
3, 2, 1, go.
I know you're about to finish Simon's punishment.
What if you just stop and then make Beast Copains?
What if you just quit?
Excuse me.
Just delete all of it.
What if you remain Simon's punishment, but instead it was Beast Copains and Phantom
Horn is a beast?
Beast Copains and punishment.
Intriguing.
Beast Coslime.
Man.
Okay, man.
Good voicemail.
Okay.
Next one is called Be the Bigger Man.
There we go.
3, 2, 1, go.
In this society that we live in, you are forced to choose between being comfortable and being
free.
Being comfortable and being free.
And it's a tough choice.
I could live in a shack like Ted Kaczynski and I could be happy and free or I could play
Chapter 3 of Delta Rune when it comes out.
And it's a really hard choice.
And at the end of the day it's all about being a man or something.
And being bigger because the bigger man wins.
Always strive to be the hugest possible.
Yeah.
Be huge and gigantic and tower over everybody.
You gotta be in like a fish.
It's like the fish game.
You gotta be the big fish that eats all the little fish.
And then you just keep getting bigger.
Just keep getting bigger.
Or.
Nice.
It's Spore.
Oh yeah.
Spore.
Yeah.
Okay.
Next one is called...
Wait.
I almost missed one.
Okay.
Next one is called Nathan.
3, 2, 1, go.
Bring back the no Nate, no watch guy.
I miss you, bro.
He's already here.
He's been in the cold the whole time.
Wait.
He was.
Was he not?
Did he not show up in the comments?
I feel like I saw him in the light.
Yeah.
I feel like I saw him very recently.
Oh God.
I always forget what it's like.
S C H W.
Video production, something like that.
I think it's like S C H W videos.
And I after all this time, I still, I still forget the order of the letters.
But his contribution is invaluable.
Next one is called...
It's called the two's company, Ben Saints new living situation.
3, 2, 1, go.
What?
Hey, Ben St.
It's me, your landlord.
Oh.
Uh oh.
I've been listening to the podcast.
You sound different.
Quite frankly, I have to finding out what you do.
I don't, I don't believe no more that you're going to be able to pay the rent.
Take me to court over it.
Reliably.
I fucking dare you.
And protection.
I decided that you're going to have to rule together with another person.
Now don't worry.
I've already found a person.
Oh, thank God.
Uh, her name's Trixie.
I hear she's a content creator as well.
But she has, she's got a company.
She's got a company.
She probably makes a lot of money.
She's got a studio.
Well, she should get her own studio apartment.
And you can split the rent.
And then I know that I'm going to get paid.
Enjoy, darling.
Thanks.
Sorry, sorry to put you through so much trouble, Milady.
This is the beginning of the sitcom arc.
Praise, praise be.
Due to a wacky set of circumstances, Ben and Trixie are living together once again.
Somebody on episode one.
Somebody on Kiwi Farms spotted Trixie and Bird in the wild and took their picture in a Costco.
Just standing in line.
Just standing.
Hey, Ben, if you're serious about expanding your literary palette,
you might want to pick up Hyperion by Dan Simmons.
It set the stage for a lot of modern sci-fi and is really cool.
Hmm.
Let's see.
Is it a book?
Hyperion Simmons novel.
No, I thought it was pretty funny.
Uh, next one is called Hyperion 321 Go.
It's a novel, not the Dan Simmons.
The first book of his Hyperion canto is it won the Hugo Award for Best Novel.
Oh, wow.
The Hugo Award for Best Novel ever.
Just the one.
The one best novel.
Hmm.
Uh, that is neat.
I don't know.
I've never even heard of Dan Simmons before.
Maybe I have.
I don't know.
Doesn't ring a bell.
Uh, I'm going to go to the library soon and pick up some books.
I think I want to read.
I don't know what I mentioned this before.
I think I want to read some, uh, I almost said Fauci.
No, Foucault.
I want to read some Foucault, uh, just because.
And I'll pick up some other shit, too.
Foucault is the inventor of Funko Pops.
Yeah.
Uh, all right.
Next, uh, voicemail is called.
Wait, all the gib is in the background.
Oh, wait.
Oh, she's back.
Oh, I was fast.
Um, okay.
One is called, um, application three, two, one go.
Hello.
Can I get the press pass for P three?
I want to demo all the sweets, new games, uh, interview the creators, um, do all that,
uh, stuff, write articles.
I need that press pass for P three, please.
Hmm.
Yes.
And we should, we should look into, uh, hiring fucking the bronicon area, wherever that was
in Baltimore.
Baltimore.
We get the big old thing, we hire out the whole place and it's P three and Tom still
won't show up, but we'll have his game there.
We'll take credit for it.
If he won't.
Yeah.
P for pony.
Okay.
Next one is called, uh, please wait.
Here we go.
Yes.
It's called please.
There it is.
Three, two, one go.
Ben, can you upload the episodes to Spotify?
No.
I've been waiting forever.
I can't.
Tom doesn't.
I don't know how.
Thanks for asking.
Uh, next one is called, uh, uh, next one is called.
The old Ben.
Three, two, one go.
Ben, you're starting to forgive Trixie now.
That's not like you.
What the fuck, man?
Come on.
Go back to your old self.
I missed old Ben.
Come on.
Wait, I'm starting to do what?
Forgive Trixie.
Forgive her.
When did I say that?
I never said that.
And I never will.
She was mean to me and now she's, now she's gotta die.
Um, next one is called, uh, uh, the long, the long, long enough.
Okay.
Three, two, one go.
The episodes have been too short.
We need at least a five hour show every single week.
Sorry.
Well, maybe we could if you gave better voicemails that we could riff on.
Yeah, I can't.
I can't.
Have a think about that.
Can't do anything.
You know, you gotta, you know, it's like Papa John says, better ingredients, better pizza.
And you're giving a shitty ingredients right now.
So this pizza is coming out rotten.
Just like Midgar.
If you know what I'm saying.
Midgar?
Yes.
Barrett, Barrett, Barrett calls Midgar a rotten pizza.
Old slices.
I think it's, I think, I think Tim Rogers says in English, he just calls it a pizza.
But I think in Japanese, he calls it like a rotten pizza.
Lamal.
So that's important.
That's big.
There's a, there's like a, one of the, the audio tracks is like something rotten pizza.
What?
One of the audio tracks, the name of the audio track for Final Fantasy seven of like Midgar
is like something pizza.
What, like a song in the game?
Like, like the OST, you know.
Oh.
It's funny.
I didn't know that.
Neat.
Okay.
Next one is called Ben's music career part two.
Wait.
Oh, I already posted it.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I think that Ben's music career is an amazing idea.
Why?
Well, think about it.
Trixie had a music career and she set the bar really low.
Her music was fucking dog shit.
It wouldn't be that hard to make an album.
Yes.
And that would make me tons of money.
Just imagine the ego devastation it would do to her.
It would be just another easy win.
Like, there's no reason for you not to do this.
I think it's an amazing idea.
You know what?
It would be, I should be effortless.
Just be effortless.
Just start producing music when I don't know how to do that.
Easy W.
Just an easy W.
Just the other day.
I've just been like, what if I just did a low stakes acoustic guitar album with maybe
some songs I wrote?
I thought you were going to say rap.
No.
I would never rap.
I could never rap my head around it.
Rap.
That's a rap.
Adrien Pines Rap.
It would be like Beatles Inspire.
Just sort of like, here's a song about a wet towel or whatever.
Do you have songs or would you have to make them?
I'd make them.
But like it's easy.
You just take some chords.
You put them in some sort of order and you play them.
Jesus Christ.
Sounds scary to me.
Make me uncomfortable.
A low stakes low effort little album.
I just feel like doing it.
Well, I'd be impressed.
Good.
Thank you.
I mean, I liked your old songs on your band camp.
I'd really liked a bunch of the stuff you used to put out.
I think that was pretty cool.
I like the greatest shit.
I listen to it every so often.
The greatest ships?
I don't think I remember that.
Shits.
With a T.
It's like greatest hits.
I compiled a bunch of the old songs into the greatest shits just because they were all.
I see, I see.
I think chicken and a basketball is in there.
Yeah, chicken and basketball.
I like the song about the squid.
Everybody's talking about the squid because I'm gay.
I love that song.
Who's my egg?
Also a classic.
It actually reminds me.
Short short short little story short little Minecraft story.
Yeah.
So me and my friends have a Minecraft server.
We've been running it for three and a half years.
And about a year and a half in, you know, we'd been living in this town.
We'd been working on it for a while.
We dug out, there are two rivers nearby that we connected into like a canal that led out
to the ocean.
If you take it by boat, we'd built all this cool stuff.
We'd built bridges across and everything.
One day we're just fucking around by my friend's house and we see an egg, a Minecraft egg floating
in the river.
And we're just like, oh, oh, let's go pick it up.
And we couldn't fucking pick up the egg.
You know, the egg would not pick up.
Like an egg, a chicken egg, like an item just floating.
Yeah.
Like that exactly.
And we just, it was weird.
And we were like, why can't we fucking, we have space in our inventory.
We didn't know what was going on.
Actually, I'll get a screenshot of the egg because we got a fucking video of it too.
Got to see this egg.
Yeah.
So I'm going to screenshot of the video real quick.
So that's, oh, wow, that was back when I had my old skin.
So yeah.
And we're just staring at it and we built a platform and we managed to get the egg onto
the platform and we realized that five minutes had passed and the egg hadn't despawned.
All items on the ground despawn after five minutes, but the egg was still there after
like eight minutes.
The infinity egg.
Yeah.
And we were like trying to like bring the egg to safety.
We dug like a channel.
Protect the egg.
Hold on.
Another screenshot.
We got it out of the river.
There we go.
And in the video, I was re-watching it recently.
I started singing Who's My Egg just in the video and it was great.
Is that a Gibbs song?
It's a Gibbs song.
Who's My Egg.
I can't remember how it goes.
You say, who's my egg?
And it's like, who needs an egg?
You.
Me?
Yeah.
And I love that part.
And I sing it to myself.
Well, but what happened afterwards is we're like, if the egg doesn't despawn and you can't
pick it up, is it also immune to lava?
And this was a dangerous question.
And so we, I grabbed the four elements.
I threw a piece of string at it and I said air and then I dropped some dirt.
I said earth.
I splashed some water and then I used my flint and steel for just a second.
The egg burned for like a second and then it disappeared and made the guy who suggested
it.
He had to be executed.
Yeah.
We had a public execution.
We took him to.
And it was really funny.
I'd built a giant Enderman statue like in a hole in the ground and the Enderman is holding
his head.
Oh, I got a screenshot of this too.
Let me see.
Yeah.
And so me and Four Eyes who, you know, he's been on the PCP.
He was on episode 25.
Yeah.
That's me and Four Eyes.
We executed and we both fired by firing squad.
We shot him off the egg and he fell off the egg, off the head.
Off the egg.
We shot him off of his own head and he fell to his death.
And then I chased him.
That's the Enderman.
He's holding his big face.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
The floor looks like his face.
This is a big drop because we built a full-sized Enderman like in a hole in the ground.
It was this big project.
I spent like weeks on it.
And then afterwards, I wasn't satisfied.
I chased him down his mining tunnel that was, I think, 30,000 blocks long.
And then like chased him through the air by a lighter and fucking murdered him a second
time.
It was really funny.
Okay.
One day this video will be out and it is really funny.
That's what he gets for suggesting what to do with an egg.
Dude, we were thinking about if the egg survived, we were going to put it in a glass case in
the center of town where it could sit there for all eternity.
It was going to be a monument.
It would have been glorious.
It's going to be a national treasure.
And instead, it died because he's like, oh, let's just set it on fire.
It'll see what happens.
They've ever forgiven him.
No, I wouldn't either.
But yeah, I just reminded of that story.
Anyway, Who's My Egg is a Good Song.
That's great.
I don't know.
Shit.
Yeah, I don't remember that one.
Oops.
Damn.
I'm sure the egg's still out there somewhere.
Yeah, maybe.
It's in a better place.
It's time.
It's time on this earth could have been better spent elsewhere.
And so it had to go.
It had to return to its own planet.
It's people needed it.
It's people.
You mean these people specifically?
An egg guide to Minecraft.
Oh, God.
What the fuck?
This brings back nightmares.
He's not doing so well.
And he's going to give me a guide to Minecraft.
Do you know what this is?
I don't.
I don't know.
It looks like.
I actually, I do know what it is.
I remember seeing this in like 2011.
I suppressed it.
I just showed up on Minecraft and I was looking for eggs.
It was like this weird animation series by Almond Animation.
And I had like a voice actor.
The guy, the guy I had who voiced Steve like died a few years ago.
And it was like a thing.
That's all I remember.
Fummer.
Well, that's weird.
Okay.
Well, the next voicemail, I posted it up above.
It is called, what is it called?
It's called Slime and Delainishment.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, please finish your game and publish it.
You have started reading Flat Slime and Funny Strings and it's very funny.
It will be done.
Please release it in the fight finale.
Please, please, please, please.
By the time you're hearing this, it will be out.
It will be out.
Also, I will, when I post it, I'm going to record because I am several months behind on recording my Patreon Q&A.
I'm going to record a new episode of that where I answer the last questions that were posted on the last one.
And then I'm going to post that.
And my hope then is that people will post replies to that Q&A if they want to ask me stuff about the game, right?
Because when the game is out, maybe people will want to talk to me about that.
And so I'll post a new episode of the Q&A podcast and then I invite patrons to ask me about the game probably in the replies to that episode that will be out soon.
It should probably be out by the time this is going live.
I just had a realization.
What's that?
Is an egg a door?
It's definitely a wheel.
We need an alignment chart.
We need an alignment chart of chaotic versus form versus function for doors and wheels.
And both of them should have an egg on there somewhere.
I think because it's hard because it's a barrier, the outer shell of the egg separating the inside and the outside.
But it can't be closed.
A door should open and close.
It can't be opened and closed.
But it does open.
It is designed to open via a little beak from the inside.
Yeah.
Gotta write a thesis paper on this.
Ponder it in philosophy forever.
I can't think of anything more important to be doing.
Okay, next one is called Shit's Niche, bro.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, I will send Slamming Management to APERS, a few people that have never, ever, ever heard of you.
I'm very curious as to the reaction and how much they even understand.
Geez.
I hope everybody does that.
I think he was laughing, perhaps at my expense.
It sounded like he was blowing his nose as well.
Well, I don't know, maybe.
Yeah, I think everyone should show Slamming Punishment to everyone they know.
In my opinion, part of the appeal is that probably a lot of it won't make sense.
Well, you know, I think you can read it and understand what's going on pretty easily.
I don't think it's actually that hard to follow.
There will be plenty of references that you don't get.
But they're not important.
They're just details, things in the background, stuff.
I feel like it's not actually that hard to read.
Maybe to get 100% of, to understand everything.
Yeah, super hard.
I think the challenge is not whether it's literally comprehensible,
but whether it presents itself in a way that people would want to read more.
Oh, I don't know what this is.
I guess I'll leave it.
People act like that.
Sure.
I mean, yeah.
That's what they say about the first sentence of a book is the most important,
because if it's not good, then why would the person continue reading?
Oh, I mean, the first drawings of Slamming Punishment are just terrible.
Oh, shit.
Oh, well.
That had a great cover.
Oh, it'll have a good cover.
Oh, yeah, I gotta make a cover.
I made that good promo image for Phantom's Adventure.
Phantom's Adventure is really proud of how that came out.
That looks pretty good.
Anyway, next one is called
saintcomics.com
slash patreon.com
slash bensaint.com
three, two, one, go.
Okay, last one.
I want to let you know about
saintcomics.com's mobile phone issue.
When you try to read stuff on it,
a.k.a. Slamming Punishment or whatever,
it gets cut off on the left-hand side slightly.
Does it?
Just enough to be annoying.
Let me.
And it's not centered.
And I guess phone compatibility is kind of a big thing these days.
You might want to try and get fixed out.
Yeah, let me.
I've been reading on PC though.
It's cool.
Bye-bye.
Let me take a look at this.
Saintcomics.com.
I'm gone on my phone.
Same.
Oh, it does.
It's not.
Yeah, it's not centered.
Ugh.
Yeah, what's up with that?
Damn.
Oh, yeah, it is left-leaning.
Hmm.
Oh, it's not even like I can.
I can't even like move it back into the center.
It's actually just cut off.
Who would have thought it would be left-leaning?
Hmm.
Like, I can look at...
Okay, the other comics are...
Okay, this is actually really weird.
Okay, when I go to the, like, the contents page, the background is...
The page is centered.
But all the individual, like, pages are, yeah, like, they're not centered.
They're left aligned.
Ah, jeez.
Ah, this sucks.
It must be just some, like, like a alignment thing you can change.
If the main menu, because I don't know the main menu.
It's like, that works.
Perhaps.
If it's Chapter 2, it's all going to the left.
I will...
I will fuck around with it.
This is actually going to be a nightmare to test, though, because I will have to, like,
literally...
I'll have to literally put it on the website, because I have to look it on my phone and
I can't...
Ugh.
I'll have to upload, like, a test page that I can view on my phone and then, like, fuck
around with it and see what happens.
I'm curious.
I was curious about giveandtake.site.
I have seen my website before, and I always found it amusing, even though it's terrible,
that the top of it says giveandtake and then e is on, like, another line underneath.
That seems on-brand, though.
It seems on-brand.
Site.
Let me check this out.
I click on load of ghosts.
Yeah, giveandtake.
It cuts the e off.
That rules.
The images are centered, though, so that's pretty good.
Yeah, so you got that on me.
I really got to redo a lot of my site.
It's so, like, amateur looking.
I want it to be good, but I'm stupid.
It's a big problem.
Oh, did oblivion fall?
Did you just make this?
No, I found it.
Damn.
Doctrine purist.
This is a small image.
I'm trying to find a bigger image in Google.
Doctrine purist.
A wheel has an axe.
A wheel is the connection between a vehicle and the ground.
Doctrine neutral.
A wheel propels something.
Conveyor rolls and wheels.
Doctrine radical wheel rotates.
A structure purist.
A wheel is cylindrical and has a rubber surface.
But what about wooden wheels?
That would still be a wheel.
What would be structure neutral?
I feel like tank road wheels is a weird example to use for radical.
Because, like, you could think of way more.
Like, if all you care about is that it rotates.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
But then it's a structure purist.
Okay, yeah.
Cogs or wheels.
Clock hands are wheels.
Yeah, okay.
Got it, got it.
Yeah, I feel like our definitions were more good.
Yeah, yours are more like the ones in this image.
A pizza is a wheel.
Built to roll.
I like the atoms are wheels and doors.
That's the real shit.
Dude, revolving doors?
Like, what do we even make of that?
Well, it revolves.
But it doesn't roll.
A rolling hill is a wheel.
A Rick Roll is a wheel.
This was a really good, actually.
Hell, yeah.
Anything that rolls.
Roll your own crypto.
What does that mean?
A joint.
I don't know what that means.
Maybe I like to keep it that way.
All right.
Next voicemail is called, there it is, it's called, well, it's got an image.
Okay, the voicemail is just a little stupid thing.
Anyway, here's the image that goes with it.
Is that supposed to be not a penis?
I believe it is not supposed to be a penis.
It's just your beanie flopping over.
The fact that you thought that's what it was, says more about you than it does about you.
Someone needs to redraw this even more detail, shinier.
Yeah, I agree.
Make it shinier, please.
I would disagree.
Okay, next one is, we're almost done, there's like two more.
Next one is, Slime times weekend update number four.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Why hello, gangsters.
Welcome back to the Slime times weekend update.
This week, Liam, creator of among other things, the R-O-C-K comic Vile,
has after a long history of rowdyhood, decided to turn to the killers.
Oh, shit.
But on the day of the gang swap, he expressed displeasure with the rowdy leadership
in the form of the rowdy ring leaders.
We're following the story as it develops to see whether Liam settles nicely into the edgy hymns and vape clouds
or finally decides to put on his anarchy pant and burn down the cathedral.
Liam's art is good.
He's welcome.
Tim Warner Core, a sentient carrot, has returned to active play and is down with the clown.
He immediately won Realist Rowdies for the month of February and has a snazzy new Wild West look.
Finally, on the game development side, attention was turned to the many typos persisting in our text-based MMORPG.
I wouldn't know or care, because rowdies can't read.
But for those literate among us, the fixes to this should come as a nice surprise.
That's it for this week.
And remember, the slime time is the best time.
Uh, awesome.
That reminds me.
Oh, shit.
Uh, I owe...
Okay, I owed a couple people printsep items for winning a contest.
Oh, someone just messaged me the other day.
They finally fixed the create command.
I was not able to make those printseps because the create command was bugged.
But no, it got fixed, and now I gotta remember.
I actually have to go and do it.
Okay.
Uh, and I will.
I'm glad.
This has reminded me.
Uh, I've owed zombie paper a printsep for, like, months.
Uh, we'll get assorted.
Um, okay, that was fun.
Next, this is the last one.
It's called Rip the Big N.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, cameras.
Nikolai here.
Nikolai, I have something important to tell you today.
But first, Nikolai, go and get some vodka.
Nikolai, be right back.
Do-do-do-do-do.
What's this?
Nikolai, you have no vodka?
No!
Nikolai, you don't live without vodka.
Uh-oh.
Nikolai, are you feeling the effects of no vodka?
Ugh.
It's so sick.
Nikolai, dying.
This would happen to me also.
Nikolai, I would like to tell you that he-
Oh, no!
No!
Nikolai, you've been taken too soon.
Just ever so slightly too soon.
Just very slightly.
It would have been fine if he died like 10 seconds later.
Yeah.
But he's taken exactly 10 seconds too soon, yeah.
Hard to agree.
Nikolai is, um, if, uh, if J.K. Rowling had written a Russian character, a Russian student
at Hogwarts, he would be Nikolai.
She did.
He was called Viktor Krum.
No, he was Bulgarian.
Was he?
Yeah.
I'm almost-
Well-
Well, he was Romanian.
Romanian, yeah, I think so.
Romanian sounds right to me.
He was the Paul-
No, the-
No, he was Bulgarian.
He was Bulgarian.
I was right.
From Durham Strang.
The Durham Strang Institute.
Yes.
Seeker on the Bulgarian national-
Yep, yep, yep.
Dab.
Uh, alright.
The nightmare is over.
No more voicemails.
Nikolai Vodkozinski, that would be the name she comes up with.
Vodkozinski.
Like Ted Kozinski.
I like it.
Alright, what are we at?
Did we hit three hours?
We're five minutes away from three hours.
Damn.
If we wrap up, we can have glowing visuals.
Hooray!
Just what we always wanted.
Um, well, I mean-
I remember to play Pumpkin Alley.
That demo is-
You play it and stuff.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I mean, I would hope that everyone has played it.
But if they haven't-
If you haven't not.
Yeah, definitely check out the Pumpkin Alley demo.
Uh,
Obviously.
Play my game too.
I made a game.
It's out.
It's called Phantom's Revenge.
Uh, it's-
It's hard.
I bet-
I bet the people listening right now
can't even beat it.
Because they're stupid.
Oh!
Did I mention?
I guess I'll mention it now.
The only way to read the end of Slime and Punishment
is to beat it.
If you can't beat the game,
you don't get the link to the final-
to the final chapter,
and you'll never see the ending.
Damn.
It's the only way to do it.
There's no way-
It cannot be cheated.
There's no work around.
There's no way to-
to do any-
It's impossible.
It simply can't be done.
You gotta-
You gotta beat the game.
To find out what happens to Phantomhorn.
Will he get his revenge?
Or will he be killed?
I guess if you lose the game,
he will be killed.
Yes.
Well, spoiler.
Spoiler for when you lose the game,
that you die.
Die.
How dare you.
Yeah.
Uh-
Ruin game.
Alright.
Just letting everyone know that the stakes.
The stakes are high.
You know, for the reader as well,
as for the character.
That's called a narrative-
Ludo narrative-
Distinence.
Consonance.
So they work together.
It's good play conditioning.
That's good conveyance.
Uh, video games.
Video games.
Link in the description for that.
Ludo narrative synergy is the word.
Syngism.
Fine.
Alright.
That's all I have to say about that this week.
Uh, you guys-
Oblivion fall.
What do you gotta say?
Uh, I gotta say, uh,
I don't know,
I'm not gonna be working on that animation for like two weeks
because I have to do a DA games thing,
and I'm sad.
So I would say,
it would be out this week,
but it's gonna have to wait two weeks,
and then it'll be out a week after that.
I cry.
But what can I do?
That's like pretty soon, though.
Yeah, it's three weeks that we've done.
Been working on that for a long time.
Um, not because it's a big project,
just because I was really inefficient
during the first part of it,
and then got delayed for like a month in January.
Mmm, okay.
Makes sense.
Alright.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
Uh, it's pretty good to be pretty good.
It's probably gonna be so good.
Alright.
I guess, uh, I guess that's it.
That's the end of the podcast.
Thanks for coming on.
Uh, thanks for listening, everybody.
I'll see you next week.
Uh, next week, uh,
send me a message telling me
how you couldn't beat an adventure
because it was too hard.
Hahaha.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.
Goodbye.