Hello everyone and welcome to the, to the, I remember it, so you don't have to, I remember
to show up to the podcast so you don't have to, it's Ben Saint of the Pro Crastinators
Podcast and it's finally happened, it's finally happened.
Only one person showed up for the fucking call, only, I'm the only one, I'm it, I'm
it, it's just me, it's the legendary one man cast, we've been waiting, we've been waiting,
and now's the time for it to happen, it's just me, it's the just Ben cast here on the
Pro Crastinators Podcast. Remember that, remember Howard Dean? Good times, good times, good
time in my life, the Howard Dean era. Nostalgic, ah fuck, fuck Hippo you recording? Okay, well,
damn it, I'm, Hippo just joined the call, I'm recording, I started recording, I gotta
admit, Hippo, I kinda, I was very tempted not to add everyone to let everyone know that
I was here, and I kinda wish that I had, I kinda wish that, nothing personal, I'm sure
I'm sure you would feel the same way, a sort of sense of regret that had I not added everyone,
the legendary event would have transpired. Yeah, I mean, last week I was feeling the
same way, like, it was gonna be just me, nobody else seemed interested, but I felt like I
should, cause like, sometimes people forget, and also, I mean, I don't know, it's like,
there's only two people, there's only one person, how's the whole podcast gonna come
of this, doesn't really feel like the Pro Crastinators. If I hadn't, you know, everyone, then everyone
would have said, everyone would have said, Ben, why didn't you add everyone, why didn't
you add everyone, Ben, why didn't you, why didn't you take it upon yourself to remind
all of us, you know, and to be fair, I'm sure, normally Nate adds everyone in a normal
episode where he's here and everyone's here and all that shit. So, you know, I guess,
okay, it's fine. I mean, had it just been me, I guess my strategy would have been to,
you know, just kind of, just ramble for a little bit, which I'm sure I could do quite
easily, maybe for like, you know, 15, 30 minutes, you know, just, you know, insult everyone
else, talk about, talk about, you know, do a little self-aware bit where I comment on,
you know, the sorry state of the PCP these days, where this, you know, the, you know,
the, the, the clearly, the clearly defunct, the clearly malfunctioning machine, you know,
which puts, which outputs this, you know, gestures around myself to, to the one man
cast currently transpiring, which puts this out as it's, as its output, you know, as a
way to sort of head off criticism and put myself kind of above it, you know, put, and
then, and then, and then you, and then spend an inordinate amount of time doing like voicemails,
right? And just like go through every voicemail and try to just try, just try and stretch
you to one after as long as I can, you know, just maybe try and hit an hour and a half.
I think, I don't think it would be that hard. Anyway, that was my story. I was thinking about
this as I was sitting in the call, waiting for that mythical, for that mythical three
10 to round the corner.
Yeah, I maybe I shouldn't have jumped in. I don't really have anything to talk about.
Um, no, it's fine. Well, I mean, up to you, I guess. But why don't we talk about, why don't
we talk about last week? It was just you and me last week, right?
Yeah, I was there and then you jumped in immediately as we started recording as I started
writing. And so we talked about comics and and what each of us are doing. I was talking
about getting tired with internet discourse. And I have, I yeah,
getting getting tired of it, tired to the like weary, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wasn't I thought you said hired, like, putting out an ad everyone like, Hey, guys, here's
my resume, you know, you know anyone? No, it's it's it's poisonous. It's poisonous.
It's the worst. I don't like it anymore. Internet discourse. Yeah. Yeah. I've been feeling
the same way. Twitter sucks. Twitter is where I do most of my internet discourse. It sucks.
I need I need to do something about it, though. It's it's it's always such a habit to like,
you know, you know, I go on Twitter, just to see what's going on. And then, you know,
if there's an argument to be had, I decide to jump in usually. Yeah. And it's it's never
good. It's like, sometimes I get through to someone and we reach an understanding, but
more far more often, it's easier to do that in discord than it is on Twitter.
It's just it's just bad. It's just not good. I need to delete my Twitter or do something
drastic that would force me to stop because I'm because I am I'm out of control.
Something drastic, like suicide, for instance.
Don't even talk about that. Don't even talk about that. I've been thinking about it.
I've been thinking about it just a little bit. Oh, God, no. I know. I'm sorry. It's terrible.
It's terrible. I mean, when you say when so what when the words something drastic, that's
the first thing that comes to my head. Well, all right. I'm I'm not like, like on the on the
bridge right now. I'm not like staring down like 50 feet. There's nothing. Yeah. Of that
level going on. You're not you're not you're not fucking fucking. What's his name? Billy
Madison in It's a Wonderful Life. Yeah, I more, moreover, it's just that I've sort of
changed my opinion on like the the concept of ending one's own life. Because I was thinking
about it like like a few weeks ago. And it was just sort of like, you know, the the the
benefits of staying alive outweighing the the, you know, the detriment of no longer being
able to be alive. And then it's just like, sometimes, like things pile up to a point
where I could see I could see a future where it's like suicide would not be that strange
of an option. Obviously, it's it's behooves me to do everything in my power to make sure
my life does not get to that point. But it's like, I wouldn't like the this that whole
thing where like, suicide is a coward's way out. Or like, or it's brave, like there's
a lot of discussion about whether or not like it's correct for a person to commit suicide.
And there was this there was this, this general feeling that I always had, which was I would
just be doing something bad for everyone who would be sad to see me gone. And I would be
not contributing anything to anyone. And in fact, taking away things from other people.
And so in that way, it's a selfish move. And, you know, you shouldn't even really think
about it. And on the one hand, on the one hand, that's still kind of true. Yeah. But
on the other, it's it's sort of a weird, like, if there's only one thing stopping you from
committing suicide, and it's based in guilt, I don't know whether that's good. I don't know
if that's good for your potential recovery, you know, if the only if I see what you mean,
like if the only reason that you're not going to do it is Oh, but it'd be wrong, though,
it's like, oh, you should have more reasons than that, hopefully. Yeah, I mean, I obviously
do have a lot more reasons than that. But like, that was the one thing I've changed on. Because
it's like I remember, yeah, you got to have you got to care about number one yourself.
And if the guilt of, you know, I don't know, it would be cringe to do it, you know, any
anything else, anything else in life, they say, you know, you got to do it. Maybe this
is like a malformed point, maybe this is stupid. But like, I feel like other things in life,
it's like you got to do it for yourself, you can't you can't do it for other people.
All right. So if you're just, yeah, if you're just continuing to live, because I guess everyone
else wants me to, you know, it's usually not that's not the optimal state. Yeah,
sure. Sure. But yeah, yeah, I understand, I understand, I understand what you're saying.
There was a time, there was a time in my life, I guess I was probably like 24 ish, I don't
know, something like that. And I was never like, I've never like seriously considered
killing myself, but I was pretty depressed for a while. And I do remember, and this is
kind of stupid in hindsight, I feel a little embarrassed about it. But at the time it seemed
reasonable. I was like, I'm sad. I'm sadder now than I was like maybe a year ago, I feel
worse. What if I just keep feeling even worse? What if the trajectory continues? And I was
like, boy, if I get like much, if this continues, like who knows at what point will it be like
well time to kill myself. So I called the suicide hotline. And I was like, hey, listen, I'm
not about to kill myself. I'm worried that like, there might come a time in the future
when I will though. And the girl on the phone like had she I mean, it was like a young
woman who was like, clearly just kind of reading from a script. She was not, she did
not have like robust a robust discussion in the can ready to go on the subject. She was
just like, you know, I don't remember the details. She was not ready to engage on this
on this thing like a suicide. Well, it's a suicide hotline. But like, I feel like suicide
hotline as a concept only really works for like, very young suicidal people who are just
in the midst of an emotional storm. And they need somebody to say it's okay. And they come
to it. Yeah, it is meant. I shouldn't have it was stupid. It's meant for like, if you're
like right about to do it, you call them in and hopefully like, you don't do it. It's
like, I got to talk myself out of this right now or something bad is going to happen. That's
what it's supposed to be for. Dur. It's funny. It's funny. You know, with the PCP, I'm just
imagining the PCP channel being in the state that it's in. And I guess we're probably not
going to release this episode just yet. We might not really we might delay the release,
but I'm just imagining the PCP channel in the state that it's in, and the fucking, and that this
episode goes up, but it's like suicide. It would be funny. An episode about why not kill yourself.
I mean, yeah, it's not this is not brought on by like the progress in this channel. It is brought
on by the consistent like stress of COVID and a lot of other smaller things going on. Yeah. And
as it just been like COVID has exacerbated all of the things that have made me feel bad in the
past, they've just become more powerful. It sucks. I don't really know how to deal with anything.
All right, here's a little rant I can go on. I was I was looking into online counseling because
like, I've never really bothered because I assume it's too expensive and I looked into it and yes,
it is too expensive. Fuck it. But I paid upfront for a thing. And then only after I paid upfront,
they said I would get four sessions. And then it would be a monthly payment. So once a week.
But the person they have assigned to me, their schedule is booked, was booked for the first
like two weeks after I pledged the money so that I have to I waited basically all June to get this
counseling session. It's going to happen tomorrow. But like, I've needed this counseling session for
two weeks. And it is it is just I have even wait, have you been paying without getting it?
I paid the lump sum for the month, which is supposed to be four sessions for the month.
And I've been waiting for two weeks until I get the first one. And so I really hope I really hope
that this this doesn't mean I don't like I have to pay again for the next month.
Was there like a number of sessions or like a number of like time? It was it was a number of
sessions. Okay, yeah, yeah. So like four sessions. And they said you are in charge of organizing and
I clicked on the person and they had apparently apparently you're not in charge of organizing
if they're like, Yeah, but you can't do it. Yeah. So it's like sucks. I I
I can't wait to see if that does anything because like I can't I feel like I can't speak just generally
like if I if I go if I you know, I've done multiple things in the past when I've had
like depressive episodes, I go and make a stupid video that sucks and people like,
Oh, don't worry about it. Or or whatever. And it's not there's nothing less helpful. And it's
and I sorry to anyone. I'm sure everyone's intentions are great when they do it. But
there's nothing less helpful than like when you make then when you like post online,
whether that's on Twitter or like YouTube about about like, I'm sad and people try and like
make you feel better, you know, like it just it sucks. It's not it's not the the fault. It's not
that they suck. It's that it's that the strategy of posting a terrible strategy sucks. Yeah. Yeah.
It can do something for you if you just want positive reaffirmation. But I think
too cynically of myself to like agree with any of that. It only really works when it's like a,
you know, a sincere, like friendly, like a person I'm very close to who talks about it in a sincere
way. If it's just people, yeah, it I'll read all the responses and some of them will be helpful
and some of them won't. And I'll usually fixate on the ones that aren't helpful. And or like
that just sort of, you know, don't read the comments. I read them. I'm stupid. I'm really
stupid. That's right. But you know, that's right. No, there is no, you know, I just am.
And it sucks. I want to just I pain for this therapy. Give me therapy. Give me those therapy
points. I've the only time the only time I've been I've had like a like, like, well, no,
that's not true. I guess I've done a little bit of it in the past. But most of my experience with
it was like, you know, my dad is a psychologist. And like, he never like, therapy'd me himself.
I feel like that would be weird. And you're probably not supposed to do that. Yeah. He but he
like, um, he got he got me therapy, but he always got it for me. Stop me if I've told talked about
this before, but he always got it for me when he wanted wanted it, like when he had a reason
to want me to be doing something else, not like when I asked him, like when I was in high school.
I don't remember what was going on, but they had like a period where I was
like kind of, uh, except I was like mad or something. I would know. No, I don't know if I
like, my grades weren't doing so well, or if I was like just being weird or just like my dad
didn't like how I was acting, he got me like a fucking sessions with some guy. And the guy prescribed
me, I think it was Ritalin or something. And I started taking it very briefly. And it sort of put
me like, emotionally, it like fucked up my emotions and I ended up like kicking a hole in the wall.
Which my dad, remember who had put me, who had, who had sought out a psychiatrist to give me medicine
because my dad wanted to change my behavior. It did change my behavior. I kicked a hole in the
wall. My dad was furious and punished me, made me repair the hole, maybe like buy, like like,
like repair the hole myself, made me like go out and buy like, you know, putty to like fill the
hole and stuff and like, you know, made me do this like long project of repairing it.
Which, to be fair, is a pretty fair punishment. If like, you know, you've made a hole in the
wall, you got to fix it. But I think I was grounded for a while too. Doesn't matter. And then there
was another, it was like, like when I was like in my early, my very early 20s, I think like right
out of college, my dad was like, why aren't you, why don't you have a job? Why aren't you pounding
the pavement? You know, because he's a fucking boomer, idiot. Happy Father's Day, everyone.
Oh, gonna be calling them later, later on today. I feel very good about the fact that I made like
a little card for him. And I gave it to him and it was funny and he laughed and I was like, okay,
cool. Epic. That's pretty cool. That's pretty cool. I'm gonna redo. We did, we did, we did a Mother's
Day call, which God, I can't, it feels like feels like only yesterday. Where does the time go that
it was Mother's Day? They're so close together. Why are they so fucking close together? We did
a Zoom call. Why is it that the boomers all use this teleconferencing software called Zoom?
Where did Zoom come from? I don't know. I can only guess on how it propagated, but I assume it's just
like, it's like everyone suddenly needs to communicate via voice calls, whereas they never
needed to before. And they're like, what do we use? And in a lot of workspaces, apparently people
are saying, oh, we use this Zoom thing. And so people's word of mouth has spread it everywhere.
And so everyone of that age bracket who has not heard of, I mean, most people know Skype, but
nobody uses Skype anymore. They sold Zoom as a better version of Skype. And they're like, well,
okay, let's get that. I'm just saying, why aren't the boomers on Discord? That's all I'm saying.
Because if they were, they would find out that what I say, they would see that I'm on Discord,
and they would say, hey, son. And I would like, oh, no. Oh, no.
I guess, I guess no joke. If the boomers were on Discord, people would stop using this. It would
become Facebook. Yeah. To a certain extent. Well, maybe, I don't know, maybe there could be,
you know, because, because. Imagine if your dad came into endless war.
If my, I'm imagining it, and it just doesn't track at all. It would be
it's a funny idea. But I think all that would really happen is he might
just make a couple of cringe posts and then never, never make a couple of just like me.
Like father likes son. Then he, then he'd do exhalation point thrash and then dab on you. Well,
dab on you like in a metaphorical sense. Oh, Christ. Munchy's my new son now.
Oh, no. Oof. Oh, man. The caffeine's, caffeine's hitting me all of a sudden. Oof. It's hitting me
hard. Oh boy. But yes, I would, I would be dabbed out of existence, perhaps, perhaps.
You know, you know what? You know what's really, even speaking of parents, you know,
it's really funny to me. It's, it's very funny to me that like Digi's mom likes a bunch of my
tweets these days. Digi's mom's really cool. Digi's mom seems pretty cool. Yeah. She's a big
Bernie bro. And she likes, she likes my like, she likes some of my, my more political tweets,
which is kind of funny. And I like that. I don't know. Just, that's just a funny fact about
reality. You know, when, when it comes to depression and stuff, the consistent, like,
a consistent way to stay depressed. Have you seen that CGP gray video, like 10 ways to maximize
depression? Is it the one about being on a boat? Yeah. But you're being on a boat,
how to make yourself as depressed as possible. So as, to, as an instructional guide for people
who are depressed, to just do the opposite of this and you will be, you'll be on the path to
being better. It's, yeah, yeah. It's like, it's like, here are some things that you are probably
doing. Yeah. And so I'm like, all right, I feel bad right now. And talking, talking about it,
thinking about, thinking about is the worst. That just perpetuates things. Like, I'm just,
I think about it too much. And then I have an outburst on Twitter, not specifically at anyone.
I just like say, oh, I'm so sad, guys, in so many words. I had a thing. I had a thing. I made a
tweet. I succumbed to the urge the other day and I made a tweet. What did I say? Like a pissed off
and feeling bad. That was my, that was my indulgence. And it's sad. And it's like, oh, God, I did it.
I made an I'm sad post. Boo. Boo. Stop posting. Stop posting. But like, I was thinking today,
all right, I've got to, I've got to like work with myself. I am two people. I am me, the guy who
wants to stop being depressed and me, the idiot who is depressed. I need to try and coax myself out
of this. There's two wolves inside you. Yeah. And they're both going, oh. Yeah. They're both fucking
bass. One is bass and one is cringe. Which one do you feed is the question? Yeah.
Yeah. But I need to like, get myself busy with something. And I have no, the thing that, oh,
no, here we go again, Gibbs talking about art problems. But sucker sucker. There's the Gibbs
stupid idiot corner. Can we have a jingle? Eleazar, quick, write a jingle for Gibbs stupid
idiot corner. This is the stupid idiot corner. Hi, stupid idiot. All right. So I'm a stupid idiot.
And I've been talking, I talked last time about how like, there's a difference between working on
something which is mindless and you're just following orders and creation, creativity.
Right now I'm depressed for various reasons. And going to work is difficult because it requires
a lot of thinking. Do you physically go to work? No. I mean, at my desk, you know. Right. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. Okay. Like drawing. So like, but creation, creativity is all very thoughtful. I need to
think about a lot of things. But if I'm, if I'm allowing myself to think too much, I'm easily
slipping into how all of the depression thinking I've been having that distracts me. And it's like,
all right, I need to busy myself with some like hard labor, some stuff, some meaningless tasks
that I can just say to someone, tell me what to do, sir. And they will say, okay. And so
I'm going to, I'm going to like be a good boy and just ask my parents for if they need help,
if they need me to do something around the house, ask my brothers if they need help.
I'm just going to do that for a few days. I'm going to see if me being a workhorse will
figure out like, just get me out of this, whatever it is. Because like at the end of the day, there's
no one but me that is the guy who can get me out of whatever I'm in. And I need to find the easiest
way to stop myself from lounging around thinking about how everything sucks.
Interesting. Interesting.
Selfless volunteer tasks. That's my new plan.
I mean, you could, I mean, if that doesn't work, I mean, you could like volunteer for
like an org or something. I don't know if you just, yeah, that would probably be the next,
the next step. The next step. I mean, the reason I haven't gone immediately to that is because
I don't know what's open. I don't know whether you can go anywhere and do things right now.
Sure, there probably are. I could look into it. I don't know either, but I'm sure there's probably
something, but like, yeah, okay. Yeah, but my brother has like a leg issue, so he needs help at
the moment. He's been like walking around with a cane. Oof, yeah, sucks. Him and Tom, I guess.
Yeah, he's, I don't know whether I mentioned it, but I don't know if you mentioned it in the chat,
I think. I don't know if you've mentioned it on the show. So one of my brothers,
how long has that been going on? Can we say names? Can I say who it is?
I don't think it matters, but we won't say names, just because.
Oh, sorry, should I cut that? Ellie's are cut that. Cut that, Ellie's are.
Okay, cut out the part right. I mean, they know who my brother's are. Not even that.
Okay, fine, whatever. Leg problem. Basically, the point is leg problem, which cannot be seen by
doctors because doctors are so busy with COVID. Yeah, really? They're that busy?
Well, I mean, he's tried to get an appointment so many times, and it is just like delay after
delay. It's gotten worse, and it's like he's really feeling like. That bad, huh? Yeah, I mean,
it's not like, I don't know exactly what the problem is, but he can't walk very well, it hurts a lot.
He's trying to get medication for it, but that is like, it really sucks, and I need,
if there's a person who needs help right now, it's him, just with physical things,
moving stuff around. I need to get myself busy, and that is a good excuse to do it.
It's not the same for a couple of reasons, because one, it's not like actively hindering me from
doing anything, and two, I haven't really tried. It's not that I have not been able to pursue it,
it's that I haven't really tried to pursue it because of COVID, but I really need a dentist
appointment, because I have a couple of things. My teeth are not green, but I have,
this feels like oversharing, but whatever, who gives a fuck? I have one cavity that I can see.
It's minor, but I know where it is, and if I look at it, I can see it, and it's very
distressing for me. Whenever I think about it, it doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt or anything,
but it's like, that looks weird, and there's also, I've talked about it, there's a,
I had a bike accident when I was a kid, a teenager, and I broke my two front teeth, and I had them
partially replaced with false tooth material, and this has been the case for a while, but I think
it's gotten worse. There's like a stain on the part between, there's like kind of an ugly line
that has a visible line that has appeared between like the fake part of my tooth and the real part,
and it's, I hate it, I hate it. So, oh, and then of course, there's the fact that I broke it
when I was biting into the poster. I broke the fault, I broke a piece off of the fake part of my
tooth when I bit the poster at Rat, not Radcon, RFC Kong K, RFC Readyfuckers con killer, whatever
it was called, on the Endless War lecture, which is gone now, but that's fine. And,
You didn't upload that to the Endless War YouTube channel?
No. Wow. I mean, okay, I think I have a backup file, but like, so I don't think
God, I hope, I'm sure, I'm, we must have, I'm, I'm almost positive, somebody's got a backup,
maybe I do, or no, it must be Munchy or Ethan. Oh God, there's no way, there's no way Ethan would
have, they would have deleted it. It has to still exist. It has to, I believe that it does, but you
know, it's, it's not on, right now, and it's lost all its views and all that. Okay, that's a tangent,
but like, you know, so I have a chip out of my tooth. It's not very visible, and I can't,
don't even really notice it anymore, but it is there. So, so that's, that's three good reasons
why I really need to see a dentist soon. But I, I don't want to go, I don't, I was like, no,
wait till the pandemic's over, but like, God, what if the pandemic lasts like another year,
you know? Like, what if this cavity gets really, gets worse, like I, it starts to hurt or something?
What if, what if I need a fucking root canal because I wait that long? I don't know.
I haven't been paying too much attention to the recent COVID statistics like I was when it started.
So I don't know whether it's in any way slowing down anywhere.
In, in, in Massachusetts, it has slowed down. It's actually pretty good. The stats are pretty
promising in Massachusetts. Actually, I haven't checked for a few days. Let me see if there's
been any reversal. COVID cases in Massachusetts. Yeah, no, since, since the middle of April,
in the middle of April, we were getting like over a thousand new cases, like between one and
2000 new cases a day, it has dropped off to like, like maybe two, one to 300 a day. And it's just
kind of there. It doesn't, it doesn't seem to be spiking again. So that's pretty cool, I guess.
Pretty cool, man. So that's how, yeah. I guess I should feel good about that.
What were we talking about? What were we saying?
You were saying dentist.
Oh yeah. I guess I should, maybe it's coming on time where I need to be like, okay,
the risk is managed now. You just go out, wear a mask, go to the fucking dentist.
You may as well if you can.
Yeah. I guess I should start looking into that Lamal.
Because I've been, I mean, when people was first talking about the how long COVID is going to
last, they said that some people were like doom and gloom and saying, oh, this will be a thing
forever now. It's like, don't say that, don't think that, don't be that, but maybe it's true.
Maybe it will just have a like, it'll slow down in the summer and then come back in the winter,
hardcore, and then it will stay for quite a while into the next year.
There are states where it is having a second wind, shitty states where they didn't take
social distancing seriously, weren't that strict about it, culturally didn't value wearing a mask
and whatever the fuck, thought it was communist or whatever. Some of those states are seeing
like a second spike, which I, you know, great. But we're not so, you know, cool. Good for us.
I like Massachusetts a lot. I'm proud of us. I hate everyone else. I hate all the other states.
They suck ass. That's it. That's all I gotta say. That's my useful commentary on America is,
hey guys, Massachusetts is good guys. Everyone else is the bad guys, the end.
What were we talking about? Dentistry sucks. I hate the dentist. I have become,
I have become an extremely fearful, cowardly person. I'm terrified of everything.
Yeah. Well, I say become. I definitely didn't use to be this bad. I didn't use to be this
afraid of planes or the dentist or death in general or any anything. Now I am like,
I was thinking about, thinking about the dentist. I'm like, that's so fucking scary. I'm terrified.
I was thinking about thinking about like, we're at a father's day again, because I think my dad
wants us at some point to go on like a, see as a sailboat, he wants us all to go out on the boat.
And I was thinking about that last night. And I was like, that's, I don't want to do that.
That's scary. What if we drown? It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, I'm scared. I'm scared to do
that. I think I'll die if we do that. What do you think this is like a new thing? Why do you think
you've become more scared of things? I don't know. I mean, I think, I guess I have a couple
hypotheses and they could all be true to a certain extent. One is that the pandemic has made me more
conscious of, of, of death and stuff, of bad things happening. Two, it might just be because I'm
older and like think about, think things through more thoroughly and the logical consequence of
almost anything could be like, yeah, but what if I die and that's bad? I mean, I don't know whether
that's thinking things through so much as overthinking things. Is it overthinking things?
I mean, that's all that matters. That's all that matters. All that matters in the end is that I
don't die. And what if I die doing anything? Yeah, I mean, I think that sure would be a mistake.
A lot of people know that things can be dangerous, but like they weigh the options and they decide that
most like statistically speaking, there's not much of a risk. So they're not going to worry
about it. I mean, I know that like it's so unlikely for you to die in a plane crash,
but I was so scared on the flight. I mean, on the flight to Radcon and especially on the flight home
from Radcon. I mean, the flight home was that was fucked me. I was off to like COVID had started
spreading. I was like, oh, shit. I wasn't scared of the pain. I mean, I was scared of the pandemic,
but that's not what I was like thinking about in the in the in the seat. I'm thinking, what if we
crash? Which is like, it's almost guaranteed not to happen. That's like as close to guaranteed
not to happen as almost anything in life. You know, to me, this says with my armchair psychology to
you know, tints glasses, twists glasses, I don't know what I was going about to say there.
I'm imagining you like gendo gendo aricato pushing your fuck. That's the guy from Eva,
right? The dad pushing your fucking glasses up with your middle finger or whatever.
Well, that's that's the stampede that does that. Never mind, whatever.
What this is to me is that you for some reason care about your own life more, like you have some
like these all these things have always been like, like if you were suicidal, for example,
and you're on a plane, you'd be like, man, the plane could crash if only, you know,
that would be a comforting feeling if you wanted to die. But because because you you want to live
so much. Yes, that it's extremely scary, the idea that you could die. Yeah. No, you're absolutely
right. I want to live so bad. I want to live forever. Why do you want to live? What's what's
being alive so fucking based being alive is so fucking based. It's not it's nothing. It's not
I'm just here. I'm just here in my fucking room. You know, it's COVID, man. It's quarantine.
And that that sucks compared to like it not being like that. But it's so good compared to
being dead. I'll take anything. I'll fucking I'll fucking live in a fucking in like a room.
I'll fucking live through the the drudgery of like the day to day,
every day the same, nothing happens. I don't care. I'll take it. Yes, please.
Experiencing anything whatsoever. Based. Thank you, sir. More please. I'll take all you got.
I don't know, man. That's I don't understand. I don't understand. I don't understand the mindset
of like, uh, sorry, I'm not trying to single you out. This is not about you. This is about
any any time any time I hear someone like thinking about life is life is shit. Life life share life
share is suboptimal. Is it even worth it? I I that's I'm never I never I never think that I am.
I'm definitely coming at it from a very extreme pessimistic point of view. Like I think of the
things that life could give me in the future. And I'm like, yeah, well, it's not going to happen.
All those things are not going to happen. I'm just going to be sad from now until then may as
well end it quickly. That's just the the mindset I get in when I'm in the worst spaces. The the
thing that makes me the saddest is thinking about how I'll be dead one day. So like, you know,
the the answer to that is clearly not like, oh, might as well just actually once in a while it
does good boy, since it's going to happen anyway, might as well just get it over with now. I mean,
but like I never seriously entertain that thought, because it's like, well, that doesn't make any
fucking sense. It does cross my mind occasionally, if only by by happenstance by chance. I was I was
going to say something else. I was going to say something else about that. What did you just say?
What was the last point you just made there? When I'm in the the the worst of the worst feelings
that the extreme pessimism says the only time I was thinking like maybe it'd be better to be dead
was when I was having was when I was in the throes of my fucking kidney stone episodes
like earlier this year or last year. How long I don't even remember how long ago that I feel
like that was last year. That was it was last year. It was more than a year ago. That's right.
And like, you know, that, you know, is considered considered by many to be one of the most painful
experiences a human being can undergo akin to, you know, childbirth, say, and it was so bad then
that I there were times and I was like, maybe maybe death, maybe death would be better than this.
That was the that's what it took to get me to really think like is life worth living?
So that's, I think, I think that's what it's so but like, you know, I feel I feel so upset
thinking about mortality that it paralyzes me and it ruins it kind of ruins my life
in a way that it that it upsets me so much. I feel like I feel like I'm just whining now.
Ah, well, we're all whiners rule. Yeah, we're all we're all just
trying to deal with a really bad time. Yeah. Well, that's the thing I was thinking of like,
COVID is not like directly affected me. It has made me scared to like go outside.
Just generally, but aside from that, because I don't go out that much anyway. So it's like,
it hasn't truly personally affected me that much. And I wonder if some part of the pandemic,
quote unquote, as a as an idea is just sort of me having some sort of excuse to feel like shit.
Yeah. Yeah, because like, it's really it's like, I don't know.
Yeah, I can't imagine that I'm correct on on what I think ever.
What do you mean? Oh, just anything? Yeah, you just doubt yourself all the time.
I don't I don't I don't trust myself. I think I know what I'm doing. And then I'm like, oh, yeah.
Oh, okay.
Welcome to the procrastiners podcast. That was the pre show.
That's the pre show. Now we're going to be like funny, goofy, funny people that are having fun.
No. Do you do you want to move on from this topic?
I mean, if you've got nothing else to say about it, yeah.
Nothing in particular. I feel like I've feel like I've thoroughly covered everything.
I guess I do want to talk about like the state of the channel.
Last time, I don't know how much I have to say about this might as well touch on it.
Last time, I think we did talk about how, you know, oh, the channel's been terminated.
That sucks. Maybe it'll be back and then now it's back. But like it's videos are still missing.
Let's I like I said, in my announcement video, you know, it's you might as well reiterate that
because I don't know if yeah, probably a lot of people didn't click on it. And I
I yeah, like we because because we record these so far ahead of when they released, it's like
if you if you had just if you had if you just heard the episode, you wouldn't really understand
what's going on with it. And and who knows, maybe by the time this one comes out,
there the situation will have progressed in some new fashion and who fucking knows what that could
be. But like, okay, the a bunch of the latest content is gone. That's the gist of it, including
almost all basically all the rad content, except for that one stream, I don't know. But like,
when when we got the news that channel was terminated for quote unquote, like,
encouraging illegal activities, or violating term or encouraging people to violate terms of
service or something like that. My first thought, and I think a bunch of people's first thought
was that it was the the Black Lives Matter charity stream, which I had insisted on doing.
And graciously, a few people who were on board with were wanted wanted to see happen and everyone
else didn't seem interested. But whatever. My first thought was, oh, that's it. Oh, because
we're because I said fuck the police a cab like though that's encouraging.
Political violence or whatever. I don't I don't think so anymore. And the reason I don't think
that's it is because of the weird fact that all all the videos that were struck it is
for terms of service violations. Like I think because all these videos were struck and removed
for terms of service violations, I think that it must be the videos were struck and that triggered
an automated response from YouTube to terminate the channel. And the fact that all it is explicitly
all the videos from when the hack occurred onward, it's those videos. So it must have
something to do with the hack. That's too big a coincidence, right? Do you think so?
Yeah, I feel like that's pretty, pretty easy to together that something about like,
I don't know, a very delayed reaction from YouTube to like, oh, this hack has been announced,
you know, the team YouTube Twitter people, they dealt with it, but then
the initial flag was maybe still in the system and has only just now got around to
implementing itself. It goes to that date and it says, oh, wrong, wrong, wrong, get rid of,
and then deletes the channel, you know, without without, you know, just a robot looking at it.
Yeah. Well, the stated reason given being like encouraging illegal or terms of service violations
is like weird and doesn't really fit that idea. And I don't know why it would be like that.
Well, if you think of it being like the Brad stuff, like would that have been
well, the Brad stuff was just advertising fucking cryptocurrency, right?
Oh, yeah, I guess, I guess that's not technically illegal in any way.
I mean, I don't think so. But who knows, since it's an automated response to who fucking knows.
Yeah, still no no actual knowledge about what is what is the reason.
No, not really. Okay. Well, so yeah, that's that's what I mean. I mentioned it just because
people are I see comments on like the announcement video saying like, you know, people one of them
one of the more common, you know, probably the most common theory is Brad, which yeah,
I think it's probably Brad. Second, second most common is probably Oh, it was the Black Lives
Matter ACAB thing, which was my initial thought too, but I've changed my mind. Then it's like,
Oh, it was because what about the what times you smoked weed? What about that time you encouraged
someone said you encourage shop? I don't remember encouraging shoplift. Maybe I did. I probably
did. I feel like that was a thing like looting is cool in the Black Lives Matter stream.
Like it's looting is cool if it's against target or something was definitely said.
Somebody said shoplifting, which shoplifting is not looting. I don't know. I feel like they were
talking about something else, but it doesn't matter because I don't think that's the reason.
I don't know. I guess. I mean, what do you think? Do you think the videos are going to come back?
I feel like eventually. I mean, they were responding to you weren't they about like you
gave them a list through the PCP account on Twitter of all the videos and they said,
Okay, we've got the videos now we'll get to work or something. I actually okay. I actually
fucked up a little not not very much, but yeah, they responded through Twitter. I did give them
the list the list. Okay, I actually I don't know if this is a good idea or not. I felt like I had
to make a split decision in the moment. I told them this is all of them I might have missed some
and I deliberately left out the ones with weed in them. So so maybe I shouldn't have done that,
but that's what I did because I felt like desperate and I was like, I don't want to do anything risky
at all here. So I didn't include like the two streams that are the two videos that the dude
weed them out or whatever, but I told them like this is not all of them. But then accidentally,
I forgot because I had looked at the the live stream lists because there's two on your YouTube
studio, you can see your uploads and you can see your live streams and I had looked at the uploads
and okay, for some reason on the uploaded videos, the deleted videos are listed as the most recent,
but on the live videos, the removed videos are listed as like not recent, they're listed at the
at the end of the chronological list instead of the beginning and I didn't realize that at the time.
So I thought that the ones on the stream were just gone. So I told them these are the uploaded
videos, the streams are simply gone. It turns out they're not gone, they are there. So I went back
and I replied again like a day later to that thread on Twitter and I said, hey, I found the
more URLs here are the streams and I gave them the and I gave them the streams and again,
perhaps out of cowardice or whatever, I didn't include the the BLM stream, but I told them I
don't think this is all of them. And like, logically, I don't see why I should have to give them every
single URL for every there's like 50 or more videos, right, that are gone, maybe even more,
maybe there's like 70, I don't even remember, there's a lot, but I gave them at least most of them,
almost all of them. I don't see why I should have to feel like they should be able to just look at
our fucking channel and see our videos, see which ones are deleted, and be like, oh yeah, these are
wrong. I don't know. But that's what I did. And they did respond to it. But no action has been
taken this far. And honestly, what what I'm afraid of is not that they will is not that they do it's
not that they do not intend to restore the videos, it's that there will be something about the process
of removal that like, they will take too long, and they will like, maybe they have the videos
stored in some like secondary form right now, and that will like, the timer will run out and they
will be like, they will hit some sort of hard limit where it's like our auto remove videos
are no longer even stored secondarily, they are gone forever. I don't know if that's the case.
Why would you assume such a system? I'm not assuming such a system, but I don't know that
that isn't the case. Right, but I don't know how I wouldn't even have considered the idea that
there's a time limit. I mean, YouTube has taken a long time to bring back a channel before.
And when it does eventually happen, it just happens. It's all back.
I feel like, okay, I have I have mixed feelings about this. Sometimes it feels
and like, you're not so much a culprit in this, but sometimes it feels like I am the most
worried about this. And everyone else to varying degrees is not taking this seriously,
not present in when I like discuss it in the channel or something. And sometimes I feel like,
what is everyone else doing? Like, why is that? Why don't they care? But then sometimes I
consider and I'm like, is this just an extension of my semi new tendency to be afraid of everything?
Is this just me being paranoid about yet yet another thing?
I think it is.
Is this just an extension of my, oh, but what if I die though to like, oh, but what if the channel
dies though? What if the what if the I mean, I think it's I think it's fair to be like,
you know, paying a close attention to it and doing stuff. But I think the rest of the guys,
then it's not like they don't care. It's that they assume with enough time, it'll come back
because we've already sent the tickets and there's nothing else to do but wait. And, you know,
like, like, I don't think people don't give a shit. I think they just aren't like freaking out
about it like you are. Yeah, I am freaking out about it. I'm very upset. I've been very upset
constantly. I don't know what's it been like a week now, more than a week now because the channel
was terminated before the last time you recorded was a terminated on like a week before Friday or
something. I don't know. I don't know. But, you know, that that's a worry. It's just very nerve
racking because I don't know. I don't know how it works. I feel like the success rate of YouTube,
you know, saving, you know, erroneously destroyed content is not 100%.
And who knows? Who knows if Radcon 4 could just become a statistic at any moment,
just like me, you know? Things are so fragile, so subject to fucking cruel fate.
I mean, yeah. Yeah. I don't know. Strangely, I don't feel as pessimistic about the YouTube channel
as I do about life itself. I see. Fair. It's, it's, I expected to come back,
all the videos to come back. I maybe a one or two will be like,
actually, this one is the bad one. So this is the reason and we're not giving you back this one.
And we'll be like, ah, fine. They already, they copyright struck and removed the end of YouTube
episode for the the Ava footage that I used in that one. So not an illegal activity, not the
stated reason for the deletion of the channel, just like a knock on effect of, oh, in addition to
wrong, like as we review the case of your channel that we deleted for no reason,
we found some other shit that we want to inflict upon you. Ha ha, gone dead. Cool.
When's things going to be fucking happy? When's things going to be fucking based again?
How does one escape into the virtual realm anymore when the virtual realm is just as bad as the real
realm? Yep. It sure is. Twitter sucks. Everything going on in the world sucks. And Twitter, I don't
know, just shows me that. And it's, it's a bummer. I guess, I guess the one thing that I got to say
that is good, in spite of everything else, I have started working on slime and punishment again,
like in earnest, like I've made actual progress on the finale, which is cool. I put that off for a
long time, couldn't bring myself to look at that for a while, but now I have. And it's good. It's
going pretty good. It's not, it's not that bad. It's going to be fine. And that'll be, and I'll feel
better. I'll feel better about life in general once that's done, I think. So that's how I'm,
that's my strategy for improving my own lot in life is that that's the thing that I think will,
you know, improve how I feel is getting that done. So I'm getting it done. And it's going to
be pretty cool. I think that what I've got done on it looks pretty cool. And I think it'll sound
pretty cool too. Sixten is going to be, he's, I think, I think he's, he's going to make a track for
it and it's going to be pretty sick because he does really good shit. I don't know, man. What else
you want to talk about? Oh, the itch.io games. Oh, the bundle a little bit about that. There's a
big old bundle with like 1500 itch.io games. I think it's at least over now, right? I think
they've stopped selling it. Yeah. So, but I've been going through those, you know, every so often
I'm like, I don't know what I'm doing with my life. I sit, I stare out the window and I turn
around to my computer and I hunch over on my back, my hunchback back and I click download on some
random one of these games and I play it and I'm like, Hey, you know what? Things are okay.
Right. I've really gotten into this trilogy of point and click adventures called forever lost
which is it's like a computer generated 90s looking CG
backgrounds and you click around on things, you know, there's a drawer, you open the drawer,
there's a strange puzzle piece and you've got to find where the puzzle piece fits in another room.
There's lots of out of the box thinking puzzles and it's really, it's really good for that,
for that sort of thing. They got this great game mechanic where you can take a picture
of a clue or a thing so that you can take it with you and reference it later when you think
you need it and it's like these games often they have clues that are just given to you as clues
like you click on a thing and it's like, oh, I jot that down in my notebook and that is giving
you too much information sometimes. Like sometimes you need to, it's really good because you are
tasked with the taking of the picture yourself. The pictures don't need to be taken, they're just
for your own reference but by having that automaty, automony, how do you say?
Automonicity.
Autonomy. To take the picture, when you think you have found something that can be a clue
in another area, it sort of makes it so that you're figuring out everything and there's no,
there's like tiny bits of story here and there but there's no characters, it's just like,
find your way out of this creepy strange place with these elaborate puzzles that couldn't possibly
exist in real life except they kind of could but nobody would build them but forever lost,
there's three parts. Right, cool. I haven't played, have you played a lot of the games
from the bundle or? I've gone around and I've played, I don't know, like 30 or something.
It's more than me. I've played maybe, I've tried out maybe like six or seven, I don't know.
There's so many of them that are like tabletop booklets and pixel art asset packs and things.
There's a lot of things that are not video games. Yeah, I don't mind that though because
occasionally it's like a Photoshop brush pack, like pixelated something or other and it's like,
oh cool, I'll just add that to my things. Yeah, nothing wrong with it.
Interesting cool fonts. I usually don't like having to pay for fonts so having it for quote
unquote free is pretty cool. It would be funny if there came a sort of almost a baby boom,
if you will, of indie games in the next year or so that all had maybe a lot of the same assets
in them and it was like because a lot of people bought this bundle and like a lot of the packs
got used by like first time devs or whatever. That would be pretty funny. I don't know if that'll
happen. I don't know if it's that if it was that big of a cultural event. It was a bit of a cultural
event, I think, this fucking bundle. I played this one game. There were so many fucking games on the
list that I had no idea so I just googled like best games on the racial justice bundle or whatever
and I found a couple of like articles counting down what they thought were some good ones.
I played this one called the stillness of the wind which is like a, you seen this one?
Oh no, his microphone's muted. Sorry, it's just a thing. Actually, wait, I've got a thing too.
I just got a package. My roommate was just like, hey package for you. I'm going to open it on the
podcast. All right, I'll just take a quick break to piss and then I'll be back. Oh, shit. Oh, okay,
all right. If you must, if you must. All right, so viewers, this package is some more ingredients
that I have gotten for my gummy worm making. I'm trying to branch out into alternative
ingredients in order to achieve the broadest possible range of consistencies because different
different kinds of gummies have different consistencies to them and I'm trying to,
like the ones I've been making are pretty decent. They have a kind of a fairly similar consistency
to like a traditional gummy bear but that's actually not my favorite kind. I actually like the chewier
ones better. So I have, okay, I have another bag of erythritol which is an artificial sweetener
which is very good. That's fine but I've already been using that. I've got rice, rice flour.
Rice flour I think is a good, I mean it's not keto but you know, you only use a little bit and I
think it's fine. Rice flour I think will be good to give a nice sort of mochi like stickiness
or thickness to something. I'm actually very excited about experimenting with that.
And this stuff called inulin which is, it can be derived from various things. I thought it came
from, what was it, chicory root but this is apparently from Jerusalem artichokes. I don't
even know what that is but inulin, based on what I know about it, I think it's similar to the main
ingredient that I've been using which is soluble fiber from tapioca. I think inulin is just soluble
fiber, oh from, from another source. Okay the stuff I've been using is isomolto oligosaccharide.
This inulin is apparently fructo oligosaccharide so I think it's similar but it might have, it might,
I don't know how it's different but it is different so I'll be, I'll be fucking around with that.
Probably later today I'll be fucking cooking up another batch and seeing what,
this is very exciting. It's very exciting because the recipe I've been using has gotten a little
stale. They're a little samey, I've sort of gotten bored of the same consistency. I'm glad to have
new ingredients, new ingredients to fuck around with and see what happens. Ah boy oh fucking boy.
Right. Did you hear, did you hear any of that? I did, I was listening to most of it. Okay sick.
Um I've got more, I've got more shit on the way. The thing I'm most excited about is pectin.
Pectin is a normal, is it like a perfectly normal ingredient that normal recipes call for?
I thought and yet it's very hard, very difficult to find on like Amazon like almost every,
almost every like thing I could buy that was called pectin on Amazon was not pectin. It was
a combination of like pectin, dextrose and citric acid which I don't want because that's not keto
but that's like overwhelmingly that's the form you can buy it in which I guess most recipes that you
would use it in like it's traditionally used in like jelly and like most recipes would call for
those things um but I don't want that. That's not what I'm looking for. I want the pure, I want the
pure shit. I've got my own citric acid, I've got my own acids, I've got my own fucking sweeteners,
thank you very much. No need, no need. Um anyway the uh yeah the stillness of the wind is about
being an old woman on a farm and getting letters from your family and I don't know having nightmares
cool. It's very, it's pretty good. I like a lot of the weird like non-tradition, not
unusual concepts that these itchio games go with. Yeah stillness of the wind is like you're on a farm
so it sort of feels like a farming game um because like you know you can, you milk your goats,
you make cheese out of the goat milk, you like pick mushrooms, you collect eggs from your fucking
chicken coop, you have to cook, you have to cook food and eat it so you don't get exhausted uh or
whatever um but I'm pretty sure that other than eating I'm not sure you can actually lose like um
I kind of think the farming is it like that like it's not like uh like that's not really what it's
about it's just kind of there to add like texture to the experience of being this woman and getting
these letters um but I'm pretty I'm pretty sure that you can't actually like fail uh I but you
could probably like you could probably arrive at a point where like your farm sucks sooner and maybe
that would change your experience a little bit uh but uh yeah yeah yeah yeah I don't know it was a
very sad game oh this looks cool it was it was a big it was a bummer I like I like this sort of um
sunsetty orange glow it looks it reminds me maybe it's just the way she's dressed but it
reminds me of journey a little bit yeah um it kind of looks like that it's got that sort of minimal
minimalist realists aesthetic I guess it's like a it's like a sort of mundane world rendered in
this kind of cartoon style I don't know anyway you just you just make cheese and the mailman
comes by and is like got any cheese oh no cheese oof sucks see you later bro yeah cring yeah you
literally it's like oh great the mailman will like the mailman will give will sell you these like
treasures he'll sell you these like fucking like far off like magical treasures from like
ancient times or whatever that have these big like highfalutin descriptions I think they're all
worthless I think there's no point to any of them uh and I I don't know why they're a thing in the
game I feel like it's maybe it's just another thing to like distract you from the point and I
don't know what the point is the point is I don't know I don't I don't know what the point of the
game is but I but I guess I would recommend it anyway there's another game that I thought looked
cool and I fucked around with only for a few minutes and I was like maybe I'll get back to this
and fuck around more and I haven't yet it's called Mendel as in Gregor Mendel and it's like
you land on an alien planet I guess and there are these different plants and you can go around
and discover plants and name them you give them whatever name you want and then you can like
take samples of them and like combine them and I guess it's sort of combines their genes I guess
the game has some sort of like genetic modeling component somewhere in its code and you combine
their genes and it produces a new plant that like combines their traits in some way and then you can
name the new plant that you've made by combining them and stuff and I guess it's just sort of a
fuck around and make weird plants kind of thing which is cool and the kind of thing that I could
get into if I was in the right mood but I didn't I didn't get that far into it uh
what else did I play I haven't I haven't I've never played night in the woods but now I guess
I own it because I got the bundle um I think I've probably already mentioned uh a short hike which
is great yes I played that on this I played that on a stream one time well like a year ago
and it's a really cool video game and uh the the I think I mentioned this too but the dev the dev
of the game like showed up to my stream one time because I tweeted I was streaming it and I guess
he saw and that was pretty that was pretty based that was you you play as Reginald you play as
Reginald from Beartato you know who that is no there's a webcomic called Reginald and Beartato
and it it's the the main Reginald okay the the website is called Nedroid but um yeah the
character the character in in um a short hike looks exactly like the stupid bird Reginald from
Nedroid and it's very funny it's like ha ha there he is that's it that's my observation
hey uh uh Ben I think yeah I might need to leave quite soon because there's a thing that we're
gonna do uh and it requires it is uh like light sensitive like the sunset happening
oh do you might do you want to can I know what it is oh yeah yeah we're just gonna do a bonfire
but it was like a fireless day thing oh okay uh all right fair enough well do you want to do you
want to start voicemails or if you got to leave soon I can just do voicemails I'll just fucking do
it myself man I don't I don't give a fuck you can you uh what do you want to do that I don't know um
how how soon are the are the okay I have not gone I have not gone through them uh but there are
have you not prepared them to play no I have not prepared them to play I I was just gonna play them
on uh a speak pipe oh and you personally would okay yeah in that case uh that's gonna take too
long so I will do and then you can do the voice unless I mean the only other way if you did want
to do them is if you just logged on to speak pipe and we both just hit play at the same time
um but if you gotta go then it's fine yeah sorry I genuinely I genuinely don't mind doing it
okay well happy father's day uh I will do I will I will soldier on um and I'm uh good good good talk
uh yeah yeah cool I didn't didn't really feel like didn't really feel that much like recording
an episode but that's okay no but I mean that's fine I don't care it's it's weird doing a two man
it sure is I wonder why I wonder why it's come to this why is it like this what's everyone
fucking doing what's so goddamn important uh sorry sorry sorry for my emotional literally
anything else yeah I guess I guess so um all right well I will see you all right man
oh put your fucking audio wait we gotta sync oh shit let's yeah we didn't think it okay I guess
we'll do this right now Ellie is our I don't care if you cut this do not use your own discretion
all right I will see you later later dog um well we're at an hour and 14
it's just me everyone hey it's time for the it's time I guess this we've returned to the part of
the episode that's just the Ben solo cast similar perhaps to what you might get monthly if you were
a five-dollar patron haha I'm doing it I'm fucking doing it at patreon.com slash ben saint where I do
the month I do the same thing that hippo does I stole the idea from him where I do the monthly
roundup Q&A kind of thing I do a little question and answer thing or you ask me whatever and then
I answer them and then it's just me and I talk about stuff um but you know I feel like I touched
I feel like in talking to hippo I touched on everything that I might have wanted to bring up
had it been the true solo Ben cast um so I guess it's time to go to voicemails yes um
let's let's hear let's hear from our good friend and I have not I have not uh edited these at all
I haven't listened to them beforehand so this is totally unfiltered and maybe if they really are
bad let's let's see let's see what Nate has to deal with every every time when he when he's like
going through them and picking let's have a raw uncut experience I will I guess I'll tell Ellie
is already cut any that I feel are not appropriate or good enough anyway this is from Pokemon's
greatest nemesis one thing I find especially funny about the traders of america list is that
there's pokemon listed uh and then there's pedo which is listed parentheses pokemon's greatest
nemesis um is so co context this this guy on twitter who I think was just doing it for attention
one that one angry gamer or one angry gamer he made this list that made the rounds of traders of
america and it was just have a god I hope I haven't talked about this before whatever it
and it was basically just like brands and celebrities or people who basically is just
supported black lives matter that's basically all you needed to do uh to to get on to get on this
traders of america this is people who are have betrayed the united states and uh oh god the
state of the world and um I got on it long story short I've said this before where where am I what's
what's happening um and uh so I guess pokemon's on it that's really funny uh and pita yeah you get it
you get the iron I don't have to explain but that's why this is happening that's why this is all
happening problem solved riddle answered okay next one from tom I love a zoomie please focus
all your effort into a zoomie I think he is doing that but whatever let's let's go
you know tom I just played a zoomie in the vertical slice for the first time
this is the same god a big fan of the character but I couldn't play the official game because
like my pc was shit and I had to fix it and then finally a zoomie I can finally do it
and I did it I beat the game basically like what is of that exists so far absolutely brilliant
the only problem that I have with it is that the jump button is C and the spacebar is like
literally right there and it would be so much more intuitive for me to use the spacebar maybe
like include a thing to map the controls to whatever you want you know like a menu to do that
so it would be uh very based anyways good game bro uh that's it
cool tom please respond uh I personally um I have only the only I have I have seen tom's
a zoomie updates I haven't played it since that first like vertical slice came out
so I don't know what the current I don't really know what the current state of it is
but uh I'm sure I'm sure it's looking good because it was looking good before and seems
like things have only progressed upward from there that's what I think here we go summoning
sponge what do you fucking have to say for yourself first 100% shower through just two minutes and
47 seconds that's a four yes good no towel separate shampoo conditioner and body wash
long curly hair external objects you should stream it just a sponge I used warm water
but data mining suggests that the torment that cold water brings might actually help save some frames
we just have to see how the history of the shower speed on the wall the music
I get it I get it summoning sponge summoning salt that's the joke cool good good I mean
we what we need is like a comparison of like who who brought the record down what were their
strats what were the what was the new tech that allowed for new breakthroughs to be made
obviously that would take more than 31 seconds um okay uh next up we got margar here we go
hey bcp members um I just have a really quick question I think it's been on a lot of people's
minds lately but no one seems to really be talking about it um where the fuck is brad
garling house and what have you done with them uh and if you haven't done anything with them then
what is the situation is he safe uh thanks uh I mean you know not to not to spoil anything but
but you know in spite of in spite of appearances now future rad content is coming that elaborates on
the saga of brad garling house um I I will not I will not um I will not divulge you know I have
nda agreements that I've signed that said I cannot divulge the details of that I will only say that
it seemed as though the threat has been neutral had been neutralized uh but um I won't comment on
I won't comment on matters of his personal safety but uh uh apparently I was mistaken so I guess at
this point in time margar your guess is as good as mine uh gulp okay uh this next one is from
pancakes colon got a message from legion cool let's let's hear what that's about
we legion take responsibility for the attack on the pcp for the transgression against our savior
liberator brad garling house you tried to stop the message of our movement that one day savior
brad will flood the world and get rid of the sinners and now unbelievers and we the congregation
will float on our crypto to salvation temporary termination of channels and flagging videos that
use racist epithets is a mere pint of our overall influence that's not what happened you cannot
destroy it you're a fraud we are the legion of brad garling house and we are many I can't I can't
believe it I don't I don't buy it you're you're this is just this is a false flag attack this is uh
this is a hoax you're this is uh this is uh some copycat you're taking credit for you can't you
can't be the mastermind it's impossible um if you if you really were then you would then what
did what have I got in my pocket huh three three guesses what have I got in my pocket uh wrong
wrong wrong no no you can't you can't be you can't you can't be the mastermind it's gotta be
there's there's there's uh the the the the just the the conspiracy goes deeper and deeper than I
can imagine there's there's leave me alone stop stop going through my garbage at night uh cool
great um next up we got the ben Shapiro collective has a message
let's say you've been a bad girl let's say hypothetically you've been a bad girl even
okay and if you were a bad girl you'd also be my dirty little slut right then I've been
speaking you would be my little cunt so now let's say that you're also daddy's girl
now that we established you're both a bad girl and daddy's girl and I believe you agree with me
when I say you're doing this thinking am I not correct a bad girl and as I am daddy you are my girl
so I am the one who must provide punishment mm-hmm yeah that tracks yeah that tracks um
um I'm glad I'm glad we could clarify I gotta say Ben Ben's in the in the plural uh your logic is
flawless uh perfectly sound as well as valid and the conclusion follows from all the premises so uh
good job you've uh you've done yourself proud yet again you did it buddy uh buddies okay uh last one
this one is
https colon slash slash tiny url.com slash yeah ben um as in y e a h b e n u m uh
I'm gonna follow that link I'm gonna follow that link right now and see where it takes me
oh oh the url goes to what I think is the voicemail I don't know why it's like that
okay here we go we have a procrastinator's website if like like it before until we know
exactly what the fuck is going on we can release this in non-youtube areas
sure yeah sure yeah yeah yeah sure sure yeah
shut up okay I'm sorry
it it me it me though hey you ever you ever get that you ever get that feel when sure yeah
you ever you ever get that I I sure do that's relatable that's relatable content uh fucking um
um uh link I'll link to um link to that fucking track in the uh in the in the doobly-doo
her her her her uh great great note great note to go out on thank you whoever the fuck you are
you fucking you fucking psycho um well that's it guys um this has been the uh this has been the
semi solo bencast um on the parole procrastinator's podcast bringing a fucking bringing you a big
fucking cock every fucking sunday every friday morning evening since the since the cows came home uh
uh send us a what are the fucking links hang on gotta go to our own fucking youtube channel
and figure out what links I'm supposed to I'm supposed to tell you to send things to um go go to
send us a send us a fucking voicemail at um where's the fucking what what link is it
whatever it's at the procrastinators mail at at gmail.com is that how you do it do you do it by
email is it like PayPal I don't know um uh follow us support us for bonus episodes at um uh um
what's our fucking page on url patreon.com slash slash the procrastinators yes it's the
procrastinators full words this time um we get you get a lot of a lot of bonus content an awful
lot for five dollars only um uh what else do we usually say um like like comment and subscribe
ring that fucking bell we never say that why don't we say that that's what you gotta do um
uh um pray for us pray for our our fucking fate pray that the whatever fucking capricious
capricious entity controls the youtube algorithm or the fucking youtube headquarters pray that they
see fit to show mercy on us and un and unpunish us for for unspecified crimes that we didn't
commit um what else what else what else um I don't know things are things are shit things are
really shit right now things are probably shit for you as well as for me and as well as for us so
uh be be be nice to each other be be be good be make be kind and make the world a better place
I myself have been thinking about how maybe I need to be kinder maybe I need to not be so angry
even though there's so much to be angry about right now uh uh consider uh uh you guys all hey
everyone knows the pcp audience is a bunch of fucking jerks and they suck maybe be be be be just
just be nice be nice you know what I don't know why I'm saying that I don't know why I'm saying
that I'm probably worse I'm worse than all of you I'm the worst there is you're fine I'm just I'm
talking to myself that I'm just me talking to myself but I'm but I'm projecting it on to you
yeah you guys have the problem you guys should just be just just be cool guys don't just get
fucking so mad about everything don't be such a fucking pussy who's scared to fly on an airplane
scared to fucking go sailing on a boat or whatever just uh yeah what is wrong with you why would you
be like that uh you all gotta fucking shape up or ship out that's it thanks for listening everybody
end of the episode good night lads