Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint and I just don't have the fucking patience for it today. And we got Gibbontake here.
Yeah, I wonder why Ben is feeling down right now.
I'm gonna fucking kill you. It's literally your fault. It's literally your fault. You did this.
What did I do?
Who the fuck are you? Oh, it's Zero and Hoodie, the Kato guys.
Hello, and just so everyone listening knows, Ben invited us to record this 55 minutes ago. But of course, this had to be delayed because he had to get some beef on Twitter real quick.
I had to take a rare L. I had to set aside time to take a rare L. I'm not used to it. It really snuck up on me and just laid me out.
Yeah, it was pretty ridiculous.
The gist of it is that I assume it was you that made the comment. I mean, who else would it be? I guess on the PCP Twitter.
Wait, okay, wait, okay. We don't wait. Let me just like the context of it is that Trixie has had Radcon footage since Radcon.
And we've been asking her for it. I have personally asked her for it and you have personally asked her for it for months now for months.
We have sent messages being like, when are we going to get it? When are we going to get it? We need that footage.
She said in YouTube comments, she told people she would give it to us. She said she would do that and she has ignored all of our requests for it.
And we had a meeting the other day and we talked about like Radcon stuff and we all agreed like, yeah, she hasn't sent it. She's ignoring us.
I don't think it's coming. So today I log into Twitter and I make a fucking tweet saying Trixie has the stuff and it's probably gone.
It's probably destroyed. She's lost it, whatever. Only for her to reply that no, actually, she sent it like two hours before I made the fucking tweet as it could completely randomly.
Is the implication of this that maybe she does listen to the PCP still because it wasn't the last episode that you guys were talking about?
No. No.
No to her. She's just psychic.
I don't know. It's just, no, because we didn't talk about that. We didn't talk about this stuff in specific.
We talked about it at the meeting we had. We didn't talk about that stuff that she has saved.
The last time I asked her about it was the 19th and I mentioned it on Twitter, DM and Discord and she didn't respond. So I don't know.
Right. Just so happens that she sent it to me. She sent it to me while I was asleep and then I woke up and I had seen, I saw the tweet that Ben made first and then assumed Trixie sent it to me in response.
But it was the other way around. I looked at the time that she sent it.
The worst part, the worst part, Ben, is that you got fucked on the math is not only were you wrong about the initial tweet.
I was wrong on the math.
The initial tweet is just fate, right? That's coincidence. No one can really blame you for that. But afterwards, the three more tweets doubling down. That was the rough one. That was the big O.
I mean, it just, yeah, it's an L and I just, it just seemed so, it's just so unlikely that the timing would have been like, I was like, no, it can't possibly be.
So I insisted like, no, you didn't know the math's wrong. No time zones, blah, blah, blah, but no, no, it's all wrong. It's all, it's all in vain.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's really tragic.
It is tragic. This is, it's also really fun.
You know, I, I think this is probably the worst thing to happen on the world stage, you know, within the last several weeks.
Probably of the decade so far.
Yeah, I think so.
I think news heads are going to start talking about the PCP debacle instead of Israel versus Palestine. I think one of these is you serve the other one.
Finally.
Benz finally takes an L.
Headline.
And it's fucking and, and, and Joe Biden withdraws critical aid from Benz saying when he takes an L on the world stage.
Are we much humanitarian aid?
Much like Israel versus Palestine. I mean, this, this has been going on for centuries. I mean, it's really like just a lot of historic.
Yeah.
I mean, really continue long after we're all dead.
Yeah, it is.
I'm so mad. I'm, I just, yes, I'm late. We started the episode late because this, she made that reply like literally as the episode was about to start and I was so flabbergasted and I just, I had to respond to it.
And it, and I just had to see you for like an entire hour.
I just, I just, it's just, it's just the way these things go. And if you don't understand, you have a lot of growing up to do. I don't know.
Yeah, we, we're the immature ones here.
That's right. Everyone, everyone else, everyone else is the problem. Yeah. It's your fault for not understanding why I needed my, my me time.
It's, it's, it's a coming of age ceremony when you have your first big seas.
Yeah.
What, what a, what a fucking disaster. Okay, so that's, so that's why I'm just not in it. That's why I'm not feeling it today, but it doesn't matter.
You guys, you guys are our guests this week. And I was, someone suggested I invite you on because you're running the Kickstarter for the anthology, right?
Do you guys want to like introduce yourselves and tell us what your deal is?
Yeah.
They know who we are.
Okay. Well, I'll introduce ourselves.
Well, you, well you, wait, hoodie, you were on the all guests episode, right?
Yeah. One of the masses in that episode.
Yeah. You were, I remember you were in team red.
Yeah. Actually, in that case, it was actually just me and one other guy, which that was slightly uncomfortable.
Yup. It sure was.
I remember.
Well, anyways, we are the two, two person team behind Kato, Kato, however you want to pronounce it. And yes, as Ben alluded to, we are currently running a Kickstarter for the Kato anthology, which both Ben and Gib are part of, which is basically just a collection of short stories in all different styles and genres about 80 pages.
Definitely check it out. We just passed our stretch goal, literally, not, not our stretch goal. We passed our initial funding.
You hit your own. Yeah. Yeah.
Just last night.
On the next day. On the next day after, yeah, 36 hours, I think it was around there.
Yeah. It really fucking crushed it. What, there's a stretch goal, right? I didn't check, but you said you were going to add a stretch goal when you hit the goal, right?
Yeah. So we, what's the, what's the first one?
We have a few stretch goals lined up and ready to go. We try to be pretty meticulous in the planning of this.
But the first one that we just announced was a variant cover done by one of the included artists in the anthology, Nas.
It is a sort of Bakuman homage to one of the covers that we both really like, which is Ashiro, Ashiro, Ashiroki? I mean, whatever the character's name.
I was, I was going to, I was going to ask you guys are zero and hoodie, but together you are Kato. Is that a Bakuman thing?
That was going to be my first, like, interview question.
And the answer is yes.
Okay, cool.
Well, yes and no. It's in some ways a happy coincidence, but obviously we both, both really big fans of that property. So, you know, I'm sure in some way it warms its way into our subconscious.
So where does, where does the name Kato come from?
It's largely a nonsense name, but in the anthology, we do have, we included a page, which is a series of text messages that zero and I had, I guess, four and a half years ago at this point where we were trying to come up with the name.
And the methodology behind it was, well, it was kind of inspired by Trixie, to be honest, because Trixie had put out a video back then explaining why the name was Digi Bro and not Digi Does Anime or whatever.
And the, the gist of it was that, you know, you don't want to tie your branding down to like one specific thing if you wanted to branch off.
So the methodology going to our name was basically like, let's just come up with something that is short, catchy, simple, but does not limit itself to any specific property.
We don't want to just be talking about, you know, fucking Naruto or whatever, or, or any, you know, specific anime.
So it's basically just a bunch of nothing.
Wait, so what is Kato then initially? Was it supposed to be?
I was going to ask what is, which came first, the YouTube or the comics?
Because you guys, because you guys are make comics.
Yeah, we do, we do comics, but the YouTube was definitely first.
I've always wanted to, you know, like before I even wanted to be a YouTuber, I wanted to be, well, you know, I don't even know if right now I necessarily want to be a YouTuber, but my main goal is to be a writer.
So that technically came first, but my first comic came out after the YouTube channel because I am not an artist, I'm just a writer.
So it was through the popularity and the funding of Kato that I was able to launch that.
Unlike me, who's been a comic book artist from day one.
That's not true.
Is that right?
It's not true at all.
No, that's true.
I was making comics before I met you.
It is.
Okay, you are an artist in the way that won the author of One Punch Man as an artist, except you lacked all of the writing.
That's so cruel.
That's such a cruel thing to say.
And it's accurate.
However, one is a genius.
So thank you.
You're right.
You're both right.
Oh, okay.
Sick.
Yeah, you showed me.
I've seen, you have the one comic called Embers, and then the other one that I read of yours was the one about the espion, right?
Which I think is not finished.
Yeah.
But Embers is a complete story.
The first one that came out was called Always Tomorrow, which is a sort of apocalyptic Pokemon fanfiction.
Which is, I like, I think it's a pretty good first couple of chapters.
But unfortunately, just looking at it, it was going to cost me a ton of money to make to hire the artist and also not make any money in return because it's Pokemon and I can't monetize that.
So I was very limited in my options for that.
So unfortunately, that series just had to get put on indefinite hiatus until I'm rich as fuck.
So after that, I was kind of at a loss for what to do.
And that's when webtoons announced they were doing this short story contest, which was basically that anyone could post on their canvas or discover or whatever it's called, basically where you put amateur comics.
And they were going to pick a bunch of short stories in two different categories and give out like a $15,000 in rewards.
So I found an artist who, like the script I had written, luckily was willing to work for a very modest rate and I put that together.
So yeah, Embers is a completed short story.
And in my opinion, it's pretty good.
I liked it.
I thought it was cool.
Actually, I wanted to talk about not Embers too much, but I wanted to use Embers to talk to Gib about something because Embers, because it was for a contest and we had a very strict deadline.
We were actually coming up on the wire on that and I had to rewrite the ending entirely because we just didn't have enough time to make it work.
I think, Gib, correct me if I'm wrong, you had a similar thing happen with the Tezca Awards, right?
You had to rewrite Clarissa?
Oh, yeah.
I was drawing the Clarissa thing.
I had written out like, oh, this is going to be a fun little short story, but I don't know.
I don't have much experience understanding how much comic page a page of script becomes, usually.
So it was too long and the maximum page limit was coming up, so I had to chop it off.
I had to stop the story at a point where it could potentially end and it's a bad ending.
Instead of being like, well, it's a bad ending and then Clarissa gets thrown in jail and then there's a joke and that's the end.
Instead of beating the bad guy, she doesn't.
It's just all his lost moment.
It's the, what's the second Star Wars?
It's the Empire Strikes Back.
Empire Strikes Back, yeah.
And there's more that happens after that, that I didn't end up drawing.
So did you write this out as a script, like as a screenplay?
You know, I can't really remember.
I think, well, I definitely had a Google Doc of what happens.
I was trying to figure out like plot points and stuff.
I could check, but I think with regards to it being like a script, like everything being written down, I don't think I had that.
I think I had some basics and then I sort of made up the dialogue on the fly.
I knew what was going to happen, but I don't know how they were going to say the things.
And yeah, not as well planned as the Lord of Ghosts, but it's still, it's alright.
It is absolutely bizarre to me how common that is among people who draw their own comics.
Because as someone who just writes, well, first all of my informal education is in screenwriting,
so all of my scripts are written in a screenplay format.
So I was relating to the fact that like, you know, sometimes I write, like I wrote a 14 page script for Embers
and that ended up being super, super long just because I had, I thought that would be short.
I thought 14 pages of a screenplay, that's, you know, I could probably do that in three chapters.
That's not too crazy.
Massively wrong.
It took a lot, a lot of panels to cover all of that.
And it's not even like an action comic, so massive difference in mediums there.
I just, I just would, I just, I wouldn't, I don't think I would ever script out a comic
because that's just not how I conceptualize things.
When I, when I have an idea, I see it, I visually see it in my head.
I don't think about like, I mean, I don't think about like the words.
So I don't, yeah, yeah, I don't like write it out.
I see it and then I'll draw it and then I think of what the words are later.
I write it out only so that, because like I also have like flashes in my head of like,
ah, this shot would be great, this panel, I want something to lead up to this panel.
And then I have to think about like story structure, like, okay, beginning, middle,
end, you know, all that shit, like, oh, it's got to have, you got to set things up
so that they come back later and it's like, it's like everything is there for a reason.
You don't want a meander, you don't want a bunch of bullshit in there that has no relevance
to the climax or whatever.
And so I just say, okay, so this happens and then this happens and I get the basic plot points.
For the Lord of Ghosts, I did script out the dialogue just because I wanted some lore to be explained
and I wanted to figure out what was the least lame way to do that.
I wanted, I wanted to like write it out just so that I, so that it felt like a conversation
and that it wasn't like exposition-y.
Like I would, I would write something and realize, I don't want them to talk for that long.
I need something to happen here so that like, I don't know, some noise happens at the window
and they get interrupted or whatever.
It's just like something to interrupt the flow so there's not just a big block of text.
That's usually why I would go into writing the script dialogue.
Yeah, I was thinking maybe this, like, this style of just unscripted, not freestyling necessarily,
but a little more freeform, is a little easier for you, Ben,
because you do the vapors because that's, you know, this is so light on plot.
It's just, there's a lot of variance and there's a lot of room to sort of mess around
with how structure is played with.
But I would, I wonder if maybe that wouldn't work as well for the champion
because champions seemed like it was going to have a larger sort of narrative overarching story.
Yeah.
Yeah, even so, I still didn't like write out any scripts or anything.
I just had kind of like a plot outline like, this happens and then this happens and then this happens.
And it was a matter of like, yeah, I don't know.
I didn't, I don't write anything like dialogue wise until I've drawn the picture.
And then when I see what they're doing, I can imagine, what are they saying while they're doing this?
Uh, yeah.
Is that usually accurate right off the bat? Like, do you have the first line of dialogue
and that's usually the last line of dialogue, or is that, like, does it, are you readjusting the bubbles constantly?
I don't do any, uh, yeah, I'll, oh god, I don't know, it depends.
It depends. I'll just, I'll just fit text wherever I need to.
Usually I have an idea like, okay, in this bubble, she's gonna have to say a lot, so I'll leave like a bunch of space.
But I don't, I don't like have it, um, I don't know exactly what, I just have an idea like, ah, she can probably get this across in like two sentences.
Um, I need to go to the bathroom all of a sudden, so I'll be, I'm sorry, I'll be right back.
Should we just keep going or should we stop?
Yeah, I, I got something. Yeah, I found my, my, my Google Doc folder of the Tezuka one-shot planning.
I think initially Clarissa wasn't a fully formed character in my head and I needed to figure out what type of person she is.
So I've got like, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
I've got eleven overall documents that have like, outline volume one, brainstorming, uh, what is Clarissa?
Uh, outline version two, uh, plot points.
Uh, and then there's like world building for the Wild West place that she lives in.
And it's all stuff that I should read again, but I never will.
I never look at my own notes.
There was this one panel in the Clarissa comic that I really, really liked, which was, um, I don't know which page it was,
but it was, it was this dramatic pose where it was, the camera was like lowered and she was just saying shut up while she pointed the gun to someone.
I thought that was perfectly, uh, in my opinion, representative of why I like your comics and why, you know, I wanted you in the Cato anthology so bad,
which is that like, you don't, I hope this doesn't come across the wrong way.
Is your art is not like the most mind-blowingly, technically amazing art in the world,
but I do think you have a really solid eye for clean paneling, you know, interesting poses.
I think you put a lot of thought into like, uh, the occasional action shot that I thought was really, really good.
And particularly with Lord of Ghosts, I was really surprised with, beyond that, when that first couple pages of the comic was so empathetic,
it was so, um, emotional, maybe not.
Like, I really immediately fell in love with the character, with the Lord of Ghosts character.
So I thought, like, that to me, your Lord of Ghosts comic is the perfect blend of every talent Gib has, which is that it is these simplistic,
you know, charming character designs, the occasional really badass panel, uh, and then suddenly this amazing heartfelt story about this, like, really touching character.
Yeah, well, thank you.
Um, yeah, I feel like I do, I do put a lot of thought into everything.
Um, I, I remember while I was streaming the, the drawing of the Clarissa comic, I would have revelations and then I would just feel the need to explain.
You see, I, I'm deciding, I'm putting this panel here because, like, it's like two viewers.
And I was like, ah, you see, this is the, the reason for this is sort of, it implies, like, I'm thinking of theming when I'm drawing, like, panels and, and locations of characters.
I love everything that I'm doing for it to, like, have a purpose for being the way it is.
And if I can think of one, if I can, like, if I'm just drawing something and it just so happens to be, like, relevant in, if you think of it in a certain way, then I'm like, yes, fuck yeah.
It's the coolest thing ever.
It's, it's all linked.
It's all deliberate, even though it was, it's kind of made up in, in a moment.
But that's relatable.
I think that's just how, how art usually is, is like, yeah, not everything is planned ahead of time.
You have to be making it at the same time.
I feel I've, I've done a lot of planning in for other things.
Then, then I make it and it's different.
I mean, the Lord of Ghosts had different dialogue every time I would come up to a point where they would say the line that I had written.
It's the same amount of text because I made the speech bubbles, the right size for the thing.
But then I'm like, you know what, this is a cringe way to say it.
I should rearrange, I should change what they say and I don't want to redraw all the speech bubbles.
So I just make it work.
Right.
I mean, if for fans of Lord of Ghosts, for fans of the Lord of the Ghosts, if you pick up the Cato anthology, you will see that 99% of the
99% of the same is the same pages that were, you know, on your website and everything.
But there's like just two small changes to the dialogue and stuff.
So, you know, I think art is like a really malleable form and I'm like huge into planning.
Right.
So I like, unlike, unlike Ben, I do script out all of my comics.
I do script out every story I write.
I also outline.
I write pitch documents.
I, you know, the story I'm working right now, I have like 30 pages of stuff.
And then also I'm currently writing 25 pages of stuff, like 30 pages of outlines.
And then 25 pages of the actual story.
So like, I am very heavy into planning, but even doing that, you know, I start, I open up my document.
I start actually typing out the story and things change.
And I'm like, hmm, that I can't find the line of dialogue to make this work.
Maybe I need to change the scene a little bit.
Maybe I need to put another character in here.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't even consider this, you know, XYZ, whatever.
Things are super malleable when you actually start writing.
It's like, because, you know, how like a sketch or a first draft, it's hard to write the first time, but once you're reading it, you can realize what could be improved.
And when you have all the different pieces there, like if you, when I get to a point where I've got the sketch of the drawing of the page, and I have the dialogue from before, and I put them together, I realize the dialogue could be improved, or maybe I should leave this revelation for the next page and then move the panel away.
And then change or add a different panel to make up for the space.
And, you know, when you're looking at something that does exist, it's easier to edit it to make it good.
When you're planning it, you're always imagining what it looks like in the end.
I think one of the things that changes the easiest is scenes that, the way scenes transition into each other, right?
So when you're planning something, you kind of, at least I don't think too much about like the overall weave.
I don't like, well, you know, overall structure is definitely important, but I don't think of like, how am I going to make this scene connect, scene one connect to scene two in an interesting way?
I just kind of think, well, here's scene one and here's scene two, and I'm going to start working on scene three.
But when you're actually writing, you're like, is there anything I could do to make this like, can I put an interesting cut right here?
Can I make a matching piece of dialogue?
Can I, you know, have these scenes reflect each other in some way?
And there's a lot of different ways you had to think about, you know, interconnectivity and you had to think about segues and natural transitions and, you know, interesting ways to cut between things.
I think that's the type of stuff that ends up getting changed when I'm actually writing the most.
Zero, what about you?
This is, from my understanding, Zero, this is your, the comic coming out in the Cato anthology is your first real, you know, quote unquote real written work.
Am I wrong or no?
That is correct.
What was the process for writing?
Well, initially, I wanted to go in, or I went into this wanting to do an excerpt from this story, and initially it was going to be an entirely separate excerpt.
But then I realized, wow, action, it takes up a lot of time, doesn't it?
Yeah, we were working in an interesting time frame, or not a time frame, but like a page limit, which is that because this was all self funded and because neither of us artists, we did have to hire someone.
So it was very much working within specific constraints, which honestly, in my opinion, tends to breed creativity.
But correct me if I'm wrong, this is, you originally had like a shootout scene, and now we just have a dialogue.
Can you actually, can you just pitch the people what exactly your comic is?
Sure.
So, Queenside is like a battle shounen superhero parody.
It's about this group of, you know, three young individuals who sort of get roped into Zeus's ambition.
And Zeus, like the ringleader.
Her philosophy, her nindo, is to surpass the old Titans.
That's also something, I mean, there's no way to say this without sounding a little pretentious, but that's something I'm attempting to do with this story.
I want it to, you know, be the next one piece.
Dude, same.
It always feels like that.
That's such a dangerous ambition, though.
You got to try, though.
You got, I mean, I, speaking about like loads of planning, there's like hundreds at this point of Google Docs in my folder for webcomics,
ultimately to set up the biggest, coolest story with all the characters that I've written, all of them, and they're all going to be in one piece,
but it's going to be written by me instead.
And it's going to have all of these interconnected lore things that don't mean anything yet, because I don't fucking know what they mean,
but they will mean something and people will be able to go back and say, oh, Pog, chapter one of bell shape.
It's like it set us up the whole thing.
It's every artist wants to do that, everyone.
I think that it's the coolest.
That is exactly what I was just thinking, which is that it's the ultimate, ultimate comic gambit, which is that you have such this great ambition that probably is not going to work.
It's just being no one.
There's a reason there's only one one piece, right?
There's no reason not everyone's doing that.
But if it does, you look like the genius is the type of thing they make documentaries about.
It's the type of thing people will be like, can you believe he was working on this for 30 years?
And can you believe that she in bell shape chapter one?
It did this and that paid off 30 years down the line like Oda with the fucking laboon.
You know, it's the ultimate comic writers have it.
Have you guys seen you guys seen fully coolie?
I've not.
Yeah, I didn't watch season two.
What the fuck?
Well, I haven't seen season two either.
I don't care about that.
The bit where Nina Mori gets hit with the Vespa and then later at dinner when all the the family is eating the curry, the little Prince curry that's too spicy.
And then she gets sick.
She gets diarrhea or something and she her face goes all and she has to go to the bathroom because she having a delayed onset like stress reaction.
That's me.
That's what what I just had to do in the bathroom right now and getting and getting hit.
But for me, getting hit with the Vespa was taking an L on Twitter.
It was so traumatic that it made me sick.
And I'm probably going to have to go back again.
I wasn't thinking that sees shit has been gone for a long time.
So if I'm sorry, I'm going to try and I'm going to try and it's because I'm going to try and I'm going to try and cope while I see, but I don't know if I can do it.
It's because you're so unused to feeling an L, you know, you're not inoculated to the L virus and it's like doing severe damage.
That girl got hit with Vespa's more often.
She wouldn't have had any issues.
It's like what's the it's like at the end of Oh God, what was it called?
Dr. Horrible.
You guys know Dr. Horrible sing along blog.
Yeah, the Dr. Horrible sing along blog when Captain Hammer feels pain for the first time.
When he takes when he gets it's that's me.
I'm Captain Hammer.
I'm Captain Hammer looking at my what does he get like shot in like the chest or something.
He gets shot somewhere and he starts like screaming on the ground like mommy mommy.
That's me, but it's because I think the solution here is that you need to take more L's.
Oh yeah, you think so.
Let's let's let's up the Twitter L game.
You know, it's time to cringe post everypony.
I you guys were saying every artist wants to make the next one piece.
My ambitions are more like I want to make the next Cerebus, which is to say a like weird piece of art that like has no that like clearly doesn't know what it's doing.
And meanders for like 17 years and everyone now just goes, you know, Cerebus.
Yeah, that was that was really weird.
But boy, he sure did make it for a long time.
I feel like that's literally that's also a goal.
Yeah.
Yeah, you've already made it.
You've been working on the you've had three chapters of papers over eight years.
Well, it's because I don't work on it because I have all these other weird flights of fancy that I have to actually said this is interesting.
Sorry, I'll let you go in a second.
But I was what I was saying before about envisioning it and seeing it visually in my head so I don't script anything.
That's true of like the game to like I saw what the game would look like in my head.
And I was like, I that's what it has to be.
And like right now I'm working on cut.
I'm putting cutscenes in and I don't know what the dialogue is.
I just like I'll make the cutscene.
I'll make the characters move around the screen and then it'll be like, OK, here's where a dialogue box pops up.
The cutscenes already made.
What am I actually going to have him say?
I guess he'll say clickety clickety clickety clickety click.
Well, wait.
Yeah, that's that's it.
Yeah, that works.
I do envision that there is a cutscene, but not even that there is some information that needs to be delivered to the player.
Like you don't know that.
I envision that there is a cutscene and there is dialogue, but I don't like there.
There's no reason for it to exist other than that you can see a cutscene.
No, it no, it's it's not that it's that I'm like, OK, at this point in the game, it would make sense.
You know, there would be a scene.
There would be a little cinematic scene and, you know, plot would be conveyed through dialogue.
I wonder if maybe you approach this from a tone and pacing perspective as opposed to like a sort of necessary plot perspective, right?
So like it seems like you're saying it would feel right for the game to have a cutscene here because that will help the tone and pacing.
But I don't know what that cutscenes about and I don't know how it's going to progress this plot structure.
That's just not a concern.
No, I don't think I'm explaining this well.
I know what it's going to be about because I have a very clear idea of what the story of the game is.
So I know like what what beats need to be hit along the way the path from the start to the end.
Well, that's what I was thinking.
So then I'm thinking like, OK, yeah.
So I'm thinking like, OK, this part is where we can hit that beat and then then we can hit that beat right here.
And then I know in this beat, you know, Phantom Horn encounters such and such, you know, they interact in such and such way, you know, he'll he'll they'll talk.
And I know generally what they're going to say.
I just don't I don't know the actual words they're going to use until I write them.
I think this is an interesting topic because I wanted to ask I want to ask a question just a sort of thought provoking question, which is that if money were no object, what is all of our artistic dream projects?
But I wanted to specifically ask you, Ben, is your like, is your end goal to be someone who makes comics or is it to be someone who makes games?
Because it seems like this is just a feeling, but it feels like you make comics because you're good at it and it's pretty marketable.
But I get the impression that you have a lot and maybe even more passion to just making the occasional game or two.
I don't I don't really care.
Like what medium I'm working in.
I don't know.
I just the reason why I'm making a game right now is because when I thought about how does this story end?
I just envisioned it happening as a game.
And so I was like, well, I guess I got to do that.
I mean, I plan to make more comics in the future.
I'll fucking do I'll fucking do whatever.
I don't care.
I probably wouldn't.
I was I was going to say I probably wouldn't do like prose writing because it's not very visual.
But I guess I wouldn't like never say never about that.
But yeah, I wouldn't say that I have a preference one or the other.
I mean, I think the reason why I the reason why I started making comics was just because I just think I thought comics were cool
and I kind of had some of the skills necessary for making them.
So I was like, I guess I'll just I guess I'll just do that.
Yeah.
But I'm not.
Okay.
The question was like if you had unlimited budget or something.
Yeah, just like if there was no reason if there was no limitations on like practicality or time or whatever.
I guess the larger question here is like, what is the end goal of your artistic artistic ambitions?
You know, like,
Yeah, it's it's odd because a lot of the time I think of the things that I want to make and I see my characters, but just in the place of
the feeling of reading or watching or playing a thing that I have already played.
So like, oh, wouldn't it be cool if I made Homestuck?
Like that's the way I think.
Wouldn't it be cool if I made one piece?
What if it wouldn't be cool if like I made my favorite PS2 games?
And I'm like, I don't really know other than like, I guess it's it's a weird question to answer for me.
Because it's like, why'd you make art?
I don't know.
Sometimes I look at the stuff I make and it's cool.
And I want to do that again.
When I had when I think of like, if I had all the the resources, I guess I would pay people because I don't feel like I'm good enough to make the things in my head reality.
And I would need a team like I could make a Ghibli film.
I could make a fucking, I could make a, you know, classic PS2 game.
I could make all these things, but they would be with my cactus in them.
And then I would have to say it's kind of childish now that I think about it.
You just want the credit actually.
Well, well, it's it's not that I don't want any creative input, because obviously the point of it being by me is that it's my idea of a story.
And I don't know why create anything, because I feel like it.
If I had all the resources, I would make bigger things than I am currently able to do with just myself.
And that wouldn't be, it's not like I have a passion for a specific craft or trade.
I'd like drawing, but I'm not very good at it.
And it's, yeah, I don't have a lot of patience for learning because I'm stupid.
So I'm improving, but slowly.
I also like all these other things that I never I'm like, dipping my toes into every profession ever.
A creative profession I wear at me.
And, you know, it would be cool to make games.
It would be cool to make animations or music or or, you know, all these things.
Drawing just seems to be the easiest one because right now all I need for that is a drawing tablet of some kind and.
I make comics.
I don't think I don't even read that many comics.
I do like mine.
Same. I don't read.
I don't read enough.
I do think there's this sort of cultural obsession with being the artist, being the director or being the writer or some sort of like having a really direct control hands on with a, you know, artistic product or whatever.
But I do think one of the lesser aspire to positions, but talk to any professional and it will be one of the most important is the role of like an editor or the role of a producer, which is that like this person is not necessarily, you know, quote unquote creating the art, but they are invaluable to the process, at least in like larger scale productions.
And they, in my opinion, it is still very artistically satisfying.
Like 90% of this anthology has nothing to do with anything that I technically created.
I wrote one comic and I helped zeroes a little bit.
But other than that, it was just the process of recognizing talent and other people collecting, you know, collecting information from different people, providing slight input on what might need changed or how things can fit and like basically just the act of producing this anthology.
Even though I wasn't involved with a lot of the artistic process for most of it, still felt incredibly artistically satisfying.
So I do think more people should are would be in it would be it would behoove more people to really think about the artistic process in a less specific focus lens of just I, you know, I am a writer, I am an artist or I'm a director or, you know, so on and so forth.
Yeah, I mean, if it turns out that like, ultimately, I would be heading a project to make my things that other people other people, I just like, I don't need to be the one to draw all of my comics or all of my ideas.
I definitely design them first and then they would draw them better.
But yeah, I guess I just the way I see art that is fulfilling for me is a way for me to communicate emotions, feelings, ideas, things like that through any medium.
And usually just the mediums that I personally enjoy experiencing, which is like comics and animation and games, I probably wouldn't write prose because I don't like reading.
I probably wouldn't, you know, do I don't know if I can take talks because I don't like those I don't care about that.
But the the thing that would like get me to want to continue is is the the ability to be making the decisions.
I don't like the idea of working hard for someone else's vision.
And I feel like I know a lot of people who are exactly the same, which is unfortunate because we do.
The world does need a lot more like managers and and people who can organize these idiots we are and put us into into a place where we'll actually make the things we're trying to make.
And producers and stuff like that.
It's just I just I'm just selfish.
I just want my thing.
I want my thing on there.
I think I have to go to the bathroom again.
I'll be back.
I'm dying.
I'm I'm dying so much.
I'm sick.
I'm ill.
I'm I'm I'm wasting away.
No, the capital.
I'll be I'll be I'll be I'll be fast this time.
I promise.
Well, let me use this as a transition point.
And this is better to talk about what Ben's not here because Ben will just go on an angry tirade give.
I wanted to talk about Kickstarter's and obviously you guys have a lot going on with with Trixie and all that and divorced from that divorce from those.
Oh, yeah.
Well, whatever.
Oh, we can talk about it if you want to.
I don't mind.
I just didn't, you know, I wanted to ask like I wanted to get some input into because this is our first Kickstarter.
And this is the first time we're doing anything even remotely related to this.
There's a lot that we don't know about like what's going to happen.
We don't know about the obstacles we don't know about yet.
So I was wondering if I could get some insight into some of the first Kickstarter's you ran individually.
You ran for like rad cons and stuff and some of the things that like notably went wrong and not including the whole Trixie to Vakul.
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't have as much direct experience with the Kickstarter's as Ben does because Ben has had a number.
How many?
Is it two or three?
There's the RFCK pins thing as well as the Vapors chapter one and two physical books.
Those were all successful.
Those are great.
Ben would obviously know how to do it properly.
I did one Kickstarter attempt, which was like aiming too high and it didn't get funded for like the punk plushie.
It was the plushie.
Yeah.
The punk plush Kickstarter.
Still on the table like in the far future.
It's never not going to be possible.
I just need more of a precedent that people would have the money and also there are enough of them because people did want those.
They're just not enough people.
I guess what could go wrong for like the Radcon stuff, especially Radcon four less so Radcon three.
I think it was the stretch goals got out of hand on Radcon four.
Not that far out of hand, but it was just sort of we were streaming right during the end of the Kickstarter.
We streamed because the hype machine really gets people going and people wanted to pledge because they could they could watch the stream and watch our reactions to it reaching higher and higher heights.
And we ran out of stretch goals.
And so we started making shit up.
And you know, some of them.
I think the animated for animated was one of the ones we came up with on the fly.
I think I'm not sure.
No, no, no, no.
That's not true.
No, no, no.
The animated OP was was one of like the long standing.
Was it?
Okay.
I guess I guess that one was just like we didn't know how that was going to be possible.
We just thought it was a cool idea.
I don't.
And we didn't realize how much money it would cost.
I don't agree.
No, we did.
We totally did.
We didn't have like a set amount of money set aside for like what?
You're technically right, but I feel like the spirit of what you're saying is wrong
because no, we didn't know exactly how much it was going to cost,
but like we knew it was going to cost some money to get done.
And we knew it was going to take a while to get done.
I mean, you're right.
Yeah.
I'm just saying we did not even have like any contacts by the time that was part of the Kickstarter.
We didn't know who we could contact to get it.
Exactly.
So after the Kickstarter ended, we started looking around.
And I feel like that was a mistake.
We should have looked around before and gotten like a better idea.
I mean, we knew it was going to take a while.
I don't know.
You're talking as though a mistake was made.
Well, I don't know.
I just feel like as general advice, it would be better to have a plan of action of how to
like how to make the stretch goals real so that there is no chance.
There's less of a chance that things could be, you know, unexpectedly more expensive.
I mean, you're right.
You're right.
But the OVA animation is not a good example of that because that is a success and it will.
And it will.
And it will be a success.
It will be successfully executed.
But what is the status on that?
It is finished, but the OVA itself is not edited.
Yeah, it is finished.
Nate is on that.
So that will be out at some point.
Nate is on it.
Nate is on it, but he was busy for a while and he couldn't work on it.
But I think he is freer to do so now.
So it is.
Yeah.
Well, all that content, you know, really.
I don't know exactly why.
But yeah, Nate says he's like more able soon to work on all the things that need to get
edited, including the OVA and the Brad lecture and the music video.
The stuff that we came up with on the fly was the, I think it was the dojin.
The dojin was definitely one.
Maybe the print version of Road to Radcon in book form might have been one that we came
up on the fly.
I'm not sure about that one.
Yeah, I can't remember.
But the dojin definitely was.
The dojin definitely was.
I think having plenty of feasible stretch goals ahead of time is an important thing,
obviously, because if you have to make stuff up on the fly, there's a chance it could go wrong.
Yeah, even though I don't feel like it had terrible consequences or anything, it probably
wasn't a great idea to just make shit up on the top of our heads.
But it's fine.
Yeah, it's fine.
I mean, my second Kickstarter, the Vapors 2, there came a point when I just kind of started
making up joke stretch rewards because I didn't have anything.
The Oculus Rift.
I started doing the like...
That was funny.
That was the first one.
Yeah, the first Kickstarter had the Oculus Rift Kickstarter, or a stretch goal, which
we hit and which, yeah, I bought an Oculus Rift and which we ended up using at Radcon 4.
So, you know, some content came of that.
And then, yeah, the one for Vapors 2, I just started making shit up about the Slime and
Punishment character, Uwupati.
It just was like, send him to college, send him to rehab.
Oh, yeah.
I'm surprised it worked as well as it did, because that went pretty far.
I think people just leave off with him not being able to go to rehab.
I believe he...
Yeah, he didn't make it to rehab.
He didn't...
No, canonically.
And this is canon because I say it is.
If Christine Weston Chandler had just retweeted the Kickstarter, we would have reached enough
for Uwupati to go to rehab, but she callously ignored its plight.
And so it saw no other alternative but to hurl itself into the Slime or Dissolve vats in
the Slime Corp laboratories tragically.
But then, of course, the timeline split again when two different characters appeared to rescue
it from its fate.
So, you know, it all gets very complicated.
What the fuck even is Slime and Punishment?
It's just some bullshit.
Don't worry.
It was a small joke, but it became the biggest thing ever.
Yeah, my next Kickstarter that I'm going to do is when Slime and Punishment is done,
I'm going to make a book version and sell that.
That'll probably be this year.
I don't see why it would take longer than that.
That's going to be fun.
But yeah, I don't know.
The thing about Stretch Goals is that everyone kind of understands that they're just sort
of there to generate hype.
It's not, with a Stretch Goal, you don't really have to justify the price.
I don't know.
You don't have to be like, okay, this Stretch Goal, if I make exactly another $1,000, the
next Stretch Goal is something that will cost me exactly $1,000.
People just want to hit Stretch Goals just for the hype factor.
And even if the thing that it gives you is very insubstantial, even if it's just like,
oh, we will make the cover glossy.
Nobody really cares if the cover is glossy, but that's a perfectly acceptable Stretch Goal.
What sort of person would like not donate to a Kickstarter unless a specific Stretch
Goal is reached like a glossy cover or something like that?
Yes.
You're browsing Kickstarter.
You see the Kato anthology.
You think, hmm, I'm on the fence about this one.
Oh, I see that if we reach the next Stretch Goal, the cover will be converted from, will
be card stock, glossy cards.
I'll come back when we reach that one.
I'm not investing until we get that goal.
No, no, it's just not how it works.
Yeah.
I think we have.
By the way, I saw the two.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
The delay.
I saw that the, the, it got the, it got the, the, the mark of the Kickstarter approval,
the project we love stamped on it, which was pretty cool.
And also it's like close to the top of the anthologies list.
Like, like if you browse anthologies on Kickstarter right now, Kato anthology is like number like
three or four or five.
So it's in like the top couple rows.
Yeah.
The highest I saw it was number three, but I don't really know how that worked.
Like, I don't even know how they organize this at all.
Cause now we're at number six.
So I think, I think it's some kind of weighted thing where like probably the fact that it
made its goal like really fast, uh, pushed it up a little bit in the, in the algorithm,
I think.
And probably also the fact that they gave it project we love, which I have no idea how
they decide what to give the project we love stamp.
My, my first Vapors Kickstarter got it.
Uh, and, but neither of the other ones that I did, uh, got it.
Vapors too didn't get it.
And the RFC Cape Inn Kickstarter did not get it.
I wonder if the second Vapors was too, uh, with all the slime stuff, maybe that was just
too weird for them to sign.
Cause it's probably like some sort of liability there.
Like they want to be careful about who they give it to.
I don't think so because I didn't add that stuff in until like way later, like until
I was adding like late, late stage stretch goals.
So I don't think that would have done it.
The RFC K1, I totally understand because it literally has fuck in the name.
And so probably they might have been like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like that one I get that one.
I am like, yeah, that makes sense.
Um, oh, let me tell you my, my genius idea, my genius idea though, um, to double dip,
right?
Cause being, being a successful, being a successful artist is all about double dipping and extracting
as much profit as you can out of as few, out of as little, as little work as you can.
So I'm going to double dip on the RFC Cape Inn Kickstarter.
Cause now since I have all these extra pins from that Kickstarter, I can offer that stuff.
I can offer the coins and the pins and the patches and stuff as bonus rewards on the
Slime and Punishment book because it's all related.
It's all, it's the same cannon.
It's the same setting.
It all connects.
It's like a spider web.
It, it, it's like poetry.
It rhymes.
I gotta, I gotta be honest.
I am a little jealous at how, how successful Ben St.
Kickstarter lore is.
It's just like you have these, these, these pins and everyone's really hype about them.
And then I failed, man.
I still feel bad about it.
I gotta, I gotta have successful Kickstarter one of these days.
I gotta make something to be, to be fair, the pins did not actually make very much money.
Like most of what we made on the Kickstarter went back into like, it made a little bit,
but like most of it did.
We didn't like keep most of that as profit or anything.
But the second Vapors one was, was a huge success.
And like, I couldn't believe how successful it was actually.
I was shocked.
The, the, oh, the other, the other synergy.
I did a similar synergy with, with Vapors two, because with Vapors one,
I ordered 500 copies, which is more than I needed because there was a price break at 500.
And I did that knowing that if I Kickstarter number two, I could offer the extras of number one,
which I had paid less for it because the lower price point, because the price break at 500,
I could offer that as like bonus rewards.
And that's exactly what it did.
I didn't have to make any new copies of Vapors one.
I just had like hundreds of them left over.
And I, and it was almost, I literally have like only like 20 copies left of Vapors one
because the number that I ended up selling with the Vapors two plus Vapors one was like exactly 500
or like really close to it.
It was just like, no, no, it was, it was, it was Belissimo.
It worked out.
It worked like a dream.
That's pretty clever.
I wanted to say, Gib, I do think a plush just happens to be a pretty niche product.
If you kickstarted any of your comics, it would be, I mean, within reason it'd be successful.
The problem with, the problem with the plush Kickstarter was just that it had a high price point.
Yeah.
The, the, like a comic is cheap, you know, like my, like, you know, 30, my like 40 page Vapors comic,
I think the basic tier was like 15 bucks plus shipping for the book.
And that's just, you know, that's a low, that's a low floor with the plush.
What was it like $40 or something?
It's a, it's a big, it was a big, it was a big initial hurdle for people to, to jump through to get it.
It's a lot of ghosts isn't technically finished yet.
There's still like act three they need to make, I guess.
Yeah.
I've been wondering about whether it would be like a good or a bad idea to like package act one and two,
what currently exists and then make that a book.
Because I feel like that's, that's what I was thinking.
It would be like possible.
I just, I just liked the idea of all being in one, like, oh, the whole Lord of ghosts all like 190 pages.
Yeah.
That's, that's really long though.
It's already like 90 pages.
So who knows?
I mean, you could always just reprint it as a completed book once you're done.
I think you could do a Kickstarter for the first part and just say that this is going towards the funding of doing more.
And at that point you are not only getting people who want a physical copy of Lord of Ghosts,
you also are getting people who just want more comic and therefore see it as desirable to give you money.
And then yeah, just reprint it again at a later date once you have the entire thing as like some sort of deluxe edition or whatever.
Yeah.
It makes more sense, I guess.
I could, I could do that.
I, it's, it's all, it all exists.
Why not?
All right, Lord of Ghosts Kickstarter launching tomorrow.
Link in the description.
Oh God.
Now I've got to think.
Now I've got to think about stuff.
Well, all right.
Yeah.
That'd be good.
I've got, I've got to think about stuff.
Sorry.
I hope, I hope a topic change isn't unwelcome.
But speaking of stuff that you got to think about.
I'm losing my house.
And that's fucking epic.
Talk about elves.
Yeah.
That's only the second biggest L of today.
They saw your dope and there's like, oh, the lease is up.
Get out.
Lose it.
L losing my house?
Losing my house, no reaction.
Taking an L on Twitter, it's like, I got to go punch a wall.
I got to, I get, I get stressed diarrhea.
I got.
Fuck, I'm going to throw up.
Yeah.
It's, it's be like that.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm gonna, I got to move.
I got to move in like two months and I don't know where I'm going.
And my rent is going to go up because there's no way I can find a place.
Consider it an RV.
I, I stole an RV.
So, but, but it's condemned.
It was condemned.
Well, like haunted.
Yeah.
It was haunted.
It was bewitched.
You might say.
Haunted by the soul of Trixie's career.
You got him.
Got him.
You killed him.
But no, I can't live in that.
No, it's cursed.
It's, it's out of the question.
So yeah, I got to find a new house and my rent's going to go up and I'm, I'm, I'm sad about
it.
I'm kind of, I'm a little stressed about it.
What do you guys think?
Homelessness?
Pretty cool.
I don't know.
Are we pro or anti?
It's pretty cringe.
Pretty sus to be homeless.
No, I think it's pretty base.
Thank you.
Zero.
Someone had to say it.
I can't, I can't.
I'm named after my number of possessions.
I can't take the idea that once homeless, I would be cringe.
I just have to think it's based.
I, I saw, um, oh, I saw, uh, that artist did the, the zero and hoodie like drawing of
you two.
By the way, I saw you, you retweeted it.
That was a really cool piece.
Uh, which one are you referring to?
Um, oh God, who did it?
It was, um,
Was it, was it like the little chibi things?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait.
Yeah.
Those are fucking dope.
Like, I don't know what I'm going to, I need to use that for something.
Put that in the fricking, put that in the fricking like bonus page or something.
Uh,
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
I'm going to put that, put that here in the chat for Eleazar, uh, show that one on
the fricking, on the fricking video by Nass, by Nass in the sky.
Yeah.
Who also did our stretch goal, uh, variant cover and is in the comic.
Uh, she does, she does pretty excellent like slice of life manga.
I have, I have a question.
I don't think Gib asked this while I was gone.
Uh, how did you choose what to include?
What was your criteria?
Oh yeah.
Um, well you two got invited because we're just both huge fans of your work.
Right.
Even though my work is shit, I just, I'm, I'm, I was grandfathered in.
Yeah.
Just how I like it.
Uh, the six other people all paid us lots of money to get in.
Uh, epic.
That's how those was.
All of which, all of which you then turned around and gave to me with the privilege
of putting my stuff in there.
So it was the circle of life.
Uh, yeah.
We had to, you know, it's like getting a new credit card to pay off the old credit
card.
We had to pay you so we had to get them to pay us.
It was a lot of work.
That's right.
The real answer is just to clarify all the, all the contributors got paid for their
contributions.
Right.
Okay.
That is something we are touting pretty heavily is that regardless, even if this
Kickstarter failed, everyone got paid.
Everyone retains the rights to their comics.
We didn't want to, this was never about, you know, uh, owning the lord of ghosts so that
Gib couldn't run her Kickstarter tomorrow.
Yeah.
I'll, I'll, um, uh, if I can contract where it explained that you don't have the rights
or, or, but you, I give you permission to publish it in a thing.
It's like, wow, that's like professional.
What, what the fuck?
That's like sensible.
Yeah.
I think the terminology was like until the end of the universe or something or like ad
infinite.
It was something like till death, like the, you know, till death of you.
Yeah.
Um, that, that, I mean, that contract was just something I found online, not to shatter
the illusion of professionality, but yeah, that was just a basic template I found.
Well, that means it's, but it does hold up in court and I will sue anyone who tries
to fuck us.
Good.
That's right.
He's lying.
He wrote it down as I dictated it.
Um, the real answer to how we, how we chose these is that we had, uh, we, we put out the
announcement video saying like, uh, you know, any two to 12 page comic can enter and we
had about 70, 70 or 80 entries.
I don't remember the exact number, but, um, we had a lot of entries, Ben, you were actually
on, uh, you were on the form.
I had sent you an invite, uh, so I don't know if you, uh, I assumed you didn't want
to help us choose, but you weren't allowed to.
We did, uh, you know, invite you.
Really?
Yeah.
That was like one of the first things I had told you about.
You had, you had asked me like, uh, you would ask to see if you, you'd ask to see the
entries.
I was like, oh yeah, sure.
And if you want to help us pick, that's cool too.
I, you should have reminded me cause I have a vague memory that you did tell me that,
you, you could have, you could have, you could have asked me once or twice, like, hey, Ben,
do you want to weigh in on this cause maybe I would have.
I don't know.
I assumed, I assumed you were busy by the fact that you had a failed deliver on the cover
for two weeks.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Well, whatever.
I'm sure, I'm sure you, I'm sure you've made great choices.
Yeah.
I mean, I, I think the comics and the anthology are the criteria.
We didn't, we didn't have like a list of, you know, a rubric or anything, but we read
through them all.
We had narrowed it down to a fair amount that were good.
We actually had, we were deciding for a long time who was going to get in and we had like,
by the end of it, we had like four different lists and we had decided on one and it didn't
include someone that we thought like maybe we just increased the number to 11 comics
because we just liked their story so much.
Yeah.
It was, it was incredibly difficult, but one of the things that we were looking for was
that like, we didn't want all the comics to feel the same as, you know, as people who
make and consume art, we have our own interests.
We have our own subjective things and there are comics in the anthology that might not
have been my particular interest, but I thought a story as varied and as wide appealing as
I want this to be should have a comic that appeals to people who would like this story,
even though it's not necessarily like my ideal aesthetic or whatever.
What, what made you, what gave you the idea to do like a community anthology in the first place?
I think anyone would have paid attention to this Kickstarter if it was just us.
Well, I don't know.
I think there's, there is a, an answer that is true, but so the real answer is that there's
a lot of practicality behind it, which is that are you saying, are you saying that like
having more artists involved with it just gets more eyes on it?
Is that the idea?
I think that that is, that was definitely 70, 65 percent of why we did it.
There was, it started, it started with the idea of I was looking, I had, for the first
time, I was just like, how much does it actually cost to print a comic?
Because I, I've always assumed it was super expensive.
I didn't even want to bother.
And I looked at it and I was like, oh, it's like 10 bucks, it's 10 bucks per comic,
basically, you know, with, with a lot of variants and depends on the page count and
color and whatever.
But yeah, yeah, it's something.
It was not wildly expensive, like I thought.
So I had considered, you know, do I want to adapt embers, which is written in like a
scrolling webtoon format?
Do I want to adapt that into a print thing?
Because I kind of just wanted something to hold.
And I decided, no, that's lame.
And then I thought, well, we also kind of have had terrible success with raising
money in the past.
This is our first Kickstarter, but we do have a Patreon, which I think we are,
we are fairly bad at promoting and it's something we've never really pushed too
hard and therefore it's not super successful.
So there was, there was my practical mindset was thinking like, it's going to be
really embarrassing if I launch a Kickstarter for my own comic book and it
fails entirely.
So part of that was like, well, this would be a good opportunity to get the
community together.
This would be a good opportunity.
Cause one of the other things that I say this in the Kickstarter description is
that like I am very heavy on the mindset of like just creating even if you don't
necessarily have the skills.
So constantly on the channel, I'm telling people like, if you want to be a writer,
just go write something.
If you want to be, if you want to make a video, go make a video or anything.
I constantly tell people to do that.
But one of the things that I think I am particularly aware of is that there is a
financial element to making art and not always.
I mean, I think if you are very comfortable with the baseline of only doing
things yourself, even if you absolutely suck, you know, you can do it for free at
that point.
So it takes time, but you know, as someone who has paid artists for all of their
comics, I understand that like this is something that I can do because, you know,
I, I have a good amount of savings or, you know, the channel makes a good amount
of money or whatever.
It's not something that everyone could do.
So part of the anthology was like, for as much as I want to push this idea, it is
also, you know, I think a good thing for us to do is to help fund people who we
think can do it.
You know, to go back to something I was saying a little while ago is that I find
one of the most artistically satisfying things that I could do.
And I don't know if everyone feels this way is finding talent, identifying people
who I think have the skills and helping them cultivate it.
Whether that means, you know, like saying, hey, this little tweak to writing
could make your story a little better.
Or like, hey, have you considered framing the panel this way?
Or even just saying, hey, do you need money to make this work?
I find that stuff incredibly satisfying.
So that was, I wish, I wish more people asked me that question.
Yeah.
Yeah, I get you.
I, I do think I, I actually feel this way a lot about you, which is why I wanted
to, you were the first person outside of zero.
You were the first person I reached out to about this.
When I, you know, this was back in November or December, like six months ago,
I had asked you, I told you we had this idea and we wanted you involved in it.
Because the fact of the matter is I do think the vapors and the champion and all
of your work is incredible.
And I do think, you know, it seems like you have, you are underrated for your
skillset.
So I, I thought if there was anything I could do to help out with that, even
though I'm always saying this, I'm always saying this.
I don't want to overstate our audience.
We are not huge.
Like we have, we have a hundred thousand subscribers on YouTube.
You have a hundred thousand subscribers is a big channel.
You're, you're, you're like as big as Nate.
You're bigger than Nate.
If you, we could go, we could go and kill Nate right now.
That's probably not true though.
You're probably going to be bigger than that.
Yeah, there's no way we could kill Nate.
No, he's too big.
He's too big.
Yeah.
Have you seen his posture?
It's incredible.
There's a line of people waiting to fuck me and how are we going to get
past those guys?
Okay, but go on, go on.
What I was going to say is that Nate has the same size as audience,
audience as us by numbers, but his are way more passionate.
His are way more dedicated to sporting him.
You can see this in like Patreon numbers, average view count, whatever.
We have a pretty large audience, but that just, I think that's kind of just
because we hit the algorithm a fair amount.
Like we tend to make videos that YouTube likes.
So we hit a wide net, but we don't have like the most dedicated core fan base.
So in a lot of ways, I actually think, you know, the PCP, you know,
in your individual audiences kind of outweigh us in at least certain regards.
So, you know, I don't want to make it seem like I'm just doing charity work here.
I mean, like, I've come down from Mount Olympus to bestow this boon upon you.
Congratulations Ben.
I was, I was going to say, you talk about like, no one would pay attention
if there weren't like, it's like, you have like 100,000 eyes on you.
But I guess, I guess the YouTube audience is not necessarily
the comic book Kickstarter backing audience.
Certainly not.
Yeah.
Like if you, if you look at our Twitter accounts, our Twitter followers,
Twitter followers, you are like in the thousands and we have like 500,
which is fine.
Like I'm not complaining or anything, but yeah, yeah, it was, it was this,
is this reaching out to you was both a business decision.
And like, I feel like having someone who's done Kickstarter's and,
you know, does have a pretty good audience would be good for the comic.
And also it was like, I think Ben is really cool and I want to work with him.
And I think I want to get his comic in front of as many people as possible.
And then I reached out to Gibb too later on.
And I was like, I think the Lord of Ghosts is a fucking awesome comic.
And if I could, Lord of Ghosts is too long to be in the anthology,
but if we could figure out a way to make it work, I wanted it.
And we luckily were able to.
Yeah, it's a very small slice, but it's it's a nice one.
Oh, oh, fuck, my headphones are about to die.
And wait, no, they won't die though.
I can prevent it. I can prevent it this time.
When you told me that you were doing a.
Well, I like the idea of like a of like a community project.
I like the idea of a project that many different people contribute to.
So I thought it was neat just and when you told me that like,
yes, you know, we're looking to we're looking to pay the artists that contribute.
I was like, oh, OK, they're not just these these guys aren't fucking around.
Is this serious? This is a professional endeavor.
They have a professional attitude about it.
So all the ingredients are there for a success, in my opinion.
So I was like, OK, yeah, I'll work with these guys.
This seems good.
Yeah, I mean, the last thing I wanted this to come across was like a grift or something,
which is why I was like really adamant about the fact that every
single person involved has the rights to their comic.
You know, we just want like we the contract states that we could like republish it.
That's only because, you know, if we want to do more anthologies,
if we want to reprint the first anthology that we not we want that as an option.
But like I have no interest.
I don't even want like soul publishing rights.
Like I hope Lord of Ghost gets its own book.
I hope you do that, Gibb, on Kickstarter that, you know,
and I wouldn't I didn't want to do anything to impede that.
And likewise for anyone else in the anthology,
I never wanted to own anyone's comics.
I wanted to pay them to get their story done because, you know,
frankly, for the past two years, I've been trying to find anthologies
that I could submit to and there are not many and there tend to be super specific,
which is another thing about ours, which is that like we did maybe in the future,
there's going to be themes like, you know, we want comics around this idea
or around this aesthetic right now.
It was really just about like submit whatever you want.
If it's good, we want it because, you know, I don't want I don't want a small crew.
I want to I want to empower as as many creatives and artists and writers
as I possibly could.
I am looking at the Kickstarter.
I am looking.
It is.
Damn, that first day, that first day was a was a roller coaster.
It's leveled off a little bit right now.
This is this is how mine went to all.
I think all Kickstarter's do this.
They have a they have a good first day, then they slow down for a while.
And then and then, you know, you promote it where you can.
Sometimes you get some new eyes on it.
You get some new you get some new support there.
And then you have another big push at the end.
And that's when you hope that all the people that were like on the fence before
come back and go, ah, FOMO, if I don't submit that, if I don't pledge now,
I'll never get to I have to do it.
You got me by the balls.
And that's when you.
Yeah. Yeah.
I have been worried that we might be a bit of a hot start.
And then this is sort of the the height of it minus, you know,
give or take a hundred or whatever.
I honestly don't know how how it will go or what I hope I hope.
I mean, I hope that maybe some people who had not checked it out before,
because I've mentioned it on the show a bunch of times,
but I hope maybe a few more people from listening to this will take a look at it.
Obviously, the link will be in the description.
And I don't just keep plugging it.
Just keep keep keep yelling about it.
You know, be obnoxious. It's fine.
Yeah, I will say that we don't want to give out the number just yet
because it's it's very used, depending on, you know, how many people of a certain
tier or whatever.
But we do have a stretch goal in mind that is if we hit this number,
we will get to work on the second volume now and, you know,
send out another calling card for artists to submit their comics.
So I do, you know, this is this is something you would just go right into.
You would just go right to volume two.
If we if we got a certain number, which I will say is a pretty high number,
because the fact of the matter is this took, you know, like we started six months ago,
it took maybe two the last two or three months of like strong effort.
We barely uploaded to the channel or anything.
It was a long time of just solely focusing on this and not to mention
because I wanted it to be that even if the Kickstarter failed, everyone got paid.
This cost a lot of upfront money.
So it was it's definitely not something I could just
continue to do unless this one is pretty successful, which, you know,
I'm not trying to guilt or anyone, but if you're someone who makes comics
and we've got a couple of messages like this, like, hey, this is just a bad time
or hey, I heard about this too late.
This is something I want to do a lot of.
So if that's something that interests you, if you want to just support
anthologies like this in the future or, you know, purely greedy,
greed wise, you want to support it so you get another chance in the future.
That is something worth considering.
That one, that's the one.
You've got to be kind of cool, cool, cool.
Well, I mean, I'm really glad to see that it's it's it's that it's funded
one one way or another.
It is funded now, so it's it's real.
It's happening.
Congratulations.
A book.
And I'm going to get one.
I'm going to put it next to the Vapors.
And I really like physical comics.
Part of me.
I almost I almost was like, I almost sent you a message like, hey,
I get a free one, right?
But then I was like, no, no, Ben, don't be a bitch.
And I back.
You know, I did.
I did message zero right after you had pledged.
I was like, I wonder if we could scam Ben Singh, because he does get a free one.
But I mean, he just pledged, does he need two books?
Why would he want? No, it's.
Fuck it. No, fuck it.
No, no, I kind of I half the reason I backed was just so I could take a
screenshot of it saying you're a backer and tweet it just to prove
just to just to put my money where my mouth was.
I mean, that's a tax write-off right there.
That's marketing.
That's that I couldn't afford not to.
Base base.
Uh, yeah.
All right.
That's all good shit.
Anything else to say about that?
Or should we like, should I complain about being homeless more?
Well, I'd love to hear about your homelessness a little more.
I did want to. I'm scared.
I'm scared of the elements.
I'm going to freeze. I'm going to starve.
I'm going to die.
I did want to at least mention this just because it's been something
I've been thinking a lot about recently is that recently the author
or the monk of Berserk died.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Yeah, I was going to bring this up as well.
Miura, right?
Kentaro Miura. Yeah.
Yeah, I had read like the first, you know, I've read the what is it
called the eclipse arc?
Is that what the first part is called?
No, I think it's the Black Knight, the dark.
The very first part of the Black Swordsman.
The very first part is its guts going around with his big sword
and he kills few demons.
Then there's the guts going around the flashback to the thing
that leads up to the eclipse.
The eclipse, the eclipse, I swear, like the beginning of Berserk
up until spoilers, Griffith.
Yeah, I mean, that's the god hand that is the eclipse arc,
but it takes a very long time.
It doesn't feel like the beginning of the comic.
OK, there's a lot of changes.
Yeah, but like it goes on and on after that,
because I have not read further than that.
I read like the next chapter couple cut the little next like
mini arc after that and then I fell off.
So I wasn't like a regular.
I wasn't like keeping up with Berserk or anything,
but I did really appreciate that that first bid.
It's very, very sad that he died before it completed.
He was a fantastic artist, you know, like he was insane.
Like just even even if you don't watch the series,
just looking at any manga panel from Berserk is like this looks insane.
It looks like this is probably took him a month to do this one panel.
It is something that can be appreciated by anyone.
He's he's the quality and quantity boy.
He had like so many.
I mean, you should definitely reread all of Berserk.
Well, yeah, you should read all of Berserk
because it's not going to be continued and then reread it again.
And then reread it again
because there is a lot of really, really incredible
like mind shattering stuff that is like stuck with me forever
beyond the eclipse.
There's just like, oh, wow, wow, Pog, you know, it's like a Pog manga.
You read it and you just can't help saying you're saying
that it's a manga filled with with real with real life Pogger's moments.
Yeah, for sure.
It's very good. It's really good.
It's not really much other than like
to say that it's like extremely accurately illustrated.
Like he's he's really good at drawing people.
He's really good at drawing expressions, action,
like like horses, armies, landscapes, buildings, like everything.
He's just good at everything.
And it all is incredible to look at.
And it's so much of it.
The boy worked incredibly, like incredibly hard.
And it's really sad that he wanted he's he's he's dead.
It's so young, fifty four years old.
Right.
One of the things I want to talk about was that I, for my understanding,
and this could be wrong, so take with a grain of salt,
I did hear that this is like a stress induced illness.
And to me, that is utterly tragic.
I mean, he did work a lot from what I read,
from what I pieced together.
He seemed like kind of a recluse and was constantly working.
Not that that's too different from, you know, any other given manga author in Japan.
They work extremely long hours and they have very few breaks.
And that's just the culture.
And that's just how it is.
It's just what you got to do.
And yeah, I wouldn't I would not be surprised to learn that his lifestyle
and his speed at which he made all the stuff contributed to his death,
which is really fucked up and sad.
But didn't he he he was slow, right?
I thought people complained about him going on hiatus all the time.
Yeah, missing weeks.
Am I confused?
They they did because he he did take months off
probably because he was working so hard when he was doing it and he needed breaks.
And people would constantly tell him, you've got to not take breaks anymore.
And he's like, OK.
That's one of the things I mean, I'm I'm sure we can all relate to this
is that like even when you're doing no work,
if the if the expectation is that you should be working a lot harder,
doing no work is still fucking stressful.
You know, like taking a day off sometimes is the most stressful thing I could do.
Yeah, I feel that all the time.
I it's yeah, what is stress over not working?
I mean, it's like the theme song says I'm supposed to be working right now.
You all know you all know what I'm talking about.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, he wasn't a procrastinator.
He was when he was working on the the things
it makes sense why they take so long.
I feel like earlier on in his career,
he would be like a beast of a human being
churning out panels that look that good at a like a consistent schedule,
like how the fuck and the fact that he slowed down is like, OK, well, he is human.
He needs he needs to take breaks.
And here's what I don't get about the manga industry is why.
So there's been a lot of talk recently about like should
Shonen Jump switch to a bi weekly model instead of weekly,
you know, giving all their artists a little more leeway and their deadlines and stuff.
My question is instead of doing that, why not just have bigger teams?
You know, like it feels like Japan has such this culture of a tour ship that
and I and I get it, right?
Like I understand why being the sole creator of Berserk or being, you know,
Togashi and being the one guy who does.
I mean, I'm sure they have assistance, but it seems like not.
It seems like a lot of focus is put on the work that they do individually.
It just feels like with all this money, I mean, I guess I don't know.
It seems like they would make a decent amount of money with with all the infrastructure in place.
Why not just instead of doing bi weekly, just have twice as many people working on it?
You know, I'm not sure.
I think I wouldn't really know because it would not.
It wouldn't necessarily depend on like the the artists themselves,
whether they want a team or not.
They usually they definitely have assistance for things.
Not not every artist works with assistance and not every production could necessarily be
sped up just by like, you know, increasing the amount of people working on it.
I think I say every every every man is different.
Right. I mean,
certainly at least kind of it could because right, I mean,
I mean, some some people just work solo.
The neighbor industry of this being anime.
I mean, every anime has I mean, anime still has its crunch problems,
but like every anime has like 20 plus people working on it at least, right?
Fuck, I don't know.
Well, I guess my point is just that I feel like the reason why some manga,
mangaka or solo has more to do with culture and just like sort of a bad mindset.
Oh, you know, my opinion, bad, a bad mindset.
I think I think it is dangerous to be so focused on the individual.
And I think, you know, I OK.
But I mean, most I think most like serialized manga are not solo.
Like I think most of them do have assistance, but not all of them.
Like at least at least one.
Do you watch do you watch Mon?
Do you guys watch Mon Ben?
You know, the Mon Ben now?
Oh, God, Naoki.
Oh, what's the fucking Urisawa?
Uris, Uris.
Oh, my God.
Wait, I posted a link.
I posted a link
in my server before it's the guy Naoki.
Naoki Urisawa.
Yeah, Mon Ben with Naoki Urisawa,
the show where he interviews manga people and films them working.
One of the two episodes that you probably didn't see.
There's one where the guy he's interviewing is like he draws
like he draws animals like he loves drawing animals.
And the series he's working on is about like human animal hybrids
fighting each other.
And he draws like very naturalistically and he draws very naturalistic
like backgrounds and like natural environments and stuff.
And that guy is like some kind of weird prodigy and he works completely solo.
But he's like the only one.
Every other one has like a team of people that they work with,
either in like an office where they're all in there together
or some of they just some of them just ship it off to to people
to do like processing and stuff on it.
So I guess most of them do, you know, split up the workload like that.
This is speculation.
And I guess I just worry that someone like, you know,
Mira and someone like particularly Togashi, because I think Togashi has stated
that he tries to limit his assistance.
I worry that people like that are putting so much pressure on themselves
to be the guy, to be like, I'm the one who does this manga.
I do every panel.
I do everything but the backgrounds or whatever.
I think they put so much pressure on themselves to do that.
And again, just speculation that I could easily see how that stress can overwhelm
and turn into, you know, in the worst scenarios, severe illness.
And in the best scenarios, just an unhealthy lifestyle.
It's it's silly.
I mean, fucking Quentin Tarantino is still thought of as like supervisionary man,
but he literally does not do everything in the production of a film.
Quentin reviews is seen as a visionary filmmaker, but we know that he has a team.
He has a script.
I am sorry.
You just said Quentin that I this is how fucked up I am.
Is that when you said Quentin, my mind goes to Quentin reviews and not Quentin Tarantino.
God, you you're you're a cursed being right now.
And it's awful.
But yeah, like you can you can be considered like a cool person
and still be not the sole creator.
I mean, I know a manga is different, but like having assistance to learn
that somebody has assistance does not devalue from them.
Or like that if if somebody writes and somebody draws, like, I don't know,
you don't need to.
I don't I don't actually know what the culture is in Japan,
whether it's like, oh, you're not cool unless you do it by yourself.
I feel like it's probably just normal and people have assistance.
I have just looked up Kintaro Mira.
He's had over the years, so not all not not necessarily at the same time.
He's had four assistants working on.
See, that's isn't like a pitifully small number.
Yeah, it's that's way too small at the moment.
They said that apparently they say Kintaro Mira's assistant,
like singular, posted something on social media saying they'll do their best,
which could imply that he's going to try and continue it or maybe not.
But the important thing is that it's one at the time he had one assistant.
That's just him and one other guy working on it.
Yeah, I think it's not enough.
It's not enough.
I don't want to speak to all of Japanese culture, because I don't know what the
fuck do I know?
You know, but I does feel like it might be just a distinctly Japanese thing,
because I don't, you know, you know, referring to Bakumon.
There's that whole arc.
This arc was so funny reading it for the first time, which is that, you know,
the main character has to go to the hospital and the editor is seen as a bad guy
for making him want to for telling him to take a break.
Like the whole fucking cast bands together, say, fuck you, editor.
This guy should be allowed to work himself to death in his hospital bed.
That's what I assume with the Japanese culture.
A fucking streak of like, yeah, it is good to work yourself to death to do art.
And like, no, it's not. You'll die.
What are you insane?
You can you can live a few extra years and get it done a little slower,
and it'll be fine. You don't need to do it now. I mean, yeah.
I don't know. I feel like there is a bit of a culture around that.
I'm maybe thinking incorrectly about after World War Two,
there was a lot of like a wave of humility hit Japan.
Like they just got nuked twice.
And so, like struggling and working hard,
even at the cost of one's own life is important for the restructuring of the nation.
I feel like that sentiment is carried over through generations.
And it's still sort of around where it's like your own personal well-being
is important, sure.
But really try to get the chapter released on time.
It's like, OK, I will do that.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
It just it seems like I don't know.
This is again, this is just speculation on my part.
It just seems like a pretty big issue.
And I hope that there is if if Mira's death has anything to do with
the lifestyle of being a normal mankaka in Japan, I just hope I doubt it will.
But I just hope something changes.
Yeah, I mean, the the reason why isn't isn't the reason why.
Oh, God, it's it's it's a bit of a I guess a chicken and egg problem, maybe.
About like is it the industry like the publishers like pushing them
to like work really hard in their chapter, or is it just that like the industry
is so competitive that the the artists have to compete with each other
to such a degree that like that does definitely seem to be.
Yeah, like they like they have to push themselves really hard,
or else someone else is just going to do it better.
And the magazines are just going to run whoever is is doing the best work.
Like I guess I guess I could whatever means it takes to do the work, you know.
Like you can't like you can't like regulate and say like, you know,
mangaka are not allowed to like spend more than like 40 hours a week drawing.
No, it's like they're going to do what they want to get it through.
Yeah, it's it's just like a cultural thing.
Like it's I assume it's it's more so that if somebody is pushing themselves too hard,
not as many people will try to stop them.
They'll just see is like, ah, damn, he's working hard and just move on with their own life.
Something interesting not in Japan, but in Korea is for this is only semi related
is that if you're playing a video game too long, at least I know this
for like League of Legends or something, if you're playing League of Legends
for too many hours, the game itself will send you a message which says like,
hey, you know, take a break, you know, go get some water, stand up.
Let's not I assume there is some wide epidemic problem of people in Korea
just being too addicted to video gaming that like it is now baked into the systems
to be like, you know, ease up a little bit.
So, you know, hey, maybe someone from Shonen Jump can just give
send everyone a text, say like, hey, ease up a little bit.
Why they work so hard?
They should learn from us Westerners how to be lazy.
It's so much better.
I agree.
You get to wake up late and be like,
but they make better manga just objectively make better manga than we do.
So, you know, what at what cost?
Yeah, but we've got a fucking Steven Universe.
How about that?
That's true.
That's they make better manga until mine comes out.
Yeah, they haven't read the Cato anthology yet.
So it's a flip in the script.
Flip in the script.
I would have won the Tezuka the Tezuka contest.
If only I had finished it like properly, like it had an ending.
I think they were turned off by how it didn't end properly.
And a curatorial on a red end, he was like, ah, there's no resolution
to the conflict, dislike.
They could tell you weren't working yourself to death.
And that's yeah, it reads in the comic that you took a break at some point.
I do like the the knowledge that they did look over the Clarissa comic.
Even even if it was briefly, they did look through all of them.
And if they saw mine and they were like, oh, OK.
Sammy and and the guy Hunter Hoda's eyes.
Toriyama's eyes, eye holes,
absorbed photons that bounced off of your work.
Yes. And H and H for Oda as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, not going to lie.
I feel like good connection there.
Just the knowledge.
Just the knowledge I wanted you to you.
Stimulate you stimulated their neurons.
You did it.
So what is Oda like exactly?
Yeah, tell us now that you have such a close connection with them.
What was it like basically?
What was it like to stimulate the?
What was it like to stimulate the neurons of the age here, Oda?
Oh, I was like looking into the end of one day.
It was like looking into the one piece itself.
I know all of the secrets now and I laughed.
Because that's what that's what Gold Roger did.
Excellent. Very good.
That's what he would have wanted.
That's what Oda would have wanted. God rest his soul.
Ben, you want to tell us about your homelessness now?
Well, there's not much to tell other than that.
I everyone in my house is moving out.
And I mean, I can't afford the place on my own.
So I just got to find a new fucking place to live.
And it's a.
It's probably going to mean I have to spend more money to live in a house.
And that makes me a little sad, but it is what it is.
I don't know. I guess I'll fucking have to get on Craigslist or something.
Is there a possibility to like to like get in another apartment
with a bunch of other people?
Well, I mean, I guess probably not to this degree.
This was a bit of a unique situation.
We had a bunch of people all come together and split the place.
And we had, I mean, you know, we had like six people living here,
which is more than I'm likely to.
Oh, my rent is probably going to double, honestly,
just because it's most houses don't fit as many people
into a smaller space as we did here.
But it's fine.
I'll just.
Oh, God, the the the housing market in Boston is a real nightmare.
It's bad both around.
Yeah, it's it's bad.
Both are you guys are from here, right?
Or one of you is.
No, both of Massachusetts.
You both are. Yeah, OK.
Yeah, there's nothing.
There's like nothing to find when it's not like September,
but then like when it's September and leases are up,
like everyone is looking and the competition is fierce.
So it's like you're always fucked.
Uh, uh, I kind of just haven't got to start squatting.
I have started squatting.
I have started squatting again.
I've been working out for a whole week now.
I feel so powerful that I could take on anything.
Even take on any landlord.
You could beat them to with an inch of their life
and then say, can I have this place or I'll kill you now?
And then they say, yes, now that I can.
I'm so fit now that I can sleep
on the anti homeless architecture benches
with like the spikes on them designed to keep me.
I haven't even I found out about this
maybe like two weeks ago or something.
And I just kind of have not thought about it that much.
I've just kind of been like,
well, I'll just think about something else
because it's it's two months away, which.
And I'm it doesn't feel like a long time.
It feels like no time at all.
And I'm like, oh, God, there's a clock on me.
But but but like I want to finish my fucking game.
I just want to finish my fucking game in peace.
How much how much left on the game?
Aren't you?
Didn't you a pretty solid version of it already?
I well, I released that.
I have I have been working on like I mentioned before,
I've been working on it, adding cut scenes,
which I didn't have very much of that stuff
in the initial demo.
And I have been really banging my head against it.
It's taken me a while to work through it.
So progress has been a little slow recently.
I feel like yeah, getting it done within two months
is not is should should probably be doable.
But it's hard to say because I won't know what's
I won't know what problems crop up until they do.
I don't know.
But but it's like, OK, should I should I know to the grindstone,
like really like grind out the rest of the game
and get it done really fast so that I can then focus
on looking for a new house?
Or is do I need to start looking for a new house now
so that, you know, maybe I'll have it'll take my attention
away from the game, but that'll mean that I can, you know,
go somewhere, not be homeless and be able to work on that
uninterrupted, even if my focus is off for a while.
These are the questions that I am grappling with at the moment.
Do you you don't have like a side job?
Do you you do this full time?
Yeah, I I do not I do not currently have any side gigs or anything,
which is why my which is why my uncommonly low rent
living situation was such an instrumental part of my setup.
And now I don't have it anymore.
So I got to deal with it.
I got to cope.
But I'm not going to see you about it.
I'm not going to see it, but I am going to cope.
That's the ticket.
I don't know. That's all I have to say about that.
Pray for me.
Will do.
Thank you.
Well, shit, anything else or should we go into voicemails?
Let's do it. Hear the voicemails.
OK, then let me let me find them.
Voicemail number one.
Let me pull it up here.
Message three, one, eight, five.
Yes, here it is. This is the first one.
It is called out, out, and there it is in general chat.
OK, so let's give this a listen in three, two, one, go.
This vaccine is fucking killing me.
Damn, I like just got a new job and now I have to call in sick,
even though I've only been with them for like three days.
And fuck, I'm going to I'm going to get fired
because I got the vaccine.
Damn, fired because you got the vaccine.
That's I do feel like this probably.
I think we've we've we've accepted that that's going to be OK.
I don't think your job will fuck you on that.
I feel I feel like they'll understand.
I'm this makes me nervous, though,
because I am getting my second dose in three days, I think.
Yeah, on the 26th, so I will be fully vaccinated by the time this episode comes out.
And I don't want to get sick, man.
Sucks, man.
So which which shot did you get the first time?
I got Pfizer. I got Pfizer.
Oh, the elite.
What is the center?
Is that the elite? I don't know.
You should be OK.
I was one of the unfortunate few who got Johnson and Johnson,
which did mean I only need one shot,
but also means that I'm now fucking bottom class.
Oh, you're a pro.
You're a pro.
That's Hufflepuff. I got that Moderna.
Very excellent pathetic.
Let me tell you, it did kill me.
Real a few hours after that second shot.
Really dead. Yeah.
God, no, I don't want to.
I don't want to be made to feel ill.
This is this is despicable.
This is a nightmare.
It can't be worse than the Twitter L.
So, you know, nothing's worse than it.
Nothing's worse than a Twitter L.
Oh, they're making fun of me.
Oh, they're making fun of me on Twitter.
They're still going.
Oh, they're having a fucking victory lap.
No.
Oh, this is the worst day of my entire life.
This is even worse.
This is even worse than the day when I get vaccinated.
Ben, Ben crying and diarrheaing from having a Twitter L
needs to be the title and thumbnail of this video.
OK, all right, shut up.
No.
Wait, was it was I was I talking about something
about getting a vaccine?
Oh, oh, yes, I was going to make a genius analogy.
Pfizer is team mystic.
Moderna is team Valor and and Johnson and Johnson is team
Big Bird team.
What's the other one?
Instinct. Yeah, it was instinct.
I literally forgot what it was.
Pfizer.
Pfizer is AstraZeneca, I think, right?
Oh, I don't.
Pfizer and AstraZeneca is like a joint, joint venture or something.
They is.
They're only now in the UK.
Are they are they vaccinating 35 year olds?
So soon, I guess I can get my first one.
Yes, I and I are both fully vaccinated because we're just that important.
Oh, no, I'm wrong.
No, it's Pfizer BioNTech is like the joint one.
And AstraZeneca is AstraZeneca was the one they took off the market
because it was given people like blood clots, right?
Oh, yeah, I think that was disputed.
It was it was made up.
Well, it wasn't made up.
It was just like like no evidence for there's no like causation,
like not enough data to suggest that was true.
It was just sort of like blood clots in people
that were the same as like normal unrelated blood clots.
Unrelated.
But people were scared because Europeans hate medicine, I guess.
It was just a bunch of stress induced mangaka, you know, just normal.
God, I can't believe it.
I got I got the Pfizer shot and then less than three weeks later,
I take my first L on Twitter.
It's it's not a coincidence.
It's a side effect.
There's correlation implies causation in my in my opinion.
Ben, you're impaired.
Next voicemail is called put it there.
What's it called? It's called I am coming.
Loud sound warning.
OK, three. Yeah.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm coming.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming. Where's he going with this fucking kneecaps?
You hear me?
I'm going with like ten nine elevens on your fucking kneecaps.
Your knees are going to bend so far back.
You're going to look like a goddamn singer.
No, no. Yeah, I hear you.
I hurt my head for the sake of this fucking joke.
Are you happy?
And I had to re-record this thing.
God damn guys, because I wasn't satisfied with it.
I hope you're pleased.
I am pleased. I am pleased.
You know, joke's not bad.
I don't know if it was worth the first four seconds.
I just don't know.
Well, what I I appreciate that he just went for it.
Yelled full volume.
There was no like, you know, whisper yelling.
Don't want my parents to wake up.
Bullshit.
So like that's refreshing.
So I mean, this guy lacks nothing in commitment, if anything.
So he has no shame.
He's he's going to go for it.
Next voicemail is called
Oof, addendum.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Excuse me, addendum.
I actually meant to say three weeks, not three days, but, you know,
still pretty bad to call in sick after three weeks.
I don't care.
I actually hope this thing just fucking kills me.
I hope it's population control, like all the righties say.
And we're all just going to like start dropping like flies pretty soon.
Because you know what?
Everything's going to get automated in like 15 years and like I live in America.
America is just going to like totally collapse.
Because the right wingers would like the idea of like a shot
that like kills the pain right now.
I'm like so sick of going to get fired from my job.
Sounds right up there.
Have to be an artist again.
No, you would you would think they would be like, you know,
they love they love Corona for its for its, you know,
less than one percent killer death rate, you know, it calls the week.
You would think they would love a shot that gives you blood clots
and, you know, gives you sends you into a anaphylactic shock
and kills you if you're allergic to stuff,
because it's going to it's going to fucking eugenics us into the moon.
It's going to it's going to make a stronger human race
free of our free of our weaknesses.
So I don't I don't get what the problem is.
It is I don't see the conflict that they think they they realize
they are weak and they would be scared of. Yeah.
That's what I was going to say is that these are the same people
that probably would be offed by that stuff.
Oh, I see. I see one for me and not for me.
Yeah, self-preservation trumps all ideals.
Naturally, we've we've cracked it.
We've cracked it.
Next voicemail is called
outdated description and thoughts.
And I am uploading it right there.
OK, three, two, one, go.
So I noticed that the description of the speak pipe page
is actually kind of outdated because it says that it's a show
where a bunch of content creators pick a topic and talk about it
until no one cares anymore.
But now it's just more like the content creators talk about whatever is on their
mind until you guys get bored and move on to voicemails.
True. So, you know, I just wanted to let you guys know that so you can like update it.
No, it also says that you guys take questions when I know for a fact
that you guys haven't done that in a long ass time.
We're doing it right now.
What do you? Your cloud doesn't matter.
You can literally ask for anyone you want on this podcast.
There have been plenty of people I know, whether it be interviewers or podcasters
who have gotten people way larger than them on the podcast just by asking.
It doesn't hurt to ask.
Even if they say no, have a nice day, guys.
You're right.
I know.
I saw today the lead singer from Eve Six was asking, was saying, like,
I will be on anyone's podcast.
And I'm like, that's funny.
That's cool. What if I asked the Eve?
What if I asked the Heart and a Blender song guy to be on the podcast?
But what do I want to talk to him for?
Yeah, what do I want to?
What do I have? What do I have to say to the heart and blender who he was?
I can't believe you've never heard the Heart and a Blender song.
Well, it's probably an American radio, I guess.
Maybe didn't make it.
I had a talking about.
You don't know.
You don't know Inside Out by Eve Six.
Maybe if I heard it, I don't think it's the one that goes like.
Faith, but how does it go?
And I found nothing but faith in nothing.
Want to put my tender heart and a blender.
Watch has been around to a beautiful oblivion.
Rendezvous and I'm through with you.
No, no.
I appreciate the commitment, but no, I had a camp when I was a little kid.
Then maybe not that little.
I had a counselor at camp who would sometimes he was a guitar guy.
He would pull out his guitar and sing camp songs.
And sometimes he would sing the Heart and a Blender song.
And that's where I know it from.
Also, it's just on the radio.
OK, whatever.
That guy's that guy's cool on Twitter, but I'm probably not going to ask him
on the podcast because like, why?
Even though he offered them out next voicemail.
Hold on a question, huh?
Do you guys do you guys get like?
Is it harder for you to do guest episodes like mentally?
Like, is it weird?
Is it uncomfortable?
I mean, I sometimes feel like I might, especially when I don't know
what the guest does as much as Ben does.
And I'm like, oh, God, what if I?
Right. What if I make it uncomfortable for them?
That's the only thing that really goes through my mind.
Like, I don't want them to feel weirded out.
That's what actually I was a little nervous because you didn't answer
when I was like PCP time for a while.
And I was like, I'm nervous to do a solo
Ben cast with two guests because how do I fucking entertain these freaks?
How do how do I be?
How do I be engaging when I'm outnumbered?
And the only way out of that situation was to take the Twitter out.
That's it was a tactical L. Exactly.
Yeah, that's still to get good.
That's exactly this.
This Twitter L.
This is arguably worse than the time that I got drunk
and kept asking the bartender at the bar and
where's my phone, where's my phone and made him hate me.
This is this is almost as embarrassing as that was.
And and and just like that, I'll never get over it.
And it will haunt me for the rest of my life.
Next voicemail is called Never Stood a Chance.
Three, two, one, go.
And now it may be a little bit late here, but.
That anime snob bros.
We fucking won.
Did you, bro, is dead?
Anime snob wins.
I was rooting for that anime snob the whole time.
You know, it was it was such an underdog first
people that commented on our video.
Yeah, I was just about to say that.
Wait, what?
The first recognized YouTuber or any
tuber to comment on our channel.
And he he was out.
He was out for us.
He did not like the video.
Wait, which which which video?
It was God, I don't remember.
It was a Code Geass video.
Was he the one that called us a fascist?
No, no.
No, no, that was someone else on the same video.
Although, I guess I guess if you're defending,
if you're if you're like if you're pro,
if you're pro, if you're pro gay, I could see why.
Maybe you're like, that's a little fasc, right?
Because it's kind of a fast show, right?
Like the protagonist is kind of like I haven't actually seen it.
I don't I only know by reputation.
I'm not going to call it a fascist.
That's that's obviously that's harsh language.
But it deals with that.
It deals with like an authoritarian government or whatever.
Right. It's it's like imperial for sure. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, if you think about it like really,
I mean, all the chosen one shows, they're all fasc.
I mean, I'm just hotter.
I'm just I was really funny.
No, it would be really funny if he called you a fascist,
if you made like a Dragon Ball Z show or something.
But when it's when it's like a show
that's specifically about politics,
it's like, OK, I get why it would come up.
Yeah. Yeah.
If he called me a fascist on my Dragon Ball Super video,
that would take personally.
Yeah, yeah.
The the Kaiser or I don't know, colonists or something.
I don't know.
I always thought that is a great honor.
And I think anime snob every day for blessing us
with his fucking dumb, useless comment.
We we after that, we really started seeing the algorithm.
We stand that anime snob.
And his he's Greek, right?
He's Greek.
I think he's weird Greek accent.
And his and his and I don't know.
That guy's that guy's funny.
Is he is he doing good?
Is his channel is his channel blown up?
Is it? No. No. OK.
I mean, I don't know.
But the answer is no.
I mean, I was guaranteed.
I thought so. All right.
Sabotrave. OK.
Next voicemail.
Oh, I uploaded these out of order.
Why did why did I do that?
The next voicemail is called.
Wait, I think that one was actually called
Never Stood a Chance and this one is called The Prophecy is True.
Whoops. Three, two, one, go.
Women who would give attention,
bitchy attention to certain guys doesn't make sense.
So my fantasy of a bitch would be one who somehow needs some skill that I have.
She like hates the world, but she has to make YouTube videos
proclaiming it and she needs someone to edit them.
And so, you know, like, and she can only pick you who she hates.
And are you saying that if Digi was a girl, he'd be your waifu?
Yeah.
Unbelievable. OK.
That's that's a little second for me to realize it was a clip.
I thought DeVoo had sent in a voice.
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
That's a good clip. Wow.
Yeah, what a pull. Wow.
You went deep for that one.
I don't think I can say anything that would add.
I'm just just let it I'll just let it stand on its own.
Voice Grail.
It's just a clip from the PCP.
So, yeah, yeah, Voice Grail.
We'll put DeVoo in Voice Grail, Lamal.
Well, yeah, we'll put it.
Yeah, we'll put all of ourselves because, yeah, it's a group.
Grail default.
Next voicemail is called
Henlo Corgo to and there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, everyone.
And by everyone, I mean boring, probably give and maybe Tom.
So I see a lot of people on the PCP Reddit
and on your guys discord channels.
There's not a lot of people there.
Like asking to be made members of the PCP
and asking you to hold open auditions.
I don't think that happens.
That's never going to happen
because they're not showing enough initiative.
I officially declare myself the manager.
Producer, host, call yourself the producer,
the sole founder of the PCP.
So I found I did it.
It's my show.
Well, you're the boss.
No one else.
I'll be in charge of screening voicemails from now on.
And I'll see you guys next week for the recording.
You should have said you're all well.
You have a PCP.
The idea of a PCP tryout is hilarious to me.
Like what even is what the fuck is a podcast?
He he doesn't understand now that he's our boss.
He needs us.
You know, we have the power.
We can strike.
We can strike and bankrupt him.
The thing is now that he's the soul, he's the owner of the PCP.
But the PCP has jokes on you.
We're losing money.
It's a it's a white elephant.
We're an albatross around your neck.
All our debts are now your debts.
You're fine.
The stock is plummeting.
Elon Tweet is ruining the PCP.
Elon, no, he declares himself boss.
He declares himself.
He declares himself boss of the PCP only for Elon to see the epic L
that Ben St. just took on Twitter and say, man, the PCP is so cringe
and our fucking stock price plummet.
Thanks, Elon.
Next voicemail is called
where is it? Not an incel.
OK. There we go.
No, wait, it's uploading.
There we go.
There it is. OK. Not an incel.
Three, two, one, go.
Considering these facts, am I still an incel?
Yes, opinion doesn't matter.
I am a sociable person who in no way has problems talking to women.
I do not hate three DPD women and only like two D girls
who lack the agency to question my masculinity and hurt my feefies.
I have had sex multiple times.
These are spliced together.
Recently, yeah, I have aspirations to do so again.
As a matter of fact, I have a girlfriend.
This is Kiwi Founds Hero.
I am not a fat neck.
Straight as a board.
We'll never go trans exercise and practice decent hygiene.
I do not feel entitled for any games to be made to my or anyone else's tastes.
I only ask that I be able to voice my opinion.
I support myself financially and do not leech off my parents.
I forget the context of this.
I am not angry at the world for any perceived injustices.
I think it's about people asking for peace.
It's about Tifa's boobs. It's the video about Tifa's boobs.
By all these metrics, I'm pretty sure I'm not a total loser.
And yet I don't make a difference.
I said we're making this argument.
I am an incel in many people's eyes.
And no one else is saying it will change anything.
Well, I'm not asking anyone to agree with me.
And I feel that I understand the other side's point.
I simply think it would be.
That sucks.
One of my favorite things about Nate is how like it's the funniest things.
He gets so weird on like tight definitions of like abstract concepts.
There was one episode.
There was one episode where he was like arguing like on a scale of how how
cucked are you if your girlfriend uploads a bikini picture?
How?
Wait, was that that is the sort of philosophical discourse that I'm interested in?
Was that a PCP or was that in a I think it was a PCP.
I think it was a PCP.
Oh, no, I do remember that.
I do remember that.
It's all about consent. It's all about consent.
OK, well, but cucks consent, cucks and.
Oh, yeah, no, you're oh, no, yeah, you're right.
Oh, shit. No, you're right.
Fuck. OK, never mind, never mind.
I don't like I don't like this voicemail because it wasn't like clipped to make a point.
It was just like a minute and 20 seconds of Nate saying some kind of maybe cringy, funny stuff.
Am I crazy or was it edited to like be a little it seemed like I don't know the context.
Why did it just cut off at the end?
I think seemingly in the middle of a word, because he's still going.
I think it was just like one of those videos.
It was it was from the teeth.
It was from the video.
It was from the video where he complains about Tifa's boobs being shrunk.
Bad, bad video, by the way, bad video that I don't agree with.
But I'm not sure if it was spliced together.
I'm I'm left I'm left struggling.
I'm left grasping for some like what was the point?
Like what was like the punchline?
What was the what message was intended to be conveyed here?
I don't know. Do better.
No, I like it. Good job.
You did well.
That has the Cato seal of approval.
Oh, my God. Good voicemail.
Well, got what? Wow. Wow.
Your standards are really low.
I'll bet your anthology is going to suck at.
This is your taste in voicemails.
I can only imagine.
Yada, yada.
Next voicemail is called.
I can't read it.
It's like a square.
It's like the character is not just it's an emoji or something.
Three, two, one, go.
Guys, I haven't watched in a year and I don't know what's going on.
Can somebody tell me what's going on?
I know it's too.
Can somebody walk me through step by step?
Everything that's happened on the PCV last year.
It's too complicated.
Guys, I'm a big doodoo baby.
Hey, can somebody tell me guys?
You will never know.
You will be you will wander in darkness.
Well, I do think people like that are funny and to be made fun of.
Have you guys ever considered doing a state of the PCP type thing?
Well, what would be the point?
I mean, I think all of the things are in the episodes.
Yeah, yeah.
But I mean, that's a lot to that's a lot to watch.
Just watch every episode. You'll get it.
Yeah, just watch all episodes.
Subscribe to what you know, it's not it's not a terrible.
It's actually not a terrible idea.
Hmm. The biggest thing I would say is I mean, a lot of the stuff seems obvious.
Stuff I've like inferred.
But, you know, it seems like for a long time, the PCP had a very specific
like end goal of being this, you know, the PCV HQ and all that stuff,
mostly being spearheaded by Nate and Tricks and whatnot.
So I think with that seemingly not in the picture anymore,
just an idea of like, what is this channel?
And like, what is it?
Is it just podcasts are now on?
Is there any plans for it to be something else?
I thought I think would be interesting, even if the answer is no.
I, you know, you make a good point.
I guess my only thing about that is that I'm not really I feel like
I don't know what the plan is, like, like the plan in the interim
is just keep making the show with, you know, the couple people that still show up,
which is fine.
Yeah, I feel like, you know, on the one hand,
yeah, like we could explain what's going on because a lot has happened.
But on the other hand, like who, I don't know, do a lot of people,
like is there a lot to even explain?
Like, is it really do people need an explanation?
I think I'm people like, and I've noticed this among a lot of creators,
is that they do not consider how much people like inside baseball talk.
I think audiences love behind the scenes, like not even like necessarily juicy drama,
just like, hey, you know, this is the stats behind our latest videos.
And that's why we're doing this or, you know, et cetera.
If people knew that I was editing videos on a titty mousepad, they would lose their minds.
It's true.
I mean, I'm kind of the same as Ben.
I don't exactly know what the future holds.
I'm mostly just thinking of my own projects and then just I'll be on the PCP.
Why not?
It's it's not really like a like to make a declarative statement.
Like, yes, the future is cold, dead and empty.
There is no future for the PCP.
We're just going to do a podcast now.
I feel like, I don't know.
People already inferred from the gravestones that we have.
Here's a question I have that I'm sure a lot of people probably have,
which is that, like, is there any future with radcons?
Like, is there ever going to be a radcon?
I think so. I think I think radcon could happen.
I don't know who I would I feel like it's it could, too.
Yeah. I mean, there would be no Trixie.
I feel like probably no Jesse, probably no Munchie.
But other than that, I mean, me, you, Tom, Nate.
Shit, is there anyone else?
Am I forgetting anyone?
There wouldn't be any DeVoo or Mage, but they never came.
Well, to one.
Yeah, true.
So.
I don't know. Yeah, I feel like, yes, I feel like, yeah,
there could be another radcon and there probably will be.
And it'll be different from the other ones.
But, you know, honestly,
personally, I know Ben probably wouldn't want Trixie back.
But like, absolutely not.
After after an apology, I could I could see it happening,
but probably not for a while.
Oh, if if if we got an apology and I thought it was sincere,
I would consider it, but we will never get one.
So as far as I'm concerned, that's not an option worth considering.
If that happens, yeah, OK, that's reasonable.
But no, but let's let no.
I guess next voicemail.
We there put it there.
Pirate leg Pete. OK.
Three, two, one, go.
You are me hard days.
This be pirate leg Pete, and I am not a pirate.
But me leggings on me legs.
Many a journey across the seven open seas.
We have spent countless hours listening to your landlub and podcast.
And in that time, but one thing has become clear to old Pete and his pirate leg.
And that is that Nate has the most succulent of boy.
Yeah, another one of these.
You're hard.
We be the crew of Nate fuckers.
And we will take his back for the lead.
We will dig into it like so many very treasured.
Also, fucky Ben St.
Return the pirate's girl.
God.
Crossing the street.
I keep I keep finding out about all these new scrolls I have.
And it's just exciting every day.
They messed up. They should have said pirate booty.
My collection is growing apparently.
Pirate booty. Yeah.
No, no, I mean, like in relation to the the Nate fucking, they didn't say booty.
This is a Nate fucker and a scroll hunter.
And there's a lot going on in a scroll.
There's potential there needs to be cleaned up.
It should be a map instead of a scroll.
Not after taking that L after taking that L.
I just don't have room in my heart for this for this right now.
We got to move on.
Next voicemail is called a fuck.
What's it called?
SF2 is based again, not that one.
OK, three, two, one is correct.
As SF2 Street Fighter two.
Yeah, three, two, one, go.
It was Saga Frontier to Saga Frontier to pay attention.
Ben, OK, also try not to get softlocked at the egg fight.
OK, when they said Street Fighter two, not that one.
I thought or rather SF2, not that one.
I thought it was just a joke about how many Street Fighter twos there are.
No, this was I don't know if you listen to the last episode,
but no, there was some guy called into opine about how Saga Frontier is based.
And I think I remember I think I was not impressed.
I think I remember I like looked up and thought it was ugly or something.
Next voicemail is called Horse Throat.
Nice. I'll put it right there.
There it is. OK, three, two, one, go.
Ben St. Jesus.
I have the files of the growing lecture,
and I want to give you to them if you meet my three demands.
Number one, you must change your name from Ben St.
to Ben St. to a leaning.
Number two, you must cancel.
Best guy ever.
This shouldn't be hard to do.
There are dozens of cancelable moments on this very channel.
And lastly, number three,
you must invite Si to the podcast.
That's why, why we should have Si on
and they come upon that number of PCP.
We should have Si on the piece of news in the next 13 days.
I'll just leave the brownie lecture.
What was the second one?
Cancel date, I think. OK, done.
I was going to I was going to do that anyway.
It was the first one.
Change your name to Ben, something I didn't catch it.
Yeah, I couldn't I couldn't get what you wanted.
Something Saint Ben St.
On a technical note, that guy's voice modular was too deep.
You got it. Don't do that next time.
It's too hard.
It was a force through.
I'll do two out of three.
I'll I'll do I will cancel name and I will invite Si on the podcast.
So that's take take it or leave it.
I got I got a I got to update.
I got to do an update on the state of the Twitter L right now.
I got I got to explain what's going on with it
because they're a development.
The current state of the Twitter L is, you know, I had to walk it.
I had to walk it back and be like, wow, OK, I guess you did send it.
And and, you know,
Riley has taken a big victory lap retweeting all these all these people.
All these weird Trixie simps that like called me mean
for like saying that she she deleted our content and stuff.
And and Riley, the story is like, haha.
Wait, wait, I'll literally really said because it's very because it's very weird.
He said like Trixie didn't send the the the stuff.
Trixie didn't send the the the the things because you asked her to.
He says that like a fan contacted him
and asked him to get Trixie to send the stuff.
And that's why she did it.
So it's not because I asked and it's not because Gibb asked,
which we again, we were asking for months and months.
It's because someone got Riley to tell Trixie to send it.
And that's what made her send it.
Doesn't it look worse?
Yes, in my opinion, it's very embarrassing.
But but this is this is what Riley is having his fucking victory lap over.
And I. I just I just don't know how to.
I don't know how to respond.
I don't know how to respond to this.
And so I will not.
Anyway, that's the state of the L.
Fuck fuck us.
Fuck a state of the PCP video.
We got to make a state of the L every every every day for the rest of the week.
You say one on the podcast permanent fixture.
State of the L. All right, here's here's the fallout
from that time that I said something wrong on Twitter and got made fun of.
It's like it spawns a whole the whole diaspora
of responses that ripple throughout the time stream.
Anyway, next voicemail is called.
I'll post it right here.
It is called.
That's base joker nine.
So get get ready.
We got some shit coming up.
OK, base joker nine, three, two, one, go.
Yeah, the studio.
More like.
Yeah, Pudio.
I mean, not the best one.
Not the best one.
There was only one.
There's only one layer to that one.
Yeah, I know.
I wanted more.
The best base jokers are when there is multiple things
you could think it could be.
Yeah, the base joker set the bar really high for these puns,
because a lot of them were very clever and like worked in multiple ways.
This was just normal.
I feel like the setup on the better ones is a little longer.
You know, it's maybe like an idiom instead of just like a small phrase,
you know, this one was just a little too quick for me.
The the the good ones have like multiple parts, like, you know,
waiting, waiting for the poo to plop is is not just
it's not just that shoe sounds like poo.
It's that it's the two words in the same phrase were like both were both
transformed in a way that worked and and changed the meaning of the
of the phrase to match.
So this is my in-depth dissection of why this shit pun didn't work.
This analysis would have skyrocketed way more than the Winnie the Pooh stuff.
I'm just telling you, that's your new series.
I'll finish that Winnie the Pooh series.
I'll finish I'll finish reviewing season one of Winnie the New Adventures
of Winnie the Pooh one of these days.
Surely someone online is doing poop joke analysis.
Winnie the Pooh, more like Winnie the Diarrhea.
More like Winnie the Stress Diarrhea from taking an L on Twitter.
Hey, oh, uh, shut up.
Shut up.
You're all fucking critics.
You.
Have you?
Have you been seeing?
There's been some things going around on Twitter where someone has been
doing like three Stooges bits, but they're bits about like.
Zoomer phrases like suss, like, hey, hey, hey, Moe, you're looking.
Hey, Moe, you're looking a little suss.
Suss? What do you mean suss?
What are you knuckleheads talking about?
Hey, yeah, Larry, I think we got ourselves an imposter.
I'm just, I love these and I just wanted to let you know how I feel about them.
OK, thank you for sharing.
You're you're welcome.
OK, next one is called there it is.
It is called cross aspect ratio preference three to one go.
What aspect ratio do you think looks the best in why one?
I think I like one.
Not one, one, just one.
Like it. There is no second dimension.
I think I think I like I think I like the old CRT three to four.
Like widescreen is fine.
There came a point in my life when I realized that like old three to four
ratio had been like completely supplanted by widescreen.
And I was like, huh, OK, but why?
I I don't I don't really prefer it.
I don't really know why it seems to have become the dominant thing.
Like whatever, I don't hate it, but I don't get it.
I think three by four is good.
I'm a bit of a zoomer, so 16 by nine is is pretty comfortable for me.
There was a great video by Captain Disillusion about aspect ratio
and it goes into how it works, but also what what works in widescreen
and four by three and like for what purpose and, you know, with phones now.
It's like two to one, but like vertically.
And it's like there's lots of different things
because like human beings, we see things
because the land is like pretty horizontal.
You go outside and outside shots work well in widescreen,
but more personal shots work well in four by three
because you need you don't need to see
so much of a person to the side of them.
A person is like vertical.
There's a good.
Yeah, I'm just just, you know, is this pros and cons to both?
I don't really know what I prefer.
I, I, I, I, you know, maybe it's just because I grew up with three, three to four.
Maybe maybe I'm just nostalgic.
I don't know. I don't think. Yeah.
I do wonder if the next generation of people
will have a wildly different preferred aspect ratio because, like you said,
you grew up on one thing, I grew up on 16 by nine.
And then weird thing now is, you know,
so many people are just not only watching stuff on their phone,
but like webtoons whole platform is like scrolling vertically.
And yeah, I can't get used to reading comments like that.
I like the pages that you turn.
The scrolling is the scrolling is because it's what's the word?
Like it's it does that because it's on a phone, right?
Like scrolling webtoons is like it's a format designed to be read on a phone.
I mean, I don't see why the aspect ratio would need to change,
but like it did once.
So I guess it could change again.
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, what do you what do you think it would get longer?
Yeah, I guess I it's weird to think about,
but I guess you would probably say the same thing 20 years ago.
Yeah, I don't. Yeah, I don't really see why it needed to get longer.
But it did. And I don't know, whatever.
It'll morph to whatever the viewer base is watching things on.
Since phones are like thin, they can hold them horizontally
or they can hold them vertically, which is much more comfortable in the hand.
And so like tiktoks and vines and other mobile app videos are all tall.
So would it be fair to say that like the
the shape of the shape of like our media has changed
literally just because a phone needs to be a certain length
to reach from your ear to your mouth.
So you're interesting.
Yeah. So it's like that's why it's long.
Like that's why the screen is elongated.
Yeah, it can't just be a square.
Yeah, ergonomically, it's also like you could have a square phone,
but it would be weird to hold in your hand.
Yeah, that's that's what I mean.
It's easier to hold it the long way with your fingers.
And so it stretches from your ear.
Yeah, like imagine if your phone were just a big square,
you just have your whole like hand around the square and it's like a handle
on the back of it so you can lift it up to your face like an iron.
You hold it like an iron.
Yeah, like you're branding yourself with a maybe, I don't know.
I mean, I guess maybe if it were square,
you could have like you could hold it diagonally.
So like the speaker is on like one corner and like the mouth,
the receiver is on the other corner and you kind of hold it diagonally
between your ear and your that sounds so that I could imagine
that would be annoying to hold with a with a human hand.
Maybe aliens would have different aspect ratios.
And I guess you would have to you could have like your one finger
on top of the one side and then your pinky on the other side
and your thumb on the other you could have.
Yeah, that's awkward.
I think about what a duck like aspect ratio would be
because they have eyes on the side of their head.
A screen would need to be like a semicircle or like I don't think this one.
Go ahead.
Oh, no, I was done.
A duck wouldn't have to make a phone call.
Who knows?
I don't think this will happen, but there is at least a small possibility
that aspect ratio will change because of VR,
in which case you're being like transplanted into the media of choice
in which in like there is no screen.
I mean, VR is never going to supplant
just, you know, traditional screen media.
I find myself agreeing, but I do.
I mean, predicting the future is pretty hard.
I guess so.
I mean, that would just mean that like the normal
if that if that became the norm, then like normal screen
resolution would be, I don't know what the fucking
it'd be like goggle, goggle shape or whatever.
Right. I don't know.
I don't see it happening.
But maybe.
Yeah, that's not even like.
Honestly, I don't know enough about how VR works to even talk about it.
So let's go to the next voicemail.
And it is called OK.
The next one is called Gibbs centralism three to one go.
Gibbs, the Middle East would be had you for being trans.
Why do you defend people who are more neo-Nazis and the neo-Nazis are?
I defend people who get blown up for no reason.
That's that's a pretty.
Yeah, pretty obvious decision to come to.
I.
I understand this point.
Because like, I know Hamas is a like fundamentalists.
Or I mean, I've heard.
I don't really know anything.
But I've heard that Hamas is a fundamentalist Islamic organization.
Yes, a terrorist organization.
But it is not representative of the children that are being killed.
You know, like Palestinians are not Hamas.
So Palestinians are not Hamas.
OK, you know what?
I guess that's not really the point.
Maybe the culture in fucking Gaza or whatever, maybe they are, you know,
very Islamic, very traditional, kill gay people, kill trans people.
I mean, that could be the case.
That could be the case.
But it's still not it's still not a case for like genociding them, right?
Like the the the extrapolation from when you make this argument,
is is the end result like, oh, like, therefore,
because these people are homophobic, because these people are regressive,
we should just kill and displace them.
Is is that the argument?
Yeah, would you advocate for that?
I don't agree with that or anywhere else.
Like I wouldn't write a little extreme.
Should we should we fucking bomb people that are like that here in America?
These are some things you might want to ask yourself,
because we have that here, too.
Next voicemail is called.
Oh, wait, there's a there's an imager link.
So I guess I will I will link that here.
Images found for ClusterPunkHell Department of Machine Verification
Appointment 99th May 7 20 7 2 0 22.
Oh, there's like a whole bunch.
OK, well, it's two images.
I guess we'll show this on screen.
There's a like a DMV schedule and a DMV card with a number.
24096 tough luck kid PA system says,
please refrain from starting revolutions while our staff
sort through the punch card record for your nanomachines.
Followed by a cyborg.
This is this is Error Array, who is the the the the voice modulator
poem person, the the the submarine.
What was their name for that stuff?
I don't even remember what it was called.
I don't even know how to how to refer to it, but hopefully you know what I mean.
This is this all started with the bear, right?
This all started for the bear for the bear, right?
And there's and there's Error Array and there's the bear.
OK, OK, context achieved voicemail.
Let us listen three, two, one, go.
There's so it guzzling bottom feeders over at the DMV.
They've confiscated our submarine, which means dealing with bureaucracy.
Who wants to stand in line and waste away when the office only opens three of seven days.
If you could end bureaucracy, which agencies do we close immediately?
This is so weird.
I don't think I know this guy.
I really like the imagery of a person standing in the DMV and then singing like this about how annoying it is.
And then at the end, they down on like a down like like the the Phantom of the Opera like on their pipe on the pipe organ.
That just happens to be sitting there.
Which which agencies do I close if I'm ending bureaucracy?
Oh, my God.
Where do you even begin?
Ice.
Done.
The the the the one where they the one where they do the Pentagon.
Yeah, the Pentagon, the CIA, just for starters.
I don't know.
It's hard.
It's complicated.
The DMV, despite being a nightmare, does serve a valuable function.
I wouldn't close it.
I would probably streamline it.
Sorry for the boring answer.
God, next voicemail is called.
How many more do we have?
We have like literally three more.
All right.
I know there's so few.
So few this week.
This is just a paltry.
This one is called hashtag when Sonichu three two one go.
You know, Ben, if you really want to stick it to Trixie, there's no bigger power move
than releasing Sonichu one or two.
You know why I'm not going to do that.
You know I have a plan for it.
You know this.
How would that even stick it to Trixie?
I guess because like, oh, I released my lecture and you didn't release your lecture.
I don't care about that.
She's not going to do it.
Whatever.
I'm over that.
You know, I'm not going to.
I'm not going to release the Sonichu lecture until funded punishment is done.
This is well established lore.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Next voicemail is called.
Pfizer gang, Pfizer gang.
One percenters, baby.
Three, two, one go.
Ayo, vaccinated gang.
Ayo, second shot gang.
Pfizer gang.
We talked about this already.
We already we already covered this, but good question.
Pfizer for life.
Pfizer is like Ravenclaw.
AstraZeneca is like Slytherin.
Moderna is the Gryffindor and Johnson and Johnson is like awful.
Fuck you.
You're.
You know, it's an underrated house.
All right.
It's an underrated house.
Helga Hufflepuff just wanted to teach all kids equal.
Honestly, honestly, Hufflepuff is the best house because it's not stupid.
All the.
Oh my God.
You got me unironically Harry Pottering right now.
But Hufflepuff philosophy was just like, we'll teach anyone, anyone that wants to learn
can be a student and that's fucking based.
Ravenclaw is the only other one that's even like justifiable because it's like we only
want smart kids.
We only want like the really like best students and like, okay, I get that.
Helga Hufflepuff.
I'll teach anyone based.
Slytherin.
White people.
I mean, wizards only.
It's like, hmm, okay.
Not a fan of that one.
And then, uh, uh, Gryffindor, uh, only if you're brave.
It's like.
Especially like Chad's like fraternity.
Yeah.
You need a big enough chin to be in Gryffindor.
It's literally, Gryffindor is literally the Chad house.
Like the frat, the frat one for the, for the jocks.
I just don't think.
Harry Potter is a juke.
Harry Potter is literally a juke.
It's canon.
Well, I mean, he is a cop by the end of the series.
And he also becomes a cop.
But I mean, no, he's like a star athlete.
He's the fucking, he's the fucking star player on the fucking wizard football team.
Wizard football.
Yeah.
I think that's, I think that's what they call it.
The problem is, I don't think there's a single, a single interesting character in Hufflepuff.
I don't think she put one.
No.
Well, that was, there was a Robin Pattinson guy.
Was it Cedric Diggory?
Cedric Diggory.
He's not that interesting.
No.
He's just like, he's.
He's like.
Everyone likes him and he's cool.
And that's like his one thing, but he's not interesting.
Um, yeah.
I mean, that's true.
That's true.
Uh, oh fuck.
I was going to say, I was going to say something.
No, it's gone.
It's gone and they'll never come back.
Something about wizard football.
Oh no.
Um, that's the.
I don't know.
Something, something about how Harry Potter and, uh, legend of the, no, no, no, not legend
of the 10, no, no masters secret in the basement by Oolulilia, both and with the protagonists
using their new magic powers to become the ultimate cop.
Uh, they have the same ending.
All cops are based.
All cops are based and all cops are wizards.
All cops are fight our spellcasters is the, is the, is the lesson here.
I think the next one is this might be the last one.
Uh, this one is called.
Uploading it.
Bitcoin will never be a real currency.
Uh, three, two, one go.
So I had to break it to anybody's still holding out on this, but Bitcoin's never going to be
a real currency that you can widely use for like goods and services and shit because it's
baked into it that the value of it is volatile because there's a hard cap on the amount of
it that can ever exist.
So anytime demand for Bitcoin increases because you're trying to spend it on stuff, the value
automatically goes up and there's no way to counterbalance it by increasing the supply,
which is what you ideally do with a real currency is you increase the supply to match
the demand.
So the value remains the same and that keeps prices stable and keeps the market like functional.
So, uh, with Bitcoin, this volatility is baked into it and it's going to keep happening
forever because that's just what happens when you have a coin that works like this.
There's other coins that don't have that hard cap on the amount of it that can ever exist,
but Bitcoin does.
So it's, it's fucked.
It's, it's always going to be like this.
I mean, just, just imagine the type of purse like a fucking mom and pop shop or a Walmart
or whatever, adjusting the prices of everything on a daily basis in order to match the fucking
the changing in the price of Bitcoin.
Like you can do it if you're a fucking artist, a commissioner who only does like a couple
transactions a day or whatever, but fucking Walmart is never going to do it.
Is it?
Okay.
I haven't, I haven't heard this argument before about like, you know, because the supply
being inelastic, which means that like, which makes the, the, the value inherently volatile.
I haven't heard that before.
I guess my initial reaction is just that like the dollar is also volatile.
Like the dollar, the dollar value, the value of a dollar does change on a day to day basis,
like relative to other currencies.
And I know that like, yeah, they can mint more dollars in a way that they can't mint more Bitcoin.
I don't know whether I'm convinced that that is like a complete impediment to it becoming.
I don't want Bitcoin to become like a real currency that's widely used.
I watched a little video.
I watched some like fucking network news, Bitcoin news network video the other day where a guy
was talking about why like Bitcoin is, you know, basically destined to become, to become
like, you know, a, a adopted as a widely used currency.
And, you know, he explained all the properties of money that it has and that it has better
than like, you know, gold and better than, you know, traditional currency and whatever.
And it sounded like maybe, and I don't know if I buy that like this is,
because the price of the dollar does fluctuate and like the fact that you can mint more dollars,
does that, does that like really help control control the price of the dollar that much?
Maybe it does.
Honestly, I feel like I'm out of my depth.
Yeah, I'm not a smart man, but I do think even if volatility was an issue, even if it like
steadily just increased in value at a very calculable, calculable rate.
Yeah, the fact that it is a fixed supply does seem like a bad idea.
Like, like a currency that is encouraged to save and not spend does not seem like it would be good for the economy.
But I am not a smart man.
You're right.
Because like, I mean, this, this guy, the guy who's the video I watched, he seemed to think that like,
he basically felt that like the Federal Reserve printing money is like a form of violence,
in that it is like devaluing money that people exchange their, you know, time for.
And obviously, you know, knowing, knowing a little Marxism as I do,
I know that like money is not like the money that people have is not actually equivalent to like time that they spend to obtain it.
Because like, that's not how capital works, capital accumulates more of itself.
So, so like, yeah, now that you mention it, the, I think that that makes that makes it a very unattractive option for me,
because yeah, if the supply of Bitcoin is completely inelastic, then if somebody gets tons of Bitcoin,
they just have all the money, right?
They just have it all.
And whereas like, if someone has all the dollars right now, theoretically, the bank can print more dollars and distribute more dollars.
And that person with all the dollars now only has half the dollars, their value has decreased because the supply was increased broadly.
And you can't do that with Bitcoin, which is horrifying.
I mean, I think it's optimistic to say that like, oh, that means it can't be adopted as a currency.
It can and it will just lead to a horrible dystopian libertarian nightmare.
Yeah.
To his other point, I do think the idea that a store could not change its prices every day probably is not true as we get more and more technologically advanced.
Like, I think what you're imagining when you say that is like, what are they going to write on a new sticker and have to replace put it over the object every single day.
And like, the answer is probably not. The answer would be that each price would have a screen underneath it and there would be an algorithm that updates the price under the screen.
And the algorithm is attached to the value of Bitcoin.
It's not something that's immediately available right now to every mom and pop shop, but like, I would not be crazy for like 20 years.
Don't stores without checkout already exist?
Yeah, they do.
And like, maybe, I mean, maybe the prices could be listed in some sort of like stable conversion metric, but like the actual transaction could still be conducted using Bitcoin.
And the Bitcoin value might fluctuate, whereas like the conversion rate is weighted in a way that the listed price stays the same or something like that.
I mean, each store has its own microtransaction currency.
Oh, like, like for loot boxes.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, we got one more one, some fucking idiot submitted a voicemail at 636pm on Sunday.
He just he just right now.
Yeah, right now.
So this is the actual last one.
This is called High Tabuska Sky Don't Watch Odd Taxi.
Three, two, one, go.
What the fuck I was listening to the fucking podcast.
I knew that I didn't send any voicemails.
But there was like a little nagging in my head like, haha, wouldn't it be funny if like you did send a voicemail and you just don't remember.
Come in Tabuska Sky, who sounds just like me, at least to me at that.
That's easily scariest experience in my life.
Easily. This is fucked up.
This is scary.
Watch Odd Taxi.
Pretty please.
Okay, bye.
That's a weird thought to have.
Like what if I what if I accidentally submitted one?
I didn't realize it.
That's a weird thought.
Just because someone's voice sounded like your voice.
I don't know.
I can't.
It's a memento shit.
So now I'm confused whether I should watch Odd Taxi and I'm like, I'm getting mixed mixed messages.
She said watch it.
Huh?
That was a very distinct message.
Yeah, she said watch it, but the title of the voicemail said don't watch Odd Taxi.
Well, I guess you should go in between and watch with one eye open and one ear open.
A true shrug.
Just watch regular taxi footage.
Put yourself in a box with a screen and for us, we won't know if you have or have not watched it.
So I think you've done both.
Spoiler.
I won't.
I won't do it.
Experiment ruined.
Okay, we've made it to the end.
Yes.
Fucking done.
We've paid our pound of flesh.
We have come to the end of the podcast.
So I guess before we leave off, anyone got any final thoughts or objects of interest or
notes to mention before we sign out for another week?
What are we thinking?
How are you feeling, guys?
Everybody go check the link in the description for Gibbon Takes New Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
Starting tomorrow.
No.
Check out the Cado anthology, link in the description.
Throw it some money its way if you feel like it.
Yeah.
If you make comics, if you pledge enough, we will do another anthology.
So it's an opportunity.
True.
That would be cool.
It would be cool if these were your regular thing.
I mean, I saw a bunch of people that were listed.
I think it was Michi Foster, I think, said it was going to be her first.
She's excited that it's getting printed because it's the first time something she's drawing
is being printed.
I'm sure that a bunch of the artists feel that way as well.
Just excited to be like, wow, something I drew is, one, I get paid for it.
Two, it's going to actually be in print and distributed.
Really cool.
And Michi's comic.
Michi's comic is by far one of the things I'm most excited about.
It is, I mean, her art is amazing.
Her art is amazing.
It's definitely, I mean, it's almost worth the price of the book alone.
True.
Yeah.
I haven't actually looked at, I guess I do have access to the entries, which I didn't
know.
I haven't read all the contents.
I didn't look at it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, but I will.
I promise.
I promise I'll look if I feel like it.
The only reason I said it is because I kept seeing messages of you being like, I haven't
actually been sent anything.
I haven't seen anything.
So I was like, all right, fuck you, man.
Here, read it.
And I knew you wouldn't.
I knew you wouldn't.
I didn't.
Okay, but link link in the description.
Go check it out.
These guys deserve thanks for setting all this up.
It's pretty cool.
And become a patron at patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
If you want to support us also, hell, you could even do both.
You could pay, you could give money to both things if you really wanted to.
If you were really dedicated, if you were a true fan and not some faker.
But we'll see.
Okay.
And if you were a real PCP fan, you'd go to patreon.com slash kato yt.
You have a patron too?
Okay.
Yes.
Also that.
That is classless zero.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Check out the kick.
I'm a villain.
Check out the Kickstarter in the short term and the patreon in the long term.
Right.
You got it.
You have to funnel them.
You have to funnel them down the, you have to whittle them down the pipeline.
Right.
You have to radicalize them on the kato ideology.
Like an onion.
You have to progress them from the outer layer all the way to the inner layer.
Okay.
I guess, I guess we're done.
I guess that's the episode.
Thank you guys for coming on.
Yes.
We're done for free.
Finally, finally over.
All right.
Thanks everyone.
Thanks for watching.
Goodbye.
Good night.
See you next week.
Peace out.
Bye.