This episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast was brought to you by our bonus episode.
Go to patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators and pledge five dollars or more to get access to all our bonus monthly episodes.
Last month's episode was Game of Thrones.
The books really are way better.
Reading is boring and reading is for little babies.
It's so much- okay.
There's just so much superfluous shit.
No, that's the good stuff. God damn it.
No, no.
He fucking let the thoughts get to him, man.
He let the thoughts get to him in a proud mig-towel like Littlefinger.
I just cannot buy that what the fuck happened to that guy.
Is Arya Stark OP? Yes or fuck yes?
Yeah, to watch her obliterate literally every religious person in the world was-
That was the fucking-
That was your apiest dream, wasn't it?
The girl said, you know nothing, Jon Snow, and I want Jon to say, and now I know.
That's Patreon.com slash The Pro Crastinators, making you squeal like a pig every single time.
Good evening, everyone, and welcome to Inside the PCP Studio.
We are delighted to welcome this evening all the members of the PCP who had 10 minutes to spare.
Stolen directly from the show we're ripping off, our guests will be answering 10 intimate questions.
We will be diving deep into the troubled pasts and unhinged psyche of our fair guests.
And by the time we are through, you may find yourself cognizant of just what the fuck actually even is the deal.
Let us begin with our first guest.
As our first guest on the stage tonight, we welcome the runt of the litter, the baby junior,
the lowly creature on the lowest point on the totem pole, the creature with every feature that a human being can have,
the strongest baby in the world weightlifting championships, the master of spice and anger, and he's cool.
Welcome, everyone. Munchy, where's Tiny Hats?
I was going to be the next in the line of the Greek gods succession. I'm haired to the throne of Zeus, and I was plucked up from the ground too early.
I wasn't able to complete my metamorphosis. I was growing inside the ground much like a potato, and I was plucked beforehand.
So I'm not a god yet. I'm half mortal. My only weakness is that I'm completely and utterly successful to all sorts of marketing and advertising.
And if you even slightly suggest to me that I should buy something, I will do it. That's my only flaw. Otherwise, I'm completely immortal.
Artist. Yes.
Podcaster.
Inventor of the arm. Retriever. Retriever of arms, indeed. Indeed. His career is as illustrious as his body mass is extensive.
He's known for all these things and more.
My waistline is almost as dense as the horizon for which my future, where my future rests upon.
My future is so broad and dense, much like my gigantic fucking stomach that I will use to consume all of you meager, mean, minuscule before me.
Like one fucking, like with one fell chomp. I shall obliterate you. I am here.
Indeed. And let's get into that process immediately.
Munchy, what is your favorite word?
My favorite, I should preface this, which I have extensive notes for all of these intense and rigorous military grade questions you have said before me.
I've read them all complete in utter sincerity and none of them possess any of my, you know, trademark tact or addiction.
And all of them will be completely straight. There will be no jokes. In fact, I probably won't even be speaking for most of them.
I'll just be communicating like so vividly through my thoughts and actions. I'll be blinking in Morse code, so just please bear in mind that.
When you just hear, you know, that's me communicating at my highest level.
Right.
All right. So my favorite word is my, I should say my favorite phrase to hear is either thank you or good job.
But if you want to be a real stickler and force me into just one word, I like the word nautical for some reason.
I wish it was like a variant of awesome or cool instead of pertaining to like sea bass aesthetics.
Like I want to just be like, dude, that's like nautical.
Dude, pass me that fucking nautical pussy, dude.
Yeah.
Good. Yes.
Thank you. What is your least favorite word?
I don't know if I even have a least favorite word like, like, like context will mean anything.
So like any word, like even really like detestable words like, like quiche or like clitoris.
They have their uses in some context.
Yes. Thank you.
Yeah.
What turns you on, Munchy?
What an awful question. I'm against all forms of being turned on, especially spiritually.
No, it's open to interpretation. Yeah.
Spiritually, creatively, emotionally.
Your Kundalini Bear Bee is flaccid as my eternally, erectile defunct triple inch pinch,
or I'll turn your clit into fucking roadkill with my steamroller.
Okay, but seriously.
Okay.
There's no one way to get me in like the creative mood or whatever.
Like anything from like coffee to like short deadlines will get me there.
You want my inspirational G-spot?
It's like blasting fucking like gay ass like weird earthbound music into my ears
and running for a real long time so I get all huffy and puffy.
That's what I'll do.
Whenever I need to get in the creative mood,
I'll just like turn on like the earthbound soundtrack,
blast it so like my ears start hurrying after a while
and just run down my street as fast as I can.
Yeah, great.
What turns you off?
Any sort of like messy work environment or like clutter in my brain.
If I'm like particularly annoyed or frustrated,
it'll lead like psychic residue in my cranium,
make it hard to like focus on anything.
So I have to like have my room be cleaned, which is never.
And I have to not be like angry at the world, which is also never.
Indeed.
What is your favorite curse word?
I'm really into it as I'm sure everyone in the audience knows a racially charged slurs.
Out of all the curse words, they undoubtedly carry the most weight.
And rightfully so because they're fucking barbaric.
Indeed.
My favorite is the classic nigger.
I mean, it's definitely my most used.
I don't actually say it as much as I used to, I think,
despite that being the go-to flanderization of me.
It's kind of boring at this point.
Like when not even an inbomb can elicit an eyebrow raised from your friend's circle,
you need to get, you know, you need to get some new material and probably better friends.
Indeed.
What sound or noise do you love?
Have you ever played Lego Star Wars the complete saga for Xbox 360?
Unfortunately, I have not, but I'm sure our illustrious audience has.
Yeah, yeah.
In that game, there are 10 collectible items in each level called mini kits.
And if you collect them all, you can build like a small Lego set
based off the level you just played in the overworld.
I never gave a shit about 100% completing games until I heard the noise
that blasts through your fucking speakers when you pick up a mini kit.
I don't even know if I can describe it.
It's simultaneously the most gratifying, orgasmic sound you'll ever hear
and probably the worst fucking god-awful goddamn like train crash of noise
you'll ever be fucking earrape with because the game is so loud on that sound effect
in particular as opposed to the rest of the game.
I'm going to try and demonstrate here.
PUSH-A-WING!
That's what happens whenever you get like a positive collection.
That's the sound of a job well done.
Yeah, it is. It is.
Well, then what sound or noise do you hate?
I'm pretty much in love with every sound conceivable,
even like unsettling or comfortable noises like moaning or licking.
I can get down in if the context is right.
For instance, if the moaning is the moan of a sad African child that I'm working to death
in order to fund my blood diamond operations,
then I can really get behind that.
But in all of the context, I'm afraid I'm going to have to pass that by.
I don't know if there's anyone against, it's all context.
Fair enough.
What profession, other than your own, would you like to attempt?
I fantasize about myself in various odd contradictory and like totally removed
from my actual skill set type job.
It's basically every day.
I like look out the window on the bus
and think about the things that I'll do when I open a restaurant
without actually having any knowledge or desire to cook above the popcorn level.
I can't even really imagine doing anything other than drawing.
Since like, Patreon has existed for as long as I could have eased,
feasibly actually started working.
That's how much of a baby I am.
Since I'm surrounded by creatives in my life,
I don't even really consider it an option to be like a construction worker or something.
And I'm too focused on drawing to actually have even like really dabbled in other mediums
that I see, to like see if I like them or anything.
Like painting, I don't know.
Maybe, like a little, maybe.
I don't know.
All that being said, I've kind of wanted to be a teacher
in the way, way back in my head.
Like one perished soul.
A while ago.
Maybe a chef, if I learn how to fry an egg.
Something like that.
Teacher, chef, blood diamond operator.
All those sorts of things.
Are right up my sleeve.
Slave master slash driver.
Auction, block, hawker.
Have you ever seen Indiana Jones and the Tip of the Doon?
Human trafficker.
That but for real.
That but in real life.
Excellent.
What a rich tapestry we're weaving here.
What profession would you not like to do?
Any job where I'm responsible for people's lives.
Like being like a doctor or a lawyer.
Like that would like put me in an early shallow grave.
My hands are too shaky and my brain is too empty
to be as noble as those dentist and airplane pallets out there.
I fucking will salute them until the day I die.
And I do not have, I do not have the mental fortitude
in order to like pluck a teeth out.
Hmm, I see.
With any tact.
And that is.
Of course.
And lastly, Munchy, if heaven exists,
what would you like to hear God say
when you arrive at the pearly gates?
Not that.
First of all, instant and incessant assurance
that I'm not in hell.
Basically for the rest of my existence.
Would you be in doubt about this?
Yes.
Why would you need assurance of this?
Even if he says that I'm in heaven,
I will never believe him.
No matter what happens, I will believe that I'm in hell.
It sounds like to me, you're creating your own hell
regardless of the circumstances by thinking that.
That's correct.
Why doubt that you are in heaven
when God himself is assuring you of it?
Who's to say that's not the devil?
Who's to say that is God?
Who's to say?
But if your day to day experience in heaven is like good,
why would you then think, oh no, what if I'm in hell?
Like as long as you're having a good time,
what's there to doubt?
Have you ever seen that one episode of the Twilight Zone
where the fucking gangster goes to heaven
and then he goes to the casino day in, day out
and he just keeps waiting at the casino to the point
where there's no stakes anymore
and he knows he's just gonna get win
and crush all the puts that he wants
so that life has no stakes anymore?
That's what I'm assuming heaven is.
Okay, okay, I see.
That makes sense.
So if everything is just peachy and good,
I'm assuming that I will be in hell.
So I need God to tell me,
every single morning when I wake up
and every single night when I go to bed
I'll be in heaven, indeed, in heaven, just to make sure.
And then after that's all said and done,
maybe like a fatherly pat on the back
and like my room key to where I'll be in heaven.
Also, preferably at some point we can reenact
the final battle from the Simpsons game
for Xbox 360 sometime as well.
Where God plays DER with the Simpsons
and in each stage you have to destroy
a new video game system in order to damage God.
That's what I would want to do.
Well, so it shall be.
Well, thank you for sharing this with us, Munchy.
We know that you're a busy man,
so kindly get the fuck off my stage.
And now the PCP studio is proud to bring you
the heart and soul of this organization,
the editor at large,
the big hair, lion main guy.
He loves roller coasters when they're in tie.
They're in typhoons, as I recall.
And here he is.
He's the DeVoo, everybody.
I am definitely not, however, an editor at large.
There's basically no one else but DG
and a few others who I would be willing to edit for.
You'd have to have really interesting videos
for the editing of them to be interesting enough
to be worth doing.
My apology will be etched on my tombstone.
Now, let's move on to the questions here.
Question number one.
DeVoo, what is your favorite word?
Power.
It's because it's so hard to decide
what your favorite word is.
You can only look at external data,
external to yourself asking the question.
And the external data I collected was remembering
that just every time I got back from work
at a job I didn't want to do,
or got back up on the horse from some lack of inspiration,
or just anything where I'm finally in the zone again,
I can't help but yell to myself,
power, power, power, power, over and over again,
a bunch of times.
I'm not exactly sure why,
but I would just sort of silently scream it to myself
a lot of times, the word power just a bunch of times.
Don't really know the meaning of that,
but it must be my favorite word then.
Fascinating.
Question two.
What is your least favorite word?
Bias.
It is used very obnoxiously,
very flippantly,
very pervasively,
not just in the reviewer sphere,
but all around.
And I guess when I press people to define it,
the definition works well enough,
but it's used in a way that makes it meaningless.
It's just like, you have an opinion
because you have an opinion,
or you're doing something with a certain slant
relative to some ideology or another,
because you do.
You know, it's always the way it's used.
It's always like, you have this opinion
because you have this opinion, therefore,
your opinion doesn't matter or isn't valid.
And it's really obnoxious,
and it obstructs a lot of conversation.
Hmm.
Davoo, you are by far the quickest responder
of all our illustrious guests,
yet thus far today.
I looked up the questions that you posted on an image,
and I just typed them all into a notepad ahead of time.
That explains everything.
Let's move on.
What turns you on?
Unmet needs in the world,
or to myself, right?
I can't artistically inspire myself,
or even just physically inspire myself.
If I can't see it working towards
a grand goal of something that will really matter
and make a difference,
and by difference, I don't mean people
dying of cancer or some shit, who cares about that,
but a certain type of video game
or a certain type of video that doesn't exist
and needs to exist,
and that's the thing.
I think a lot of artistically-minded people
spend a lot of their time doing two things,
but never at the same time.
A lot of the time they spend their time
getting mad about all the art that doesn't exist,
that they wish could exist.
If only there could be an action story
to this trope that all of them have
that I'm really sick of, right?
Do that all the fucking time.
Another thing artistic people do
is they spend their time looking at a blank canvas
and going, I just don't have any ideas.
If you just combine those two hobbies,
those two pastimes,
then you just make a thing
that is the thing that you want to exist.
Why can't there just be a video game that does this?
We'll make that video game.
Unmet needs, that's what gets me the most hyped
to make things or be inspired.
What turns you off?
Having to do boring things for people.
Like, hey, can you go
drive to this place
to do this thing, to get a thing
and then take it over here?
Because it always takes longer than you want
or you expect or you're told.
There's always something that requires you
to just stand there for 30 minutes
waiting for it to happen.
Usually it's just, once you let
that bathtub drain of
your productive day get unplugged,
it's gonna mostly drain out
before you can cap that shit back on.
The thing about doing things
is that it always takes three times longer
than it advertises.
It's like a 30 minute drive.
Well, that means 30 minutes of getting ready
and 30 minutes of chilling out after you get back
to recover your senses.
Everything takes exactly three times longer
than you expect.
Oh, a week long trip.
That's a week of you getting nothing done preparing for the trip
and then a week of you getting nothing done recovering from the trip.
It's a good rule of thumb.
What is your favorite curse word?
Face.
I'm sorry, face?
Yeah, because people always talk about
like the sort of, what would you call it,
the primers of
of swears, right?
Like what is the cracking of the whip?
But we don't put as much emphasis on
what you call it, the conjunctions of swears
and face is like a fantastic conjunction
or whatever you call it.
So as opposed to emphasizing the fuck in the fuck face,
you just emphasize the face.
Fuck face, shit face, bitch face,
cunt face, right?
It's like face kind of gets in on
gets in on all that. And I love using face just
just raw, like fuck it.
Your face, me and my brother like to say
you face case, you know,
it's just fun to say face.
It's just very fun to say.
Interesting.
What sound or noise
do you love?
I broke this into two categories.
The broad favorite sound
is rain, you know, very generic one.
My very specific one, my favorite
video game sound effect
is the laughter sound effect
of a guest in roller coaster tycoon.
They have this very chipmunk-esque
chirp and it's really pleasant.
It really just warms my soul.
How was that sound effect
carried over to the later roller coaster
tycoons? Did it get lost in translation?
Oh, well, yeah, the second game still has it.
The third game, I don't remember, probably something
stupid, like, you know,
I don't know about the fourth game
I never really watched any footage of that or played it.
Would you say, well, actually, I'll just
leave it up to you. What sound or noise do you hate?
Okay, so the broad one
that I hate the most is the radio.
The way that the radio sounds
be it AM or FM, FM's
a little bit better, I think. No, it's kind of
worse. Like, it's more pleasant
to the ears, but it's more nauseating to my
stomach. Everything about the radio
It falls more into the sound Uncanny
Valley, perhaps? Yeah, something like
that. Like, the way it's mixed, the way
that, like, car speakers emit it
especially when it's in a car.
It's bad enough that in a car I'm already getting
a little bit motion sick because I'm kind of prone to that.
But, like, the radio just stirs the pot,
literally, the pot of my stomach
and the way that music
sounds on it bothers me, but especially
the way that all radio talk people, be they
DJs in between songs or talk show hosts
they sicken me
unless they have a very distinct charismatic
voice and they can power through it. But if they're just
the generic, like, and now we're going to be
talking over here. Oh, yes, and I'm the woman talking
over here. We're going to be, like, talking about stuff
and then mildly chuckling at one another. That's right,
we are. I want to die. I want to puke
every single time. I don't know what it is. Something
about the microphones they use at the studio, the way
the speakers set up, the way that they are trained to speak
it kills me. And
my least favorite, very specific sound
effect is the
sort of stinger sound effect
that escapistmagazines.com
uses. I don't know if they still use it, I think
they do, on all their shows.
It's, like,
HA!
And do you know what I'm talking about?
I mean, it's weird, because I almost have a weird
Stockholm syndrome
for it, because when I hear it, I immediately,
my mind swells with
You think you're about to watch a Zero Punctuation?
Yeah, yeah, my mind swells with a Zero Punctuation sound
effect, with the extra credit theme song,
with the movie boss theme song.
See, I've never heard that outside the context of a Zero Punctuation
board, you need to realize. And with Jim position.
So many fucking
openings, I think of when I hear it,
but I still hate it. It's really fucking obnoxious.
It's, the
swishing of
the pen, the swishing of the pen
has sort of like this
anti-ASMR effect for me.
For people into ASMR, a lot of them are aware of, like,
it can be ASMR in a bad way that pisses
you off, and it sort of, like, rolls
you into this obnoxiousated
state. But then it, like,
punishes you with this obnoxious fucking
scream, and I don't know why they thought
that was, like, good marketing. It's, like, to be as earwormy
as possible. I don't, I don't, I don't get it.
Like, if they're trying to, like, gain more,
you know, viewers and shit, maybe they should, like,
introduce better content more
than, like, every other decade.
A question for the ages.
What profession, other than
your own, would you like to attempt?
The one
I most am frustrated with myself
for not being, but no I never could be
just because it would take too much
time, is data
slash fact researcher.
The problem with all opinions,
be they political or anything
about history or anything at all,
there's always this issue of, well,
fact X, Y, and Z says this,
so clearly it's proven. Then someone else goes,
yeah, well, here's facts A, B, and C
completely contradicting it. And it's, like, well,
shit. I don't, I'm stuck.
Now I can't, I can't believe anything, right?
But I know that if you
research something enough, eventually
the cracks in genuine
misinformation show
and you can tell when something
is legit or not, right? Like, you know, you can never
confirm everything, but
no one's gonna fucking, like, tell me some
video game history fact and convince me
otherwise. Like, I've seen the same information
like, echoed by
enough sources that you can,
like, a genuine sense of truth
can emerge from within. But
unless you spend all your time
learning avenues of information
you can't get that intuitive sense of true
fact. And so I'm constantly
fucking stuck. And
I just wish that people could always,
I just want to, like, go and, like, see things that people
are arguing about on social media, but no one's
ever, like, taking the time to research and then,
like, research it. Like, like, actually
look at all the data and, like, like, come up
with my findings.
So you want to sort of forge your own
career path here, interrupting people's
social media interaction to let them know where
the facts lie. Which I think is a valuable
service. Yeah, my favorite one to be would be
who is being, which
political opinion is being more
unreasonable to the president they don't
like? Because the thing that everyone always gets caught up
on is, uh, people are
being mean to the president for this
reason and that reason, to which people are, like, well
people are unreasonable to the previous
president for the exact same reasons.
It's like, okay, are we all,
like, basically I just want to, my favorite one
for me, the golden, the golden goose
of facts, would be to see if I could
mathematically calculate if one political side
is more unreasonable than the other.
Mathematically proven. That would be fucking
satisfying.
Well,
another question for another time. But what
profession would you not like to do?
So I thought about, I mean,
almost any job would be, you know, mind
bendingly boring for me and I just commit suicide
so I wouldn't actually ever do the job, right?
So I'm only, like, counting jobs I actually
would end up doing and not leaving
and that would be, and it's sort of, like,
a very subtle, it's almost the same
as the profession I just said, actually,
but subtly different.
It's being professionally right
where
sort of people for whom... I don't understand.
It's people for whom their job
is to be correct
on, like, the things that they're talking about.
Like, perhaps like a, uh, like a, what's the word?
A witness? What do they call them? A specialty
witness or whatever? No, no, it's like, you know,
it's hookin' YouTube political pundits.
You know what I mean? Like, the people
who have these very specific ideologies
and do a lot of research and education and all,
but, you know, like, the point of their channel
is that they constantly, like, hammer in
their ideology over and over and over again
and their job
is to be correct and
right. And it's especially... Perhaps, like,
a less biased Stefan Malinu
sort of thing? Yeah.
Well, it's like, well, that's the thing, right?
Not to attach you to his name.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, well, the problem
is that I think once your job is to
be right, then you've already, like, fucked
everything up, I think. Like, basically
your job, what you wake
up in the morning for is to be
correct about the issue.
And now, like, you've sort of, no matter
how self-aware you are, you've sort of
inserted yourself into this
this fallible, this highly fallible
state where you're just going to become
a demagogue. Like, you can't
control it. Doesn't matter how smart and slick
you are, once the purpose of your waking
up out of bed in the morning is to, like,
promote this idea and to re... I feel
like you'll probably get sucked
into this more easily if you are more
logically accurate. It just
fucks everyone up, because I see so many smart
people, like,
try to be pundits for certain
ideas, and they're just always
fucking stupid, too.
For no reason, other than the fact that they have
to, like, explain how right they are every
day. I don't get it. It's terrible.
I hate it. Sucks.
Complex shit.
And now, finally,
DaVoo, if heaven exists,
what would you like to hear God say
when you arrive at the pearly
gates? That outside
of the boundaries of heaven is just sort of, like,
an infinite plane, like, maybe mountains
and hills and stuff, but, like, you know, lots of just grass
and, uh, you know, you can
do whatever you want, like, you're still immortal
and you won't get sick, but you don't get any
heaven benefits, but you don't have to follow any
heaven rules, so the whole
crippling fear of the very notion of
heaven being a place where you worship God,
i.e. be at church forever?
Yeah, you don't actually have to do that. You can just kind of, like,
fuck off. You don't get, you don't get
God care, I guess. You don't, you don't get
fucking Jesus books, but, um,
you don't get any, like,
faith stamps, right? But,
yeah, you can just go off and, like, just do
whatever you want, like, you can fuck till
the sun comes down, right? Basically, you're, you're getting
a pitch for your ideal heaven
when you, when you talk to God, or he's
explaining to you what heaven's going to, so
how, do you need to eat in this
heaven? Do you need to sustain yourself, or is this
Man, I don't know, but maybe
I don't know. Is it basically just, like,
more life? Well, what I'm thinking
maybe is that, like, your cellular
structure is infinite, right? It's, like,
perpetually restored by your soul,
but maybe your soul
withers away over the course of, like, what would be
the equivalent of millions of years unless you go to
heaven, maybe, right? So maybe
that's how he fucking gets you, right? Like, maybe
he makes you sign contracts, like, you gotta be in heaven
for, like, this amount of time. Do you mean, like, by not going to
heaven, by not going to heaven, so you either
go to hell, or you remain as a ghost
on, on earth? I'm just thinking, like, maybe
the outskirts of heaven is a place where you can go
hollow, essentially, right? Cause, like, your soul
you started making me think about what would be
the, the finite resource of this. I think your
soul would eventually wither away, right?
And so, like, in heaven, your soul
can be restored a bunch of times, or, you know, infinitely.
So, that would be, like, the
push and pull, right? So...
You gotta rest in heaven's bonfire every once in a while
to refill your soul flask, okay?
So, yeah, I'm not expecting this to be perfect,
but, uh, I just, that's,
I just don't, I've never, I've
never fucking been convinced
that heaven would be a good place to live!
Like, all the materials that it's made out of
don't look comfortable. Would you like
to walk around on fucking shiny-ass
roads all the time? It probably, like, gets stuck to
your fucking feet, creating little, like, puddles of sweat
every fucking day.
I don't know. I guess when
I was disgusted, it was always just, like, it'll be
whatever would be perfect for you. It was kind
of how I was explained to it when I was
growing up. It's too vague. It's too fucking
vague. And the idea is that you worship God
all day forever. What the fuck?
Like, who the hell makes
this alternate species just to worship you?
Like... A sycophant.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad we
tackled that. D'Vu,
thank you. Yes.
Please go and rejoin the collective
and get the fuck off my stage.
This has been the PCP Studio. Goodbye.
See ya.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage
the one, the only,
Green Ranger, Godzilla,
Tablet Boy
himself, God
King, Lord
of
poverty.
Tom Oliver.
I don't know if I'm the God King. I feel like
Ben Saint was the ruling
poverty man. I'm just
an astute
student
in his mastery.
I've yet to eat out of the trash, but I'm working
way up there, you know? I see you too
as sort of the heads of your two opposing
parties on the war for extreme
poverty domination.
It's a war I wage under duress,
believe me.
Perfect.
Okay, let's
get serious now. This is a serious artistic
time. Mr.
Oliver, what is your
favorite word?
Fuck
is absolutely my favorite word. It's so
flexible. It can be, it's a great,
the great thing about fuck is that it can
be used to enhance everything else.
Anything, any word
that I already like can be made better
when you introduce a fuck, you know?
Like, I like,
I don't even know. Any word you can think
of. It's fucking better
when you use a fucking
prefix to it. It's great.
I couldn't agree more.
But this is not about me. This is about you.
You're the artist here. I am the industry
shill. Question two.
What is your least favorite word?
I
got
two options.
I got two options.
I'm going to lay
them both out.
I don't like moist.
I know it's a very commonly thing.
It sounds weird. It definitely feels weird.
And n-bombs, I don't like
just because it's so phonetically pleasing
to say, but it's socially unacceptable.
So it constantly tempts me.
Those are my two choices there.
Oh, yeah. Oh, big time.
Big time.
Next question.
What turns you on?
And it adds creatively,
spiritually, or emotionally, but again, fuck that.
That's boring. No, it's all about
the sensual
shit, right?
I'm all about
those sick
curves, bro.
Those hard, those like...
He likes them thick.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Well, it's more like
everything in moderation as Aristotle
so
it stutely pointed out all those years ago
which he was totally talking about the ladies when he made that statement.
Everything in moderation.
You've got to find that golden mean, my friends.
That's where perfection lies.
Duly noted.
What turns you off?
Hmm.
Just...
I don't want to say
overconfidence, because
that's pretty nice, but confidence that isn't backed up
by
actual ability.
If you're just blowing smoke
up my ass, or just like...
That's a turn off.
Also, being morbidly obese.
Huge turn off. Can't stand it.
I'm sorry. How offensive of you.
You know, I got to be honest.
This is all about
being true to yourself
and that's what real art is.
It's all about injecting as much of your soul into it.
So I got to be real with you, man.
Injecting as much of your hateful bigotry
as possible. Exactly.
Get to a gym, god damn it.
Do as I say, not as I do, because I sit on my ass too.
What sound... Oh, excuse me.
I was skipping one here. What is your favorite curse word?
I think we might know the answer to this one.
I can't say fuck, because I just did.
That's my favorite word overall.
Oh, you can double up. Are you sure?
I guess... Yeah, fuck.
Fuck's just... It's too good.
It's too perfect.
It just feels great
and it's so versatile.
It's just...
It's fucking perfect.
You see, perfect, if you just say perfect,
it's like...
It's nice, but it's fucking perfect.
It's got that nice
phonetic rhythm to it.
It plays off of everything so well.
It's great. It's the best thing in the world.
It's got just the right amount of, like,
no actual meaning
for it to be used in all situations.
It means everything.
It's just everything and nothing at the same time.
It's the closest thing to god we've ever gotten.
Indeed. Indeed.
What sound or
noise do you love?
The PlayStation 1 boot up is, like,
the best sound
of all time.
It almost... It gets me hard.
99% of the time
it's the best thing.
That should be...
They never should have gotten rid of it.
If I could, like, make every console boot up
and do that at my computer, I would
because it's the best.
What sound or noise do you hate?
The screeching
and crying of babies and toddlers.
The worst.
The worst sound in the world. Absolutely.
Every time I hear that, I had to grow up with the younger sister
so I heard it constantly
and it's deeply embedded in my
DNA now that that sound
makes me want to commit murder.
I think school shooters, they go
to just have less of that sound
in the world. That's why they do it.
I feel for them.
Hashtag we stand with the Columbine
shooters. For sure. He knew it was up.
They handled the other ones.
Yes.
What profession other than your own
would you like to attempt?
I would love to
be a musician more.
I'd love to learn how to do the musics.
I feel like that's the one talent
and skill and ability that I'd like
to spend time grinding out.
It feels like such a gargantuan mountain
decline with all this other stuff. I have no idea
when I'm ever going to be able to get around to it.
That would complete my skill repertoire
and make me a god.
Indeed.
What profession would you not like to do?
I would
hate anything. Anything involving being
stuck in a cubicle all day.
I feel like you might be able to
understand my pains in that one.
Indeed.
You're in a prison.
It's worse than being in prison because
in prison you're locked in, you can't get out.
A cubicle is like a prison but the door
is right there and you know you can't
leave through it even if you wanted to.
It's awful.
You're imprisoning yourself of your own
volition as opposed to being in jail
where you can't get out even if you wanted to.
Hmm.
It's a prison of the mind if you will.
Indeed.
Lastly, if heaven exists,
what would you like to hear God say
when you arrive at the pearly gates?
Here's your 72 virgins.
Which I'm sure you expect
to hear when you get it.
Absolutely. That goes back to the school
shooting and everything.
I'm planning it out. It's going to be great guys.
18 big plans.
It's going to go out with a bang in 2018 everybody.
For sure.
Hashtag plans for 2018. Here we go.
Well, this has been
an honor to discuss these things
with the one and only Green Ranger himself.
Thank you for being here Mr. Oliver.
Please get the fuck off my stage.
Okay, bye.
And now ladies and gentlemen, as a special treat
in her first live appearance
of all time, we have
the one, the only,
the beast from the east.
The purple creature
with no facial feature.
It is lethal aurora mage.
That's one good intro.
Right.
Off the top of my fucking head.
I nailed it. Okay, I'm sorry, but this is serious.
No, you did well.
Round of applause.
Thank you. Oh, and I almost forgot to go
of your credentials. Animator.
YouTube memesmen extraordinaire.
Purple aficionado of all
which we have in common, which we have in common.
A reverence for the color purple.
It bonds us stronger than any blood ties.
Indeed, indeed.
Now, let's get down
to these questions that people
want to know.
Mage, what is your favorite
word?
My favorite word.
And this is particularly interesting since
you're not a native English speaker.
So perhaps it'd be a whole different language.
No, I speak
more English than I do my native language.
So,
English is preferred.
I haven't really thought about it to be quite
honest.
That's the nature of the hot seat that you're in
at this very moment. Oh, no, no.
I'm going to spend 10 minutes contemplating
the reality.
What word do I say a lot?
Oh, fuck.
I should ask my boyfriend.
What your favorite word is?
No.
What's my favorite word?
What's the word I use the most?
Because I swear, no, no, because I'm
put on the spot if I forgot what I
feel. Well, you can define favorite
in any terms that you see fit.
A word that sounds good to you,
a word that you use most commonly,
a word that you just enjoy. What if it's not actually
a word?
I'm willing to accept that.
I think the people are, the people will judge.
I think I might have explained it at some point.
I don't know where.
Snuck-a-snuck
which is a stupid
mispronunciation of the word snake
from this one
video about Pokmon were
real or something like that and they had a snake
but they called it Snuck-a-snuck.
But that's what I ended up calling
my cat and now we call the cat
Snuck-a-snuck. And it's really fun to
say. Am I saying this word?
Snuck-a-snuck.
Snuck-a-snuck, like there's a hue
after the SNN.
Snuck-a-snuck.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, fascinating.
See, that's great.
That's good stuff.
Okay.
Next question.
What is your least favorite word?
I don't even want to pronounce it.
Oh, come on.
Because I hate it so much.
Please.
People...
No, people are going to harass me with this word.
If you want to spell it, I'll happily say it.
Okay, fine.
But people are still going to harass me, but at least I'll get to not say it.
And then I'll private it to you because out of context it's going to be really weird in
the chat.
Okay.
Sure.
Actually, it's going to be really funny in the private chat as well.
Okay, let's see.
It is the word...
Oh, this has become my favorite word.
Okay.
The word, everyone.
Ladies and gentlemen, Maja's least favorite word is Cummys.
Cummys, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, you know, I can relate to you.
I'm kind of coming around on Cummys.
I'm starting to actually like Cummys.
Well, we'll see.
The degeneracy is sinking in.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Serious face.
This is the PCP studio.
This is a very serious thing we're doing right now.
Okay.
Thank you.
Next question.
What turns you on?
And feel free to interpret that however you like.
Good art.
Like good line art, good colors, good position, facial expressions, good key.
Any specific examples you can think of?
I'd have to like find a link of stuff, but that's going to take a while.
I don't really want to bother, but it's just like it's just really good art.
It's the best thing.
What turns you off?
Stupid drama, I guess.
Yeah.
Simple.
Fair enough.
It's just like people just searching or making drama when there doesn't need to be any drama.
Sometimes it's just like something that could be very easily resolved, but then they make
the whole giant deal out of it and it just becomes everyone's problem.
It's so tiring and draining and I just, I don't want any of that.
I think we could all relate to that.
What is your favorite curse word?
What's my favorite curse word?
I don't curse too much.
I've been cursing a lot more in recent years because I feel like becoming jaded.
I've noticed that.
I do say fuck.
I think that's the only swear word I really say.
Sometimes I say shit, I guess.
Is it sure it's a swear word?
Absolutely, absolutely.
Not my favorite, not my favorite one, though.
Well, let's just say fuck due to lack of memory of everybody thinking about the swear words I use.
Fair enough.
What sound or noise do you love?
My cat kneeling.
I just, I love it so much.
He's so cute.
He's currently on my lap and he's purring and snagging me and that's adorable and the best thing.
Unsurprising, an unexpected answer.
What sound or noise do you hate?
Both the sound and the sensation.
I tend to grow my cat just left me.
I grow out of my nails a bit long so when they ever scrape some surface like a wall or something
the sound and the sensation just gets really under my skin.
It's like the nails on the chalkboard sort of thing, you know?
Yeah, that's what comes to mind when you said that, yeah.
What profession, other than your own, would you like to attempt?
I don't have a profession, though.
Well, such as it is, such as it is an online content creator, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess maybe.
What else intrigues you or interests you in this world?
I don't think I really have what it takes to be one, but I think it would be really fun if I could be like an artist for games and stuff.
It's always been on my wish list of things to do.
I've always wanted to make a game where you have to design cute monsters or characters or something like that.
It seems like a fun thing to do.
My art style doesn't really go well unless with mobile games or something simple like that, but yeah.
What profession would you not like to do?
Just like 99% of all professions.
Fair. Anything in particular that seems super odious to you or do you just hate the cubicle idea in general?
I don't hate the cubicle idea. It's kind of intriguing in a way.
Because it's just something so different from my current lifestyle.
It's something I've thought about. Like, what would my life be if I actually worked in a cubicle and my cat is making noise. Shoot.
Indeed. Get off of the PCP Studio stage, Mr. Pussy. This is not for you.
Now, final question.
If heaven exists, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?
You did well.
Hmm. Indeed. Indeed.
I mean, isn't that what everyone wants to hear? You did good.
Everyone has their own answer to that question. And to hear more, keep listening to the other questions.
Not necessarily from God, but just like it's a good thing to hear sometimes.
Understandable.
Well, thank you for joining us. Lethal Aurora Mage, now die off the stage.
I will do. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Welcome to the stage in the PCP Studio.
We have the illustrious, mud-dwelling, famous, small Hagrid being God King Hippocrite.
Oh, it's me. It's me. I'm Hippo.
There it is.
That's what you sound like. Thank you for joining us. You're taking time out of your very busy schedule to join us, and we appreciate it.
Thank you for being here.
Yes. I changed my voice. I'm the other guy now.
Oh, you're the other guy. Okay, well, that's good.
I'm both your guys.
Oh, yeah, I'm here as well.
Oh, good. We have the whole team. It's like you and your stand. Dude, is that a JoJo reference? Oh, my God.
No, it's a yo-yo reference.
Whoa, sick.
This is the 90s.
I would show you my yo-yo skills, but it's hard to pick up on the microphone.
Okay, right. Questions. Here we go. These are the 10 memes questions. Okay, what am I doing? Okay, here we go.
Question one. What is your favorite word?
Oh, there's so many to choose from.
I used to have like a series of favorite words, but I think I copied them from somewhere. Plinth was a good one.
Oh, plinth.
What does plinth mean again?
It's like a raised platform that you put a thing on, an important thing.
Okay. Like the pussy. You put it on a pedestal, a.k.a. a plinth. That's what we do.
Yeah, you put the pussy on a plinth.
That doesn't sound as good, but I like it.
I'm really bad with my knowledge and brain.
Hey, that's okay. Plinth. Let's go with plinth.
Plinth is all right, yeah.
I don't know how long each question is supposed to be, so please hurry me along if we're too...
Sure, sure.
What is your least favorite word?
There's so many words to choose from.
Oh, I just have a list of words.
Here we go again.
Plinth. No.
Plinth and plinth, two diametrically opposed words, arch nemesis.
I hate plinth because it's not a real word, and it just makes me upset.
It's a terrible word, yeah. It's not even real.
Okay, I guess we're going with plinth.
Okay, there it is.
No, no. I thought I was out of time. Oh, geez, I'm sweating.
Oh, no, no, it's okay. Don't worry, man.
Oh, no, I got it.
Cat.
No, I like cats. That's incorrect.
Oh, no. That's racist against...
Delete that one. Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
No, we're going with that. That's canon.
Okay, moving on to the next question.
What turns you on?
Also, it adds creatively, spiritually, or emotionally, but fuck that.
Naked ladies.
Yes.
Well, what turns me on is a big pile of mud and sticks.
I like jumping in because the sticks make it crunchy,
but the mud is smooth and it's like really nice.
That's what hippo thinks. I don't know about that.
I can't really relate.
Pretty good.
What turns you off?
Somebody punching me really hard and knocking me out.
You know what I mean? You know what I mean?
Oh, I know what you mean.
Lights out, you know?
Okay, right.
Right, okay.
Next question.
What is your favorite curse word?
I like cunt, but it's always like...
I don't know whether to say the T enough.
You can say cunt, or you can say cunt.
It's more of a mouthful.
I'm not sure whether I like it, but it's very effective when you use it.
I guess fuck, because you fucking say fuck all the fucking time.
It's a very versatile swear.
What sound or noise do you love?
Sound or noise.
I like the clanging of two pieces of wood together.
There's this one song by Elbow where the drummer is like drumming,
but he also has this bit where he just gets two blocks of wood and I saw him do it live.
That's why I know what it is.
I can't do it because I don't have two blocks of wood,
but it's like a very sharp, harsh, echoing...
It doesn't sound like that at all, but it's like...
It's not that. It's more deep than that.
That's what I like. It's like a meaty wood, but really short slice of a sound bite.
If you look at the waveform, you could cut your eyelashes with that waveform if you printed it out.
What sound or noise do you hate?
Sex noises. They're so bad I mute every porn.
Every porn is not... That's why I read Hentai because there's no sound.
There's squishy gross noises. Get out of here.
Also ASMR, which is exactly the same as sex noises, but with a guy's mouth.
I don't like that.
You can do it with women. There's women out there.
You can have sex with women?
So I've been told. I wouldn't know.
Okay, next question.
Profession other than my own.
I don't even know if I have one yet of my own.
Well, you know.
I think if I could decide to do a different thing, and I can, but if I'd completely stop being a YouTuber...
Yeah, just go crazy. Whatever seems amazing.
And I would like to be a rock star.
I would like to be a musician going around the land and saying, yeah, baby, look at that weed.
Look at my guitar.
And then the people would be like, oh man, you're cool.
And I would be like, I know, like Han Solo does.
Yeah, yeah. You could be the next prince.
That's what you should be. Only a hippo.
Moving on.
What profession would you not like to do?
Well, the artist formerly known as Hippocrates. That would make sense.
Ooh, yes.
Because I used to be Hippocrates. All right. What was that question?
The artist formerly known as a Brony Curious, aka Hippocrates.
Yes.
So what profession would you not like to do?
I don't know. Stacking shelves in a shit show.
Store.
In a fake dog shit store.
Stacking them shelves.
No, shoveling shit in a parakeet enclosure.
But only there.
Like, I don't mind shoveling elephant shit, because at least it's like a funny elephant guy.
But with parakeets, they just like, you know, they're screaming.
They're bird screaming. You just got to be there, clean up their shit.
Fuck zoos, man.
Yeah.
Oh, I don't know. I kind of like zoos.
Fuck you. Get out. Get out of here, hippo. You're gay.
And also, I'm going to punch you.
Oh, no, I don't like being punched. I'm getting at it.
Oh, dear.
Now he's ran away. Now he won't come back up in conversation again. He's gone.
Okay. Well, thank God for that.
But we're on to our last question, which is, if heaven exists,
what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?
Yay. Fuck off.
That would make it all worth it. That would make being an atheist worth it
if he was like a cool guy that just told me to fuck off and be like,
you know what? I get it. I like you. I accept hell.
It's all fair game, because you're so rad. So sick.
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
Well, that's the end of our questions.
We may have clipped the mic there, but yes.
We prefer that here on PCP Studio.
Thank you very much for clipping that mic.
Thanks for joining us and get the fuck off my stage.
Oh, okay. Thank you. I have a book out. It's called
Go Fuck Me in the Butthole, Please by Hippocrite.
And Stores Now. That's why I appeared on the show
looking my book up my ass. There you go.
All right. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the stage,
everyone's favorite digital creature, Digibro.
Welcome.
Hey, what's going on, everybody? It's me, Digibro.
Digibro, Conrad, entrepreneur, YouTuber, hero,
spiritual leader of a generation.
I feel like a Jedi master.
Welcome.
Indeed. They always give some bullshit intro.
All right. Here we go. Let's get to these questions already.
That's what we're here for, everybody.
All right. Number one, what is your favorite word?
Oh, fuck. It's labyrinth, probably.
I'm a particularly fond of words that are big and complex sounding,
but they sound like architectural, you know?
That works.
Either in that it's describing architecture like a panopticon
or a labyrinth, which are both words I love.
Or that the word itself sounds like a structure like tetragrammaton.
Those all sound excellent.
And there happens to be a manga called Tetragrammaton Labyrinth.
Oh, fuck.
And it's really, really bad, but I own the first volume of it,
and I have never sold it because it's like a meme,
because it's like two of my favorite words.
And that was my Skype name back in the day. You remember that?
Whoa. Yeah, my Skype name was...
I mean, maybe.
Like the actual typed version that you had to type in to find me
was tetragrammaton.labyrinth.
Goddamn.
All of you had that in your Skype.
Deep lore.
All right, that's cool. Maybe I never noticed.
All right, here we go.
Question two.
Oh, fuck. I'm recording it as a wrong audio source.
Oh, no.
Now we've got the right one.
Okay, cool. All right.
Question number two.
What is your least favorite word?
Oh, I don't know. Least favorite word?
Like really any name of any insect,
because hearing it just makes me think about that insect.
And I hate insects.
Or I guess animals in general.
Let's go with dog.
Sick of hearing about fucking dogs.
Fair enough.
All right, here we go.
What turns you on creatively, spiritually, or emotionally?
I mean, James Lipton always just says what turns you on,
but he'd add this bullshit here.
Titties.
In all of those ways described though.
Like absolutely all of those ways.
All right, good.
What turns you off?
Dick.
That's a lie.
What turns me off?
Shit, actually.
Like shit turns me off.
Not into, not into scat.
What is your favorite curse word?
Fuck.
Because it's just, it's so, it's, first of all, has the highest impact.
Second of all, it's the most like malleable.
And it's got a long history, you know?
Like I know a lot of people like cuck,
because it has a lot of the same powers as fuck,
but it's like kind of new, and it's a little tied up in politics,
so it doesn't really have the broad reach,
where like fuck is like the standard classic.
It will always be like the bad word.
Like the go to cool guy bad word.
You know, I think cunt can rise up,
but I don't think it's as versatile as fuck is, so.
Fair.
What sound or noise do you love?
Do I love?
Do you love?
What sound or noise do you love?
I love my wife's voice.
There you go.
Your wife's voice?
Sure, okay.
What sound or noise do you hate?
This fucking computer fan that I can hear going apeshit,
because we're trying to render video at the same time.
Silence.
Did we get disconnected?
Oh, we must have, because I was answering.
Oh, sorry, I couldn't hear that at all.
Yeah.
I mean, if that's good, we'll just cut it in or whatever.
It should be good.
Okay.
I did not hear that at all, but good, yes, understood.
Great answer.
Okay.
What profession other than your own would you like to attempt?
I really want to be a porn manga artist.
Like more than anything else,
if there's one career I could choose for myself,
it would be to draw a porn manga,
to come up with more ideas for it than anything else in the world,
and I have such specific tastes and aesthetic sensibilities for it
that I think I would make something really unique,
but it would take years of drawing practice for me to be good enough to do it.
That's kind of the path that Masamune Shiro took,
and everyone constantly gives him shit for it.
Yeah.
Constantly.
The problem with Masamune Shiro is that he doesn't actually draw a porn manga.
He just draws weird pin-up art that nobody can get into.
If he was actually drawing great porn,
people would have no problem with it,
but nobody likes Masamune Shiro's porn.
I feel like they talked down to him unfairly.
He's earned his place.
No matter.
It's not about me.
Let's see, what profession would you not like to do?
I'm sure that's a broad answer there.
Anything that requires me to wear normal pants.
Fair enough.
And last question.
If heaven exists, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?
All your friends are here.
Good.
Well, that's it.
Thanks for answering our questions,
and we'll move on to our next cuck.
Yeah.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to the stage
the Mr. Ben Homeless Oculus Rift Trash Drawing Art Saint.
It's my pleasure, Mr. Guy.
Yes, thank you.
Pleasure to be here, as always.
It's truly an honor to have a man dredge himself up from the muck
to be on our stage as you've done here today.
Yeah, Doug.
Well, let's get right down to it.
Question one, what is your favorite word?
Ooh, oh no, oh no, no.
Are you asking everyone the same questions, by the way?
These are all the same questions.
It's a standard set.
My favorite word.
God, I feel like there's so many good ones that I'm blanking,
but I'm, uh, how about, um, how about, I really like, oh no.
Oh God, this is the hardest question I've ever been asked.
What a brain buster.
What a dick tickler.
Effervescent is a pretty good one.
I love evanescence.
Bring me to life.
Hashtag bring me to life.
I really like wither and wence.
I think we should bring them back.
Oh wait, no, the best word.
The best word of all, troper, as in this troper's opinion.
I'm bringing that one back for sure.
Oh, that's a good one.
I'm going with troper.
I'm going with troper, Nate.
What a trooper, bringing back troper, right.
Next.
What is your least favorite word?
My least favorite word is step, but only in the context of when someone says to step foot somewhere rather than to set foot somewhere which is the proper expression.
Okay, good.
Take note, viewers of this crime.
Next.
Protect yourselves.
Indeed, indeed.
Overprotection is better.
No, prevention is the best cure.
Truly, truly.
What turns you on?
Evanescence.
Bring me to life.
Hashtag bring my dick to life.
Um, sex.
And sexy attributes of a person.
Alright, what turns you off?
Did everyone else have as hard a time with these?
Do you by far had the most trouble thus far?
Okay, cool, cool.
What turns you off?
What turns me off is, I don't know, bad vibes.
Bad vibes.
Just unpleasant attitudes.
Disagreeableness, perhaps.
What is your favorite curse word?
Probably something like, something like a heck.
Okay.
Or something like, something British, like wanker.
Or maybe something like trollop.
Like calling some promiscuous lady of the night a trollop is a pretty good one.
Okay.
What sound or noise do you love?
Rain.
Classic.
Yeah.
What sound or noise do you hate?
I hate the sound of indecisive interviewees, truly odious.
Why don't you fucking try it, you piece of shit.
Oh, I will.
We'll see how you do.
I would probably struggle.
You already know the questions, you fucking cheater.
It's true.
Power tools.
All of them?
Yeah, just the sound of industriousness, generally.
The sound of things getting done.
The sound of people trying their best, really, you know, replying themselves.
He just wants to escape to his oculus or a fantasy world where nothing is accomplished.
Correct.
Okay.
What profession, other than your own, would you like to attempt?
Other than my own, maybe a writer or a journalist of some kind could be fun, I guess.
I'm surprised by that.
That's interesting.
Well, I don't know, just something about, probably not like an investigative reporter
or anything.
What would you like to write about?
A columnist, I don't know, something that involves just writing my opinions, putting my opinions
out there, you know.
But it's got to be something creative.
It's got to be something that involves my own personal spin on things.
That's interesting.
It's interesting because you kind of, right now, with your work, you're sort of creating
fictional worlds where you could sort of comment through those on, you know, all art is sort
of a demonstration of one's values and whatnot.
Right.
But this would be more of a direct commentary avenue, probably, on these things.
Yeah, I mean, ideally, I'd want to be making something, making fiction of some kind.
But if I, I guess, yeah, I guess if I wasn't doing that, then I guess I would want to be
commenting on the real world or, yeah, or, I don't know, maybe like a literary critic
or something, something where I got a comment on stuff and put my opinions out there.
Ben so desperately wants to be a YouTube critic.
I know, I know.
That's his highest aspiration.
One day.
If only you had the talent or the charisma or who knows things.
One day I'll make the leap, once I'm ready.
You know, once I've warmed up myself a little bit.
He's tried being a poketuber.
It has not penned out.
It's time to try new things.
It's time to move on.
After I've warmed up with all this, with all this drawing bullshit.
Indeed.
Going into the real shit.
Yeah.
What profession would you not like to do?
God, like any of them.
So many.
Yeah.
That's a pretty broad question.
Is there any in particular that seems super odious?
Or is it just the office atmosphere, perhaps?
Yeah, just the office atmosphere.
Just anything that involves show up at a place and spend most of your time there.
Yeah.
It's bad.
Or, I mean, I would say manual labor.
Not because I think it would be worse than that.
I just think I would be really bad at it.
Sure.
Which would put a damper on things.
Yeah.
Alright.
And our final question.
If heaven exists, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?
I would like to hear.
Damn, Ben, you really knocked them dead.
They'll be talking about you forever.
And we're glad to have you.
We're all excited to meet you and we've got a lot to talk about.
So both confirmation that you have, in fact, made good use of your life.
Yeah.
And that things the party will continue forever up here.
Yes.
Where we praise what you've done.
Oh my God, yes.
Perfect.
That's the dream.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for answering these questions.
We appreciate you leaching, you know, life force from us by being on our stage.
Yeah.
Kindly.
Get the fuck off my stage.
I will be, my lawyers will be in touch.
And so watch yourselves.
Thank you.
Watch yourself.
Goodbye.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, to welcome our final guest of the evening.
Tonight on Inside the PCP Studio.
Please welcome to the stage.
Mr. Nate Bestman.
Best guy ever.
Yes.
Hello.
It is me.
I am the best guy ever.
A pleasure to be here.
Rad Dude.
Rude Dude.
Philosopher God King.
PCP Puppet Master.
As long in the dong as he is dank in the schlong.
Thank you for joining us, Mr. Bestman.
And let's get right down to it.
What is your favorite word?
My favorite word I have known for centuries, decades.
It is the word sass.
It is the word sass, everyone, because if you think about it.
Sass has the highest ratio of the letter s to its length of any word in the world.
That is my actual reasoning.
It sounds the best to say.
It is mathematically precise, 75% s.
That's unbeatable.
Therefore, it is my favorite word, get fucked.
Superlative.
What is your least favorite word?
My least favorite word.
Oh God, I don't know.
Maybe something like...
Something like...
Oh God, I don't fucking know.
Shit.
Crusty?
Crusty is a shitty word.
Yeah, that brings a lot of negative stuff to mind.
I think yeah, crusty.
Crusty is up there.
Yeah, that will do.
Unbelievable.
Mr. Bestman, what turns you on?
Well, as you recall from the fetish cast, I love me a nice pair of glasses.
I truly do, I truly do.
Other than that, what gets my engine revving is seeing people self-actualize.
Watching people achieve their dreams through their own initiative.
In a sense, this is probably a narcissistic thing.
It's not narcissistic, really, but I like it when I do that.
And I also like it when other people do that.
Hey, to give myself credit, I think that I did it because I admired it
and other people so much that eventually I was like, yeah, I want to do that too.
And so here I am, a bit of a self-starter in my life at this point.
So yeah, seeing people take control of their lives and pull themselves out of hell
or seize opportunities, even ones that people didn't think that were there.
Seeing them rise to the occasion, yeah, that really fires me up.
It really does.
Incredible.
What turns you off?
Oh, definitely entitlement or laziness are the ultimate disgusting things.
Really leeches in general.
If I see someone whose whole thing in life is that they depend on someone else to keep them afloat,
oh no, oh no, I cannot be having this.
I refuse to live my life in servitude to anyone or anyone else that I don't...
Even if I want to support someone, if I do that and it's draining my time and energy,
that means I can't go out and achieve the things I want to do.
So yeah, that's not for me.
People that are drains on time and energy and that do not contribute at least as much as they draw from the world around them.
Gross, can't have it.
Oh, sugoi!
What is your favorite curse word?
Well, I really like fuck.
Fuck is really good.
Though I've always had a soft spot.
My brother and I read this book series back in the day, he read it.
He's the one who turned me on to it, called The Wheel of Time series.
It's a fantasy series.
Robert Jordan?
Was that the Red Bull guy?
No, I don't know.
By some guy.
And maybe it was Robert Jordan.
Brian Jocks is the Red Bull guy.
Okay, but regardless, there was a phrase uttered by the character of Matt at one point in those books called,
or rather was, bloody buttered onions.
And I've always liked that a lot.
I thought that was real quirky.
Like me, a gamer girl.
But really, it's fuck.
Like I use fuck all the time.
It's great and I'm a big into it.
Transcendent.
What sound or noise do you love?
I am a big guy into ASMR.
So I really just like ASMR in general.
So I'm always listening to tons of pleasant sounds.
But hey, I can tell you, there's some evidence that things have narrowed down to what I really like the most.
I like the voice of people telling stories.
And I mean, I listen to men do it more because listening to women whisper in my ear is too sexual.
And it makes me get loboner.
And that is distracting when I'm trying to relax.
I got to take care of that.
So listening to men's soft voices tell stories is very, very nice.
I kind of like listening to guys talk about, kind of like just like, I don't know,
not like the kind of shitty empowerment stuff about how you're beautiful no matter what they say,
that kind of weak ass shit.
But I like hearing them say like, yeah, go out and seize the day.
I don't know, man, maybe I'm a weirdo.
But I like hearing like male voices whisper to me about like, go, you like put in your fucking work every day.
Basically, I like the whispering equivalent of that song.
That's like 10% luck, 10% skill, 18% positive concentrated power of will.
You know, that song that in whisper form is what I fucking like.
Also tapping sounds.
Truly shameful.
What sound or noise do you hate?
What sound or noise do I hate?
I don't know, like I kind of have encountered a lot of gross mouth sounds.
I really am not into, but I don't know, sometimes I can kind of tolerate them.
Sounds that I, hey, you know, you know what's one?
Okay, I got the perfect answer for this.
It's when I was a kid, I discovered something that like really was a pain trigger for me.
So you know the whole nails on the chalkboard thing?
Okay, that's like a meme one.
It's so much worse, at least to me.
It's the sound of, okay, no one's going to be able to understand this,
but just ride with me on this gravy train, if you will.
So the sound of a very dry hand rubbing on a cloth binder surface.
It's just a, it's very shh, shh.
The only word I can use to describe the sound is dry.
It is the sound of dryness.
And when I hear that sound, I can feel, it's like I'm being drained by crocodile in one piece.
To use an example that everyone understands.
But like I feel the essence of dryness, like murdering my body, especially my hands.
My hands feel dry when I hear that sound and it causes me physical discomfort.
So yeah, that one.
Very kawaii.
What profession, other than your own, would you like to attempt?
Well, I would like to be, I mean, I'm kind of transitioning,
I'm working on transitioning careers, like do YouTube full time.
It's funny, because like right now, I am a professional programmer.
What I would like to be is like an uncoverer of the secrets of the world.
Like one who expands the knowledge of humanity in some way.
So either like, I don't know, a physicist, an astrologist?
No, an astronomer, an astrophysicist.
Yeah, I think that's what I'm looking for.
Really just like a scientist of some kind.
I would love to just like, I'm almost any field,
but I gotta say I have a soft spot for like space travel and stuff, you know.
Starfleet, weird utilitarianism, whatever.
Like I'd love to like work with Elon Musk and like work on turning humanity
into a space faring civilization by like developing new technology
and like uncovering like physical secrets that we don't know right now
and developing stuff that'll let us do that.
That's what I'd love to do.
Yeah, sign me up Elon, I'm ready to go.
Oh, how deliciously absurd.
What profession would you not like to do?
Um, waste management?
You know, anything gross?
Oh, anything dealing with like bugs would be absolutely repulsive to me.
Also working at a pound where they have to put down animals would not be nice.
Like I would love to work around like dogs because I'm a big dog.
I fucking love dogs.
I want to hang out with them all the time.
But yeah, like that is like, I know that's a necessary thing,
but it is something that, you know, repulses me greatly.
Yeah, something like that, something like that.
Even though I'm not kink shaming people who work at the pound who have to do that shit.
I know it's necessary, but it always kind of makes me depressed.
Oh, good one.
And final question, Mr. Best Guy Ever.
If heaven exists, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?
Now this is the one question that I actually did prepare for,
and I know exactly what I'm going to say.
If I die and I go up to heaven and I see God at the pearly gates,
here are the two words I want him to say to my face.
I apologize.
That's not actually a joke.
Yeah, as everyone knows, I'm a big atheist.
I think there's no good reason to believe that God is real.
And if he was, in fact, real, if I died and he was there,
and like it is like the God that this question implies it is,
like the weirdo Christian God, you know, in heaven and shit,
I'd be like, excuse me, sir, aren't you supposed to be omnipotent?
There are like a billion people down there suffering in horrible ways,
and you created them, so their suffering is literally your fault.
I don't want to hear this cop out about free will because you control everything,
so get fucked.
I would have strong words for the guy,
but really no matter what the strength of his apology,
it will absolutely not be good enough for the terrible things that he's done.
Yeah, I don't buy that this free will shit that I literally do not even think human beings have.
I also don't believe in free will, by the way.
Maybe you've heard about it, weird utilitarianism.
Yeah, so he can get fucked.
Free will is an illusion, it's not real.
Yeah, fuck you, God.
Enlightening as always.
Now, thank you, Mr. Best Guy, please get the fuck off my stage.
Yes, thank you, goodbye.
That concludes the festivities for the evening.
I would like to thank all our guests who came to join us inside the PCP studio today.
We will see you soon with another epic meme.
Good night, everyone.
I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.