Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
That's right, take some PCP with us friends because this is a podcast on the internet with
a bunch of content creators who make cool shit and here we are talking about it.
I'm the best guy ever and we are joined by Tom Oliver.
I am a sequel to myself, I've revived my old channel, it's back, I have ten new videos
up in two weeks as I'm a fucking god, go subscribe to it.
Impressive.
Hippocrit is here.
This is part one of my sentence.
This is part two of my sentence.
The sequel.
What do you think?
A bit of use of a semicolon to break that up or otherwise that would have been two sentences.
I can't just say semicolon out loud, what am I gay?
Yeah, and we've also got Digibro and MLP once again, our favorite PCP to electric board.
There it is.
We're talking about sequels today everybody.
Sequels is the topic of this episode of the PCP.
We're really, really scraping the bottom of that barrel and God doesn't feel good.
That's where all the gold cake's on, so when you scrape that shit up, you know, the people
appreciate it.
Scraping the bottom of the barrel is totally thematically relevant to the topic of sequels
anyway because that's really what they do in sequels.
You gotta just like, original ideas, fuck it, we're just gonna milk this and we're gonna
have Halloween or 18.
I think we made that argument about remakes when we did our remakes episode, but I think
sequels are a little different depending on what kind of sequel it is because the way
I see it, good sequels are all about taking the original and looking at it with a critical
eye and saying, how do we do it even better, you know?
At least ideally.
In a perfect world, that's what all sequels would be.
Well, you know, I'll give it a go, I'll give it a go.
I was just gonna say like a perfect example of that, the perfect sequel of all time, Shrek
2, you know, it improved on all aspects of Shrek.
I actually hear that opinion most of the time about Shrek 2.
Shrek 2 is liked, I think.
And so is Shrek 3, is it?
Not so much.
In fact, 3 and 4 and 5 and 6 and 7 are like their worst than Kingdom Hearts.
Are there really 7?
There's a lot, there's at least 5.
There's at least 4.
There's 3 and 4, I think.
Okay, okay.
Well, I don't know.
This is a corporatized world we live in.
It's very possibly could be 7 Shrek movies, I wouldn't have to cast them.
Hey, well, I was just playing a sequel this very morning.
Actually, I'm not sure if it counts, so you guys can tell me.
Just like, does Mario main, like do the mainline Mario games count as sequels?
Like I'm playing Mario Odyssey right now.
And that's a sequel, right?
I think that counts.
That definitely counts.
I think that's an interesting question.
Like Mario Galaxy 2 is very definitively a sequel because it's literally like the
same thing but they built on it, you know, like that's exactly the kind of sequel I'm
talking about where they took the first game and they said, okay, this is great.
What can we do to tweak it to make it like a little bit fresh and new but still be the
same?
It's like a sequel is one thing and then there's like a next one in a series, which
is right or may not be none of it.
I think all the Mario games, they're sequels to each other.
I think the core ideas in Mario Odyssey is, you know, the platforming, the jumping and
all that stuff.
That's an idea that has been in Mario's DNA from the original Super Mario Brothers
and all of these are just iterations and ways of tweaking the formula.
Iteration is a good word, but I don't know if I'd use sequel.
Yeah, like look at Dr. Mario, beloved entry in the Mario franchise, totally totally different.
The idea of like sequel is like you would watch them or play them in a series, like
they are very closely linked and you would go, if you wanted to do all of them, you would
just, yeah.
Like Mario Odyssey is built so that you could play it as your first Mario game, like they
want you to be able to do that.
There's no need to play Super Mario 64 first, whereas with the Galaxy games, I think they
definitely intended like, hey, liked Galaxy one, now you can do another one, so that to
me is more sequel.
That almost works as an expansion of sorts.
It really is kind of like a level pack and then there's like additional new powers.
It reminds me a little bit of like Brood War from StarCraft, how like that's kind of what
you get.
You get like a bunch of new levels, bunch of new worlds, and then like Yoshi was the
big addition.
But other than that, there's not a heck of a lot.
Okay, here's a question I have for you guys.
What was Gibbs saying?
Yeah, go ahead.
I was going to say like, that's interesting, you say StarCraft because that has like DLC,
but it's also a sequel to StarCraft 1, and there's like, there's like, there's sequels
and there's like, there's expansions and sequels.
Sometimes there's DLC that basically are sequels.
True.
Sometimes there's DLC that continues the narrative.
The line is blurred.
Well, here's the thing, I think we're forgetting something very important, we're all trying
to define what a sequel is.
We're forgetting the fucking Urban Dictionaries.
Urban Dictionaries, what's going to be able to define this for us, so we don't have to
sit here arguing about it.
I've got it open.
I've got it open here.
Well, let's settle it once and for all.
Okay, here we go.
A sequel, something of inferior quality, an utterance of absolute disgust, and here's
the full thing.
A word that owes its second meaning, its second meaning, okay, to the long list of low budget
waste of space sequels to box office smashes in which none of the original actors appear.
The storyline is either non-existent or piss weak, and the only way that the 12 year old
mentally challenged director can salvage this train wreck is through gratuitous use of full
frontal nudity that would horrify even the most seasoned SBS world movies connoisseur.
That's a very interesting definition because what they're saying is they're defining
sequel as why it is a slang term to insult somebody.
That's why I'm never ending because the sequel's never equal as Endless Jess has said in The
Coolest Guy.
There's an idea that referring to someone as a sequel is referring to them as inferior
to the original.
But you know, the best sequels are typically better than the original, but here's a question
I want to ask you guys regarding the Mario thing.
Do you think of the Zelda games as sequels?
Because whereas Mario has retained most of its core elements in each of these other 3D
games, Zelda is pretty fucking different and there's only one Zelda game, there's only
a couple of them that are like considered actual sequels in the can.
There's Legend of Zelda, Orchardine of Time, and then there's Legend of Zelda, Orchardine
of Time like 2 through 7, they're all the exact same game.
There's different window dressing on them, but I've played a bit of Orchardine of Time,
I've played through all of Skyward Sword, objectively the worst Zelda game of all time.
It's a train wreck of Titanic proportions.
I've played all of them, except for Wind Waker, though I did play Phantom Hourglass.
I would count all those in the same camp as the Mario sequels, like they are refining
the formula, just because they're different sorts of games, but they're the same sort
of thing, where they're just progressing in some particular path.
If you compare Mario Sunshine to Mario Odyssey, in both games, Princess Peach is captured
by Bowser, Mario's gotta go savor, he does this by jumping on things occasionally using
the powers.
Princess Zelda's captured by Ganondorf, he has to cut lots of things.
That is not a thing that even happens in most Zelda games.
How often has Zelda been kidnapped by Ganondorf in the Zelda franchise?
It's either she's captured or turned to stone, or something that is bad by Ganon.
Okay, Legend of Zelda the Minish Cap, Zelda's not in it, Ganon's not in it, Zelda's in
it, she's at the very beginning, in fact Zelda does turn to stone, that's the whole
thing.
Yeah, yeah, Voddy does that shit.
My point is, Dark Souls 2, that's a sequel.
That is a sequel.
Oh god, that's an unfortunate sequel.
Well let me back up for a second.
Ocarina of Time vs Majora's Mask, which is actually a direct sequel to Ocarina of Time,
very thematically different, like different tone, different kind of atmosphere, and I
think some of the Zelda games are enough thematically that I don't know if I'd consider them a sequel,
although in that case it is actually a sequel and it is the most different.
I guess my definition of sequel has always been more, is in terms of games, has always
been more about the underlying mechanics and the identity of the game, because you play
a Mario game, it always feels like a Mario game, you never would mistake it as something
else, even though there's lots of other new ideas and new mechanics being layered on top
of it, the base idea of like, they all kind of feel very similar, you know, you play like
Super Mario 3D land for the DS and you play Mario Sunshine and like the core mechanics
of like how Mario handles, how he moves, the base moveset that he has ever since Super
Mario 64, that's all pretty much the same and like there's iterations and refinements
and tweaks, but like you go in expecting a certain feel when playing a 3D Mario game
and ever since Mario 64, that's really been there to some degree and so I feel like that
underlying pedigree is what defines a sequel and while you don't have to be like a linear
progression.
Would you put Super Mario 3D World in there then?
Because that game plays very differently, would you say it's also part of that same
sequel lineage?
Super Mario 3D World for the Wii U?
Yeah.
I haven't played a whole bunch of it despite the fact that it's right behind me right now,
but despite the fact that it's like, that's someone who's more like, it's 3D but it's
like an isometric kind of view, right?
Yeah, yeah, for the most part.
I think the mechanics there are still pretty much the same, like it's still a platformer,
like it moves very similar.
It's interesting to me though, Tom, that you seem to be defining sequels based on more
of like the mechanics as opposed to like any, I don't know, like a narrative thing or anything.
I mean obviously if it's something that says like Metroid Prime 2, which like I think you
were just playing, like yeah, okay, that's pretty clearly a sequel.
Nate, you just reminded me of a term that will help with this a lot.
My favorite term, spiritual sequel.
Right.
Because when you look at it-
Is that a spiritual successor or is that something different from what you're talking about?
Both are used, but I always think you're a spiritual sequel.
Like for instance, a game like Axiom Verge that is clearly meant to be a spiritual connection
to, well in this case I would say a sequel, but a spiritual successor to Metroid, to Super
Metroid, like could it be that the Mario, because when I think sequel I do think continuing
the actual narrative, like it's supposed to be the same, at least the same characters,
you know-
Mario has the same characters for the most part, but there's really no narrative to
continue.
Yeah, you know, and like if you look at something like Mario Galaxy, like there's no plot connection
like seemingly at all to like any of the other games other than Mario Galaxy 2.
Most of Nintendo's games don't do that.
Their narrative is just like a very loose framing device to have the action.
So I'm not sure describing the Mario games as sequels makes sense.
I think like spiritual successor, even though they're all like mainline Mario games, might
make more sense.
Well, as far as I know spiritual successor doesn't even, when you say something's a spiritual
successor, the term doesn't mean it's a sequel, it means it's taking the gameplay identity
of another game that won't get a sequel and injecting it into a new IP.
That's why Axiom Verge is a spiritual successor to Metroid.
It's not a Metroid title, but it's trying to play like one and invoke that kind of same
game feel.
And what were you saying?
I feel like the whole Mario, the whole sequel's a successor, so spiritual stuff, like it doesn't
need a word like that, because it doesn't apply to any of them, like aside from like
Mario 1, Super Mario 1, Super Mario 2, like even that's kind of weird.
I think the whole thing with the sequels is like people generally think of it as being
if it's numbered, then it's a sequel, and if it's not, then it's just part of the same
franchise, and this word sequel doesn't even come into it.
Will Radcon Awakening be a direct sequel to Radcon 2?
That's, I don't know, I don't know, or is it a spiritual successor?
That'll depend on the narrative content of Radcon Awakening.
Indeed.
Are we going to do the fuck shit thing that movie producers do and not put the number on
Radcon 3?
Is it just going to be Radcon Awakening?
Davoo's been making that joke forever, that he insists that the next Radcon be called
Radcon Awakening canonically.
But with no 3.
With no 3.
Oh, that burns my heart.
We need to do that, and then the next one just has to be Radcon.
Exactly.
Or like The Radcon.
The Radcon was like alternating upper and lower case for each other.
Oh, yes.
Oh no.
Oh, that's the one like Gamze kills us all, yeah, that's when Munchie disembowels all
of us.
We definitely release Radcon on DVD on each one.
We have to make sure the titles are totally different on the side.
Yeah.
Radcon 4 has to be Raphor Decon.
Raphor Decon.
I do like that, I do like that.
Hey, so I watched a sequel, I watched a whole series of sequels recently, which is interesting
because it's kind of like the opposite of all this.
So it's like, so I watched Rambo, I downloaded all the Rambo movies recently and watched
all of them.
Because I heard they were cool and whatever.
So I watched Rambo 1, and everyone probably knows this already, but Rambo 1 is like a
story of a tortured Vietnam vet who comes back home and then like, it suffers, like
he's kind of a vagrant now, he's sort of lost his place in the world because he was such
a badass soldier, and now he's just a civilian and doesn't know what to do with himself.
And like, he's just in the world and he gets into some minor trouble with the law just
by like loitering a little bit, wasn't serious, but then he gets like abused by the cops and
then they like, they fuck him up a little bit, and then like he goes on kind of a murderous
rampage as they like try to track him down after he escapes from the thing.
And then like he like kicks back into like Vietnam mode and goes full monster murder
man and starts doing all this shit, and so it's really a story about a guy like being
tortured by his past and like having to overcome it, and like at the end he turns himself in
and like obviously has deep severe mental issues that he's going to need to work through.
And then Rambo too, like they get him out of jail and then he's just sent on like a
big epic like rescue POWs in Vietnam, like a military man mission.
So it's like they've capitalized on like the reputation that Rambo established, Rambo
1, of this guy being like a big badass soldier, but like they completely abandoned any of
the like, like the actual point of the movie of it being like about.
It goes from like a movie trying to make a message, send a message about like mental
health issues and just be like, what if we have Sylvester Stallone killing some bitches?
That would be cool.
And it was great.
It was a legitimately great action movie that I enjoyed quite a bit, but like it's like
it barely resembles like, you know, in the tangible details, it totally resembles Rambo
1, but in terms of the actual point they were making, they completely abandoned it.
And it's like, I don't know like who was writing that.
I'm really curious if the same people were involved with making Rambo 2 as Rambo 1.
That feels like studio meddling to me.
Yeah.
And I know Stallone like wrote Rambo 4 and was heavily involved in getting it done, but
that might have just been like the resurrecting of the thing, you know, because this was like
two decades after Rambo 3 was made and shit.
But like, so that's an example.
That was a surprisingly good sequel though.
I liked it.
I thought it was really good.
I liked the part where that Christian lady got raped.
That was cool.
She didn't actually get raped, unfortunately.
Yeah.
It was, it was good.
It was good.
Here's a, here's a sequel, a pair of sequels that, that I feel just for the sake of completeness
needs to be mentioned is Star Wars, which has gone in a lot of interesting directions
with sequels.
Because you've got the original Star Wars, big, huge film, everybody loves it, but it's
kind of directed and edited like garbage.
Like the, it's really, they didn't like every, there was a lot of problems with the production
basically.
And when you watch the movie knowing that you can really see it and then you get to the
second movie and it's such a clear improvement.
Like they took the ideas and gave, put them in the hands of a director who could actually
like bring it to life, make it feel big and real and like, and dramatic.
And then you get to the third movie, which for some reason a lot of people don't like,
but I think that movie capitalizes on the themes, the best out of all the movies.
It like brings it all home in a really good way.
And so you got this package where it's like, yeah, you got sequels that actually took
what the previous one did, built on it, tried to improve.
And then, then suddenly they make three more sequels that are actually prequels and don't
capitalize on any of the strengths of the original and are a total clusterfuck.
But then you get like 23 more sequels a few, a decade later that are now just like cherry
picking any tangible or abstract concept from the old films and like cobbling them together
into a new film that is just like made up of the body parts of the old ones, you know.
It's a descent into corporatization, which is funny because Star Wars has always been
a very corporatized product, but it's gone to the nth degree now.
The fascinating thing about that, that trajectory is kind of like Star Wars like is pretty beloved
these days.
It's quite popular and, you know, it was popular for a long time, but like it's really had
a resurgence and it's interesting to watch the trajectory of everyone loved the original
films.
They're highly beloved to this day.
And then the sequels came out and at the time it was lukewarm and then some people were
massively disappointed and so the reputation tank, Luke Skywalker Warm, excellent.
And then, and it's funny because like, and then like now like things have kicked back
up as like JJ Abrams has, you know, been able to make some pretty good work, at least
for the first one and we'll see what the others do as well.
But like what's interesting is the first one was like a guy, Lucas, right?
Lucas is running the show, but he was tempered by the fact that he wasn't like the god of
the production of those.
His creative input was subject to the quality control of lots of other people.
And so it was, it was sort of a one man show, but then it was filtered through all these
things like sort of a committee that made it good.
But then you got the prequels and the prequels totally lost that filtering process and only
kept like what he said, like we're doing this, make it happen.
And nobody wanted to question him, whether it was his fault or not, doesn't matter.
The point is it was just what he wrote on that paper, probably too hastily without thinking
about it enough.
And that's just what became the movies.
And we all know what happened with that.
But now, and now we've got a purely corporatized product happening now, probably with people
who love it.
It's gone too far in the other direction is what you're saying.
Well, actually, I was going to say that like, it's funny that things have improved from
just like one man's mad vision by making it corporate, like they've improved, but not
like, I think the original was the perfect balance of those two.
Exactly.
Of course.
You know, he it was a lot of it was this one guy's interest and vision, but just he had
a good editor, you know, like a good like, and I mean, editor in the not like a literal
film editor, but you know what, his fellow writers and stuff, the metaphorical sense.
And now we've got like the editor writing the movie based on what he like what he thought
needed to be fixed without the actual inspiration.
There's no artist.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
We got to put we got to put a certain amount of of iconography to sell toys because he
he right.
We're Disney and shit.
And, you know, it's it's not it's nobody's making these movies because people are longing
to know what happens with with the Star Wars universe.
I mean, I mean, kind of the people kind of did because they made books and comics.
Yeah, I read a lot of this.
It's it's just it.
Yeah, it's very much like you can't see as anything other than a cash cow.
It's hard for me to think of it as like the same series.
Absolutely.
For me, I can I can easily watch those first three films and think this is three films
that were that like not that they were all intended to be made from the beginning
because like the first movie obviously was not supposed to have sequels
considering it wraps everything up perfectly fine.
But like when you watch the other two, you go, OK, this is a natural extension
of that first movie, and then you watch the new ones.
And to me, it just feels like this is nothing to do with it.
And that's it's just it's a fanfiction.
That's the thing. See, like I really did love the original Star Wars movies
and probably still would if I watched it again.
It's just it's just kind of been a while.
But like the originals have such a wonderful grittiness
of like old filmmaking to them.
They remind me and not to suck their dick too hard,
but they remind me of like like a Casablanca or a Lawrence of Arabia
when like things were just they had to get down there in the fucking dirt
and everyone got fucking filthy and dirty and things were not polished and clean
and so heavily produced.
Things were like, I don't know, fucking ramshackle,
like the fucking Indiana Jones bit where the the dude has, you know,
got his swordplay and he's danced around and then Indiana just shoots him.
Like that that's that's fucking cinema gold.
And the story behind it as well is incredible.
And I for one don't like the kind of the way things have gone
where they've proceeded to make things so polished and clean.
And a lot of it, I'm sure, just has to do with the technology that's available,
makes it easier to do.
And that's kind of just a constant thing that as the as we march forward
in technology, that's more and more of a thing.
And obviously that was done to to the nth degree in the Star Wars prequels.
But even now, I see I see elements of that in the in the newer Star Wars stuff.
And they just don't feel the same as like the originals that I did love.
So like to call it a sequel to me is like, like this is what people complain
about with sequels, that they're not the thing that you love.
So like, stop fucking it up.
The thing that's interesting about what you're saying is that those those old
classics, they were like big budget Hollywood productions.
Or yeah, I think they were the best they could do at the time.
They were a very like, like big, heavy production produced like lots of I mean,
it wasn't it wasn't like a board of directors, right?
But it the way just films were made back then exactly made you feel like,
you know, you could imagine that there's a bunch of guys in the desert
and they're trying to get a shot and then they have their lunch break
and they're like, oh, it's hot out here and newer movies.
It's like, I don't know, it just it just feels like I just imagine the color
gray and then a computer screen.
I just I just seize up.
I don't like it.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Something that fascinates me, there's a lot of different reasons,
just as there are a lot of different reasons for a movie to be made
or any product to be made, there's a lot of different reasons a sequel could be made.
And it's I think a lot of like what makes it good or bad will depend on why it's
happening. Totally. And like, like there's some that people make because it's like,
yeah, I just have more ideas.
I have another good idea with this world and characters.
So let's make a sequel and those are probably going to be the better ones.
And then there's the ones where it's like the show just needs to have a sequel,
like, like, because it has to have like, like back to the future.
One, two and three are examples of that.
Like those they had to be done because they left it deliberately open
and they did not give you the answers.
No, that's that's not what I mean.
No, that's more of like, like, that's more they had more ideas.
Like if they left it open because they knew they could make something like,
you know, Assassin's Creed, where it's like, it's a new year.
We have to make a new Assassin's Creed.
Oh, I sort of like that.
The example I'm going to use is fucking Psycho Pass,
because Psycho Pass 2 is horrible.
It is absolutely abysmal.
Why did and the only reason I think that Psycho Pass 2 exists
is because they were making a Psycho Pass movie and they wanted to keep the hype
up for it. Sure. So like that, like the Psycho Pass original TV show,
like like leading up to the film, first they reran the TV show
as hour long episodes, like they recut it.
They put each two episodes into one and they added in some like little extra scenes
and they made it like like a rerun of the show to get people hype.
Then they made a sequel to keep that hype going.
And then the movie came out like right after the second season was over.
So it was like all this build up to hype this movie.
And all the people who made the original show were working on the movie.
So in the meantime, oh, we need a sequel, but you guys are busy.
So let's hire on some other folks who don't understand the story at all.
Let's work on Dark Souls 2 while they make Bloodborne. Yeah.
Exactly. Exactly.
There has to be a sequel, but they don't have the right people to do it.
So it's like it's just born out of their needs to be one, you know?
And then that's where you're going to get the people who don't understand
the fundamental artistic intent like Dark Souls 2,
where they their mentality was Dark Souls is a hard game.
Let's make a hard game. Right.
You know, by putting a million fucking enemies behind this one door,
that there's no way to fucking defeat at all.
That's that's that's that's the difference between people
who see these things as as a piece of art and people who see it as a product
to be totally totally because the people who like the art,
they're going to sit down and be like, OK, I understand why this exists.
And I know what the vision behind it is.
And then you have people in like corporate who just like, well,
we we got to make our money for a quarter for we're going to release this land
and blah, blah, blah. I really think that a smart creator
knows that the corporate entity is a part of it.
And you can't just say, oh, I'm an artist and I have my vision
and it must just be one thing.
I think like if you're going to be a smart boy and you're going to, you know,
make things, you're going to write stories, you're going to make movies.
You should always have in the back of your mind written down somewhere
like sequel baits that if in case you're forced to make a sequel,
you have something, yes, but you should never like plan for it to exist.
You know, just like as a backup, because then then you can you can you can have both.
You can be an artistic genius boy and you can make money.
And you're very right.
It's really a delicate balance, especially. I recommend.
Sorry, I recommend everybody.
If you're trying to be a screenwriter, do anything that will involve you
in the corporate world of like creating.
Listen to everything Max Landis ever says,
because he is extremely good at explaining that world and his place in it.
And he has the mindset that Hippo is describing here.
The dude's written over a hundred movies like he just constantly has more ideas
for like if they won't take this one, here's a slightly different version.
Or like here's my ideas for if I have to make a sequel.
Here's my ideas for this and that.
It's like he's just got so many different contingencies for if it works,
because you can't be precious about your work if you want to sell it,
especially in Hollywood, you know, on this subject, though, what's interesting is
so one of the most beloved sequels of all time.
You may have heard of it is Godfather 2 and Godfather 2 was famous
because it was the first sequel ever to win the Oscar for Best Picture.
And that was quite a noteworthy event.
And what's especially interesting about it was that like as you'd expect.
So the Godfather 1 was based on a book by some Dimitri Puzo or something.
Yes, some guy who had written a book and then they adapted it.
And obviously that's where kind of Mario Puzo, that's it.
And Francis Ford Coppola directed it.
And that was a beloved project.
Actually, Coppola was actually put on it by a studio.
He didn't even want to do it at first.
And there was a lot of whatever bullshitting going on.
But it eventually turned out to be a great product.
And so once Godfather 1 was such a success, like it was a studio request
that they go on and make Godfather 2.
And like so he was not at all prepared to do Godfather 2.
And there was like no, there was nothing prepared for it.
But like it's just that the people working on the project
just happened to be so fucking good at making movies.
And I actually think Godfather 1 is like kind of vastly superior to Godfather 2.
But a lot of people love Godfather 2 and I do it for the most part as well.
I'm a big aficionado with the Godfather movies in case you can't tell.
But so ultimately like this is a situation where people were totally
unprepared. It was just studio desire to make a sequel that had them do it.
Because Coppola had no desire to do one initially.
It was just because the movie was such a fucking huge success that they made it.
And yet they just happened to get like enough brilliant people working on it.
Coppola and I believe Puzo came back and wrote the screenplay for it as well.
That they just put together something that the people fucking loved.
And so like so it can be done. It can be done.
You know, kind of that's the same story of how the Madoka movies got made.
Oh yeah. Where like Madoka Magica was just such a huge success that they came
with the Rybujigan and were like, do you happen to have any ideas for a sequel?
And he was like, I guess.
He made a movie that was the devil, you guys.
He made possibly the most divisive anime movie that I can think of.
Personally, I'm in the I fucking hate it camp.
But there's definitely a camp that absolutely adores that movie.
I enjoyed it. Dude, that opening scene of them eating the cake monster.
Well, sure. Just fan service is great.
Yeah, God, it was so fucking tight.
I like that movie. I don't give a fuck.
Here's an idea. I want us to do some I want us to do a round robin here.
Word. And each of us talk about one sequel we absolutely hate or are
fascinated with in that it is bad and one that we absolutely love.
Great. Fantastic. Fascinated with this.
All right. So we'll start with bad ones.
I've got to talk about because I've been this is something I experienced recently.
The lost planet games.
Have any of you played lost planet?
I know played a little bit of it, but are they all like dino crisis?
No. OK, never mind.
But they're there.
It's a series of Capcom games that was for the Xbox 360.
The first game was like a launch title for the 360.
And the first game is basically like an arcade over the person shooter game.
Like basically you're on this planet of ice and you run around
and you shoot like giant bug monsters.
And there's lots of mechs you can pilot and you fight lots of like
basically just you you pilot mechs and you fight other mechs and monsters.
And it's really cool. It's like five hours long.
It's a fun game.
But there's a lot of ways that it obviously could have been improved with the sequel.
Like it's it's pretty small.
It was obviously like testing the hardware because it was like one of the first games
for the console. So like the biggest strengths that the game has are that
everything's really big.
Everything's very vertical.
You can like climb any surface with the grappling hook and stuff,
but not actually any surface.
So that would have been an improvement.
Make it so you can climb any surface.
Even bigger levels, even bigger monsters, more variety and choice,
because it's very linear.
There's a lot of obvious ways the game could be improved.
So they make a sequel and in the sequel,
because co-op games were all the rage at the time,
they just completely retool the game to be a co-op game.
And even though they retain all of like the weapons and controls and monsters
from the previous game, the level design is nothing like the first games level design.
And it's not really built in a way that works with the mechanics.
Like it's built to be they just took the mechanics of Lost Planet
and put them in a co-op shooter game, but they don't make sense in a co-op shooter game.
So it's incredibly fucking frustrating and broken.
Like it's a game that has some good ideas and moments where it kind of works.
But like it's just not it shouldn't have been done.
Like it was not the right IP to transform into a co-op game.
And so it got pretty lukewarm reviews and it didn't sell as well as the first game.
So then they make Lost Planet three.
And instead of making a game, Capcom just outsources it to some other studio.
This studio, here's here is everything I know about this studio.
They've made six games.
And if you go to the Wikipedia page, all it says about them is
they are known for having a 56 average on Metacritic.
And what company is this?
I don't remember what it's called, but like all they've made is shitty games.
Like all of their games, every single one of them has like a below 60 on Metacritic.
And that is the most noteworthy thing about the company.
So they make a third game that plays like it plays kind of like Mass Effect 3
if no one with any talent worked on the game.
Like if it if it was just a boring piece of shit.
This is Spark Unlimited Spark Unlimited, apparently.
Yes, Spark Unlimited.
This game is fun.
I played like the first 15 minutes of the game.
I was like, this is the worst game I've ever played in my life.
So, yeah, at that point, the idea of what Lost Planet is is just completely gone.
It's gone. Right.
You know, and like, and so you've got this first game that I would consider
like a strong seven to a light eight.
Like it's a very fine game.
It's not amazing.
And you can so easily imagine a perfect sequel, but it's not there.
Instead, the franchise is dead now.
I've lost the bureaucracy.
Yeah. Yep.
What a tragedy.
You know, I almost I almost feel bad for like game developers
who are put in a project that like corporate influence doesn't allow them
to like actually make the game to like be consistent with the fucking mechanics and shit.
Like, can you even imagine developing a game where like you're not thinking
about how to integrate the level design with the mechanics?
I can't even think about it.
But OK, no matter.
I mean, I feel like that mindset is sort of like a paint by numbers
because you're given the iconography, the characters, the types of things
that need to be in there because of like, let's borrow, you know, we have to have
this thing and that thing from that game or movie and put it in there
to link them because they're sequels and we'll do it kind of like they're not
thinking about building a game.
They're thinking about
cash it in. They're thinking about cash in an IP.
Yes, that, too. That, too.
I was like, I can't really think of like a lot of sequels that have disappointed
me, although, I don't know.
But what about Jack two?
I love Jack two.
But I was a kid at the time.
Jack X. Well, that's that's the thing I was going to think of.
There's going to talk about because like that feels like a spin off
because it's a different gameplay style in the same universe.
And I was thinking Mario 64.
I wouldn't consider a sequel to Mario, Super Mario World because of how
different it is.
And I would also consider that like a spin off technically, like like the 3D
Mario's were a spin off of the 2D Mario's because you can't really compare
one, you know, sequel sequentially to the next.
So let me ask you the way I think of sequels.
Would it would it change your opinion if instead Mario World was called Mario
four and then Mario 64 was called Mario five?
Would that change your view of it being a sequel?
Um, I think, I mean, the numbers thing is always like like hardwired to
think sequel, right?
Because that's just a word associated with numbered stuff.
So I guess I might.
But I if I thought about it, I probably would come to the same conclusion
because it's like, OK, it's about branding.
Branding is relevant as to whether
something is considered a sequel or not.
Franchises are terrible.
I hate franchises.
I hate the fact that things in a franchise can can can exist.
I know there's a sequel that you despite Ratchet Future Tools of Destruction.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Was wrong with that one.
PlayStation 3, there's a number of French stuff.
One of the Ratchet games from PS3 sucked.
I played all of them like last year.
One of them was really good.
One of them sucked balls.
I don't remember if it was future.
It was the first one that this was the first one.
It was future.
But there was one Ratchet and Clank game for the PS3 that came out
like later in the PS3 that had it was like a weird co-op game
that didn't play like Ratchet and Clank or something.
That that is definitely a spin off.
I don't know how much leniency I want to give to things that I would consider
a spin off. I still just think spin offs are gross.
Yeah, I think of I think of Ratchet deadlocked as a spin off.
And that's actually a good game.
Yeah, I've heard people like that one.
Yeah.
But anyway, fucking Ratchet and also Sly Cooper,
like they had great games on the PS2.
One, two, three, one, two, three, three games on the PlayStation 2.
Ratchet and Clank went to PlayStation 3
and it had another trilogy of games.
But because they knew they could make a trilogy of games,
the game, the first game ends on a cliffhanger,
which always pissed me off because it's not a complete story.
And you have to like that.
They're just like, yeah, we know you're going to buy all three of them.
So just fucking don't get the whole experience.
Yeah.
Agreed.
Also, it was just kind of shit in general.
I was under the impression it was like almost like a vignette game.
Like they it was only like 10 hours long, right?
Whereas like the previous Ratchet games had all been like 25 hours to get a hundred percent.
Yeah, it was it was it was really short.
The story was more stupid and the 3D
the like PlayStation 3 shiny, shiny, shiny, shiny, shiny, shiny textures
really annoyed me and and, you know, lens flares and stuff.
But the Sly games, Sly Raccoon, Sly Cooper, the gang, the gang.
They they look really good in the PlayStation 2
and in the PlayStation 3 games, they also look good.
Like the visuals weren't fucked and the animations were good.
It was just something it's definitely because it was a different studio.
But it doesn't it doesn't feel good.
It doesn't have the same like like a wit and and and like
story structure. It's just sort of like, oh,
when you're someone who doesn't know what's what's what's up when you don't have
the people there like when you don't have the people there
who like made the thing and really understand it.
Like you see this with like Tom Hewlett and the later like Silent Hill games.
Like the soul is just missing.
The even if even if it was never clear to anyone what actually made the games great,
something's you're never going to get everything,
especially the person like Tom Hewlett is like a self-avowed Silent Hill fanboy.
Like a fanboy is never going to fucking be able to like recreate it.
Yeah, it's always it's always with the creative minds like, like, you know,
George Lucas, he needs to be there a little bit.
And it's a fool's errand to even try to recreate it.
Just make something new. OK, but whatever.
Well, that's that's the funny thing.
Something I've grown to appreciate more and more.
The more I look at art and the more I know like the backgrounds of it is like
there really is a lot of art that could only have come from that one guy.
Damn right. Like no one else on planet fucking Earth could do it.
Or that one team because of just like the chemistry between them.
Maybe, you know, like maybe it was just at the boardroom meetings they had.
We're so magnetic that it spawned this this thing and like you can't recreate that.
You know, sometimes even they can't recreate that.
But imagine imagine if all of the PCP members
had like moved on and given their channels to people who, you know,
tried to be like each of all of us.
And then the PCP podcast was like it would be technically everyone kind of.
But it would be not even, you know, not even slightly the same.
That's an excellent. It might even be better, but like it's just.
You need you need the the brain power of the weird guy.
It's true. Yeah, it's true.
Um, Tom or Nate, you have a sequel that I've got something just to bounce off
of that of the last point you were just begging, I'll go into this.
And it's like, I'll give you a like time and place is so important for this.
So like a game that I kind of like Final Fantasy seven,
like a big theme in that whole game is like death and life after death.
And all of that was caused by Sakaguchi's fucking mom dying during development of the game.
And so they wrote it in this.
They made it part of the fucking story.
And like it's a huge thematic thing throughout the whole thing.
And only because of the particular circumstances there did that even happen.
So like trying to recreate that is whatever pointless.
But that that's what brings me to a little sequel you might have heard of
called Final Fantasy seven, Advent Children, direct sequel to Final Fantasy seven.
Yeah, of course.
And in a larger context, it's the entire compilation of Final Fantasy seven
that sort of counts like sequels, prequels, side stories, whatever.
The whole thing is incredibly offensive to me in every possible way.
It's them saying that, and of course, this extends to the remake as well.
I hear all these fucking people chatter in a way every fucking day about how
oh, they're going to have time to expand on the things they didn't get to.
And the original five is seven.
Don't you want to explore a final?
Don't you want to explore Midgard?
Don't you want to, I don't know, remember other things they wanted to put in
unless they wrote them down exactly, exactly.
Only you can maybe make a case that putting back cut content in
maybe could fit in there.
But even then, I wouldn't even want that necessarily.
Maybe I'd look at a case by case basis.
But like it's been like 25 fucking years or whatever, 30 years or something.
Like everyone's changed massively from the person they were
when the game was originally made, like they have no business meddling with this
shit. Somebody who fucking tells me Nomura is like qualified to remake
Final Fantasy seven get fucked.
Yes, I know he was heavily involved in the development of the characters
and even the shaping of much of the fundamentals of the personalities
of those characters.
He has no fucking business directing a goddamn remake of the game
because he's not fucking smart enough.
He's a corporate tool and a drawboy and he has no he's no fucking purpose
here, whatever, fuck these people.
If if if if a ukulele has taught me anything is it's the yes,
the getting the same guys to do the same thing still can have
different results if the people change because they can't help but change
because time we didn't even talk about that's the same environment.
Right. That's such a great point.
Like the ukulele is such a great little it's anecdotal, but it's a great
example of exactly what you just said.
They they literally got back the team back together.
But it had been like you said, 20 fucking years since they'd made
Banjo-Kazooie or whatever.
And apparently they didn't have a minute.
Didn't have it in them and I'm sure it wasn't literally everyone
who worked on Banjo-Kazooie.
And I'm sure I didn't have the budget of Banjo-Kazooie.
And I'm sure like, you know, it didn't have the corporate structure of
Rareware, a bunch of guys fucking around, you know, where who's their boss?
Who do they have to answer to at the end of the day?
Yeah, it's it's like if you want to make a fucking Kickstarter
repackers, nobody.
If you tell me about like like close as possible sequel, you need both
the artist and the like the corporate situation that they were in when
they made the thing in the first place.
Yeah. Yeah.
So they need the same sort of incentives.
Another thing I think is you have to like keep striking while the iron's hot.
Like when you when you have like 20 years removed from the original thing,
like these people grow, they change, they have different motivations and stuff.
There's no way I could create any of the shit on my YouTube channel.
There's no way I could make the same thing 20 years from now.
Of course, like there is no fucking way.
And like, even if that stuff ends up having like a huge impact on some people
and they still remember like the asterisk where sucks 20 years from now,
like, which there's no way.
But like if if that happens, there's no way I could just make another like,
oh, I'm going to finally do season two after 20 years.
Like, no, like fucking great example of this is for all of us.
None of us could make my little pony videos with the kind of enthusiasm we do.
Yeah, great. That's a great example.
Yeah, I would be fucking impossible because it's just I'm like it's not
that I've lost the abilities I had, but the the mindset isn't there.
And it's just like like just like the most important part.
Just that it's this is so fucking basic and so many people don't fucking get it.
So let me beat into your goddamn skulls.
Like just think about it, people.
Like fucking Nomura was the one who I believe as I was reading.
Still talking about.
I was just a great example.
Nomura was the guy who suggested that Aris die.
I believe it was him because I like there was discussion about like they were going
to have a character die, maybe be Tifa, maybe somebody else.
And I believe Aris was like his suggestion is like,
she should die, whatever.
And like like it's been 25 fucking years or whatever.
Like the man's a father now.
He's like a huge corporate like he's so ingrained in the corporatocracy of
Square Enix, this giant behemoth of a company, which does so much now,
so much more now than the small potatoes of making a fucking shitty JRPG series
that's nobody gives a shit about anymore.
You know, like he is a different fucking man.
He's not a maverick artist anymore.
Like like you could argue that he was.
I don't even know if he fucking was.
But like people fucking change and I'm so fucking sick of people saying that
like just because they've got Kitase, Nomura back to work on this or Grant
Kirk and Hope or whoever to work on fucking ukulele, it's going to be the same
shit. It's so fucking obviously not true.
It pisses me the fuck off.
The people don't get it.
Anyway, fuck the compilation of five has seven.
I will kill myself on the day that the remake comes out.
It's going to be great.
Looking forward to it.
OK, let's go.
You're going to go for fucking Mishima.
Yeah, you know, you're going to go into the skier.
You're going to fly like a helicopter into the Square Enix offices.
You fell yourself on the desk of Nomura.
Like it's going to be good to no avail.
Just as a symbol.
Yeah.
You know what the best set of sequels are for the like for what we were just
talking about is fucking Five Nights at Freddy's.
All of those ones that those are well received despite.
Yeah, despite what like what people like generally think of them as like a stupid
fucking piece of garbage series, they are actually like for the
people who like that sort of thing, they are great sequels and they continually
like because of because of how fast they're being like four months.
You got a new one or something.
It's ridiculous or something like that.
And it's like that they all build on the whole thing and it's like fucking
there's a movie at some point, I think.
Yeah, like this guy is no he knows what he's doing.
Hey, I respect.
Tom, you got a sequel that disappointed you.
Oh God, absolutely.
Is it Metroid 2 Metroid Prime 2 that you were tweeting about dropping earlier
tonight?
I don't I'm not a huge fan of some of the stuff Metroid Prime is doing.
But overall, I give it I give it a solid eight for sure.
Oh, OK, it's not it's not a piece of shit.
Um, God, what was this like 2002, 2003?
And I think I might have told the story before on the show.
But I was a young lad who had just gotten his PlayStation 2 like a year ago.
And I was so excited for this game to come out.
And I was an avid reader of EGM.
And so every month I would double make right to double make right to oh my God.
I've played I've played so much of the original.
It's like my favorite PS2 game.
Fucking I have not heard you tell that story.
I just figured it out.
The details.
Well, here's let me let me tell you about this day.
Yeah, I counted down the days.
I watched the trailer over and over again because the trailer was fucking sick.
And I love the way the art style.
It was so good.
And you could shoot guns in two directions.
That's so fucking cool.
Pretty cool.
It was the fucking hype is shit.
And and I like I don't have like money to buy games.
So I buy like one or two games a year.
And so like I made all my purchasing decisions from Electronic Gaming Monthly.
I subscribe that I love that magazine.
And so I would always read every single one of them cover to cover.
Like the little comics with the two agents.
That was that magazine.
Sue and Chen.
He still makes those comics.
He has a YouTube channel.
He does animations.
They're fantastic.
Oh, I follow him.
He's great.
Um, so I get I get the month's issue where and where they are going to review
Devil May Cry 2 and I flip it open.
And I and like before you read all the reviews, there's a page where they tell
you what the game of the month is and it's not Devil May Cry 2.
Oh, no.
And it was at that moment I knew something bad had happened.
Yeah, because they would have because because a game of that scale, it could
have been like a seven out of ten and they would have made it game with it.
Like, like, like it could have been legitimately a seven out of ten, but
they would have given it a 10 because it was that big.
Exactly.
It has to be like a real because they had they had run multiple stories on
the game leading up to its release.
That's how I like my gun so hard over this fucking misogynist gamer culture
can't handle a strong female character like Lucia.
They fucking hit her just because she's got a vagina.
It's time to accept the girls can be powerful too.
You piece of shit.
Oh my God.
But yeah, I flipped to it and it's like 6.5, 5.5.
Because they did they had three people review the games back then.
And it was like a two parade spread of just like this game blows nuts.
And we're just like, oh, no, I hate.
I just I've literally I've never been the same person since that was that was
actually my first devil may cry game.
I fucking dude, it was the worst.
And then I remember my friend bought it like at some point later.
And so I played at his house and I was just like in awe of how bad they
fucked everything up.
That was like there were some cool ideas in there, too, which
which made it sting even worse because they had a dedicated dodge button
because like dodging was kind of like a cluster fucking the original.
Because you had to like hold down both shoulder buttons and shit.
And it was weird, but they had like just a dodge button.
And it made like everything so much cooler.
But like, yeah, the guns were shit.
Like there was the game feel was terrible.
Like the hits were awful.
They changed the way the combo system worked and it was really bad.
And oh, it was it was did you have to go back and beat those games
as a devil may cry fan?
Just out of I have beat I've beaten them all but two because I just can't get
through it. It's just so painfully bad.
Why was to so bad?
Like what happened in production?
Did some of it was not come a Mia or whatever.
He didn't direct.
I know he had nothing to do with it.
They passed it off to a new studio and they clearly had no idea what they
were doing. So did he come back for three?
Yes, I believe he came back for three because three was fucking amazing.
And like, yeah, it's like Dark Souls.
It's true. It's true.
You can tell that they knew that the last one was so bad.
They like, wait, kicked everything up to 11.
And if it is, if it is literally Dark Souls,
what was Kamiya doing during Devil May Cry 2's development?
Oh, that's check. That is a damn good question.
Did he work on he was beautiful seven or that have been later?
I don't I'm going to check.
I'm going to look at his beautiful Joe is too long later.
Resident Evil Zero.
Now, Devil May Cry, Resident Evil Zero, beautiful Joe Phoenix,
right? An ace attorney trials and tribulations.
What the fuck? Oh, voice actor for Godot in the Japanese version.
Never mind.
Yeah, either Resident Evil Zero or beautiful Joey is working out at the time.
It's probably Resident Evil.
Both much better games than Devil May Cry 2.
So time will spend. I'll give him that.
Yeah. But yeah, oh, my God, it's just
it's the level of disappointment.
Just it can't be described in words.
It was that was when my child.
He didn't work on Devil May Cry 3, though.
That's not. No, he did not. No, he did not.
Somebody else really.
So yeah, somebody else who is also a jury.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's deadly. The spiritual
the spiritual sequel to that man worked on Devil May Cry 3.
The same guy who did three do four then
because like it's interesting you say that that man, my favorite
character of all time, I don't know what his name is.
I don't know that.
That's the main villain of Guilty Gear X.
That man character that man.
Gabe, you are aware that that's a character or were you just
were you memeing? No, no, he was not at all.
There's a guy. Now you know, there's the main villain in Guilty Gear
is literally named that man.
God, I fucking love it.
That's not my favorite thing about Guilty Gear by far.
Rad Khan Awakening.
I'm doing a lecture on the lore of Guilty Gear.
Get ready. I can't wait.
I can't wait.
It looks it looks like DMC three was done by a guy.
It was actually done by the same guy who did DMC two.
What? Yeah, this guy.
I guess you've got a shit together.
Hideaki Itsuno and he directed
Yeah, we cry two through four and Dragon's Dog.
Wow. OK, I guess they just like, I don't know,
figured their shit out or something.
Wow, that that confuses the hell you know what?
You know what? I kind of respect that.
I kind of respect that this guy like, you know,
he pulled himself up from the from the from the abyss.
From the apparently he was only brought on
to Devil May Cry two midway through development
to replace an unidentified director
dissatisfied by how their work on the game was coming together.
Basically, he had to salvage the project from somebody.
He's the guy who brought the dodge button.
I got you. Yeah, I'm sure that's right.
Absolutely.
Fast. We went we he probably went.
OK, this game is completely unplayable.
But at least if we put in a dodge button,
beatable contribution, it was just really fantastic.
Atrocious. But yeah, that was my biggest sequel let down.
You know, it's funny.
The first Devil May Cry I played was Devil May Cry two.
And I remember thinking what the fuck is going on?
I'm not going to play this game anymore.
Yeah, you made the right call.
Good series. God damn it. Fuck.
Devil May Cry five.
When total gaming Brit, I was going to call him total biscuit.
I'm at the gaming Brit.
I've given up hope every E3.
I'm just like, is this going to be the year and it's never the year.
This is now the Devil May Cry cast.
We've really what's what's each of your favorite sequel
or one that's interesting in some way.
I got one. Sure.
All right, go for it.
So my there's a ton of great fucking fantastic sequels.
Halo two was amazing.
But but the one that I think really fucking blew my mind
in terms of just like taking a good idea and making it so much better
was Zone of the Enders, the second runner. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. That's absolutely true.
The game is the kid.
Can we just appreciate how fucking good that intro for that game is?
Is that like they build up this whole thing of just like, oh,
the Jehuti is so much more like aerobatic
and it can move around, you can shoot multiple guys.
And it's not just one on one combat anymore, but they give you like 10 minutes.
I can't aerodynamic and acrobatic.
I think it's both you correcting Tom's pronunciation.
So so. But the great thing of that game is at the beginning,
they just trap you in the shitty mining mech.
And you have to walk down a straight path for 10 minutes.
It is like, oh, my God, please end me.
And then you get into Jehuti and it's so much fucking better.
And you're like, oh, my God.
And then you lock on like 50 dudes at once.
And it's the greatest.
And then at the end of the game, you get the fucking Nitro Cannon or whatever
the fuck it's called. Oh, my God.
It was the fucking best.
That whole that whole Anubis fight was so fucking awesome.
Yeah, I gave fucking rules.
Kojima Productions, Zone of the Enders 3.
When I'm ready for it, baby, laying on me.
Wasn't there a lost in concept about that or something?
There was a hyper bit hero.
Yeah, it was like a thing that was supposed to happen.
I got to check that out again.
I forget the details.
Everything good. I don't get.
I just made a vlog yesterday about how all my favorite gaming series are dead.
I have no leg in the race, including just like your precious Dreamcasts
and your Sega consoles.
Yeah, that's everything I like dies.
So I'm expecting all of you to die soon.
What is a good ongoing game?
I guess you don't like Zelda or Mario, right?
Like, I think the only the only thing is Metroid.
Metroid's the only game that I still like.
And that like, I mean, I just got revived like two days ago.
Exactly.
So now that I'm into it, I'm sure Prime for a bomb.
It'll be terrible.
It's not going to be done by retro studios, by some fucking
what's the guys who did lots of planet?
They're going to be doing.
Spark unlimited or something.
Yeah, it's going to be a shit show.
All right, let me let me give you my favorite sequel of all time.
I've talked about it a lot.
But but once upon a time, there was a piece of shit called Gun Buster.
And then they did everything right for once and made
Die Buster like 15 years later or whatever.
Now, Gun Buster is fantastic.
And the fact that I like Die Buster even more or rather aim for the top one
Gun Buster and aim for the top two Die Buster is just a testament
to how fucking great Die Buster is.
So Gun Buster, everybody.
It's the old-ass Amino directed 80s anime about Amino.
What do I say?
Amino directed.
I say Ahiru fucking.
What's the man's name?
I know, right?
Whatever. That guy, he directed a piece of shit anime.
It was really good.
I loved it about about being in space, a bunch of sexy girls having
hard work and guts, and then they travel close to the speed of light.
So relatively gets all fucked and everybody ages.
And it's the best thing ever.
But then then his his little deputy animator guy, what's his name?
Digi director Kasia Sudamaki, that's his protege protege.
That's the word made fully coolie.
And then he made Die Buster and it was it it capitalized on everything
that was great about the original in terms of like continuing the narrative
in an interesting way by continuing like the how they were.
Humanity has dealt with the threat of the space monsters post the black hole
bombs, you know, eruption, some unspecified time ago.
And oh, the fact they don't tell you when Die Buster takes place.
And then the ending, oh my God, and then as no, no, my favorite
wife of all time, besides Nika Robin.
Yes, you know, Kasia Sudamaki, that director, he just finally made another OVA.
Like what's what's the OVA early last early this year or late last year,
two episodes called Dragon Dentist.
And I haven't seen it yet, but I've heard it's fantastic.
But it's the first because he's one who's he's one who's been fucking up
on the Ava rebuild movies for 10 years, but he finally did something else.
And Dragon's Dentist.
That's very exciting.
I should watch them.
It was originally the first, you know, the the Studio Car Animator
Expo. Yes, Mimi me came from like the first one of those was the original
Dragon Dentist short and they expanded that into a two episode OVA.
I think each episode is like 45 minutes long, too.
I should watch all of those, including the original.
Well, I can do that guy is a legend and I fucking love him.
And Die Buster is like the coolest, comfiest, beautiful, love everything about it.
Anime of all time, great sequel, great sequel.
There you go. It can be done, everybody.
And I'm a big anti-sequel guy, but like there are times when the stars align
and people just do it right, which is why I would just I would heavily discourage
doing it. But if you're somebody who's got like a genius idea and you're like,
no, listen to me, here's my proposal for the sequel.
I am going to use the themes that were here and artistically show you how I'm
going to capitalize them and make them better than ever and more relevant and
emotionally tie my story into that one, then approve.
And that's why we're all looking forward to Fooly Cooly 2.
It's going to be the best thing ever.
Well, Kazia Saramaki is not directing that.
Yeah, unfortunately.
I believe the guy who directed Psycho Pass is directing Fooly Cooly 2.
Even if he was directing it, that wouldn't necessarily make me any.
Well, OK, it wouldn't help a little bit, but, you know, it's been 20 fucking years or whatever.
OK, I'm done. That's it. Die Buster.
Oh, man, Hippo, you got one?
Great sequel.
I've got a few.
Like I was trying to think because a lot of my favorite games just happened to be
the first in a series, but I do have one.
It's a it's a Shrek 2 the game on PC.
It's actually terrible.
Don't play any game of Shrek 2.
Oh, I just want to.
Incidentally, Davoo did map out a chart for us
of the quality of the Shrek films over time, which is very convenient that.
Yes, we'll see the problem with his.
Well, OK, it's the quality consensus chart.
Oh, right. Consensus is that Shrek 1 is above the good line.
Shrek 2 is way above the good line.
Shrek 3 is below the good line.
Yes. Shrek 4 is bottomed below the chart bad, right, as well as Puss in Boots.
But the problem with this, while this is the consensus, the consensus is wrong.
And Shrek 1 is in a horror film.
Absolutely untrue.
Shrek 1 is great.
Oh, man, everyone.
You watch it. Hi, everyone.
Go watch that.
No, that's why that.
Do you not know the story info that I know that's what you said?
That's why I watch it.
So it's just watching a hundred.
No, all you need to watch in that movie is the epic video on, I believe,
a little channel called Gibb and take that's Shrek without Shrek or like Shrek
until Shrek appears or whatever it is.
Yeah, it's Shrek.
But every time Shrek appears on screen, the movie.
Yeah, that's the one.
I give it literally is like some and that's the best bang of the outhouse opens
and cuts to black. Oh, fuck, it's the best.
It's the best.
I have like a movie one.
Lord of the Rings, the two towers, I think is the best Lord of the Rings film.
Oh, yeah.
It's it's it's so it's so I've seen it on TV too many times, though.
That makes it a bad movie that the personal problem, dude.
Yeah, you're not wrong. You're not wrong.
What about the second one makes it your favorite one?
The Riders of Rohan.
But the thing that the thing like the first one's great, obviously,
there's the there's the big there's the guy you shall not go across.
And it smashes the bridge and and you know, there's the Mines of Moria.
It's like really cool.
The Nazgul, you know, he's got the second one has the trees
and the Saruman and the big attack.
And it's got the Battle of Helms deep.
I was about to say Jesus Christ, that's a big castle.
Helms deep is the obvious, the most obvious reason.
I think for me, it's hard to separate the three
because like I think all of them have strengths and weaknesses
that have to do with the fact that they are part of a series.
Like to me, I'd prefer to think of that as one nine hour story as opposed to sequels.
Well, like true. They're kind of all one.
Like there's there's nothing significantly different about them.
They're all just like the same story being told across three movies.
You know, I guess.
But the way I've always like felt is that, you know,
the first two were sort of out when I was young.
And then the third one took a while to come out and it had elephants and weird things.
And I just like that there's ghosts here.
I don't understand what's going on.
I didn't understand any of it.
So I didn't like that.
I thought the Hobbit unexpected journey was good,
but the desolation of Smough really really kicked things up a notch.
That's actually the opposite.
Like I liked that first Hobbit movie, but the second one I just gave up.
That's what I hear people.
Watch the third one. Yeah, yeah.
I still like it.
Delete yourselves.
Yeah, I've heard the third one.
Where do they kill the fucking dragon?
Which one is that at the very beginning of the third one?
Which is why it's the worst.
That's why that's also why it's the entire second movie is entirely dedicated
to hunting the dragon and it ends before they fucking fight it on a total anti-climax.
It is the shittiest ending I've ever seen.
Five minutes into the next one, they just kill it.
And it's just why didn't you just have the movie be five extra minutes?
Because they know it's the worst one and they wanted people to fucking see it.
You're not wrong, you're not wrong.
It kind of reminds me of like in the Gurren Logan like film adaptations of the show.
Like so the whole fight, this is like the most disgusting thing ever.
Like the first film ends like at the point where like Simone becomes a man,
which is like a fantastic climax, but then they compress the entire battle
against Lord Genome, which was like literally the best part of the entire show
except for the actual final climax and they make a fucking clip show out of it
at the beginning of the second movie.
What the fuck were they thinking?
What a mistake. What a fucking mistake.
Wait, did they I thought there was like a super fucking well animated version
of the fight with Genome in the second movie?
Absolutely not.
Like he walks down the front of his mech and all that.
That happens in the movie, that happens in the show too.
And maybe I'm thinking of the show then.
Yeah, I mean, the show fight is fantastic.
It's it's like one of the best points of the whole show.
But, you know, they fucked up in the movie.
Trust me.
In terms of in terms of video games, I can't really decide between
Wretched and Clank 2, Sly 2, Sly 3 and Ape Escape 2.
So all of those are like like really good.
The thing about I think video game sequels have a much higher propensity
for being like better because you don't necessarily
just use the the stories and stuff.
Yeah. And you're usually like really tweaking the game play.
By the way, guys, I just wanted to to let you know, I'm looking here
on the wiki for the Hobbit films.
The total budget for all three films was six hundred and twenty five
million dollars for all three of these films.
Just as bad as I would have thought, actually, for all three.
For all. Yeah, it's all three combined.
Look at the fucking look at the cost of like pirates three.
I will. That movie is like three hundred and fifty million dollars by itself.
All right, you reminded me of pirates.
The second one is not second.
The second one is no way.
The second was no, as soon as Johnny, not Johnny Depp,
fucking as soon as yeah, the second or third one are not great.
The first one is a legend and I love it.
The first one is amazing.
But I think second and third as like a as like a sequence
to each other. I mean, actually, it's they're good.
It's a fascinating example, actually, because the entire Pirates of the Caribbean
idea is based on a fucking ride at Disneyland and they made it into a movie.
So they just obviously had some like good script writers or somebody who thought
like, yeah, let's make a fun action adventure.
And then like it was the further corporatization as like those ideas dried up
and then like Davey Jones or something. Fine, do that.
And it was not as good. Yeah.
I got to watch them again.
Yeah, the first one is great.
The first one is so good.
I watched it recently.
It definitely holds up.
But this is just just a little bit of a level does not hold up though.
I like it.
The like there's like a part in the third one.
I remember liking the third one because of how stupid and complicated it is.
And and and all the like the crisscrossing alignments and like the stuff.
It is like, oh, I feel so smart.
This is the great Gatsby guy.
I'm really you really need a high IQ to understand the parts of the Caribbean
three. Right. Very true.
Four is four is way off.
Get out of it. I heard five was OK, though.
There that was what I haven't even seen it.
I just go. I just watched.
I thought I heard Jesse. Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
I think Jesse liked it.
So I've been just kind of combing through my favorites list.
And I've got two sequels.
I got to mention the first one and this one I'm hesitant to count.
But it's K on season two.
And the reason I'm hesitant to count it is that it's just continuing to adapt
to the manga, you know, it came out a year later.
It's essentially just a second season.
But the ramp up in production value for season two and just the way that
it's so clear they were taking it more seriously is what makes like it's
when you get to season two that K on really starts to feel like a masterpiece.
You know, yeah, like the first season is really good.
And especially rewatching it when you know all the characters.
It's a ton of fun.
But season two is where it gets like it becomes Kino, essentially, you know,
it's it's really interesting thinking about that as like an idea,
because like in real world terms, season two is a sequel.
And you would think and talk about it as a sequel,
but it is just continuing.
Yeah, something that would have been there.
Like you if you get rid of season two, it's like Dragon Ball and Dragon Ball Z.
It is just one.
But it is a new project, you know, because they like re you know, they're like,
yeah, but what I'm et cetera, et cetera.
What I'm getting at is like, there's like, should a sequel be something
that was not necessarily planned and then they decide to do.
That's kind of how I tend to think.
Like if I mean, if the manga is one ongoing work and the two seasons
of the anime are basically the same, it's just like, like, for instance,
Food Wars is a show that's airing its third season right now.
And like if you watch all of Food Wars all the way through,
you're not going to notice like a huge difference across the three seasons.
It's more like, oh, we're just doing another one.
You know, like the last one was successful
enough that we can do another chunk, but it's all the same manga.
It's all the same story.
Whereas, for instance, a Ghost in the Shell standalone complex season two.
It's an original show.
And like while it's cribbing a lot of ideas from the same manga,
like it's a it's a whole new script that they had to create from scratch
and like tell a whole different story based on having made the first one.
So I tend to think of that as more of a sequel.
In Kayon's case, like like half of the anime is original content, if not more.
In fact, in season two, almost all of it's original to the show,
because they're adapting two volumes of manga into 26 episodes of anime.
And like just adding in tons of shit and making it more cinematic.
So like to me, it's not a sequel in the sense of like,
oh, it's a different story, but it's a sequel in the sense of
the first season allowed us to do this with season two.
Like now we can make it the show.
It was always like could have been like realized the potential of it,
which is kind of what we're saying.
Video game sequels allow you to do right so much, you know,
which brings me to my second example.
Dark Souls 3 fucking per like even I would even have said
Dark Souls is a spiritual sequel to Demon's Souls, pretty obviously.
And Bloodborne as a spiritual sequel to Dark Souls, all fantastic.
But there is enough of a leap in style.
Dark Souls 3 is just straight up.
It's it's the new Dark Souls and it's fucking amazing.
I enjoyed it.
Sorry, I don't mean to interrupt,
but I just I don't want to bring up something about that.
So you and I and Jesse did our Dark Souls 3 PCP a while ago.
And like we all agree that it's fantastic and we loved it.
And that was even before the DLC came out that made it even better.
And I just wanted to ask, have you seen I'm quite perplexed by like,
I see a level of negativity on Dark Souls 3 out in the world
that absolutely baffles me.
And I don't know what the nature of it is,
but I see all the time rankings of like Dark Souls 3 like way below
like above Dark Souls 2, but way below one.
And I don't understand why I think I could understand it
if you are someone who plays the games over and over and over again
because Dark Souls 3 definitely has less choice.
Yeah, that's not wrong.
Like, like I feel like personally,
Dark Souls 1 is like easy to just go back to and on the other hand,
despite having less stuff, the game feel is improved.
And like online play, obviously, is way easier.
So like there's if you're just talking about easier,
but is it as do people enjoy it as much?
Like, yeah, there's there's always there's like because
when it comes to stuff like that, where people play it ad nauseam forever,
it really changes their opinions of it.
You know, it's kind of like how you have people who
like anybody who has ever been ever a fan of League of Legends.
If they were into it for more than a couple of years,
then their opinion of it is that it's the worst game ever made,
but they've played thousands of hours of it.
Oh, my God. Yeah, go ahead.
Good because like you can't you can't develop
like like when you're first playing it,
you're just seeing it for what it is.
Like it's a fun game.
But like as you begin to see all the ones and zeros in the matrix
and you really like analyze everything about it,
you'll find reasons to not like it and stuff.
And I think with with Dark Souls,
that game just had so many weird things in it that you could do
and so much sequence breaking that like you can play it over and over again
and usually have somewhat of a different experience.
You know, Dark Souls 3 doesn't have that ability in the same way.
But I'm not someone who's ever going to play a game
more than once every year or two.
So that doesn't affect me at all.
You know, on that way, I would see.
OK, go on.
The way I would see Dark Souls 3 is is like the undertale
of the Dark Souls franchise in that it's a great game to play through.
But it's I don't need to go back and play Undertale again.
Like it's not that sort of a game.
Dark Souls of the Undertale franchise, you know, what?
Homestuck Act 5, which is what I was going to say is my favorite.
But my might be the best sequel to an act in Homestuck was Act 5, Act 2.
That's the literal peak of which one is that hippo hippo.
So hold on, we need to clarify this before this becomes the main comment on the video.
What you mean by I don't have to go back and play Undertale again
is like in the like after having played it five times, right?
Like like it's a game that necessitates playing it over and over again.
For at least I mean, I mean, once you've done the stuff,
yeah, there's no that the gameplay is not something you would go back to.
Not that I'm saying that wasn't the comment we get.
I'm not saying in that way that Dark Souls 3
isn't fun to play like mechanically.
It's just like I would love like just to play just running around
and hitting things in Dark Souls 3.
But going through the levels again is like, yeah, been through them
in the exact same way every time.
You're not wrong.
Yeah, I did it because I played through it twice the second time
just to do the big sequence break of like fighting the dancer first
because it's easy to do that in New Game Plus.
But yeah, beyond that, there's not like a radically like Dark Souls one
that game kept getting better as time passed
because you kept learning about new crazy shit you could do with it.
Like that was what got me so hype about the game,
even though I hadn't even played it for a long time.
Let's just seeing people like put together videos of like,
here's everything you can do before the gargoyles
and it's like a crazy amount of shit you could do.
And he's like, oh, my God, have you seen that streamer?
I forget his name who does like a challenge runs
and he's done like every single challenge run possible,
like not using the left analog stick or the right analog stick
to move the camera and like just plays the whole game like that.
Fascinating or playing with incredible with the fucking rock band drums.
You know, though, this completely reminds me of a sequel
that I suppose Dabuster 2 is my favorite sequel ever,
but only because of like the whatever doesn't matter.
But the point is, I was going to say,
Kingdom Hearts 2 is also a tremendous sequel
that is one of my favorite things in the world.
And it's interesting what you were saying, Digi,
about like the whole replay issue of playing things over and over.
And Kingdom Hearts 2 is so fascinating
because it is kind of the absolute most boring the first time you play it.
And every time you play it afterward,
it gets better and better and better
because the core fundamentals of the gameplay are so unbelievably tight
and scientific and calculated and perfected in that game
that you've got these massive communities. Yes, you're going to have to
like when we live in the same city, you're going to have to sit me down
and like guide me through Kingdom Hearts 2.
The only way I'm ever going to play it is if you sit there next to me
and like explain to me everything about the game while I'm playing.
That's the only way I'll enjoy it. I would be so thrilled to do that.
But I'll give you a quick tip.
The first time I played it was a friend of mine trying to force me to play it.
Like the same way he sat next to me,
but he didn't explain anything because he's terrible at explaining things.
So I just sat there and complained about it for four hours and he laughed.
Yes, I suffered.
I'll give you a quick tip, though,
that will aid you and anyone else out there who wants to get into Kingdom Hearts 2
and not suffer through it.
Just literally skip every cutscene.
Just skip them all. Don't give a shit.
Oh, thank you.
Holy shit. Just do that.
That's the greatest permission anyone has ever given me for a game.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
Skip every single one.
Now I want to play it.
Yeah, and you will have fun.
You'll have fun if you just follow this one simple tip of not giving a fuck
about anything anyone says in that game.
The man who did the full presentation on the story of Kingdom Hearts,
advocating, I mean, all of the cuts.
There's a time that's just his ploy to get to watch that video.
That video, like the takeaway for the video was none of this shit matters.
That's why there's there's a time solving you.
There's a time when you when when a man is forced to face the reality
of the human psyche and just say no one wants to sit through this shit.
We've just got to I want people to play Kingdom Hearts 2,
but I understand the reality that no one fucking wants to
unless they skip all of this shit.
You are legitimately a hero for that.
There are not many fans of a game who will tell you that.
Well, you know what?
Yeah, it's because I've watched a lot of speed runs and like the speed run community.
Like, yeah, they don't give a shit.
They just they just like those people just want to get to to the fun stuff.
And like here, let me just give you a little taste of one of the fascinating
things that you discover about Kingdom Hearts 2.
If you dig past like all this bullshit on the top,
there is a concept called revenge values as it's been termed by the community,
which is this thing where every boss.
OK, so this is a huge difference between like birth by sleep and Kingdom Hearts
2 that the retards who love birth by sleep don't understand.
And it's that in birth by sleep, like enemies never get stunned
no matter what you hit them with.
They never get stunned, whereas in Kingdom Hearts 2,
enemies bosses specifically can get stunned all the times.
And this is what makes boss fights fun.
Enemy bosses can get stunned, but they have this thing called a revenge value.
And it's specifically that when they're stunned,
if you hit them a certain number of times, like like five or 10 or whatever,
at that point, they will immediately snap out of being stunned and start fighting again.
So it's it's managing the enemy's revenge values in very particular ways
that allows you optimize the damage you're dealing to them and utilize certain
strategies are as like this is the most advanced way to be a speed runner
and calculate how to like scientifically beat from the best while feeling
like a Kingdom Hearts keyblade slinging God.
That's what makes Kingdom Hearts 2 so much fun.
Find out this kind of shit.
But there you go.
Oh, anyway, Tom, what's a sequel you really like?
Did we get to you yet?
Yeah, I said Zone of the Unders, second runner.
Oh, right. You went first.
I do have a another kind of topic I wanted to bring up
and see if you guys had any thoughts on.
OK, this specifically deals with game sequels,
but I suppose it can apply to anything because there are some games that I really like.
The two the three examples that really come to mind are Devil May Cry, Halo,
and to an extent, I guess Ninja Gaiden, but not as much
because there's only two games in that series before they got chickened.
But like when you have you enjoy the first game
and it has like a specific feel and then the sequel tweaks the feel significantly.
And then that just becomes the default feel for the series.
And then you kind of lose a little bit of what made the first one great
because you play Devil May Cry one, then you play three because two doesn't exist.
And the feel is way different.
Like you have the style system, the way the work is different.
And then and then you go to four and four feels exactly the same.
And then you play Halo one to Halo two, Halo two overfines everything.
It changes the way it feels.
Then three feels exactly the same.
It's the very same way. Yeah. Yeah.
I totally know what you mean.
So like, do you guys do you experience that?
What are your thoughts on that?
Because I definitely feel like there's a little bit that's lost in that transition sometimes.
I can't think of many examples where it's worse.
After like, I mean, in a game like Devil May Cry,
like obviously they tried to change things for the second one and it failed.
They changed things back to the first one, but a little different and it worked.
And like everyone considers Devil May Cry three to be the best Devil May Cry.
So like, even though I think one and three are both worth playing
because they're so different, like, I think it's, you know,
three is going to be the one everybody loves.
And so, of course, they're going to copy that when they make the sequel,
though it's almost a shame to not keep experimenting,
which Devil May Cry 4 does with Nero's grabbing abilities and stuff.
I think Nero is like way more fun than playing as Dante to be.
Yeah, the Devil May Cry is just fucking great.
Yeah, I don't know if you've watched the gaming Brits like endless videos
on Devil May Cry, but you should. You should, yeah.
I have pretty great.
It's his purpose in life.
He just became a cooler person because.
His main thing is he talks about Devil May.
Like you can watch his whole, like you can watch the video
where he gets into the franchise and then the video from a year later
where he's like an expert in it.
And then you watch him just continually never shut up about it
over the course of the rest of his video.
But to your point there, Tom, like I said before,
Kingdom Hearts 2 really did the same thing that you're describing
that like Devil May Cry 3 did to its series.
And I always say when I'm talking about these games,
Kingdom Hearts 1 and Kingdom Hearts 2 are by far the best games in that series.
And obviously I like Kingdom Hearts 2 overall, but even Kingdom Hearts 2,
excuse me, lost a lot of what made Kingdom Hearts 1 really good,
like specifically like the platforming challenges that, you know,
you get abilities to overcome.
And so like there has been an abandonment of a lot of the stuff
that made Kingdom Hearts 1 good, even though they have at no point since,
you know, since after Kingdom Hearts 2,
have they reached the level of quality that Kingdom Hearts 1 or 2 was at.
So like and it does frustrate me that it seems like there's people
stupidly trying to just recreate Kingdom Hearts 2 over and over again
without like knowing how or really like doing the research
into what made that game good.
And like nobody's paying attention at all to like what made Kingdom Hearts 1
good because we've all just moved on because there's like sequels.
And that's super frustrating.
And so I totally get the the feeling you're talking about.
Another franchise that did this in Hippo.
I'd be curious to know if you think this was if you think anything was lost
in the transition here, Ratchet and Clank,
because the first first and second Ratchet and Clank games feel pretty fucking different.
The second game really refocuses as a shooter and and all the ones from then on.
I think the way I see Ratchet and Clank 2 is an improvement
on absolutely everything in Ratchet and Clank 1.
I agree. Just like and it got rid of or no,
it expanded on the things that Ratchet and Clank 1 had like bits of and bits of
like the the spaceship battles.
There's just two parts of that in Ratchet and Clank 1 and in Ratchet and Clank 2.
It's now a mode. It's like a mini game.
So I think that was like in like that.
If that was the status quo for like the PS3 games, that would have been good.
You know, if all the PS3 games were like Ratchet and Clank 2, you're right about that.
I like that. But what the fuck about Jack like Jack 1 versus Jack 2?
Talk about a transformation.
But it's but it's Jack 3.
Isn't Jack 3 also a huge transformation from Jack 2?
So it's not like the reality is really is an interesting thing.
Jack like when I was a little baby boy
and I didn't know what video games were and I just played them.
What a hellish existence. I had Jack 1.
I had I had Jack 1 and then Jack 2 came out
and I got Jack 2 and it was so different.
But I didn't know that sequels were supposed to feel kind of the same.
So I just thought it was cool and then Jack 3 came out as the same sort of thing.
So I don't really I don't know.
I think that the main thing was Jack 1 was a platformer through and through.
Just about jumping and punching and jumping and jumping.
And then Jack 2 introduced vehicles, guns,
edgy like transformation sequences
and Jack 3 also has those things.
I want to I think I think like for the
it's cool. I like it. I don't dislike it at all.
I want to jump into Tom was saying this might just be for video games.
But no, it's definitely true of like long running franchises that this happens.
And it can be really fascinating.
For instance, I think Dragon Ball kind of had.
Oh, yeah, of course, original Dragon Ball is like a funny little adventure
comedy and then like everything since then is like epic.
What's funny about a huge fucking conversation with my friend about how
Goku is a terrible main character because of that transition.
I had a whole video about that.
He did. And you know, it's funny, though, is that that transformation
actually wasn't even within a sequel like in Japan.
That's just Dragon Ball like all the way up just happened.
Yeah, but then Dragon Ball Super.
It does feel like a very stark contrast.
I mean, they kept the same name in the manga, but like Dragon Ball was supposed to end.
Oh, was it really? OK.
They made him. It was supposed to end multiple times.
Like the story behind Dragon Ball is pretty fucked.
I only know like this very surface details.
But like Goku was supposed to die and Gohan was supposed to be the main character
after Cell. Hey, question. Back.
Just the thing I remember was that the way Dragon Ball ends is very,
very similar to the way Dragon Ball Z ends, which is like he just goes off
and he's implied to have more adventures, but he just doesn't want to talk about.
Yeah, right. And that's what Dragon Ball was going to be ending there.
But then he came back and there was.
Hey, does Dragon Ball end with Goku as an adult or is he still a kid?
I he's he's like a young adult.
He's like in his 20s. Yeah.
Yeah, like I remember him.
I thought he had his final fight with like King Piccolo.
That was the thing.
He had he had his final fight with King Piccolo with Piccolo's son,
who we know as Piccolo. Oh, right.
Yeah, like the great Demon King Piccolo was like the big bad guy of Dragon Ball.
And he beat him and then his son came back and they fought in the martial arts
tournament and then Chichi came and said, you promised me we'd marry.
And then they went off and we didn't see the wedding in the manga.
But that's like now Goku's going to get married and that's the end of Dragon Ball.
Bye. So did he end with Piccolo's son on friendly terms?
I mean, obviously we see how Dragon Ball Z.
I know I get into Dragon Ball.
I'm just curious.
They don't end on friendly terms, they hate each other.
Yeah, like it starts.
They start with Raditz because they're they're not their enemies, right?
They're right.
He has to like, right, right.
The thing was like a Goku, like the son of Piccolo,
I keep thinking of him as that because that's what he is.
Because he came out of an egg.
He he came to the martial arts tournament
and he tried to kill everyone and Goku eventually beat him.
But then he says, you know,
he got a Senzu bean is like, thanks, guys, I won.
I won the tournament finally.
That's that's literally canonically the first time he won the tourney.
Because he's still played by the rules right until the very end,
even though fucking everyone was evacuated and everything was destroyed.
But then he gave a Senzu bean to Piccolo and Piccolo was like,
really, and he just ran away.
So it's like it's implied that he will be a villain forever.
But he's he's like, oh, I respect you or something.
That's cool. That's cool.
I'm trying to think of some more examples of this.
Another one that is kind of like that is Ghost in the Shell,
just in that like the original manga is so much goofier
than like any other adaptation of it.
Like the original manga definitely has way more of a sense of humor
and more like loose with its characters and designs and everything.
And it's like it's just more of a pulp adventure with like really hard sci-fi.
You are 100 percent right.
It's just that like I in my mind,
I have them so partitioned as like different,
like like real alternate universes as opposed to sequels.
But you're not wrong. I mean, yeah.
I mean, some some of those sequels we're talking about.
I guess all all the ones we've talked about like a rise is obviously like different
and then stand alone complex like like the major herself is like totally different.
I know it's a prequel and it's all fucked up.
And yeah, but like just just the idea of how the franchise
like if the original film had been like more accurate to the manga's tone.
Yeah, then I feel like it was not at all like I don't know if it would have become a success.
But like whether it did or not,
that's probably how Ghost in the Shell would have been from then on.
Right. Like not that the TV show is exactly like the movie or anything.
Like the TV show definitely adds more levity in.
But like the fact that it even is such a serious military show.
Oh, yeah. Like like it's because that movie had set the press.
Like, that's what people identify in Ghost in the Shell.
In Ghost in the Shell, the major is way more informed as a character
by the movie's Motoko than the manga's Motoko. No doubt, no doubt.
The manga's Motoko is just like a goofy, like she is the best version of Motoko.
She's always got like boyfriends and stuff.
She is great. It's great.
I fucking love her. I like I like them all.
I like them all.
She fucks around and cracks jokes and like it's just way way more human.
Is a literal sex worker.
A literal sex worker makes sex software.
It's great. She's the best.
Yeah. Well, shit, guys.
Are we are we done? Are we done with the questions?
I think we can't we can't have a podcast about sequels
without taking a stab at our good friend, Mel Gear Solid 5, The Phantom Pain.
Oh, of course. I hate you forever.
Of course. And and and that's that's the biggest disappointment
after Definitely Cry was Mel Gear. I hate you.
Oh, you fucking fanboys.
Why can't you just turn off your brain and enjoy this sequel like the rest of us?
What the fuck? Let's get into questions.
Student of Ethereum says on a scale of one to ten, which
I pick oh, wait, I say a little academia, little academia.
Got him. Got him.
Yeah. Enough of that.
I'm interested in this. OK.
This guy just seems concerned for like concerned for us.
That's why I'm getting out of this.
OK. Me cool man asks, when was the last time you talked to your parents?
For me, it was like today.
For me, it was like four days ago.
I talked to them for like a whole hour on the phone.
I don't talk to my parents that I can go like months without talking to my parents,
really, which is not great.
But I have recently communicated with him over the fact that we're using
too much data on our phone plan.
So yeah, my dad, my dad has like a 45 minute commute to and from work right now.
So like every month or so, he'll remember like, oh, why don't I just call
Digi while he's on his way home?
He doesn't call me Digi, but you know, right?
He calls you Digi Brony, your real name.
Oh, I only want to know Nate's answer to this.
If you were a girl, would you use your body for money?
Not necessarily prostitution, though.
I would argue that it's almost impossible for a girl to not use her body for money
just as she goes about life.
Righter answer that I ever could have hoped for.
All right, here's what we could all answer.
The gobs ask, what was the spookiest thing to you when you were a kid?
That could be a whole podcast, honestly.
You're not wrong.
Yeah, that should have been the Halloween one.
Yeah, what the fuck's wrong with that?
Well, this won't even be out for another week anyway.
Spookiest thing is, I mean, like the rare occasion when I was a kid,
when I saw a actual horror movie, when I was a kid,
I was much more susceptible to them.
So like I remember being young and I saw this movie starring Harrison Ford
called What Lies Beneath.
And this movie, it was sort of it was about like a wife with a cheating husband,
professor guy, and like he was sort of like the murderer, bad guy,
because like he had like killed a girl that he had had an affair with long ago.
So he was kind of the murderer.
And like some of the imagery from that movie stuck with me for years
and really fucked me up.
Like whenever there was like a darkness that I had to walk through,
I would imagine like Harrison Ford was going to fucking come and kill me.
You know, things of that nature, things of that nature.
It was good.
Similar for me, I mean, this was not when I was a little kid.
I had lots of like little childhood trauma like things I'd seen that like haunted me.
But like in terms of what made me afraid to go into the dark,
blood the last vampire with the Corruptorans.
Oh, really?
Because we had kind of like a sort of a meme.
But me and my brother Victor, because I saw the movie
and I was like probably eleven and he would have been like ten.
And we watched it with my cousin, Boyd, who was four years older.
And like we would play this game where if it was a dark night and we were all hanging out,
we would try to see how far into the darkness we were willing to walk.
Like how far into the dark you willing to go before the Corruptorans get you, essentially.
And like so like Victor would start walking into the darkness and then Boyd would go,
oh, Corruptoran.
We all go, oh, we run away.
I don't think we were so young that we like legitimately thought Corruptorans
were going to eat us, but we were spook.
We were easily spooked kids.
That's hilarious. Never dealt with horror.
Well, by the way, are these all questions coming from our beloved PCP Discord channel?
Yes, they are.
If you are a PCP Patreon discord, yes, that that thing.
Given what spooked you as a as a kid.
This question is from the gobs, by the way.
I that I was thinking and there was this very
what is the question was from the Corruptorans and their back.
They're coming for you.
This one thing on Newgrounds, I saw this flash animation
and it was it was it forever.
Well, I'll just explain what happens.
It's like a brightly lit kitchen and there's just a guy walking in.
There's like stuff on the TV and it's like you can see outside.
It's like dark.
It's like nighttime.
It's just the window is black because it's dark outside and he's just coming in.
He's fixing some cereal or just getting going to bite to eat his little snack.
And, you know, he's just watching TV and nothing happens for like 45 seconds.
And you're just sitting there is like what what what is this?
And then suddenly out of nowhere, because you know how Newgrounds flash animations,
you can't like turn the volume.
You can't pause it.
You can't click on it.
You can't change the volume unless it's on like you're you're turning the knob on your own speaker thing.
So it was just an extremely loud monster smashes through the kitchen window,
grabs the guy and brings him out in like like three frames.
And from then on, every time I was in the kitchen and I saw that it was dark out,
I thought that would happen to me.
And I just stayed really far away from the window for like for like years.
Because it was such a specific like normal setting
and it was really tense and suspenseful.
I don't know what I feel like the guy
would expect us to say just like clowns or like werewolves.
But it's just like, no, this very specific flash animation from newgrounds.com.
Scared the shit out of me.
He's dealing with it. Yeah, I know.
I mean, I ruined Shade's life one time by showing him.
There was one of those.
It was just like a a flasher or whatever they're called when you put
what's it called when you put like a sudden loud screamer screamer.
Yeah, that's the one.
I there was this one thing that was a it was wears Waldo.
And like after like 10 seconds, it's a screamer and it's scared the shit out of me.
So I, of course, show my little brother who is six at the time, this thing.
Shade legitimately cried for two hours.
And it haunted him for years.
Like in the way he describes it is that like up to that point,
he had not known what fear.
You thought of the meaning of fear.
Oh, my God, like he legitimately like gained the sensation of existential
dread from that because it gave him like a perpetual fear that at any time,
like the world could end or something like that.
OK, that like everything can be normal and then it can be horrible, you know?
And like, could he stomach like actually finding Waldo?
I have no idea.
But I don't know if you even remembered that it was a wear wears Waldo thing.
Amazing, the screamer.
But he, a few years later, he became like really afraid of the apocalypse.
Like any time we would like like people would talk about the end of the world
or anything like he would get really freaked out that the world was going to end.
And yeah. Hey, I've got a question from the Twitter here that I think is
wait, Thomas, not answering. Oh, I'm sorry. Yes, please.
Yeah, I remember when I was a little kid, I watched a lot of sci-fi channel
and I watched all the alien abduction things and all the like crazy fucking
conspiracy theories about like aliens living among us or like Area 51 and shit.
So I was always terrified of that.
I thought I didn't get abducted by aliens and like get like some like fucking thing
because I already have a really weird phobia of like like bodies and organs and shit.
So like the fact that like I get abducted, like opened up and like they implant
something in the face of my skull. Yeah, that was fucking terrifying to me.
So even to this day, whenever I watch that alien shit, I'm totally fucking into it.
But at the same time, just like, oh, God, the government's watching me.
There's a spaceship outside my house. Yeah, that's aliens.
Yes, that's a good thing to be afraid of.
OK, here we go. Also, Simpsons Treehouse of Horror really grossed me out.
And I hate gore because of that. Anyone specifically, they do love gore
on their Treehouse of Horror. They really do. They really do.
And it's specifically like the sound design of the gore.
Just really like I hate horror movies because of the Simpsons.
Fascinating.
Well, OK, here's a question from at Lord Saiba.
By the way, this is on the Twitter.
Hashtag use ask PCP, send the questions out.
OK, so it's if you were sent back to high school current age,
would you be a Chad or a Virgin?
How will your experience go?
Think realistically.
I'd be currently absolute, absolutely a Chad.
Like, well, OK, am I actually 26 in high school because I don't think
anyone's going to want to fuck the weird 26 year old?
Let's assume that it's your current like mentality put in your body.
OK, yeah, because as as a woke adult, you understand that
like when I was in high school, the reason I couldn't communicate with anybody
or get laid is that I just didn't know where anybody was coming from.
Like, I didn't understand what they were thinking or what anybody was doing
or like what like how to take control of a situation or anything like that.
Now, I feel like with high school girls, you could just walk up to them
and be like, hey, suck my cock.
And they'd be like, oh, OK, you know, like it's a little working up to it.
I don't know about that.
You may have been watching too many anime.
Just the way the way I've learned about how like people how people think,
especially young girls, like like 14 year old girls are literally
all trying to get laid when they enter high school.
Like they go in. Well, OK, all right, they go into high school.
Like if I don't get laid, I won't be cool.
You know, like, OK, OK, who's did I have to be cool?
You know, yeah, but but like as a guy who has no social
like you are socially anxious, you're not just going to ask some girl
to have sex with you, whereas a girl can absolutely do that
and a guy is going to have sex with them. Well, of course, of course.
So so if I was if I was that guy, you know, like now I just have to have
the confidence to realize that the girls also want to fuck me, you know,
like I think that's what I didn't understand in high school.
Like I thought I want to fuck them.
They don't want to fuck me.
And now I realize no, they do.
There are there.
Sorry, there are so many.
There are so many like looking back on it, like obvious girls
who were interested in me and I never did anything about it.
Like because I just didn't I didn't understand that that's what was going on.
And now I do. And I'm like, oh, you motherfucker, you could have had it all.
There are only two things that a man needs to get laid.
And this is true at any age.
One is just sometimes you can just use one of the two.
One is just like the confidence to just go up and, you know,
just just put your balls on the table and say, here they are, sweetheart.
Pick them up.
So there's that, as Bill Burwood put it.
And then the other thing is something to back it up as in like, let's say you're
like, yeah, like if you've got, you know, you're you're you're like the
the fucking marching band can mean a lot of different things.
Well, that's true.
That kind of ties into a bunch of this stuff.
Like, you know, like really disgusting, fat slobs can get late.
Harry Weinstein, I was the kind of the way I looked in high school is one
of those like, change the outfit and you've got a good looking guy.
Sure. Sure. But it wasn't.
But instead, it was a guy with uncombed hair that goes down to his
knees and like shit facial hair and like wearing three different outfits
that don't like parts of three different so much of this is incredibly simple.
Like, yeah, literally get decent clothes, get a haircut and just like, don't be
gross. If I had cut my hair, shaved my beard, dressed in layers and spoke to a woman.
I would have gotten late in high school, but I didn't do any of that.
I didn't know better.
It's not that complicated.
But but social pressures are real.
I don't want to just say that I would immediately be a Chad.
Like there's unique pressures in in high school and how to make this work.
Your current mindset, though.
I mean, I have no doubt you like literally just transplant your brain
into the brain of a high schooler.
Like, I'm sure you can get.
I think anybody could.
Yeah, I really don't have much 20 could easily get late in high school.
It's just a matter of keeping your focus, you know, being willing to play
the long game when necessary and then just be be cool, be cool.
I mean, I'm I'm sure that if I had my brain and I went back,
I could have like actually made friends, which is like the first step.
I think you're right, because I didn't have really.
I didn't really have like a group of friends that were my group.
I just hung out with other people's groups of friends and just stood around them.
So like and it was always because, oh, I'm I'm worried that they won't like me.
So I won't do anything.
But obviously now I'm much more, you know, prone to just doing things and taking risks.
So I would be definitely able to make friends and be maybe the most popular guy
because I was like I even back then I was kind of good at guitar.
If I had capitalized on that, I could have been the guitar dude.
We had some guitar dudes who were very well respected in my grade.
Sam and Matt.
So Davoo points out, also, don't be in an exclusively religious social environment.
That usually helps you.
You're not wrong.
But but if you can cut under that, if you can be like the rebel,
like, oh, baby, I'm going to fuck you while God watches, you know?
I mean, you can maybe make that work.
Jesus Christ, it's like me.
I know Davoo, it's a big negative song.
I feel like I could probably have the social skills of this point
to be a Chad in that situation.
But I probably choose choose not to because if if we're going back
to our high schools, because, A, every one of my high school,
I wouldn't want to fuck anyways, because they're all horrible people.
B, I would have to lose all my weight again, and that would take a long time.
And you're in you're not.
It's not literally you have to lose the weight anyway.
It's your brain in your high school, self's body.
Let's put it that way.
Sure, sure.
I mean, I don't know if you're like a real.
All right.
Did you mean that you were fat in high school and you've lost weight since then?
Oh, yeah, I'm fat in high school, significantly fatter than I am right now.
So I have to work on that.
But then also, I'd probably to be too busy trying to invest in Google.
And then I could be fucking rich.
How the fuck you get invested age 16?
I could find a way.
I have I have a 28 year old brain.
So I could figure something out.
You put you put your piggy bank in an empty type.
I'll be like, dad, by Google, by Google.
I know it's a weird word, but trust me, do it.
Yeah.
Mail to Steve Jobs.
Wait, wrong guy.
OK, whatever.
All right.
Well, that's a good bunch of questions.
I think everybody I think we're good to wrap this one up to top that one.
So we might as well.
It's true. It's true.
If we're currently I am a drunk and that's because the next episode we're
going to do is a bonus episode, right?
We're recording it immediately after this.
I think it'll actually come out before this episode, though.
It will. That's right.
So if you want to hear the aftermath of me drinking throughout this entire
PCP and then getting shitfaced right afterwards, go become a patron for five
dollars, you get the bonus episodes that we record once a month that are always
goofy, hilarious, weird shit.
The next one's alcohol or the one that's already out.
The newest one is alcohol.
We're going to be talking about alcohol and getting shit.
And there'll be eight of them by the time you hear this out.
Eight episodes.
Yes, you can listen to all eight.
So you can literally pledge five dollars, watch all eight and
the value gets better every month.
Don't give them ideas.
You've mongoloid.
They won't because they watch all eight and they realize that they want.
They want to be able to access the future ones.
Exactly. Exactly.
That's how they know.
And no one's got that.
No one's got the kind of like weird patience that they're going to like
pledge once every six months or so and like get someone to do it despite us now.
We're counting.
Don't forget, we're also on iTunes and Google Play music.
So if you want to listen on your mobile device, sans YouTube.
The only the only people who the only people who would do that like like pledge
once every six months to get the episodes are the people who would not have pledged
until they just found out they could do that, you know.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Like there's some people who we might get because they just found out
that there's like a scheme they can do and now they'll actually pledge.
So we're still getting people we wouldn't have.
It's true. It's a net gain for us either way.
And of course, we've got a little bit of merch.
If you go to our red bubble page or our print all over me page,
there's links in the description.
Click on those and buy some dank PCP mugs and shit.
They're dope.
You know, we need to we need to run like our ads in the middle of the episode.
You're not wrong.
That's what I've been watching other big podcasts and they do that.
They do it like right in the middle.
We should do it like before the Q&A or something.
That'd be a pretty logical time on the hour.
It's usually a good place to.
Yeah, OK.
Also, is there anything else?
Twitter, we already talked to at TP Crasidators.
Subscribe to our Twitter and pledged to the fucking Patreon.
Subscribe to this channel for new shit because there's a lot of stuff
that doesn't even get on the Patreon.
Just videos uploaded here.
Like the current intense spat going on between Tom Oliver and Ben Sane
over why D&D is good or shit.
Who knows how that side will say Ben Ben's argument did not impress me.
I respect his opinion, but he literally just said everything.
I dismissed in my the first 10 minutes of my video.
Oh shit, Ben, you hear that?
You've been called it as a fucking hack fraud.
You're an embarrassment.
All right, everybody, that's it.
Thanks for listening and we'll be back next week or sooner.
No, wait, bonus episode.
Yeah, OK, give us money.
Thank you, everybody.
All right, we're leaving.
Goodbye.