Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, and today we are joined by Ben Oliver.
Patreon.com slash Polystation 2 Hippocrates.
Franchises more like French Isis am I right?
And here's Lethal Aurora Mage, speaking of terrorists.
Why do my introductions always get interrupted?
I don't know.
The real terrorism is destroying intros.
I feel Nate has a grudge against me.
I didn't interrupt shit.
Don't blame me.
It was not my fault.
I've been here for zero responsibility here.
Alright, now I'm in a bad mood.
I'm ready to fight.
I'm ready to kill everybody today.
Let's fight.
Let's do it.
Listen up, team.
Today's episode is Franchises, subtitle, and how to ruin them.
That is the overall theme that we're sticking with here.
So there's a lot of franchises in recent years that have just gone to shit.
And we're here to kind of discuss why.
What, if anything, can be done to avoid it for the ones that have survived,
the few that still remain.
And I guess, you know, also to examine the other side of the coin,
see who's doing well these days.
So let's get into it.
What do you think, guys?
Who's got an example?
Who wants to start us?
Wait, Urban Dictionary.
Urban Dictionary, what have I done?
What have I done?
Almost.
Almost got away with it.
The PCP franchise was almost cleansed.
I have a horrible meme, but.
Okay.
All right, Urban.
My friend, here is the definition of a franchise.
Franchise, an entire series of the film.
Wait, this doesn't have to be a film.
The original and all its subsequent sequels thereafter.
This is terrible.
No, what the fuck is this about?
Of course it's terrible.
It's Urban Dictionary.
Yeah.
I don't think this has ever been good.
Have we ever had a good definition?
No, that's not true.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Oh, I get it.
Fourth definition of franchise.
Franchise.
Verb.
To get it in, to smooch, a.k.a. to have sex.
And here's the example.
Did you franchise?
Oh, I franchised last night.
Hashtag sex, hashtag fuck, hashtag hookup, hashtag penis, hashtag smooch.
That's, I assume they mean that in like the fight club definition of franchising where
Ed Norton's dad, like said, a bunch of families of which he was one.
And he's like, you know, like that, that sort of thing.
You with me?
Yes.
You with me on that?
I understand.
But wow, I've never.
The thing about franchises.
The thing about franchises that I was going to talk about is that they sort of ruin certain
things within a franchise.
Like if you've got like a series of video games, good games are overlooked or like harshly
judged if there are better games in the same franchise.
Like the label brings down opinions on the things that are good because they're tied
to things that are better.
And then things that are bad are elevated because they're tied to things that are better
than them sometimes as well.
That's definitely true.
It's funny we're doing this topic when we are.
Because our good friend Jesse Wood just made a video all about this topic concerning the
God of War series.
That's very true.
It was very, very topically relevant and everyone should watch it because it was fucking fantastic.
It was a great classic Jesse video that everyone should definitely watch.
But probably link the show notes below.
But if you like that, what was interesting about his video was that it was less.
I mean, that actually was about kind of how like how much more credit the God of War series
deserves than it's currently getting just due to a change of Zeitgeist.
And people endlessly spinning their wheels about like how games should be art and getting
all wrapped up and insecure about Roger Ebert's ghost.
Like I feel like if the new God of War game wasn't a God of War game, people would not
be shitting on the old God of Wars because it's not connected by a franchise.
There's no reason to compare them.
I mean, it's just Jesse said.
They're just looking for an excuse to sound like this one's better.
Yeah, yeah.
I would.
I mean, as Jesse very well painted, people have simply just forgotten what happened or
never played a lot.
Like you'll hear like game commenters today.
Oh my God, I fucking hate these people.
They come out.
I mean, Jesse made a very, you know, we're just reiterating his case.
So go watch his video.
But it's just like they come out.
They're like, oh man, this is so much better than the character Kratos was way back in
the day.
It's like, oh, so you're experienced with it?
No, no, I haven't played any of them.
Right.
Yeah.
And then again, like Jesse points out in that video, like the whole, like you read the original
reviews for the OG God of War because I remember when it came out because I'm an old fart.
And I remember reading about it and like, oh man, Dave, you have to make the game and
all this shit.
Everyone was like, this is like Devil May Cry with an incredibly good story.
That was like the elevator pitch for the OG God of War.
God of War One had a great story.
Yeah.
Better than Devil May Cry once.
Definitely.
He actually had like character motivation and depth and complexity, which, and everyone
was like, this is why this game is so good.
It has everything.
I feel a meme brewing.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait.
Kratos is like, he's holding like his dead wife and daughter's body.
And he's like, it was supposed to be my job to fill your dark soul with war.
No, not light.
See, I made a twist on it because it's God of War, not God of Demon Cry.
That's my joke.
Okay, it was a terrible joke.
I'll take the paycheck.
I don't like it.
It was the worst.
But yeah, no, it was good.
It was a good video and it kind of is on point because a lot of the times the new stuff in
the franchise is automatically classified as the betterer by some people, especially in
games.
That's why we need remasters and stuff because like, well, the old stuff's too old.
We got to make it more accessible and newer.
It's disgusting.
It's very specific to video games, but like the whole graphics thing needing to be updated
for people to even think about giving a shit.
People think about that about movies to a degree as well, but yeah, it's mostly games
for sure.
But it's not really because like movies, I mean, I guess movies still always had like,
you know, they never really changed the frame rate or increased.
The only thing they increased was like, you can put things on Blu-rays now, but you can
still turn like old, what are the millimeters, like 100,000 millimeter film?
35.
Right.
And also like put things in CGI now instead of like making puppets or stuff like that.
That's true.
Yeah.
I mean, you look at like old like like 60 sci-fi and stuff.
It's hard.
Some people have a hard time like, you know, is the Gorn really that threatening?
It's like, come on.
Well, that's just terrible acting.
I mean, you know, things like Citizen Kane, for example, like, I don't think people look
at that movie and think to themselves like, man, this looks dated because of the artistry
of the thing.
It like really like the just the cinematography and the clear, like, I've actually watched
this movie a lot.
So I'm not talking to my ass like people always do about like, oh, it's Citizen Kane.
It's so good.
I actually have studied this film quite a bit and quite it really deserves all the praise
it gets.
And so like that's in an artistic way.
It stands up as opposed to, I mean, what I would argue about like, like a pixel based
Final Fantasy or even one like a Final Fantasy 7 versus like the Final Fantasy 15 struggle
for photorealism.
I think it moves.
Like the seven remake and stuff.
Film just ages more gracefully than video games do.
And that's just because it's still real life.
You know, like you're still it's it's like a very low resolution recording of real life
versus, hey, look, it's like seven polygons with like a five.
Well, image slapped on it.
I'm pretty sure I'd still enjoy watching like the Back to the Future movies just as much
as I did when I was a kid.
Yeah.
I mean, those are those like the special effects and those are actually pretty great
and hold up pretty well to this day.
Like they invented a lot of effects for that time anyways.
I think the thing is like, like when people say movies are too old to watch them.
I just realized there is definitely going to be a resurrection of the Back to the Future
series without question.
Oh yeah.
With Marty, Marty is now going to be an old professor.
He'll be the professor.
He'll be old and be like, hello, I'm old and now I'm smart.
Here I built another DeLorean.
That is probably the series that will be most fucked up by like reinvention and like doing
more because it's so reliant on time travel and like everything was really packaged in
those three movies.
I can't wait for it to show up on Netflix in a year or two.
Marta, she's too shaky, though, or whatever his name is.
Frightened.
He's got the, he's got the shakes, whatever that's called.
Another thing that's like just happened was that there was an announcement for a Thundercats.
We were just talking about this.
And it looks like every other cartoon out there at the moment.
It's literally Steven Universe.
It's Steven Universe Adventure Time, okay, KO, all of them.
Can we say officially that Cal Arts has ruined cartoons?
I mean, they have their legacy is it's too much.
It's simply too much.
I would say at this point, Cal Arts is a franchise that has been ruined.
Oh shit.
Yep.
Okay, just, I just want to, I just want to say something like I really dislike the art
style.
I'll say that like even emotion is just like, I don't like it.
However, I don't want to knock the series out before I've even seen it because like it
could have like good writing or something.
I am only commenting.
I completely do not care how good it is.
It is a reboot.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of things coming back.
I hear Tom Slade Queen.
I kill these fucking necromancers.
These skeletons stop coming back.
I can't get through all the catacombs.
I thought you liked skeletons.
Like, we're not the target audience though, guys.
That's fine.
Your opinion doesn't matter.
That's not fair to say.
My opinion is everything.
I'm on the internet.
My opinion means everything.
Well, actually, I was going to be more generous and say, I'm not judging the writing.
I'm just judging the art style.
But I think there's, right, right, right.
We can separate those.
I mean, after the really good 2011 reboot, how can you just turn around and turn it into
this?
Was there a reboot in 2011?
It was amazingly good.
Really?
Wait.
So actually.
Yeah, Fundercats.
Was it the Japanese anime one or whatever?
Japanese anime style.
Yeah.
It was gorgeously animated.
It had amazing, dude, there was a super fucking amazing episode because it was mostly a continuous
storyline, but then they had short one-off episodes.
And there was one episode that was super cool, and it's been a while since I've watched it.
But it was about Lyno's all depressed and shit.
He's a sad boy because shit's going bad.
And he comes on this race of small little flower people, and they only have 24 hours to live.
Their entire life is in 24 hours.
So he meets one of these characters as a newborn, and throughout the day, he sees him trying
to use his short little life to make a better impact for his people, and that reinvigorates
him to keep going forward and fighting.
And it's like the fucking sickest concept.
That sounds fucking incredible.
It's so good, dude.
It's fucking great.
And then they come out, they're like, what if we just made Teen Titans Go furry edition?
And I'm like, I'm so fucking angry.
Hey, Teen Titans Go, I like more than this because it has an original art style.
I give it more credit.
The whole thing about, like, we're not the target audience.
I don't...
Aren't we, though?
No, well, I mean, kind of.
The target audience...
The new kids don't remember sending cats.
They don't have kids.
But it's also going to be like, hey, guys, remember how old you are?
Now you can relive how old you are by thunder cats again.
Yeah.
Well, you know what I would say.
Well, mage, you don't know that it's not a more mature show with an older audience in mind.
So maybe we should all wait.
And maybe you should die.
The thing about it, though, is that stuff like...
It's just...
Ready Player One, Ready Player One, Thunder Cats, everything coming back,
it just makes me not like the things that they're originally attached to.
I'm sick and tired of reboots and remakes and rehashes
and reintroductions of old things that I haven't experienced.
So maybe I have experience.
And it just makes me like, okay, now I will never want to look at Thunder Cats
because of this fucking shit.
Everything that gets rebooted goes into a vault in my mind brain
where it's like, this is bad because it came back and I hate it
and I never want to see it and I hate everything associated with it.
And if I see anyone enjoying it, I'm just going to spit right in their eye.
I just want to say, I'm not describing your disappointment.
I fully agree. If someone took something I really liked when I was a kid
and rebooted into shit, I mean...
I have never seen it.
Yeah, I haven't seen it either.
But the thing is, I guess it's just...
Yeah, I'm also tired of the reboots.
If they wanted to do their completely own original weird cookie thing,
just do it with a new IP.
Why do you have to reboot Thunder Cats and make this thing?
Of course, people are not going to be happy.
And if your target audience is new kids that haven't seen the show before,
then just make an original show.
They're not going to care.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
Where did the reruns go?
Reruns are so fucking easy and cheap.
You just do those, it's so much better.
You know, that is a really good point.
Because this is all about making a safe bet
and trying to make more money off the franchise.
Why even spend any money making a new show?
Just put all the money where it actually matters,
where all the money comes from for these fucking shows anyway.
Merchandise sales.
Just re-air Thunder Cats 2011 and drop more merch.
Or re-air the original, because everyone has memories of that.
But those are old and they look gay.
I feel weird in my penis and that's not good for me.
That's just the thing that gets me like,
oh, but all the Thunder Cats is in 4-3 resolution aspect ratio.
We can't air that.
That would be laughed out of town.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll just kill you if you think about that.
Just mirror the edges.
Us YouTubers have figured out the solution for airing 4-3.
All you do is zoom in on another layer and blur it out.
So then you have a 16x9.
Yeah, it works.
You could have a funny little side things,
pillars, drawn little side things.
Just draw the Thunder Cats roar characters as your border
and then just air the original.
Right. That could be the whole show.
It's in the border of a normal Thunder Cats episode.
Just imagine, guys, remember,
just think about all the hilarious epic meme references.
There's going to be two the 80s into old cartoons
in this incredible new show, Thunder Cats War.
Oh, it's going to be great.
I know that I'm reached.
I don't know. I haven't seen the show yet.
But I do feel that you can both, one, have fatigue for reboots
and two, also sincerely determine if a show is good or bad as it comes out.
I'm sure.
I'm sure you can.
Like Teen Titans Go is like one of those things where people hate it
just because, oh, it's not the same as Teen Titans.
But it's actually okay and it's kind of fun.
No, no.
Okay, like I like the original Teen Titans
and I wanted to give Teen Titans Go a shot
because when I first saw designs,
I kind of liked them.
They're cute and chibi sort of like, oh, that's neat kind of,
you know, that sort of thing.
It wasn't the same and I didn't expect it to be the same,
but I watched the show.
I watched several episodes
and I really didn't care for the humor, I guess.
Sure.
A lot of it was very mean spirited and that's what I dislike.
I mean...
What? No.
What are you talking about?
What was mean spirited?
I don't buy.
That episode with the pie, Mother May pie or something.
What's wrong with that?
I don't remember any mean spirited humor in that.
I hated the song.
Three of the Teen Titans got cooked into a pie
and then Cyborg and Beast Boy ate them.
But like, that was a joke.
I don't like, I don't like, I didn't like it.
I don't like that sort of humor.
I understand it because it's funny, but for me personally,
I really didn't like the humor of the show
and because the show relies heavily, like solely on its humor,
I didn't like the show.
Mostly you.
Okay.
Well, okay, fine.
The thing is the people that usually hate Teen Titans Go
hate it on a very surface level.
If you watched it and you didn't like it, then that's fine.
But most people, I think I've never given it a shot because
but, but what happened to my ones that I grew up with?
Where did they go?
Oh, yeah.
I feel like, same with the Powerpuff Girls reboot.
I also watched a few episodes because I wanted to see.
It's, I don't think I reached like the few episodes
that people were really, you know, talking about like the ones
with the twerking and whatnot.
But I've seen quite a few episodes.
I'm sorry, did you say twerking?
Yes, there was twerking in the Powerpuff Girls reboot.
What?
Wait, wait.
The Powerpuff Girls of these like six year old children
and twerking.
What's the...
That was awful.
I haven't seen the show but I've seen bits of like,
this is how terrible this is.
Yeah, I haven't seen, I haven't seen the show
but I think the context is like there's some sort of villain
maybe and they're like, then they're kind of drugged
and then like they twerk.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're talking about drugged children twerking.
But like I'm just...
I'm just guessing that they're drugged
or like the illusion to being drugged.
What?
Okay, alright.
Nate, do you know there's a whole like conspiracy
in that show that one of the artists
where the show has a self-insert of himself
and maybe they're talking about himself.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Who's the love interest, blossoming right?
But guys, guys, guys, no, like it came out
and like the artists people were making a joke
and they made the character without the person
actually being aware so it was meant to be
as an inside joke.
He didn't do it himself.
So we all got pranked.
Okay.
There's a ton of disdain.
It's interesting, we're talking about all these shows, right?
And they run the gamut of we don't know how good they are,
if they're good or they're not good.
But they're all symptoms of a terrible disease
that has infected popular culture,
which is it's much safer to just rehash
what we've already done than to dare go
into uncharted waters.
It's a serious question that'll have.
I just want to finish one when I started
with the pop-up girls.
Like, yeah, so I seen a bit,
it's not as terrible as people make it out to be,
however, it's still pretty bad.
I mean, I dislike it, that's my personal opinion.
Some people might find it good,
but it's not, it doesn't have that charm, I guess.
But it's really not like the end of the world, you know?
It's not the end of the world,
but like there's a reason people get so upset,
because as much as I don't agree with the people
who react badly to Teen Titans Go,
I totally get why they would have such a reaction
when it's a completely different sort of show,
but with the same name as the one that they remember,
which was, you know.
Yeah, but like now speaking about franchises
and being ruined and stuff,
well, it was Teen Titans Go,
as much as like people like to dislike it,
it hasn't ruined the franchise in terms of like business
and stuff, because apparently it's making a lot of money
for a scene.
However, with the pop-up girls,
it is ruined.
I think it is ruining the franchise
because it's not making a lot of money
and I'm not sure why they're still making it.
Well, okay.
I'm not sure, and I might be wrong,
maybe they are making a lot of money or enough money.
Here's a serious question on this front though.
Okay, so the Teen Titans like show,
like I never read, I know it's based on the comic books,
I never read them, so they're completely irrelevant to me.
And also Powerpuff Girls was like mostly like just a show.
I know it'd been, there was like an actual anime,
may have been stuff a while back,
but like it, they were mostly, they were what they were,
like the one show.
Okay, but like, so when we talk about ruining a franchise,
like for example, does it ruin the franchise
of Teen Titans to make Teen Titans go
when like, frankly, the series
simply would have remained dead without it?
All right, the way I see ruining franchise is that
it's, you can see it from like a money perspective,
in which case,
loads of terrible things are completely fine
because they make money
and the franchises aren't ruined in that sense.
But like the way I think about it is that
it's a personal thing.
If you feel like you're enjoyment or you're like it,
you know, something about one of the things
in a franchise spoiling the others in some way
and making you feel bad
when you think about the thing as a whole.
You know, like, oh man,
that would be the perfect series of movies
unless they, and you know,
that one right there ruins a lot of them.
Yeah, another thing I think is like
from the consumer perspective,
it's about the legacy of the show.
Teen Titans was very much beloved
and although people really, really wanted like
a sequel or a continuation or just, you know,
to finish the fucking series because it wasn't finished.
People remembered it fondly and they were very, you know,
and they liked it a lot,
but now whenever people think about Teen Titans,
they can't help but think about Teen Titans Go as well.
And the fondness just sort of like gets pushed it aside
and like the anger and the disappointment takes first place.
So the legacy of the series is now ruined
because Teen Titans Go exists.
Yeah, it's really gross how like something
that has fans and followers is like as long as it's,
you know, it has like people who regard it fondly.
As long as there's that, it will eventually be, you know,
exploited for money down the road unless you have an author
like the guy who made Calvin and Hobbes
who like explicitly forbade any adaptation of his work.
And so that is like super beloved
because no movie has come around
to fucking ruin it for everyone.
It's just perfect forever.
I mean, yeah, copyright expires in 80 years
and like some like fucking brain Najara
has been waiting since this little late 70s is like,
finally I can make my CTI Calvin and Hobbes movie.
Isn't that recently occurring for like The Catcher in the Rye?
I forget the name of the guy who wrote that.
I thought that happened like they were,
I know he expressly forbid the thing to happen
and I believe he's still alive.
I can't fucking remember his name, I'll tell you.
J.D. Salinger.
J.D. Salinger, that's the one.
I don't know, whatever, just throwing that out there.
Well, I mean, when I think about these questions
like legacy and stuff, that's a fair point.
But like there's two different ways
things can be ruined in my mind.
Like Final Fantasy comes to mind a lot
and I'm sure I'll discuss that a bunch in this podcast.
But like, so there's two different things
going on with Final Fantasy.
One, there is the current constant ever changing
Final Fantasy series that itself like is still being developed
and like never stopped from like the 80s when it started.
So like you could definitely say
that like Final Fantasy as a series has been ruined
because they continue to put out, you know, like worse products.
I mean, I know a lot of people like 15,
like that doesn't even matter.
Like you can make a case along those lines.
But then just as one example,
there is the specifically Final Fantasy 7.
And so Final Fantasy 7 exists as one game
that came out at one time.
But then they made sequels and prequels
and side stories and a million different things
and books and visual novels and all kinds of crazy shit
as well as they are currently working
on the remake of the game.
So the game itself, like so the Final Fantasy series
is one franchise that you might consider ruined
by later games that are actually changing
what the Final Fantasy series actually is.
But Final Fantasy 7, it is what it is at that time.
You know, like if they updated it for like,
there's like a PC release or whatever,
there's updated stuff,
the remake will obviously be a huge change.
They've added lore with all the side games.
But that original game is what it is.
And it will never be different
as long as you have a copy and don't lose your fucking copy.
I'm gonna protect mine like the fucking sacred tomb.
So like has the legacy of Final Fantasy 7 been ruined?
Is like, I think the answer is like to the public, yes.
Because everybody thinks about like Zach Fair
and Crisis Core and the Turks and all these side stories.
All these other things.
To me, like if I was gonna define like what this would be,
like what like ruining a franchise is,
I think it's like either the erosion or negligence
of the artistic merit of a property.
I think that pretty much sums it up, you know,
like either through like continued like,
iterance, like the original idea that like
attractive people in the first place
gets kind of lost in the shuffle.
Or like it's just blatantly ignored
for a crazy like left turn.
Usually both of these are done with monetary hopes
from corporations and stuff who never really understood
the merit of the franchise to begin with.
You know what comes to mind for this though?
I think about like, if someone today says like,
I've heard about Final Fantasy 7,
let me get into that thing.
Like that person will experience not what was intended
when the first game came out, you know?
Unless they start from the beginning.
If they start, but see, that's what I was gonna say.
I was gonna say that like for me,
as like an old fan of the series,
like what I do in my brain,
I've played almost every of the compilation games
and I'll play the remake, I'm sure too,
just to find out what's going on.
But like in my mind, I simply discard everything
that happened outside of the original game.
Now it's unfortunate because things like
Cloud's personality and because of how great
and interesting like a character Cloud is
and how nuanced and how amorphous he was
even in his old game.
It's given people like Nomura an excuse to depict him,
you know, in ways that I would argue
he should not have been depicted
in like subsequent games and prequels and stuff.
So like, I definitely can't help but have the character
as a monolith tainted in my own mind.
But if someone could just play the original game
and ignore everything that happens,
but the reason is how would they know to do that?
They wouldn't know to do that.
They had no fucking idea.
Yeah, I still, it's hard to like say
that a franchise can be like...
I've never played any of the Final Fantasy games, by the way.
Okay.
I just want to say, and I've been curious
about playing Final Fantasy 7 specifically,
but there was like a steam seal that I didn't take up
or didn't take advantage of of all the Final Fantasy games.
I really wanted to play like as many games as I could,
you know, in order to see what's up and stuff.
Okay.
Well, your boy Hippo did play it
and was just talking when you interrupted him.
So let's see what he is to say.
I've been waiting to say this for a while
because you were talking as well.
So I guess interruptions...
So let's just interrupt Hippo, not me.
That makes sense, that makes sense.
If you can't beat him, join him wagon
when it comes to interrupting people.
She's had enough of being interrupted
and dealing it back out.
This is all Nate's fault, let's agree.
Sure, I agree.
Gabe, what were you saying?
I forgot.
Well, any thoughts on the legacy of Final Fantasy VII
as someone who's recently played that game?
Oh, I remembered.
The idea, I think, I don't agree
that a franchise can be ruined for the public necessarily.
With education, they can figure out
what's good and bad probably.
That's probably true.
Yeah, because like...
But do they get that education?
If nobody plays the original Final Fantasy VII
in the way that it was intended again,
but they play like the remake and they like that.
There's an argument to be made
that they're not getting like the true experience
because maybe the remake is not as good.
I mean, it may be good, but we don't know...
No, no, no, why do you say it?
No, what I'm saying is that I think the franchiseness
of the fact that this is a remake of another thing,
but they're different, is what is the problem here,
because they may prefer on a base level,
human, like this is what I feel at the very core of my being.
They may prefer whatever the remake becomes
to the original game, but if they were not franchise connected,
they could just see them as two different things.
There's Final Fantasy VII, the game, it's an old thing.
And then there's this new thing that is not supposed
to replace it, but it is implicitly being a replacement
because of it sharing the name and being a remake,
which is why I think franchises like destroy the legacy
of things for people who come into them later,
unless they do a lot of research to,
unless they put in a lot of effort to sift through
all of the updated new things that have muddied the waters.
Okay, I wanna quickly say,
I've been playing Shin Megami Tensei,
and that's like all those balls franchise, I will say.
It's like older than Pokemon from my knowledge.
And like I played the fourth game
and I started playing the apocalypse.
And I did a lot of digging like with the history
of the Shin Megami Tensei because I wanted to know,
because it fascinated me, like something this old existed
and it just, I liked it.
And from my knowledge, the franchise was never
sort of ruined by any game.
And all the spinoffs were either mildly successful
or became persona, which like super successful.
So like, I think it's an example of a franchise
that's like hasn't been ruined yet,
despite it's very long lifespan.
And although I-
I know that some people, sorry.
Yeah, I know some people have been sort of complaining
about the newer games for some reasons, like, oh, they-
A lot of old school fans, don't they say that like,
they're mad that the focus has gone to like persona
and that like that side of the Shin Megami Tensei?
I've heard some degree of that.
At some point was, but then they revived Shin Megami Tensei
with Shin Megami Tensei 4 and the apocalypse
and there's gonna be a new Shin Megami Tensei on the Switch.
So it hasn't died and has actually has been sort of revived.
And a lot of people because of persona are turning,
you know, their focus on Shin Megami Tensei
because they want something of similar but not the same
like me because I started with,
I sort of started with Persona 4,
that MMO game that I talked about aside
because I wasn't even,
I didn't even know it was a franchise at that time.
Anywho, but like, yeah, I started with Persona,
I really liked Persona 4, I couldn't play Persona 5,
still can't, I want to, but yeah.
And instead I turned to Shin Megami Tensei
because it seemed like, you know, something I'd like.
At first I was sort of a little bit turned off
because of the, even in the fourth game,
which is pretty recent and Apocalypse also,
recent enough, I think,
but they still had like the sprites
rather than like 3D models and stuff.
And it sort of feel like very clunky
and sort of like bloated, not bloated,
but like very visually heavy, I guess,
not heavy, overloading, like, not sure how to say it.
Well, so are you saying that like,
what you're saying is that like the games
that some people might consider ruining something
actually can bring people into the fold
and expose them to, you know,
like aspects of the series
that maybe the hardcore fans would say,
like, is the real experience
or something along those lines?
No, I'm saying, no, what I was trying to say is just like,
originally I was sort of turned off by the graphics
that kind of looked very outdated,
but then I played the game
and I really liked the story and the setting
and the idea and the mechanic.
I think the heart of the Shin Megami Tensei
still lives on through its franchise,
the Persona thing aside,
it's become its own thing very much.
So it's like very different games.
Like, but I think Shin Megami Tensei
has always had that core sort of fight
between good and evil, but not like,
I mean, the demons and the angels
and the apocalypse happening
and like world going to hell.
It's always seemed to have had that theme.
I think originally started like on a small scale-ish,
now it's becoming bigger and bigger over time.
I'm not too certain because so many games,
but yeah, and it's just like,
I think it's still a good franchise
and although some people are grumbling
about the changes, however,
like you can't remake the exactly same game each time
whenever a new game is made,
changes are gonna happen.
And some changes I think are made for the better.
They're like sometimes-
But if the changes are bad,
then it's fair to criticize them, right?
Oh yeah, that's fair.
I mean, but I haven't seen like legit criticism above,
like, oh, it's different than what I remember it to be.
I mean, there was one,
like there's like a legit one
that like the overall world map was very,
very confusing and hard to navigate on the fourth,
but they improved upon it on the fourth game, Apocalypse,
which was meant to be a DLC,
but it became its own thing.
It became too big to be just a DLC,
so they made a separate game out of it.
That's what I've heard anyway.
But yeah, my point is it's a good franchise
and I'm happy to experience it
and I'm happy to say that it hasn't gone to shit yet.
Hopefully it won't.
I don't like this idea
that I am like guilty of sometimes,
that if you don't like the new thing in a franchise,
you're a grumpy old man
and you're just looking back
in the nostalgia goggles and all that,
because I definitely have done that for a few things,
but I don't like the idea that it's okay to be that either.
Sometimes new things are just good and they're not for me,
but like I was saying,
it's like the franchise has kind of tricked me
into needing to have an opinion on it
because it's from something that I used to like,
which was different from a different time.
And now this new thing is coming around with the same name
and it's the new one and oh,
but it's made for a completely different generation of people
and I don't like it.
Do I criticize it?
Do I get mad?
I don't really know what to do sometimes.
Yeah, just like the God of War game
is just made for like modern gamers
and so they had to completely change the kind of game it was
because nobody likes action games anymore.
There's a case to be made that some things
are better than other things
in terms of like the thematic relevance of like,
the original game in every franchise
is usually the one that makes the most sense
with all the reasons for everything being put there.
And then everything after that is some kind of like muddying
of the general idea.
Like with the Dark Demon Blood series,
Demon Souls is like the most,
the perfect like mixture of the way the game was told
and what is in the game
and the way it's played and everything.
And then beyond, after that,
it's sort of shifted in Dark Souls
and then Dark Souls 2 and then Bloodborne and Dark Souls 3
into something that's just a bit far removed
from like you're a real human being or you're a dead guy
and you're trying to survive at,
you've got a realistic-ish strength level
and you're trying to survive in this harsh world
that is fucking going to destroy you.
But then in Dark Souls 3,
it's like you are a super being from the very beginning
and you're really fast and you dodge well, super good.
And it's like the message is different.
And that doesn't even make sense
because like in Bloodborne,
you're designed to be like a speedy dashy guy,
but you're wearing like heavy plate
and doing this shit in Dark Souls 3.
Yeah, Dark Souls 3 is just sort of,
it's not bad, which is the thing,
but it's like, it's a muddy,
it's a, it's a, it's a removal,
removal of the core of reason for like stuff.
So, so like what you're arguing is that like,
there can be an artistic thing that was done
in the original thing that can be diminished
as sequels go along.
It can be diminished, but like there's no reason
to think that if it's not perfectly artistically cohesive
with gameplay and whatever.
I'm talking mostly about games
because I don't really watch movies.
Sure, sure.
But like, you know, there can be that,
but there's nothing to say that you should like the old game
or the old one more, even if you like the new one,
because it's a game you like more.
It's just, it's just always confusing
because they're the same franchise
and there's different things.
Franchises should not exist.
They should not.
That's, I mean, I definitely want to say a thing about that.
Yeah, I wanted to say something, but you can go Nate.
Okay. Well, I was just going to say that like,
so when it comes to like,
my mind keeps going back to Final Fantasy 7
as like the main example in my mind.
And it's like, so that is a little different
in the sense that like, well,
actually Dark Souls had direct sequels,
but like there was Final Fantasy 7
that had its own artistic integrity, love or hate it,
you know, whatever it was, it was its own thing.
And then you've got years later,
they make Advent Children.
It was like the first thing that was made
for this compilation of Final Fantasy 7,
which was followed by many games and whatnot.
Like, okay, you could theoretically make a prequel
to Final Fantasy 7, which actually they did.
There were some animated films
that came out before Advent Children.
There was at least one, I think it was called Before Crisis.
That's just like an anime version
of what happened in Nibelheim
between like Zack Cloud and Sephiroth.
And like a prequel that just makes the events of the game
into an anime, like that's totally fine.
Like that generally doesn't hurt anything
and is pretty decent.
Now, the problem is when you make sequels
to Final Fantasy 7,
that's when artistic integrity gets its Achilles heel sliced
because the entire point of the end of that game
was there was a question as to whether or not humanity
was going to be wiped out.
And like, we don't know the answer to that question
at the end of Final Fantasy 7.
By making sequels, and that was the whole point
that we as the viewers have to wonder ourselves,
are human beings actually a plague on the earth?
It was about the environment.
It was an environmental question.
It was about the nature of mankind.
Are we deserving of survival?
Are we just a virus on this planet the way Genova was?
Or do we actually deserve to live here
as part of this ecosystem and this world we're on?
That is the question asked at the end of Final Fantasy 7
and we do not know the answer.
So you are given the homework to spend the rest of your life
thinking about the ending to that game.
Until Advent Children comes out a couple years later,
when they say, nope, everything's fine, humans are cool,
don't worry about it, they just got Geostigma.
So shut the hell up, everybody.
Like bad, like no, stop.
I watched Advent Children without having any context
for any games or anything.
And I was young and I quite liked it.
It was like, ooh, shiny, basically.
I liked it at first too when I first saw it
because I also was just like, ooh, shiny.
Because I hadn't really thought seriously
about what it all meant.
But then as the years went on, I did and I am where I am now.
But like, so that's just one example.
I did a full cosplay of Vincent Valentine in my youth.
Made his gauntlet, made his whole thing.
And there's a picture of it, there's pictures of it around.
But anyway, I worked at an anime convention
to work at Anime Boston.
I wanted to make my larger point here
and it's specifically about,
and keeping with what Ghib was saying,
it's why I hate franchises.
And it's this, it's a whole bunch of things.
But it's, it's a whole bunch of things.
And I think it's a whole bunch of things.
But it's, any time that is spent on making a sequel to a game
is time that could instead be made
making like a new thing with original ideas.
And there are absolutely sequels that are good,
that improve various things.
But I'm approaching this from the lens of like,
like how much intellectual content really in the story.
I know a lot of people don't care about fucking stories
and games, but I do.
And I, and you know, the whole Gazambkutsfark
of story working with gameplay, blah, blah, blah,
all that bullshit.
And it's like when, when you have to sit down
as like a game designer,
cause I have been a game designer many times.
I know what it's like, even though I don't do it right now.
Like you have to sit down and think about,
okay, what's the whole basis of our game gonna be?
And you really have to go through an intense struggle
to come up with something original.
And that's where the most of the intellectual labor is done
when you're making a game.
It's when you come up with the concept
and then like all the shit that comes afterward
is all like filling in the blank.
So that's, you know, that's how you make your game.
So like, you know what, this brings to mind
when I was doing the weed cast with Digi and the boys
and we would watch episode one
of like every anime that came out in a season.
I loved doing that because episode one
of every single show that's ever made for the most part
is interesting or absurd or just,
it stands out generally in some way.
But the thing is, watching another 11 episodes
of that thing generally for most shows is not worth it
because you're not getting that like,
that spark that's like leading into a whole show
when you watch the whole thing.
You get all the ideas presented in episode one
and then they string it out for 11 episodes in some way.
And you know, a lot of the times that makes sense
because it's a complicated narrative, whatever.
But the point I'm getting at is what I really liked
about that and the good thing I get from that is
when you're forced to like start over
and start from the very beginning
and come up with a unique premise,
that's where most interesting things that I like in a show
and generally in a video game as well, like are done.
It's at that first stage.
So to go on and spend a million fucking years
reinventing the wheel and trying to come up
with sequels to games to just like refine art
or refine gameplay or you know, make a sequel to a show
and like find excuses to like have like new characters
show up in season two.
Like, oh, cause we didn't mention them
cause they were off doing a secret mission
but now they're back
and here they are main character of season two.
I hate all that shit.
It's terrible.
It generally, I'm not gonna say every time
but a lot of the time it violates artistic integrity
and like to all the things that the big push right now
of like doing like the big remake thing,
the reboots and whatnot.
It's just like I do not blame studios for doing it.
They've got to make money.
They've got, you know, bills to pay.
What I hate is when people just are content with it
and accept it and are just like, yeah,
this is a perfectly good use of everyone's time.
Like this ThunderCats reboot, maybe it will be great.
I don't know, but I don't want people to think
that it's a good thing to do to spend all their time
making a new ThunderCats show when they could instead
be making something actually original, you know,
from the premise up.
Okay, I still have a point to say.
So like, oh, I wanted to bring up a franchise
that I also like, Dragon Age.
I really, really like Dragon Age.
It's one of my favorite franchises, I guess.
I really love the first game
and the second game got bashed to the ground
because people hated it so much because of the changes
and like, not just the changes,
like it was lacking severely in a lot of things.
And like, it was obviously a very rushed project
and it looked, it felt more like a DLC
and it didn't connect so well, story-wise.
Like, there were a lot of problems.
However, I still liked Dragon Age too
as blasphemous as it is to say.
I quite liked it.
And now after, you know, talking with you guys
about all this.
Is that the one with all the gay minotaurs and stuff?
Is that the one?
No, I mean.
No? Okay.
Okay, okay.
Maybe a little bit.
Konari, maybe if you're talking about Konari,
they're not minotaurs, but they are people
with giant horns in their heads, most of them.
Yeah.
Is there a big gay one?
It's in the third game, not the second one.
Maybe.
Ah, okay.
My apologies.
But yeah.
So in the second game.
That's the one Nate's interested in, for sure.
Yeah, that's the one I want to know about, okay.
He's called Iron Bull and yes, I need-
Iron Bull?
Oh, damn.
That's hot.
Now I need to come go back to my game
because I remember I made a character
specifically to romance that guy, so.
Now we're talking.
Yeah.
Nate did too.
It's called Nate Bestman.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I was gonna, I was gonna, I was gonna,
if he was originally, I was going to originally romance him,
but then Colin happened and oh, my heart.
Because of the story this guy has had
throughout the whole games, like in the original game,
I played as a female mage and you meet him.
And he has a crush on you in the original game.
And yeah, that's really cute.
And then like you meet him in the second game
and he's sort of like, not exactly an antagonist,
but he, but like if you play a mage,
he's not really happy with mages at that point
for a lot of reasons.
Oh wait, is he that, he's that like Ranger guy
who hates magic and wants to kill everybody, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's-
Does he wear a bandana?
No, he has fluffy feather things.
Like he's like a captain of stuff.
Anywho.
So yeah, so the Ranger guy is a DLC character
which I never got because I dislike him severely
and he messes up my game.
At least how I want to play it
because I want people to be as happy as possible
and he just kind of nopes out
of one of the endings of the game.
And like he forces me to make a choice
that I don't want to choose.
That I don't want to make-
What does he make you choose?
What's the choice?
Either kill one of my party members-
Straight or gay?
No, no, no, either kill one of my party members
or like he gets the fuck out or something like that.
I don't remember.
Like he really advocates for the killing
of one of my party members.
And I'm like, no, I like this party member
despite all the fuck that shit he's done.
So.
Okay.
Anywho, so yeah, so like Cullen and the second me
and then the third game he's finally romance-able
and I was like, I've been playing female majors
throughout all these games.
Wouldn't it be so cool if he could finally
get it on with like a female age?
Isn't that how it was with Tali?
You could only romance her in Mass Effect 3 as well
or something.
I never romance her.
You could romance her in Mass Effect 2.
It was the first game that you could-
I got you.
Yes.
Mass Effect's another good example of that.
It was kind of different because like Mass Effect 2
was way different than Mass Effect 1
but people were generally positive towards it.
Like there was like a hardcore group of people
who played Mass Effect 1 who weren't a big fan of it
because like Mass Effect 1 was a role-playing game.
The combat was pretty bare bones
but like there was like loot and gear
and like everything you killed, you had drops
and like you could change your armor
and change like all your equipment and stuff
and like it reflected things like one of the big memes
of Mass Effect 1 is you could dress everybody
in pink armor and it looked ridiculous
because like there were pink armor sets
that just were really good.
Like the designs were really fucking weird
but then Mass Effect 2, they changed all of that
and it became strictly a shooter with RPG elements
and the combat got a lot tighter
and it was much more fun to actually like have firefights
and stuff which became much more the focus of the game
but there were only a couple armor sets
and they weren't like equipment, it was just kind of like
rewards you got throughout playing the game.
So like everything, all the RPG stuff
was like very streamlined or stripped out entirely
in favor of being a shooter
with a light leveling progression.
Well, you know, I still wanna make my point.
So Dragon Age 2.
Wait, so let me just finish, I just wanna say on this,
it's just that what's interesting about Mass Effect
is just that like that, so that was always intended
to have a sequel but like obviously the reboots,
like that's another story with the Andromeda and whatnot.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Yeah, I mean Dragon Age also I think, you know,
they also, it's made to have sequels
but yeah, Dragon Age 2, like it got bashed to the ground
and people really disliked it.
However, I think like if it wasn't tied to the franchise
and had come out of its own thing,
people would have been as harsh to it as they were.
It probably wasn't-
But that harshness though, like would it have gotten
as many sales, you know, like would people pay attention?
Like I think the reason they're mad
is because they have an expectation
and then they get tricked, you know.
When you buy into a franchise, like a franchise,
the reason a franchise even can exist
is because it's formed some sort of identity
and expectation in people's minds.
So when you say we're going to make more of this,
they expect more of this,
not like something different with the same name.
And because of Dragon Age,
because they're trying to tell a story
throughout multiple games, like it's all said
within the same time span kind of mode, like generally.
You can see recurring characters, whatnot.
You usually don't, you can't make like an RPG game
into like a first person shooter
and then just so seamlessly and tell, you know,
a story I don't think,
because the fans of the original ones,
like the, that were fans of the RPG part,
I'm probably not going to want to play it
as a first person shooter, you know?
So you can't make too much drastic changes to the formula.
However, you can try to update it and stuff.
And I think with Dragon Age II,
I liked the agreed to the combat,
at least as playing as a mage.
I'll say that much because I haven't played any other classes
because I only play mage, but yeah.
Mage only plays mages, no.
Yeah, so they made the,
like I really liked the combat as a mage in Dragon Age II,
which I think was a nice upgrade
because in the first one, it just,
it felt really clunky and the animation was sort of like,
I'm poking someone with a stick just for like,
with a distance, like very big distance.
Like I poke someone with a stick
and then like a lightning bolt comes out
and then like hits them and just like,
it just like, it looked like my character was going like,
nyeh, nyeh, it's just so silly.
And so unsatisfying because like Dragon Age II,
they kind of like combined like martial arts with the staff.
So you can do like really cool moves.
So like you switched staff around and like,
Is this in first person?
No, it's a third person.
Oh, okay.
I'm just trying to get a picture of what's happening here.
It's like, it's like, it's a lot more satisfying the combat.
And like when you melee people within like range as a mage,
even that looks cool.
Even if you don't do that much damage, like it's,
it's really neat.
I liked, I liked it to the combat a lot.
Okay. So, so basically,
so not every franchise immediately goes to shit.
I like, and there's things to be enjoyed.
Well, here's, here's my question.
I'll just quickly want to say like,
Dragon Age Inquisition was the third game
and I think it was received positively enough.
They did a lot of changes that people heavily disliked
because they sort of made it feel like an MMORPG
with a lot of little mini quests and very big worlds
that kind of felt a little bit on the empty side
and just like a lot of little tedious quests here and there,
you know, pick up five herbs, kill 10 boys or something,
you know, those sort of quests
to make it feel more bloated than it actually is.
However, I didn't, it wasn't a deal breaker for me.
I didn't have too much of a problem
because I'm a great big MMORPG junky sort of person.
So I didn't have an issue with that.
It didn't, I liked the game regardless
and it's my favorite game of the three.
And I hope they do better with the next game.
And I'm really scared
because the EA has been fucking up recently and...
Oof.
Have you considered being a video game YouTuber?
No.
I mean, I sort of like, I did an Undertale Let's Play
that I never finished, but no, I don't wanna.
I'm not, I'm not, no.
I'm a wee, you know, so many things.
So just get that out on the PCP.
Yes.
In the middle of every PCP with Mage,
we'll not have a game review, just out of nowhere.
I don't play that many games that I don't know.
Like I usually play like very cute farming sims
or something like that.
Well, okay.
I mean, I'm trying to come to like a thoughtful thing
to say, to summarize.
Like, okay, is it fair to say that franchises
are always bad?
No, right.
It should never happen.
He's what I can say about things.
No, Mage, pause.
Give talk, god damn it.
Franchises.
I was fucking pausing.
You, then you interrupted.
Also you went on about your shit for a while, Nate.
I waited a long time.
You're absolutely right.
What we need to do is to stop giving a shit
about the names of franchises
and start giving a shit about the people behind them.
It's always the case.
It just always is.
Even sometimes when it isn't the case, it's the case.
We should literally criminalize naming movies.
We should name them one, two, three,
starting with the first movie we made now
and just naming them with numbers forever.
The artist behind the thing is so much more
of a reliable way to tell whether a game is going to be
the sort of thing that you want from a franchise.
The most obvious example is Dark Souls 2
in the Dark Demon Blood franchise
was not helmed by a hit attacker Miyazaki
like the other games.
And it's not as good in various ways
that it was good in the other games.
That's a great point.
He directed all the other ones.
And it's clear that he has a very clear vision
of what the game should have in them
and why things are put there.
And so when he's in charge, you can tell before you buy
that at least there's going to be a good shit.
I was upset with Dark Souls 2,
but then hit attacker Miyazaki
coming back for Dark Souls 3.
I was like, OK.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He made Bloodborne and Dark Souls 3.
And I'm like, OK, this time I've never
liked the idea of believing something
is going to be good before reviews come out.
I never liked pre-ordering.
Pre-ordering is stupid.
But and I didn't pre-order Dark Souls 3.
But I had this idea that if he's there,
I feel like it's going to be good.
And it was.
Like fucking, oh, shit.
I just had like the godfather.
Everyone, the Godfather 2 actually won more Oscars
than Godfather 1, I think.
And that was just another by Coppola, you know?
Like if that had been outsourced, like, for example,
I forget who the director was of American Beauty.
Like American Beauty 1 is like a legendary film
that everybody loves, Dubs.
But then America, I mean, this may be a bad example,
but American Beauty 2, it is a sequel.
It features the character in a small way.
I have not seen it.
It stars Mila Kunis and it's like, it's like a joke.
Like it's a, no, it's just not real.
Like if you bought American Psycho 1,
I knew it was a video game,
and then you bought American Psycho 2, I mean, no, it's not.
There's an American Psycho 2?
There is, starring Mila Kunis as, I mean,
but that's so bad.
You said American Beauty.
God damn it, American Psycho, no beauty involved here.
Okay, I was very confused.
Except for Person Fail, if you know what I'm saying.
Got him, hashtag gay.
Yeah, there was another, oh, I was gonna say,
and another one is like Hideki Kamiya directed
like Devil May Cry 1,
but then like Devil May Cry 2 was by some other asshole
and it was a complete nightmare.
It was terrible and this was young me before I knew.
I think that's, yeah, yeah.
I think that same guy also went on to make
Devil May Cry 3 and like redeemed himself, I think.
I think that's what happened.
Yeah, I thought that Kamiya came back for 3
and then someone called me up on a previous episode
and was like, no, you're fucking retarded.
It was the same guy who just like learned to not suck.
And I was like, oh, well, I take back all the things
that I said for him for like 15 years.
It's not a guarantee, that's true.
It's not a guarantee if the same guy is,
but it's more reliable than seeing the brand's name
or even seeing the company behind it
or like the publisher or the game studio or the,
you know, the team.
I mean, sometimes the team is just,
it's not the same team, even if it's all the same people,
if it's been like three decades, like with Ukulele,
most of the old gang came back and it sucks.
And it's just because they weren't doing that,
that whole thing for so many years that they had changed
and they didn't know what they were doing as much anymore.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Like, go ahead, Mitch.
I wanna say, so we can sort of like agree
that like the things, like criticizing things
just because they're different from how they used to be
isn't really a good sort of basis to criticize things,
but it is okay to criticize things for actual faults
that things have.
So like, basically just take your nostalgia goggles off
if you wanna criticize new games
because you have to consider like,
are they good on their own, you know?
Like your games-
That's definitely true.
Yeah, I mean, a lot of people, they don't do that
because they're judging it based on the idea
that they want a new version of this franchise
and that is what they're being sold,
but they're not getting it because it's different.
And that cuts both ways though.
Like some people, because they played the old thing,
will be more critical.
I think that's most of us here,
but then other people have like a rose colored
nostalgia glasses and like they'll see
the Final Fantasy VII remake and like I grew up,
myself saying this and my friends saying,
whatever console Final Fantasy VII remake
eventually comes out on, I will buy.
And this was like more than a decade ago
that me and my friends were like saying this shit
because like this, like obviously
it's going to be the best game ever,
but of course we didn't know
that like the compilation was coming, man,
the compilation and like,
and there were all these directorial issues,
like the game isn't being worked on
and like all these problems are happening in development.
And most people still don't,
most people don't like fucking, you know,
follow gaming press and dev logs and all this crazy shit.
So like they're not gonna know.
They're just gonna be like,
oh, I remember Final Fantasy VII and they're making it again.
I think this is the problem
and there's literally nothing we can do about it
except possibly advocate that people change their mindset,
but I think it's not going to happen.
The problem is that people stop
when they see the name of a thing
and like the company behind it possibly,
even that is probably too much.
They just see like new Marvel movie
and they think, okay, gonna be great.
Or, you know, or like new Final Fantasy game,
okay, it's gonna be great, new Kingdom Hearts,
okay, it's gonna be great.
But what they need to do is investigate
who's directing it, what have they done recently?
What is the team developing?
It's a bit much to ask that people do that for everything.
But that's why we YouTubers
can bring them that information, you know?
I think that the most I can do specifically
to quell this problem is just to be like,
I don't even know his name.
The guy who made Calvin and Hobbes,
he's a genius and he's a school.
George Harrison.
That's the-
Bill Lauderson, you fucking fools.
Don't sully his name.
The greatest human I've ever lived.
All I can do is when an if, no, when,
I make a big, giant franchise, like big thing,
like, oh, everybody wants to make a movie of my thing.
I'm gonna say no, and I'm gonna write my will, fuck you.
Nobody will ever touch anything I make
and they'll be great as a result.
That's what I want, man.
That's what I want.
I didn't wanna say the-
I made it if you were gonna say.
It's okay to sort of like, you know,
have initial dislike or like of a thing to reaction.
Like, you can't control your emotions to a thing.
Like, so you might have a knee-jerk reaction.
But if you're gonna like,
don't go and pick fights with people
over your silly emotions
and just like, think a little bit before you do that.
I mean, I totally hear you on the image,
but like, what I'm advocating for
is a severe and massive amount of rage
if you have a well-researched opinion at like, for example,
my feelings on the Final Fantasy VII remake.
I feel like I know the score.
I have done the research.
And again, I know likely what issues are to be.
So I will continue to raise these concerns.
But however, when the game is finally before me,
I will drop all of that as best I can
and attempt to give it a sincere, thorough, clean slate.
And you will buy the collector's edition.
He'll get the cool cloud statue
and he will fucking do it all.
I think something really important
when looking at franchises and remakes and stuff
is that there's a difference.
You have to understand yourself.
There is a difference between saying,
I don't like this because it's not what I wanted it to be.
And this thing is terrible and I hate it
because it's possible for something to be really, really good
but just not at all what you wanted.
That was what happened with me when Kill La Kill came out.
Like, I just had the wrong expectation.
I went in thinking like, you're in login too, here we go.
I did the exact same thing.
That was a huge mistake.
Yeah, I didn't have that explanation.
I quite liked it.
The reason that happened is because they advertise it
as like another Gurren login.
If you watch all of the previews and stuff.
I mean, I accept responsibility for misreading it,
but yeah, I mean.
At the end of the day, I've never seen a Gurren login.
Oh my God!
Well, well, good luck.
I watched one episode, it's not for me, it's not for me.
Oh, oh, oh, do we have to, all right, all right.
Everybody, we have to disconnect mage,
we have to hold hold vote right now.
Kick mage, yes or no?
How you can't?
Well, how interesting.
So you watched episode one and just didn't like it?
Yeah, I think I watched like two or maybe two episodes.
Go watch, go watch this anime ever, Gurren login part,
one and two.
I don't, I don't wanna, you can't,
the more you force me, the less likely I'll be to watch it.
I'm not forcing anybody, blame Tom, it's not me.
Yeah, stop nagging.
No, oh no, I'm so sad.
Don't be like everyone's mother.
I'm so sad now, I have to be mage's mom on this.
You know what's funny, Tom is like almost as big a fan
of Gurren login as I am, I mean, you know,
maybe not as intellectual, an analyzer of a fucking anime.
You like it with your brain, I like it with my heart,
okay, Mr. Gurren?
Remember when I was, yeah, yeah, sure.
When I was working on that video,
I remember discussing it with you,
like the thought of possibly getting you involved.
I mean, it just didn't work out that way,
but I remember that came out,
that was like four, three years ago,
it was something.
It was a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember Ghost in the Shell coming next, man,
I can't wait for Nate to release his third video.
I know, right?
I like the memes, though, I'm aware of it.
The memes are good, all good.
That's pretty good, right?
I don't know, weaponized thickness,
not from that video, but, you know.
All right, team.
I think we've, I'm actually pretty happy
with where we've arrived with this.
That was a pretty decent summary.
The issue is just, you gotta do research,
and the problem is that no one ever will,
like the problem is that the dummies of the world
who don't know anything, they see like, you know,
it's Marvel, baby, and they're like,
yeah, I will get my mind to this uncritically
and have no, you know, whatever.
Just a quick disclaimer to people who,
like, because we namedropped a lot of games,
and there might be people who are like,
oh, you like this game, but there were like these faults
in it, or like, oh, you dislike this game,
but like, it has these and these good things.
Like, this is not a game review podcast,
so we can't go in-depth about all the things
good and bad about games.
If you like any video game viewer,
you are a fucking idiot piece of shit, loser,
and literally delete yourself from real life.
And basically, if we let something out,
it's not because we're ignorant, it's just like,
we had to move on, especially me and Nate,
we talked a lot.
That's, sure, sure.
Yep, that's true.
All right, I think we're done here.
Gib, Tom, any final thoughts on this?
Thanks, everybody, for listening to the 108th episode
of the Procrastinators franchise.
That's right.
I look forward to getting to 180,
so we can do a 180 degree change
to do something completely different
from the PCP up to this point.
That'd be very funny.
Like, upload, that would be a great idea.
It's dead now, we killed it.
That'll be great, that'll be great.
Gib, any thoughts, any final thoughts here?
Oh, we should pretend to be each other on the 180th.
You're not Gib.
Whoa.
No, there are no more thoughts.
Zero.
I am out of thoughts.
There's nothing left in my brain.
No more simple thoughts, they're done.
Yes.
All right, well, all right, it's time to switch on gears
over here to our hashtag ask PCP section, everybody.
I, on the Twitter, I use hashtag ask PCP every Saturday
when we record, I send out a tweet,
if you, well, don't respond to it,
but you just send a thing with hashtag ask PCP.
You'll see it, you'll see it.
All right, I just want to give a shout out
to this guy, Cult of the Yellow One.
Someone's been continually asking about, like,
our stances on gun control,
and I think it's this guy, like, every time.
It's just like, I don't know,
I don't want to get into that shit.
I have no fucking idea what the right,
I'm just saying, like, I don't know.
Every baby should have a gun,
but anyone over the age of two should be killed.
I have no complaints.
I'm satisfied by that answer.
Wait a minute, oh, here's actually a relevant question.
It's at discount Picasso asks,
are normies the root cause of all problems with art?
I think that really sums up.
I mean, what we covered in this podcast.
That pretty much sums it up,
because, like, the people who don't care
determine they're the vast majority,
the vast majority of people don't care,
and the vast majority of people control
the market conditions,
and market conditions are responsible
for all major decisions,
because all major decisions are based on money and not art.
Mm, there you go.
Yeah, that's, and I don't see that changing
until we become a post-scarcity society,
which may never happen.
I mean, we don't need to be a coma post-scarcity,
we just need to have a lot of money to be like,
I'll just give this strange artist like those.
Or if we just have everybody after two years old be killed,
there are no more normies anymore.
I mean, that'll fix this problem right now.
But the reason I don't agree with that, Gabe,
is because as long as money has any influence,
people will always want as much money as possible.
So I think as long, and like,
cause that equates to power.
No, but like, like, the,
there's like times in before big money crashes
and bank collapses and whatever,
more weird art was being funded
because people were like, yeah, sure.
You know, there's money to go around,
there's jobs for you to have.
We don't, it's not a big deal.
We'll give this strange artist some funding.
I agree.
But now you have to be a giant super world
dominating franchise or you're gone.
I think the question though is less about
like what art is being made
and more about what art is being supported.
Cause like, even now you can make whatever you want
on the internet or whatever,
the normies aren't always gonna do the normie thing.
You know?
And that's the problem.
Yeah, that's right.
Whatever's popular, it's just whatever's popular.
Even if a studio threw a huge like budget
behind like some crazy art film,
like people are gonna be like, yeah,
but Avengers 12 dude, and they'll just go watch that.
Yeah, I mean, that's, yeah.
There's a real consolidation of entertainment.
Honestly, just behind Disney.
Like Disney's just buying everything.
I mean, if things are being funded,
that's the main, if things exist, that's the main thing.
It's not about whether you can convince
the majority of people that your weird art thing is good.
Well, what would you say to this though?
Like let's say that...
It's that the artist is allowed to express themselves
in the way that you are.
Okay, here's a real question though.
And this is kind of a separate thing,
but it's like, if, so let's say that like,
there's enough money to go around for whatever reason,
like we've got fucking, you know,
universal basic income or whatever,
where like everyone can make their art.
But the thing is though,
like there's so much market share dominance
by like mainstream things like Avengers movies
and you know, just like all the like normie stuff
is so pop up that it like on social media,
which is how people communicate,
it just like drowns out that.
So like all audiences are like,
like there's always gonna be a couple people
who are into your shit,
but like the vast, vast majority of people,
which I guess is actually true right now,
are just like inundated with like, you know, Marvel
and you know, like the new, I guess, Final Fantasy,
even just like the AAA stuff,
new Uncharted or whatever.
And they don't like pay attention to the small things.
I don't know, do you think that's like,
I personally fear as things kind of like power seems
like it's getting consolidated online these days,
that things could end up in a place where like,
just through a lack of ability to compete
with the market share and like the budgeting,
the advertising campaigns of like big Disney stuff,
that like it'll really drown out people
and they'll, you know, do bad.
They won't get the word out about their stuff.
Any thoughts?
I mean, that's how it's always been.
That is true, that is true.
It's all marketing.
I mean, that's the whole thing.
That's why a lot of mediocre shit does so well.
I want the world to be like,
every man like is by his own strength and will
can like break through and become, you know,
like king of his own castle
and acquire his own little domain or whatever way,
as opposed to, and I don't know if that's realistic
I feel like the reason then,
there's clearly a reason that normies don't like weird shit
and it's like the weird shit only appeals
to a very specific mindset
and only a certain amount of people have that.
So even if everything that's weird gets funded,
it won't be that important for most people
that it gets funded.
That's true.
It's the same thing.
Not everybody has the capacity to build their own castle.
Some people just be the vassal
and that's just the way they are.
Yeah, fair point, fair point.
So that's why you have to get to the top,
have all the money and abuse all those stupid people.
And that's what Comcast did
and look how good they're doing.
They're doing pretty damn well.
Pretty fucking damn well.
Did you hear they made a cash bid for Fox
trying to take the rug out from under Disney?
Oh, I didn't hear about that, damn.
Yeah, they're gonna have like $60 billion.
I'm gonna straight up here you go
and they want to steal Fox from Disney.
That's their big deal.
Damn, okay, okay.
Think about this though, everybody.
Imagine like your internet and TV service provider
also owns the entertainment company that makes the art
that they distribute.
They own like TriStar and like they own Coca-Cola
and a bunch of crazy shit.
Huh, I'm sure that doesn't cause any problems at all.
I'm sure that doesn't influence
like the stuff they create whatsoever.
I'm sure I'm not gonna see Coca-Cola ads
in front of every movie ever
since like the late, the mid 90s.
Oh wait, I do.
Yeah, it's pretty fucked up.
Hey, here's an interesting-
Watch the Jack and Jill Red Letter Media review, everybody.
Oh, I love that.
That's one of the best.
Hey, look, here's a good question.
This is my hashtag down with Ben St.
Oh.
And this is in the page.
It's a hashtag I can get by.
The thing is, I think actually a bunch of people
are using hashtag Ben St.
So I'm just gonna, I clicked on this thing.
It says center, I think this is center point.
I think this name is center point.
Is that the name before?
Yeah, I think he pledged it like the RideCon fund and stuff.
But anyway, I believe it's center point.
And his question is,
if you guys could get a sponsor for the podcast
in exchange for slightly censoring yourself
like bleeping the word nigger, would you do it?
Would you do it?
Cause I'm curious what you guys think.
Cause I've always had a deep personal aversion
to the idea of like getting a known sponsor.
It's just-
I never say the word anyway so it doesn't matter to me.
That's true, that's true.
I'm not against sponsorship deals
because the, you can, like Game Grumps has shown
you can make them really funny
to the point where I don't care at all.
Those are, yeah, I like that.
Here's the thing, here's the thing for me.
In that specific example,
it would A, dependent on how much money it is.
But if it was enough money to make it lucrative,
I think that that specific censorship
would have no artistic impact on the show itself.
I think it would be funnier to bleep out certain words
like that because-
I mean, let's just say-
Okay, go ahead, go ahead.
But like if the deal was like,
these are like certain topics or things you can't go into.
Like if it was like legitimate like censorship,
I'd be like, no, like fuck that.
Like nothing's worth that.
Cause then like the entire time,
because even if you never like,
even go near those grounds,
the entire time in the back of your head,
every time we record from now to the end of the time,
we'll always constantly be thinking about not doing that.
And then like 10% of our brain CPU is gonna be dedicated
to making sure we don't go somewhere.
And it'll just make the product worse.
That's true.
I'm okay with bleeping swears
because a lot of the time bleeps are funnier.
Bleeps are funnier than saying swears.
That is definitely true.
I don't know, people don't agree with me on this.
I'm glad that you do.
Listen to something back everybody.
Bleeps are literally way funnier
than just leaving in an actual swear.
I don't know why.
I like the idea of like having different bleeps every time.
Like a different noise.
Like I don't know, like a jackhammer or like,
I don't know, like a siren or something that I...
The whole podcast is just that one episode of SpongeBob,
where they all swear.
Wait a minute, I've got it.
What if for each individual swear,
we use a specific type of bleep
so that it's like saying N-word or whatever.
It's like, so they come to associate
that specific noise, whatever it may be,
with the actual word of question.
No, they have to be common sounds
you hear all the time in real life.
So as you're just going around your everyday life,
you just hear swears subconsciously.
This is a great idea, we should do this.
That is a good idea.
We should do a censorship episode where we do that.
That would be awesome.
I'll edit that, cause that sounds fun.
It actually does sound fun.
Like that should be, at the very least,
a bonus episode for sure, locked.
Oh, that'd be a great bonus episode.
I wanna be honest, so please don't do it while I'm away.
Well, we've already got one lined up for this month,
so that'll be next month, at the earliest.
Sick, all right, on the post.
Okay, that'd be dope.
But I don't have a microphone, by the way.
I'm gonna take it to Lafayette, so.
Oh, that's dope.
Sick, awesome.
Glad to hear it.
Here's a question from Kajuro Bitterthorn
on the Patreon, asks,
question, I mean, this has a question for Dayton Tom,
but anybody can respond.
How do I abandon my nihilistic hedonism
and embark on the path to becoming a productive boy
that has goals?
How do I convince myself that life will be better
if I haven't achieved goals?
I mean, I've got an answer to this.
Yeah, what do you think, Tom?
Shit, I guess you need to ask,
I think for me, giving you an answer would really depend
on knowing exactly what your current mindset is,
like how you feel about being more hedonistic.
If it feels good and you have no real desire to change,
it's gonna be hard to really,
anything that I would say or suggest to take your heart,
because it has to start with a motivation to change.
I'm going to assume that because you're asking the question
that you have that desire,
and that desire is probably stemming from the fact
that you're sitting around doing nothing long-term
and you feel like shit.
And that's the first step,
is because you have to realize,
like for me, like what I make,
my root source of all my good decisions,
which I'm doing more of lately,
is that like, especially like,
even like a simple example is like dieting,
because my diet's been on point for like three weeks now,
and it's fucking great.
Nice.
And like I just ask myself,
like a really simple question,
like would I enjoy doing this now?
The answer is usually yes,
like going out and ordering a pizza.
The answer is like, will I enjoy this in an hour?
And the answer is always no.
And that's like a really good,
like kind of like stop gap for me,
is just like realizing that like,
instead of thinking like,
oh, I can't wait to have this pizza,
I'm gonna be so happy.
I'm like, the real thing is like,
I can't wait to have this pizza,
I'm gonna be miserable for the rest of the day.
And that's like-
That is a great way to look at it, yeah.
That is a great like way to be like, fuck that.
I'd rather be like stoked later.
And like in like 10 minutes, I'll just be fine.
Like literally 10 minutes, I won't care anymore.
The path to productivity is,
it stems from the realization that suicide's kind of gay.
And why would you-
That's true.
Why though?
I mean-
Like if you're not doing anything,
you're gonna be depressed.
And if you get too depressed,
you think, why am I alive?
And then you think, I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna do it.
But then if you think about it even further,
you realize it's kind of pointless
and who cares, nobody cares.
I think the core of it-
Nobody cares about you, except you.
And if you don't care about you-
It's true, no one's gonna give a shit.
And like the thing is,
is that one of the big things to realize
if you wanna start being more productive,
is understanding that happiness is not the goal,
fulfillment is.
And fulfillment means doing things
that aren't going to make you happy.
Because you need to fill yourself with a sense of purpose
and feel like you are accomplishing something.
That's what gives us a sense of more than just happiness.
Happiness is like eating a pizza and feeling good.
And it's not like you have to find a sense of purpose
before you can do anything.
You have to trick yourself into having one.
Right, if you don't know what your purpose is-
Sure, they could really make it.
If you don't know what your purpose is,
your purpose is try as much shit as possible
until something clicks.
Yeah.
That's step one.
So if like, oh, I don't know what to do.
I don't know if I'm an artist or a viewer guy or anything.
I don't know.
It's like, yeah, you do.
Your goal, your purpose is to find your purpose.
And that's what everybody should be doing until they find it.
Because the only way you find what it is
is by trying a ton of shit.
When my dad, when I was living with my parents
and like looking for work and stuff,
like my dad just said to me like,
Nate, until you get a job, your job,
your eight hour a day job is looking for a job.
And like, that's basically the same sort of thing here.
It's like, yeah, you should be focused
on trying to settle this.
And you know what, you're asking this question.
So off to a great start.
And here's what I would add to that.
Like you're specifically bringing up the idea
of nihilism and hedonism.
And on a certain level, I agree that both of those things
make sense in a way.
But like, okay, like what do you want out of life?
Is the question that you've got to ask yourself.
Like we can accept all the realities that like,
there doesn't seem to be any objective value to life.
Okay, fair enough.
But you're alive.
So why not make the best of it?
You know, and like hedonism.
Like, okay, wouldn't it be nice if we could, in theory,
just like pleasure ourselves at a max rate all the time?
By let's say, you know, just doing heroin.
But okay, would doing heroin every day
actually give me the kind of life that would be the best?
Like, am I going to enjoy having to do an illegal thing
that could get me thrown in jail?
Am I going to enjoy, you know,
having to scrape up money to afford this thing?
And it doesn't have to be that bad obviously.
It could be a symbols ordering a pizza, like Tom said.
Did you want to cut in give?
Do you want to say something?
I just thought like, doing heroin,
doing any drug over and over will reduce
like the impact it has on you.
So you'd need more.
Indeed.
It goes back to being happy now
but it's being happy in an hour.
But you know, what doesn't fade.
But you know what doesn't fade.
I mean, so this is actually how I arrived
at like what I want out of my life.
You know what I want?
I want a big happy family that loves me legitimately.
I want to be financially secure
so I don't need to worry about the world.
And I want to live in an environment
where I, you know, feel good about myself.
I feel good about like my environment.
It gives me positive vibes.
And I want to physically like take care of myself.
So I live as long as possible
and get to enjoy all this stuff.
So like, okay.
Like if you disagree with those approaches
then we're not going to agree.
Like if you think like a good life
is to just feel like, let's say sexual pleasure
as often as possible.
Let's say that's your goal.
Then I would highly recommend
you start investigating how it is.
You can actually like make a plan
to have as much sex as possible.
I mean, maybe the plan for that
is to literally just get a wife who loves sex.
Then you need to like, okay, gotta be able to support her.
Gotta be able to fucking, you know,
like what is your goal in life?
That is where you need to start with this.
You heard mine and that's what I want.
So to get there, I'm doing things like
pursuing careers that make me happy.
You know, like making sure I make enough money
so I don't need to worry about
and have freedom to do what I want to do.
You know, like in my relationship
I try to make sure that I'm happy,
that the other person's happy.
Like all these things are worth thinking about.
And to the point of being a hedonist.
The thing is though, everything I described
sounds like, I don't know, like fucking life coach,
you're like, hedonism's wrong.
I think that like every human is basically just a hedonist.
I'm simply a hedonist who wants to maximize across
like the entire 70, 80, 90, maybe longer years of my life
how happy and enjoyable life is.
And there's a completely rational basis
to do your homework.
Work out several times a week.
Eat healthy and deny yourself sugary foods
that are a fleeting high.
See, it's a fleeting high versus delaying gratification
to live a happier life.
That's where I would start with you.
Think about what you want out of life
and think about how to get there.
That hashtag emotional edging life, you know?
Exactly, that's the one.
I mean, yeah, that's pretty much all I gotta say about it.
Good luck dude, I hope you fucking crush it.
Yeah, Kajuro, crush that puss and crush that dog also
with the opposite of puss, you get it?
Excellent.
Next question, this is a funny one actually.
TamakiXaid asks, what is your most boring passion?
Your most boring passion?
I like that a lot, I like that a lot.
Damn, that's interesting.
Okay, this isn't a passion, but like for example,
I like to count to the number eight repeatedly
throughout the day, and I really enjoy doing it.
That's, yeah, like it's like a text.
Well, it's like when I'm driving,
I'll do it, I'll play a little game with myself
that I'll like, okay, it's gonna be hard to explain,
but like I do a thing where like the telephone poles,
like I try to count my own car lengths
as I drive by them, and I count up to eight
and then I start over, and I like to,
it's really satisfying for me
when my eighth car length lands right before
a final finishing telephone pole
and isn't one of several lengths,
because you can fit like four cars in between telephone poles,
and I do this constantly to myself.
Yeah, that's what I've got, go to hell.
I enjoy it.
Anybody else?
Yeah.
I just wanna think of like a boring passion I have.
Okay, it's just related to Nate's thing.
I also do like a little counting thing in my head.
Whenever I'm waiting for something.
What do you count to?
Yeah, whenever I'm waiting for something,
and like, you know, like let's say
I'm hitting something at the microwave
or like something else, basically it's just,
I count down from six to one, three times.
Wait, I'm sorry, say that one more time.
I'm trying to parse that memory.
But I'm waiting for things.
Let's say I'm hitting something in the microwave
and like I see there's like less than a minute left,
then I start counting in my head, like six, five, four,
and I do it like, when I reach one, I go back to six
and I count down again, I do it three times in total.
The mark of the beast.
That's so appropriate for Mage.
Interesting, now let me, do you do that
as a way to kind of force time to pass
so that when you look back?
Yeah, I totally get that.
I totally get it.
I just felt like that too.
Yeah, it just like, because I'm dragging out the numbers
like six, five, it sounds like I'm counting seconds,
but like each second takes like five seconds to count,
you know, so like.
That makes sense, makes sense.
You know what I do, when I'm on the treadmill at the gym,
like, and I see that there's like a minute left,
that's when I like really start to like,
I try to really forcibly distract myself,
like hardcore from not paying attention
to like what I'm doing or the, you know, pain.
It's not really pain, but like the pain of running.
And then like, when I look back,
I'm like, yes, 10 seconds have passed
and I keep forcing myself to like be distracted by things.
It really only works in that last minute,
because like, I try to do it when I'm like running
for like long-term things and like distract myself
so that when I look back at the clock, more time has passed,
but it's pretty ineffective, just because like,
I don't know, whatever, it like,
my brain is only like excited for the end to come
when I'm actually close to it,
like in that last minute or whatever,
but whatever, just saying, I do that too.
Like when I have to wait for longer things,
I count down from 60 and I always count down
because like, when I count up, it just feels like it doesn't,
it's not as satisfying as reaching like the last 10, nine, eight,
you know, it's just like, it's exciting.
Like the lesser the number, the more exciting it gets.
Like counting up is really, really tedious.
It could go on forever.
Like, well, okay, I reach 60,
but I can't go like 61, 62,
but when I'm counting down to like the last numbers,
like I need to reach zero, zero, zero,
and that's it, that's all, that's final.
Everyone's dead.
Tom or Gibb, do you have any boring passions in life?
I have, well, I don't know whether it's like a boring passion.
I thought just because like the things you said,
what didn't seem like passions,
they just seemed like funny things.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
If we're talking about funny things,
I like to open doors the absolute minimum amount
that I need to slip through.
Oh, okay, okay.
Like, if I need to just leave my room,
I don't open the door the full way, I don't push it.
I just open it just enough to slip through like a cat.
Yeah, I was gonna say you're just like a cat.
Yeah, exactly like a cat.
Cause I feel like, well, I mean, I'm quite thin,
so I can slip through and I don't know why.
I think it's just sort of something I've always done
because why expend extra energy to push a heavy door
even further?
I would argue you're spending more energy
by doing it this way.
Okay, you know what?
I'm not here to judge.
This is just interesting.
No, but like, I do movements like that for no reason,
real reason.
Like I just like weird pirouettes and like moving swiftly
from like, I sort of glide.
Like when I'm getting a cup of tea, you know,
I put another kettle on and I sort of,
when it's time to get the milk in,
I sort of glide over to the fridge,
pull it open with enough force to like,
open the seal so that it's not like sticking
and then the door slowly opens and while it's opening,
like I let go of it to, to let it swing open slowly.
I grabbed the milk and then I kick it back
as I swoosh round like I twill around.
Like it's completely pointless,
but it's sort of like nice to have like a flow
to random pointless movements.
You've completely failed this question
because this isn't boring at all.
This is fascinating.
Yes.
Where was, where was this during
Give Makes Breakfast on the rag?
Yeah, I want to see those pirouettes and shit.
Well, it's only when I'm like really, really into,
not into, but like familiar with the location.
Right, right.
So like if I do something a lot,
I get, I get bored of like doing it normally.
So I just do it.
We need a candid camera of Give Makes Breakfast
in the home.
That's true.
Clearly.
I mean, I do a lot of talking to myself in the car
that I feel might be a similar sort of thing
where I'll just like yell things at myself.
Like just cause like I feel like I wouldn't do it
if there was a crowd,
but I like feel free and I can just like go crazy in my car.
It's why I love driving.
It's just like, I can just,
I'm free.
There's a sick animation video of a guy.
I can't remember what it's called.
I'll link it to you later.
It's like a guy is in his car.
He's going, he's doing a Mickey Mouse voice
and he's been all completely retarded.
And then he gets out of his car
and then he walks over to someone and just says, hey,
it's just like when you're in your car,
you're completely insane.
As soon as you come out, just like a normal person.
It's awesome.
Shout out to Sick Animation.
Maybe we can find that later and look at the shots.
I don't know how people do that.
Even when I know I'm completely alone
and no one can hear me,
I still can't like bring myself to do like noises,
like yell or sing loudly or something that I hear.
I do it all the time.
Yeah, I just turn into a complete idiot.
I just let my full autist just come out
when no one's around.
I do something.
I think you're joking, but that's kind of a half.
When I forget.
Like I'll just make weird sounds to myself.
I'll be like, ew, ew, ew.
I'll just do that.
I do that sometimes, but only when like I'm thinking,
I was like, I forgot how this sounds.
Or like, would I be able to make,
like would I be able to pronounce this thing?
So I just randomly say things sometimes, but not loud.
My brain just needs to like make sure it's alive sometimes.
So it just gives me like these weird vocal spasms.
It's like, yeah, your vocal cords still work.
Just double checking.
Oh, oh, I've actually got a boring passion.
Okay.
All right, I enjoy, I don't have a scrapbook,
but I collect things as if I was going to put them
in a scrapbook and I leave them in a drawer.
Things like every plane ticket I have,
every like thing, when they wrap the thing around the bag,
the bag tags, I keep those after I rip them off.
I just put them in there.
Cause any tickets or things that I've been to,
I'm like, you know what, that has a date on it.
I can look at that date and try to remember what happened.
So I'll keep it.
So that's really boring, but I enjoy doing it.
Yeah, okay.
That qualifies, that qualifies.
Like a stamp collecting thing.
It's pretty boring for people.
I mean, you know, other people don't care.
Yeah.
All right, all right.
Tom, did you have one?
I'm like trying to think of something actually.
I know it's hard, right?
I think mine was the total failure though.
I can't think of a good one.
I think there are probably things,
but they just blend into my life
cause I don't think about them 99% of the time.
Yeah, yeah.
It's hard to think of something that you can understand
as boring and also something that you are passionate about.
Yeah, that's true.
Cause if you are passionate about it,
you don't think of it as boring.
You know what?
I think I actually have one.
And this is sort of demonstrably boring.
It's like, I have a passion for playing video games alone
or like to like just like Zen, like cause like in college,
my friends would all gather around
and we'd play like all these games together.
But like when I was playing like
Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep came out during that time
and like people would like try to talk to me.
I'd be like, fuck off.
I'm playing like I care about what's happening.
Shut the hell up.
I can't stream games for that reason
because I still feel like there's a crowd of people.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I would only stream a game I like don't care about
or like have beaten a bunch of times.
That's the only thing.
If I play a new game, like get the fuck away from me.
Yeah, yeah.
Like when I talk to you, I don't want to see you.
When Ben and I did our legendary T-Bat plays
of Equestria Bound, I think one of the reasons
it was so nightmarishly horrible
and it lasted for more than a hundred episodes
was just because like, because of this like new game syndrome
where like I actually like was trying to like figure out
what was going on and I'm incapable of both like being
a funny let's play boy.
I mean, this was years ago at this point
and also like trying to like enjoy a new game.
I can't do both at the same time.
For a while I was streaming Devil May Cry 5
or DMC Devil May Cry.
And I could stream that fine
because like I'd already played that game
by like at least seven times by the time I streamed it.
So I was like just talking in the chat
and like having discussions and just like mindlessly
like destroying that game because it's super easy.
It's like me and my like in Boston
there's this awesome theater.
I don't know if it still does.
I assume it still does.
It plays the room like every like Friday night or something.
And it's like a big event and everyone has so much fun
because there's so many like community things.
Like we all win the spoons appear on screen.
We all throw spoons at the screen.
I've seen stuff about that.
You actually participate in those.
Oh, that sounds so fun.
We went a couple of times.
Dude, it's so much fun.
You guys should definitely come sometime.
But the thing is I took my friend John to one.
He had not seen the room before
and this was a nightmarish experience for him.
He had no idea what was going.
He was a mistake.
It was just like we were going anyway
and he was in town.
I actually haven't seen the room.
I keep planning on watching it.
Doug, you're gonna love it.
I promise you.
Yeah, I know enough about it.
It's even better than Gern-Loggin.
Well, let's not get crazy.
I feel like I'm overhyped for the room.
I feel like if I actually would have watched it,
it wouldn't be that fun.
I just, it seems fun to just like throw spoons
at the screen whenever spoons appear
and everyone's, spoons!
It just sounds so stupid.
I love it.
There's times when they go outside
and throw the ball around
that in the theater we have footballs
that we toss around to each other.
Oh God, it's, I mean,
just one of the best movie watching experiences
I've ever had.
But yeah, don't get overhyped.
I remember hearing about that movie first
from the nostalgia critic and his review of the room.
That was a lot of change.
And I must have watched a dozen times,
a dozen times I watched that video.
And then I was like, you know what?
Let's actually check out the movie.
And amazingly, it was even better
than the nostalgia critic review.
Of that movie.
I know, I know.
Shocking.
Okay, I've got one more question.
Actually, Tom, did you think of anything?
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, the only thing I can come up with
which is super fucking mundane and really boring
is that like when I'm just doing nothing sometimes,
I'll have like my phone or like a computer or whatever.
I kind of like just playing
with like the little animations that they put in
and just like trying to like slowly look,
like sometimes like I got an iPhone right now
if you swipe down, it goes like the search bar
but it slowly blurs out the background.
Like just slowly playing with that sometimes
like watching the animation.
Yeah, it's dumb.
I'm just like, yeah, this is cool.
It's a blur.
Fun.
And like any little thing,
I'll like play with little transitions like that
because I'm easily amused by things that move.
I am very passionate about like whenever I'm bored
or tired that I don't want to go to bed,
placing my forehead on the table and just sitting there.
Oh, that's awesome.
That's a perfect example.
She's passionate about placing her forehead on her desk.
I love that.
That's fantastic.
Waiting for death.
Somebody please draw a mage, waiting for death,
sitting at her desk with her forehead pressed to it.
Oh, I love that.
That's so visual.
I love that.
How long will you sit there for?
I sometimes actually sit for more than an hour
because I just-
Oh my God.
What a logic.
God damn.
To be fair, I am thinking about things
while I'm doing it.
I just don't, I just can't or don't want to go to bed
and I'm just too exhausted to do anything on the computer.
I knew we'd get a good one.
That's perfect.
Yeah, that's-
I love that.
Sometimes I do something similar,
but it's not when I'm tired,
it's when I feel like death.
When I'm really sick.
And I curl up in like the prayer pose for like,
you know, how Muslims pray,
they do that pose.
No, they're like head to the ground sort of thing.
Yeah, I just, that's the most comfortable position.
I go into the bathroom, I sit down there
with my head on the ground.
I know.
And I stay there for like until I feel better.
Wow.
And it works, it works like a charm.
Mohamed has blessed you, I guess.
I guess so.
Yeah, well, fantastic.
Are you facing Mecca when you do this?
Yeah, so that's an ask.
Are you facing Mecca?
I've never checked.
Oh, maybe you are.
I'm probably facing Mecca like one quarter of the time.
Your bathroom's positioned in such a way
that you just happen to be facing the Holy Land.
He's facing Mecca, AKA Gurren Logan, AKA Gundam.
Get it, do you understand the joke?
No.
All right, excellent.
I hate you.
Mecca, I get it.
Excellent, excellent.
Terrible.
All right, all right.
Here's one more question.
We should, where did it go?
This is from RU guy, or RU guy says,
I can't come up with a question.
What's your favorite anime?
Okay, no, I'm just kidding.
This is that actually was a question though.
You already made a terrible joke like that last week.
That I, it's funny to me every time.
Please keep asking what's your favorite anime.
No, don't.
It's so funny, I can't stop laughing every damn time.
Oh shit, where did it go?
Fuck, sorry.
I lost my place.
No, that wasn't it.
It was, God damn it.
I know I was gonna read something.
This is why you don't read the ones about anime.
The fucking anime questions are the bane
of this fucking question section.
No, I already read that one.
How about, no, that's shit.
Okay, here's one sort of relevant.
A meme slayer, and I think another person asked this to,
Iroxen basically asked,
biggest dip in quality from a franchise?
Like started good and did terribly.
I mean. I'm stuck.
Oh shit, and that was like, that wasn't even a reboot.
That was just the same thing.
It's just the same thing, it got so bad.
It got so bad.
I don't know, like, I really gotta watch that
American Psycho 2,
because I think it might be American Psycho 2
from what I've heard.
I think American Psycho 2 just makes me think of like
all those not really made by Disney,
not high budget Disney sequels.
Harvest Moon.
Right, Harvest Moon, really, you think so?
I've only played one, and only barely.
I've played one on the PC.
Have you played that one, or seen anything about it?
I've been playing Stardew Valley, but no, no, I have not.
Stardew Valley is not from the franchise.
It's like, there's like, it's been,
Harvest Moon things sort of like split between
like story of seasons and Harvest Moon,
and like the original Harvest Moon people,
I think are working on story of seasons games,
and the current Harvest Moon is just like,
absolute crap if you know anything about the PC one.
Oof, oof, that's terrible.
I never played, click disclaimer,
I never played like the old Harvest Moon games
because I never had a handheld.
I played one of the story of seasons games, and it was okay.
But the PC one, they charge like $40 for something
that's like worse than like a mobile game, I feel sometimes.
It's just like, oh, the graphics are so terrible.
How can they charge so much?
For something so horrible.
And like, I've heard the reviews and sort of like
the let's plays I've watched, I thoroughly researched
because I really wanted to get a Harvest Moon for PC
because I like PC games.
But like, it's so terrible, it's not worth the money.
It's so disappointing that I only got into the Harvest Moon
when it started being absolutely shit.
At least you got the old games, I guess.
I've got one.
Bionicle, the first six Bionicles were the coolest ones,
and then after that, they all sucked.
I totally stopped caring about Bionicle for that reason
because I really liked the first designs,
and they were super cool.
People were really into Bionicle.
Shut the fuck up, Nate, Bionicle's dope as shit.
I will kill you.
It literally is dope as adults of Bionicle.
This is a while ago.
I want Bionicle so bad, but they're too expensive.
And I lost all of mine.
Dude, yes!
No, Hippo, did you get like the Lego magazine back then?
Did they have that in the UK?
I did.
Did you get like the original like DC comic book
with like the little interactive CD
that like introduced all the characters
and like blew my mind to shit?
I didn't get that little CD.
It was so sick.
It had like full 3D animations
of like all the characters and introducing the world.
That is a big nostalgia, but I completely forgot about that.
But yeah, it was like a game cube sized CD.
Yes.
And it came with like the, it was like the first comic,
I had like the one with Kopaka, the ice guy,
that was like his store, his back store,
and then the disc had all the characters on it.
And like for the next couple of issues,
just kept up a comic that told about the characters.
I was like, I love this.
This is the coolest shit ever.
It was dope.
And I bought all the sets,
my mom hated me because I spent all her money,
but it was so cool.
And then like two years later, or like a year later,
they changed all the designs
and nobody looked cool anymore.
And I wanted to kill myself.
They fucking nummered them.
They nummered all of the blind people.
And they had too many bells, too many whistles.
The masks were not iconic anymore.
I agree.
They sucked.
I agree, the worst.
The only bionicle spin-off I liked
were the little spinny guys that turned into a ball
that you could ride around those with.
I remember those, yeah, yeah.
I think Biter told me about exactly what you guys
are talking about, like how they used to be cool,
but they're not anymore.
A long while ago, it's just like, this is so weird.
It feels like deja vu.
It still haunts me.
It still haunts me, the bionicle sucks.
Yeah, it's awful.
That's a good answer.
Well, hey guys, okay, enough questions for now, I guess.
But I've got a thing though.
So I've got two things to say.
Now, the number of the first one is I want to announce
on an actual episode, in case we haven't already,
the PCP Highlights channel exists now.
Did we mention that last time?
I don't think we did.
So there's a new channel, it's called PCP Highlights,
and it is highlights from various PCP episodes.
Now, it's time of recording, there's only one,
but there's going to be a bunch out
by the time you see this shit.
So I'm just letting everybody know.
That's where we're going to be putting highlights
in little clips, episodes and shit.
It's kind of trying to get off the floor right now.
It's basically just me doing it.
But you know, we're working on it, we're exploring.
I think people are going to appreciate it.
So there's that, there'll be,
I'm sure there'll be a link in the description,
and I'll probably put like a link in the channel banner
as well, you know, if you have links for that.
Are there people making their own clips as well already?
Yeah, a bunch of people have, I only made one,
a bunch of people have like submitted clips,
and a bunch of other people have just given time codes
for things they think are good things to do.
And if you go, if you're a patron,
and you go to the PCP Highlights channel
on the PCP Patron Discord,
then people are submitting stuff there
that I'm like taking suggestions from.
So if you just give a good moment, you know,
I'll give it a look over, and we'll see how this goes.
So, you know, just letting you know, just letting you know.
Should we announce the, I think we already announced it,
but like the contest for our theme?
Yes, that was announced two episodes ago
as of this happening.
And it's- Yeah, we forgot to mention it last time.
That's right, because like the episode hadn't come out yet,
so nobody's submitted anything.
But we've gotten at least one submission already
from our buddy AJ Shoup.
Now, like I, full disclosure, I have not listened to it yet.
I'm like, so like we're getting them in.
I think what we should do is by next time,
by next time we should wait for them,
some more ones to roll in, see how many we get,
and then do a review, or like kind of go over it
as a segment and see what we've got.
I mean like musical themes or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Intro themes for the procrastinators.
That's right.
So I guess for now what we'll say is,
so people, keep submitting them
and keep sending us your shit.
If you're a patron, go to the fanart warehouse
and submit them.
If you're not a patron, feel free to tweet us.
You know, what do we say?
Like hashtag PCP theme, I think was the deal,
or at TPCrastinators and we'll take a peek.
So do that and it sounds good.
Now, the only other thing I wanted to say
at the end of the episode here was,
so a while ago we did talk about doing like highlighting
people's like art and stuff.
And I think we should do that.
I think we should do that.
So we still got that fanart warehouse
in the patron discord there.
Other than that, you'll have to tweet at us
if you want to send us your shit.
So feel free to add TPCrastinators
and I guess hashtag PCP fanart?
PCP art?
I don't know, I'll check both of those.
So if you guys are in the fanart warehouse thing
on the patron discord, I'm looking there.
I also linked one in the main chat.
Check out this drawing who showed up
in the last bonus episode of the Lord of Ghosts himself
by Lens Lines.
I think it's Lines Lines, I think it is.
Looks awesome.
It looks awesome.
Does the Lord of Ghosts canonically have a gun?
Let's be serious here.
Well,
I mean,
Autistic Liberty is taking care.
It's the ghost of a gun because gun control laws
and they killed all the guns.
So now it's just the ghost of a destroyed gun.
Yeah, when you outlaw something,
the ghosts are now, they have it.
So they used to be drunk a long time ago
and now they're all hooked up on drugs,
but now weed is legal.
So now all they have is guns.
Excellent, excellent.
Check out this other one from the Undertailer fan account.
I think I've seen this around,
but it's submitted here regardless.
It's like, it's a magenta filter
overlaid picture of Briska
that says I have so much sex with my husband, Tavros.
This is Sublime.
This is Supreme.
That's Digi.
It's definitely like Digi, Briska.
I forget the,
I remember there was context to why he drew this
and I can't remember it.
Was there?
I mean, I get that it's like Digi, Briska.
Like this is what Briska would be like
if she were literally Digi.
But I like the,
I actually like everything about this.
This is great.
This is fantastic.
Now next one here is coming from
ya boi Chip in the Franks or Chip Wiseman
at Chip Wiseman Art on Twitter.
And it's a picture of a good ol' arm
defeating Digi for good and all
in the legendary Radcon 3 Royal Rumble.
I read what I-
One of the most amazing moments.
How he drew that, like the motion,
so it is-
And the impact feels tangible, I like it.
Yeah.
It's so dynamic.
I love it.
By the way, these are from like months ago.
So like nobody's been submitting them.
Anything that has Digi getting his ass beat
is great day material to me.
I don't know about you guys.
That's, yeah.
I mean, that's pretty good for now.
The problem is we've just totally let this like lie
and like haven't been doing it at all.
So like we gotta-
We've been talking about it, we never really started.
So, you know, the best is right.
This is the start.
People send in images of PCP related stuff
and we will talk about it next episode
if you put it in or tweet at us.
I think the most reliable way is to use Twitter to,
let's develop a real hashtag right now for things for this,
that I can just search the hashtag and it'll all be there.
What we should do is if we're gonna do it on Twitter,
we should just create a moment on the PCP Twitter account
and gather all the tweets we got.
What the hell is a goddamn moment?
I don't know what-
You never use that.
A moment is a thing where you can save tweets
in like a gallery.
In a place.
That sounds actually super helpful.
It's what I use on Twitter for all my 3D stuff.
I just put them in a moment.
I have a moment of like when I invented
the alley-oop character.
Oh shoot, can I like make like a moment out of all
like the art sort of tutorial things that I favor?
The favorites.
Yes, you can make a moment for whatever you want.
Ah, that is so useful.
I've been wanting that.
There you go.
Yes.
Well that's cool, that's cool.
So all right, so maybe we'll do that
but I guess we should still just have a hashtag.
All right, let's call it hashtag PCP art.
All right, we'll go with that
and just whatever you wanna submit, we will look at it.
We'll do, we have to develop some like infrastructure
to actually listen to like music or something.
I don't know how we could work that in.
All right, but we're working on people.
We're trying to improve, we're trying to expand.
And you know, people have also been asking
about like having a voicemail box to listen to voicemails.
I'm totally down for that.
I mean we brought that up a while ago
but the problem was that logistically
we just don't know how to do it yet but I'm sure.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm sure we're a little bit of Googling
and maybe some actual effort.
Please send us instructions on how to do it.
I don't know, I'm too baby, I'm a baby.
I hope someone sends you a link.
When I hit two years old I'm gonna die
and I'll be replaced by another baby.
I'm not allowed to live.
My gun won't protect me from that age limit of my life.
But that's a good name.
It's a quality name.
Please draw that and send that to hashtag PZBR.
Please draw every baby with a gun.
Draw this perfect society of under two-year-old babies
all armed with guns and all the two-year-olds
being shipped off to the glue factory.
That sounds perfect.
No, to the gun factory.
The babies become the guns.
They get turned into guns.
Oh my God.
Well, I've done half your work for you artists.
Now get out there and put pencil to paper.
I'm the Ideas guy around here.
He is the Ideas guy.
All right, I think we're actually done now, everybody.
Hopefully we covered everything.
Feel free to tweet us at TP Crasinators
if I missed anything.
But hey, you should definitely be a patron.
Patreon.com slash theprocrasinators.
One dollar, you're in, you're in our shit,
you're up in our grill.
Two dollars, you're out.
Oh my God.
Someone should make it so it works that way.
Incredible.
One dollar and you're in, you get into the main chat.
You're in the fucking, the chat, the TPC.
Fuck, what is it?
The goddamn questions bar, the questions bar.
But we read lots of those questions
from in addition to the hashtag AskPCB on Twitter.
And also there's like 14 fucking bonus episodes.
And you get them all for patroning five dollars.
That's five dollars.
And beyond that, well, you're just a bit of a madman.
Well, that's it everybody.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for joining us for this intellectually
stimulating conversation.
I had fun.
I hope you did too.
Yeah, me too.
Four people is a nice chill sort of discussion time.
Yeah.
We should not have 70 people on the next episode.
Well, I will be on the next episode.
So there you go, one last person.
Look forward to Mages next game review
on the next episode of the PCP.
Indeed.
We'll insert it post, you know, in editing.
We'll get a little robot to say it.
We'll fly a little drone around Mages wherever she goes
that just pipes back audio only about game review
and game analysis.
It's got an algorithm to determine.
Draw that to everybody, this drone.
This game analysis drone.
Fucking everything.
Draw it all, people.
Draw it all.
All right, thanks for listening, everybody.
Give us your money, you know, do that.
And also, thanks for watching.
See you next week, everybody.
Bye.
Goodbye.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I come jerking myself?