The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I agree has a lifetime a lifetime more like
Nate says he's feeling fit and fine, and I gotta say that I feel nothing of the sort post rad con and that's what this
Podcast is all about fat fuckery
That's right
journey of being fat and not
It's I think just every aspect related to to fatness just
Odious forms. Yeah, of which none of us have because we all have I
Well, that's that's true
If we didn't have it before red con we do now that's that's for sure action giraffe was it worth it though?
I think it was
You know you can't get a giraffe job like that anywhere
It's all right
He kind of he coils his neck around your dick. Yes, that's how it is
So, let me give a little bit of backstory here like because right before rad con
We were all talking about like these sick diets. We were all gonna go on or we're on even
Jesse had just lost like 30 pounds or something through like just fasting for a month
Jesse's an insane person and can do these things. I don't know how Nate had just lost a bunch of way my broken
Brilliant, I'm down like 25 pounds for when I start so I'm looking good. I'm under 180 now
I had lost like a
Like 10 to 15 pounds before rad con Ben was talking about how he's bringing the squat rack down and me and him and DeVue
We're all gonna use the squat rack Ben. Why don't you tell us what happened with the squat rack?
Well, is that still a problem? Well, yeah, it is because okay
My squat rack at my last place
I had the squat rack, but we didn't have a place to put it because our landlord
Despite promising us the basement kept the basement locked and wouldn't let us in it
We were gonna set it up there. So when I finally moved down here to the fucking Casa de Conrad
I
Well, you know we we disassembled the squat rack put it in the car brought it to my parents house loaded up into the other car brought
It down here set it up realized I was missing a crucial part specifically the pegs on which the barbell rests
So yeah, so I called up my friend in my old place and was like hey are the are the parts lying around somewhere
And he was like yes, I will mail them to you. I was like, thank you friend
So like a week and a half later or like two weeks later
They arrive in the mail and it's the wrong part. I realized I was missing two parts two crucial parts
And he sent the other ones and I was like, oh are the other ones lying around and he was like, let me look
Oh, yep, here they are and so now and so now I'm waiting for those to arrive and once they they're
They'll be here soon
Okay, well, that's that that's great, but I just want to lift
I just want to fucking squat and deadlift and bench and be a strong boy
Understandable used to be however because I hate going to the gym
I fucking hate leaving the house to work out if I had the rack in the house
I would lift I would lift on the regular I have I have a I have a pull-up bar
You know like like in rad con house
There's a there's that pull-up bar in the kitchen, but I've got one that I'm looking at 24 hours a day
So all the time I just get up and bust out a bunch of pull-ups. Oh, yeah, like 30 now. I'm doing I'm killing
I'm a strong boy right now a lot of fucking pull-ups
My record is 50 my record is 50
I'm not that's that's legit that's legit when I was like 18 not not all at once right all at once all at once
We've got the we've got the one here I've been doing the same
I'm up to I'm up to guess guess how many I'm up to I'm gonna guess to 13 15
Human ability have been warped
Yeah, I'm up to five five five, okay
After like a week of doing pull-ups on the you know the biggest thing by far
Cuz yeah, the biggest thing is wait if you weigh little you can do like that's the most important thing even more than
Well, so so Radcon happened and I guess I
Decided everyone else I guess sort of got folded into my my my my big
Theatrics here that we just all completely let loose no one gave a fuck
Eating it all we ate out like 18 times we ate giant I hop and waffle house meals. We fucking we I
Personally, I drank probably two boxes of wine in the span of a week like you know, it was just non-stop debauchery
We were truly handboys that week I went there prepared for a week of decadence. That's what I
When I was there, I had no idea that that wasn't normal what you were doing
Well
It would be normal if it weren't for the fact that we were all on diets
Well, yeah, I went from I went from like before I got there like frying one chicken breast a day
To after getting there like going to Wawa and shoving ten donuts in my mouth
16 times a day. I was not planning to start a diet or a workout thing during Radcon
I went there with the full intention of you know, just you know indulging my all my vices and you know, you know
Just having fun just having fun with my hand boy. The problem is for Ben Radcon never ended and he's
Because at Radcon it was like yeah celebration. Let's you know, I'll get the soda with every meal
I even bought some sodas for the house for me to drink man. I was drinking alcohol every night, right?
So then Radcon's over and we're all like me and Ben and DeVoo are all like alright now
We're gonna start eating good again, and I'm immediately like I have withdrawals for everything
Yeah, I hadn't been smoking for like a month and a half
Ben comes around me and him start smoking together then somehow gets me up to like
Then somehow get like three or four a night Ben burns through like three packs in two weeks
And we're both fucking smoking up a storm. Don't tell them about my vices. I
I can't stop everything
I
Finally it took me like a couple weeks to like put the soda back away and be like, okay
No more soda again, and then I bought in a lot. I'm now smoking an electronic cigarette. So yes
Here's cancer. Good healthy excellent. I don't know if it cures cancer. That's that's what I hear
Maybe helps avoid it to some extent. Oh, yeah, where's my vape? Where's my oh, no, where's my vape? Oh, no
Crisis mode
You know what let's let's take this, you know, this is very this we're all just kind of talking about our own fitness right now
But let's take this a little bit more broad. Why do we all care so much?
What because it's the only thing that matters in life is being hashtag not fat I
I
Agree for me
It's not that the only thing that matters in life is having everyone know that you're well-laid
You're happy people have to know that your hashtag well-laid so that they'll know that your hashtag not fat if you
You have to get not fat to get well-laid so they know that you're not fat because just being not fat isn't enough to make them know
That you're not fat people are insane and they'll still think of you as fat like on the inside fat is like
Everyone is always looking down on you first for one reason or another and in my mind is just be that's their way of saying you're fat
So you have to get then and then you have to get all the girls and then you have to parade this this
Secession of sluts around these trophy girlfriends take them to all the parties and go look I do it with hot girls
Look, I'm not fat and they go well. He does have a girl around his arm. I guess he's finally truly
You know fat Jesse
I as the guy around here who's the most long-term committed to two fitness goals
For the longest stretch at least anyway
It is absolutely because I want people to see me and think this guy has his life together because I'm a deeply insecure person and
Only am happy when I'm feeling externally validated and I know it's because when you look fit people like you more
They'll assume that they are a better person and you're you know more likely to not even have girls
But you don't even get treated you don't even get treated like a human being unless you're a certain level of attractiveness
Yeah, let's be real. Yeah, you start with that with it. Well, I gotta say, you know, I'm I'm not that cons like for me personally
It's not like I need other people's validation
But when I see other people like Nate who are fit
I do think much more highly of them as a person just like automatically when I see fit people
I'm like, yeah, like anyone okay like not just any fit person though
Right if it's just like some bro, and he seems kind of douchey then I'm like, oh, whatever, you know
But if it's someone who's cool and they're fit. It's like a double whammy
Cool and fit let me have fucking everything. Let me tell you let me tell you about what a great person I am
See I have realized but by living, you know through my learned experience
See, I think I'm a pretty mediocre looking guy
Even when I was more fit like, you know, I still just I still just look like myself, right?
Like I mean people I think people work out with like they have these long-term goals
Like they want to look like I don't know they want to look like
Yeah, they want to look like Z's or they want to look like, you know, they want to be ripped or they want to be Brad Pitt
Some muscle guy or whatever, but like in reality the changes are subtle and
No, like almost no one ever fucking looks gets huge or looks like a fucking model or
No, no one ever it looks like their goals because there's things about your body that you can change and there's things about your body
That you can't like like your overall proportions are all gonna stay the same
You know like your height and like your shoulder to waist ratio and stuff
Depending where you start that can I mean if your hips shrink when you lose weight then you know a little bit
Anyway, I realized that you know like even even if I got even when I'm more muscular than I was now
I still like, you know, I still had kind of like a stocky build, you know, whatever and I'm just like, you know
being fit
doesn't matter and
Now I don't respect people for being fit. Well, I what this ties into my I mean, I mean I do
I mean, I think it's cool and all but like I used to I
Used to feel bad, right? Like watching say like like watching anime or something like the main character would be like pretty fit
Right, and I'd be like man, you know, I you know, I wish I looked like that or something like like I wish I was like
DBZ man DBZ inspired a generation including me to work now
But now I'm like, you know what looking like that is like half genetics and and it doesn't matter
And I no longer think that people are better for you just because they're worth it
I think I think they're worse if they're not. I don't think they're better if they are well
No, I do think they're better if they are I think I think what it is is like if there's a cool person
And he just happens to be fat you you don't hold it against them, but you like yeah
That's a shame. Oh, yeah, but if there's a bad person who's fat then they're way worse. Well, you know
I actually really like fat people who like own their fatness and throw it around those people are cool
You know, here's what it is. Here's what it is. If you if you like someone
Then yeah
That they're fat. It's true. It's totally true. It's really not a question about whether they're fat
All right, imagine this for a second. Do you like them? I don't know if I agree Ben
I don't think they'll like I know I think that people who like you like you less if you're fat
I genuinely don't know if you know if someone's cool then they're being fat is a part of their cool
I would say it's not that they don't it's not that they think less of you is this that they they feel like a
Separate sort of little disappointment in you that yeah, exactly like I have no chime in anyone
I know who like anyone who I know who is cool who is fat and I know that they like
Don't necessarily wish they were fat. Yeah, but that's it
That's but I feel like this constant Chloe like every time I look at them
I think God why won't you fucking not be fat anymore? Okay?
Here's what you people talked about like here's here's an example Drake and Josh right Josh peck started that show off chubby and adorable
Right and that's was part of his persona right is this chubby adorable guy by the time the show ended
He had somehow lost all his weight gotten tall gotten like really prettier than he was prettier than Drake at the end
Yeah, you know I'll drink at the end a hundred thousand dollars in debt
His whole persona just like didn't work out was fat Drake so
So so me and my brother
We go up we're watching that show back when we're kids loving that show and we watch that decline of his persona didn't work anymore
Well, it just so happened that my brother himself was a very chubby boy for like all his life until he was like 16
When the when the summer drought of 2012 came in and it was a hundred and five degrees every day
And he played tennis up against the side of a barn every day for hours and lost all of his weight
And one fell swoop and as he was doing it
I was like, you know like now that you're gonna lose your fat
You're not gonna be able to tell the same kind of jokes anymore
You're gonna be like Josh peck you need to adapt your style
All of his skits all of the like videos we did that were like little comedy things
He completely changed his persona to being like this like freaky weirdo guy and it totally works
So it's important whether or not you'll lose your charm if you get fit is just to be smart and adaptive and create a new
People are way terrible people are terrible at adapting to changes in their lives in general if they were better at that
I think that would help a lot with people like getting fit in the first place and then avoiding these like oh if I get fit like
Oh, I'm gonna have to change things about my life
You know just just be a new person just do things that you know lie to that
There's a great quote from from hot diggity demon Max Gilliardy where he said like you can't be funny if you're not funny looking
And after he said that like no after he said that
I looked at every single person I consider funny and I realized all of them were funny looking, you know
There's an episode point out looking in what way like Robin Williams doesn't look funny, but he still yeah
He does he looks incredibly funny because he looks like that guy looks like he will tell Jim an amazing joke
He just looks like a happy dude. I was gonna say Jim Carrey because Jim Carrey is spectacularly handsome
But that guy makes some pretty funny face. He's really funny. I don't
I'm funny looking as in like bad looking. I mean funny looking as in you look as though you can be funny
There's lots of people I look at and I go that person looks so fucking boring and unfunny and shitty
To do is not look funny, so that's true funny
He does not look weird as fuck
He's got like a weird bald head in spite of being like
He's he's a year older than me dude, I think he might be the most boring person I've ever looking
There is no scientific correlation between funny-lookingness
My confirmation bias
Clear
What's up, if you have like a like a
Like exaggerated features that you look kind of like a cartoon character or you can make funny expressions
Then it's easier to be like be visually funny
Anyone can make funny expressions anyone in the world can figure out that's not true look funny. It's not true
Is it if you have to accept this idea then you have to accept that you're funny-looking and you don't want to do that
Yeah, I know I'm funny-looking
What are you encouraging people to do when you say like you have to be funny-looking or you'll never be funny?
You're just living to figure out how to look funny the worst conversation
Let's get off of this. This is dumb. What are we talking about?
So I was thinking about why I would be drawn to like big muscly people
Because you're gay
Viewers at home spoiler. It's cuz he's gay. There's nothing more. There's nothing more beautiful than the male form. Okay, go on gay aside
You know I was thinking I think of myself as a pretty smart guy, right?
Like smarter than most people and so I think that like when other people are like there like what makes them impressive or whatever
Is that they're smart? I feel like yeah, but I'm smarter than that guy so that guy doesn't impress me
But then when someone's fit, it's like I'm not fit. So if someone's fitter than me
It's like I have some trust in them to be the muscle in the scenario
But there you go. There you go. You're coming from a place of ignorance
You're coming from a place of lack and it's making you and it's warping your perceptions if you had well you would if you had that
But okay, let's just how worthless it truly is well Ben
Let's say that we were out like let's say like at rad con like if we had been out for a drive
And my car had broken down in the middle of the highway and like who do you think I could most reliably expect to be able to
Push my car. I'm going with Nate and then probably Jesse next and not at all
Hippo can ride in the fucking trunk while we push the car
Like well like who would be physically capable of doing it. Yeah, that's what I'm saying like you have to innate like to me
There's some when I see someone who's physically fit and they're around it's like I I know I have someone
I can rely on when I need something physical to happen if I were to get if I hang out
My favorite thing about hanging out in like the city with some like my cousin boy. Who's this big motherfucker, right?
He's I mean he's fat, but he's also just big
If I'm hanging out with Boyd no one will ever fuck with me because if I was alone
I don't look imposing at all, but that dude looks scary. Who's gonna fuck with you anyway?
How often do you get into physical altercation?
Will you live in RoboCop world then when was the last time you lived the house leave the left yeah exactly
Okay, the point the point doesn't it doesn't really matter if these things happen or not what what really
What is at the heart of the whole thing is that we perceive these people to be more useful?
So we you know have a positive
You know because I know that I never get into physical altercation
Well, I have a constant paranoia that every single person in the world wants me dead and is going to kill me at some point
Yeah, but they're not gonna they're not gonna do it as a fair fight
Paranoia, but I'm smarter so I realized that I'm not gonna do it in a fair fight
Being fit has all kinds of real-world advantages and you never know when they're gonna be needed
And it's kind of a safety mechanism as well as like it helps your health
You know, there's a bunch of benefits to to be in fit. So it's a whole package. It's definitely positive basis
That's the thing with me. Is that like by not by not worrying about it. You mean?
No, I feel no by worrying about it
It just makes me feel more comfortable all the time sitting around like oh, hey
I did push-ups a few minutes ago. I'm okay with this feeling of just sitting or standing. It's a lot better
You know for me. I feel the rate what draws me to fitness is just how eat how like
I'm not all that tempted by like really delicious foods much more than I am just by like healthy food
like you know get some chicken and
Cook it with a tiny bit of butter and some water and some mushrooms and some cabbage and some
A spinach and then just eat that
I only like that taste slightly less than like a hamburger with like
Frot like like toasted buns and cream cheese and ketchup and a tomato
You know, but I feel a lot better after eating the other one. I feel like a lot of people
Can probably eat healthy and it's not even like wouldn't even be that hard if they just started because they're just not as tempted as other people may be
Yeah, I'm tempted by all food equally
Um, which is to say a lot
So you might as well eat healthy then you might as well, you know, yeah
I am by far most attracted to food prepared by professionals. That is the kind of food that I gravitate
Well, I know I never I never eat professionally like like a mcdonald's professional
Here's why I here's why I never eat out because one it's too expensive and two I resent paying
I resent paying food preparers for their labor. I don't think they deserve it
I don't think anyone deserves anything every time I every time I look at a menu the number one thing
I I think about is like can I what can I order that can justify?
Having someone else making it something I couldn't make myself, you know, but it's really almost nothing. You can't just make it home
I just I I emphatically disagree
There is nothing I've eaten at a restaurant that I could replicate with anywhere even 50 percent of
Oh, yeah in terms of the details, but you know what the main details are all that matters
I know but 100 percent of it. This this whole thing is very interesting to me
The uh, the the way you guys are talking about how food is important
But to me the perfect world is a world in which all the only food there is
Is that slop from the matrix that has all the nutrients you need basically soylent
All I want is that because then I don't have to even think about it. I can just work
I can do the things I need to do and I'll get a hundred percent of what I need supplements
Why don't you just become a supplement guy?
The only reason I don't is because I have to go out of my way to order it and currently soylent is not perfect
If we had the perfect thing that had everything I needed that would be that would be that I already do supplement
I have tons of whey protein like every day with shakes. I make delicious shakes, by the way, which are awesome
And they're super easy to make
But my dream is to not even have to spend any time on it
I would love to be a hamster with just like a spigot, you know with like a water bottle outside and just like put my
Mouth to it. I'm not all over my body. It's all I want. I do like food and making it
It's just I I like it, but I think of it as a human weakness that we crave it. I want it gone
I want to be a robot. I don't want to think about these things. I'm not really that extreme about it
Even if I had a robot body, I probably spend most of my time eating
Okay, well if I was a robot I could eat anything and just discharge it and it would matter
If I could have enough synthetic parts in my body that like that eating didn't make me fat
I would just never not be eating. That would be like my whole life. Sure. We all would but the machines we have
You know do get fat, you know, I'm referring to the human body. We get fat. We got all these issues. So
I've been considering being bulimic just just you know for the intellectual experience of like, okay, I'm growing up
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm talking about
Because then you can eat whatever you want. You can satisfy your cravings and then turn your teeth out of your face
Right, that that is one of the reasons that I haven't tried it yet
But maybe one I guess if you wear one of those mouth condoms, maybe
Well, it's just to go all the way down to your stomach. Yeah, I mean when you throw up. Yeah, okay
a mouth
Wait, I don't I don't
Oh my god
You get just gotta be like you just gotta be like fucking uh
Josuke and fucking wear a fucking rubber glove down your throat. Yeah
Catch whatever it is
Exactly
I'm gonna say be like Josuke and like punch through your stomach and just grab the food pull it out and then heal
In the most reasonable scene the most reasonable scene in the history of anime
When he fucking puts a rubber glove down his esophagus
Well, you know, whatever man to stand stands are well established to be crazy psychic things. They can do anything
So who cares
There's rules to these things the rules are they can do anything
I've personally never been fat
Just because of well
D
I'm saying I'm saying that I've never been fat. Nate has never been fat. That's true. The fattest I ever was
You know who else has never been fat hitler
Oh
No, he got fat. If you look at the later part of anything. I don't care about being thin
It's uh, uh, go on the point was that that's thin privilege talking
You can't see your own privilege
All right, forget it. No, no, please
Well, give I think I don't really know what my point is. It's just that I
Exercises has never been like a lose weight thing. The only reason I've been exercising recently
Is because I'm tired of having a bony butt and I want a nice butt that I can sit on that doesn't feel like shit
You gotta eat big you gotta eat big
You know, I was I was gonna say the hardest thing in my life so far was like when I was right now
I'm I'm losing weight
But when I was trying to gain, you know muscle for a long time. It was really hard
Uh, significantly harder than right now just restricting calories to eat more than I was comfortable eating
Per meal and just having to really calculate physically come do it. It's hard. It's really hard. Yeah, if you break it up over the day
It's easier. That was what killed victor when he was trying to do boxing was like rest. Oh, yeah
Like and rest and like yeah
I think a lot of people like anyone who doesn't know about like bulking doesn't realize like because uh, you know
My brother shade you guys all saw him. He's skinnier than all fuck, right?
Because he doesn't eat anything and like he's been for like months now
He's been working out like pretty regularly, but he hasn't really gained much because he just like
Even though he'll he'll move like you need to eat more and he'll be like I've been eating way more
I've been actually eating three meals a day and it's like
Yeah, you need to eat like 10 meals a day, buddy
He needs to get himself a calorie calculator and it's so just keep track of what you eat
And then you'll know like what you're doing now and then just add add some shit
You know, it's easy once you start thinking about the thing with calorie counting that I can't stand is that you have to
You have to expend calories thinking about it
It throws off the whole equation man. It's so much work try to think
I remember seeing a commercial advertising a cereal like
There's like all these cereals that say that they're really, you know
Have very few calories and then there was another cereal that came out saying it has even fewer calories
And the commercial is like a woman at a breakfast restaurant and she like looks at all the things and she has like a calorie scanner in her brain
Apparently non-diagetically. She looks at a donut 800 calories. She looks at like a waffle 400 calories
Then she looks at the competing brand. It's like 120 calories and she's like she's like i'll have that one
But then she looks at the other cereal 105 calories. She's like wait. No
I'll have that one and I watched that commercial when I was like a kid and and that was so retarded
I vowed to never calorie count because she looked like such an idiot doing it
I'm happy if no one else does it because I want everyone else to be a fat fuck because I'll only look better by comparison
It's great. Please continue. Please continue everyone my my fitness goals for here at fucking at digi house
Is I don't want to count my calories because I don't really feel like I need to lose much weight
but I do I do want to start like when I get that last part I want to start lifting because
I I like I haven't really gained or lost anyway
Uh, but I just want to get all right because even if you don't if you don't change what you eat at all, right?
Here's here's what's supposed to happen in theory if you don't change your dietary habits at all
But you start lifting then what starts to happen is your your you start you gain a little bit of muscle
Your metabolism goes up because your body has to burn more calories in order to maintain that muscle because muscle is more
Metabolically active than fat right um and then so just
If you start working out, you know, you will keep keep yourself at about the same weight
You won't gain or lose weight but more of your weight will be muscle and less will be unless will be right
Which is what I want to happen. So I don't I'm not that big about my diet
I just want to start lifting and fucking change my body composition because I'm because I'm a little bit
I guess I would say I'm a little on the skinny fat side right now
Which is a shame which is like the worst thing to be it is the worst it is the worst
But you so yeah be careful of that uh since are you following the teachings of ripeto mark ripeto because t-rex mode
Is always a danger when you're living the squat lifestyle doing that go mad gala milk a day
Yeah, I want to I want to be I don't want to be t-rex mode. I just I just want to be kind of the squat rack can be used for benching
Too it's got a I know I use mine for benching too. Yeah. Yeah, um
I want to bench all the time because I've always had my bench has always been my my worst lift
It's fuck lifting
Lifting is great. No it is not great shut up
You shut up. It feels good. We need it. We need it. There needs to be some discussion
The world needs to come together. We need to come together as a society and talk about how fucking boring
Lifting is it is boring. That's true miserable. Okay
Jeff everyone goes. Oh, you know, uh, yeah working out is hard
But you just gotta push through it and then you can do it. No, it's not hard. It's fucking boring
I
Why don't I just fucking kill myself
Well, I have to take out of my day to go lift is always the reason that I end up missing it, you know
Okay, here's here's here's all right. Yes, it is kind of boring
But I mean most people that exercise don't lift they do cardio and cardio is 10,000 times more boring than lifting
It's also more effective for overall health. They say cardio is a lot easier
It's a lot less boring because you're doing the same you can go on autopilot by just running on a treadmill
That's why it's fucking boring, dude. When you're lifting when you're lifting when you're lifting you have like a little micro goal
No, when you're lifting it's like it's like standing at a conveyor belt and the conveyor belt is your body
And you're just like Lucy shoving those chocolates into your mouth the same fucking repetition over and over lift it up and put it down
Lift it up put it down
No, you have to like concentrate on what you're doing when you're lifting so it's less boring
There's actually like a risk. All right. Hang on. Good. Good. What's up?
The thing was like when I'm like running or cycling on a thing
Like it's a it's a repetitive thing you you can turn your brain off
But you can listen to music and that makes it not boring when you're lifting
You have to you have to concentrate on it and you can't
That's exactly why it's not boring
Okay, if you have to concentrate on lifting
Lifting which is boring then that is twice as boring like going out for a run at least you can think about anything else
That's boring fucking plot out your novel like I mean to me like going for a long walk
I don't even feel like it's like cutting out of my day in any way because i'm thinking about the same shit
I'd be thinking about at home. So it's like I'm just doing what I would be doing except
I'm also walking or else like something that you can something that you can zone out of and think about something else
That's the definition of boring. That's all I'm saying. Yeah, but there's nothing. I find more boring
It's always boring. It's just that when you can zone out you can do something else, which is you know, it's entertaining
That's that's literally the definition of layering or you see that's what being boring means
Everything I've been doing has been all focused on making any sort of routine or habit that that is
Is structured around the lifestyle and daily flow. I already have you know and what I've been doing a lot
Every almost every day is just watching tons of anime
And so I like to do things that make that flow in with that really easily like getting a dumbbell and doing curls
Because you can watch stuff while doing curls. So I just like to do that, you know sometimes
Yeah, but then you're just curling. Yeah, but you know you can do more like one thing
I usually will do is that I will do like push-ups and sit-ups during the opening and ending themes
And that has made me able to do way more push-ups than I could before I'm sure at the beginning at the start of the year
I probably couldn't do like five
Because I hadn't been doing anything and now I can do like 30. I just busted out 30 pull-ups by the way. No big deal
I said push-ups day niggers from outer space. Uh, everyone worship me. I'm the greatest man in the world
Now you're going to sound all fucking winded through the whole podcast
Because I do cardio I recover quickly. All right, here's the thing
Here's a big part of why I have such a trouble working out
It's kind of tied to what devu was saying that like, you know, it's good to find stuff that flows into your day
I don't feel like anything flows into my day because for me
That's why I want to have the rack in the house so that I can just take like a little half an hour break
Head over there do like a couple squats and I mean just get right back to it even then like even just doing normal like
You know calisthenics stuff like when I feel
Sweaty and winded it makes me not want to do my job
You know like the job of sitting at a computer and typing which is entirely your arms sitting up
You know like as you type shit and it's like if your arms are sore because you just did 50 push-ups
Then that suddenly is miserable. You know, well did you all right? Let me tell you that's why I really love gross or something
That's why what I I have a ritual that I love doing of exercising
Immediately showering and then for the rest of the day, I feel like a golden god because I did my shit
Then I can just do my work
That's part of why I want to get back into an exercise routine because it was great because it'll make me shower more
Oh god, because I really should and let me tell you Ben needs that Ben could use that
Fuck off. I I admit. I'm look
I fucking I fucking live at my fucking house and I don't I work at home
Mostly, you know, I sit in my room and I draw all the time. I don't worry about going out very much
So yes, sometimes I go a few days without a shower because I don't think anyone's gonna see me
And but you know what? I feel terrible about it and I hate myself and I want to change
As long as you do that, okay
As long as they're shame
I'm satisfied so anyone listen. Oh, they're shame
You don't necessarily be discouraged by what did you said about not wanting to do computer stuff
After you've done a little bit of like working out because like I'm totally I don't I don't feel the same way at all
Usually when I've been sitting around too long
I start to feel like death is approaching
I know that feeling and I got rid of that feeling when I bought a $500 computer chair
That's how I got rid of that feeling
Well, don't so guys whatever you do don't buy a $500 computer chair. What's what's so special about this chair
You can sit in it for eight hours before it starts to really make you feel like yeah
Does it have a butt dildo? Is that what it is?
You've you've seen my chair, right? Yeah, but I didn't sit. I didn't experience it. I didn't experience
Well, it's the thing is it's not like it's not comfortable in a traditional sense. It's just
You can sit in it. Sounds like $500 well spent
Well, no like okay when you sit in like a comfortable chair
You're like, wow, this is real comfy and then like an hour later. You're like, oh my god my back
I'm gonna die in this chair. You sit in it and you're like
Oh, this is this this doesn't feel like anything but then suddenly like eight hours have passed and you're like
Now my back's starting to feel funny. Oh, right. I've been sitting in this chair for eight fucking hours
Let me bring up a fitness related pet peeve of mine and Nate. I'm sure I'm sure you're gonna agree the rest of you
I'm not sure. We'll see. We'll we'll see how stupid you are. I'm interested
um
When when girls say I don't want to lift because I don't want to get all ripped and muscled
Ah
No, no one please
Let me just I hear this all the fucking time. It drives me insane
Yeah, girls are well, well, you know what I was about to say girls are stupid
But actually everyone's stupid everyone's stupid on this point. Nobody doesn't people when you work out when you lift to gain weight
First of all, no girls think okay
Well, I just what I just said about you know how if you don't change your diet
But if you start lifting all that happens is you lose fat and gain muscle
You used to keep the same weight you keep about the same proportions or you keep about the same weight
You lose fat and you gain muscle you get you know quote unquote toned you get more toned is what is what happens
um
I don't want to get ripped. I do want to get toned. That's what I don't want to get
I don't want to keep muscle mass. That's gross girls think that if they gain any muscle
They will look like a bodybuilder
They will they think that if they fucking touch a weight if they pick up a single dumbbell that they will
Ew they'll get like some weird bulgy bicep that they'll get like veins in their arms
People are so fucking you know, you know, even guys think this too even guys. Can you imagine a male being stupid? It's true viewers
Even are you fucking SJW piece of shit? I
Yeah, guys think gut people think that if they fucking touch a weight like oh
I only want to do cardio because I only want to get toned people work for fucking years
They put in years of hard work and dedicated effort to fucking get ripped and people think that they'll do it by accident
Like it'll happen overnight without them noticing and then they'll be oh, no
Oh, no, I'm so muscular all of a sudden. Whoops. What a shame that I fucking lifted it all
Guys just to put a some numbers to put some numbers to this. That's not necessarily stupid. It's also
All right go all right you're first
I hate them
All right. Well, anyway, it's stupid. I was just gonna say to put it I was gonna say it's not necessarily stupid
It's dishonest and lazy. They know they're not gonna accidentally become ripped. They're just making excuses for themselves
Fucking idiot faggots
All right, I know people all right that is part of it that is sure some people I'm sure fall under that
But it's a lie that they've convinced themselves of
I agree and by the way, if you gain 10 pounds, so like less than one pound a month of intense lifting
That is like miraculous. That is great viewer. If you're sitting at home if you're sitting at home and you don't exercise
Um
100 percent of you would look way better
If you gain 10 pounds of muscle 100 percent you might think that that would look bad
You might think that being muscular is not an attractive look. You are wrong. You are wrong and ladies out there
I love muscular girls get ripped get ripped. I'll fuck you. I'll fuck the shit out of you. I love
I don't I don't really like I don't really like I don't really like the muscular look on a girl
But I do ladies at home
If you gain 10 pounds of muscle, you won't look like a fucking ripped weirdo. You won't get that look
You're just gonna look female bodybuilders female power lifters. Watch the watch. Look how cute they are. They're perfect
They're perfect women. I want us
I I used to I mean when I was in like college, you know, I read up
I read shit tons of literature on like the science of weightlifting and the science of you know
gaining muscle and stuff and so I like I haven't put it into practice in a while
But back in the day I did I was lifting like not I wasn't lifted
I wasn't breaking any records or anything
But I was lifting respectable amounts and I want to get back there and but yeah during that time
I would talk about fitness with people and nobody had any fucking clue
Nobody reads the goddamn sticky
I I don't want I don't want I only do cardio. I don't want to lift at all
I don't want to look like a bodybuilder. Ew idiots if they knew what bodybuilders eat
They would not have that concern. It's just such really should not such ignorant
That's what kills me. There's so much ignorance on such a vital
Area of being a fucking human being with a body. No, no
Ignorance and as Jesse said dishonesty and laziness. Yeah, right. I want to ask a question about about uh about uh
Lifting and stuff. Sure. I'm a kind of a new but at exercise and stuff. So I you probably know what to do. Um
If I want to bulk up
And I do the the right exercises for that. Am I supposed to do
A bunch of reps or like hold the reps for a really long time
What you want to do there's a there's a sweet spot that has been researched
Uh, and I think in like the 80s
They did some studies or this and they found out that like if you if you shoot for first of all you always want to go
To exhaustion. So just do reps until you can't do anymore
But you want to shoot for about 12 to 15 reps is the optimal sweet spot
So if you can do 15 and you fail, that's great
Do you mean 15 reps in one set or do you mean like three sets of five?
I mean, I mean 15 in one go
I mean, there's distinctions between um, if you do if you do it for 15 reps per set and do three sets
Like doing 15 is more for uh strength and then doing five heavier
You know doing five reps with heavier weight that more builds muscle or builds like size
All right, I'm just saying that this is this is what I've been hurt
And it's all of all of the strength building routines that I know of recommend sets of five
When I think it's you just want to do it you want to do it with enough weight
That that three sets of five exhausts you when me and victor were going to the gym together
We would start with like like weights that we could like whatever weight I could comfortably
Do 15 reps with and then from there
I would go up to each different one and see how far I could get until I got to a weight. I couldn't lift
Yeah, yeah, that's what you're supposed to do. And then I mean you keep the same number of reps, but you increase the weight
Yeah, and that basically every time you do that exercise. Yeah, you increase the weight try to do it
And like whatever your number is that you are able to do until your failure
That's fine. But just do it again next time until you can do like 12 or 15 then up it and so on
Okay, what I've been doing at the moment because I think I misheard you at one point earlier
Not none this podcast, but like I told me to hold it for a really long time
So I've just been doing like two or three
for like holding it until
That is that's that's really funny. Uh, yeah, no, no, that's not the no, you don't know hold
Holding a rep is not is not a thing
But I mean some people do it, but it's dumb doing them slowly is a good idea like doing it take like one one thousand two
and thousand up one
Maybe if you're doing a curl or some other gay lift well
If you're doing like a good lift like a squat or a bench press, you don't want to hold it
You want to you want to just you want to do it like explosively and just like power through them
Yes, that's true
And if you got any other questions give ask me anytime because I would love to be of use in this area
How do I muscle my dick?
You kegels dog kegels, you know, you got to do dick push-ups
Those two
Power or size man. Are you looking for power or size? You gotta all about the size
I only I only do cock push-ups for aesthetics
Hey, Jesse, we can see you're playing Tomb Raider
What discord discord is is what it's betrayed. Oh, yeah
Quit playing Tomb Raider anniversary
traitor
I hate
I bet the best program
Sulking and I'm playing Tomb Raider. No one can stop me
Laura Croft lifts for share and she looks good as fuck. So ladies be like her
Hey guys now, let's talk about another issue relevant to this which is being held back by the people around you
Oh, that's a big one dude. That's a big one. It is pretty big. You gotta be in a really depressing topic
Well, okay, here's it. Here's an example from my personal life, you know, because like
My family has
Up until we all got old enough to start affording our own groceries and shit, you know
Like my family has a problem where everyone has different taste and food and different needs and wants from the grocery store
You know, and it's like at dinner time. We make dinner for five
So it's gonna be whatever all five people can eat and if you're trying to do like a hardcore lifting regimen
Then you're gonna be stuck eating some fucking dumb bullshit that has nothing to do with your diet and plan
You know, it's like you kind of have to be self-sufficient about your food or at least like, you know
If you're if you're not old enough or you don't have enough money to be self-sufficient about your weightlifting then convince your parents like
Let me buy 10 cans of chicken, please, you know, like
Cans of chicken. Well, you know, I I think I really think that wait, mate
You don't do cans of chicken for uh, I buy I buy breasts dude. I buy fresh fresh chicken in a can fry them up
That's a common thing chicken in my my my friends when my friends were talking what they would do is buy like
Five like each each day they'd come home from the gym
And my friend brando would take like five huge cans of chicken and five huge cans of tuna
Mix them all into a bowl with like like an egg and like a bunch of other shit
And then just have this gigantic bowl of chicken and tuna and then just eat all of it and that was how they bolt
So this is this is like that's pretty good. Okay, you know, wait, wait, wait
Do you not know canned chicken? Is this weird like yeah, this is weird
I've never known anyone who does is it like can chicken with
Grady that you would get from a pie. Is that so no, it's just chicken breast in a can
It's like the way you get tuna in a can same thing. Yeah, it's the same
I don't know that I have no idea what that is. I've never seen this actually sounds pretty good. That's great. That sounds really
It's extremely great and extremely convenient. It's the best canned chicken
It's by far the best like because the reason they all ate that is because it's the best protein for your dollar that you could get
Like you can get eggs
Eggs are number one in my book. Like you can't eat 20 eggs at once or you're gonna get sick
So, you know, you can eat 20 cans of chicken that are like Gaston ate two dozen eggs every breakfast and three dozen every evening
So don't tell me what you can't do with eggs. Gaston's a fucking car too. Gaston is just fucked though, bro
Three dozen eggs, but now that he's grown, he eats four. Oh my mistake. I undersold it. No, it wasn't four and now it's five
It keeps going up. I don't know when he's I don't remember the Gaston diet
You know, you know why the beast was able to beat him because he eats six dozen eggs. That's why that's why I should
It's a lot of eggs
It's a considerable amount
But no to get to DeVue's point
It's entirely true that especially if you're a kid if you live it's it's because we live in these little pack units
Where if you're a kid you're entirely dependent on whatever your parents buy you have to eat it. You can't even argue
I think people I think that generally like the the cleanliness of one's diet is overvalued
I think people should worry more about the lifting
Unless they're like unless they're like an experienced lifter and they're really trying to do like a dedicated bulk or something
Well, that's the thing dude
If you just I think lifting's more important and that should be the focus
But oh if your parents buy you shitty food and you eat it for dinner
Well, yeah, it's not great, but you know what there are worse
Well, I'm not even really concerned about the quality of the food so much as the volume
Because when you're trying to bulk you need a lot of fucking food and you need to eat the right
You can't have fucking pies all the time and expect to gain
You know the kind of muscle you're looking for you you need, you know protein
You need that shit in your diet and even for me
I eat a ton of protein supplement with my food
Even then it's still hard to get like there's a there's a rule of thumb that if you're trying to bulk
You should go for like a one gram of protein per pound of body weight you have per day
So that's for me. That's like 180 grams
Oh my god, you really have to eat jeep. That's a lot
That's a lot of grams, right?
Well, your average person does not eat that much
Families like families and stuff is I think that a pretty sizable percentage of parents want their kids to be fat
Because or rather they don't feel better about themselves like they don't like I feel like a lot of
I was being hyperbolic. I feel like parents, especially moms usually put way more emphasis on
Having their kids be fed than having their kids be fit because of their, you know
A genetic desire to feed their children once again really hard for them to care about fears about their past like my dad
My dad grew up when he was in high school. His family had no food
So he was like super deathly skinny and like he was a super sporty guy
But he couldn't play on any teams because he was too fucking skinny
And so like he saw it. He's always seen it. It's like, you know
Everyone should like, you know, if you live in if you're in my house and you're hungry
You can eat you can eat whatever it is
It must be like he's always wants there to be food for people to eat and for you to eat whatever you want, you know
and I mean
Thankfully
Me victor and shea to all have pretty small appetite. So none of us have ever become super fat
But we easily could have you know, it's like overcompensating for my dad having been, you know, right?
So once again, this meme of uh caring about your kid's happiness strikes. Who gives a shit how happy your kids are
Our children need to be swole earth. They need to be more muscly. They need to be bigger
I don't care about my kids being happy. They should be as unhappy as possible
Uh to make them productive members of society. They're happy to see if they can figure that out someday later. Great
I don't care
incidentally, uh since I brought up my dad one of the one of the
biggest reasons that I feel the need to work out and get swole is because my dad is really healthy and really fit
And like it there's there's definitely for me a deep sense of embarrassment that I am half my dad's age
And he could easily beat me in a fight easily outrun me any I mean
He runs fucking like 10 kilometers in a in a morning just because he feels like it, you know
He'll bike across the whole fucking city and I can like run across my lawn and I'm winded, you know
So like just knowing that I am this able-bodied, you know
20 25 year old guy like I should be able to do all these great things, you know
But no my dad if he wanted to could lay me out in a heartbeat, you know, and like that's upsetting to me
I mean he doesn't upset me as much that victor is so fit because victor's also like
I mean victor's like broad-shouldered and like
Like he has he has the kind of physique that he would be able to beat me up even if I was muscular, you know, but uh
Millennials are ruining the movie industry and everything else says able-bodied man
That's a headline. Yeah
You said you said able-bodied. Yeah, I know why it happened
Um
Oh god, you completely threw me off. I have a problem eating a lot of stuff specifically like when
I have the opposite problem
It's the middle of the day and it's lunch lunchtime and I'm supposed to go and make something because no one's around
And I just like I'm too lazy to just get anything. I mean just don't eat anything
Hippo, I advise getting into protein powder because I mean you don't have to eat it
You just consume a bunch of powder and like a drink and it's done and that'll give you all that protein you need to build with
Some of them are even good. Yeah, it's not bad. Yeah
The protein powder I used to make my shapes is it make me shakes is absolutely delicious. I love it. It's the best
I eat shapes. I eat shapes. Yeah. All right. Let's talk about something more interesting. Um, such as
Fat women we hate them. Yeah. All right guys. Are you ready for a mind blow? Okay, but way long ago
We were talking about how if you like someone then like their fatness, you know, you'll like excuse it for them or whatever
It's picture this picture me seeing a fat woman
Liking her and not wanting her to die. It's happened. I'm just saying it's happened in my life. Can you believe that?
It's hard for me. I knew it. I'm a traitor. I'm a traitor. It's true
I've even been attracted to some imagine that if you like someone
Then it doesn't matter if they're fat. You'll excuse their fatness. It's true
It's not really the most important thing. I can't see myself talking to a fat person. Honestly, you know
Look at you fat person. You talk to cider. Well, not fat. And yeah, you think that
You were friends with fat people before by the time I became friends with cider. He was already hashtag not fat
I mean, he's fluctuated here and there but uh, you know, I mean when he when he was a kid
He was like 300 pounds and now he's like my weight. So
I don't consider myself fat. Well, you know, I mean, I definitely stupid
I used to consider myself to an adherent of the peter griffin rule of
Men can't be fat only women are fat, but I found myself excusing even them
When I when they're just when they're cool people, you know, it's just if I just don't like fatness
I think it's a bad thing to do for the most part unless you're hilarious. Um
Yeah, well, that there's a threshold where it becomes a bit
Much where like they're whiter than they are
Our healthcare at some point I have to pay for people who are less healthy and being fat makes you more risk
Uh a verse, you know, and that's just a bad I just just don't do it like I have to pay for that
Wait, that makes you risk a verse. Well, I don't think he meant a verse. You know what I mean
I think it means prone prone. That's that's what I meant. Oh, yeah. Yeah
So on that basis, I think I have a reasonable claim to ask people politely to uh, be consider the rest of our tax dollars
Thanks, obama
Yeah, um, I I okay. I'll talk about now. Um the problem I'm
I I encountered
Today yesterday
Uh the the past month so rad con happened all my vices came back and I've been struggling to get rid of them
but like
uh, the problem I'm having right now is
That there's a lot of shit going on in my life at the moment, you know
I got two new people living in my house. My parents are gone
You know, the house was a huge fucking mess after rad con and we only just cleaned it. Um
Like and I'm trying to get like all these projects off the ground me and devour working together
We're watching all this fucking anime trying to make these projects and stuff and at the same time trying to like
Work out and or diet and and stop smoking and all of that at once is just too much
And at some point I thought okay, I can't do all these things at the same time
But I need to get the work stuff done first
So I kind of went like fuck it, man. Fuck the diet. Fuck quitting smoking. I'll buy an e-cigarette
And uh, that's where I am right now. So I mean I'm in the danger zone if you will
What what advice do you have about this, Nate?
Well, that's that's was my that was my plan too. That's why I wasn't worried about anything else
The only thing I really wanted was to get the squat rack set up and start lifting and you know, fuck the diet
And if I get that settled then I'll be good
I think that what's what the best thing to do in a situation like you like you can't make a
No one in the world can just do a lateral shift to like a whole new lifestyle all at once. So like
It's small changes. I guess I would definitely make a plan of everything you want to change
For these things they're concerned like just get them all in a row and then just like do one like the easiest one preferably
Yeah, whatever it is. Just like do that the biggest problem for me is like, yeah, okay
Eating out makes me happy and working out does not make me happy and that's the hardest part is like
You know what?
It's you know deciding because I'll be midway through the day and I'll be like man
I could really use a sub sandwich right now or I could really use a cigarette at no point in any day in my life
If I ever gone man, I could really use 10 push-ups right now. That would make me feel swell, you know
No, but when I when I was when I was actually work
When I I didn't I didn't I never got the thing about feeling good after working out
But I did when I was so good afterwards when I was into a lifting routine
I did just kind of always passively feel a little better like yeah
It feels good to finish
Hey, you know what I mean?
Yeah, it does do because all the time I could just think I don't know
I just just felt more energetic and I could always think like yeah, I'm fit. I lift a bunch, you know
I it just passively felt a little better all the time
Do you really not feel Ben after like specifically after I work out and then if I shower right then and then I step out of the shower
I feel like a god. I feel like I'm glowing. I feel so great
I mean like I feel like Dennis Reynolds like I am the king of the entire fucking world
And everyone is below me and with to do with what I will like two years ago
Was the period when I was most regularly working out it was and me and victor were actually going to the gym
And uh, and I I got down to like 155 pounds
which is the lightest I've been in my adult life and uh, and you know
I I felt
Like measurably stronger and I really liked that aspect of it
I liked the idea that like I can I felt like I you know
The idea of like getting up to go do something was so much less tiresome
Like if I if I was thinking uh, let's say my dad calls me up is like hey, uh, go buy this thing from the store
And I'm like, yeah, I want to move. You know like that part was cool
but
Every single time I worked out I felt like shit for the rest of the day and usually the next day as well
And I really like
The last few times I worked out I felt like shit for
For a while, but it's just because I wasn't into the routine anymore. I wasn't accustomed to that level of activity
Is it because the doms? Is it the doms you're getting?
Not the doms just like fatigue
Every single time I did it
I was thinking like when am I gonna reach the point that I am that I am capable
Like when is this gonna get to the point where I've done it enough and now I feel good about it
But the thing is if you want to make progress you have to constantly you have to always push yourself to the limit
You know like your your muscles won't grow unless you rip your muscles
And if you rip your muscles then the next day your muscles are gonna feel like shit and so like
No, that goes away. You eventually get accustomed to that level of exertion. Let me just tell you I my friend Femian college
Uh, absolute legend of a man like he once he once thought that he checkmated me so expertly
This is after I like first started working out. He's like Nate. How? Okay, so when you work out
You rip your muscles then your muscles are torn the next day you work out again after your muscles have healed
They're torn again, but you're tired from that previous workout at what point will you ever get stronger than when you started?
It's never gonna happen. They checkmate working out as a waste of time
Get it out. You've got it out like understand that like how I mean how would anybody get strong if that
true
It's like zeno's fucking period
It's impossible to get stronger because you're always getting tired from working out like
To give Femi credit. He might have just been dunking on me and I just I mean
Did you at some point ask him like explain strong people then?
Well, yeah, and he also started working out recently
So I think he got over it if he ever really wasn't just fucking with me
But yeah, like you are going to feel uncomfortable. Okay, but the whole thing about dom's
Just as okay dom's goes away after you've worked out for a while
You stop getting the pains in your muscles for me
It takes maybe like two to three weeks of like lifting maybe every other day
And I just don't get it anymore after I've taken a break for a while and as for the fatigue
I mean I've been doing a hardcore running program running every other day for the last
Three months or so now and I just I just feel great all the time
I can't wait to run when I do I feel good when I'm running at the end
I feel like shit and I want to be dead and I hate everything about my life
But right afterward after I've showered and feel like a god again
Uh, I just I just don't feel tired and I can sleep easier
It's easier for me to go to bed at the right time and my whole life just feels bad
I'd love to be at that point, but like you know those months are hard those starting months are tough
Yeah, like well because you know me we've all been doing these pull-ups on the pull-up bar
And like there was a day where I got up to four pull-ups is the the best I'd done yet
And then this was like two weeks ago
I went into the to the garage where ben's got the squat racks set up
But you know obviously doesn't work and I just grabbed each of you soon
I just started taking the weights off the rack and just like doing a bunch of uh
Arm workouts with them, you know, I did a bunch of curls a bunch of like
Shoulder things over the head stuff like all all that good us as shit that you could do with big fucking round circular weights, right?
and I
Have not yet been able to do like more like I like every time I go to do four pull-ups again
I'm still sore and it has not stopped for two weeks
I have not had a single time where I could get up and go to do pull-ups and I felt like oh now
I'm finally ready again. Like it's just you know
I hear you dude. I hear you on that but what I would recommend is just literally ignoring the pain doing it anyway
I've I've been there. I have lifted done specifically with leg works out
I've done it and felt like sheer agony unable to walk straight without limping for like a day or two
But then I like it's been two days. It's time to do legs again
I do it again through the pain like it feels like sheer agony
Except when I actually start to do the actual movement of the lift itself
I have felt like the pain kind of goes away and then after the workout things have started to feel better
So I really think just doing it kind of mixes up the lactic acid gets it out a little bit
And like helps you move along towards recovery. I don't know about you
But for me, how much pain like bothers me depends on whether or not I know or slash think it's bad or good for me
Like there's a pain that all bothers me unconditionally
If it's pain, it bothers me
No, like if I'm feeling sore after a workout, it's like good because like I know that it's good for me
Whereas like if I'm if I'm getting like, you know
If if I'm going to the doctors and like getting a shot like the pain of the needle entering my skin is the worst feeling in the world
You guys you guys should see ben you guys should see ben when he needs to get a shot
He is the biggest spaz in the world. I've been I've been better. You know the last time I got a shot. I was way better
All right, that's great
I'm really freaked out when when when I don't what were you been there for?
We were getting shots together. I I don't know. It might have just been that time
We were going full gay or something. I don't know. Yeah
We were getting our age shots
um
I've been doing exercises for like I think like almost a month and a week now
You know like I've never really done any sort of regimented exercise before
And the first few days, um, it was mostly my legs. I was doing and my legs felt really heavy
Yeah, and it was weird like all the time. They're really heavy and then
I just sort of got used to them being heavy and now I realize that it's just because there is more muscle there
And my legs are no longer just sticks
Well, okay, too. It doesn't it doesn't hurt at all. It's just they feel like
Like they feel normal. Mm-hmm, but they don't feel like they've gotten lighter at all
Well, okay, sure, but just as a public service announcement
You can really only expect to gain like maybe a pound of total body mass
When you're working out at first, you know, we're talking about noob gains or something
You know that that is true noobs do gain faster significantly no no no no noob noob gains means that
Noob gains isn't about putting on muscle noob gains is about your lifts going up
And it's because you're right. Am I right here? That that's definitely true. You know that that actually might be right
All I know is that it happened really fast. Okay, well, you know, I'm not gonna question it. I'll believe it
If they feel heavier sure, okay
I mean, I have like really
Skinny legs forever. So what's that line from get action?
Creativity is a muscle and da da da da. I'm just gonna jack it something like that
I know the line because I wrote it, but I don't feel like telling you
Oh
This show sucks get out of here
When you go back to just interrupt me anyways, why don't you go be uh back to fucking burger king you piece of shit
It's sorry about interrupting you
I don't work
That burger king
I
Sounds like a sheep he does
Uh, are we going anywhere with this where no, I feel I feel like we're we've just been saying things about a clean hour
We've got a clean. It's very clean at that time. Yeah
I um
What else could we even talk about specifically?
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Jesse was gonna tell us about his nightmare of a burger run that he did before this
What happened with that shit? I don't know. You know, I had some wacky rant, but uh, oh come on
Come on
I stopped caring pretty quickly. I went to get a hamburger
Well, look, this is why uh, you know the trick to losing weight
Is to not eat
And that's pretty easy because eating is a tiresome burden
And it's miserable and no one should do it the act of getting food
Is usually so miserable that it makes the act of eating food not even fun
Like I had to get a hamburger today
I ordered it from the burger bar
So I get in my car. I'm driving to the burger bar to pick up my burger
There's all this traffic
I could have just walked there in half the time that it took the drive there. I'm hitting every red light
I can't park anywhere. There's like some weird halloween festival going on. There's cars everywhere
There's a fucking beer tent set up in like the entire parking lot
So I got a like I got a park halfway across town
I could have walked there in the time to get my burger
I get into the burger place the guy behind the bar. He's fucking ignoring me. I'm like, yeah, I can see my burger
I can see my burger behind the bar and the guy's just walking around and he finally he takes my card
He takes my debit card. I'm paying for my burger
But then he starts shaking drinks and mixing drinks and fucking around and doing all this bullshit
He's gotten my debit card. I've paid for my burger. I can see my burger. Just give it to me
Just give it to me and he goes to the cash register
He's finally about to start, you know, entering the shit with my debit card and he fucking answers his phone
Oh, yeah
A bartender answered his phone at the bar while I was trying to pay for my burger and then he turns around
After he's done on his phone
He's finally, you know, punching in my numbers in the stupid cash register. He turns around and looks at me
He says some stuff at me
He starts speaking in tongues in this bizarre alien language with like this weird goofy smile on his face
Like he's conversing with me. He thinks in his mind
He's speaking English, but he's like having a stroke or something. He's looking at me and I swear to God. He's going
Ah
And I'm just like, why what are you saying? What do you want me to say? I'm just like nodding and being like, yeah
burger boy, yeah
And he's fucking so then he's like, okay, uh, do you want to buy a burger by ketchup packets?
He's like monkey man. It's like a tick to this guy. You want to need a burger boy ketchup packets?
It's like, yes, I'd like some ketchup packets, please
Finally I get home. I open my I open my burger boy container
And I'm trying to get my burger. I look at the ketchup packets. There's like one ketchup packet. There's six mustard packets
Oh, no, I didn't ask for mustard. I didn't want mustard. I don't like mustard
I hate him. So now I strongly dislike mustard. That's I'm never fucking eating again
I'll never be a burger boy as long as I live. I'm a ham boy and only a ham boy for the rest of my life
Crucial crucial difference between a hamburger boy and a ham boy. That guy can never be a ham boy
A hamburger boy is not a good one. I don't know what a ham
I don't know what a burger boy is, but I don't want it anywhere near me a ham boy
You can trust a burger boy is some kind of child molesting monster from hell
I don't like him
But that's why you should never eat. That's why everyone should go on a strict
Um anorexia diet. It's the it's the diet that works. That's the campaign slogan that I invented for my invention of anorexia
You know, I I know that guy and I asked him what he was he was speaking burger boy language
And I asked him so what were you actually saying to just he said he was like what I was saying was jesse
Why don't you go back to work?
at burger king
No burger boy. No, I told you once I told you
I don't work at burger king
And you know, okay on a serious note, uh about this whole not eating thing jesse is actually
Jesse is actually let me just say real quick if if I had to get in my fucking car and drive to eat
I would never eat because fuck that. Yeah, that's why it's terrible that I keep that
We have all this food in the house that I have food in my fridge. I gotta stop. It's a meal that needs to die
Agree, but but okay, uh the the whole thing we've talked a lot about lifting
But the thing is if your goal is just to lose weight
Uh, the what just eat like the the food is what makes the difference just figure out what you're eating wrong
Eat less calories just eat like half of what you're eating now
That's that's the way to do it a lot a lot of people think that just losing weight is a good goal when for most people
It's not most most people should be if they want to look better
A lot of people think they'll look better just by losing weight
But really everyone should be trying to gain muscle too because it's always good
Everyone thinks it's everyone thinks it's less important, but it's more important in my humble opinion more important than you know viewer
I I'm more I'm talking to like the fat people right now who are seriously looking to lose weight
I think people really need to spread the word it needs to be made
More people need to be made aware of the fact
That losing weight is the easiest fucking thing in the world
It's not difficult anyone who says it's too hard to lose weight is a whiner and a fool
You know memes really reinforce themselves is just is just eat less shitty food or just not eat at all
It's so easy you see food and instead of sticking it into your craw you don't stick it into your craw
And that's all you have to do. It's zero effort
It is a massively destructive meme out there about like the incredible difficulty involved in losing weight when like you said
It really is not that complicated if you put a little bit of thought into it a couple months ago
I just got bored of being fat. You know it was funny for a while
You know I I figured you know everyone every every great artist should have their fat years
It's it's you know
It there's a novelty to being chiefly for a little bit. You're like, yeah
I can sit around in my chiefly body
And I can you know I can have the women flock to me because women love a man who's well fed
They love the the biggest man in the tribe
But you know after a while the novelty wears off. I'm like, okay. I'm bored. So I just decided one day. I'm done
So I fucking stopped eating. I lost 30 pounds in like one day. It was the easiest thing in the world
He cut his leg off he got his leg off
Rad con I go to rad con and you know rad con is like my week and a half of decadence while I'm there
I I gain like like a bunch of you know, first of all, I went from like in a couple months
I went from 225 to 195 and I was feeling good. I'm like, yeah, awesome. I'm the best at this. It's super easy. I'm cool
I'm smart. I'm bad. I'm cool. I'm nobody's fool. So then I go to rad con. I'm like, okay
I'm gonna shove all the fucking food in my mouth. I don't give a shit. I'm at rad con. It's party time party central
Drinking beer and smoking cigarettes. Do I like to party? The answer is yes shove it all in me, baby
So I'm I'm I'm going to rad con. I so I I get I get a little way to rad con
I went from 195 to by the time I got home from rad con. I was like 205 again
Mm-hmm. So I get home
But then within a fucking week of getting back to my old habits. I'm back to 195 again
So it's so fucking easy even if you fucking splurge and get fat again for like one week
It doesn't even matter. You just stop eating again. These things are always fixable. It's always fixable
There's no need to despair. You know, it's always always always I was saying earlier. There's always room for mistakes
There's always room for a fun week of decadence and splurging
Anorexia
Invented by Jesse Wood
The diet that works and I just put that on a t-shirt. It's just important to think of of eating as a part of like
The mechanism of your body. It's not just indulgence that you do three times a day of having infinite fun. It's important
You know, that's what I want people to know. I promise everyone
Everyone in the audience if you stop drinking soda, you will just
Naturally lose like 10 pounds join the water club, baby
Every time I've ever started drinking soda. I've gotten like fatter instantly and every time I've stopped drinking soda
I've gotten thinner instantly like it's
Unbelievable drunk. I've probably drunk less than a hundred sodas in my entire life because I just don't like them
Yeah, that's that's pretty good. That's probably why I'm so skinny
I drink a soda now and it's just I think I had a soda when I was like a year place
There was dr. Piper like I haven't had in a while gross way too sweet. Can't it's like drinking a syrup of sugar can't do it
But whatever it's not about me. Incidentally, if you're an alcoholic like me scale back your drinking to once a week
It helps also
Drinking is like a lot of calories a lot of calories in that alcohol
Also, you might be interested to know that alcohol is
Technically a poison only in the sense that it has no nutritional value whatsoever
And is converted directly into fat the alcohol calories are nothing else happens with them
Other than the mechanism of your body processes those calories into fat
There's like nothing else happens with them. They just get stored as fat
It's interesting and that's the same with sugar sugar is the exact same way
Yeah, I was gonna say yeah
Carbs do that too. I think well it depends on the type of carb, but but yeah, like is that right?
Yeah, there's a little bit of a difference into what they do, but whatever anyway closing statement viewer
If you're worried about getting healthy fuck off just go lift
Just lift and don't worry about anything else. Everything else will take care of itself. That's what I think
I would say just eat right and don't worry about lifting that much worry about that later
Okay, so let me get nothing and lift all the time. Yeah
So if you are if you are at home if you think if you think you have a fitness problem
You do but no matter what the problem is you will find that lifting is the solution
Here's my tip and all other paths will become clear to you of all the solutions all the plans you could do
Do whichever one is easiest like if you love soda you love chips
You love Fritos, whichever one you love the least try to stop eating that one. That's how I've done everything
I've just been like I'm not when I started like you know, I quit my job
So I had the baseline of having had a blue collar job for energy usage
But now I'm like, all right, I'm going to try doing push-ups and setups and stuff like that
But I'm not going to give it any schedule because I know I'm not going to be able to do a schedule
I'm just going to do it randomly whenever I remember to do it
And I has such low expectations for myself. I was able to exceed my expectations all the time and it was awesome
Yeah, excellent. Yes. Take it small steps. Couldn't agree more. That's the way to do it. That's the way to do it
Or you could be a hero like me and make spreadsheets and do everything
You know hardcore all the time be the strongest man in the world. Yeah, that's also possible too
Or just take a start like that though. Yes. I started as a guy. I was born a god and I've been one my entire life
Or just take up smoking. It makes you less hungry
Nate you were you were never you were
You've always been you've always been fit-looking, but like yes before you ever lifted you were like skinny skinny ripped
And then now that you lift you're like muscle ripped
He went from a Simone to a Kamina is basically what you're saying
Oh, don't don't sell Kami to that short by saying my current body can rival the god himself one day
I'll be a one day. I'm gonna do a the reason I lift is so that I can do a good Kami to cosplay one day
And one day I will no I can't I'm not fit enough not even close. I have to be twice my size
You were kind of fat. Yeah, Nate's not cut enough for it yet. I'm cutting right now. He has been he has been
I need bigger shoulders too to be like Kami, but whatever. Anyway
Oh, whatever you think Kamino would fucking worry about the size of his shoulders. I want to look like him and I know what he looks like
Hey, yeah, you know what you know what?
Oh, god the closing statement on all this. Um
People that lift to be cool. Yeah, you know what's way cooler than being fit is not is not worrying about being fit
Worrying about how you look is way more uncool than being fit is cool
Well, if you're like me and you bottle it up and never tell anyone then it's perfect
Then if you just pretend then you're just then you're just secret uncool
That's fine. I'm prepared for that
Absolutely like he said it's about other people thinking that's right. That's right
We've been we've been we've been talking. You know what? We've gotten off topic the real topic here
I don't know why I haven't pushed this harder the real the real truth of the matter
Is that none of it matters and being fits not important and if you think it is then you're not cool. Yeah, you know for me
It was that's only if your priority is happiness
Right. Mm-hmm, which is not for me. It was like I think it should be for anyone
It does not believe in happiness. Nope
Everyone everyone in the world is just a pile of misplaced priorities. Like people that's true
People think they have to lose weight. They're wrong. They actually just need to lift
But then that whole thing is based on thinking you need to be fit
But that's wrong. You just need to fucking not be a little bitch and not worry about how you look
That's how that's the truth. Honestly. Honestly. I think being fit is kind of gay
Or no, I think I think being ripped. I think I think working out too much or I think I think like
No, that's I've only seen sometimes
I think it's the only way in my life to this point that I've seen other naked men has been at gyms
So that's hashtag pretty gay. You know, hashtag pretty gay. I don't know
You know what? I think I think there's a suite. All right. There's just way too many closing statements
So we're gonna wrap this up now. There's a sweet. There's a sweet spot of how much you should worry about fitness
And I think I am I am under that bar. I am I am worrying not enough right now
But there is definitely you can definitely worry too much. Sure. Okay. All right. All right. Yeah, I agreed
All right, we're done. Fuck fitness. All right. Thanks for listening everybody. We will yeah hashtag fuck fitness. We'll see you next time
Thanks for listening everybody say bye. Bye
I'm sorry. I apologize. I apologize everyone. I fucked up. I fucked it all
Oh
Be working right now, but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick. I'm jerking
Myself. I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money
I'm supposed to be creating funny
Things that the people gladly will pay for
Artistic genius. That's what they came for
Instead I'm tweeting
Ashtag repeating
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling
Yeah
It's quite the burden
It's a hard knock life
Being a genius