I'mma bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello internet, welcome to Pro Crastinators.
It's uh, it's looking like I'm here. It's 10 25 a.m
No one showed up give us give us silent
Withered on the vine whatever that means
So, you know what that means looks like we're starting another
We're starting another Ben cast will it conclude a Ben cast or will we have a or will we have a new interruption?
We have some such an inconsiderate interruption as the last time
Only time we'll tell but you know what this means. This is my opportunity to phone it in. Oh my god
Did you wait until I started what no I didn't know you had started I was sorry I was late
you idiot I
Literally just started like a minute ago. Well, I guess it looks like I'm on time
All right
Very good very very nice. Hi Gib. How you doing? Hey, I'm good
Okay, sure are you recording I am yes, okay cool very very nice
What's going on
Uh
Nothing I was just playing I was just playing a even colony
On which is free on the epic store, but now it will
until November 11th
So you you've you've missed it if you're listening to this lol
I guess I'll I guess I'll google it. It's uh, it's like a city
Simulator building thing but on space
New planets and
It's it's pretty good. It's pretty nice
You got your you got your buildings and you got your immigration to for new residents. You got your housing
air filtration
farming
Pretty good. I I have never really played a city builder games
Although I think I can understand the appeal
I've just I've just never really really delved into the genre
I have played a lot of them
uh
Actually, I guess I've played sim city 3000 a million years ago
And and some other like tangentially related stuff
I like I like city building in in like the the the
The uh
Oh, what is it? What do you call it when it's like stats and figures?
When you're over viewing all of the all of the numbers
Spreadsheets
Yeah in the spreadsheet fashion. I don't know how to describe it
But it's like nice like balancing all of the food intake and food
You know consumption you can ration things
Sure. Yeah
I had a I had I had a version of sim city on like fucking windows 3.1
Uh
Like I had a really old like it came that had sim city and sim or like I think the original ones
And I that was when I was a kid and I and I found them I found them impenetrable
Uh, I couldn't really understand them. So, uh
Didn't end up playing a lot of them
Uh, I would fuck around with them and like like try and make natural disasters happen
Uh, and that was like pretty much all the enjoyment I could get out of them
Because I was an idiot
Yeah, there's like there's usually a point where it's like it's so big
That either it's too big to fail and then there's no like challenge anymore
Like you've got too many completely filled storage
Things and it's like you're never gonna run out of food or water or anything
And you're too powerful to be killed by an invasion
So like natural disasters are the the only thing that can like
Like make it tense again, but they're also annoying to deal with because of how many things break
Yeah
Well, I mean, that's the that's the point you that that's the point but like you're annoying yourself. Yeah
There's a point in in a lot of these games where like I haven't reached that point in even colony
I'm sure it'll get there where like
There's no challenge or it's too challenging and too stressful
My favorite, uh, just like real life
Yeah, my favorite city building things are one where like
The it's it's more casual, but like the real fun is going down into your city and exploring it
Oh, right you can do that and some of these kind of like how
Kind of like how
Or couldn't you do that in the roller coaster tycoon?
Yeah, all of the tycoon games where you can
Uh, like theme park world as well
Yeah, you can make your theme park you can make your roller coasters and then you can ride them
You can walk around zoo tycoon. I love all those fucking
I've I've also never played a I've never played a tycoon
I never played what I cool
Zoo tycoon's good because you can get a lion and you can just pick it up out of the enclosure and put it
Into the normal part of the park and people will scream
Will they die they'll scream and run and the lion will not really kill anyone
Unless no wait, I think the lion can kill people
What's the point of a lion if it can't kill people?
I think it can kill people and then like the park rangers are like, oh shit
They dart it. That's what I would shoot it shoot it with sleep darts and then it gets put in a cage
And suddenly it becomes an RTF suddenly becomes tower defense as you put more lions out of the cages
that there was this zoo tycoon like like expansion pack
for like
Like dinosaurs where you could make you could unearth like fossils go to a research station
and then like ala pokemon create dinosaurs with the fossils
And and then you can just have dinosaurs and then if you break the thing the dinosaurs will go on the on the rampage
And try to kill people just like Jurassic park and then you can go down into first person view
and like use like the the the special harpoon gun to like
Like put it to sleep again
And that's what I used to like doing. I used to like getting a bunch of dinosaurs and then becoming an fps in zoo tycoon
That's just great
Just play just play a game that works. You're supposed to shoot dinosaurs. No because then they're hard
They'll they're like, oh the dinosaurs have a lot of hp and they'll kill you. It's like that's not what I want
No, no, I want
It's not games to be easy and never challenging
I can't get off to shooting dinosaurs in a context where I'm supposed to be shooting them
I want to feel like I really shouldn't be shooting these dinosaurs. That's that's what does it for me
uh
It's the transgressive element of it that really gets my that really activates my neurons
Yeah, uh
I'm trying to think if I ever play at any fucking any good video game in my in my whole damn life
No, uh, yeah, I have the old really old sims on my old ass computer. Um
No, I've just played fucking jrpg is like a fucking nerd
I mean those can be good
No, they fucking can't you could you can have like an a story and it's like you've watched a a movie
That's the worst over the course of like 170 hours. God. I would
I would never watch a movie
Uh, uh
Yeah, I fucking hate movies
What a waste of time am I right? I hate me. Uh true movies movies are always like in that
awkward spot of
Like they're too long to just casually put on and like I need a break
But then you're you're like fucking up the pacing of the movie if you take a break
So you feel compelled to like watch it all in one go, but it's a little bit too long to watch all in one go
I actually watched uh, I was cajoled into watching a movie
I was I was plied with alcohol and then coerced into watching a movie that I would never have consented to
Is it the my old pony movie?
No, no, no, this was on halloween. Uh, we watched uh, we watched uh house or house or house or you know the japanese
Uh horror movie the old one. I do not know that
Um, I had heard of it. Uh, I don't like horror movies and I was I don't watch horror movies on halloween
I know ha ha that's what you do on halloween, but like I hate that shit. I don't want to do it
Uh, but they got me to do it and it was fine because it's it's a movie
It's old enough that like the special effects are not convincing at all
And so it's just kind of silly
Well, I mean it was legitimately creepy at times because you could tell what they were going for and what they were going for
was pretty creepy, but I wasn't like
You know, it was fine, uh and uh
very
Very compelling the cinematography was very weird and interesting and they did
The movie started with like just lots of like
It starts really weird it starts
in like a very self-aware sort of like
parody
Of like of like a like a like a lighthearted drama
But they have all these uh, they have all these these scene transitions of like
The the one thing we we kept noticing was that the the there are all these like painted background
There's like very obviously painted backgrounds in like every scene you can really tell like that's not a real sky
Like that's a painting and then at some point they start like
putting characters in front of
Paintings and you think oh, it's more painted backgrounds
But then the camera will move and you'll see like no wait
They're actually just standing in front of like a mural at their school
Uh, uh, that was one weird thing that was very disorienting about it. Uh, uh
I don't know it's hard
I could probably talk a lot about house, but it's really interesting. I've seen I've seen the poster of this cat
with the big lip
teeth
Yeah
The cat was just kind of
There at the end only at the very end was I like oh, I guess that's why the cat's on the poster
Okay, sure
Is it if I just search house movie I typed in house japan movie and I got it. Yeah
um
What else could I there were there were
Yeah, the the the
Like the kills are very
It's not like a slasher like people don't get like killed by a person. They basically get like
they basically get like
sort of
separated into pieces by some sort of like
the the
magical force
of the house itself and like their
Pieces will like keep doing things that like they were doing while they were alive like uh
The the the the girl who eats all the time like
She like falls down a well and like her head gets separated and like they find the head and the head tries to like bite them
And like one girl is like playing a piano
And like the piano eats her and then they find like they find like her disembodied fingers like are still like are still like
You know playing the keys of the keyboard and stuff
This is a spoiler but like
One of the girls is named kung fu
and she's just like tough and does karate or whatever or kung fu I suppose and um
She's like the last she's like one of the last ones to die
I think like the house is going like crazy the house is like really like
You know the ghost is like all right. No more fucking around. It's time to kill all you motherfuckers
And uh, she starts like she does she's like doing karate
But like she gets sucked into like a closet or a mirror or something. I don't even remember but like
Her like but like after she does like her like legs and her like hands like come out and her legs just like continue doing
Like karate kicks like against like the ghost
Uh, I just started like bloody disembodied like legs just kicking
Very amusing. It was very cool. It was very cool
Uh, yeah a a rare w a rare w for cinema as a whole
I thought you were gonna say a rare w for the nation of japan
That that too that too. Yeah, finally they've contributed something to culture
Um, apparently the director also made a live action the girl who leapt through time
Which I guess is based on a book
Oh, you know that that that anime movie go through like time
I've seen the anime. I think I thought it was an original. I didn't know it was based on a on a book
Did the live action version come before the anime?
Uh, 1983 so I think so
Uh girl who
Yeah, the movie was 2006. Oh, I didn't know that I had no idea. Um pretty neat pretty neat
I don't know. I don't know what else to say about it
Um, is that the same guy who did summer wars right summer boys some it's not summer boys
Summer boys and that was okay. Okay. Am I crazy?
But the summer wars is the movie by the guy who made the digimon movie
But like the digimon movie was really good
Yes, you're thinking of it's the right person
And then and then he was like, wow, I wish I like I wasted my great idea on the digimon movie
I'm gonna go make the movie again, but not digimon this time
I'm gonna make it my own movie and that was summer wars, right, right
I
Think so
This is a story that I feel like I've heard repeated many times
Uh
Uh, yeah, yeah, this is all it's all the I have the pieces of this story in my in my mind
But but but scattered but separated you might say into their various pieces and they continue to do
They continue to do things in the house of my mind. Hmm
curious
Yes, he did the digimon adventure. He did the go through it through time summer wars
Yeah, and then wolf children more recently
Uh another one I have not I have not seen wolf children wolf wolf children wolf children is that one that has
That scene right didn't like Trixie talk about that scene one time where like
It's like the kids growing up and it's like one shot from like the side of the house
And like you see them like living their life in the house as they like get older or whatever
I have no recollection and it's like one shot from one one side of that
It's just one like cut out shot of the house and you see them dude
I filmed this anime movie in a single take and yeah, they did it in one take
They drew it in one take
No, we're racing
Yeah
House is cool house was a good movie
I got
I was I was I was getting drunk, but I didn't start drunk and I and I was uh and I
Even even at the beginning while I was mostly sober. I was like, oh this
The tone of the tone of this movie is very weird very interesting and and and I'm engaged
And so I was
Yeah, do you do anything on Halloween?
Uh, oh
you know
Not really in fact, I was we were recording the pcp on halloween. Yeah, we recorded it in the in the morning
Uh, but for me that was like
Oh, right. It was like 3 p.m. Going into like going into the beginning of the afternoon. Obviously it was dark
So like it was trick-or-treaters happening near the end
And I will I really there
Oh, that's pretty really like maybe just after we'd finish recording. It gets dark at 6 p.m. For you. Well. Yes winter
I mean it gets dark pretty early. I think it gets dark around like seven or eight this year
Uh
I forget how long we went but yeah, that was happening and I
Earlier in the day had carved the the jack-o-lantern and I was like that's that's a good one
I think I was it was pretty good
And then that was put outside and that's it. I didn't really answer the door because I don't like doing that
I didn't have a costume because I never remember to do that through the whole of october
And I was like, well, whatever
And then as soon as halloween was over I was like, you know what I'm ready
I'm ready for halloween now
And that's how it always goes. I'm always ready for halloween after halloween is over
Well, it's easy to be ready when it's too late and you can't do and there's nothing to be done
Yeah, but like spooky stuff Howard's way out spooky stuff is fun
Like like quote-unquote spooky because I you know, I have a pumpkin oc is my main character that I use for things
So I just use I just do that all year
I don't feel compelled to only do it during halloween. So I can just do it now. I can just do halloween
You know november if I wanted
And it would consist of me watching a scary movie
And drawing a picture of a scary thing
It's it's true. It time is merely an illusion. The calendar is a human invention
It's merely a it's merely a social construct in fact
You know, you could dress like a goth whenever you want
That's true. You don't have to do it. That's true specific night. And you should do it all the time
If you want to be cool
Just like me in high school
Um
How how goth where are you been? I was uh, I was not the most goth. I was a bit of a
I was a bit of a poser, you know, I had some I had some trip pants
I had a couple of pieces of hot topic jewelry
I spiked my hair a little bit, but uh, I wasn't like, uh
I didn't like go to like I had a couple friends who went to like like, you know rock shows and stuff
Like like, you know local bands and whatever. I didn't really do that
uh
uh, I just
I was I was like
Five out of ten goth, you know
Uh, so like I was a bit of a hanger on just kind of all my friends were doing it. So I did it too. They I'll be I'll be honest
trip pants. I never actually had trip pants
No, you should get some you should fucking get some I they they look like like
The goth equivalent of like flares, you know, you know, uh, uh, what do they say? Uh, they say, you know, the millennials
Millennials are still wearing, you know, um, skinny jeans
But like among zoomers, you know, the big like baggy jinkos are coming back in style
I feel like the trip pants should come back along with that trend
I think that would be some of them look cool
But some of them definitely look like restrictive in an in an annoying way like chains connected. Well, they're not they're not built for
They're not built for performance skip
But they're built for performing honestly, I'm feeling I'm feeling
Stupid I oh I feel like maybe I should get some
And just wear them. Well, I already I already look I already looked like a fucking moron in public
I already dressed like a fucking child like a complete imbecile
Why not just go all out, right? Yeah
they're funny
I
Have like always been like, oh fashion that's for like if you're look at look at this shit
I've never really been like, oh, I'm gonna do like a an outfit. It's like too
Feels like too much of a statement. I don't want people to notice
But I I feel like I should not necessarily trip pants, but like
Something a statement, right? Yeah, make it. Yeah making a statement some of those like huge puffy like cute like sneakers
That I've seen I guess these are like girl pants
I guess these are like girl pants, but like what's the difference like who who would
Who would see you wearing these and be like?
Those are girls trip pants idiot. I don't think anyone would wait. What are you looking at this picture?
I just posted in the general. Oh
I think it's the midriff, but like the pants themselves are yeah, the pants themselves. I don't think you genderless
Yeah
I mean heck it's getting chilly out the weather's right for trip pants. It's trip pants season, baby
Some people get some people, huh? We know the metal get really cold
Just you just gotta wear long johns underneath
Some people some people get excited when it gets chilly because it's sweater weather for me. It's trip. It's trip pants season
Look at all those pockets you could like keep
All sorts of things girls get so excited when they're like, oh this dress this dress has pockets
This dress has pockets. Oh, I love it. Well, guess what losers
I've been wearing. I've been wearing more. I wore more pockets in high school than you'll wear wearing your entire thigh
More zippers
chains straps buttons
I I do I have been meaning to go
I have been meaning to go and and buy clothes. I have I have not bought clothes in a long time
um
Say I have lots. Yeah, like most of like redo my wardrobe
I got rid of a lot of old like
like pre-transition
genderless, but
nevertheless
lame
T-shirts that are just black or whatever
I need some real shit. I have a lot of uh, I I have a lot of clothes from
Before my transition by which I mean my transition from uh, uh fit ben to fat ben
um, so now I have
Well, I have a bunch of like things that don't fit me, but also
But also I'm losing weight again because I'm working out again and I've
But also just kind of the stuff from before just I sort of don't want like I don't have anything
That's like really good and I'm like excited to wear it again. So like
Fuck it. I should just get some new shit
Um, but maybe I should wait until I lose a little more weight because I am on I'm on I'm pretty on track with that
And like what would be the point of buying, you know
Fat pants at the moment when like if they'll be too big for me in like a couple months
Well, that's why you get trip pants because they got like they got belts so you can adjust. Yeah. Yeah, true. Yeah, true
Um, you can tighten it with the belts halfway down if you want to show off your knees
Um the shape of your knee or something
But every every I don't know every time I go
It's been it's been it's been a while since I've like gone
Clothes shopping and and it's been even longer since I've gone clothes shopping and found anything that I like
Usually I'll go someplace and I'll be ah, I'm gonna look for something like yeah
I'm gonna look for something that's cool and that is like my vibe and then like makes a statement
Right and I know, you know, that sounds like such an easy thing
But then like it's so hard to actually find something like that
I feel like to find shit like that you have to be like making an active effort
You have to be like going out and like clothes shopping like regularly and once in a while you will come across something that is like
This is just what I'm looking for
This is something that I'm like excited to wear and then I think is is gonna like, you know
Bring my ensemble together. That's not something you can just casually stumble upon which is sad and demotivating
Because it's like damn. What if I just go out to the garment district or whatever and I look around and like
There's just nothing good there because usually there's just nothing good
That's like, what was the point? Why did I even leave my house? Why do I even get out of bed this morning?
Nobody knows no one can answer that you could you could learn to build your own clothing out of
scratch
That's a hole. That's a hole over here
That's a whole other fucking can of worms right there and even harder
Even harder
Let me complain I'm gonna complain about something. Uh, yeah, nobody
Nobody wants free money
I haven't I have been preaching I have been preaching the word about free money
for months now
And nobody cares nobody listens
Because I'm offering the car journey. It's it's car. Yeah. I I um
I asked on twitter
The other day it was a bit stew. I felt a bit stupid asking but I couldn't think of a good reason not to ask
So I made a tweet a tweet about like does anyone want since I've been talking about credit cards
Does anyone want to sign up for a good one? I have a bunch of good ones that I recommend
And if you sign up for one with my uh, uh
Six with my referral code, I will get they will give me a bonus
So you the sign-upber will get, you know
Cashback offers and you know the the um, what's the word?
Yeah, the sign-up bonus, you know
For instance like $200 bonus cash when you spend $500 with the card for instance. That's one of the good sign-up bonuses
Uh, so it's good for you and also they'll give me like a hundred bucks if if I sign you up
And so I don't know I would really
I have a I can make I can make up to like $500 if I find five people
Who would sign up for such a thing and I think
That there are probably people who aren't who don't use credit cards who should be using them
I genuinely feel like I would be doing people a service if I got them to sign up for
Many people not everyone most people if I got them one of these cards
And so I don't feel like I'm like trying to scam anyone
I feel like it's a mutually bad, but nobody nobody bit nobody bit
Nobody wants free money
Maybe they assumed that to do it they'd have to start shurning as well
You can just you can just turn one card
Churning is when you get is you get one is you get one card after another after another and you get all the sign-up bonuses
Churning one card is just getting a card
I don't know I feel like I can't be the only one
Who made it into their 30s without ever
reaping the benefits
of uh of of credit
And I feel like there's definitely people who probably should
have it
Uh, but that it's okay. They're shy. It's okay. They're a little gun shy. That's okay. You know what?
You know what listener
The girl listening right now. That's okay. Take take your time. You know come come to me when you're ready
Uh, oh you can you can ease you into it. No no pressure. No pressure
um
I assume it's like american only I couldn't
Uh, I I think so probably I'm gonna say probably
I don't know
Michelle asked me
For a recommendation. I gave I gave her
A link she has not used it yet. Just like I just once again once again
Michelle walks right up to the brink of wisdom
And then just and then spurns it and turns away at the last minute
Just like when I gave her a copy of a conquest of red
Two christmases ago
And she never read it
Spit in my fucking eye. Why don't you?
Uh, and now I give her I give her this referral bonus for the capital one saver one
A beautiful card
She's and she says I'll get around to she asked me
Motherfucker she came to me and asked me for for it
And she didn't even do it
No respect no respect. I tell you
Um, you know of all that I think that PayPal credit has no benefit at all that I was talking about earlier
Yeah, I looked it up and I believe that it does not like
Report to like credit bureaus. I I don't think you can like build a credit history with PayPal credit doesn't seem to be any
Sort of number associated
It's just like if you need to pay for something you don't have all the funds in your account right now
Yeah, you can do it. Yeah. It's okay. Well, whatever
Which is which is like the most the most basic function of a credit card is that it does that
But also credit cards have other benefits aside from that which PayPal does not
Yes, I should get something
I I need to I I was looking at like
like
British
YouTubers, uh with their British, uh, you know credit card information and I'm like, okay, but you're wow
You're so boring and I don't I just want it to be for dummies. Please. I put on I put on um
I put on some like finance credit guy some youtuber the other day
I didn't watch him for a long time
But I watched like one or two of his video and I was a bit disappointed because he didn't really tell me anything that I
Didn't already know so I was like, okay. I think I get the picture
um
But I was curious like if it's like if I
If there is anything else that I could be knowing right now that would be I did learn actually that the
This is not helpful information, but I did learn that there are certain cards that you cannot sign up for that like
If you if you have like a million dollars in in in a bank the bank will contact you and be like
Hey, do you want to sign up for our like super ultra fucking premium?
like
gold star platinum card
And then you say yes, and then it gives you better benefits than any card you can just get as like a normal human rich get richer
I mean, yeah, I mean, yeah, basically
um
We'll give you a free horse every year
The guy the guy said that guy it was oh actually there was an interesting thing. He said he said like
For many cards like for a bunch of the cards that I have like you need a good score
You need a good credit score, but you don't need to have like an amazing credit score
There's no there's no card that like demands that you have like an 850 plus
You know credit score like most cards that are choosy
Like they just want you to be above like
Six something right maybe 700. Yeah, they're not they just they want a pretty good score, but there's none that are like
The really exclusive ones do not exclude based on like do you have perfect credit score?
They exclude based on like how much money do you have like are you rich basically?
I mean the point of a credit
Is in theory like to just make sure that the person
You're buying something from or whatever selling something to you. Um has some understanding that you can
Get the money to them
Yeah
Basically, and if you if you're if you're at all capable then most people will be like, okay, you're a normal person. Yes
Did you see that guy on twitter some fucking nft loser made a whole thread about how like
Job hiring could be done on the blockchain
Yeah, I have no idea what he meant
He just it assumes that like the blockchain would allow people to get hired instantly somehow
It's a it's a half-baked idea. The idea is that like the blockchain is a permanent
record of transactions
therefore your entire like life history and financial history should be recorded on the blockchain therefore like
interviews would be unnecessary and like the
Like the hiring company could just check the blockchain instantly know whether you were hireable or not
And I mean his idea is that it like saves on like time and energy and effort
but like
You know at the at the cost of there being an indelible record of a person's life that may or that you know
May or may not be accurate and can never be changed ever
Yeah, so you know
It's they didn't quite grasp the idea that like
That would be very bad for certain people
Someone was like
You know, you know that meme of like the soy face is like angry at the one thing
But then like make it he's soy soy facing at the other thing. That's the same but slightly different. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I saw that one that was like
Social credit system. Mmm social credit system on the blockchain. Wow
Yeah, literally. Yeah, literally literally
Just put it on the blockchain. I like that's the answer to everything
I like uh social credit because I assume I would be at the top of the food chain in that one. Hmm. Yeah
I said there's no way it could go wrong for me
If we did have a dystopian social credit on the blockchain system
I would simply I would simply have a clean record and and and not have any problems with it
I would simply not uh, I would simply not encounter any difficulties. Yeah
Six society six society
uh
We're talking about fuck. I've completely lost track
Uh, you wanted to complain about not oh, yeah, nobody wants my free money. I'm I'm out here
I'm I'm trying I'm literally peddling free money
Some people probably couldn't take me up on the offer. Some people probably don't have credit scores that are good enough
uh, which is a shame, but uh
If you've got if you you listening if you've got like a decent credit score
And you don't have a credit card, but you've been considering
Getting one and you want my recommendation
And you want to give one of my referral links to try I can I can uh, I can hit me up in the dms
I can I can help us both out
I'm winking I'm winking into the microphone if you can hear that if you can hear my eyelids my eye my eyelash is brushing against the
Against the microphone
um
Buh, I know it's pretty it's pretty gauche. It's pretty gauche
It's pretty gauche to be peddling like credit card referral links on your podcast and on your twitter
But you know what but you know what I just don't care anymore
It's no more it's no more gauche than being at least I'm not an nft bro, right? Sure. I might
That's what I'll do
I'll be like at least I'll be like committing
I'll be like committing committing high treason committing mass murder at least I'm not an nft bro, right?
um
accidentally accidentally like uh
Accidentally like drop my phone in the toilet before I shit and like accidentally upload a video of me
Of my asshole just shitting into the toilet
And I look at my I look at my timeline blowing up as people go lull cringe and I go at least I'm not an nft bro
At least I don't have a lazy line for my pfp
People saying lull cringe to like a scat video accidentally uploaded by ben sing
It goes viral it makes the rounds it ends up
They talk about it on lull cringe. Oh, no, they would just say lull. They feel lull. Great. Can you believe this guy?
What a nerd
That's what that's what I would do and that's what a dork
What a dork, uh, what a look I can you look at let's look at this guy
pause as they consider
The asshole the feces emerging from the asshole
Dang man. I boy would my face be right?
Fucking reaction video circuit
People couldn't yeah keem star keem star comments on on on asshole gait
Like I said, I've been
Think of like the situation that would lead to that like your your live streaming on your phone
And then you say hang on i'm gonna go take a shit
You drop your phone that you know your live streaming you drop your phone in the toilet
And continue to shit anyway forget don't notice that I drop my and just keep shitting onto the the phone camera
Which continues to operate while it's in the toilet bowl underwater
You know it could happen
Oh, yeah, totally. Why not? Why not?
Uh
I
Right I was gonna say sorry
I'm I'm I've lost a little bit of weight in the last couple weeks. I went to the doctor the other day. I had a I had a check up
Uh, uh, they didn't do anything
I thought they were gonna like have to like test my blood or something test my cholesterol now
They didn't do it. They were like now you're not old enough for that. I was like, okay
Uh, uh, they gave me uh
the
Oh, they weighed me right and I have lost I have lost a few pounds in the last couple weeks. I've lost like 10 pounds
Uh, which is pretty good. That's a decent rate. Uh, considering when I started
Uh, uh, working out again and stuff. I was hoping to be down to like 175 by Christmas
I don't know if I'm gonna hit that goal, but uh, I'm I probably won't be too far off
Christmas is the season to be getting fat again
Uh
What happens?
Yeah, but like whatever
at the end of the day
It doesn't matter. It doesn't really matter
Uh
If I if I eat a bunch of Christmas gain a few pounds
Whatever, it'll be it'll be less than I've lost on the way there
It's insulation from the cold
It'll all just it'll all just go to my gains anyway, you know as long as I'm lifting as long as I'm lifting
It doesn't matter that much because even if I overeat one day or another like it just goes to your gains
It just goes to fuel your muscle growth and turn you into a a metabolic furnace
Uh, uh
I've been I've been my deadlift has been skyrocketing but yesterday. I think I hit
I think I've hitting a wall with it. I think I finally
Experienced I like oh this deadlift doesn't feel that good. Oh, my form is not great. Oh, I probably shouldn't have done
That I probably should not have attempted to complete that
Uh, it was 285 285 is the wall
Uh, I will I will maybe have to uh a slow down on it. I've been going up 10 pounds per per like
lift like every time I deadlift, but I've
I have to slow down
I had I was hoping I would hit 300 but I'm not quite there and I'm in my forms my form is breaking down
So I gotta
I gotta cool it. I gotta cool it. Um
Talking about how much I lift is probably about as interesting as talking about what bitcoin is worth right now
Yeah
To react to it like oh cool nice cool nice number, bro
Yeah, um
Newton
Newtons
force
Pound mass times mass times acceleration of gravity
divided by
Something area no
Uh, you just gotta go to jupiter and then lift a small amount and then it'll be a lot easier to gain
Because the gravity that's this DBZ method. Yeah
You gotta go to well you gotta go to the moon and then you can lift six times as much and you go
Oh, I deadlifted I deadlifted 1800 pounds on the moon
Wait, no, it wouldn't be pounds because pounds is a measure of force
Pounds is weight. It's not mass
but so you could say I deadlifted, you know, like
2000 kilograms on the moon and then that's out of the sound that would be accurate and sound like a lot
So uh, but then if you stayed on the moon for too long you've become like
Jelly your your your muscles will get too used to
And lifting yourself, which is which way is less
I bet your bones would become brittler and you'd you'd elongate
I bet did did the astronauts
Did the astronauts do like resistance training?
In space they must right
Uh, I've heard I've heard the space stations. Yeah, they do something to keep them. They must they must do some kind of exercise
To prevent like muscle atrophy from like the low gravity, right? Because I've yeah, I have heard that like
If you're in space your muscles like atrophy because like
You don't use them
So they must do some kind of resistance training. They do like like Naruto fights
with each other
I mean, I mean, yeah
I mean, yeah, but that's that's cardio. That's cardio. It doesn't count
They try to do like the samus morph ball. They're all just nerds up there
They do the samus morph ball
Wait, why why do they do the samus morph ball? Well, it's it's really really stretches your back muscles
I mean, which is uh, actually it's a way to do something. Okay, you know how you know like
You know how when you like spin something
Maybe you spin something that's like long
But then you like contract it and it spins faster. Do you know what i'm talking about?
Uh centrifugal
Something I vaguely understand. Yes, like yeah, it's it's it's concentration of angular momentum. It's like if it's like if you um
Oh, oh like that playground thing the thing on the playground where it's like a wheel
But it's like a flat like wheel on the and there's there's handlebars to hold
And you run around it and you get it spinning and then you jump
On to it and then you move to the middle of it and it moves like much faster
No, it moves much slower in the middle
No, that's not true
If you if you get on it if you get it if you get it spinning while you're standing at the outside of it
And then you move to the middle of it. It'll spin faster
Oh, if you move it'll spin. Yeah
Yeah, if you if you if you if you move if it's spinning and you're standing if you're on it on the outside
And then you move to the middle of it
You'll move it'll spin faster
Yes, because if you're trying if you're trying to grab and walk towards the middle it'll feel
You'll slip off if you don't increase the the strength by which you grip the handlebars because it'll speed up as you're doing that
There's there's also okay
There's the things you can like they're a little thing that sits on the ground
And it's like a little like disc that you sit on and then there's a little like handle of a wheel that you hold
and you twist kind of like the thing at the middle of like the teacups ride at like disney world
and
Do you know this thing?
It's a it's a it's a little thing that you sit on and you hold the handle and you twist it
And the disc that you're sitting on will spin
And and so you're you can make yourself spin while you're on this disc
And you do that with like your hands and your legs out like you spread them out
And then you get yourself spinning and then once you're spinning you pull your arms and your legs in
And then you spin like way faster
Do you ever you don't know what i'm talking about? I I do I understand now
Okay, I have hold on um
Sit is it just called the sit and spin?
Is that what that is? I don't know what it's called. Yes, it's called the sit and spin
uh
The one of uh
The shit and spin
uh one of uh
I guess I might as well post a picture in case
Oh my god, please fucking load. Oh wait. I don't know what this is
It's like a tiny baby toy
There is yes, it is it is a tiny baby toy
Um
Here I'll post a picture in the so if you're if you're you put a baby on that and they spin really fast
Aren't they just gonna be flying off and hit their head? I don't I don't well
No, you put your legs around the like middle thing
So like you're you're like in the middle of it. You're not on the edge of it
You sit on it um and and and I mean a baby wouldn't have the fucking hand-eye coordination to like
Actually make it work
But yeah, you sit on one of these and you spin and then you pull your arms and legs in
And due to conservation of angular momentum, you spin way faster while you're when when they're
contracted in than when they're extended out
Um, why the fuck did I start talking about this? What were we talking about that made me start talk?
Well, we were talking about people in the space station trying to maintain. Oh the morph ball
That's what I'm saying
So if you were in if you were an astronaut and you were in the space and you are floating in a in a you know a room
And you get
By some means by pushing off the walls or whatever you get yourself spinning
Rotating forward extended and then no no no no
Specifically specifically think about this you you you're rotating forward, right?
Like you're going like head going forward
and down
legs going backward and up right and you're and you're fully
And then you and then you yeah you crunch and you curl yourself into a ball, right?
You curl yourself into a morph ball you would suddenly start
You would you would start uh fucking screw attacking
Right, you would because your moment your angular momentum would increase so much
Well, it would stay constant
But your speed would increase to conserve angular momentum, then you would be a little fucking screw attack morph ball
Oh my god, samus is real
It really it really works it really works if you think about it
God I wonder if I wonder now that I'm thinking about it like I
I almost wonder if like they had that in mind when they came up with that idea for like the screw attack
It's like
Yeah, if she put if she pushed off if she gave herself a bit of rotation
And then she curled herself up in a ball her angular momentum would stay constant and she would spin really fast
I I I I wonder I mean
Potentially, I think also it's just the fact that if you're like doing trapeze jump trampoline jumps
Curling up in a ball makes you spin around faster and that's just sort of common knowledge
You see people jumping and spinning like that. I guess it's the same. It's the same principle. Yeah
Yeah
Curious
Fascinating fascinating uh
This is what my this is what my physics degree. Let's me do let's me think about uh,
Samus's screw attack is actually scientifically accurate. And here's my here's my 25 minute long youtube video explaining why
um
That video would probably do pretty well on youtube, right?
Yeah, it'll it'll be like. Oh, wow video game
samus screw attack physics
Hmm
It feels like the sort of subject matter that a game theory would be about like years ago
Yes
Like a classic game theory before they
Were almost entirely about why a scary game has lore that makes sense. I'm on
I'm on the wiki troid. I'm on the the metroid
Uh wiki on the screw attack page and I have control f'd momentum and no results
So apparently no one has ever thought about this before
We're misbusters and we're gonna see if morph ball could really work
Answer yes answer. Yes. It's real answer. Yes
No
No, I'm the first one
I'm the originator. I wonder if hang on morph ball
Uh cosplay has somebody done a morph ball and rolled around
I don't know you find anything
Uh, well, I can see okay. I see people walking around with a morph ball somebody getting into it
But not as a morph ball. I think that maybe they just have a ball with them
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's that's what I'm seeing. Uh, oh, I found uh, I found this this is good
Um posting that right there
That's a winner
This one this one
No, no, no, what what is going on here? What is going on here? Now?
Why would samus be with a morph ball samus should be in the morph ball?
That doesn't make any goddamn sense
Uh, it's it's it's samus's twin sister samus
She took it she took the suit off and hit the like auto morph ball button if you know for for store for easy storage
Yeah, is that is that ball just like placed into the
It's photos if you look in the background. There's an orb like a
Concrete orb in the back. So it's probably just that
That they photoshopped it over
I okay
Yeah, now that you mentioned it. Yeah, it is a bit weird that there's another orb in the scene
I feel like they didn't need to like sample the orb
Okay, right. I think they did it for the shadow on the ground
But but look there's like
There's like some shit in front of the orb though. They would have had to like photo edit the
I don't know. I feel like that's like wait what more and more effort than it's
Well, look the orb in the back. There's like shit on the ground. Yeah, that's because it's really there
It's a concrete orb in space. I'm saying that would make it really needlessly hard to like
Sample that orb. No, they didn't suck a bad orb. There's the orb that the morph ball is
There's just a separate orb
Oh
You're right that has orbs around if some reason
Is this okay? Is this uh, is this baltimore? Is this the baltimore convention center?
Um, you know those trees and that thing in the back. It looks a little it looks a lot like that fountain area
By the fucking brony con. I don't it could be
Is that an ice cold water truck?
Ice cold water that guy didn't have a truck. Uh, not a truck. They're like a little cart
Yeah
No, it's just a
somebody's pushing a pram
That has
cartoons on the side. I don't know what the hell that is like a
uh
Hold on. Hold on. I guess I got to check google maps. I gotta check google maps and see if there are orbs. I've got a geo guess for this
We've got a geo detective find this location
Have you seen any of those videos by that by the straight line mission man?
Oh, you uh, I've heard about them and I think you've talked about them
Yeah, but I haven't really has like pictures from his patreon of people
Uh, who have taken a picture or just sent him a picture of them in a place and he uses like geo guess our knowledge
And google maps to triangulate and like find exactly where they are as a challenge
So like if you take any given picture you could probably do it if you have
Then the the wits to like notice. Ah, this is probably this kind of a country or that kind of a
Something or other
Hey, what was the name of the place that the that the that brony con was at?
It wasn't was it just called the baltimore convention center? I think so
Well, like i'm i'm i'm google mapping baltimore convention center and it doesn't look like it. It doesn't look like the same place
Uh
Was that the gay lord hotel nearby?
Like connected to it was there
well, there was um
Well, there was uh
The the horse there was the horseshoe in right
That was a little not. Yeah, that was somewhere. I don't know where it was in relation to the convention center
Hmm
Well, we we would pass it on the drive
Brony con baltimore
Location this is not interesting. I just i'm just
Ball yeah, the baltimore convention
It doesn't look like
I must be looking at like the wrong side of the building or something because like this doesn't look
Like I remember it maybe i'm thinking of like the harbor area
Maybe i'm thinking of like maybe i'm thinking of like when we're hanging out or like around the port
Ah, whatever
I'm i'm just gonna google brony con. I just i i just want to see
The fucking the fountain area. Okay. Okay. This is the
Oh, this is the area. I'm looking at the this area of the map right here and this is where okay
Yeah, this is where um
I sampled this image
for
the scene
of slime and punishment
Uh in which they activate
The device the the trans dimensional
timeline
Device uh for the for the pseudo finale s revert
This is the this is the the scene that I that I photo bashed into that
That that hole that hole kerfuffle
Uh, I literally just want to find
the fountains
and see
The orbs
I just want to see if there's orbs there. I'm going to scream
I'm going to fucking scream
Because google is just not is just like it's simply not it's simply not
Just just show me the just function just function as intended
I do this all the time and now when I need to do it now when I am trying to do it on it in the timely fashion
It's totally impossible
uh
Okay, whatever I don't care about this. I don't care anymore
Uh, unless you do in which case I also I'm I'm still looking wait, so the
I'm at the bolt more conventions center
On google maps
I see you remember you remember the fountain area the found the fountain area
I don't really remember the fountain area. Is it was it near the front?
Or was it just yeah, we hung out. Yeah
It was like it was out front and to the right of the
Of the of the main convention area. There was the like funny little like
There was the funny little like cave tunnel you could sort of walk under that had like little waterfalls inside
Oh the cave tunnel I do remember that
What was that? That was like sort of down the road a bit
A little bit
I don't know which direction this would be in
Hilton. Oh, yeah, there's the hilton that it was connected to
With the walkway
Sheraton inner harbor
You okay, you couldn't you couldn't see the harbor
And there's the harbor. Yes
Well, yeah, I mean it was it was near the harbor. It wasn't it wasn't on the harbor. Um
I'm trying to remember I'm remembering like the time when it was like dark after the convention
Okay, I'm switching rck people sitting on the the harbor
I'm switching to photo. I'm switching to photo view instead of map view. All right. I'm looking around
The the convention center
And I
Okay, there's a
I guess there's a baseball dime and like right near it. I don't even remember that
Okay, I remember the bubblegum shrimp company. We would walk by that all the time
Oh, and uh, and then
Oh, oh the kona grill
Okay, we would walk past the kona grill
So it must have been down in the easterly direction. Oh, there it is. Uh, yes
yes
It's a mckelden square and mckelden plaza
I believe this is the the
Region I'm looking for
Okay, now we got it now we got to find these orbs
Hmm
On my back
Yeah, did you leave I disconnected uh for a second
Okay, what am I looking at
This is
All right
Yeah, there's the pnc bank. Yeah, this is familiar. I remember this street
but then
Like there's supposed to be
I feel like I'm looking at
The exact place
But there's no fountain
How old is this uh, uh, mckechted november 2020 so yeah, it's not
Probably not yeah, I can't be that old
Well like hold on like
I'm gonna show you this this street view
And tell me I mean tell me if you're having the same sensation as me
I feel like this is the corner
where it was
And and and there was a fountain
Like maybe that like concrete thing over on the left
Was part of it. Was it like in from the from the
Wait a minute
I remember you it was like there was a wall of water and you went down steps to see it
Maybe it's hiding. Yeah
I'm losing my fucking mind
I'm losing my fucking mind over here
Uh
Was it past like we got to go back to brony con to find out looks like we got to go back one here we go again
The real last brony con this time. Um, all right, I'm going insane
I feel like I found it and it wasn't there. This is like some this is like some mandala effect
I swear there was like a cave and a waterfall
And like a a magical fairy gave me a magic sword while I was down there. It wasn't just a dream mom
Um, okay. Well, that was stupid
Um, if you could find it
Give us a yeah, like give us a comment about that comment in the description saying like
Where is this fucking fountain? Where is this looking in the wrong direction? Where are these fucking orbs?
Where are the orbs? Where are they find the orbs?
Find the we're on orb hunt
We're on this is this is an orb hunt if you can find the orb
Send us a voicemail and uh, we will voice grail you telling us you didn't don't tell us unless
Unless multiple people do it and then we won't voicemail voice grail you all that would be stupid. Um
Okay
Okay, I found
I just found something there is some okay. There is something in mckelden square
That is called mckelden fountain
uh, but it's like
Street view is like, you know, it's like too far out
From the the square that like it's hard for me to actually see it from the street
So like that's gotta be it. That's gotta be the thing we're thinking of
It's just you just can't see it with street view because like they didn't take pictures inside of the square
Or wait, no did they?
There are some
It like
It looks like there are spots it seems to suggest to me that there are spots inside of the square
that you can
That you can drop your little man your little street view man into
Oh, wow, they took like a drone shot
What the fuck
Wow, I wish uh, I wish I had had this drone shot
For slime and punishment this look look at this
This looks great
I would have used the shit out of this
It's surely it's surely the thing we're talking about. You just can't see it at all in this fucking uh
In this app, but oh, oh well, I mean I feel like mystery sol
No orbs though
The question of the the question of the orbs remains unanswered
um, okay, so um
What else what else what else?
Uh, well, I've been working on oh, yeah go on
Yeah, I mean, I haven't really got much to talk about
because this past week I have
Oh, excuse me
I have been working
uh tirelessly
and I say I but like I
There's a secret project that I talked about
A while ago, and I've been working on it
And it is going well and if you want to know I know what it is
Ben knows what it is if you want to know more about it
I do reveal what I what I'm talking about in my latest money spenders podcast
Over on give and take a patreon.com slash give and take well now. I don't feel special for knowing anymore
No, that's okay because I am a money spenders
You are a money spender. Yeah, I am a money spender
Um, I haven't listened in a couple in a while. I should go catch up
Yeah, they're all the secrets. So all the things I I want this one. I will this one. I definitely want to listen to
uh, so yes
It's it's unfortunate for pcp because I don't have anything to talk about yet because I want to keep a little under wraps
Until I'm ready to be like hey everybody. This is what I've been doing this whole time
I was uh
My project is not a secret. It's uh phantom's revenge
But I was I was working on it yesterday and I was posting in my
In my patron discord server my server is public
But my my patron channel is private for patrons only and I share
updates on on what I'm working on for the game in that channel
and I was
posting some uh this week. I've been working on uh
Room like background art like like the final the final version of like every room in the game because you go through a series of rooms and like
They're each different. Um
And I've been making the background art and I took a break from that to draw some
character portraits for like the talk sprites that I'm going to need for the final
cutscene
and I
drew them
And they were so good. I loved them so much that I had to I went and I posted in the patron secret project discord
I said hey guys
I want you all to know that I drew some portraits today, but I can't show you because they're too good
And uh, I have to I have to save them
I don't want to rob you of the experience of seeing them in their in their correct
Context for the first time. So I won't be showing you get fucked. Uh, you're welcome
Uh, that was just yesterday. Uh, it was very exciting
Yeah, I'll have to go check out that uh, I mean, I already know what the project is
But I do want to hear you talk more about it
In the in the money spenders, uh, so
I could listen to that
Because I know I don't I don't know that much about it. You've shown me a little bit of it
Yeah, I I don't know if I go into like a lot of depth
With regards to the process or what I'm currently like exactly working on
It's more of like an announcement and like a
vague plan of action for that release
Okay
Okay, I should go into it. I mean I do want to know another at some at some point I do
Yeah
Yeah, I kind of want to know. Yeah, like what I want to know about like
The the the the without without revealing anything. I say, yeah, the the details the nitty gritty of it
Because I don't understand
I mean I kind of do but I I don't
I don't know. I don't know. I'm curious
Um
Yeah, pretty good pretty cool. Um
Does that like
Didn't you say that it's getting kind of close to being done?
Yes, I started it this year
And I wanted it to be over finished by the end of the year
So I'm really you know working hard to make it a reality
Then I will announce it and it'll be it'll be uh
Good, I don't know how to to like not spoil
Yeah, yeah, but also mention things about it in a vague fashion that would make people interested to go to money
To patreon.com slash give and take
To find out
That is the goal. That is the goal
Speaking of
Patreon I want to I want to our our our patreon the pc patreon has continued to increase
Uh since the uh since the uh the the the latest drama bomb
Uh that was uh
It what do you mean you guess
Well, it's like drama bucks
Are they really gonna stay for really anytime at all? I don't know
But can I actually oh but oh drama bucks
Can I actually pay for things with them though?
Like won't they turn me away at the store and say no you can't pay for no
Oh this is drama money. Oh, it doesn't matter. Ew. I mean I mean like the staying power of it
It's probably not very it's probably gonna dip back down unless there's more drama
But I don't I don't want to do more drama if I can
Well, it might it might a bit it might a bit. I don't mean we'll see. Um, it's nice to see you go up. That's for sure
Um
You know there was actually a bit this isn't like full-on drama
But there was people people were telling me after um the last one that in the the follow-up episode of um
Who are these podcasts? There were there were
You know they they read out a bunch of like comments from the subreddit all of many of which were very like
Trixie sucks don't have her back on
And they got one voicemail
About it and I thought that maybe I could play
There that voicemail that they received
Just in its entirety. What do you what do you think? Do you want to hear it?
I have heard it, but yeah, oh you listen to it
I think it was something like
The one I think you're talking about is the guy who says
If you have Trixie back on the the who are these podcasts
um
Then I'll un
Patron who are these podcasts and patron the guys she hated. She's making fun of us. Yes
He does say that here. I'll I'm just I'm just gonna post it. It's only like a minute long
I'm doing it. Uh
Here we go
Is it a minute? It might be like a minute and a half
It is yeah, it's a minute and a half. Okay. Here we go three two one go
Uh, all right last uh voicemail
When my former co-host didn't need to retweet me tweets from me
When these same people that unpaid me are
Okay, sorry, that that is true, but did you let that's the funniest part?
Which is that those people just one guy that was giving him one dollar a month and he was gonna unplug anyway
So he took his former co-host co-host Ben St. up in his office
So Ben paid him two dollars to unplug one dollar a month on patreon
Like if you're that if you're gonna like screw out that hard or one dollar a month
if
Make these make something give people something that they'll want to pay one dollar a month for like I I
I pledged five five a month to
Patreon because most episodes are great if the ladies from the vanished or a southern john or some someone who just
Wanted to give me six dollars to stop giving carl five good bucks a month. I say no because
You've given me something worthwhile. I'd rather give them six to five bucks for what I get and then then get six bucks and stop
Handing to all right. I think we get the point. Yeah
Took a while to get there, but very good point
When trixie brought that up they were gonna pay people who are subscribed to their show to unsubscribes like people won't do that
They enjoy subscribing to that right they enjoy the content
I'll give you 20 bucks to stop getting net flex like well. No, I'm in the middle of squid games. So what are you talking about?
Yeah, I'm enjoying. Okay. That was different from the one I had heard. That's pretty oh
Oh, okay. I weird. I thought it was the same one, but I guess there was another one that uh
That I that I missed uh, this is the one the the the
There's not there's nothing. I don't know. There's there's something that particularly rankles me. There's a certain
There's a certain kind
Of of a of a of gig head or trixie defender or just or just loser in general on the internet who will
Who will get really offended?
get really offended
About the uh, the like pay pay someone to un
Unpledged thing like it's like it's crossing some kind of boundary
Like it's like it's like oh you can say what you want, but you can never you should never affect
Someone's money in any way if you should never like do anything that affects
A person like materially
That's like too fucking far and it's uh, it's very cringe. It's very stupid
You'd have to be a complete moron to think that like it's it's it's like it's like oh if if someone
If someone is getting money
They always deserve it, right? They they they they they they must they must deserve it
No matter what and if you and if you say hey this person doesn't deserve
Literal literal it's literally the same it's literally the same as if like a guy is like running a scam
The guy is just is just scamming people and you go hey
don't
Support don't pay this guy this guy is a scammer and someone goes um you can't that's his income
That's his livelihood. You can't how could you how could you do that to him?
Because it's literally the same because Trixie like promises a product
She promises that the the patreon that she runs supports her anime content. It doesn't it all goes to weed
She spends it all on weed. She doesn't need the patreon income
Anyway, because she just like lives for free in in her well now in her in her boyfriend's house
But whatever she's just a moochie. She doesn't need the money for anything
The money just goes to weed which makes her content even worse actually just makes her worse at what she's supposed to be doing
So there's literally no reason to support her and I have ever and I would never ever feel bad
Uh for this uh, even if it worked even if my my scheme to pay people to unpatron worked
Uh, which it didn't you know, it was one dollar
But even if it worked I would do it and I wouldn't feel bad if I could drop $1,000 right now
Just to make her patreon go to zero
I would do it just out of spite and I would feel good about it
I would think it was the morally right thing to do and I would be correct in that
uh
Yeah, it's because like
In in the hypothetically if people are willing to not pledge to Trixie anymore. It's because
They understand that it's because they don't value because they don't value the thing that they're supposedly pledging for enough
It's not like you're paying them
And that's somehow coercing them to do something. They didn't know how to do anyway. Like there's it's the free market
It's the free fucking market, baby libertarian for life
Uh, yeah
Yeah, it's cry. It's it's crybaby bullshit. It's crybaby bullshit to cry about it and say like, oh, you're not that's too far
It's you're not allowed to do it. I think it's even crybaby or bullshit to say it about someone else
Yeah, I think people are just scared of you ben. You're just too dangerous. You're too powerful
In their eyes, I am too there was that one moron on twitter the other day
that one moron on twitter was like
Yeah, they were they were like um
They were like it makes me scared. It makes me scared that ben's allowed to do this
Good
Good, it's like, yeah, it was what this is cancel culture ben. You're canceling someone. What if what if someone wants to cancel me?
It's like, well
Then you'll be fucking kid then the market will cancel you. I'm sorry. This is the
The invisible the invisible hand will will smite you
um
I am the invisible hand of the free market
and um
um
Uh, wait that guy that guy said something else that guy said um, oh really funny that guy said like
It he made a bunch of like reply tweets me and one of them he was like
I just don't think ben is actually doing this out of like genuine concern for tricksy. I think ben's doing this just out of spite
No fucking shit my dude. No way. You are you are you are you are you serious?
Are you really what would the difference be?
And then final note about that guy because I really fucking hate that guy that guy's a huge loser. Um, uh, uh
The final thing that guy finally was like
Was like block the guy finally he made one final tweet was like well, I'm gonna okay ben
Well, guess what? I'm gonna go patron tricksy now just to spite you block and then he blocked me
Uh, and then I checked a little later to see if tricksy's patreon had gone up by one person
Uh, it didn't the guy's a fucking liar. I hope you're listening right now. You fucking loser
Eat shit. What a fucking bitch. What a pussy do it pussy
He won't
I'm really mad about that guy. Can you tell yes?
That guy ruined my fucking day. He was I saw him and he was
It was very much like
I don't know
I I thought it was like status quo like there's a status quo in the tricksy is getting mad. You're trying to change that
Yeah, true
You're trying to change the status quo dude. You're trying to affect something in the real world and that's frankly that offends me
um
Wait, I was gonna say something um
Oh, yeah, I thought I thought I had burned away like every person who might still be following me who might like
Get offended on tricksy's behalf. I thought they were all gone
But this guy had somehow managed to escape the purge
And survived this long uh good good riddance I say
um
Anyway, I thought that was funny and infuriating
What else what else?
The the the the portraits
The port i'll say i'll say this the portraits that I was drawing for phantom's revenge that I was so happy with that I wouldn't show anyone
where um
I won't say exactly what they were of
but they were of someone uh uh screaming
and I
I realized as I was drawing this I was like
I'm I'm drawing this character
screaming
And I'm like making the face myself like I'm
I'm like grimacing and like and I'm going like
I'm like
Do you do that? I think a lot of people do
I I I I I don't know. It felt great. I loved I loved it. I loved it so much. It had such a good time just
Like I was like not screaming, but you know grunting like you're making rage sounds. Yeah, it's like um
Even when I'm like writing dialogue or something
Or I'm thinking about how they would say it or what their expression would be
I I realized that I'm doing the expression in my head. I'm like, yeah, yeah, yeah
Like a flower head says this and he's got like, you know, I'm like, oh wait, I'm doing it. I'm doing the flower head face
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, but it felt great. It was a it was exhilarating
I was just like what is like the angriest that I could possibly be well
Let me just try and conjure that
In my soul right now and then translate it
Into um into onto the the the the digital page and that's what I did and it was uh it was beautiful
um
Can't wait for fucking finish the game. I think
I'm really crank. I'm really cranking it out. I feel
I I rue every minute
every minute that I spent on like
Funny little graphical flourishes
I don't know. It's hard. You're some of them. I really like I sort of regret them. I feel like
Honestly
The reflections in the floor are nice and all
I don't feel like it was worth the time that I spent making the floor reflective. It was
A big the the blood effects the blood effects are good
The blood effects look good and I think they were a worthwhile inclusion and I spent a few days on them
But like I think they were worth it. The reflection in the floor
Was harder and it continues to it continues to be a thing that eats up development time
It continues to be something that like I
Keep finding new like ways in which it fucks up and having to fix it and it continues to be a drain on me and I
Find myself being like I wish I had just not
Added this feature. It's it's nice and all but it's really not the game would have been fine without it
It doesn't add enough to justify
All via the work that I put into it
Oh, oh well
You know, I really should have focused on just delivering
The minimum viable product just making the good the game
Just as good as it needs to be to be the complete product as envisioned. It didn't need floor reflections to be that it was
But it's got them
I mean, they look pretty slick
They look pretty slick. I don't really care about the game looking slick. Well, I mean, I sort of do a little bit
Yeah, I'm too I guess
I
Just wish it was I just wanted to be done
I feel I feel like getting it done should have been should be the priority
and I feel like
adding something like that is counter to the
The real goal, which is just yeah, you gotta be careful about finished. Yeah feature creep. Yeah
That was a do you have like a list of like things that need to functionally work?
For it to be considered playable
Do I have that?
Yeah, because like if you have a list of things and you if you notice
You're like, oh, I could add this then you add it to the list and if the list is growing then you realize
You're never gonna get it done if it just keeps growing. You've got to strike things off the list
Yeah, I
Yeah, I do have a list
Sometimes I will sometimes I will just think of something and be like, hmm
What if I did that and then I will
Kind of you know, if it's an interesting idea and I think yeah, floor reflections was one of these things
I will fuck around with it a little bit
And then if I like the results I'm getting from the fucking around I'll be like, okay
Sure, I'll go with it and floor reflections was like I added a simple version of it initially and I thought yeah, that's good
And then I and then I kept working on other stuff and then I was like
Hmm
I think I could make the floor reflections look a little bit slicker and then I got a bit
I fell a bit down a rabbit hole of like making trying to make them look as slick as possible
and
I I eventually did figure out like a hey, that's pretty good. Hey, I'm pretty happy with that
Uh
And it so I did I did it in pieces. I didn't do the whole thing at once. I first I added the
simple version
Then I like went back and refined it more and then I went back and refined it more and um
Yeah
it's it's just something that like
I have a list
But if I think of something that is interesting
I'll divert I'll divert from the list and fuck around with something else and then if it turns out that I like it I will
It gets de facto added
To the list. I don't really I don't
I had a big list of things. It's like I got to add this. I got to add this
I don't really have any like features that I need to add anymore. I do have a
A spreadsheet not a spreadsheet. I have a text file that just lists like bugs that I have found
And like things that I need to make like I need a couple more sprites for this or that
I need um and then lists of like
You know if I do this the game crashes like if I do this like the sprite disappears
Like if I do this the the character the the sprite draws in the wrong place or something
And I I'll have to go down through that list at the end and be like make sure that like, okay. This is fixed. This is fixed
This is fixed. Um
Uh
Do I I have I have it open right now
um
Yeah, but all the features are in all like the all like the things the game the features the game needs are in
It's just the content that needs specifically the the enemies all work
I think all the main enemies function as intended
I have one or two that I want to make a few small tweaks to change their sprites around a little bit
Uh, and then the lat and then I have the the the the the the boss basically is like the thing
That right the thing I was drawing the the the portraits for uh, the that's not really like adding features
That's just like I sort of have to build a I have to build a scene in the game
You know a cut scene basically that is like has dialogue and it has sprites moving around and it has uh some
Custom responses for certain commands that only happen in that in that particular
scenario
Uh, there's a lot to do there's a lot to do and I wish
I think if I could go back I would trade in the time that I spent on something like floor reflections just to
Have have more done of like the essential things that the game needs to have to be done because like like
Like I started mine at the end of last year
And I really would like to have it done by the end of this year to say like yeah, I worked on it for a year
I don't want it to go on more than that
I didn't want it to go on for a year in the first place, but it did
um
Yeah
I think it was december 19th that I started working on it last year
I think that was the game
How much of what you've done has been like you learning how to use the program?
and then doing um
Not
Not really learning how to use the program
The program is easy. Well, I mean like and I understood techniques and like yeah, how do I make floor reflections?
How do I make blood splatters like you didn't know what to do?
Initially, you just have an idea, right?
Yeah, I mean I
I didn't like I mean I I would
The the only thing that I like looked up how to do
Was building a like menu
Combat system. I looked I did look I looked up a tutorial that somebody made about how to create like an rpg
battle menu system and I implemented
I basically copied theirs
And then after that
I would look up like certain
Commands like, you know, you code it in this uh, uh gml language
And I would have to look up like what certain commands do in gml
But I didn't like look up guides or like research anything. I just kind of just made it up
As I went along
Yeah, what I mean is um
The the skill you have as a game developer
Is something you were working on as you were building the game
So like in the future if you were to make another game like this, you'd be able to make it a lot quicker, right?
Uh, I would say
Yeah, probably. Yeah, probably a lot of what I have been doing is transferable. I I think that
I think that if I were to do something like this again
I would have a better idea of like what not
to
Bother with
Yeah, I think it okay. I have learned
It has it has taught me the value of like
scripting by which what I mean is like
A lot of the like old code in the game is like
It's similar code on similar objects that do similar things and I think next time if I if I did another project like this
I would really want to emphasize in my mind like ben make sure
You use external scripts that like do certain functions
And do certain things like I did I did this for the floor reflections like I did eventually build like a
A a repeatable script that I could apply to different in-game objects that would give them the same
you know floor reflection
effect I so I didn't have to like
Custom code the like the floor reflection for each individual
object
Certain objects I do because they move in a certain way that the the regular the script can't handle
But like stationary objects can all all refer to the same like
A floor reflection
Algorithm
So I would make more use of that
Kind of thing and and try to consolidate things so I can just get away with making something
Once and then reusing it and reusing it as much as possible
Uh the original menu the the tutorial that I followed it had it included a bunch of like other
Shit that I didn't need like
My game does not have like it has items, but it doesn't have like magic. It doesn't have like like spells
So his whole his menu included like a spell system
So my code had my menu system. It has like a spell system in it
It's just like that option is just disabled and skips over and there's just a bunch of like ghost code in there
That doesn't do anything that it like would support a spell menu if I wanted to add one, but I don't
um
So I mean I just I wouldn't
I would exclude
Things like that. Uh, yeah, I think I just have a I have I have built up a sense of like
how to look at
code and know what it does and mostly what that does for me now is I look at my
I look at my code and I think
Like wow, this is a fucking mess like wow
This is like this is like this thing is like under so many like if then statements
This is under so many like conditional modifiers
It didn't need to be buried this deep
It could have there could have been so many fewer like branches to this like logic that I created here
I'm not going to go back and fix it because it works
But I could have made it a lot simpler if I had just had a
Clear idea of what it should look like when I had started
out
Uh
Oops
Oops, so it's so answer your question. Yes
Yeah, so to answer your question. Yes, I do think probably like if my the things I have learned
Would be transferable to another project on this one. So that's pretty cool
Yeah, although I mean there's plenty that I don't know like, you know the the the guy who made the original menu system
He used a lot of um
Like arrays
And I just don't
I like don't use arrays. I feel like probably I could
And it would make things certain things easier. I just like don't I find them awkward to think about
Uh, and I just haven't like like lists and arrays and stuff are things that you can just make in and I kind of just don't use them
Maybe I don't really need that many of them in what way lists like in the in the way that like
In the way that like um
I don't know what I what I will do
With a thing if I want like an object to perform an action is I will basically just make like a new
variable that exists in
The object
And I and it will be toggleable true false
And if I wanted to do the thing I will just be like, okay set this to true
And then he will you know, he will do that thing
You know and then
So I end up with it has all these different like true false true false true false
Probably maybe I could have used something like an array to like, okay
There is an array of possible states that he is in
And we can switch from one to another
Instead of having like, okay set this one to from true to false and set simultaneously set this one from false to true
in you know like
Just that's just one example at the top of my head of something that like
probably I could have made that
Probably could have made that simpler probably could have I could have like uh future proofed that sort of thing
Yeah, and what I from what I see
a lot of coding is
Like you can do a lot
Uh at a very low skill level, but that's me
The the real like the the the progression of skill is not so much being able to do more complicated things
It's being able to like do simpler things a lot simpler like with a lot with less lines of code with less like
spaghetti everywhere
Yeah, I think so I think so my code my shit is not clean my shit is not clean and it's a mess and it it
Oh man, there was um
Again, this was the thing it was another problem I had this week with um with reflections there was a
Uh, what was it? What was it?
Uh
Shit there was something with a character object in the game that was
What was it doing?
What was it doing it was doing something? Oh, I remember it was like it was um
When the when the turn ended he would not
It would not
Increment a certain variable a certain a certain counter was supposed to count at the end of each turn
So such that at a certain effect would last a certain number of turns and after all the enemies were defeated
You're supposed to be able to continue to take turns like in preparation for the next
room and so but the way that I had it
um
I had written a script that would if there were no enemies
It would simply repeat the turn
But it didn't consider the turn to have ended and a new turn to have begun thus iterating the counter
It would simply like revert back to the beginning of the turn without actually ending it so the timer didn't increment
so I had to
So I knew that this was the problem
and I knew
How to fix it and it was simply a matter I just had to comb through all the code to find like where did I put that
Instruction to repeat the turn. I just need to find it and delete it and I just
Couldn't find it. It took me like an entire day or like a day and a half actually to find this
I knew exactly what it was
It was a one it was a one-line solution and I just couldn't find where to put it and in the end
The reason why I couldn't this is a bit stupid the reason why I couldn't find it was because I had put it in a script
It was in a separate script
That was handling that instruction. So I eventually when I thought maybe it's in a script
I look through my scripts and then I found ah, there it is
There's the like turn repeat script that I just have to go in and I have to take out that
I was I was looking for the instruction itself itself when I should have been looking for the instruction to
uh, you know, um
You know refer to this that script
So I eventually found it and then it was easy to fix
But this is you know, messy. This is this is the kind of thing that happens when your shit is messy sloppy
Uh, but that's me I guess
Code talk
coding
Time to be coming on the pcp to talk about his coding
Tom I'm calling out tom. I'm calling out tom. I'm doing it
I saw people in my discord were asking like, where is tom? Why isn't tom on the pcp?
What why did you change the the pcp recording time to 10 a.m?
Now tom's never on the podcast and I said no
tom was first of all tom was hardly ever on the podcast before
And second of all, I specifically asked tom. Hey tom, do you mind if we change the pcp recording time to 10 a.m?
Would that be a problem for you and he said no, it's fine
And then tom, I got you tom. I fucking got you and then someone in my discord was like
I'm just I'm just saying what he said and I think he posted a screenshot. I think it was from like the im games
Discord server or something where they asked and like hey tom, how come you're never on the podcast anymore and tom said
Uh, well, they changed it to 10 a.m in the morning and that's too early for me. So I don't do so
That's why it's because ben changed it on me
And like no, I fucking asked you
I fucking asked you and you said it was okay
This is excuses excuses excuses
Just say you don't want to be on
What the fuck this made me mad. It's actually made me a little bit mad
It's talking about two sides of your mouth talking on two sides of the mouth. It's weaseling
It's weasel words what it is
Got them caught you
owned
I'm diligent, you know, I I I
I uh, I check I I take care. I take care
Not to fuck people over. I really do
Uh
A little a little credit a little credit would be nice. Um, but it's fine. It doesn't matter
um
Duh
All right
That's probably enough code talk. That's probably enough code talk for now. Um
What's up? What's what what do you think? What's on tell tell me?
I don't know. It's really just the secret project is like full-time job hours working on it and then I've been
stupidly
Fetching out
Doing like idle games and listening to red letter media like usual like normal. It's not good
I was a brief stint where I was like, oh, I'm gonna like watch some actual media. I'm gonna see some anime that I haven't seen
I watched a few but then as soon as I started getting to like
I was watched a few movies
But as soon as I started to get to like the tv shows the anime shows
20 episodes of something I'm like
Uh, you know what? I'll get around to it. It's just that there's too much of a time investment even though individually
The episodes are shorter
I don't want to watch a show
I could be doing I was I could be doing better things
I was starting to watch uh kino's journey, which was sort of interesting
It's about I've seen a bit of that
Get on a motorbike and the motorbike can speak to him
He's like wait is kino a boy
I think so
Oh, he doesn't have a he doesn't have a feminine voice. He looks he's got that 2000s anime like androgynous face
I'm like 90% sure kino's a girl. Well, I don't know maybe I I only watched one or two episodes
Wait now I'm curious uh
Oh wait. No, I noticed they they didn't have like any
Oh, kino's kino's area. Okay kino's
sex is ambiguous in the beginning
She okay. She is a girl
Okay, well, what do they don't they it's like deliberately ambiguous. Okay, whatever. So yeah, all right
I've seen a a bit of it
It used to be on anime network
On demand. I watched a few episodes of it
I think it could be more interesting
It's just sort of quite slow and
melancholic
Yeah, and like uh
Talking about like exist existential stuff and I'm like this feels teenagery. I'm not really interested yet
Like like big brain like what if the universe is like
Stupid what if what if what if life doesn't mean anything? Huh?
Yeah, a little bit of that, but it's not like a stupid version of that. It's it's like it's earnest
So maybe it'll be like cool
I just I wanted to finish it before moving on to some other anime that I have on my list of things to watch
But finishing a show is too hard
Because you have to watch it
And there's a lot of that's true
That's true
So I don't know what to do. Should I continue to watch kino's journey?
Tell me in the comments of what you thought of this anime
You just gotta you just gotta follow your heart
You just gotta let your heart might know my heart is stupid because it leads me to play idle games and look at numbers go up
Damn that is stupid your heart sucks. My heart is like like
I just need to rip it out of me
My heart doesn't like art
I'm ripping out another seltzer
I'm ripping out another sparkling water with a twist of triple berry
What flavor berry refreshing
Huh, what flavor berry?
um
Well from the packaging it seems to be blueberry strawberry blackberry
uh
Yeah, so there you go. That's the answer triple berry
All right, uh, I had one last thing to mention on my weak notes. So I was listening to
I was listening to the uh
Anamorphon time I was catching up on anamorphon time
I was a few episodes behind
and
They they started doing a voicemail segment. I think I might have talked about this tyler from
Anamorphon them asked me how we do our voicemails and I told him about speak pipe
and um
They started doing voicemails
And I am pretty sure that one of our
shit poster
voicemailers
Shitpost voicemail them as well
I should have shut up. I don't remember exactly what his question was
But there was one guy who voicemailed them and he had what I think
Was like a some kind of hispanic accent
but he talked in like a very
Very drawing kind of low voice and kind of slur his words a lot
And I don't remember exactly what he was asking, but he just he's I think he's just asking like
He goes on this like long like tedious
Like uh
Like tell me about life like I don't know what to do about my life. Give me advice about relationships
Uh never had sex and that's the end of the voicemail
And like there it's the episode where they have um
They have chris grine, which is a like the graphic novelist who is drawing the official like animorphs
Like graphic novels
And like need to listen to that
Yes, and he has and I'm and I'm pretty sure that guy has called into the pcp before so
Fuck you guy
Uh
Yeah, I don't know
I think I think it might be my fault because I um
Tyler was asking on twitter like people to leave voicemails for the show and I like retweeted that so
Um, it's probably my doing
Yeah, oops
insanely toxic pcp audience
Exactly exactly
Uh, I thought I'm I'm like I'm I'm like 99 percent sure that same guy has called his voicemail thus before
Hmm
Um, yeah, that's all I got for this week on my list of shit to say
I know the list
I usually I write stupid
I write like a little note or two throughout if something interesting happens like oh, I'll put that on my little text
No, let me bring it up on the show
um
Oh, you want to go to voicemails? Yeah, let's go to voicemails. I didn't really okay. Okay. Um, sure. Well, let me let me pull them up here
Uh, okay, the first one is called
Uh, it's shit. Shit. It's called um
I love you gib or il y gib
Oh, wow
Wow
Three three two one go
Ben Ben Ben. Yeah, can I get uh, uh, happy birthday?
Uh, happy birthday
Happy birthday. Whose birthday is it?
This guy's I guess
Happy birthday
Uh
I hope your birthday is
sexy
God
Next one is called fancy for the love of god
Please for the love of god three two one go
Go back to uploading the pcp mp3s
I need them to listen to the fucking show and they're not on any of the new episodes and fucking all the youtube mp3
Websites aren't working anymore. God listen to the podcast
Um, what did we do about that? I thought we um, we stopped doing that because they're on itunes or something
Or I don't I don't know. I don't I don't remember. Um
Yeah, they're on like itunes and are they on spotify?
There's just there's just itunes
Apple podcasts, maybe the wait they're on the
Okay, you can download the mp3 from a website, right?
Of the procrastinators.com has all the episodes and I believe you can download them as mp3s from the website
Let me check that
The procrastinatorspodcast.com
Um
Yeah
Yeah, you fucking nerd you can literally download them from the website. That's where you go
There's no google doc. There's no google folder anymore. Just go to the website. Oh, yeah problem
Problem solve problem solve. Maybe you didn't know that now, you know, I mean most probably don't know that there's a website for that
but yes
Check that there is a website
by the way, um
Oh
So I wanted some point to release the um the pdf version of road to radcon
I guess I should put that on the website. That seems like the appropriate place to put that
I don't actually I don't actually know how to edit the website though. I don't know how to make a post there
I've never done it
um
Still got the like default like plant at the top
uh
Yeah, I mean Tom uploads uploads the things you know what?
I yeah, I guess I could just ask tom to post the pdf
Uh, yeah, I think I'll do that. I'll I'll ask tom about it. Um
Okay, the next one is called
Uh, shit. Where did I lost it? The next one is called. Uh, it's janez
Here we go
three two one go
What do you think someone should do if they want to improve their commenting skill? Uh, let's play or stream
They're commenting skill
Hmm
Uh, I think a lot of it
Yeah, do do a lot of it
Do a lot of it
I I would say aside from that
It might be a there might be a mindset thing
Try and maintain the mindset
Of that there are no
There there are no, uh, uh
Trying to be the mindset of not caring too much
Uh, be like be like, uh, what if I say something stupid?
I think some people
Are like shy. I think some people maybe
Would be shy in that situation and would hold back. Sure
You should you should not hold back. You should say even if something's stupid
You should be of the mind so that if you say something stupid, that's okay
Because you can just you can just make a joke out of it and laugh at yourself
And uh, and I don't know learn learn not to this learn not to give a fuck about looking stupid
Which is is good advice, uh in general for life
True that in practice are probably too. I'm trying to think because like in in a let's play
I mean, nobody really does let's plays but if you're doing like live streams
um
It depends on why people are watching or what you're trying to do if you're trying to just be a gamer
You don't really need to commentate that much as long as the gameplay is interesting or like high level stuff
I mean if you just haven't fun saying something
You don't well, I mean you do in some certain stances, but like speedrunners don't need to not that you know
It's it's it's nicer if you can
Commentate while you're playing but like if you have okay, well that if the trouble is like
With trying to play a game and speak at the same time
I yeah
Just try to do it and then you'll get the hang of of doing that
But like I don't know if there's like a specific way to get good at it other than that
I don't think I don't really think so and I guess if if if you've got like a
A friend who could be in a call
They could like ask you questions to force your hand for your react
Yeah, I think doing it with another person is a lot easier than doing it by yourself
um, if you're doing it by yourself, yeah, you might
You might just run out of things to say you don't have anyone to bounce off of you have to keep coming up with shit on your own
Um
Yeah, the only thing with oh, yeah, that's that's a good
Yeah, that's a good fallback if you if you are having trouble doing it on your own doing it with someone would be a good uh
Yeah fallback
Next one next voicemail is an image or an imager album
Riley the type of geezer to go down on a chick and be the first one to come
Oh
That's funny
Uh, is it true?
Uh, well, I mean the meme says the meme says it's true. So I have I have to believe it
I have to take it at face value. Well, it's it's not really saying it's true
But he's saying he's the type of geezer where that would happen. Oh
Oh, well, that's
Well, that's true. Obviously
He seems he seems the type
Next one is uh
Is this an image it's a paste ben wait, why is this a paste been?
What the fuck okay, whatever. It's a text file for summary. Why would you
Okay, ben you should make a pcp lecture on the rise and fall of digi, bro
I bet a lot of people would be interested to know what happened to that anime youtuber from 2016
You know, you're not you're not the first person to suggest this
um
Yeah
I mean, I would
Yeah, yeah, I mean, that's not a time I'd consider it. I'd consider it. Maybe it's it's doable. I mean, there's plenty of interesting facts
There there are yeah, there's enough there to make for something of a lecture
I mean genuinely the the problem is just organizing a lecture like when would I have the opportunity to do a lecture?
right
Yeah
That's the biggest obstacle
It'd be like rad con with me and you and tom
Yeah, maybe night. I don't know that that's like I don't know either
I just don't know I just don't know um
Yeah
Honestly, if there was like something
some
New rad con or spiritual successor to a rad con. I probably would I probably would like attempt to do something like this
Just because like why not?
Uh, it would be funny
um
I actually be a lot I'd have to like go back through like
Okay, there were there would be a lot to say there's a lot you could say about the rise and fall of digi, bro
But the hard part is separating the wheat from the chaff because a lot of it would be boring
a lot of it would be like
Oh, and then
you know shit talking about like uh
Like digi bro's turntable or like the hentai samurai. Oh, no, I know what nobody cares about that. It would be entirely like
the drama
People only really want to know about the fall
I mean, yeah
You know, you're kind of right actually
The the other rise would be like youtuber begins and then grows in popularity is like a story everyone knows
Yeah, like you can you give the you give the you give the broad strokes of the rise the rise kind of speaks for itself
Like, okay, this is what they did. This is why they were popular and then what happened. Well, yeah
Honestly, yeah, honestly. Yeah, it's not about it. It's not a bad idea and given the opportunity. I probably would do it
um
Q the Q the
Suddenly yig studios
Is is alerted that I said that and then they become uh, they they
They their new mission is to stop stop the stop rad con at any cost. We can't allow we can't allow another rad con to happen
to be devastating
They have a history of stopping lectures from existing
Yeah
true
They've got a proven track record. They can do it. They love it. They love
They love it. Uh, next voicemail is oh god, it's
You know, I guess this I guess this is a way to get me to read your text message
um
Okay
I'm sorry if you've been told this already, but you don't seem to understand
That mining cryptocurrency and processing cryptocurrency transactions are exactly the same thing
The miners are rewarded a set amount of currency for processing transactions
I don't believe you. I don't think you're right
You have to mine the currency before it can be traded
Trading trading currency
No, you're you're you're wrong
You're just wrong. Do they mean the same thing in terms of energy usage or whatever?
Because that may have been what we would know this guy this guy says they are literally the same thing which they cannot be
It can't that can't be the case. So
dismissed
Next
Oh god, okay. The next one has a video attached to it. Um, but here i'll i'll put the
Here's the voicemail
Come on
Okay, three two one go
Hey, ben I heard you like ridiculously long video essays
This dude just posted a seven and a half hour fucking analysis of this
great
British tv show is it hose
Okay
Wait pyrocynical. Okay. I know I vaguely know pyrocynical the best and worst show you like a shitty reaction
channel
That has a lot of drama around him
Okay, didn't this guy get like uh, this guy get canceled for grooming or something
It's it's in that bull park of like a bunch of bullshit that i've heard vaguely
I don't know. Maybe they're all right, but I doubt it
Okay, this is the this is the kind of video that I like I like seven hour long videos about some bullshit
I wish it were about a video game instead of about a tv show, but
Wait, let me let me hear this guy's voice. Let me listen to this guy's voice
Shut up no, let me hear the the guy's voice stop playing clips
Okay, his voice sounds fine some people I can't watch uh because their voice is bad uh bread sword
uh super eyepatch wolf
uh nightmind
uh joseph galler
I can't watch any other shit because their voices are too obnoxious
Wait, this this is he's going through but this guy sounds okay at a time
That's why seven hours long. Yeah
Yeah, which uh one like a doctor who
Um jody woodiker
Like breakdown episode by episode why the writing sucked and the characters have nothing to them and that was good
That was a good ride
Okay, the name
the
The the the go through every episode. It's a bit of a cheap shortcut
To length pat out a length. Yeah
It's a bit of a cheap shortcut. It can still be good
I'm a bit it's a bit
Dodgy, but I might give it a shot. Maybe I don't know it's one of those things where like
Something that's true in one episode
Will often be true in multiple episodes, but they end up seeing it multiple times
Um didn't uh, oh god that guy um
I think the guy ls mark
He did a video where he goes through every single like all like 700 episodes of the simpsons
And he gives like a little he doesn't give a long summary, but he does like he summarizes like each one
I watched that whole thing
I mean he does you know after a while I
It was pretty good because it wasn't that could get really annoying
But he eventually he starts being like, okay, there's only so much I can say about each of these
Like he doesn't he doesn't like repeat
Hems his his point over and over again for like
Each of the new one like it gets to a point where he's really like rapid firing them like bam bam bam
And like, you know, that's how you got to do it
Um, yeah, I like that one. I like that video. Um
Okay, the next one is called help. I can't figure out how this thing works
Uh, why didn't it hold on please post in the okay help. I can't figure out
How this thing works
Solaru plus it keeps asking for an email at egg.com. You've you've sent voicemails before
Whatever three two one go
Hey, y'all, it's me again. I just wanted to say that last week's pod was really good and thank you again
Oh, so I wanted to leave a comment for the guest Advil you had on
Hey there
You're a complete coward and I honestly feel sorry for you. Hmm. I watched the video you made and gave up 31 minutes and four seconds in
You talked about looking at things in context and yet you were more than happy to protect a complete garbage of a human
Who's done actual harm to my community?
Just to try and get a dub against pina or whatever the fuck
I'm not going to be cute about it. Go fuck yourself. Hmm
yeah, um
I wouldn't I wouldn't collaborate with antunes under any circumstances
personally
I didn't actually go back and watch
Or listen to the part of the that episode before I arrived. So I don't know what was talked about. Oh
But I don't really care. So that guy. Yeah, that guy. Yeah, he did a he did a video where he talked to
Ethereum and antunes about why daft pina is bad
Yeah, there's there's no way that daft pina is anywhere as bad as antunes. So like
It's pretty stupid. Uh
Yeah, a bunch of people in my discord were
I haven't didn't actually watch the uh the daft pina takedown video or whatever that guy had a bunch of people in my discord
Complained about it and said it was bad for various reasons
Uh
But I don't know that's that's not me talking. I don't have an opinion
um
Okay, next voicemail is another image. So here we go what we got
Okay, what is I think I think this speaks for itself
That arm goes like that's like a triple jointed one piece. Yeah, she's got a she she's she's from the long arm tribe
The long arm. Yeah
What what more is there to say it's my my friend. It's my friend ben sain. It's my friend ben sain
You know what i'm referencing there. Yeah, I know what you're referencing. It's just okay
Okay
Next one is uh nnn week two reddit.com slash r slash no nate at gmail.com
Uh, here we go
Three two one go
Hey guys go in one week strong
I haven't made it all week long and I feel better than ever to clarify from last week
Participating in this challenge is to not watch listen or engage with Nate bestman or any of his content for the whole month
Wow, anyone just joining the challenge. I know it can be tough
Yeah, so i'm gonna read an excerpt from an inspirational reddit post about this month's challenge
This comes from reddit user ihdn 2012. He writes. I was addicted to Nate for 20 years
I was lonely miserable and desperately wanted a part sometimes so badly. I wanted to die
Skipping ahead a little he says about two weeks after I stopped watching Nate. I met an amazing woman
I knew that if I was still a Nate addict, I would not find her attractive
She doesn't have the enormous intellect that Nate has
And she is an incredibly perfect person. She is so beautiful to me and I'm way happier now
Wow, isn't that inspiring? I know I'm ready for another week of not nating until next time
No, Nate. Yes watch change change your life change your life the powers in your hands
Lesson is you you just have to take that change your life doesn't really work
Unsubscribe change. Yeah, we're yeah good enough
Um unsubscribe change your life
Nate not even once
Nate even once uh
next
What what what can I say but that I wholeheartedly endorse no, Nate November
um
Next next voicemail is called
Trixie's dignity equals
All right, three two one go
Oh nothing, I get it. It's nothing
There's nothing I thought it was gonna be like I thought it was gonna be like a quote of somebody yelling something
Oh, I thought it was gonna be a fart noise
Yeah
No, okay. All right. I got it. I got it message received
Uh, this is the last voicemail. We didn't have that many this week. Uh, this is uh, Australian father finds out how much pcp makes on patreon
Three two one go
$900 dues
Tobias
Did you send money to patreon.com slash the procrastinators?
Yes, but it was an emergency
Trixie was talking mad shit to a bunch of dickshits
So Ben and Gabe had to react true. Oh my god
She didn't go and get herself ratioed now did she?
No, that's a cool dad
Cool as fucking damn, I wish I had an Australian father
We are up to uh
$954
dollars, I think um
Dollar reduce if we it
It's over
Um, if we could get to I think if we could get to 1,050
So if we got another hundred dollars, we would have tripled our patreon in over the last like three months
Uh, which would be really now. I mean we're all we've almost tripled it, which is pretty good. Thanks everyone for your pledges. Um
Yeah, hey what I would suggest what I would suggest
And I mean this in an entirely legal
Way and that I am not responsible for anything, but I would suggest uh, I would suggest goading
I would suggest goading Trixie into into making more
podcast appearance into uh making more uh
Making more statements against us. Uh, I really want more of those. Uh, they've been a
They've been a huge boon
Uh, uh, uh to us. So, uh, uh, I want more you want more
Um, send send her like I don't know send her like lies about us
Tell her that she that we said things we didn't say
And have her get mad just make her mad
Um
I don't like you disavow you disavow
um, I think it's funny but like
It's it's like I don't know. I don't think it'll work
And I'd rather not
Lies being flung around even in a joke way
I would like for lies
Who knows how many dick show fans will latch onto that and agree with it
Maybe even two maybe three people three care in any way about the procrastinators
Then we can't have that we can't have that we can't have that
We're we're we only need every one. It's really funny because like like if if if it results in like Trixie's spreading lies about us who
Will pay attention and also who will care. It's really no one so I know but it's not much of like a reason not to do it
Exactly. That's what I'm saying. I don't know. I'm just
I feel like all right. All right. Trixie is a person of very low intelligence, but I think even even she
probably
Noticed that like hmm when I tried to attack the pcp
I made a fool of myself and gave them a bunch of money
Uh, I won't do that. I shouldn't do that again and
And you know that chill that chilling effect is unfortunate
Because I want it to continue, uh, but I feel I feel like maybe it won't I feel like even she may have learned the lesson and that's a shame
Uh, so I don't know
of
I don't know
Can't can't force her just can't force her to make a fool of herself, but uh, I don't know. Oh, she'll do it
Just give her a chill. She'll she's
I really think that she the the the the recent spate of like the recent spate of of uh
outspoken
attacks and and and
She's because she's become more active on twitter and I and I think
I sense that I sense that something is is something is shifting there something is is
Things are things are hitting the fan or things are coming to you ahead and and uh
The the the the the
The the
There will be there will be hostility. I feel like I feel like we are coming to a point where there may there may be greater hostility
Um, because I mean once once she's lost everything like what else will there be for her except to like
Lash out, right? So, you know, hopefully that day comes soon
Uh, but I guess we'll see
um
Anyway patreon.com slash the procrastinators
If you want to hear us respond to her
appearance on who are these podcasts
Very funny stuff
Also, if you want to hear about some fun facts
and learn
what to do
If someone calls you a gay wizard. Hey, you know what I was thinking yesterday
Uh, Rowling said
that Dumbledore
was gay
and he's a wizard
And you know, he didn't he he didn't deny it
which made it true
Well, and I just
That's all he was in the grave when that happened
Damn
If only he'd if only he'd been alive to say if only he'd been alive to well, I won't say I won't say what he should have done
I won't say what he should have done when Rowling said. Oh, yeah Dumbledore. Oh, he was gay all along
I won't say what he should have done
You're gonna have to go listen to the fun fact challenge if you want to know what to do
in that kind of a sticky situation
It could save your life
Uh, um
yeah, and uh
speakfipe.com slash
Uh, is it tpcrastinators?
I feel like shit. What's our fucking
uh, what's our what's our fucking
tpcrastinator, I think
Is it tpcrastinators? Why is it different?
Why is it different on every fucking platform?
Okay, uh, send us a voicemail if you want
um
Check out, uh, check out, uh, the money spenders podcast
Oh, give me your microphone check out the money spenders punk. Is it is it patreon.com slash
Give and take give and take patreon patreon.com slash give and take for, uh, the money spenders podcast
Uh, I will be I will be going
I will be going and listening to that
Uh, probably today because I do want to hear about that secret project
Also, check out the drawcast
YouTube channel the new one
with oblivionfall
and teleperte and others and I am on
Later today, in fact, I am going to be recording
our
us all like talking about the, um
The telephone channel last week. I talked about how my uh, my my fucking stream fucked up
Oh, wait. Oh, you're on that too, right?
Yeah
Oh, yeah, are you gonna?
Yeah, right that's tonight. Yeah. Oh shit. Wait, what?
There's what was what's happening tonight? Did you not did you not get a message? Uh, in yeah
I got an at in the server and oblivionfall said
We're gonna record the video tonight
Oh my god, you mean everybody that was in the drug uh, the the thing
He well, I might have missed an earlier message, but he specifically added
Wait, let me check. He specifically added me and teleperte
I
Don't know why he specifically added just us
Uh, I told him it was good for me
You might want to you might want to respond to that
Huh
Wait, there's the art telephone chat, which I assume is where that was
No, this was in well. I got an ad in scheduling
uh
Did he just not message you
I is it for
I don't know what's going on. Wait, isn't that just a normal draw cast that you're doing?
No
Wait, yeah for the draw cast you're doing you're doing a draw cast wait. I am
Oh, that's not the the telephone thing. That's another thing
What you're gonna be on an episode
Oh god
I don't remember saying I wanted to do that
I thought oblivion. No oblivion for telling me that he you wanted to put you with teleperte
I thought like you you wanted to be with I don't know
Law
I don't remember. Okay, whatever. Well, I guess it's too late. I already told him I was gonna do it. Uh, oops
Oh, well, I guess I'll be on I guess I'll be on that or whatever
Uh, I just want to work on my fucking game
sucks
stupid
um
Okay, whatever
Uh, anyway, watch that if you want I guess, um, okay, that's it. Okay. Bye
That's the end of the episode. Bye