Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We did it ladies and gentlemen.
We actually made a fucking podcast.
Hey everybody I'm Mumkey Jones, you look up Mumkey in the dictionary, that's a p-
He really is the best guy.
I wish I was there.
Whoever.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
come on, come on, come on, come on come on, come on, come on, come on
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh fuck. I'm going to fucking withdraws. Oh god. Oh fuck. I gotta put that
Give a better than occasional guest right into my veins. Oh god. Oh fuck.
Oh no. Hey everybody. Excuse me. Excuse me. What's going on? What's going on here?
You're all banned. You're all gone. You're all killed. It's 2018, Give. Nothing bad ever happened
ever. No. Get out. Get out. I'll attack you. I'll kill you. I killed Ben. This is the
announcement of the episode 300. Ben's dead. It's my show now. It's my show. It's Gib show.
Yo. Oh hell yeah. Let's start. Let's just fucking. Fuck yes. Give. I really like this
comic you started. I think it's going places. Thank you. Oh you know what? You can stay.
You're too kind. What a generous overboard. Money. YouTube dollars. See this is what happens
when a YouTube channel is run by a woman. They kill their co-host.
But they accept compliments. That's the that's what happens. Let me check all that city.
Should we be already recording? I mean Craig's recording right now.
Craig was recording so it's fine. I don't trust Craig. I'm recording. I'm recording right now.
I don't trust him. I'm sorry about my recording in a second.
Well you know it's a nice year 2018. Wait when did the PCP started? 2016? Was it before that?
Oh yes. I forgot. It was very late. It was late 2050 and it was right at the end of 2050.
Yes. Let me check. It was one or two episodes in the year. The PCP outlasted Trump. That's funny.
Oh yeah. First episode. So December 2015. Hey Ben. It's me. What the fuck Ben? I killed you.
I stabbed you. I saw you die. She did. You wish. It's a guess like a girl boss.
Oh no. That was your ninja clone jutsu. It was just a log.
It was just a log that appeared in a poof of smoke. I know you've just been waiting
until the day that I die and you can take over the PCP. Damn it. It was my big plan.
You'll curl claw this PCP for my cold dead hands. But instead of a log it's a
even the whip blurry. Yeah. Instead of a log it's the lord of ghosts. I can't hear anything.
We're all on left. That's because Gabe stabbed you in the ear so that's why you can't hear anything.
Can we invite like CMC and pretend like he's Jesse?
We need Jesse. I think we're fine. We've got Jeff, we've got Monkey, we've got Nate.
Who can be mage? Like Gamer's Tavern? No.
No. Yeah, that sounds about right.
Oh, Lumia, it feels made to Jason. Oh god. That is true. Where is Tom Oliver can come back and play the boo.
That's great. That's great. Perfect casting.
Okay, I'm going to take this opportunity to pee. I'm going to also pee.
Don't do it, guys. Wake up at 1am for this and you two need to pee.
Just pee in a cup. Just pee on stream.
Yeah, 1am then.
1am waking up in the morning. Gotta be fresh. Gotta go downstairs.
Gotta have my ball. Gotta have cereal. I'm pretending to be Monkey Jones.
Okay, I'm trying to think of like what Monkey sounds like and my first thought in my head was
like Jacksepticeye's intro where he does the whip crack and he's like, what top of the morning to you?
And I'm like, that's not... I've never heard Jacksepticeye's intro.
Oh, you got it. Let me get the... Oh, you haven't lived. You haven't lived.
She's not wrong. She's not wrong. I watched the beginning of a Monkey video before I showed up
and it's like, hey, everybody, it's me, Monkey Jones. So it sounds like it's...
It's Monkey Jones here. I'm fresh out of... I'm fresh out of fucks to give and I'm ready to rape you.
That's what he says, right?
You know what? I think we should recast Ben as Monkey and I should pay Ben.
All right, all right, this is a video. You should just watch this video.
Oh, god. Come at the morning.
Okay. I think I've seen this one. Oh my god. Fucking rape my ears.
I need to make a version of this with, like, all of the...
Hello and welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast and have that be the intro.
You need to make one with the...
Is that the bite of 87?
It's the bite of 87. It's always the bite of 87.
I need to grab, like, 100 episodes of the PCPs and, like, put all of them in one audacity and,
like, have them aligned where Nate says, hello and welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast
and then it's just incomprehensible noise on either side of that.
Why don't you make a noise album or radio oblivion?
You know you want to.
Who's oblivion?
Can you make a noise album already, Jeff?
Now you want to.
Yeah. If algorithm... I don't know what Jeff means.
I just know he's a money machine.
I was, um...
He's the paper's gone.
I was editing the, uh...
I was editing the documentary yesterday.
It's so fucking weird that Jeff is in there.
He's just walking around.
Just walking around.
Documentary?
Yeah, Radcom the Documentary from the Blu-rays.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
I guess I should mention, uh...
Yeah, I'm, uh...
I'm gonna put...
Along with the 300 episode, I'm gonna put out, yeah, Radcom the Documentary.
There's no, like, ending.
It's just, like, random footage.
It just ends at no particular point.
Uh...
It's just, like, two hours of random footage from Radcom, too.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Oh, and I guess, uh...
I'm gonna put out that along with episode 300.
And I think, Gib, I think we're gonna do a commentary, right?
We're gonna do a commentated version.
Are we?
With all the slur...
Yeah!
With all the slurs.
Unedited.
No.
Well, the private version.
Private version.
I'm taking them out.
I'm cutting that out of the public release.
Of course.
It's not the...
It just ends.
I don't know.
It's, like...
I think Victor edited it, but it's just, like, random footage.
And there's no point.
There's no, like...
There's no start.
You just end it.
It starts...
It starts like it's gonna go somewhere.
It starts like there's gonna be a point to it.
Like, it's gonna tell a story.
And then the footage just becomes, like...
It's just random things that happened up until, I think, you know...
Jeff arrives, and then Jesse arrives.
And then it's like, well, we're all here.
And then we were just, like, fucking around in the living room.
And then that's the end of the documentary.
That's exactly what the PCP is.
Yeah, yeah.
You just end with a fade into black and say a text that says,
and nothing bad ever happened.
That's such a good idea, Nate.
They made so much content.
And everyone was content with the content.
And it was fine.
Just to check, let me see how many episodes of the PCP I've ate.
Gotta be...
Is it 100?
It's probably less than 100, right?
Oh my god, no, it's more than 100.
Are you serious?
I started with Christian Minecraft and Soup.
I guess we should talk about this on the episode.
I'm recording already.
Is everyone else recording?
Yeah, I'm recording.
I said when I was recording.
Recording.
I mean, Craig is recording.
It's recording, all right.
Just notice.
They uploaded to Spotify the rooftop performance of the Beatles from Get Back.
And to listen to that.
Sometimes I forget that you and Lane had huge Beatles heads.
I used to be an Amos swan's head.
You should listen to swans, each one.
Yeah, it's a funny guy screaming.
If I wanted to listen to that, Elisa, I'd listen to the PCP.
Cute laugh track.
A funny guy's creamy.
Yeah.
That's he then.
You're the funny guy.
Although keep in mind, the Beatles do scream a lot.
You know, I just, I just...
I saw, I had a little bit of a panic attack when I looked at the chat and I saw Jeff and
Mumkey and Nate in here.
But now I realize, I'm looking again and I'm like, oh wait, it's that picture of Mumkey.
Yes.
Wait, where's...
Is that really the picture from the sextet?
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
I've seen it.
It's so weird.
It feels weird.
I haven't seen it.
And I...
It's very strange.
I mean, whatever.
It's pretty funny.
I don't feel that.
I don't feel bad laughing because he filmed it on purpose.
So, like...
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, it's, it's, yeah.
I don't feel, I don't feel bad.
But when you record it, it's very...
When you record something like that, you're like, need to expect this.
It is going to get leaked.
Only if you're a public figure.
Yeah.
All right.
It could have been, that could have been me, that could have been me having sex with that
furry pedophile, if only, if only the dice of history had landed a little differently.
To see that you needed to be with sheep over first.
You need to be with someone who treated you well.
So, so you'd be sick of them and treat them bad.
If only.
Okay.
So, is this the episode?
Have we started?
I started.
I didn't think we had.
I thought this was...
I thought you saying you killed Ben was a cold open.
That could go right at the beginning and then Ben could appear and I like that part.
That could go that open at the beginning.
Well, I'm recording.
So, fuck it.
I am recording.
Let's sync.
Okay.
On the count of three, say sync.
One, two, three, sync.
Sync.
Hello.
I'm the nostalgia critic.
And this is the Procrastinators podcast.
The podcast that thinks racism is good and civil rights are bad.
I'm Ben Sane.
And this is everyone else.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Just episode 300 of a show that we're in.
This is 300.
Hello, it's me, Jeff.
I read the algorithm and it said,
I should come on to the PCP for big YouTube money.
Jeff sitting in his pondering chamber
observing the algorithm like his wizard's orb,
just reading the signs and the tea leaves.
Somebody else go.
Hey, it's me, Monkey Jones, freshly reborn from Nate's Busy
and ready to take a hold of my personal responsibility.
Oh, my God, he's monkey.
Oh, I didn't see him there.
I hope you like that impression.
I'm not doing it again.
It's Monkey Jones here.
I had to commit a real life school shooting.
Hey, it's Monkey Jones.
It's a school shooting.
I mean, I'm taking a camera into the girl's bathroom.
It's me, Monkey Jones here to commit real life sex crimes.
Let's let's get into it.
Shall we put some typo?
And it's me, Nate.
Today we're going to talk about personal responsibility.
Personal fucking responsibility.
It's going to be a five hour podcast of that.
You can't believe like you can fix poverty
just by telling people that it's their fault, but they're poor.
Yeah.
It's really amazing.
Jeff.
I can't believe you can fix suicidality
by cheating on your girlfriend with a pedophile.
Oh, Jeff, you and your lib, you and your libcuck ways,
you and your, you probably voted for Hillary
because your sex worker girlfriend told you to.
Fuck you.
Yeah, that's exactly what happened.
Yeah.
Actually, you fucker, you got me.
I know.
Die.
Oh, fuck, Jeff's dead.
Shit.
Darn.
Now, now what'll I do?
Now what big money connections will I use
to get ahead in the YouTube game?
This is stupid.
I know it's stupid.
I know.
Jeff's dead.
Oblivion Falls here.
Hello, welcome to the PC.
Wow, it's Oblivion Falls.
I prefer that person.
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that Seachole?
Oh, yeah.
Seachole?
I like Seachole.
Oh my god.
I broke, I broke through the shell that was monkey Jones.
I split myself out of his organs and now I am here.
I've killed him.
You are all saved.
Thank god.
Praise him.
That's me, Elia, Sardator of the BCP.
Elia, is I the editor of the pro?
Pressnators is here.
Dude, that guy's famous.
Are you guys hungover?
I'm hungover.
I feel terrible.
No.
Oh, no.
What happened?
You drunk alcohol?
Why are you drinking alcohol?
Tragically, I did.
Tragically, I didn't buy a bottle.
My, well, my good friend John, a.k.a.
D'Wubo, invited me over for a Friday game night and I bought a beer and I drank it.
And I guess, and I guess I, you know, I was too, you know what?
I was just too demure.
I was too like, I was, I was so focused on making a good impression and being polite
in polite company that I was like, no, no, no, I can't, I can't drink water.
I must not drink water from the tap to prevent a hangover.
Yeah.
So now here I am dehydrated and in agony.
And that's, and that's just how it goes sometimes.
Why not drink water?
That's so silly.
I told you why because I wanted to make a good impression on polite company.
What would they have thought if they had saw me drinking water?
They would have thought you didn't want to be a hangover.
They would have shaken their head and said, what an filthy animal, filthy animal.
Why he might as well be drinking, he might as well be drinking it directly out of an
outhouse latrine.
No.
That you would think it's bad to drink water.
I don't want people to think badly of me.
No, he thinks it's bad to drink water from the tap specifically.
These, these friends that I've known for years and years, if they saw me drinking water,
they would, they would, they would lose all their respect for me.
They don't sound like very good friends when you put it that way, Ben.
You know what?
You're right.
Fuck those guys.
Damn.
I was hungover on Saturday because instead of sleeping, I was in the pronoun server
watching Dog Day Afternoon, which is an amazing movie.
It's about Al Pacino robbing a bank to get money for his wife to get a sex change.
Uh, it's from the 70s.
It's a great movie I recommend it.
Like, like a trans woman, like his wife is a, is a, is an MTF and wants a sex change.
Yeah.
Neat.
The head of it, the head of its time.
And it's like from like 75 the movie.
So it's like, it really is a hit of the time.
Damn, be gay, do crimes.
Is she like a prostitute?
Is he like falling, falling in love with a prostitute?
And it's like, I'm going to get you as that sex change I always wanted and then we're going
to run away to Mexico together.
Oh no.
No, they run to Wyoming.
Okay, that's good.
That's good too, I guess.
I watched a movie.
Tragically, I watched a film this, this week.
Oh my god.
I know.
I never do that.
The story is I saw, I saw a random tweet that was like, hey, it was a random tweet
in appreciation of some filmmaker who had made two movies before dying at the age of 39.
And it said both.
Both of this guy's movies are on some fucking streaming service.
I think I still have the tab open.
Wait, the streaming service is...
Tooby.
And it was like...
Yeah, T-U-B-I.
And this guy made two movies.
One is called Night Vision and the other is called Mind Killer.
And I was like, fuck it.
And I went and I watched Mind Killer.
And it was okay.
It was bad.
But I guess it had some charm to it.
It had some things that I liked.
I liked the nerdy friend side character who liked to howl like a coyote.
He was charming.
It's about a nerdy weirdo who has no success with women
and watches like pickup artists' self-help videos.
He works at a library and he finds a manuscript that teaches him
concentration exercises to unlock the power of the mind.
And it turns him into like a psychic genius and he becomes like a sociopath freak.
Who like controls women's minds to fuck them.
I'm looking at the poster of the movie.
And this looked like when I ate the PCP.
Hold on, I don't even know what the poster looks like.
They should have called the movies Night Killer and Mind Division.
Hold on.
I gotta see this.
That Rubik's Cube sucks.
I gotta see this shit for myself.
Is that only three colors?
In general.
It is.
It's a three-color Rubik's Cube.
Wow, this poster actually is exactly what the movie is like.
This is exactly what it's like.
Warren's brain is out of his...
Ew.
You know what?
In hindsight, this movie ruled.
This is a great film.
Looking at this poster, I'm like, hell yeah.
This is what March Simpson looks like.
I feel like I'm gonna say...
This is like a thing that like an idiot...
This is like a thing that an idiot would say to sound...
But think they sounded smart.
And other idiots would think, wow, this guy's really smart.
The appeal of this movie was not so much in the monster
and in the special effects and in the horror.
It was about the characters.
You know, it was about the characters really.
It was about getting invested in their characters.
And then only then did the fear and the terror
presented by the creature and the horrific scenario,
you know, impact one emotionally.
When one was already invested in the drama
of these characters and their lives,
much like a film ought to do, right?
Wow.
Yeah.
Sounds like at the end of every nostalgic critic review
where he gets serious and he actually reviews the movie.
This episode of the Road Runner, the Coyotean Road Runner,
it says so much with just a desert road
and a rock dropped off of a cliff.
It really shows the dichotomy between men, you know,
a wolf and a road runner.
It's a coyote.
Yeah, same diff.
No.
Well, cool.
I didn't watch a film.
Good.
Don't.
So I will never speak of such things.
Don't waste your life like I did watching one movie.
While you were studying...
It's 90 minutes.
I'll never get back.
While you were watching simple media made by artists that suck.
He sucks so much, he's literally dead now.
He died at 39.
I was studying.
Just like you will when I get through with you.
In many years time.
Yeah, in nine years or so.
11 years.
Right, okay.
Close enough.
I've been getting really into ancient history and geography and stuff
because springing off of my world building sort of interest,
building maps and stuff and mountains and being like,
oh, lore, you know, like how do I make lore?
How do I make a lore of like ancient civilizations
that rose and fell and wars they had?
Oh, I'll look at history.
And now I'm just into history videos.
I know why you've been looking into this stuff and I'm surprised.
I'm surprised that you've delved deeply into it, I guess is what I'm...
Wait, you know why?
Partly, yeah.
I don't know if I can say it without spoiling stuff.
Maybe you're thinking of something else.
Maybe I am thinking of something else.
My secret project.
Isn't this stuff involved with like your secret project and the backstory for it?
Yes, yes, a little bit.
A little bit, okay.
I just think it's cool.
I just think it's neat that like, you know, things happened
and people wrote it down so we can learn about it.
Dude, people had cats and...
It's just so novel that I can read like letters
I can read funny lines on a page or hear them spoken by a person
and like get a sense of stuff that was happening before I was born.
Isn't that crazy?
Like the Beatles?
Yeah, there's kind of still alive.
I can walk around in Colombia in Bioshock Infinite
and I can pick up little record tapes and play them and people say,
hey, and people say, hello, everybody, welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast.
You can listen to podcast episodes.
You can find on little tapes that people left scattered around the wreckage of the former world.
Like an annoying like secret.
Like you've got like this big open world like fallout or whatever
and the logs are entire episodes of the Procrastinator's podcast.
And then like four hours later, you're still playing the game,
listening to this thing I'm like...
I think when Phantom's Revenge is done,
I think I'll have to start work on a new game that is just a walk around like world.
It's just a post-apocalyptic walking simulator.
There's no combat, nothing happens.
You just walk around and you pick up audio logs that are just all 300 episodes of the PCP.
And you piece together the wreckage of the old world.
You should make that game.
Like in 200 years from now, in 200 years from now,
it would be the younger video game Nerdmeme.
It's like, hey, wanna listen to some tunes?
Hello, it's the piece, the Procrastinator's podcast.
What you should do is you could put them on little tapes
and then spread them out in the real world.
And then they'll be like a weird mystery that people will freak out about.
The literal lust tapes.
I like that.
And then we archive the PCP.
I mean, I have a burner.
I have dick.
Those discs could be cheap.
One episode of the PCP would probably fit on...
It'd be pretty small, right?
It'd be a pretty small file.
You could fit that out.
As an audio file, yeah.
It wouldn't have to use...
Yeah, it's like an MP3.
It wouldn't have to use a whole 50 gigabyte Blu-ray disc.
I could just use some fucking like four gig.
Some four gig shitty CD, yeah.
No problem.
I mean, I was thinking of literal cassette tapes, but I can't.
But nobody has a player for those anymore.
No, no, no.
Exactly, only true chats can actually listen to them.
Wait, I should just leave them around on the USB thumb drives.
Just leave them scattered around in garbage cans.
Leave them scattered in garbage cans for civil waste municipal sanitation workers
to find.
Only the big market for the PCP is garbage men who find it in trash cans scattered
around Boston, Massachusetts.
I can guarantee no garbage man actually.
You could look at the waveform and then film the waveform with an old timey camera
and then make a film real of the waveform that people will have to look at and then
decode and turn it into audio so they can listen to it.
There's like a skill floor.
A skill floor for listening.
You know, and they get like arguments about Final Fantasy and Pokemon as the reward.
Do you know about the Boyager, the gold disc that they send to
space for the Martians to find?
The what they send?
Not Martians, just anyone.
Aliens, just aliens in general.
It's like they send a satellite into space just to travel around the whole galaxy with a gold disc.
Oh, does it with the little plaque on it that has those things that they hope will be decodable
and understandable by anyone?
Yeah, they should send another one with PCP episodes on it.
No, I don't think.
I think they've suffered enough being aliens and all.
Talking about.
Where's Ben?
Ben died.
Ben did die.
We're talking about ancient history.
I watched this video, just the archaeology I swear to explain.
That was that was a really interesting theory that I found there that I don't know if you
know this kind of statues are very famous.
Oh, I've seen that statue.
We've talked about this stupid thing.
I hate this thing.
Why do you hate it?
It is ugly.
Yeah, look at it.
Why do you hate it?
I hate it for the same reason I hate you.
It's ugly.
Oh my fucking god.
Typical white male opinion.
I know, right?
This is the right thing to say.
What's ugly about her?
There was a theory that's like.
Got no face.
She looks she's basically she's basically been saying look at that cap.
She's pulled it so down low.
It's just like Ben's saying.
It's just too close to home.
It hits too close to home.
That's why you have to lash out.
You can't you can't handle it in the video.
There's the theory of why they look like that.
And it's that since they had no mirrors,
they just like look below their bodies and that's how they saw their bodies.
So that's how they that's the best.
Tarbuck transom said the same thing in a voicemail.
Stupidest fucking thing I ever heard.
That was making sense.
Just look at another human being.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I know why they look like that.
It's because back in the day,
there was a prehistoric oblivion full who needed to make people
with fat tits.
That's all about them hips.
It's all about them titties.
It's all about that little chub.
You need that.
Yeah, that's what that's about.
That weird like hoof foot mess at the bottom there.
Feed a hug.
I'll tell you what that's up.
Have you ever noticed that like 50% of porn artists just never draw feet?
The image always comes off at the ankle.
I have noticed that.
And I always find it to be.
All artists never draw feet.
They just cut them off.
It's it's so much easier and I hate it.
But I also I'm like, I guess if I want to draw more often,
I should I should take shortcuts where nobody cares.
Nobody actually wants to see the except specific feet people.
That's exactly it.
I mean, like that's what you do in life in everything you do.
You got to be like, how can I what's the cheapest way I can do this?
The easiest possible way so I can do so I can do more of it.
The only reason Quentin Tarantino shows the feed is because he's like,
look, I'm not taking shortcuts.
See you.
He didn't saw off their feet to make the access cheaper.
You know, speaking of fertility goddesses, this month I came up with Febubrary.
Hashtag Febubrary, which is rolls right off the tongue.
It rolls right off the page, not off the tongue.
You can't say it, but you can read it.
Um, and I'm like, I wanted to draw more like titillating imagery
because I just need practice in that.
And I like the idea of being good at that.
And that's what I'm doing this month.
It's a gimmick art month, just like many other gimmick art months
where you do something every day for a month.
And I'm drawing a boob every day, kind of sort of.
I'm putting it on Twitter.
How's this for a gimmick month?
Uh, hold on.
January, February, March.
How about ape, uh, ape, ape, live April?
How about April live real where I just am alive?
I just live for every, every day.
I just live in a hole all day every day.
Oh, sounds like a hustle.
30 times a month.
I, I like April where in April you draw ape.
Just draw apes.
It's too, in 2022 it's a little, it's a little NFT adjacent.
It makes me a little uncomfortable.
But they do be monkeys though.
They do be monkeys though, but, but they just,
you know, it's, if it's ape adjacent, it's just, it's just,
there's something, uh, what's the word I'm looking for?
It's too, I don't know.
Make an active effort to co-op the apes back from the NFT bros.
And I steal that property.
They love so much.
We do have to reclaim.
We have to reclaim the apes.
You know what I haven't, you know what?
I haven't seen a lazy lion in months.
Everyone forgot about lazy lions.
Oh my gosh.
The apes are still around.
The apes are the ones that everyone knows,
but the lions are gone.
So that's cool.
I, I, I unfortunately was, I was approached by someone
who, they were really desperate to message me.
They pledged to my Patreon.
They tried every avenue to be like,
hey oblivion, oblivion, I've got an idea.
I've got an idea.
It's going to be big.
It's you, you're going to want to do it.
It'll, it'll be bigger when it comes on.
It'll be the biggest thing ever, please.
I have such a good idea.
And I'm like, I, I didn't get back to him for a month
because I was like, I had just caught COVID
around the time I saw their messages.
And I'm like, I'm a fucking bleh.
And then they unplugged my Patreon.
So I'm like, I'll, I'll get back to you later.
Eventually message them on Discord.
Turns out they're just an ideas man.
And I mean, okay, they want to get the ideas good.
They didn't give me specific ideas for what their idea was.
So I'm like, I don't know.
How can I know if this is worth my time?
But I checked again the next day and they have since then
now have a fucking monkey profile picture.
And it, there's a little Discord verified sticker next to it.
And I'm just like, oof.
I'm a little, I mean, you say they're an ideas man.
Like what did they, what did they want?
I don't know.
They're like, it's going to be the next come zone.
What's going to be the next come zone?
What?
I don't know.
They have ideas apparently.
What are you talking about?
Like, do they have lyrics?
Do they have, what do they have?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know.
Well, what did they expect you to do before they would explain it?
Did they say, like, give me your bank account information
and I'll tell you all about it?
Like, what would they say?
I don't know.
Look, when I make my Discord, like my Patreon Discord,
I will let them join.
And, and if they want to like explain it forever,
like I'll hear them out because it's possible they'll have an idea.
And I'll be like, oh yeah, that sounds fun.
Maybe I do want to do that.
But like, currently I have, I don't know.
Oblivion, I have a great idea.
It's possible the sun won't rise tomorrow as well.
Yeah.
Yeah, hear me out, Billy.
It's going to be the next come zone.
This idea is so great.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, Fed Boop Worry, right?
Oh my God.
We just do that on the PCP, on the PCP, on the draw cast with Giv.
Oh yeah.
We give on, we do one of the short quick episodes of Fed Boop Worry.
Okay.
What about this?
We should do an episode that isn't tits and ass, it's just tits.
And then later, we can do an episode that's just ass, you know?
Hell yeah.
What about, oh yeah, we'll do an episode called Top Heavy
and then we can do another one called Bottom Heavy.
What about, what about?
What about July?
A month where every day I say I'm going to do something but I don't do it.
Wait, what?
Listen, listen, if I didn't-
July, July, a month where every day I say I'm going to draw something but it's a lie
and I don't do anything.
Sorry, I was thinking of an alternative spelling then.
Yeah.
I feel like that would encourage certain individuals that I know to get on my back
about certain things.
Okay, okay, I didn't even think of that.
I was just, I was just thinking.
Wait, how did you not think of that?
That was a great, that was a great, like funny joke that you just did.
Max, you would have been so proud of you, you know, before he died in the war.
I was just going for the lie part of it.
I don't know.
Listen, I don't see, I don't see color.
Unlike whoopie gold, unlike whoopie Goldberg, I don't dehumanize the Jews
by calling them white.
All right.
Elias are eight that out.
You always heard of that out.
My God.
Definitely.
If it was for Madrakas, I would have fucking bleeped that whole thing.
You would, you would just cut it.
You would have just straight up cut it.
When are we going to make the Garfield episode?
Oh yeah, you want to do another Garfield episode?
I mean, we did one already.
No, we did one.
It was just a comic jam.
Yeah, we need, we need a Garfield episode.
That's just Garfield.
How about Garfield boob?
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait.
Arlene's a pretty, is a sexy, sexy cat.
Oh, fuck that cat.
I'd fuck that, I'd fuck that cat for a dollar.
Oh my God.
You just reminded me.
Have you seen this meme?
It's awful.
It's so bad, huh?
I have to pull this up.
Apparently it's from 2017, but I never heard of it to now.
It's a brick and roll.
Creative, it's like normal people versus creative people.
Oh, the dragon, the dragon cooking the turkey.
The dragon.
Oh no.
Yeah, yeah.
What?
Wait.
For creative people, it's like a dragon lives in their oven, cooking their fucking turkey.
Wait, what?
It's the person who said that.
It's the most boring individual I can imagine.
Bore on, yeah.
Creativity is Western fantasy and nothing else, yeah.
Yeah.
Like, I'm not like other girls, but just slightly different.
I'm not like,
I'm not like other girls.
When I play tennis, I think it's a sword instead of a racket.
I watched Lord of the Rings.
That's it.
Yeah.
Are they Lord of the Rings?
Which one?
I'm not like other girls.
I have dissociative identity disorder.
I am a danger to myself and others.
I'm not.
I'm not like other girls.
I'm a boy.
Hold on, I found it.
Let me get these images up.
Wait, is it like that thing from The Little Prince
where grown people see a hat and a little kid see an elephant with a rope?
I mean, it looks like the elephant is underneath the hat.
You say an elephant with a rope and all I can think of is an elephant committing suicide.
Why would you put that inventory into my head?
Ordinary people, creative people, yes.
So apparently creative means you also have like bad eyesight, I guess.
This one, I saw, the original one is, you know, four different things.
It's not all dragons.
Creative people just can't do anything without thinking there's a dragon present.
Guys, this burning is crutch for the dragon.
I'm looking up the sky, but wouldn't it be great?
I was being fucking burned alive.
It's just the same drug.
This also was, oh god, there's one not included in that image.
That's like a fucking, when I saw this, I thought this was a parody.
Because I, well, first glance, I thought the the conclusion would be creative people just
want to fuck the cat, but it wasn't.
No, it was disappointing.
Ordinary people, because not that.
I don't like the dog, but really, what do we need him for?
This is okay.
I took matters into my own hands.
Oh my god, this is so awful.
I'm looking, okay, the original, the original one is so, it's almost as bad.
It's almost as bad as this like joke version.
So ordinary people see a purring cat, creative people imagine the cat is talking like it was in
like a cheesy DreamWorks film.
God of some kind.
This way, look at this one.
Look at this one.
Okay, ordinary people, water bear flower, creative people imagine like, what if my
flower was like a little bit bigger?
What if it was ever so slightly bigger than it actually is?
That flower was from Undertale.
Yeah.
Creative people wear a slightly like fit flowier dress and they dye their hair and they have
glasses and some and several necklaces.
Ordinary people just wear gray and they don't wear any necklaces at all.
If you look closely, you can see, you can see that the way they're pouring their water is more
like there's more force coming out.
So creative people care more about watering the plants.
Creative people care more about over watering their plants and then getting upset when their
plants are dead.
Just like the mom of the guy who created the mental like, unlock the power of the mind guy
in Mindkiller.
His mom was like crazy lady and she was like, don't overwater the plants.
There's all her fault.
The nurse is over watering the plants.
I'm going to lose my fucking mind.
That's what happened.
That's what happened in the movie.
In the movie I saw.
Dude, this is the guy we went and he was like, oh, you know, you know what I'm fucking talking about.
Oblivion is a great name.
The skeleton appears.
It's not even, it's not even creative people.
It's just like, what if it's instead of an ordinary day?
The skeleton appeared.
The skeleton.
I like how it's not a skeleton, it's a de-skeleton.
The one.
I'm going to steal that and use that elsewhere.
Thank you.
The skeleton appears as a, it's been going around.
I just ate a whole pint of Nick's Swedish chocolate ice cream and none of you even knew.
None of you even knew that I was eating while I was talking to you.
You fucking morons.
Okay.
In post.
Nimrods.
No, in post.
I'll just add like, sounds.
Look, Elias, I'll get some food.
I'll start eating and then you just take my audio of me eating and put it when Then was eating.
No, it'll be too sexual if you do that.
Elias R, put at the beginning of this episode, when I say the thing about the documentary,
the documentary, I have it open.
I went through, I watched Radcom the documentary.
I made a note of all of the slurs that need to come out.
There's about one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
There's about 10, there's 10 of them.
I'm going to edit those out.
Those are going to be, we're going to, we're going to commentate it.
We're going to put the, that's going to be Patreon.
Patreon bonus.
Patreon paying for slurs.
Paying for, yeah, well, yeah.
Well, basically, yeah.
Most people pay people not to be racist, but people pay you to be more racist.
I was a little bit, I was, you know, I was a little bit hopeful.
Okay, I'll admit, I'll admit to this.
I was a little bit hopeful that Jeff would say a slur and I would have to edit that out,
but he doesn't, because I know that that would bug him.
I know that that would bug him, but he did not on, not on camera anyway.
He didn't say any slurs on camera in the, in the documentary.
So good for him.
I may, no, I said the R word.
I said the R word one time in the documentary.
I'm not going to cut that.
I'm not going to cut that out, but I'll bleep it.
I'll bleep the R word if you, if they haven't said it a few times.
What's the R word on the PCP?
Like, you know, you know, retarded, the, the, the, the retarded word.
Oh, I thought you meant like something like rapist or.
No, no, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving raping.
I'll preserve the integrity of God.
Bricks in, atelisms out, kids.
That's right.
That's correct.
Just so you know, the title of this episode will be Nate Returns.
Yes.
Whatever you want.
Listen, I don't care.
I'm hungover.
It's, it's, it's over for me.
I've decided to never drink water again.
Why?
I've decided this is, this is the end.
You know, this hangover is good, actually.
This hangover is good.
I'm just going to lean into it.
I'm just going to lean into it and just go hard.
And this is it.
This is where it ends.
Just going to, just going to drive right off this cliff that I'm on.
So this is, this is the PCP, right?
So this is the, this is right.
This is episode 300 of the Procrastinators podcast.
Does that mean it's okay for me to talk about the new Pokemon game?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, no.
Well, I haven't played it, but I mean,
I suppose there's whatever.
It looks good.
It looks fun.
And I like the look of it.
I have not, I don't have any opinion.
Okay.
It's fun.
It's a different kind of game.
Some people might not be partial to it, which is fair enough.
I don't believe you.
But I had, that's why it looks good to me.
Yeah.
I had fun sneaking around in the grass,
trying not to get killed by giant Pokemon.
I caught a massive Lopini.
She's twice my size.
It's great.
That's pretty cool.
Can you have sex with the Lopini?
Exactly, dude.
This is, this is set like back in the day when people and Pokemon were equals,
you know, when they were seen of as equals.
And you're the newfangled person going around putting these things into balls.
Is it, okay.
Isn't there a line in one of the games where they say that like people
and Pokemon used to marry each other?
So something basically equivalent to that.
Yeah.
And this is the, and this game is set in those times in the olden days.
Yes.
And you get a massive Gardevoir.
I got a Gardevoir and she's the same size as me.
And I'm looking around for a massive Gardevoir.
Can you make your Gardevoir fuck your Lopini?
Oh, that's a great idea.
I don't even want, I don't even want sex with the Pokemon.
I just want to make them do it and watch.
The bonus points if they don't want to do it, but I make them anyway.
You can toss your Pokemon out.
Yeah, you need a pretty high gym bench level.
Yeah, you need to have beaten all the gyms or else they won't fuck.
But if you get enough gym badges, you can make over the canteen.
I know, because it's like.
If you have enough gym badges, Pokemon have to consent to sex them.
You're on their trainer.
You are their owner and they are your possessions.
You say when they have sex or not, I think so.
I think because this is a back in the day, you're like a little adventurer.
You're like making the Pokedex.
And it's a little book because of course it fucking is.
Of course it is.
I just read the last creative one and got to the part where you have to use your pee.
Yes.
I didn't read it before.
And it throws to the little flower.
You have to water me.
You have to use your pee.
Ow, ow, ow.
OK, the rib cage.
That's a lot of people too.
They are massive Loponies and massive Garth was.
Yeah, it's fun.
It's a fun game.
It is a Pokemon game.
Some people might not be satisfied.
But you know, I'm depressed, so I have no standards.
I used to when I was playing fun, comfort game where I roll around in the town.
Yes.
High five.
Pokemon challenges said that like the new the new like battle style is cool,
but there's only like five of them in the whole game.
Five what?
Of like a new some like new style of battle.
Oh, yes.
That's for like specifically like battles or something.
Yes.
There are like the noble the noble Pokemon or whatever.
Basically, they've they've they've taken some ice and they're trying.
God gave them some ice and now they're trying to kill everybody.
God gave them ice like like jewels.
Like the like the drug then.
Ice like they're high.
OK, OK.
Like like God zaps them with electricity and made them go crazy.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Ice ice baby.
Like like the like the government body.
Yes.
Like vanilla ice.
Like ice cubes.
Yeah, ice tea.
Anyway, God fucked them up.
God fucked them all up and now they're going crazy.
And you're the kid that got isekai to this land and everyone's like,
hey, kid, you're not scared of Pokemon.
I saw you walk up to a cricket to your super powers that you don't know
that you should be afraid of the power is that you are from the future
and therefore are unafraid of Pokemon because you can be babies.
But in this world, they will kill you and do try to.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah, it sounds.
Should I?
Well, I don't have a switch, so I don't even have the means to play it.
I wouldn't I wouldn't get a switch just to play it.
If I had a switch, maybe I would buy it just to fuck around.
I don't know.
Yeah, babe has a switch and he bought this game for himself
and therefore also bought it for me.
Who did?
Babe, my partner.
That's what I call my partner.
Renown character, babe.
Yeah, everyone's favorite character, babe.
Yeah, babe, pig in the city, as I was going to say.
Yes.
Don't tell them my secret.
I call them.
When you when you.
Yes, I read that out.
I read that out.
I want people to think I'm white like Shane Dawson or something.
Time to go.
Time to go get a girlfriend just so I can start calling her pig in the city.
We know what it means.
You know, the only reason I want to get married so that I can say,
hey, that's my wife you're talking about.
Yeah, so I can punch people and say.
And say, what are you doing to my wife?
But she's not even there.
She's not even anywhere, anywhere nearby.
Allison, why don't you just marry Lane and then you also get citizenship in America?
Or she gets citizenship where you are.
Having a wife is reason to punch people.
It's reason to punch someone, I think.
I don't know why it's also a reason to punch people.
Yeah.
Punishing people is good, actually.
There's never not a reason.
You know, I've done the math.
To commit assault.
So I've done the math and I've edited a hundred and twenty two episodes of the PCP.
My God.
You're insane.
I was a young innocent 17 year old child and now I'm 20 years old.
A hundred.
Wait, a hundred and twenty two.
But that's yeah, it's a lot.
But that's but that's so too many.
It can't be.
It's not even it hasn't even been that many episodes.
Ben, don't panic on don't panic on me.
No time to panic attack right now.
Ben, I'm trying to gaslight you so it doesn't have to pay you.
You're full.
There hasn't been that many episodes.
No, no, you only ate 20.
That's right.
I don't think we I don't think I agreed.
I don't think we agreed to pay you for a hundred and twenty two episodes.
And yet here we are.
This is this Chris Chan and soup.
Is this the first one you did?
No, that is the first one.
Damn.
Well, I I didn't think.
I didn't think you didn't.
I didn't think you'd be doing it for that long.
But I guess time.
A hundred and twenty one is our I did edit one of those since then.
Remember.
Oh, that's right.
That is right.
So Ben was right.
You haven't done that many.
Ah, you know, you know, how the funny story of how, like,
for the eight or contest, I think, like, I tie with first place with.
I don't remember who.
But you just won because you were just so much powerful than us.
We pick.
Yeah, we.
Yeah.
We had a couple.
There were there were there were a few that we liked.
I can't remember you talking about that green, fleshy flowers was a name that was
bandied about.
Yeah.
That guy is an art guy.
That guy.
I'm assuming that they do the sketchy people podcast.
Yeah.
When I look at those videos, I see all the little TVs and I'm like, oh, yeah,
that's similar to what they did for the PCP, isn't it?
Yeah.
He has another he has another handle that he uses.
He's got like two and green, fleshy flowers is one of them.
I forget what the other one is.
But that guy's good.
The guy's good at art.
I don't know.
Back at that time, when you won, I have I have sworn revenge.
I will as I will fly to America and kill oblivion fall for taking this opportunity from me.
Somebody's got to do it.
Somebody look at us and we're best friends.
It's true.
Oblivion.
Oh, yes.
Hello.
Sorry.
You got distracted for like a second.
This is this is like the worst hangover I've ever had.
This is so bad.
I can't even believe it.
I didn't even drink anything that bad.
I just drank beer.
It was just beer.
And on the 300 episode of the podcast, Ben,
I like Chuck vodka and I don't have hangovers as bad as this.
I'm not old.
I'll never be old.
You keep telling yourself that, sweetie.
You keep telling yourself that I'm just going to do a Carl Pilkington.
And when I get old enough, I'll just start aging in reverse and become a baby again.
Oh, yeah.
You wish.
Ben says, I will never get old also.
300 episodes of the PCP.
Oh, no, no.
It's true.
I'm not old.
I'm just dehydrated.
I just need some water to fill my cells.
You need water from the fountain of youth.
Yeah, I love that part of the Caribbean movie.
I love Jesse's review of that movie.
I don't remember that.
I haven't seen Pirates of the Caribbean 5, but Jesse did like an hour long review.
We're halfway through it.
He just breaks down and starts screaming, my doubter.
And it was funny and I liked it.
I remember my doubter.
My doubter.
It's good stuff.
People who don't watch Jesse Conn and are missing out looking at you, Simsie.
Do you think to just send Simsie piss style on repeat?
P-style.
Piss style.
I was thinking of Piss Christ.
I should just do that, yeah.
Wait, Piss Christ?
Yeah.
You know about Piss Christ, right?
No, what's Piss Christ?
Wait.
How do you not know about Piss Christ?
I don't know.
Elisa, you need to read the Bible.
Yeah, I'll send you.
There's a picture of Piss Christ.
People get really offended about Piss Christ.
What do you think Piss Christ is, Oblivion?
I think Piss Christ is Jesus.
Okay, it's like a reverse urinal.
You walk into the bathroom and instead of a urinal that you pee into,
there's like a sculpture of Jesus on the cross and he pisses on you.
Okay, what do you think?
What do you think Piss Christ is, Elisa?
Jesus Christ drank holy water and he holy pissed on everyone.
Okay, cool.
Here's Piss Christ.
Here he is.
He's entering General Chat.
It's Jesus Christ on the cross and a giant piss that someone took a photo of.
Why a piss jar?
That's like, that's baby shit.
Come jars of the real effort.
Because it's us.
This looks like a great album cover for a heavier record.
Because also because it was made in 1987.
It was made in 1987 by Andre Serrano.
Oh, so it's old.
Is that the title of the album?
Yeah, it's old.
It's old and French, so it's old.
Really? I thought this was like made a couple years ago.
It's American, actually.
Okay.
Hmm, hmm, yeah.
All right.
I'm going to go back to sleep.
End of the episode.
Are we done?
No.
You're going to go back to sleep.
You all get Ben.
Ben, do you remember what time it is for me?
Mr. Ben St. You're going to go back to sleep?
You said it's like 1 a.m.
Is it time to get vaccinated?
I already did.
I've had all my jabs.
I'm a good boy.
Is it time?
I haven't, should I still haven't got my booster?
Is there even any point anymore?
Is there even a point to getting boosted?
Is there a point to anything?
Any of this?
After 300 episodes,
should I even bother getting the booster
or should I just let COVID take me?
Just let it take me, just sweep me off into the...
You've already had COVID, Ben.
Trump won't do anything.
Look at me, my maid.
Yeah.
Yes, I know.
I'm so proud of you, Ken.
Look at it.
That's good.
Also made a fucking template as well.
I made the flower turn its frown.
Smile upside down as well.
You're a genius, Ken.
But it still has the heart.
It still loves it.
That's great.
Creative people.
Creative people have...
They dye their hair.
Just like you.
That's true.
Just like me.
That's how we know that you're creative.
I'm not creative anymore
because my hair is normal now.
What the fuck?
You just have to re-dye it, Ben.
The branding, the branding, Ben.
The pink is gone.
The pink...
No, they have no more brand.
My hair is normal color,
and I don't vape anymore.
And what...
Who are you?
Normal color.
What's the point?
Are you even doing keto?
I have been.
But the strip doesn't turn purple.
I think you just fucked up your body, Ben.
I have been eating so clean.
I have been eating so strict.
I've had a very strict low calorie regimen.
And yet...
And yet the keto strip does not turn purple.
I don't know if it's because...
It must be the water.
The water can't be keto.
Oh, I have stuff to drink in water.
I can only drink alcohol from now on.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe you're pregnant.
I wish.
That was said almost like sincere.
It was too sincere.
Too sincere.
Yeah.
You could have a keto bun in the oven.
I just...
I don't understand.
I don't understand why I'm not in keto mode.
I've been very...
I've been very scrupulous about it.
And yet...
Listen, Ben.
It just doesn't happen.
Your keto in our hearts, okay?
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, that'll...
Means nothing.
Yeah, that'll keep me at it.
That'll keep my body weight optimal.
Yeah, sure.
Just jump into your death.
I think I have lost some weight, though.
I've been...
I'm not in keto, but I've been eating very...
I've been eating at low calorie.
And I think I have lost a little bit.
I think I look pretty good.
I looked in the mirror the other day and I was like,
fuck yeah.
So you know what?
It's fine.
It's good.
Lamal.
Yeah.
All right.
I have a small topic.
It's sort of like a two-part topic.
Let it to what I've been working on the last couple of days.
So does anyone remember a video by a guy called Noodle
talking about AI interpolation for animation?
Yeah, I've seen that.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe.
I don't know if I actually watched it.
I would like to destroy the purpose.
Yeah.
Every time you see a video, it's like anime fight scenes in 60 FPS.
Track down the people who made those videos
and kill, oh wait.
I can't actually.
And kill them?
I can't kill them.
I want to say that, but I'm not allowed to.
Because of how YouTube-
Why do you chose this?
Look, in Minecraft, okay?
Just destroy the ship.
Blow up the house in Minecraft.
Exactly, exactly.
You hear that, Susan Wojcicki?
It makes me so mad.
It makes me so mad that people,
one, don't understand that 24 frames per second
cannot be converted to 60 frames per second
without fucking up literally everything.
Even if you have a line moving at a set speed,
it'll get fucked up because going from 24 FPS to 60 FPS,
some of them will have to be split into two frames
and some of them will have to be split into three frames
and it'll just make all the motion look jumbly and bad.
And also the AI does a shit job anyway
because it doesn't know what the fuck it's doing
because it was trained on live-action footage and not cartoons.
It's all just terrible.
But.
It is.
But, but.
That doesn't stop me.
You see, I am a smart boy.
I am using AI interpolation for my own animations
to double the frame rate.
And it does kind of a crappy job.
I'll show like a little example.
I'll drop a little mini MP4 in chat
because I've been manually cleaning up all the frames
that got fucked up, right?
And that's just what I've been doing for the past couple of days,
just painting out all the mistakes that the AI made.
But it has actually saved me a lot of time.
And I'm not applying the AI to the end product for 60 FPS.
I'm actually just using it for basic in-betweens at 30 FPS.
And I'm doing the cleanup before all the effects
and all the camera shake and all the gradients and bloom
and all that shit goes on top.
So it's actually working out pretty well
and I've pretty much finished all this work.
And that's what I've been working on.
I like how the cleanup video is just a close-up of the kuchi.
Yeah.
Not that big.
Can I post this?
Can I like show this on the video?
Just put a demonetization symbol over the poos
and you'll be fine.
Okay.
Or I do remember seeing this noodle video.
Those are the things with like video
Dragon Ball Z, but a thousand frames per second.
I never click on them because I know they're stupid.
And this noodle thing was like,
yeah, animation fundamentals don't work
because AI doesn't know whether something is supposed
to be bouncy or not, or what is the meaning
of the movement in the scene.
You can't say that.
It cannot best go in between two different frames
and if it understands what a human face is and what an arm is,
it can be like, okay, this is the arm here.
This is the arm here.
So we need to make a frame in between that meshes them.
But like for intent, it's hard or impossible for an AI
to like know what the hell of like an action scene is trying
to do, especially with a cartoon.
We needed some AI to act.
People love it though.
People really enjoy looking at those videos.
It's like-
Because we're stupid.
Not like go out and make their brain feel good.
It's like, do you remember AT Audio?
It's just like music that pans all over your head.
It's like that.
It's just like gaming.
You know when like a 3D has like
tastefully decided to run at a lower frame rate
for like effect or-
Like spider-verse and stuff, yeah.
And you know, there's always going to be that
sect of people who look at it and they notice that is not as
smooth as other three-dimensional imagery they've seen before,
such as a 60fps game.
They will think of it as bad animation.
Yeah, I saw that.
Even though they're like, they're basing it on like stupid things,
it is the response they have.
I don't know really what the solution to that is.
Um, the solution is you need to-
Kill them.
Like it's a legitimate response.
Like people feel-
It's because they've played too many video games that they think,
oh, oh, it's dropping frame rate.
Oh, I'm bad.
And that's the response they like have been like led to expect.
They, I bet they don't even realize that like every fucking like 2D animated
movie ever made is animated on twos and frees for the most part,
using ones like sparingly.
Sure, sure.
Like every Disney movie, everything.
And no one thought that looked bad.
No one ever thought there was a problem with it.
Um.
I think there's more to just like people being stupid.
I think, like, because people don't complain about those Disney movies
because it's not even noticeable that it's at a lower frame rate.
For some people, for, I don't know.
I don't know how to describe it.
I just feel like there's more going on than people thinking about video game frame rates.
Yeah.
Sometimes things do look-
Maybe it's just like, okay.
Maybe it's like-
Not in a bad way, but like in an artistic way that they're just not ready to accept.
I don't know.
Like maybe they, like they see the low frame rate, they notice it,
but they don't know what to say about it.
So they like interpret it as like something to criticize.
Yeah, so-
Even though it doesn't look bad.
Like nobody thinks that like Spider-Verse looks bad because-
Oh, there are people who think it looks bad.
I've seen people who can-
Do they actually, or do they think that they ought to think it looks bad?
Because-
Like there are some people who said that like, because it's actually a mixed frame rate.
Like Spider-Verse is animated at 24 FPS.
I'll say at least half the movie is animated on ones.
And things are only animated on twos in a way that looks good,
like in a way would for 2D animation.
The thing about 2D animation is like in-betweening everything on ones,
which basically means that every single frame is a new drawing,
doesn't always look better.
Using twos and frees sparingly can actually improve the look of the animation
and help it feel more like organic and good and stuff.
I know.
Oh, no.
I know that.
You know.
And especially for like limited animation as well.
And using those techniques for 3D is like really cool.
And Spider-Verse did it extremely well.
Like the animators, people seem to think that like,
oh, they were being lazy.
They were just cutting corners and saving on costs.
That is like provably false because even on frames
where the characters are standing like still for like two frames,
the lighting still moves.
Like if there's a lighting effect but it's moving on ones,
like you'll see the light update on their model even though the model is like still.
This is like that old DigiBro video about Kill-a-Kill.
And this is like the Kill-a-Kill, you know, the parts where like a limited thing,
a thing doesn't move.
But it's like, yeah, Kill-a-Kill did like super like limited,
like they use like tweens and stuff in a way,
like for comedic effect that looked really good.
Yeah, they use it for comedy.
Like it's obviously, they're obviously doing it on purpose,
like because it, yeah, for effect.
I think that's the main thing is when it's used for effect
and the effect doesn't distract from the content
of the scene or whatever is trying to be shown.
If like you're watching something and the main thing you get out of it
is that the frame rate is like notable,
then the animation hasn't really done a good job at like making you not think about that
and instead pay attention to like the thing that's happening.
I mean, if you're watching a scene and all you feel about it is
the like something about the frame rate seems weird to you,
then like I guess the artists has failed, right,
in making the scene effective in the way they wanted to.
There's definitely a lot of like misunderstandings and like pseudo,
like what's the term for someone who thinks they know what they're talking about but they don't?
Pseudo-intellectual?
I don't know if it starts with pseudo, but like, yeah, basically it's like people
thinking that they have
like a misunderstanding of terms, they just use terms that aren't
correct in analyzing the thing they're looking at because they had an emotional reaction to it
that was negative. Yeah, I see a lot of that going around as well.
I've seen that with, I've seen a lot of bad animation takes in general and like when you
read the responses, people just, it's clear that they just really don't know much about animation
at all. I have a good example actually. I mean, you can't expect the layperson to know about
techniques, right? You can't expect them to know like the technical,
you can't expect the audience to know like the technical aspects of it.
All they should be expected to know is like how it impacts them, right?
Okay, so here's an example of one thing recently where someone's like,
I, because you know, High Guardian Spice, it's that show that everyone hates even though
I know it's just kind of mediocre, but you know how every time like something is like
not great, people have to freak the fuck out and call it, say it's a travesty and a disaster and
all this bullshit. Well, High Guardian Spice had all this other
reasons for that. People hate it for reasons that have little to do with like the quality of the
show itself. They just hated it in concept and in pop culture. It was because of,
it was because, not even for the thing itself, it was because it was like the fact that it was
crunchy roll and the fact that it called itself an anime despite looking obviously western and
the way that it marketed itself as like diverse, right? Like the thing about, they sold it on like
Oh yeah, I mean, the trailer had absolutely nothing to do with the show and everything.
It's categorically not an anime. It's made by a fucking western studio.
Right. Yeah, but that's the sort of thing I'm getting at is like the reasons people would go
and like talk about these things and try to dissect it on a technical level when they don't
know about the technicals. They're going into it trying to destroy it because of all these other
things that they're actually the things they care about. And so the thing I posted is someone's
being like, oh, look, I remade a scene and doesn't it look so much better? And it is just
worse. Like the animation is worse in every object by every objective measure. Yeah,
they just made the art style more anime-esque. Yeah, they've made the art style more anime,
but the movements are way worse. There's like, I've left a huge comment, like a huge breakdown,
like pointing out every single way in which it failed to be as well animated as the original.
You know what? There's one thing specific. I mean, I always hate bloom, but the bloom in the
remade version of this little scene here is a thing in anime that I've never liked ever.
And they turned it up to like fucking 12. Yeah. Why did they make the ground look white?
Digital anime always has bloom to make it look like it's actually real.
Yeah, I don't get it. This scene that they re-animate, it's literally like six frames.
I feel like you spent longer writing this comment than you spent drawing it.
He did. I mean, I spent two hours on writing that comment to be fair. I should never be allowed
to write anything because I'm so picky with my words. I like to think that the creators just
reply with, okay. That's what you would do, Eleazar. Well, apparently the creator thanked
people for like constructive feedback and I made sure my comment was constructive.
I like how I click on this video and the first comment I see is from a month ago.
The original VA is definitely not helping, but the animation is way better than the original
props to you. The animation is not better than the original. It is worse animated.
It is objectively worse. They complicated the image to the point where they had difficulty
animating it. It's so short, it's barely even animated. Yeah. Yeah, it manages to be worse
than the original, which is a pretty low bar because the original is nothing special.
Yeah. Hold on. The motion, the drawings are not consistent. Her ear like moves all over the place
like. Her hand is tiny, tiny little baby hand. Yeah, the hand is badly drawn. The hat changes
size. Her face like facial proportions change. Every frame it's moving. The easing on her arms
is nonsensical. I feel like this person just thinks that like the fact that they drew it more
anatomical is just like categorically better. Yeah. The fact that they made it less cartoony,
I guess. I don't know. Yeah, it's like the problem is that it looks like a Western art style and
that's why it's bad. It's like, no, the art style for high guardian spice is fine. It's not even bad,
in my opinion. It's just like kind of like. It's a cute cartoon. You might not like it,
but this is what peak performance looks like. I saw similar things when people are like,
what if Gravity Falls was an anime and then they draw like a scene that it's not even,
the style doesn't even look like anime. It's just some like kind of chippy deviant art version of
anime and all the comments are, wow, you're better than an entire studio, even though like the production
is like mostly just gradients and bloom filters and shit. It's easy to animate a single shot.
It's easy for like, yeah, one person can do that. Imagine doing like an entire season of a show.
It's almost like animation studios give shots to individual people and that's how a shock gets
done. Makes you think. And then these YouTubers come along and do like a version that from a
technical animation perspective is nowhere near as impressive or like clean or well done and uses
a whole bunch of shortcuts and filters and people just eat it up because they see a gradient or
they see an anime eye and they go, wow, and they clap like a seal. Yeah. Media literacy. Makes me
mad. This reminds me of on, on Saturday after in the pro and on server after watching Dog Day
Afternoon, we watched Raging Ball with my good friend SackDev. Like in the afternoon, I was
hanging out with a friend and I said, oh yeah, I watched Raging Ball. It's a, it's a movie that
despite being from the 80s, it's in black and white. My friend was like, ugh, I could never
watch a movie in black and white. So I'm like, you're awful. You're awful, Murray.
This is why we need to break into Zack's home. I'll remove his skeleton eyes and replace him
with skeleton eyes from the 80s. I can only see in black and white. That'll show him.
What is this, this ordinary creator, this, this, all right. So ordinary person is like,
hates their boss, but is too weak and shy to do anything about it. The creative person imagines
them as a witch and likes them. She's just gay. She's just gay. She's just gay. She's gay for her
evil boss. She's gay for her evil witch boss. She's insolent. Ordinary person hates being,
being chastised and abused by their, by their boss. Creative people get off on it a little bit.
It's true, it's true. What if my, what if my, what if my sexy boss were a green witch who hated me
just as much? He didn't drink coffee, but instead swept the floor. She's imagining that the boss
is going to sweep the floor for her. See, Tull, I just, just to say, I really like the, you know,
need, but I need to make him creative. She's just going to be really confused when the boss
like starts taking a swig from the broom. I like, I like the creative, creative people live in a world
where everything is reimagined as being part of intellectual properties that exist already.
Creative, creative people populate their, their, their, their inner fantasy worlds with the, the,
the inner life of a creative person is basically like Ready Player One, where it's just like, you
know, the Iron Giant and Wicked and, and Pokemon, Pokemon. The person, the person who made these
images definitely is a big Ready Player One fan. Yeah, yeah, definitely. Creative people are just
delusional. Delightfully devilish. Delightfully devilish. Delightfully devilish.
Yeah, yeah. Creative people imagine that their, their thing is on fire, but delightfully devilish
people actually have it on fire and it burns their, their roast and ruins it. Delight, to, to,
to ordinary, ordinary people see that the house is on fire. Creative people say it's just, it's
the Northern Lights at this time of year in this part of the country, located entirely inside your
kitchen. Ordinary people think they're hamburgers. Creative people steam hams.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna throw up. I'm gonna throw up.
Like tell the steamed ham story on the PCP. Ordinary people throw up, Ben.
What? Yeah, Ben. I wish I was an ordinary person. Creative people drink tap water.
Oh, ruined. Ben's ruined.
Creative people drink, drink beer and never drink tap water. They'll never, they'll never
hydrate themselves. Ben, you know, being straight edge is more creative than, than consuming
substances nowadays. This lady, this lady with the, with the pink hair, is it pink? It's like
gray pink. This lady with the gray pink hair is, is, is straight edge. She is, she's straight edge.
Oblivion, she's high on creativity. Oblivion, what is that, steamed ham story?
Yeah. The steamed ham story. What is it? I know I told the story somewhere. I don't remember if it
was the draw cast or the PCP, but um, I don't remember hearing it. Oh God. All right. So I have
an interesting history with fucking English classes. With steamed ham. Throughout my entire life,
throughout my whole fucking life. The first, the first example when I was at this fucking
microscopic tiny school for Amoeba that had like four students after me and my sister joined.
It was the tiniest school you could ever imagine.
It wasn't a Christian school. That's my, that's my question.
It was a Christian school and it was in Mozgiel by Dunedin in the south of New Zealand.
If anyone lives in Mozgiel by Dunedin. If anyone lives in Mozgiel watching the PCP,
that's crazy because it's a fucking microscopic town with like no one in it.
Um, if one person there watches the PCP, they all do.
Well, we got a creative writing assignment and I had recently watched that episode of The Simpsons
with steamed hams and I thought it was so funny. You did tell the story. You did tell the story.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Didn't you just write, you just wrote it as your essay? You just wrote it as my
assignment and submitted it and I got failed. Yeah. And I didn't know what Aurora Borealis was
and I just made up the spelling in my head. No wonder you got it. So you called this your essay
when it was clearly steamed hams. Despite the fact there's obviously steamed hams.
That's funny. Well, there is a part two to this because later in high school I did some similar
bullshit in terms of just, except this time it succeeded. This time I worked out my favor.
So me, a little boy in high school with autism, we had to do speeches. We had to write a speech
and deliver speech and I was kind of nervous because public speaking, that's like scary. That's
like even scarier than just talking to a regular person. What the fuck? So my plan was just to
write this stupidest like speech imaginable and I was currently like obsessed with DarkDemon.org,
the Pivot Animation website and me and my friend had a bunch of inside jokes and so I just took
those jokes and I turned them into a story and I wrote a story about how there was a guy called
Damon who's just a guy from this animation website who created a time machine to go back in time
to create a bunch of free legged creatures that are like indestructible and wiped out
the dinosaurs and they're also immortal and they worshiped him because they consist of
free legs joined together and that's their entire anatomical structure.
This sounds like something out of pastel defender heliotrope.
Maybe. And they worshiped Damon. They thought he was a god because he has four limbs. Imagine
four limbs and they're religious symbol for him. In the land of the three legged, the four legged is
king, I guess. Yeah. And so their symbol for him was a swastika and that's where it came from
because four and these creatures live forever and they made all the decisions throughout history
and they created World War II and Hitler was actually one of these free legged creatures
after all and they covered it up and I told all this bullshit that I was just making up when I
was 15 and I delivered the speech and I got the highest marks in the entire class only because
I was enthusiastic and actually projected my voice instead of fucking mumbling.
Didn't even listen to what you were saying. Did they just edit in like Hitler's other arm
into all of his old pictures? Yeah, exactly. They had to turn one of the legs into a head
because these creatures don't have heads either. It's just like free legs connected and there's
no torso. Yeah, he's just three legs. He's just three legs in a trench coat.
Very strange. I'll be right back. I gotta go to the bathroom. I'll be back in a second.
Who did the rule on? Elias are other puking sounds and fart sounds and toilet sounds.
Fart with reverb specifically Elias are. Fart and fart with reverb. Puk with reverb.
Puk with reverb. That'd be like a cool archaeological find. Is the fart without reverb?
No. Without reverb. The original. This is like with a brush taking the dust out. Oh my god.
Is this just a fart? Is this fart without reverb? That's insane. I don't believe it. I don't believe
that's possible. I had to scroll so far down on that video to see your comment oblivion.
Did you even find it? Yeah, I found it. I was like, for a second I was like, wait, did they,
I kind of have this many comments. It's not a big video. Did they delete it? And then I found
it. I'm like, oh, they didn't delete it. Okay, that's nice. Yeah, I took the screenshot like
just earlier when I clicked on the video because it shows up for me, obviously,
because it's my comment. Yeah. So, for February. Yes. Yeah. Go check out Big Girl Squish on Twitter.
Dude, I like that one. We should definitely. I forget if it was Gun Girl or it was probably
Gun Girl. Just looking at the boobs. Gun Girl. That was a good one. That makes me feel inspired.
I'm like, I need to draw big again, but like even more like, like the boobs have to be like
disgustingly sexy. I gotta do it. It was really just like, I had drawn like a few images. I don't
know why, but I've always had trouble actually committing to drawing like, oh, this is like
sexually attractive woman. Obviously, like, I can do it sometimes, but it's like difficult,
or I try to mask it with like, oh, it's comedy. There's a joke. I'm not actually serious. Haha.
It's a, there can't be serious feelings here. It's just a comedy. That was your first mistake.
And so I'm like, I'm trying, I'm trying to like, to get over that because like, I know I have the
power. I have the power to draw good stuff that's like actually good. You know, and I spent a long
time on that drawing. You know, hiding behind irony and sarcasm and cynicism didn't help anyone,
especially Dr. House. But he had a whole TV show. He got a TV show deal. Oh, shit.
But yeah, that's, it like started as like, haha, wouldn't it be funny if, and then I'm,
I'm getting more like serious about like improving my drawings with each drawing.
Maybe too serious. Why so serious? It's just big boobies. It's, it's, it should be fun.
You want to know who I got these boobs?
Do you want to take estrogen every day?
Oh, it's an animation I made around the time I gave that speech.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Hey, look at that little stick guy.
The little, yeah, it was, so it was like a meme to take a regular stick man,
delete his arms in his head and treat the torso as just a third leg and just animate them fighting.
Oh, I was going to say, I found this one.
One of them had four legs. It would be Nazis.
Yes, I love this image. It's so good.
I'm big. It's so, so big. Six foot nine, nine foot 11.
Oh, I see. She is not actually that tall, but the amount.
Felly is spooky for him that I haven't drawn yet is like nine foot 11 because of course it is.
Oh, big is only nine foot tall.
Damn.
Only, I say.
Yeah, only. What a shame.
She could be even bigger.
Make it bigger.
A regular Gib, regular Gib has Felly as a tits resting on her head in spirit.
Probably.
Huh? Regular Gib?
Gibbob.
What do you mean resting on?
Because you're not, you're not, you're not super tall.
Oh, no. Yeah. Oh, I get it. Yes.
Yes.
Notice, we've got to do the attack on Titan size comparison video,
but it's all like the big booby OCs from Twitter artists.
That would be kind of interesting.
That the thing with like huge women is that when you draw them in a white void,
you can't tell. There's no like, there's nothing to compare them to.
So like, if you really want to show off the size, it has to be in relation to something
either that a normal person will know what it is, like the average size smartphone.
If it's like smaller than their thumb, it's like, wow, that's a huge woman.
Or, or like, you know, trees or buildings or other people.
And the laziest is just to say, oh, this is how many, this is how high they are in a number.
But it works sometimes when there's like two people there.
But like, Fali is quite tall in this image and big is even taller,
but the average person is so much smaller.
Exactly.
I need, I need to, I need to draw one with them.
Oblivion, you need to remake show of the Colossals, but with Fali and all
fucking the giant woman you drew.
Funny, I could, but that would take a million years.
I've, in general, I've just been thinking of, of like improving it out.
And, and like, I was getting a little frustrated because I feel like when I try harder than
like not at all, if I, if I don't try at all, it's like a sketch.
It's like a very simple thing.
I don't go over it a second time and it's fine.
Maybe it's funny.
If I try a bit harder and I try to like, okay, let's do a sketch layer and then like
clear, clean it up with some line art, maybe color it, shade it.
If I try harder, it looks worse.
It's less interesting.
People don't care about it as much.
I don't care about it as much.
And yet I spent longer on it.
And then to do like a really good image.
I, it's not like spending large amounts of time is actually like necessarily
going to make it better, but it's more likely.
It's just, sometimes it sucks.
Sometimes it sucks when you work hard and then nobody cares about something you did.
I've been feeling, feeling a little bad about that recently.
I want these images, I want Febubri to be a success.
I want to make stuff that people are actually like pogging about.
I'm pogging.
Like for most of my favorite, like NSFW art is just like sketches or like uncolored things
that like they made in like a day, you know.
If you make these really gestural, like especially with porn, if you can get like the feel,
the visual feel of the squishy bits, right?
That's all people need.
Yeah.
And for that, you just have to learn the shortcuts for like,
like in your mind, you just have to like get it, get a knack for like,
which, what are the essential lines?
Like I can construct like a nicely shaped boob with just like free lines and it looks great.
And like figuring that out is what like gave me like confidence to like keep going.
And then I figured out, you know, fies and figured out other things.
And a lot of it, a lot of it helped.
A lot of the like progress I made came from just being on the draw cast
because I drew women all the time.
And because I have to be fast, like eventually, like I figured out,
oh, I can do a five, like using just two lines like this.
And then like, if I want to like add a more detail, I can, but I don't usually need to because
it's, you know, just a couple lines can be enough to convey like the shape well enough, you know.
This is how plan is still give. This is how plan is still give. This is how plan is still give.
Yes. We will still give.
It's time to back onto the draw cast more often.
I mean, I'd come on. I just, you're always doing something with other people.
Oh, shit. We'll just invite you more because we love having you.
Yeah, you're fine and cool.
Thanks.
All right. Look at this one. This one was the second day or third day.
Yeah, this one.
I was like, I tried really hard and I feel like I did a pretty good job.
But like, I don't know, people didn't really care about it.
And I don't, I think it was just sort of demoralizing because I spent so long
trying to get that looking right. And I look at it now and I'm like, yeah, so it's fine.
But there's just sort of like something about it that feels like,
not that it sucks. I'm not trying to say like, oh, woe is me. My art sucks. It's bad. It's just sort of,
I'm in an art moment. I'm having an art moment these past few days.
A creative people moment.
I don't know how to be good at what I'm doing. I'm just going to draw every day and
That's just how, that's just how you do.
I mean, the ultimate trick of porn that I have seen is don't try to have them or not.
Is this podcast still going?
I know, right?
Yes, Ben.
It's been 300 episodes.
300 episodes.
It's been 300 episodes. Give it, give it a rest already, guys.
Go drink some tap water, Ben, Jesus.
Is it a coincidence that you got the worst hangover on the 300 episodes of the PCP?
Yes.
He did on purpose.
I'm drinking Hannaford sparkling water beverage tropical punch flavor.
It's the best one.
It's got pineapple, kiwi, mango, raspberry.
No, I was drinking raspberry before, but I finished that.
Now I'm drinking tropical punch and tropical punch is yellow.
It's not.
I'll tropical punch you.
Don't do that, Gip. That's what he wants.
Violent. That's, I'll sue you.
Ben's a creative person. He likes it when people do that.
Ordinary people just get punched, you know, the bones broken.
Creative people.
I love being beaten.
I'll take them to court for this.
This is going to make me a rich man.
Mm. And also I have pink hair and wear hipster glasses.
Nice boob drawing.
Yeah.
I'm sick.
Thanks.
You're sick.
Fuck.
I like this situation.
I've been, I don't know.
These boobs look great.
These are great boobs.
Yeah.
Okay.
Gip, back to my tips on porn art that I see that people like.
Don't try too hard on the line art, because no one cares about that.
That's true.
Make the skin shiny.
True.
Because everyone loves that.
That's just true in general.
Yeah.
I was looking at Clip Studio Paint.
I don't think any of the brushes are brushes I like using except the marker,
which is like a, doesn't taper.
And it's just sort of like a, a fixed size and it's very thin.
Could you make a custom brush that's like got the same texture as the marker,
but also has like the kind of taper that you like?
I, uh, I was looking around.
Like maybe we'll just need to look at a tutorial.
Oh, you can just edit.
You can just edit the brush size.
If you, next to the brush size is a little like, like button.
And if you click on it, you can.
I pressed around with some of the buttons.
They didn't seem to like actually do anything.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Also.
I saw that Ben.
Also the important thing.
Did someone post this already?
Oh, I don't know if it was posted in this chat.
This one, this one's a winner.
This one's a real winner.
Oh my God.
People do love to be racist.
I just, I just saw the Godzilla dunking
the basketball.
That does remind me of something to bring up.
I love that image so much.
Yeah.
Well, I'm just posting.
Yeah, man.
How big is that fucking basketball?
Oh yeah, Godzilla.
Yeah, that's, that's too big.
Godzilla got busy.
Um, I don't know.
Godzilla's a little bit is even darker
than the man in that image.
That's why he's so good at basketball.
Ben's words, not mine.
Keener.
Disavow.
I mean, he's got night, he's wearing nikes.
As we know, creative people love to be racist.
It's true.
You're, as those two images together,
the, the pro, the procrastinators podcast,
300 episodes of creative people being racist.
Loving it.
Here's the 300 more.
Yeah.
Speaking of racism towards.
Oh no.
That group of people.
You're so slur, I can't remember.
No, I've been, I've been workshopping it.
Have you guys been hearing about
the Canadian trucker protests?
That's stupid.
Yeah.
I have heard a few things about it now.
It's like super co-opted by alt-right fascist type.
I heard the Simpsons predicted it,
but I also heard that the Simpsons didn't predict it.
Simpsons successfully predict and don't predict everything
because they've just done everything.
So what is it?
Because I don't know what's going on.
All right.
So, you know, vaccine, I, I, I, I don't know.
Vaccine's bad.
Trucker's not real.
That's why Ben hasn't gotten this.
Trucker's driving back and forth across the Canadian
and a U.S. border or other places,
wanting them to be vaccinated
because they drive around a lot
and they could potentially spread things.
Uh, clearly, uh, dumb.
Oh, why would you want them to be vaccinated?
So they're just blocking a bunch of like major roads,
blurring the horns day and night.
No one can sleep in those areas.
Um, I got, I got messaged by a Canadian
who like lives near of a protest
and is like being annoyed by it.
And then, yeah, it was co-opted by right-wing people.
There's been people spotted with, uh, like Nazi flags,
harassing people in homeless shelters,
taking food from homeless shelters and shit.
These truckers like, what the fuck?
Why?
Um, and just generally being terrible and inusense
and the police are just kind of letting
shit slide.
They don't give a fuck.
Um, which sucks.
They really need the mongrel mob down there
to straighten things out just like they did in New Zealand.
Hell yeah.
But you know what?
There is one group of people
who are rising up against the truckers.
I got contacted by one of them
who sent me this little video
that I'm putting in chat.
Oh my God, Garfield.
Garfield?
Um, look, look at that video I just dropped.
Yeah.
Um, that's a counter-protester.
Welcome to ComeZone.
Yo.
Yeah.
Wait.
Hello.
Is that on the news?
All right.
So what you're watching is not the news.
It's some kind of like pro-trucker,
like a live stream event.
Right.
Um, apparently there's a bunch of us going around
and they're letting people call in to give their support
and then a whole bunch of people are calling in
and just playing welcome to the ComeZone on full blast
to fuck them over.
That's hilarious.
And it's great.
I support them.
Like you have my official blessing.
Fuck these truckers.
They suck.
That's pretty lit.
These truckers are fuckers.
These are mothered.
Actually, they don't have moms.
They got nothing.
They should, uh, what did I see?
I saw, I saw, uh, Don.
It's not one Twitter account.
I saw Don something said like,
we need to, we need to confiscate these truckers' trucks
and like donate the proceeds to vaccine research.
So that we can, so that finally the vaccines
will have less side effects.
And then everyone will be happy.
I don't know.
Get those trucks, crush them into tiny little cubes
and, and, and put that into vaccines.
Squish it into, like, ring it out and take all the vaccines.
If they didn't want, and then when you get injected,
you'll become Optimus Prime.
If they didn't want people to protest.
If you get injected, you'll become a trucker.
If they didn't want people to protest the vaccines,
they shouldn't have put 5G in them.
Well, I'm sorry.
I don't know what they were expecting.
Oh, a friend that believes in all of that.
They shouldn't have, they shouldn't have.
Age people.
That is, that is what age people look like.
I mean, they're right.
It's true.
It's just a fact.
I love those gifts so much.
It's great.
These people.
Are they from, are they from like a Dr. Seuss
interactive video game?
These are from, I don't know, there's a little clip art.
They're from something.
See, this is, they're probably from some, like, software.
It's like, it's just like a reader rabbit bullshit.
This is like a really good example of the frame rate being good.
Yeah.
More frames would not improve this at all.
Sator the Barricade, son.
Quick, someone take, someone take those little gifts and make them,
uh, I'm having frames per second.
Yeah, yeah, interpolate, AI interpolation.
Disgusting.
I like that little tappy feet.
I love this.
Like shifting around their weight.
Well, let me see if I can do it.
The more it, there's actually like more frames than you would think on this,
this P, like his foot, his foot goes through like a dozen different positions.
I know, right?
Damn.
They put more effort into it than they probably need.
P for effort.
Yeah.
That's a P for effort.
And it's still like five frames a second pathetic.
I can't, I can't get off to this.
I need it to be smooth.
That's me.
G-I-B-E.
Every time I'm on rule 34 and I see like,
Oh, this thing's an animation and I click on it and then I see that it's like interpolated
and these just just disgusting, like blurry, like smeared frames,
like every other second, I just want to vomit.
Yeah.
How dare they.
I knew people were going to do that to my animations eventually too.
That's why I'm going to do it for them.
I just want to vomit, but instead I come.
I can do it right.
That's very flippin' cool.
It is.
Yeah, that is for you.
The animation smearing like high frame rate stuff is like,
it's like a, it's like a way to like fuck with the video in the same way that like,
what is it called when like a video file holds on a frame while it seems to be moving in the
background?
No, you're like a P frame that's called data mashing.
Data mashing.
You could use that as like a data mashing-esque fuckery thing to make something deliberately
look weird.
Okay, I saw, I saw a tweet fairly recently that was about like, it was, it was like,
you know, it was like soyjack versus Chad, but the soyjack was all like warped and looked shitty
and it was like, don't use like 3D model, don't like trace 3D models for your drawings.
And the other one was like, a well-constructed anatomical drawing of a head and it was like,
uses 3D models for their drawing.
And it really annoyed me.
Did you, did you see this?
I think I've seen that.
I don't think I've seen it.
Can you find it?
Yeah, uh, yeah.
It's, it's just sort of like, don't, don't, uh, trace 3D models and the one on the right.
It's like tracing a 3D model with the yes face things like I did anyway.
The implication is like, if you don't use, if you don't trace a 3D model and your drawing
will just be bad and you can't, you can't draw without it.
I think the implication more in a, in a, in a meme format like that is that, um,
you say that these are the rules, but I'm breaking them and it's fine.
I'm okay with it.
It's not that it's bad to not use 3D models, but that it's fine to use 3D models.
Yeah, like there's probably like people who will like, oh, using 3D models is cheating
and it's like, it's just a fucking tool like anything else.
Go for it.
Yeah, I'm, I'm fine with that.
Like I don't mind, I don't begrudge anyone their, their method or whatever.
But I do think that like, I don't know.
I think it was annoyed by the tone to be like, I've, I've, okay.
Intended or not.
Ben, Ben saw the meme and he's like, this is about me.
I feel like the implication is like, your drawings are worse for not doing this.
And I was like, no, it's not.
Ben, you are the big artist, not retweeting little artists.
Why would you be proud?
Why, why would you be proud that you can't draw without using a 3D, without tracing a 3D reference?
And then I, okay, I, I, then I went and I saw this person's art and like,
they, their, their art is like, they do like headshots.
They do like close up headshots of, of characters and like, you know, all they do,
they use like a big anime head shape, just, just the basic head, no features or anything,
just the shape of the head and the neck and the shoulders.
And it's like, why not simply learn how to draw a circle?
Like that's it.
Like it's just a circle with a chin.
Like there's, they, they barely even, they, I don't even see what they need the model for.
It was a, it was so, these are, these are experts, experts.
I mean, it's, it's, it's, I mean, they're, they're fine.
Like their, their stuff is good and fine and, and, and, and all right.
I just, I don't even see, I don't even see the point.
Let me see the point of, uh, I'm trying, I'm scrolling through their feed right now,
trying to find like, I'm assuming that it just helps remove guesswork early on,
so they can get into the groove faster.
Here, here.
That's probably like the main purpose.
Their, their work definitely has like a bit of a, like, you can tell quite clearly that
they're using a very similar skull for all these heads.
Yeah. Here, here, watch it.
Watch this video.
It shows them starting from the model and it's like, all you would need to do is just
learn how to draw that shi, that head shape, right?
And if you knew how to draw that shape, you wouldn't even, you wouldn't even need the model anymore.
Honestly, I agree.
Like I feel like the model is really like not even necessary for this.
I really, I really, yeah.
I don't even think it's, like, the purpose of a model is like to help with like a complex pose
or if it's like a lot of foreshortening and like, you know, like a wide angle lens sort of thing.
A complex pose, like, like, like a, a, I don't know, a baseball guy, like in mid-throw,
it's like, well, what, what does that pose look like?
Use a, use a reference, trace a reference to get the pose right.
Because it's complicated.
This is not, this is not complicated.
You know?
It's always good.
So it seems like, like, not the time to use it.
Like, I feel like that's like, this is like the easy stuff.
They're getting a bit of same face going on.
Yeah.
Because of it, I feel like.
Maybe about two.
A bit.
The, the, the, the inaccuracy of human beings is what all art is based on.
If it could be made by computers perfectly accurately,
then what the hell is the point of us doing it?
Yeah.
Like, like the, no, that this is exactly that, but that's just sort of the feeling.
Like these look fine, I guess.
I just, I just, they look good.
I just didn't like the, I didn't like the, the like, well, I can do this because I,
I can do this because I use a 3D model.
It's like, you can do what?
You can, you can do what exactly?
Leave me alone.
Stop bullying me.
Stop bullying me for not being like.
Ben, you know, full well, they're just mad at,
like they're just responding to like certain like annoying people
and their comments or some shit.
Yeah.
And making fun of them, not you.
I know it's, it's, yeah, it's about, it's about something.
It's about some context that I'm like not privy to.
You're right.
Someone says like, oh, that's not real art.
That's not real art if you use a model.
Yeah.
And they're right.
There are people like that.
Oh, so that it is about you.
If you use a computer, if you use a computer, it's not a drawing.
There's this channel.
In my opinion.
There's this channel on, um, it's from.
Ben admits that he's not an artist.
Finally.
It's from Spain.
And he's like, he only like criticizes artists and says like,
oh yeah, Bob Ross is not a real artist because he just knows how to paint landscapes.
I don't know how to do portrait.
He's like, fuck you.
Fuck off.
When has Bob Ross ever drawn like a huge milky kid?
What did I see?
You know what?
I saw some, I saw some video of a guy, some crypto shell being like,
yo, NFT is the future.
And then he has like a little interview with another guy.
And the other guy is like, finally, you know, like, finally, you know,
creators are now empowered.
Creators will finally start creating digital artwork.
Yeah.
And then he qualified it with like, and then he qualified it with like,
I mean, I mean, like, you know, like master artists, like, like real, like real artists.
I guess the implication is like, sure, like shitty, like shitty artists use,
would make digital artists.
But now, now that NFTs are a thing, real artists will make digital artwork.
And this is, and this is going to be a game changer.
The Epes will just steal the Mona Lisa and sell it online.
There's a weird sect of like, tech enthusiastic people who are,
I could only imagine, like, learned about the, the email was a thing like last year.
Like they're so stupid.
They're so out of the loop on everything.
They're like fine, they're like fine.
People who like see the metaverse and like, whoa, you can be online?
Like, yeah.
Yeah.
Like these people have never watched serial experiments lane,
which warned us about the metaverse.
And you don't see me to understand.
Understand.
I think it's like, it's like finance people that are like,
account that are like career accountants.
You like, these people are big nerds.
You would think they'd be online, but they're not that kind of nerd.
They're like some weirdos.
They have, they have the real picture on their LinkedIn of the photograph of a,
like a professional photography and they smiling.
Not anymore.
And now they got an eight.
Then they're like, now they've got an eight because it's the future.
Because it's worth it.
We don't need to look like human beings.
Because it's worth.
We can have digital computers.
Computers can make art.
I thought they were just used to like, look at the stocks numbers really fast.
Okay.
So I just Google Garfield NFTs and I made an amazing discovery.
It's like, oh God.
Is it Garfield Eats?
No, no, no, no.
There's these like cards.
They're just different kinds of Garfield.
Why is it so small?
Why, why so small?
Who's, who's, is this like an actual NFT thing?
I don't know.
It just found it on Google.
That is pretty funny.
Some, somebody's, somebody's, somebody's been inspired.
Bonefield.
It's funny unless it's real.
This is better than every other fucking NFT collection I've ever seen, TBH.
If it is an NFT, it might not even be an NFT.
It might not just be someone making like horror Garfields.
I would have to assume someone just stole someone else's art and put like a border around it.
I mean, it's all the same stuff.
If this, if this is what NFTs are like, then I guess I'll,
maybe I should jump in.
Maybe I should.
Okay.
These are from a post on Reddit from r slash.
I'm sorry, John.
Oh God.
And the title is Garfield Cards.
Please no NFT talk in the comments.
I'm really tired of hearing it.
Sorry, guys.
No wonder the art's good.
It's not an NFT.
That's funny.
Oh, did you guys know that like the eight,
I'm pretty sure the eight person was a commissioned artist.
He wasn't told what the art was for.
And so.
Really?
Yeah, but I think I heard that.
I'm not sure.
I saw a picture of her.
Yeah.
She's like a sexy lady.
How dare she?
How dare she be sexy at all?
It's a problem for me that she looks the way she does.
I don't like it.
I agree.
I guess what you're talking about.
The NFT lady, the one who's supposed to be the monkeys.
Oh.
The apes.
Yeah, she's just a person.
She's a pretty lady.
Yeah.
But I just, that's the thing I heard.
I'm not sure if that's true, but it's true.
No, she's ugly on the inside because of the NFTs.
I don't think, okay, but I guess she, I mean, I don't know.
Did she not know what the apes were going to be used for?
She was just someone that someone hired?
Yes, from what I heard, from what I heard, she was commissioned to draw the NFTs
without being told.
But they're, okay, okay, but they're, but they're not drawn, right?
They're like assembled from, you know, the template.
Yeah, they're randomized.
I mean, she had, she drew the assets, obviously.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I guess, I guess it makes sense.
I mean, before they, before they blew up, like how would you even know?
Even if someone told you what they were, you'd be like, okay.
Oh yeah, no, she didn't.
Did she see like any of the fucking millions of dollars?
This was back in the beginning when NFTs were first.
So I found, I looked up, I literally just looked up NFT lady, monkey lady.
And it's like, NFT lady, monkey lady.
I feel, I feel extremely sure that they, she does not see any like profit sharing from the
Yeah.
She created the artwork after connecting with a creative, creative agent,
Doug Nicole Munds, who came across her portfolio.
And they basically, like, this is like, they, they had to like draw these assets.
They just, they just wanted an ape that's like kind of jaded inside of life,
but has all the money and time in the world and hangs out in a mental bar, in a metal bar,
apparently, that was their instructions.
And hangs out in a metal bar?
Yeah.
She was the lead artist behind the original collection.
Whereas other artists took care of the ape traits and environments,
put a whimsical settings, the base structure and the character ape was all her thing.
She expressed sadness that despite the popularity of the multimillion dollar ape,
not many people know that she's made them.
And yeah, she didn't even, she didn't even get, um,
Yeah.
She didn't even get credit.
I'm sad, but I'm not being harassed by all the people who rightfully hate NFTs.
No, no, no.
However, however, comma, she's dropped her debut NFT series under her own name.
I bet she was paid like a few, I bet she was paid like a few thousand dollars.
Yeah.
She's got her own NFT.
She's, she's not, she's not good.
She dropped her own NFT series.
Yeah.
Okay.
She deserves to miss out then.
Of course she does.
I mean, I think she deserves to miss out because I think people should be paid
for the labor that they, that you know, that they do.
However, comma, I think that she shouldn't, communism.
You know, you know, you know, Seatull, your principles, I agree with them.
Wait, people should get paid for their work.
What?
What have I been doing hating the PCB all these years?
It was where this is your exposure.
We're finally showing you.
This is it.
You've been building up credit for the, for, for two years now.
And now you're finally catching it in.
Yes.
Finally after 70 years.
A Stereos coconut liked my, liked my tweet.
Not, not even a good tweet.
Not even a, not even a funny tweet, not a popular tweet.
This tweet got like four likes.
Sorry.
Seven.
One of them was him.
It was, it was one of them was him.
It's just a reply.
It's just a reply to someone posting about the, uh, oh God, what's,
fuck, what's her name?
The, the lady, Mallory, Mallory Eudicious.
Oh, the, the lady who made the comic with shoplifting new guy.
I just, I just, I just made an angry reply to someone posted about the,
the, the, the shoplifting comic.
And I just made a reply.
It's being like, I hate, I hate people that are mad about this.
No, no joke.
No, nothing, nothing, but, but, but, uh, a Stereo saw it and was like, I agree.
I also hate these people.
Me and, me and, me and the, me and a Stereos were, we're like peas in a pot.
I gotta say, in all my years of hating PCP, the worst, the, the, the most hardest
to edit was the, the Wonderbird guy.
It was just so annoying.
Oh yeah.
He just sounds like an insane person.
He sucks so much.
He's so boring.
It just the entire time it sounded like he was just like on the verge of like
snapping and like screaming.
He just sounded like he was just like on edge, like an angry.
I didn't understand.
That guy is neither wonderful nor weird.
He had.
I don't know.
He had a way of speaking like he was always on the verge of getting to the point.
He's like he constantly sounds like he's about, he's about to get to the point
and say something important, but he never does.
It's not real.
The point doesn't exist.
Hey, we've been going for like a couple of hours.
Do you want to get a voice mask or anything?
What are you, what are you, what are you in a hurry or something?
I have, look, it's not like I vaguely, I vaguely remember Eleazar complaining every
single time these, these podcasts.
Eleazar has to put all of these Garfield images in the episode.
So much editing Eleazar.
Now we'll see.
So this is the 300 episode.
This is 300.
Yeah, do we have 300?
All right.
I have some, I have, I have another topic.
I said the AI thing was a two pronged topic.
Here's part two.
AI voice generation.
Someone called in the last PCP after I left because I listened to it.
They had a Nate AI voice.
They have a bunch of them.
They made a Dr. Wolf one.
They've done all the ponies.
I want to know who that person is because let me tell you, when I edited the PCP,
you know, I eventually went back and deleted all the files because they were taking up
literally like 150 gigabytes or like a terabyte on my computer or some shit.
Yeah.
But I kept all of Nate's audio that I had cleaned up because expressly for the purpose
of an AI, if you want 10 hours of crisp, clean, Nate audio and wave format that is completely
unfettered by like YouTube compression and there's no one else talking.
It's just Nate by himself.
I can give you like 10 hours worth of training data and you can make that AI sound really good.
Oh no.
I will give it to you and then we will really have Nate returns on the PCP title will be correct.
The perfect Nate.
I don't know if I have to ask you to like
We can build a new Nate.
The voices.
A better Nate.
Maybe a voicemail is where she fucks Nate.
You can build a new Nate.
This Nate will give spew communist propaganda.
I see you always manage to.
I bet a foster should know how to have a weird socialism.
Weird socialism.
I just think that I just think that communism is like weirdly utilitarian.
I don't know why he doesn't see it.
Oh, Nate had a Nate had a Oki on the on the last.
What's what's it called?
Gamer zone.
So I like I like I like Oki.
Me and Oki have talked on Twitter a little bit.
Oki's good.
I forget that Nate still makes content.
He just makes the gamer zone.
It's like content but with funny people who aren't tricksy.
This is this is not really a I can't it's not Nate's.
This isn't Nate's fault exactly.
But it's funny that like people on Kiwi Farms like love Nate.
Like Kiwi Farms people when they talk about the PCP.
There was one post recently that was really funny because it was like
just like he didn't even go into specifics.
He just was like, man, it's funny.
It's funny just how far all the PCP all the PCP have just fallen into complete
ruin and disrepair and disreputability.
And except Nate, except Nate, obviously, like Nate's Nate has
Nate has obviously been fine and and kept his his head out of the muck or whatever.
And I just don't know how you can how you can read that.
I don't know how that's your reading of the situation that he's like Nate hasn't
been putting out content really like regularly for like two years.
How can you have a sense going full since going full time is output is dropped.
Yeah, I mean, that's what Sean's constantly shitting on him,
which is why I don't understand why Michelle thought he was going to spicy salt her.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
Sorry, spicy salts Nate, not spicy salt her.
She was afraid that would be stolen by well to spicy salts.
Well, I mean, the the analog would be if you spicy salted Nate,
that would mean you tried to kidnap Michelle, right?
Oh, I thought if you spicy.
Okay, then you did just spicy salt.
Someone is to attempt to kidnap their wife.
Okay, but it would never show.
I was trying to spicy salt Michelle wouldn't he be trying to kid that.
Well, Trixie also didn't get married.
Never.
Nevertheless, she called.
She said she said she said wife.
Same as she said, like she bought a house when she merely rented it.
This comes this comes up occasionally.
Crack, crack occasionally complains that and he's right to do so that like,
Trixie would just use the wrong word.
She would just describe things wrong in a way that is basically lying,
but like in a way that you're like, I don't know if if she knows that she's wrong
or if she's just dumb and doesn't understand that these things are different.
Things like renting a house versus buying a house.
She said she bought bought a house when she rented one.
They're like, they're not the same.
And like, I genuinely don't know if she knows these two things are different.
Calling May her wife when she was a young saying, you know, that's not that's a little
less of a thing.
I guess, I guess.
Did you know, you know, this this is funny.
May messaged me the other day or a few weeks ago.
Oh my God.
She meant she meant.
Okay, I call I call me.
I openly call May a Nazi on Twitter.
Like I add her and I say like, fuck you, Nazi.
Die.
Right.
Like I say stuff like I say stuff like that to her and I mean it.
And I absolutely mean it.
And it's not a joke.
And then she but she sees me like post mean things about Trixie.
And then she messaged me to be like, Ben, I appreciate you so much.
Like, I like this made my day, Ben.
I love that I'm like, she doesn't have any standards.
Yeah, she doesn't have any like a true Nazi.
She doesn't have any standards.
She's not even like offended.
She just likes you.
She likes that you hate the person that she like that she doesn't like.
That's it.
It's true.
That's all there is to it.
It's exactly like that guy I was arguing with in the YouTube comments
of that one guy who claimed that Stone Toss was and smiling friends when he isn't.
Yeah, because most of the comments were rightfully complaining.
Like one that's not Stone Toss.
Also, he's a Nazi.
I don't think they'd put him in.
And there were like two or three people who were like, no, he's not a Nazi.
Why would you think that?
He's never done anything like that.
He said he said he said he's not one.
So he's not one.
Yeah, he said that he wasn't in Germany in like the 1940s and that all the Holocaust
and now stuff is true, which is actually how he responded.
He said, yeah, yeah, all the stuff I'm saying is true, actually.
Yeah, yeah, literally.
That's just defense.
He's like, I can't be a Nazi if the Holocaust actually didn't happen.
Like that's just fucking different.
And he's like, oh, and also like I like crypto.
You know what?
Nazis don't like crypto.
Yeah.
He's like, dude, you're just a Nazi and a crypto bro.
You're too bad things now.
Equally bad things.
Equally, equally bad.
Yeah.
But the person I was arguing with, like I went through the trouble again,
another huge YouTube comment where I like listed 20 of his comics with the dates and
explained exactly all of the Nazi messaging, all of the Holocaust denial.
How do you look at the one about like, you know, the one with like the the pie graph
with like the 2% of the Jewish population?
Yeah, yeah.
How do you look at that?
How do you explain that?
If it's not, if it's not not, it's just not.
The implication is that Jews aren't white people, which is a very common Nazi thing
because they they need an excuse to kill them or some shit.
Whoopie Goldberg needs to learn that.
Okay, look, I'm sorry I'm being so hard on Whoopie this week.
Yeah, I left this huge comment detailing every little thing all the times that he's like
shown scientists like proving that, you know, people of color are dumber and then like,
oh, but the cowardly leftists are too afraid to admit the real science that black people are dumb.
I know he's done that shit.
And I listed all these things and the guy like responded by like saying,
those things aren't even wrong.
Also, the Nazis aren't that bad.
Did you know the allies sided with communists?
Yeah.
So I'm like, okay.
So you just admitted he was a Nazi.
That's how it always boils down.
It always comes down to that.
If you get into the weeds, that's it always comes.
It always shakes out that way.
Can you give a comment for a key screenshot that and have Ellie say.
I have I have the video got fucking deleted.
The guy deleted his own video probably because of a comment section.
And also because they probably realized, yeah, it's not a stone toss difference.
So the video have screenshots.
So the video was about how stone toss is in smiling friends, even though he's not.
Okay.
So the video was called like like internet like references in smiling friends and it showed
a bunch of examples and it showed a picture of a grease puddle on the floor and said,
look, it's a reference to smiling friends is just one of many examples.
You mean it's not a reference.
It looks nothing like stone toss.
It's just, oh, let me see.
I could find a picture of the grease puddle.
Hold on.
Yeah.
And then it shows the screenshots of the comment so we can all see it.
Is a grease puddle a stone toss thing?
I don't even know.
It's not.
It has a face.
They think that they it has a face and they think that it's the cost of face.
It ascribes the the lip the over.
Oh, sure.
That this grease puddle had like it's sort of like it's sort of like a blur has that.
Yeah.
It's like because the Simpsons never existed.
Oh, yeah.
The Simpsons and Futurama and all that.
I mean, what what else could that be but a stone toss reference?
Clearly.
All right.
Oh, I have.
Oh, let me find the comment.
It's so funny that he just in the end just admitted that he is an Aussie and that's why
he's defending stone toss.
Here it is.
Let me copy that and show me, show me, show me.
There you go.
Show me, show me, show me.
That's like the end.
That's like the very end of the discussion.
Do that trick.
The one that makes me scream.
She said doesn't calling them.
Do you have a little screen?
Shut up.
You're all those things.
All those things are demonstrably true.
Just calling it Nazi propaganda doesn't mean that it's not true, dude.
Nazis aren't even all that bad.
Just not even.
Oh, my God.
I thought you were paraphrasing.
Nazis aren't even bad.
That's disgusting, he did it.
Good old Hazen.
Nazis aren't even bad lucks here in the comment section.
Good for him.
Living, sticking to his principles.
All I wanted to say about that was I said something.
It was a few weeks ago.
I just made a tricksy tweet and the day after I called her a Nazi may message DM me to be like,
Ben, I appreciate you.
Thank you so much for doing this.
And I said, thanks.
And then she told me, did you know, did you know tricksy used to cry,
used to literally like cry tears when I, when I would say like,
we need to take care of the taxes?
Like instead of, like instead of doing, doing her taxes,
tricksy would just cry.
And I was like, lol, that, that sounds about right.
That doesn't surprise me at all.
But thanks for confirming.
Thanks for confirming what I already assumed to be true.
Show me, show me, show me how you do that trick.
The one that makes you be Nazi.
Die, die.
All those things are demonstrably true.
Calling them Nazi doesn't make them any less real.
And it has to be stated, the things I listed were Holocaust denial,
the JQ, the great replacement, race, realism, anti-Semitism,
and right supremacist pseudo-science.
Even admits that the pseudo-science is true.
Calling them Nazi doesn't make those things not real though.
I love it.
It's so fucked.
I can't believe, I can't believe smiling friends, I don't even need the final word.
I can't believe smiling friends promotes Holocaust denial,
the JQ, the great replacement, race, realism, anti-Semitism
and white supremacist pseudo-science.
That's so fucked up.
Doesn't the smiling friends guy do NFTs?
He did some like very early on and then never mentioned NFTs again.
Oh, did he?
Okay.
No, it was just free of him, I think.
It was just like free little animated GIFs.
Well, all right, okay, nice.
Show's good though, I liked it.
I have, you know, I tried to watch it, I googled it,
trying to find some site that had it for free to watch
and I couldn't find it and I gave up.
You can watch my first two episodes for free on Adult Swim
and I can link you a little funny zip file with the rest of the episodes if you want.
It wanted me to like sign up for an account,
I didn't want to make an account on Adult Swim.
Wait, I didn't even have to make an account.
No?
Did you already have an account?
I wasn't even allowed on the site.
Because I was a child.
No, because I was swimming or maybe because I wasn't swimming.
I mean, I can just give you, like, I have a media fire link
that I uploaded myself with all the episodes except episode one,
which should be available for free somewhere.
Isn't that the pilot?
Yeah, the pilot.
I thought it was just, wasn't it even on the YouTube for free?
I don't remember.
They put it on YouTube, that's how...
I don't know why, I googled it and I didn't see any result,
I didn't immediately find results that showed me it and I was like,
ah, I'll just go watch Mind Killer instead.
I'll just go watch Mind Sweeper.
No regrets.
No, why Mind Sweeper when you can play Wordle?
Yeah.
Wordle's the new Mind Sweeper.
Because Wordle is only fun due to luck.
I found a...
Like it's easy to do.
It's easy to do, but like whether or not you have
a fun time is due to like the luck of your guesses versus what the word is.
Wordle basically solves itself.
Wordle, I think Wordle is designed to make you think you're smart when you're not.
You think you're solving a puzzle, but actually the letters are eliminating themselves.
I guess that's good puzzle design.
Good game design.
There's some smartness going on if you can think of the word with the information you have,
but not when it starts off, you have no information.
I use a Scrabble dictionary, so I don't think there's not even any skill involved.
I don't even have to know words.
Feels like cheating.
I don't even speak English.
Feels like cheating, but it's not.
I should play on a hard mode.
It should switch to hard mode.
Yeah, you got to switch to hard mode.
I mean, I pretty much already play on a hard mode already.
Playing on like when you can just do whatever on each thing.
You just do two words that have a bunch of like common letters in them.
You get too much information and it's like, oh, it's obviously this.
That's right.
Well, but I want to win though, but I don't want to lose.
You can't win.
The only way to win is to get extremely lucky on the first guess.
Are you winning, Ben?
Yeah, because it's some playing on easy mode.
I use the same starting word every single time, audio,
and eventually it'll be Ryan.
I use aches.
Wait, aches?
A-C-H-E-S.
I use a different word every time.
If I think of a funny word, I'll use a different one.
I wanted to start yesterday.
I wanted to start with the word think.
I wanted to start with the word think, and I'm like, no, I'll do audio first.
And then it only got me like one letter.
And I'm like, okay, well, that letter is in think.
So I'll just type think anyway.
And then think gave me way more results.
And then I got it the next try.
I could have gotten it in two if I just started with think.
Do you think of like the common ways that letters group up
to form parts of words like T-H and S-H?
Somebody.
And Q-U and like things.
I usually go for like there or not there, but like maybe there with an I-E-I-R.
Somebody somewhere has gotten it in one.
Yeah.
Munchie got in one.
What?
Whoa, really?
Munchie got in one really early on.
He was like, wait, really?
Now every everything will be like less satisfying for now.
Yeah, why?
Yeah, that's it.
You're done.
You beat wordle when you get it in one.
You don't have to play anymore.
You're free.
Then they show up at your house and give you a medal.
They give you a word.
And then that's when he quit the PZP.
He's like, you know, I already accomplished my life.
I don't need to be here.
Because he had a vision of him winning wordle.
Exactly.
And it like in years in the future.
Hayao Miyazaki comes to your house and gives you a congressional medal of honor
and gives you the purple heart.
I don't know why it's him.
What are the what's the mistake?
Does Ohio have five letters?
H-A-Y-A-O?
Hayao?
Because I must.
Ohio.
Do you see my you see my Simpsons?
You see my Simpsons comic?
The what?
Yeah, you retweeted it.
I retweeted some.
I think Cheesy Manfredo, I think like remembered it or someone someone like
remembered that I drew that Simpsons comic playing like three years ago
and like liked it and retweeted it and I was like hey that was pretty good.
I should it was the best thing I ever made and it's all been downhill from there.
Yeah, let me let me find it.
It's it's almost like it's okay remember when I used to make comics?
When I used to draw stuff.
Ben same predicted the Simpsons.
Oh my god, this is great.
I love this.
I think it's pretty funny.
It's probably the funniest thing I ever made.
Well, look, the image appeared.
He's drinking CC lemon.
I love CC lemon over there.
I've never had it.
I just know that it had like Simpsons branding.
I guess it's lemonade.
I don't know.
It's constructively criticizing lemons.
They could they could they could be better.
They could they could be doing a better job, frankly.
That's what the lemons say to you when you drink it.
Constructive criticism lemon.
I don't know.
Lol, Japan.
Japan sure is wacky.
Wow, it's so funny.
I love Japan period.
I do love Japan period.
I don't know.
You guys want to go?
You guys want to start?
I love Edo period.
voicemails or Japan?
Yeah, voicemails.
All right, voicemails.
We have two two fucking many of them.
Oh my god.
I can't wait.
Is it people saying 300 related things?
I don't know.
We didn't even say this is Sparta.
That was my big idea and I forgot.
Say it.
I know there is there is actually like not too late.
It's too late.
The moment is past.
Hold on.
You just reminded me.
Microtopics.
I have like 11 YouTube channels actually.
Yeah.
Wow.
And all of them,
almost all of them have like seen success at some point.
Randomly.
Oh, I need to find this one.
I don't.
I know.
I only I think I know three of them.
You have that.
Yeah, I have that.
There's a pony audio one.
Yeah, pony audio one.
Didn't you have one that was like a pony audio drama?
Yes, I did.
Yeah.
So.
So I know three of your channel.
Yeah.
So I.
All right.
So there's a blooming fall.
There's a blooming fall after dark,
which used to be called Demis Studios.
It was an old ship post channel that made like really bad videos
and promoted conspiracy theories as a joke.
My favorite.
And then I rebranded it when it got popular.
There's Nightfall Studios,
which also used to be called a blooming fall that has like 60k subscribers.
There's Nightfalls Radio,
which has the audio drama.
Yeah.
There's a blooming fall plays,
which is a gaming channel.
I had a video blog there as well.
Actually, let me mention that.
So yeah, the the Mrs.
Spartiffing reminded me of this video on one of a fucking random channel I made in like 2009.
Dragon Master Pivot.
Um, this video got 100,000 views randomly on that like 29.
29 subscribers.
Yeah.
I it's the only video.
Okay.
So back in like 2008,
I was like super obsessed with like 13 years ago.
Did YouTube even exist 13 years ago?
It usually has been around since 2005.
Oh, dear.
Um, it's been around for like 17 years.
Okay.
Yes.
Oh my god.
That's crazy.
Whatever.
But anyways, I made like a free side channels because I was like,
I want to create the Aragon series.
I want to animate the entire all the Aragon books in pivot animation.
I'm going to do it all by myself and I'm going to have a YouTube channel for each book.
Actually, no, that's unrelated.
But like, I'm like going to animate the Aragon books and I'm going to have,
I created a special YouTube channel for each.
Um, so there's, there's, there's like the Aragon book one, Aragon book two,
Aragon book three.
So I was free YouTube channels,
but I also want to pretend that I have fans who like love me and like simp for me.
So I'm going to create free extra channels for the free channels
and we're going to pretend that we're collabing,
but it's actually just me collabing with myself.
And that was Dragon Master Pivot.
Word of the Senior and a few others.
So I created six YouTube channels just for this project
and free of him would just fake people.
And this is one of the fake people and this
animation is an animation that this fake person they made up
created to enter one of my competitions,
to create an animation about that.
So this is you pretending to be someone else making a cartoon
to enter my contest that you made?
Yes.
And, and so that's like six YouTube channels
by itself.
And then I have like six other ones now.
But yeah, when you said this is Sparta, Sparta, I got reminded of that.
Do you ever see Double Cast, Minerva Double Cast?
The Misccribe video?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
No.
We had, we had.
Yeah, we had Double Cast.
What's your channel name?
Wall.
Hold on.
Duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, Duh, Double Cast with a five.
Is it just called Double Cast?
Eldina, Eldina Double Cast, the video about Misccribe.
It's this, it's this story about
a true story of this lady who like rose to become one
of the most powerful Harry Potter fanfic writers and community mods.
Of all time, basically by like creating basically her,
her tactic was to make fake accounts pretending to be like Christian like moral guardians
who were there to like defend Harry Potter fanfic from like sin and then as these people
she would make lists of like bad like like don't read these authors because they're sinful
and then she would put herself on these lists and then people would be like oh my god I
gotta go read this shit yeah she wanted to be part of the cool kids club with like the
cool Harry Potter fanfic yeah yeah yeah yeah she would make the list would have there and
all the people she wanted to be friends with who were like popular yeah it's like a time
I got you on like the bad list of American bad what the fuck hold on traders of America
yeah traders of America it's like that seat hole you got me you got me on the traders
of America lists and I'll forever be grateful right right next to like Billy Eilish and Bill
Nye the science guy I saw that list and I'm like Ben would love to be on that list I do
I do give I see you posting YouTube comments from this ancient video of mine I just saw
these yeah I just saw it too there are a bunch of just these comments this one person you
know this is toilet or whatever XD oh my god they have a sweeper hello Jeff I come on
yeah I love these comments cuz they're decade at least a decade old most of them and they're
just so quaint and simple like haha XD like oh wow the problem here is that you throwed
me in a giant hole XD look look at these people whoa whoa whoa whoa what the fuck and there's
an 11 years old comment in between sandwich between two 10 year old comments that's weird
I don't even know what the fuck they're talking about this is crazy people are laughing through
that's fucked but you got sorry I wish comments could be stupid and fun and like full of joy
again never again commenters commenters comment lol on this episode thank you please comment
lol please how about a voicemail okay so I play a bit of clone hero clone hero is like
guitar hero but it's free it's for the PC it's better it has a whole bunch of features that
original guitar hero games didn't it's really fun and you just download it and you make custom
songs and it's good is it called clone hero because it's a clone of guitar hero it is literally
just a clone like it uses some of the same code but a guy was caught cheating a guy called
shmui he was he was too good at the game and he was like posting accomplishments that were like
inhuman and it turned out that he was faking them and he got caught earlier this month and what I
did is the day I found out I posted a video of me doing one of his fake accomplishments but like
really fake is that you yeah that's me in the second video and my video surpassed the original
in views that he had faked as of yesterday are you faking this or is this real it's real
that second link I posted like give it a watch it's just a minute long this is real real live
there's nothing fake about it that is you I recognize you are you are you are swimming goggles
those are gamer goggles those are gamer goggles I don't I don't really know I don't really know
what to make of what I'm seeing here you play with your teeth
ordinary people Jimmy Hendrix created people this video
good good good video that's a great note to end on thank you everyone for the PCP 300 episode
goodbye PCP just realized my audio has been fucked this entire time I hope it's better now oh well
we got Craig we got Craig all right should we start voicemails okay let's let me just all
right let's not let's not dilly-dally too much here the first one is hold on the first one is
called message on crypto three two one go okay on that on that crypto chat from last step I think
majorly your points kind of stand but the thing is there is one major issue that I see with your
guys's view of it and that is that you think that crypto is a investment and my opinion it's not
to be I mean it's in the name it's cryptocurrency and not a crypto investment that's meant to be
used kind of like you use cash yeah that's what it's meant to be and it doesn't function that way
because people only use it as an investment because that's all it's a meal or something and you do
it through crypto and I think that's like a major thing that a lot of people don't really get no
no similar kind of deal like I get that that's what it's supposed to be mainly it doesn't the
problem is that it doesn't work as currency because it's so inefficient I have just meant to be used
like it costs me $80 to move $60 worth of tether out of my wallet you know it's worthless stuff
like that with the blockchain it's all public right there are cryptos that are better at doing
that this guy likes crypto for example tomorrow it's got this signature thing we're basically five
people sign the transaction and then it goes through so you can't really tell which of those
five people were actually quite surprised that someone just sent an unironic like so crypto
good actually one of five people send this transaction and you don't know who jeez when I
send a transaction through visa it's not fucking public record for anyone to look at isn't that great
like yeah only like the bank or visa card holder like usually sees that so I you're supposed to
like a currency but it's worse in every way than I have I have dabbled like having all your
transaction public is a good thing I don't understand I have I have dabbled in it yeah
that's true also I have I have dabbled in it enough and everything I have learned an experience
that way tells me like oh this is this sucks this is I would never I would never use this
this could never be like a thing that I would like use you know in the real world for anything
it's simply you know you know the only gas fees man it's insane imagine you gotta spend a hundred
fucking dollars every time you make any transaction at all unbelievable did you see like a year ago
like there there was like I saw this being posted around like a bunch of like twitter threads
of um people like just linking to child porn and being like send me like one dollar's worth of
bitcoin and you can access um people were just posting this shit publicly on twitter and I'm
like wow what how do you think the crypto market is so wonderful how do they how can they do that
and be free citizens I don't fucking know does that work like I like the thing is I it was like
it was like a year ago I saw just a bunch of posts people were sharing them like going look at this
shit it's fucked up and like yeah and like there were tweets like you could like look at the tweet
and it like wasn't deleted by twitter and it's like what the fuck how is this allowed um but
great question you know I saw like 10 or 20 of those and that's more of when I've seen genuine
products added like advertised using crypto so I guess they found the market crypto is for
illegal thing crypto is such a it's so reputable it's for illegal things you know when you want to
buy it's for illegal things that's like the only thing yeah that's what we're child for is illegal
things the the the reason NFTs are hot is because it's like oh finally there's something not illegal
we can buy yeah the the only um the the unwieldiness of of like of the transactions and like like
gas fees and stuff are just they're just they're just they're totally prohibitive they'll they'll
simply never it's an issue that can never be overcome and can never it's it's simply can't
be used for what it was sort of maybe meant to be used for as in money I don't know you know
there are also there are also communities like in America and around the world that are being
destroyed because the electricity price is locally skyrocketing because there's some fucking crypto
mine nearby right and that's using up so much energy but they have to jack up the price and then
regular people who are like poor can't fucking afford it um well you know they rise up those
people should have invested those people should have invested in crypto and then they wouldn't
be if they took personal responsibility they would have invested already yeah
the problem is the responsibility of seeing into the future to know when everything rises and falls
responsibility if you didn't want your art to be stolen after you died and minted into an NFT
you should have made it an NFT you should have minted idiot if you didn't want your art to be
stolen you should have just made it an NFT already and you shouldn't have died you should have lived
long enough to like that's an NFT bro thank you somebody I don't understand people who like
NFTs because I can't separate them from the concept of theft anymore it's not I'll be honest
I'll be honest I don't I saw I saw one person the only I saw one person who was like posting some
NFT shit and it's all it's all people that have financial stake this one person posted an article
that was like here how how I how I succeeded with my NFT project and it was like their their their
project was it was like you know it was one of these shitty like asset uh you know mix and mix
and match uh uh what's the word it was one of those dress up game icons yeah what's what's the word
for uh for like the the character creator pig pig crew yeah it's a pig crew avatar it was it was
it was it looked like shit it was ducks it was a little cartoon ducks and it was like I had a
successful NFT launch like here's how I did it everyone an article about it and I responded
with a single word trash and they they blocked me um I felt great I felt great I felt great
about him because he spoke the truth yeah um I loved it uh but I guess I'm thankful that like I
don't see I don't I feel I feel like the tide is turning I feel like public opinion has has
come down pretty heavily on like nobody likes this shit I mean it's all the bad things it's theft
it's does nothing for anyone everyone is only used to speculate uh it it's bad for the environment
and it's ugly there's nothing positive about it I I mean you know you're not you don't get the art
you just get a receipt that's it's you get a receipt for the URL as people can change and I
I mean the URL can die yeah I I just want people to change I want someone to hack into them
and change all the URLs to a link to um Rick Astley's never gonna give you up there's
to a rick roll there should rick roll plenty of there's been like loads and loads of examples of
people's NFTs being hacked and stolen because they're just yep they're not actually secure at all
they're not as secure as they they imagine it's much easier to not worry about owning a PNG
in that way because you just it's not valuable nobody cares about the only reason the only reason
they care about it is because of its uniqueness and that uniqueness does not actually exist because
it's so easily stealable even in NFTs you just remember I mean literally nobody can stop you
literally there's no value for anyone literally the point of it is to say I spent $200,000 on a
worthless PNG of an ape like it's that's that's the point of it uh no no the the apes must have value
the apes must have value so the value can keep going up so everyone succeeds the second you
start talking shit you're gonna make us all fail we have to all believe that this is good and right
and we're going to make money otherwise it will the point is not to say that you've spent $200,000
the point is to convince people that you actually did that so that they can spend money and then
you can like get like money from people being tricked it's just it's well yeah it's to say I
spent $200,000 on an ape and I don't regret it and number and line go up and also I made some new
apes that you can get and you can be like me if you buy my apes
or ducks or whatever. Can we make this episode on NFTs? Can we make this episode on the blockchain?
You know what I think probably I mean Saber Sharks YouTube channel is an NFT
someone minted it someone minted it without his permission yeah like just just the channel itself
that's awesome holy that's awful that's really bad good for him you know good for him I'm proud
in a way but it also means absolutely nothing it's really funny I wonder what the ramification
I wonder what the ramifications of uh of minting uh the uh the asterisk or suck series would be oh
my god Ben you should do it you should do it it's all fake don't encourage him oh my god yeah
what if I did Ben there's one way to find out because you know you know I'm referencing that
just Trixie said that she tweeted the what would the ramifications of minting the asterisk war
sucks series be I what if I just minted it yes it's a funny joke but please it's not funny if you
actually do it if you actually do it it becomes stupid I don't even know how I don't even know
how one well minting it would probably cost you more money than like you'd actually it would probably
it costs like a hundred bucks right to like mint artist overwhelmingly lose money on NFTs like
most of them will sell for like 15 bucks yeah like like the average sale is like 300 but that's
only because of like the few whales who spent like 60 million dollars yeah you know yeah but like if
you look at if you look at the mean sale it's like 15 if you're if you're a famous if you're famous
already if you have that social capital or whatever and you have a famous person who will buy it off
you and like you both like we can nudge and like you know that you're doing this just to inflate the
price so you can both benefit which is yeah how the shit actually works I am I am rapidly dying
shall we move on to the next yes yes that's fair yeah oh I just wanted to show this image that my
good friend Lane show me today so the stick the son of John Lennon posted this oh Sean Ono Lennon
haha this y'all better follow the inimitable sailor aka gigachat aka the rocket man aka bitcoin
i i saw this loser uh he was shilling some like skull NFTs uh just just pathetic just
I'll turn him in just for just for the record julian lennon is a thousand times per kid julia
lennon is that they're different julian the oldest john lennon okay i don't even know i kind of didn't
even know he had his is named after julian oh yeah it's about yeah well that's well this guy is like
hey jude don't worry that your mom is now yoko ono uh don't worry that your dad abandons you and
doesn't care he's doing caring if i was if i was sey on lennon i would be mad that hey jude wasn't
about me too so he's got it he's probably got some anger becoming a bitcoin a bitcoin uh freak
is he's acting out it is have you seen have you seen get back documentary i've watched the first
three or two episodes there are three episodes huh there are three episodes there are only three
i guess i haven't seen the third one yeah it's great it is very good okay okay next next voicemail
is called two-headed coin uh there it is three two one i know this reference i'm mad i'm always getting
gay porn ads just because i'm watching gay porn i don't like what they're implying
i thought it was going to be the neutral milk hotel yeah two-headed two-headed cock
well i would say you made your bed now you gotta fucking it that's my response well i would say
stop watching gay porn but that would be homophobic don't do watch more gay porn that's actually
the solution to all your problems yeah just lean into everyone just click just click the ads just
click the the ads and and what's what's the problem um all right here's here's another
here's an image the real reason why ben stopped trading bitcoin he bought dumb
this is nate that's nate right yeah why does he why does he look like that did they like
hit his face i don't know he looks like like you he's it's like he's your brother or something
he's like he's they like stretched his chin out yeah and they like and they like airbrushed his hair
they gave him like a widow's peak this is this is like so weird this is like from the
so no madden president skid thing here so no so no madden president that he looks stomps on
that shit is wrong that doesn't look very wrong it's very wrong dude he looks like he looks like
the fucking agents from the matrix movie he looks like he looks like the fucking the bad guy from
spy kids uh loop wait no who's a bad guy or not or like not not the guy but like his his minions
or whatever with like the weird like fucking putty face thumbs i don't know yeah the freaky god i
forgot i forgot that i had all that shit people i forgot about that i i repressed that holy fuck
yeah scary scary like it was scary shit uh we got we got another one we got another one here uh
what's this sweet jesus ben that's not so a you're eating honey not so i is also not keto
but as i've said i am mysteriously been unable to achieve ketosis recently despite despite my best
efforts uh you're not so you're not soy boy enough i'm not i'm i don't i don't eat soy i don't like
soy milk i mean i've had it once and it was okay i don't think the first image by itself is really
good oh soy milk is just kind of gross yes it is good you know what it's good you don't enjoy a good
soy product depending on his natural habitat yes just eating goo out of a pot make make the honey
green and it's and it's uh rfck basically make make the honey white and it's my life
hell yeah uh all right uh next voicemail here we go this is called what is this
this if we got cucked we would kill ourselves three two one go yeah yeah definitely i think we
could all agree that if we got cucked we would kill ourselves i would i would first i would first
go gay and then i i don't know this is from dead oh is this from it's from something pcp
something sounds like it could be like the first uh red con like live yeah with the audio yeah well
i would first go gay and then kill myself trixie says as gay and gay and dead gay and dead yeah
i mean gay and i i can't lie gay and dead is a fucking great name for an album i can't
sure it was it was uh all right uh next one is called uh what is this no no one ben fans
three two one go oh my god look it's ben saint let's take up on our clothes okay okay okay
yeah okay it's so true go ahead clothes are off i mean why would they do that though it's so cold
out it is pretty cold out they live in australia it's summer here oh that's right you live in
fucked up backwards land yeah it's white summer i am see tall i have your plebe in the weeb uh
copy here and i'm just i'm gonna i'm gonna have to wait until the united states is sending mail
yeah i know it's okay it might be i don't i have no idea how long it will be but i will hold on to
it one for as long as i have to visit my i want to visit my friend see tall but the borders are
closed is it do something about it see tall what do you want me to do it can be a terrorism
yeah open we got to open those borders somehow yeah summer here in argentina too right uh okay
next one is called what is this next one is janez three two one go hey ben since you're
so into speedrunning i found this guy's youtube channel called dark viper au he's a gta5 speedrunner
and he made so much fantastic content on youtube from showing the glitches he came across on his
various speedruns to making ramble videos about various different types of topics
that which tricks he could learn a thing or two fun i don't know what that means anyway i hope you
talk more about his content on future episodes of the pcp i think they will provide you
like something to enjoy on breaks when you're not working on your content was a dark
dark viper
hey you so it's chill it was i guess so dark that maybe it's good but like i like youtube channel
so i like doubt honestly uh if he does like commentated speedrun i like commentated speedruns
of like almost anything i'll watch any i don't even like this guy's videos before even though
i don't watch speedrun content i just know that name uh i like i like speedrun content i like
commentated stuff uh it's great uh so maybe i'll maybe i'll give it a give it a look uh if he
if he commentates stuff then maybe i'd watch it uh if not then i'll kill him uh oh this guy's this
guy's younger than me so i hate him i hate everyone younger than me that's the rule that's the rule
ben hates everyone at this podcast right now old man uh yeah so i hate a lot so i hate a lot of
people um why are you so old then i i asked myself that all the time have you come up with an answer
i think it's a punishment i think it's a divine punishment for what what thing did you do that
caused it do you think next voicemail is
next voicemail is an image here we go it is called scary communism here we go
my dad tried to escape communism yeah yeah it do it do be like that sometimes
uh go dear old dad um all right next one is
fucking too many windows too many fucking windows open please post thank you uh next one is called
newfound ben simp three two one go
okay thanks
he's the hero you deserve not the one you need that's right
right uh next one is called to a little bitch three two one go
what the fuck what is what is
is there just
okay cool thanks i can tell there's something in there
i can't i can't be bothered i'm not gonna think about it even another moment okay the next
the next one is called bourgeoisie three two one go
hey ben your last tweet saying you'll donate five hundred bucks to a charity of trixie's choice
if her patreon drops below 500 bucks it kind of seems like your leveraging capital against
your fellow proletariat bourgeoisie scum that's true you're right what what of it nothing you just
say you're bourgeoisie scum he's just congratulating me on a job well done of leveraging capital against
my fellow proletariat uh i'm not going to mention that it's episode 300 the voicemail
no no no they don't care they don't remember these things elia's are these are all recorded
before they realized that uh next one's you got an image here ben carrying the podcast
there i am happy 300th to digi bro's anime podcast there we go hey speaking of a death
hole wait just what i said just what i was asking yeah hell yeah there it is somebody somebody
remembers uh all right next one is called uh pov uh you are ben saint about to play
a voicemail there it is posted right now three two one go oh no another voicemail yep oh god
that's what it's like oh fuck shit god please help me not another voicemail no kill me please
oh lord oh my god fuck okay here we go three two one go that's right that's correct that's accurate
that's also me when i ate the both go ben you just counted down and you didn't put another one in
what the fuck why would you do that to me what did what did i do huh you just counted down you just
said three two one go and there was nothing there what the hell yeah there is oh now there is
ben why the fuck are you lying
what but i but i know and why are you trying to guess like us ben wake up from the coma
you're always gaslighting
wait no no i'm not i'm not gaslighting yes you are ben you're just so stupid you don't know
you're gaslighting you didn't say you lost your mind and wake up from the coma we all miss you
we all miss you so much anyways next question yeah okay i went into a coma six six years ago i
fell into a coma and i dreamed that i started a podcast called the procrastinators uh seven years
oh yeah you're probably right um okay whatever next one is called uh addendum three two one go
i will buy a copy of the plea and the weave if ben didn't say true i didn't i didn't say it
i didn't say it looks like you owe me looks like you owe me 30 buckaroos plus shipping and handling
uh plus shipping unless you're in australia in which case you well you still do you must
pay with your life if it's too expensive shipping and handling is just more expensive are you sure
you want to just ship it just ship it to me and i'll go in a boat to australia to visit don't do
that no don't do that whatever you do not in the boat not in the boat elisa could i just like send
it to like canada and then like canada would send it to australia for me can i just do something like
that kind of just not a person ben i can feel like the kind of true true oh no it cost me
self a sale um all right next voicemail is called me dusa with some numbers instead of letters
three two one go hi bill and give hello i'm not sure if you experienced this before no maybe this
is just mightism but have you ever experienced artistic jealousy no so to what extent did it go
never i draw a bit but i'm not that good so when i see artists that are way better than me
i immediately close the page with good art in it i recently stopped watching anime because they
so jealous of the skilled animators that i cannot really bring myself to watch anime that's funny
bye it's an awful way to me not on such a scale i know the feeling but i wouldn't like get mad at
like a a produced show made by many people yeah maybe if it was a it was a if it was a peer
here's where i do get a little little envious little mad is when somebody like improves faster
than i have i see them like oh they they they draw like this and then they get better and then they
overtake me and i'm like fuck i'm sorry that's undeniable no it's not you
i was mad for a little while but like you have been animating for like years and years so you
have like yeah you have you have skills that you applied but like it's yeah it's just sometimes
when i'm feeling like i'm not improving i'm not working as hard as i could be to get better
and someone else comes along who is who is like arguably i can like appear and they just
outclass me i'm like fuck that motherfucker get a little mad it's only in that context though
i am only and i can usually get over it i am only jealous that i never that i didn't write the
hit song while honey pie
while honey pie white honey by palma carney let me just show you the song before you even like
started talking ellie is our like the second i heard you go i i knew you were gonna say something
about the beetles i was gonna be jealous of something here's here's a meme i made here's a
beetles meme what she was it's it starts with well honey pie i think north of england it's a white
album yours starts with honey pie give talk about why honey pie oh the
this is what i'd say
this is just a medley
it's a good decision i hate music
bang bang max is having made sure she was dead
you never heard maxville silver hammer wait is that like a past murderer wait is it actually
the the whole song is just about a guy killing a bunch of people with his hammer i i guess i have
never actually listened to the song and and the rest of the beat was hated it really
palma carney wrote it and everyone hated it except him is that where is it about i
thought the song was about dwarf fortress because silver is the best material to make
hammers out of because it's the heaviest and deals the most damage uh that's not true because dwarf
fortress did not exist no it is no it's true gold's gold's heavy even silver minecraft facts told
me this uh in i think though i in i know that in dwarf fortress steel steel is the best metal to
make like blades out of but silver is the best metal to make clubs and and hammers out of uh
because i think it is heavier than it's maybe it's heavier than gold or maybe like the softness
of the gold makes it worse in some other way i don't remember wait there's no silver in minecraft
what the f**k am i talking about i'm talking about dwarf fortress bro better next voicemail
next what yeah you're right next voicemail next voicemail is called uh blown out mic man intro
three two one go hello i'm blown out mic man i knew uh i called a police officer here uh this way
right here uh uh goodbye bye that's not blown out enough you need to really yeah yeah rake hit
no there hey this is what lias are i'm gonna blow your mic now your mic's too good your mic's too
good you just sounded normal next voicemail is called irish man sadly gives you an l three two one go
sorry but that there was not a very good i think bagpipes are scottish actually
from the four but i will have to give you an l as well bagpipes are not irish and they are scottish
i got corrected by my ex-girlfriend 10 years ago when i mentioned bagpipes and Celtic folk metal
music and they're like that's not irish and i was like oh i'm a fool people not even close
mistaking irish and scottish things is very common and it's sort of annoying but i'm not
either of those so i can't really get that mad in fact i'd laugh about it
being a filthy english english just anything anything you've seen groundskeeper willy do
just remember it's it's scottish not irish so don't get it twisted
uh next voice mi English next voicemail is called wait did i miss one no dear
yes uh no the numbers line up 11 11 11 12 11 13 yeah no you're right okay the next
one is called uh official PCP more shoe impression contest entry three two one go
So, okay, this is my official entry for the PCP Morshu impression contest.
Here we go.
I don't know.
Lamp oil.
Rope.
Bombs.
You want it?
It's yours, my friend.
As long as you have enough room.
You win.
That's really good.
Sorry, Link.
I can't give credit.
Come back when you're a little richer.
That was pretty good.
Bombs.
That's the only entry.
That's pretty good.
That's by default.
Rope.
Why would you want to buy bombs?
What are you, a terrorist?
Because you can blow up things.
That's terrorism.
No, I'm going to buy TNT in Minecraft.
See?
It's legal.
Excuse me, princess.
Why would you want to buy silver?
What are you going to make of hammers and kill people with them?
Next voicemail is a vocaru.
It's called PCP Not Even Once, 3, 2, 1, go.
Cool.
Yeah.
Really?
Bang, bang, maximum.
I fell down and hurt my knee.
It's all okay with PCP.
Is this the episode intro?
Yep, this is the intro.
This is the episode.
Yeah.
Bambi nimble, keep me quick.
He's pretty long gone.
I don't get why.
I get sick.
PCP.
Is this going to end?
It's two minutes of this, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to fucking withdraws.
Oh, god.
Oh, fuck.
I've got to put that given benefit of occasional guests right into my veins.
Oh, god.
Oh, fuck.
PCP.
Yes.
Oh, fucking god.
It's in my veins right now.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, fuck.
I feel so fucking good.
Just show me straight up my veins.
My veins.
Oh, they're fucking bulging.
My veins are bulging.
They're biting.
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck.
Yes.
That guy really do be true.
It do be like that, though.
Yes.
Wow.
The happy 300 episodes.
Here's to at least one more.
That'd be cool.
One more.
We'll have 300 episodes.
That was great.
That deserves a voice grail, I think.
Sure.
Why not?
I think that was another one from Mutsu Dusty Dumps.
Tokyo Man.
Maybe there should be a different thing.
Tokyo Guy should be.
That guy definitely deserves grail, a status by this point.
I said his name last time.
PCP greatest hits.
He should release an album.
He should release an album on Bandcamp of all his PCP voicemails.
Unironically, yes.
Dude, I should do that with Floss Tapes Archive.
Make it a bank.
Yeah, sure.
Yes.
Yeah.
Why on God's name?
Unironically.
There's no reason not to.
Okay, next one is, I've got to find it here.
It's called Boston Question Mark.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm going to Boston in a couple of weeks for the School Psychologist Convention.
It's in like, I don't know, Central Boston at the Heinz Convention Center.
I mean, I don't know where that is in Boston.
I don't know anything about Boston.
That's what I'm asking.
What are some things I can do along there?
Jesus.
Wrap up warm.
Yes.
Some things to do in Boston that are good and don't suck.
Ride the T.
Travel from A to B.
That's it.
That's my favorite thing about Boston is the T.
So just ride it.
There's restaurants?
I mean, when I was in Boston, I was mostly just hanging out.
We went to restaurants and I played Pokemon Go.
Yeah.
It was fun.
I don't know about things to do.
I don't know if there's anything that I'd be like, oh, you got to check out the such-and-such
museum or whatever.
I don't know.
I don't.
I just live here, man.
I don't do shit.
I feel dumb.
I feel like I should have some.
One good thing.
One interesting neat thing.
That's cool.
But I can't.
There's nothing.
Gabe, was there anything that you thought was cool when you were here?
I mean, I generally like the vibe of the place.
It's got cool architecture and roads.
It's not like a grid city.
Just ride the T.
Just get on the T and just go wherever it takes you.
Don't even sweat it.
Don't even worry about where you end up.
Just get right from the end of the green line all the way to the end of the red line to the end of the blue line.
Dude, red line is so cool.
Seven years.
Hand drawn.
All right.
Next one is...
I don't know what this is.
Hold on.
Is that the URL?
Yeah.
Okay.
This is a blog post from Blogspot called
The Truth in its Essence
about my debut book.
Do you carry a secret?
Here's a synopsis about do you carry a secret and fear to let it out.
Veena Schecker.
I am a practicing optometrist in India with over 25 years of experience in the field.
I don't...
Okay.
Cool. Yes.
Is there a joke hidden in here?
I don't know.
I'm not looking for it.
Veena Schecker is a fan of the PCP.
She's promoting her book.
And you know what?
I'll give you a song called Deck and Schecker for you to listen to.
Veena, I'm proud of you.
You did it.
They said it couldn't be done.
Deck and Schecker, what is this?
It's just a song by Infected Mushroom.
I've seen the word Schecker twice in my life now.
First here and now this person's surname.
Oh, my head.
It's a weird album cover.
My head is pounding.
You drew that album art.
Somehow my hangover is getting worse.
Somehow it is getting...
It is only progressing and becoming worse as time goes on.
Next.
How many fingers am I holding?
What time is it?
I can't tell.
It's 1.25 p.m.
Oh, it's 4.25 a.m.
Maybe I feel sick.
Maybe it's not a hangover.
Maybe it's that I broke keto.
Maybe it's that I stopped being keto, even though I already wasn't.
Maybe that's why I'm full of poison.
I'm full of poisonous carbs, causing deadly inflammation.
You really couldn't make such a mistake.
I ate a couple of french fries.
I had a couple of french fries someone gave me yesterday.
I was already drinking beer, so why not?
Why are you drinking beer?
I have been so clean.
I have been two straight weeks.
Feeding socially.
Two straight weeks of extremely scrupulous calorie counting.
I deserved it.
Now I deserve this hangover.
Whatever.
Shut up.
Next voicemail is
for Cybershell with Love.
3, 2, 1, go.
Cybershell, I hope you're on for this one.
If only he were here.
If only.
We'll pass it on.
Yeah, we'll let him know.
We'll just tag him.
Hi, here's a special message for that guy who just left that voicemail.
Sorry it wasn't on this episode,
but it was just on that 5 and a half hour long episode that came out less than a month ago.
So just listen to that one again.
Next one is called
Come Eat Duck with Wong Chung.
Okay, 3, 2, 1, go.
Wong Chung goes back.
You like to say,
why don't you come to China with me?
We can both catch corona
and eat duck together.
I like duck.
Duck is good.
I just got reminded that one character is supposed to come back on the 300 episode.
Which character?
I guess we'll see.
Wait, what?
Spoilers?
Alright, next one is called
I hope Riley is on.
Posting it now.
Okay, 3, 2, 1, go.
Okay.
I'm sorry, he's not on.
Maybe next time.
He quit Yig.
He quit Yig. We'll never hear from him again.
Wait, really?
He did.
He just cancelled and he's taken Yig out of his profile,
his Twitter bio.
That's funny.
Is there an RB yet?
The PCP lasted longer than Voidcasers.
That's true.
We'll miss him.
We'll miss that boy.
Is there an RB yet?
He's moving back to the defunct one in his dad's yard.
One assumes.
Next one is called
Come With Comrades, 3, 2, 1, go.
Hello, comrades.
Nikola is back.
We have offer for you.
Would you like to come invade Ukraine with Nikola and other comrades?
Yes.
Sounds good, yeah.
Thanks.
Ukraine has always had a similar name to the UK.
I think it's time for them to die.
I think it's time.
Ukraine.
That's not in Ukraine.
You just want to kill mage, Gabe.
You've always just wanted to kill mage.
No, it's not true.
It's not true.
It's Brexit because I will break her legs.
Ukraine is next to Poland, I think,
and so is Lithuania more or less,
so I'm pretty sure they're the same.
They're different plays.
Adjacent to refuse is refuse.
She went to the Ukraine for the weekend
exactly when you went to destroy it.
I swear, I don't want to kill mage or break her legs.
This is my pledge.
Didn't she go to Ukraine
for some kind of weird health therapy camp
to prevent her gallbladder surgery or something?
She got the gallbladder removed.
She did get her gallbladder removed,
but before that she went for a long time
to some kind of crystal healing health camp
in the UK.
I think she just wanted to see a lot of the purple
that was there.
She made up the health stuff
just to see some purple.
I think that's probably true.
Good old mage.
How come we never get no mage, no watch in the comments?
Because mage doesn't deserve this podcast.
Mage just hangs out on her Discord
and is cool and people talk to her.
Yeah.
They watch her live stream.
Do you actually?
That's Rem Kochmar?
Yeah, Rem Kochmar.
Yeah, I watch one of them.
She does the VTuber thing pretty well.
She even sounds like a VTuber.
She learns to talk like them.
She's always had a nice voice.
I guess it's a logical thing.
She sounds like a little crazy character.
It's like she doesn't sound like herself.
She just sounds like a character ever so slightly.
You can tell it's her,
but she talks just a little differently
than she would on the PCP and it's interesting.
Huh.
I guess given her skill set,
VTubing makes a lot of sense.
Now that I think about it.
She's like a natural conclusion.
She has a pretty voice.
She's good at drawing.
All her art is like she would draw like,
she's doing like,
what's the word I'm looking for?
Animated.
Kind of like static character art.
Illustrations?
Yeah, she's like character illustration.
And so like, I don't know.
I guess VTubing is a pretty natural
convergence of those two things.
But I haven't seen any of it.
That's interesting.
It's really good.
Yeah.
I wonder, I would just want to know
if Roshmar is related to Remlazar.
Remlazar, yeah.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yes.
Red letter media? Okay.
Is Remlazar related to Eliazar?
Yeah, basically.
You tell me.
I'm connecting the dots here.
Next one is,
it's called,
wait, we didn't listen to the last one.
Sorry, the last one is called.
There's no reason to do that.
The last one is called Digi Bro.
No, we got to listen to it.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
I told you.
Eliazar cut that out.
Eliazar? Eliazar?
Yeah.
Eliazar? I just did an even better burp.
Enjoy yourself.
I've been burping this whole podcast.
There's nothing special about it.
You're a baby, Ben. I know.
I spit up a little bit.
When I burp, it will puke a little bit.
That's okay.
Next voicemail is called
nose. Three, two, one, go.
Why?
Why send this?
They just like breathe with their nose.
Why make this?
Why do this?
Next voicemail is called OVA.
Three, two, one, go.
So when's the OVA
supposed to release?
Yeah.
Last time.
The answer is the footage.
Nate has the footage.
I said they're working on it.
So I don't know.
I asked him
not long ago.
He told me.
He told me at Christmas
that he was going to make it before
he was going to make the
not the OVA, but the
Brad Garling House
music video.
He said it wouldn't take him long.
He was going to take a day and do that before New Year's.
He didn't do it, but I asked him again
like a week ago or something
and he said, okay.
I told him, you know,
Kaiju has taken up
the dojin job.
And so that's only a few weeks away.
And I told him like,
Nate, I would really,
it would be really good if we could have
the Brad Garling House music video
and the OVA
at the same time as that.
So can we have that in a few weeks?
And he said, yes, he'll do it.
So supposedly he's going to do it.
Have you ever heard of this little thing called
personal fucking responsibility?
Right, exactly.
Yeah.
If Nate doesn't deliver on time,
just message him and be like, God, Nate,
it's not being such a tricksy.
I mean, it's too late to deliver on time,
anything, but I mean,
it's...
I'm sure he intends to do it.
I just,
I hope he does.
I hope I don't have to hound him
too many times.
Because he says he'll do it.
And I,
even as of recently,
I said, are you going to do it?
And he said, yes, I will do it
soon.
So, you know,
I don't know.
Next voicemail is called...
What is it?
That was OVA.
Next voicemail is called sorry.
Here it is.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Why?
God, not number one. Why?
This voicemail just wants the voicemail segment to end.
The voicemail segment's died.
It reminds me of song one.
Trying to communicate. I'm going to breathe with my nose
until I make a smoke signal.
Why do this to me?
Why would you hurt me like this?
What did I do to you
to deserve this treatment?
What did we do then?
Next voicemail is called
what have I done?
Three, two, one, go.
The same guy.
Why would you click on it?
So quiet.
That was pretty good.
I guess.
The loud what have I done.
I could do something.
Okay, next one is...
Okay, it's just a question. It's a text question.
It's Riley Bird Mint.
Where did these people come from?
Answer their dick show people.
I don't know.
Next one is...
What did you see?
When two people love each other.
They met a burning dick.
That's the answer.
Next one is called...
Oh god, okay.
X zero.
The hour of reprisal.
This is what it's all been building to.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
He...
Has...
Come... Jesus.
I knew it.
Hello.
Hi, Samurai-sama.
You expect...
Anybody else?
Fuck off.
Samurai-sama.
Come to say...
Two things.
Number one.
Fuck off.
That's right.
And number two.
Episode 300.
I know, right?
What the fuck?
Yeah. That's probably true.
Yeah.
That's probably true.
Right.
Okay. Until next time.
Goodbye.
Love you, Samurai.
I knew he was going to come back.
He's right.
I just...
I accept it.
I accept. 300 episodes is cringe.
There's just no getting around it.
Curingy.
Fuck off.
What do you even want to become Curingy?
Okay.
Lovely to hear.
Lovely to hear from the Samurai again.
Okay.
The procrastinator's podcast political compass.
Me too.
Oh, hey. They placed me pretty accurately.
They actually put me pretty accurate to where my actual political compass is.
That's Fidium C or Kimster?
That's...
That's Fidium C.
Okay.
No, that's Fidium C with the beard.
The Wonder Bread guy is up there.
Why am I authoritarian left?
Why is Cheesy authoritarian left?
Why is Kazzy authoritarian left?
I don't know if this makes any sense.
Cheesy is authoritarian left because he holds a gun to begata's head
and he says you're going to redistribute the retweets around.
And God bless him for it.
What's the second with Megaman supposed to be?
Oh, that's to Snaker.
That's from the animation of Meta Knight on his period that I heard about.
Uh, no.
Who is that red blob on the right?
Oh, it's Shreddit.
Yeah, it's Shreddit.
Uh, I don't know.
This is silly.
I don't know if I have anything to say about it.
It's sort of in the right ballpark, but with all alignment charts
that have a fixed number of spaces but way too many people,
they can't actually fit them properly.
Why is Maryweather far left?
What's the explanation for that?
Has Maryweather been on the podcast? I just missed that.
Yeah, he's been on like three times.
He's been on at least twice.
Once as a VTuber.
That's right. That's right.
Marydog.
What was the editing process like?
Did they just give you like a green screen footage to put on at Eleazar?
Yep.
Yep, exactly.
There's unhoxtable right leading.
I don't think so.
I think at a certain point, I'll put the people roughly where I know they are
and for everyone else, I just have to find room.
Because they can't overlap us with how I've set it up.
Yeah, exactly.
They're just going out their ass, I guess.
Victor is a big right-leaning centrist.
Davoo.
I guess Davoo has moved left a bit.
Davoo finally realized that Trump bad like a few months ago.
Good for her.
Congratulations.
Did you not know that he's trying to do a coup?
She, I don't know.
She saw some, she made some stupid posts about it.
Like who cares?
I mean, orange meant bad.
How hard is it to understand?
It was like earlier this year.
It might have been before the insurrection or whatever you want to call it.
No, it was, I don't know.
She made like seven tweets about it in a row.
It was a big thread.
It was just like rambling.
I don't even remember what the point was.
Orange meant bad.
Orange got good.
Yes, orange cat is good.
I don't know.
I don't know what to think about the use of my picture in this is.
Because on the one hand, it doesn't look like me anymore.
But it is one of the better facial hairstyles I had.
I do think that was like people like that.
What about the starfish beard from those early Patreon videos you made?
That was stupid.
That was me having too much and being like silly.
I'm glad I don't have the beard feeling on my face.
I guess it does look good though.
I just thought it was really funny.
I remember I showed my sister, my older sister, your videos and we were laughing so much.
We laughed at you.
We laughed at your spam.
We thought you were just a real funny bean.
And then you'll never guess what this person looks like.
And I pulled up those videos and we were just like, oh my God, giga-chad energy.
Holy fuck.
We loved it.
We loved the crazy hair.
It was so good.
You did not look like I envisioned you.
When I first heard your voice, Gib, I envisioned a person much different.
I envisioned like a chubby Swedish guy.
Like a big chubby blonde guy is what I thought you looked like.
I don't know why.
I don't know.
That's weird.
Do I have a voice?
Of course they look like this.
I don't know.
Or did I have a voice?
I can't imagine why you would think that.
I don't know.
I also don't know why.
You just sounded like you do now.
Just a little more British.
Basically.
I guess you'll never know where Cittor and I are placed.
You got to place yourself.
No, no, no.
No one will learn.
There's only a few spots left and they're mostly on the- they're all on the right.
You've got to go somewhere.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's only- yep.
You're locked in.
Sorry.
No, you just can't.
Elisa only believes in peace and love.
And I for one agree.
Not.
I for one believe that good things are good and bad things are bad.
I believe in peace and love.
Accepts what it's been saying.
My politics are that we should support good things and oppose bad things.
What the fuck?
Controversial.
Next one is called, remember Paul Joseph Watson?
No.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, remember when Paul Joseph Watson said, conservativeism is the new counterculture?
Yeah.
And I believe them.
How cringe was that?
Pretty funny.
That's pretty cringe.
I only know Paul Joseph Watson.
He wasn't the only one.
Reaction videos.
He wasn't the only one to say that.
His services are against like near-lib, but like it's not like counterculture because
it's also like the backbone of the dominant culture.
Everything the current culture is built upon, it has like conservative undertones.
There's really nothing less punk rock than like being like we should like make gay marriage
illegal.
We should keep the status quo.
People should have less rights.
Women should have more of their bodies.
Let me show you my political alignment.
It's this game.
This gives my political alignment.
Is that Ringo?
That's Ringo.
Look at him.
Ringo star.
Now, here's a guy who lived long enough to become cringe.
I guess he was always cringe, actually.
Nah, he was never cringe.
Shut the fuck up.
Ringo?
Nobody likes Ringo.
Shut up.
Underrated Best Beatle.
Patrick Star from SpongeBob saying, Ringo randomly.
I don't know what episode it was and it's haunted me for like five years.
I just had this memory and I don't know what episode it's from and I don't want to watch
it.
Someone tell me.
Why would you ever watch SpongeBob?
Did Patrick Star say Ringo?
SpongeBob is good.
It's a love SpongeBob.
What do you say?
Once upon a time, been people with children?
False.
Dude, the original free season of SpongeBob, hold up.
It's still really fucking funny, but the rest is meh.
The next one is a vocaru.
What's it called?
I don't know.
Three, two, one, go.
It's time for Ben Sings the Ripes of the Week.
Pretty good.
Pretty good jingle.
I'd use it.
I'd use it for a segment.
I didn't have any gripes this week other than that I aim hungover.
That's my gripe for the week.
Your gripe is that you drank alcohol and you shouldn't have.
You should have had the tap water.
I simply should have drank the tap water, but I didn't want people to know that I am immortal.
You didn't want the brain parasites.
No.
I didn't want the fluoride.
I didn't want to control my mind through the fluoride.
Fluoride.
They put fucking chlorine in America.
It's really gross.
Chlorine?
At least, at least, unless it's just a Texas thing.
The water here tastes like chlorine.
It tastes like pool water and it smells too.
When you take a shower, it smells like the fucking pool.
Mine doesn't smell like that.
I guess you got fluoride and we got chlorine.
I prefer fluoride.
It doesn't stink and you can't taste it nearly as much anyway.
I mean, no, I can't taste the fluoride.
Here's something.
What is this?
Good thumbnail.
I saw this thumbnail and title combination and it made me laugh for some reason, wanted to share.
Agitation in the Hairless Chimp Group.
It took me a moment to realize that is actually a Hairless Chimp.
It's noisy again at the chimp enclosure.
They're getting introduced to the remaining chimps.
These guys are, they're so ripped.
It's just because of the lack of hair.
They're usually ripped, but this guy is so fucking jacked.
I'm not on Twitter and I don't use Twitter.
And every time someone mentions Twitter, this is what I imagine.
Agitation in the Hairless Chimp Group.
Getting agitated.
That's me.
I'm getting agitated.
I'm a Hairless Chimp getting agitated.
Dude, the Hairless Chimp Group is like a great name for a band.
Yeah.
All right.
Good stuff.
Good stuff, I guess.
Next one is called Addressing the Future of Kyle and Funny Man in Space.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello.
This is me, Mr. Funny Man from The Iconic Show,
Kyle and Funny Man in Space.
Yes.
I love Kyle and Funny Man.
I'm just here to address the future of Kyle and Funny Man.
I love content.
I've been getting a lot of comments from people.
I love intellectual crap.
They're saying the show is too dark.
The people on the PCP podcast last episode, they said,
they started crying, they started shitting themselves.
They, you know, a lot of people have said they're suffering from depression now,
anxiety, my full disorder, or any...
Irritable bowel syndrome.
How dare you not make me shit myself?
The crazy argument that Kyle and Funny Man did,
as well as that time when Funny Man actually killed the man with a gun.
So we hear you.
The show has been getting a bit too dark.
So we're going to course correct with the next episode.
Get excited for that.
It's going to be the mid-season finale,
and it's probably going to be like five minutes.
So get excited for next week.
I guess we'll have to have more than 300 episodes.
Yes.
You know what I like about this is that it's a character from the show
giving a press conference.
Is that Funny Man?
That was Funny Man.
Well, I didn't laugh for once.
You're not supposed to...
This is serious business.
We're talking about the future of the IP.
IP?
There's money on the line.
That's funny.
You know what? It is funny.
Funny Man, you did it again.
Another masterpiece.
He really is the funniest man ever.
Yeah, that mad man.
Next voicemail.
Where is this?
Okay, the next one is called both Imgir and Voice.
So here's the voice clip,
and here's the Imgir link for the accompanying image, I guess.
Okay, oh god.
All right, let's give it a listen in three, two, one, go.
Attention, attention.
All the music in this voicemail is copyright free.
No need to mute it.
Thank you for your attention.
Hello there, this is me, Jay.
You might remember me, you might not,
but you will remember to repost my card book.
Or else...
I will mint it.
I'm having...
I will mint it all.
Slime and punishment, blue face,
even then does what itself,
and then when the climate change comes,
and humanity ends,
everyone will remember,
when same as the Imgir of the...
Having a little trouble understanding...
Yeah, I understand one word from that.
I heard Slime and Punishment, and Harbinger.
Ben St. the Imgir of Dave.
Notice that.
Like in Phantom, that's the...
Yeah, I was about to say.
I like that they're being crucified.
That makes me smile.
Hard voicemail, but the image is great, I love it.
Yeah.
The image is very good.
Ben will make the blue race.
Is that Slime?
Is that like an ocean of Slime behind them?
Looks like it.
I'm gonna say it is, yeah.
It's kinda now.
What?
Okay, next voicemail.
There it is.
It's called...
Backwards Message.
Three, two, one, go.
Erklaas kak yezee tnees neb.
Skak nekas knyal ya tnees neb.
Ze amin nyam.
Sounds like oblivion.
Definitely oblivion.
I wonder why it sounds like me.
Oblivion.
Let's see the next voicemail.
Do you want to translate for us?
The next voicemail.
Just do the next one.
How many more are out there?
We're on the last page.
There's only maybe 10 or 15 left?
10.
Yeah, we kinda got a lot this week.
Oblivion, I never told you how much I love
when I was editing the episode and the fucking...
Oh, put the baby in a blender.
The fucking stuff.
The baby in a blender.
No, you want to.
You need to.
The next one is called...
S-A-G-S-M-S-D-R-O-C-C-A-B.
Three, two, one, go.
My name is Ben St.
I like sucking cock.
No!
Ben St. is a cock sucker.
How did you get this secret recording of me saying that?
I knew that the word cock was in there
because it sounds the same in backwards.
Yeah, cock.
I was struggling to say cock backwards,
and then I realized just say cock.
Yeah.
Yeah, I really did.
I really did say it backwards and then reverse it.
It was a little fun, but if you do it one syllable at a time,
it's easy.
You can't...
It's not like Yvonne at Nia's.
You can't just read.
You can't just write it backwards and then read it phonetically.
What I did is I recorded myself saying it,
and then I reversed the recording,
listened to each syllable,
every two syllables one at a time,
and just recorded myself just saying those parts
and putting them together.
That makes sense.
Think that's what I did in 10 minutes.
For Twin Peaks.
Yeah.
Yeah, Twin Peaks did that.
Wait, wait.
Didn't you retire?
This took me like 10 minutes to see it all.
It was fine.
10 minutes.
Who has time for that?
I need satanic messaging is so important.
Yeah, in your music, not in the PCK.
Nothing more satanic than Ben saying,
suckin' a big cock, dude.
I like the medium size.
Regular cock, please.
Next average.
I wanted to sit right on top of that bell curve.
Ben, that's my cock you're describing right now.
It's most cock.
Exactly six inches.
Wait a minute.
No more, no less.
I'm average.
Next voicemail is called,
Newer fan wants lore, please.
Three, two, one, go.
So inspired by last week's
newer PCP fan asking about
Prince Isolation asking about
Colt Corona, Hilarious.
Questions about lore as a newer PCP fan myself.
So I'm a fan of the comic,
Slam and Punishment, I think it's good.
And I get pretty much everything that's going on there.
With the exception of strawberry milk.
Who is strawberry milk?
What's the deal with strawberry milk?
What is strawberry milk?
Give me some lore on that dragon looking boy.
Sure, fair.
Strawberry milk was Munchie's MLP Sona.
Use a dragon.
Yeah, that's it.
It was cool.
I had Phantom horn, Nate had keg standard,
Munchie had strawberry milk.
He never made any videos with strawberry milk,
although he is in the RFCK episodes
where we talk about brony shit.
Phantom and strawberry.
So he's kind of...
He's also kind of RFCK.
Didn't he make strawberry milk for something like that?
No, he had strawberry milk.
Strawberry milk was his Sona even back in
at BronyCon, back in the day.
I saw some doodles of him.
He looks like Spike the Dragon plus Steven Universe.
Basically.
Yeah.
I made him big.
Because, I don't know.
He changed the design.
Originally, he looked much more like Spike the Dragon,
but I think he changed the design to be taller.
So this is the redesign version.
My version of strawberry milk is not faithful.
I basically fucked up and I wrote him wrong.
My version is not faithful.
The real strawberry milk is just a rapist
and a sexual predator.
It's just kind of like a funny bro who likes sex.
I soften the character a lot.
Munchie hates sex.
Yeah, Munchie hates sex, but strawberry milk
likes it to a criminal degree.
It's canon.
But not in Slime's Munchie.
Pledge to the PCP.
Listen to the fucking Five Nights at Freddy's versus...
Chucky Cheese.
Munchie's 20-minute long rant in that thing
is one of my favorite things ever.
Oh my god.
Do you want to know a funny story about that?
You know what?
My then-girlfriend was on that bonus episode.
And she was really excited to just talk genuinely
about Chucky Cheese.
And she was mad.
She was angry afterwards.
She was angry that Munchie had talked too much.
I wanted to explain the history of Chucky Cheese
because I watched a documentary about it.
She was mad for a while.
She did get to explain it.
She explained it very well and it was interesting.
She did, but she was still mad.
I thought she did a good job.
She was mad.
She succeeded though.
I learned a lot and I thought it was cool stuff.
She was so shallow by Munchie.
I thought it was funny.
She did not appreciate it.
You know what?
There's a reason things didn't work out between us.
I'm going to fucking...
One day, one of my goals before I die
is to animate that rant.
I just have to do it.
It's so good.
400 episodes.
I remember in the moment
thinking that the rant was pretty funny
but also being very uncomfortable
because I could tell she was starting to see.
She was sitting right next to me
and I was like, oh, no.
Oh, dear.
I don't know what to do about this.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I kind of remember what happened.
I think I was losing my breath laughing.
I remember him launching into
this diet ride.
This huge thing.
It just went on.
It just kept going.
Munchie's rant about the alternate world history
of the atomic bomb landing on a mouse
and creating the ultimate Adonis
who is the crust of the earth itself.
That is almost on the level
of the story that I told in English class
for my speech.
Oh, the one that was just steamed hams.
No, not the steamed hams.
It's just a speech about time travel
and the dinosaur is being wiped out
by these free-legged creatures.
Chuck E. Cheese is my godfather.
He's my father, but we call him a god.
Somebody should...
Look into his eyes. There is no lust.
That was so good.
Man, yeah.
I haven't thought about that in a while, but that was great.
Pledge to the PCP Patreon.
Bonus episodes.
He's my father, but he's so powerful
we call him a god.
It's amazing.
Honestly, I don't...
I forget most of the details.
I could go back and listen and refresh myself.
It's fucking funny.
I have a condensed version of the rant
where I cut out all the fluff
and cut out as much of Jackie as I could.
Alright, next voicemail.
It's called...
It's just called voicemail.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Perfect.
A lot of just bodily sounds today.
A lot of burps.
This one's really...
These are not mine.
That is not mine.
That sounds like your...
This is because I'm the only fucking person
who puts a rasp in my voice sometimes.
You hear any rasp when you think it's me.
He just can't quit.
He said he wouldn't do it anymore,
but he can't break the habit
and now he just calls the voicemail
and just sits on the phone
and just breathing into the microphone.
I hear all the time.
When you thought it's over,
there was the force in everything.
I'm not even posting most of them.
I've cut out so many of them that are just oblivion falls.
Heavy breathing.
Hold on, let me try and go...
It's exactly the same.
It is.
It's the same. It's a match. We have a match.
Computer enhanced.
That one generally wasn't me
about what I was saying.
It's over.
It's as easy as a broadcast.
Sorry.
Your time in the League of Natefuckers.
You've been forcibly expelled from the League of Natefuckers.
No, I built that with my own hands.
No, you've been usurped.
You're fired. You're destroyed.
I mean, the League is cutting off your payments.
The next voicemail
is called Trixie.
Three, two, one, go.
It just doesn't quit.
They just won't quit.
Next voicemail
is called
3, 2, 1, go.
I don't know what this is.
Attack on Titan?
It's what?
Just it's.
Attack on Titan is...
Wait, there's another one.
This one is also called
3, 2, 1, go.
Good.
No, bad.
Okay.
People were saying I should...
I've heard that Attack on Titan gets bad.
A couple people on Twitter were telling me
no, it's actually fine
and you should read it and maybe I will
read it at some point.
Dude, there's just some fucking great
art every so often.
Some giant funny skeleton creatures
that are cool.
Yeah.
I mean, I like that it
has an ending.
The fact that it has an ending makes me
like, I appreciate that. I should finish it
just in honor of the fact that it had the courage
to end. Good for it.
I appreciate it.
Next one is called
OPM
is 13 years old, by the way.
3, 2, 1, go.
One punch man has become shit, too.
Don't read the manga
even though it looks awesome.
You read it anyway to look at the pictures.
Look at the pretty pictures
and read the webcomic for the awesome story.
That's what I've heard from my friend Fade
all up.
The manga
with the nice art
started adding on all this stuff
like a tournament arc and a bunch of other shit
that apparently is just really boring
shown and stuff apparently.
That's really dumb.
That's what I've heard.
I don't like it. I feel like the point of it
should have been to adapt
one's story.
I've totally lost patience
with tropes
like that.
Tropes.
Fucking tropes.
The tournament arc is like every single
thing has it. I've seen it.
It's the laziest way to make
fights happen.
You could totally make a good
tournament arc in a good way.
Tournament arcs are only good
in D&D where you're the DM
and you don't want to have
to do any work.
That's where they...
I want a story where there's a tournament
going on and the characters in the
show they go and watch it
and they're in the crowd. It's like, oh fuck
well that was fun. Let's go home.
I can't believe it's still
going after 13 years.
Where does that...
I don't have to read it to find out, but where does
that story go?
I can't even imagine.
The theme is that it's one punch
and he doesn't care
about life.
He doesn't care about combat
but he's really good at it. He cares about
other things.
That doesn't really have a concrete
ending
unless he stops
punching.
I read the part where the
alien comes
because he's seeking
the most powerful opponent or whatever.
He's the most powerful alien.
That's what I read up to.
And I felt thematically
that was like, yep, this is the thematic
conclusion to this whole
conceit of this story.
Makes sense. And that's where season one ends
which is the season with the really good animation
that's worth watching IMO.
So I can't even...
I can't even imagine where it goes in there
and I guess I shouldn't write it off without
reading it. I don't know, maybe it's so good.
His arm gets cut off and he can't punch
so he becomes one kick man.
No, he gets...
Everything removed except one finger
and one arm and he's one flick man.
He loses an arm
so he becomes literally one punch man
because he's...
He can only punch once.
Then he becomes fruit tropical punch man.
Hawaiian punch man.
Maybe he meets the red, like that guy
you know, the guy with the red hat
or whatever, or is it a snail?
No, the Hawaiian punch guy.
I don't know who he is.
The guy who punches people.
Uh, hold on.
Oh, I just finished another
in-between session from animations.
I've been working on this whole thing and I just finished. Hell yeah.
Here, here, here.
This...
This fucking guy
who...
I don't even know what he's supposed to be.
That's a cool hat.
You know this guy?
I think it's a hat.
This guy looks like he doesn't follow the rules.
I don't trust him.
There's seven kinds of fruit in Hawaiian punch.
Dude.
This guy's drunky.
He asks you, do you want a Hawaiian punch?
And then you say, hell yeah.
And then he slugs you.
He should be wearing a punch.
He beats the shit out of you.
That's his thing.
He should be wearing a Hawaiian shirt.
Wait a minute. Okay.
Okay, check this out.
This showed up in my search results.
Somebody else made the joke.
Somebody else made the same joke.
Oh.
Nothing's original then.
No, nothing new under the sun.
Alright, next voicemail is...
I think I already...
No, this is what it's called.
How is no one abusing this every week for fun?
Three, two, one, go.
What is this fucking system?
Can I just send a hundred voicemails right now?
Yeah.
I could send one every ten seconds.
For the rest of time.
It has been abused.
Sometime.
We're constantly being abused.
Dude, I abused the fuck out of the system
with the pig episode.
My god.
I got that up.
I ruined Ben's day.
I hated that episode.
I really, really hated it.
You have no idea how much
I was laughing listening to that episode
and how much I got you.
When I did that,
I just wanted to make fun of pig squealing.
It's a vocal method
in death metal.
Pig squealing needs to be taken down a peg.
It's been too high on the floor.
It does.
I didn't even do it anymore.
I somehow did it that one time.
Yeah, it was me. That was my voice.
I did the pig squealing noises.
Then I'm like, this sounds terrible.
What should I do with it?
How could I make this a voicemail?
I thought about it.
I have so many old voicemails from way back.
What if I just grab some of those?
What if I just put them in unexpectedly?
It's a different person every time,
so Ben will never expect it and he will just get jump-scared.
That's exactly what happens.
It got even better than that,
because I knew that Ben would eventually become wise.
He'd eventually realize early on,
wait, this person sounds like they're talking about Nate
or some shit from years ago.
Then what I did is,
I'll throw in a bunch of false flags.
I'll do three ones with the pig.
I'll throw in four false flags,
and then I'll throw in the other three.
The very first false flag I put in
was the first time you said,
it's the pig, isn't it?
And then it wasn't.
It was perfectly down to where you would
be bamboozled,
and then you got so fucking mad, too.
I think so much listening to it.
Mastermind.
I'm just like a mouse
running through your maze.
It was so fucked.
That is fucked.
I did my fake British accent
and Ben's like, that sounds like oblivion
and gib the British one.
No, it's too British.
Alright, next voicemail
is called 30s.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my god, I'm leaving a voicemail
on the 300th episode of the PCP.
That's right.
It's all I ever wanted.
Same.
This voicemail has been brought to you
by your 30s.
I'm down hill from here.
Woo!
I'm happy
that I am not
I'm happy that I am not
one of these people
who has suffered
any kind of like horrible debilitation.
Some people are like,
you get 30 and then you just are in pain all the time
and everything starts to
fail. And I'm like, well,
it hasn't happened for me yet, so I guess
I'm should be pretty happy
about that.
It started hamming for me
in my early 20s with my fucking back.
This is what I get
for not getting drunk and hungover.
That's right.
It's good for you.
Yeah, it gives you exercise, makes you get out more
so you're not stuck sitting in a chair working constantly
hurting your back.
I still do that.
Okay, next one is called
The Chew Dynasty.
3, 2, 1,
go.
Nice beat.
There's lots of things you could imagine this being.
Just imagine like a little ant beatboxing.
Is this just going to keep going like this?
I'm not mentioning a little mouse
like you in the beatboxing.
I wanted to cut off and be like,
okay, cool. Anyway, what do you think of the new Pokemon game?
Just giggling at weird noises.
This is the procrastinator's experience.
He's really going for it.
He's really going to do a whole minute of this.
Okay.
Nice. Good luck.
Is that Peter Gorfin?
Yeah.
Peter.
You're a Peterphile.
Hey, Peter, I'm married to you.
That makes me a Peterphile.
They had to have made that joke.
I can't be the first one to make that joke.
A water potter?
This reminded me of that time when I was sus.
Next voicemail
is called...
Well, there's an image.
There's an image to go with it.
Let's see.
I'll post it. I don't know.
I feel like I've hit a point
where I've deduced all I can deduce.
Ben saying
PCP bonus episode number 43
at 23.
Okay.
Alright, this is from the bonus episode
where I was learning...
Gib was teaching me how to play Minesweeper.
I was learning.
I was in the process of learning.
That episode was so frustrating
to edit.
I'm sure it was.
If you know how to play.
I figured it out, though.
I figured it out.
I figured out how to do it.
I taught you how.
Well, yes.
With your help, I figured it out and I did it.
You can watch me expand my mind
in real time.
I'd love that episode.
I don't know if it was as bombastic
as
Munchie's
the
Chuck E. Cheese ramp.
You know how you can change the world
in Wordle by just changing the date
in your PC?
You could make a Wordle...
That was a voicemail last time.
You could make a Wordle competition.
When you finish a word, you just change the date.
Whoever does
the Wordle faster
wins.
But then I won't be able to do Wordle
for 10 days.
You'll be clean.
I think you would want
to do it in the least guesses.
I think you would take 10 Wordles
and be like, who can do
these 10 Wordles in the least
total guesses?
There are other sites that
do the same thing as Wordle,
but it's not one per day.
It's not Wordle.
You need the IP.
Yeah, it's all about that IP.
Anyway, let's listen to this voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Ho, ho, ho!
I am the
mind-sweeper deity!
And I think that you are
bad at the game!
Ho, ho, ho!
Why is the mind-sweeper deity a goat?
It's a goat woman.
Maybe?
Um, is it
Toriel?
June.
Sex question mark?
Sex?
Yes.
No, I'm good at the game now.
I learned it.
Next voicemail is called a quick question.
There it is.
Okay, we're almost done, by the way.
We got three more.
Three, two, one, go.
Funniest compliment you ever got.
Go.
Funniest compliment?
Someone said I was really...
They really liked that skitser girl
once on a pro and on episode.
And you know what?
They really liked that skitser girl.
Yeah.
Wait, I actually
do know the funniest compliment I got.
Let me find it.
The funniest compliment I ever got is
kiss you then kiss Paul McCartney.
That's pretty good.
I don't know if I can think of
like a funny, like a compliment
that was funny somehow.
I can think of compliments that were like
upsetting to me because it's like
a trait that I didn't want to have.
And that they liked.
God, I can't, I can't...
I can't think of any compliments
I got on that one.
It's my cat. Does that help?
Almost as cute.
I would never imply that anyone is
actually as cute as my pet cat.
My cats are very cute.
Almost.
That's a pretty high bar.
I don't know if the compliment itself is funny
but it's from a funny person
because they've tracked me down
on the PCP, on the draw cast,
other places in the left comments like these.
I love Oblivionfall.
I wish they were mine.
They will be mine.
Oblivion, I think that's called a stalker.
Look, if they're an adult female,
like maybe...
I wish they were mine.
Like a bro.
Like a conglomerate.
God, I can't think of anything. Sorry.
I only get sincere compliments
that are good because I'm
so cool.
I did um...
I don't know if it's...
I did win... This is bizarre.
I did win Best Dressed
in my high school yearbook
in my graduating class.
Show up in nothing but slime.
They could see all your junk.
I'm stupid. I just wore suits.
I just wore suits all the time.
Why?
It's like a quirky affectation
that I did to be funny.
I just wore suits to school every day.
That's so quirky.
And they won Best Dressed.
Yeah.
I wasn't actually well-dressed.
I just had some suits and I wore them.
There were other guys who actually...
There was one guy, I remember,
who was actually well-dressed.
He wore a sweater vest
and buttoned down polo shirt combinations.
He was actually a well-dressed guy.
And that guy should have won.
But because I was not
better dressed, I was more dressed.
It was like how in the Oscars
you don't really get an award for best editing.
You get an award for most editing.
Like the flashiest editing wins.
It's why people like the high-framing anime.
It's not about the animation being good.
It's about just having lots of it.
Yeah. My stupid jokes
wear a suit every day gimmick.
Attracted more attention than this guy.
This guy's sweater vest.
And so I defeated him.
And I taught him a valuable lesson.
No matter what you do in life,
it'll never be good enough.
And you'll never be rewarded for...
Right. You'll never get your due.
You have to...
You gotta be a piece of shit.
You gotta be a piece of shit if you want to win.
But stay hydrated.
Yeah. Always stay hydrated.
Okay. We got two more.
The PCP logo is actually good.
It's actually just an image.
From afar, the new PCP logo
actually looks pretty good.
Oh yeah. That fucked up one
last time. Well, everything looks good from afar.
Everything looks perfect from far away.
Yeah.
If you can't see it very well, it actually looks pretty good.
Uh...
It's true, I guess.
Okay. Last one.
My girlfriend read something.
Three, two, one, go.
PCP.
I just wanted to say happy 300 episode.
Thank you. If I made it in time
and if not happy 300
and one, that's also a cool number.
So I was on vacation
with my girlfriend last week
and I brought my road to Radcon
which finally arrived because Ben
learned how to write the number three.
We should all be really proud of him.
I mis-addressed this guy's own book and she said,
what is this? And I tried to explain
it's a book written by some podcast people
I listened to.
And she said, okay, I'm going to read it.
I don't want to know what you're into.
So she started reading it
and she said, what the fuck is this garbage?
They broke up.
Okay, but she read...
She started at the beginning, so she was reading
Trixie's chapters, so that's not on me.
Uh...
If she wanted to know what it is,
the book explains what it is on the back.
You can just read the back of the book and it says.
So I think she just can't read
because if she could she would have known.
There's a full explanation.
Right there, so.
RotoradCon is very funny
and it has called Corona in it.
And it explains the origin
of the coronavirus.
I've said too much. I've spoiled everything.
The front cover is really cool.
We are the reason people are dying.
And yes, the front cover by Michi
is awesome, of course.
She's so good.
Actually, I don't know if they're a girl.
I don't know.
I just... I assume Michi's a girl
because Michi sounds like a girl name.
Because I knew a girl named Michi.
Or who went by Michi.
But I actually have no idea.
Okay, that's the last voicemail.
We're done.
We've been going for what, is this like four hours now?
Yes.
Four in a bit.
Lol.
I'm going back to bed now.
I need to go eat.
I need to go back to bed.
An hour ago, I wanted nothing more than to go...
You know what? I'm over my hangover. I feel better.
I feel fine.
I felt so shit this whole time.
But now I feel okay.
I've been invigorating.
I have work in two hours.
I have to go to a concert in like four hours.
We're great.
It was fun being on that.
It was a good...
You know what?
I would wake up at 1am
and do this podcast again.
Sorry about your
geographical handicap.
Sorry that the mail doesn't go
to your god forsaken country.
I only wish I didn't have work today.
If I didn't have work today, this would not be a problem.
But I do have work today.
So it's mildly inconvenient.
Just tell your boss.
Just like drag yourself into work.
Un-shaven and un-camped.
And you'd be like...
And show them RotoradCon.
Wait, what the hell happened to you?
And you'll say I was on a
podcast.
Ben, no.
I'm a cleaner
and I'm the only employee right now.
I have to get the work done
before the building's open.
And I'm the only one who can do it.
Are you like a DeVoo window cleaner?
No, worse.
I'm a whole building cleaner.
Oh.
Which includes windows.
Oh, so you're better than DeVoo.
I kept vacuum.
I wipe things down.
I have to clean the gym
today.
It's gonna be fun.
Okay, sweaty.
Leave them a note
on the bench press that says,
okay, sweaty.
I don't know if I can get away with
that passing person.
After you wipe their salt stains
off the pads
or whatever.
I feel like it uses the machines to wipe
any touch points down.
And we got any last words before we conclude today?
Good night.
I think I'm good.
Peace and love.
Patreon.com
Is it the procrastinators?
Oh my god.
It's Patreon.com
forward slash the drawcast.
We have bonus episodes up.
Extended episodes up.
Go give us some money, baby.
Yeah.
You still don't know how the URL is.
I don't like the PCP.
We all pay our guests to be on when the Patreon
earns enough.
And we also
already pay our editor.
And we keep that up to date.
We pay for the work he does.
How does that feel?
It's Nate's fault.
Nate's in charge of the finance.
Personal responsibility.
Ben, you're the host.
Personal fucking responsibility.
Okay, I guess that's it.
I guess that's the end.
Okay, bye.
Check out the fucking February.
And 300.
300 episodes.
Bye-bye.
Peace and love.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.