The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Hello and welcome to another episode of the Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It's your three best friends here once again to talk about stuff that is interesting to
us.
We're keeping it a little bit smaller today, it is me, your host, bestie boy, the best
guy ever.
We've also got my good friend Digibro, and Ben Saint of Patreon, and our topic for
the week is something, I'm going to call this a bottom of the barrel cast.
Our topic is, since no one's here, we had to put aside all the good topics, all the incredibly
juicy topics we've got lined up.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Such great topics.
No, some of them are good.
I like them.
Some of them are good.
Some of them are good, and I hope to get into the more.
Most of them, though.
Total shit-fest.
Total trash.
Including, for example.
Shrek vs. Harry Potter.
I don't know who wrote that.
Is that one?
I don't know who wrote that in the topic.
I don't get it.
Wow, some idiot.
It's in there.
Jesus.
Shrek.
And today's topic, which is never going outside, or, I don't know, being a Hikikomori, you
know, keeping it in the homestead, not being a social butterfly out in the real world.
And I don't know, I thought we'd just share anecdotes, how we feel about it, our relationships
with the outside world.
Share some hot tips and tricks for all you aspiring Hikikomoris out there.
Exactly.
So, who's got something to say, Saraswamy?
Digi, I know you have.
Okay, Ben.
My room is pitch-dark right now.
It's 6 p.m. The sun is out, but my room is pitch-black because I got my bathrobe tape
to my window.
That must be some strong tape.
Because I don't want it.
Actually, it's not tape.
It's wedged into the frame.
Whatever.
Oh, okay.
And I got my air conditioner in under it.
It does not let any light in.
It's nighttime.
Oh, nice.
It's nighttime all the time.
Here in Ben St.'s house.
That sounds great.
So, do you like it dark for any particular reason?
Well, my sleep schedule is off.
I've just been staying up until 9 a.m. or staying up until noon the next day drawing,
and I don't want to reset.
So I just said, I'll just ignore what time it is, and now I don't know.
Now I'm just...
Now I don't...
I never know what time it is, so I just work until I'm too tired, and then I go to bed.
And that's my life.
That's the way to do it.
If you can.
Is it more of a that you don't want to know what time of day it is, or that you can't get
to sleep with daylight?
Both.
I mean, I always do know what time it is, so that's...
I wish I didn't know what time it was, but no, I can't go to sleep when the windows open
and there's a sun.
I can't go to sleep with the sun.
Oh, Jesus, a fucking garage door opening under me.
Is that loud?
A little bit.
You know, our dad had his office was built into the building, or like the room right
above our garage, where he would, you know, he's a psychologist, he would have like patients
there, and all the time he would just get fucked up when we'd come home and open the
garage door.
I still wonder why he chose to put it there.
I don't know if it's...
It's not a choice.
Never mind, never mind.
All right, anyway, Digi, I was curious.
I mean, you've talked about this many times before, but you've got a friend who was like
a professional Hikikomori for a while.
Yeah, like full blown.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Yeah, it was at a time when, you know, I was in high school, was probably my most, like,
well, I don't know, it's hard to say.
I mean, obviously right now I'm the most Hikikomori because I have no social obligations at all,
and when I was in high school, I was going to high school.
But like, back then was when I was the most, like, paranoid about going outside and like,
you know, I had, luckily at the time, well, luckily for this lifestyle, there was a bathroom
that was right at the bottom of my stairs.
Like I had, my room was a room over the garage, which it is as well now, but now I have my
own bathroom.
But there was a bathroom at the bottom of the stairs, and a door, like, basically like,
I would go down the stairs and to the left is a bathroom, to the right is a door, right?
Yeah.
I'd keep that door closed for the most part.
And I would always, like, I was always paranoid when I was like, because I was doing pretty
bad in school and stuff, and just generally my mind was falling apart at this point in
my life.
Uh-huh.
The same time as the story I told in the school episode, like, this is that time.
Oh, yeah, right, right.
Okay, sure.
Yeah.
So, I was like, I didn't want to see anybody, like, I would always be worried that if my
parents, like, saw me, they'd ask me questions about, like, how school is going.
Oh, yeah, very understandable, sure.
And so, I, yeah, so I would go down the stairs, like, you know, real quiet, and then go to
the bathroom, like, real quick, and leave, and then I wouldn't, you know, I wouldn't
go into the kitchen or anything, I wouldn't, like, go into the rest of the house.
And this is when I started, um, like, because I would, like, for drinks, like, all I drink
was Mountain Dew at the time.
Yeah.
And I'd get, like, a two liter of Mountain Dew, and I'd pour myself, like, this, I'd
have this huge cup, and I'd just fill it up to the top and take it up to my room and
just be drinking that, like, all day, and not leave, you know.
Like anything to not leave my room, um, because I was so worried that if anybody saw me, they
were gonna, like, I don't know, I, I don't know about you guys, but do you ever feel
like, uh, your emotions should be more readable than they are?
Like, um, yes, I understand that, yeah, I know what you mean.
It took me a long time to realize that, like, my depression was not on my face, like, because
I would always wonder why nobody was asking me what's wrong, because, like, I'd be, there
would be times where I'd be, like, at dinner, and I'd just be, like, crushingly depressed
and have, and, like, all I'm thinking is, like, someone please ask me what's wrong,
because I look, I feel like I look terrible, but then I'd look at myself in the mirror
and I'd look completely normal, you know, but, like, I'm basically going all full feel
guy right there.
I'm the opposite.
All my life, people have been asking me what's wrong, even though I'm fine.
I'm not kidding, like, something about my face or something, like, in school, people
would be like, oh, are you okay, you look sad, and I'd be like, what?
It's, it's fine.
I've seen, I've seen a little bit of that, I've seen some moments where I saw you and
you looked like you were gonna cry, and then I talked to you, you were okay, and I burned
a car.
Yeah, um, I, other people have said that, and I don't get it, but, uh, whatever.
Yeah.
Man, that's, that's interesting.
But you know, did you, I can totally relate to, uh, when me and Ben were growing up, like,
we would, uh, it's not like we would hide, but like, we would go upstairs to our rooms,
and we knew if we came downstairs and saw our dad, our dad might make us do things,
you know.
Oh my God.
He might make us do chores.
Oh God.
Or make us take out the trash, and at the time, I would do whatever it took to avoid having
to do that.
Yeah, same.
I don't, I don't want to, I don't, okay, if it's the same for you, then maybe this
isn't that important.
I just, our dad, I don't want to go on a big thing about our dad, but like, his, his,
he always like, he always like needed, I don't know if you felt this way, Nate, but he always
needed me to be doing something, even if nothing needed to be done.
Dude.
That was the biggest thing.
Seeing me not doing something would make, would irritate him, even if nothing needed
to be done, it would irritate him so much that he would make me do something totally
unnecessary.
To this day, I'm uncomfortable playing video games unless I'm like locked in my room alone,
because if, if whenever I hear someone come along, I feel this pain, like this sudden
panic and guilt, like I'm going to get in trouble for like doing something fun instead
of doing the work I'm supposed to be doing.
Dad, dad would be mad.
He made me a fucked up guy.
Dad would be mad just for seeing us play video games, even if it was totally fine.
But, alright, I don't, I also don't want to get into a big thing about that, but it was,
it wasn't enough for him that like we do our chores.
What he wanted, he wanted us to like, want to volunteer.
Yes, he was like extra things.
He would lecture us about this.
It's not enough that you do the things I ask you to do.
You should be doing them without me asking.
Dude, it's exactly like, it's exactly like that speech.
You should be volunteering to clean the yard and do the dishes.
Oh my God.
Dude, it's just like an office space.
When that boss was lecturing, yeah, go on.
My dad did something similar.
He was never as, my dad was never as like a strict with us, but he would always get
mad at us that like, he'd be like, and y'all like never do the dishes.
And I'm like, well, you never say do the dishes.
Whenever you say do the dishes, someone does them.
And he's like, I shouldn't have to be saying do the dishes.
I'm like, well, the thing is that like, well, it's like, it's like not understanding a difference
in values, right?
Like to my dad, he's, my dad was in the Navy and like you had to keep your room perfectly
clean.
Right, right.
And he's kind of a neat freak anyways.
I live with a guy in the Navy right now who's, who's kind of the same about like our
business and shit.
And so like to him, when he sees mess, he registers it as a problem in his life that
there is, that he comes home to a messy house, whereas for me, I come home to a messy house
and that's just what it is.
It's, I don't care.
Like there's nothing about what I'm seeing feels wrong to me.
That is the exact same.
And I've felt this the same way about like the difference between me and my dad.
Like my dad is like, what are you, what are you doing that your, your, your room is messy?
And I'm like, why, why shouldn't it be messy?
What's the, what's the big deal?
There's a, there's a clear difference in values there, but you know, I understand how this
might sound.
And I don't want it to come across like, because I too, like now that I'm an adult, I understand
that like when I see that there's things that can be done, it's, it's not like you have
an opt in or opt out only option to like everything in your life.
Like it's good to, to contribute to the environment in which you live.
It's like a responsible adult thing to do.
And it's good.
And like to not do it could be construed as generally shitty.
Well, here's a funny thing because you guys both moved out when you became adults.
Oh, that is not.
No, that's not true.
Oh, in that sense.
Yes.
In that sense.
You went off to live in dorms.
We came back for a while.
Me and Victor and Shade all still live at home.
And at some point, at some point around when Victor graduated, I guess, maybe even earlier,
when I graduated, my dad realized this difference.
Like he finally, it's like clicked in his head that we were never going to care about
certain things.
Right.
And so he just stopped asking and started hiring people, like for the, the lawn, our,
our house, he has like a whole team of yard workers who come like every weekend or so during
the summer.
Ben, have you had to do those stakes on the, on the goddamn perimeter trees anytime recently
in recent years?
He has to do all of the yard work.
A year ago.
Yeah.
Oh God.
It's, it's, my dad has never learned that lesson and never will.
He will insist.
Well, he would, you know, cause, cause people would always say, you have three strong, strapping
young boys.
Why are none of them doing the yard work?
You know, he'd always say that and stuff and I'm like, because I don't go outside.
I don't see the yard and when I do see it, the fact that it's two inches longer doesn't
bother me.
I don't care.
It looks fine.
It's a, it's grass.
It's supposed to be long.
I don't know.
Yeah.
My dad would like, he would like, see me come downstairs and be like, Ben, you're not doing
anything.
I'm automatically upset about this.
Uh, here's some mulch, go and spread it in the yard.
And then I'd be like, well, since you asked, okay, and I go out and I spend, you know,
like an hour or two, like fucking spreading mulch on the flower beds or whatever or something.
And then, yeah, this is the sort of thing he would say.
He would come out and look at this mulched yard and be like, now, Ben, he would like
sort of indulgently, like smilingly be like, I got him now.
Like now, now, Ben, look at this.
Look what you've done.
Look at this yard.
Doesn't this look better?
Like, isn't this satisfying to you?
Don't you feel like you've done something good here?
And I'm like, no, shut up, stop, stop trying to make, stop trying to make me care about
what I've been doing.
Yeah.
And that's the thing.
That's how it ties into this.
Because for, for a lot of us, our world doesn't extend to the perimeter, the outside lawn
of the house that we're living in.
For us guys, we're like, we're, we're, you know, we're, we're ghosts living in the
shell of the internet.
My world does not extend beyond my room.
Like, I mean, yeah, like my, my mom does the dishes and, uh, like these days and like,
if there was one thing that I, that I feel the slightest bit bad about not doing, it
would be the dishes.
Cause I'll just leave my plates down there and let whoever is going to clean them, take
care of them.
But other than that, like as I've grown up, um, because like we all eat or we all like
get our own food now at this point, like no one, we're not like meeting downstairs for
dinner.
I don't go downstairs much.
I, I have no opportunities to mess up anything else in the house.
So as far as I'm concerned, it's not my house really, you know, like the yard outside, like
if, if it was, if, if my dad was like, uh, the yard is partly your responsibility cause
you live here.
I'd be like, no, the yard is your yard.
I don't, I don't interact with the yard.
It's not my yard.
If it was up to me, if I lived in my own place, I would get a place without a yard.
See, you know, that's, that's, that's where our dad had a different mentality.
Because we lived in that house with him, he viewed that like, okay, you're benefiting
from this lawn.
You're living in a nice place.
Yeah.
But are you really, I mean, the thing about that is, yeah, I agree with you that no, I'm
not really getting anything out of the yard.
And if I had a place, I wouldn't own a yard.
So like, uh, it's your responsibility dad.
I agree with that on the one hand, but on the other hand, like lawn maintenance contributes
to the overall value of the house and the value of the house is well, I know that's why
he cares about it.
Yeah.
And that's, that's just like, that's just like protecting your investment in the house
base.
I've come to understand that is like the purpose of lawn care is so that the value of your
house does not fall.
Okay, sure.
And my dad is constantly like refinancing the house and like doing stuff like that with
it.
But, uh, but you know, for me, it was like the second I started paying rent, then it
was like, all right, I no longer feel like, cause, cause a lot of the obligation is like,
well, I'm living here for free.
So I should be doing things to help my dad.
But if I'm not living here for free, then, uh, I'm doing my part and I'm giving you money.
You can use my money to pay the guys who mow the lawn.
And now like I live in an apartment, I stay in my room, I do my work.
I don't give a shit about the fucking lawn outside.
What am I going to do?
Go mow the lawn?
Why?
No, never.
Not in a million years.
I think of doing anything for the lawn outside and that's, you know, that's the place I want
to be in life where I don't have to be loaded up with these extra worries about things.
I'm much more concerned with getting, using my time to get my fucking work done because
the nature of the work that all of us are trying to do is like spent as much time as
possible doing your shit so that you can fucking make it out there.
So I was living in this place where the people on the lease were being evicted and no one
was paying any rent and it was a very stressful situation.
We were all afraid every day that the landlord was going to show up with this sheriff and
either evict us or just murder us or something or just burn the house down.
He actually came into our basement uninvited and unannounced one time and cut our internet
cord to try and fuck the landlord.
Yeah, the landlord actually came in and physically chopped the internet cord in half.
We were without internet for several weeks while we were trying to figure out what was
going on.
Yeah, man.
It was fucked.
His name was, that guy's name was Charlie Tseng, but Charlie was his American name.
His actual name was Dragon.
His name was Dragon Tseng.
Awesome.
Holy shit.
Was he in a Yakuza?
What do you think?
More likely the Triad.
Yeah, the Triad.
All right, go on.
Anyway, anyway.
And I also lived with this, a couple of guys, but one of them was a really stressful, heavily
bipolar dude who was always like, he just had weird manic episodes where he would like
make us all move furniture around and like get me.
And whenever I got involved with him, it was always this big fucking thing.
It would always take like an hour and a half of like him deciding where all the furniture
was going to go.
And like, I couldn't leave.
I couldn't get out of it.
It was very annoying.
Anyway, all of this is to say that the stress of this environment made me so hesitant to
leave my room that I was actually peeing in two liter bottles for a while because I didn't
want to walk to the bathroom.
I knew we had to get to that because that seems, to me, that is the thing.
The Hikikomori technique.
That's when you know.
Really?
That you've arrived at Hikikomori.
I was.
I was for a while.
That's very interesting.
Yeah, go on, go on.
I do not understand why all I would have had to do was walk to the bathroom and walk back.
This is like, it was not a complicated thing.
Looking back, I don't understand why I decided this was the right thing to do, but I did and
I won't apologize for it.
That makes some sense to me, but what doesn't make sense to me to this day is that when I
was a freshman in college, my roommate, James, was a super alpha drug dealer and he was a
pretty cool guy.
Alpha drug dealer.
Yeah.
Why do you say that he was, was being a drug dealer making more alpha?
No, no, no.
Those two things were separate.
He just happened to be a drug dealer.
He wasn't a bitch at all.
He was on the baseball team.
He fucked bitches constantly.
He sold a little bit of drugs and he was just, he was a pretty cool guy.
We didn't really talk much, but he was all right.
But the point is like, for whatever reason, one day we had a recycling bin, I look in
the bottom of the recycling bin and there's just bottles of piss.
There's just bottles of piss down there and thinking back on it now, in fact, this is
just a current in me right now.
I had assumed, I see do this in the middle of the night sometimes and I was like, what
is this?
And so the next day I took the bottle, put it on his desk and just said like, this has
to stop.
I didn't even speak to him about it.
It's so confrontational about it.
Well, I just didn't know what to do.
I was completely thrown.
This has to stop.
Yeah.
And, but you know, thinking back on it now, I'm wondering if he was maybe saving clean
piss for some sort of exam.
Well, maybe he would have been keeping them in the fridge then.
That's true.
He wouldn't have put them in the trash can.
I just think he didn't want to leave the room.
Maybe it's that when he was on drugs, he didn't want to be seen by anybody.
Maybe he wouldn't leave the room.
Maybe he had.
It seems likely to be.
Maybe he, yeah, maybe it was he was saving piss, but like they'd been there too long
and they were too old or something or maybe he had gotten through the test he was saving
up for and he didn't need them anymore or something.
Why would you need that much piss?
That there were multiple bottles.
There were literally several bottles full of piss at the bottom of the recycling bin.
I think the best logical reason would be that he didn't want to be outside his room when
he was on drugs.
All right.
If that's the case, if that's the case, then he still was pulling a boner move by not getting
rid of them the next day and leaving them there to pile up in our shared room.
Fuck you James, you're all right though.
That friend of mine who was a Hickey Comrie to get back to that story, because God, we
got on a 20 minute sidetrack.
You guys are at 25 minutes, right?
Yeah, about 23 or so.
Yeah.
23 or so?
23 or so.
It just hit 24.
Okay.
Well, that's right.
I think I started.
You probably started before us.
Yeah.
I'm making sure because it looked like it was like somehow the time was going faster than
it should be.
It was why I wanted to stop my recording.
Yeah.
Okay.
It looked like seconds were going by in half seconds on the recording.
Weird.
Yeah.
It was really bizarre looking.
But the recording itself looked fine, like the waveforms looked fine.
I don't know.
It was fucking weird.
Anyway, yeah, when I was in high school and I was talking to my friend, like he had cluster
headaches and he just stopped coming to school because like he would get them in the morning
and it would just be like a severe debilitating migraine that would happen at like 6 a.m.
And it could last up to like hours.
And so it would just happen every single day.
Like every day on the news, he'd get a giant headache.
And if you look into cluster headaches, they're like a weird thing that like is not well documented,
like medically.
It only became like a known phenomenon like 10 years ago.
Yeah.
We had a neighbor who got those who would occasionally, they should get mad at us for
like our dog barking too much and aggravating your shit.
But yeah, it sucks.
I wouldn't want to live like that.
It was crazy because like it's something that everyone who had it, it would be different.
Like each migraine would have a different intensity.
Some people had it like multiple times a day.
Some people had it like, you know, just once a day.
Sometimes it was on a schedule.
Sometimes it wasn't like everyone had a totally different case of it.
And they had no idea what the cure was or anything.
So he became a part of a experimental like thing to like try to find a cure.
And it ended up being literally psychedelic mushrooms.
And he hasn't had one since and that was like 2008 or 2009.
So he basically got the Eric Andre, feed them LSD, link arms in a circle, scream nightmare
and cured his retardation or in this case, his cluster headaches.
Yeah.
Because of those, because of him not going to school because of the cluster headaches,
like from what I understand, because he told me about himself in middle school and it sounds
like he was pretty normal in middle school.
Like he listened to a lot of hip hop hung out with other kids his age, you know, like
just was just a normal Asian middle school.
That's the gateway drug.
Yeah.
And then once he got like in late middle school, early high school, he started getting the cluster
headaches and he became a full blown otaku and just dedicated himself to just sitting
in his room watching hundreds of anime and playing like he was one of those guys who
played like every video game, seen every anime, read every manga, like he did all of it because
he had nothing but time and he had no real interest in like making things.
So he would just sit there and consume all of the information on the internet, essentially.
He was like, he was a fucking genius.
He knew like, he managed to get his, like he got his GED and he like passed all the
tests without even studying.
He just like walked in and took them all and got a hundred because he just knew everything.
But like, but because of the cluster headaches, he couldn't come to school and so he would
just be in his room all the time and he told me that like before he met me, there was a
period where he reached a level of paranoia where he wouldn't leave his room at all.
Like his parents would leave food at his door.
Oh, hardcore.
He'd wait till nobody was around and drag the tray in, you know, like sometimes he'd
get like super paranoid and start pissing in bottles and not even, he's like right next
to a bathroom.
Crazy shit happens to you when you're isolated.
Yeah.
It's just like you get these, these weird ideas.
I mean, there was a few times where I was like, I almost was pissing in bottles.
Just I couldn't, I couldn't bring myself to do it.
It was weird because like, didn't expect to be so important in this podcast, but yeah,
no, I remember a time where like I had, I had like an empty two liter bottle and I'm
sitting there like, just contemplating, like really having to piss and like holding my
dick over this thing and I'm like, I can't do it.
I'm seeing, I'm seeing like, I'm seeing Digi like push himself back from his computer,
like slump down in his chair and then like, and then like his head turns to the side and
then the camera focus changes and he blurs out and in the foreground, the bottle comes
into focus and he's just like, oh my God.
The fish I let zoom on it.
Yeah, I could never bring myself to just piss in bottles, but but I had a lot of times
where like I got to that level kids at home.
Don't do it.
Don't fucking do it.
If you're thinking it might be a good idea.
Yeah, just go.
It's not.
It's not the answer to your problems.
OK, however much it might seem like it, what was always funny to me about it is that it's
not that weird to piss in a bottle.
Like it doesn't, it doesn't mean anything.
It won't do anything bad.
Like it's there's nothing wrong with it.
It's totally like some people have like a mouth nearing trick to like keep yourself high.
Well, here's, here's what I found about it.
Once I started, it was very easy to continue.
Once, once I pissed in that first bottle, I was just, I was just like, well, this is
OK. Once you pop, you can't, you know, it really is an issue of it's not the answer
to your problems you're looking for.
You know, you can do it.
Like if you do it once in a while, no big deal.
You know that Casey Green cart or comic of the dog sitting in a room full of fire and
he's like, this is fine.
Yes.
Just imagine me sitting in a room full of bottles of piss.
With a little coffee cup full of piss.
And I looked down into the, and I looked down into the piss filled cup and I go, this is fine.
And then he picks it up and takes a long slurp.
You see, that's where you go.
That's the path they're going down.
Yeah, basically.
I could, I could decide if I want to get into a whole unrelated piss story or we just
want to sit you with the piss cast dude, go for it, go for it.
All right.
Well, when I was getting my job at Target, I had to take like a piss test
to the doctor and like I was sitting there waiting for them to like call me in.
And I'm like drinking a bottle of water, you know, trying to get myself ready to piss.
And I had like by the time she called me, I had to pee more than I've ever had to pee
in my entire life.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
So she calls me back and like there's two women working at this clinic that I'm at.
One who's they're both like fat black ladies, one at the register
and one who's taking me back to do the test.
And they're both just pissed.
Like they both seem like they have no desire to be there or to be alive at this moment.
Understandable.
She she calls me back and like the the the the room where they do the test is just
it's like a a bathroom that's like real small.
It's just like a toilet and a sink behind you.
Yeah. Right.
And it's one of those real narrow ones.
But she was like standing right outside the door and had the door slightly open
because like I guess they have to make sure you don't try to, you know,
yeah, yeah, yes, whatever.
And I get like really bad like piss paranoia.
Like I don't want people to hear me.
I don't want them to be next to me while trying to pee.
You know, like I've always had a problem with that.
I've sort of incurving it over the last few years because of this incident
making me realize how much of a problem it was.
But I I'm standing there with like the cup in my hand.
I have to pee more than I've ever had to pee and I cannot make myself pee.
And I'm standing there like trying with all my like pushing with all the force
of my body and it won't work.
And finally, the lady's like she she keeps like going like where are you up in there?
You know, in the green mile.
I don't know. I haven't seen the green.
He had a yeah, but she keeps saying like hurry up in there.
And I'm like, I can't I can't like I can't make it happen.
And she was like, well, you're taking too long.
So now you have to go wait again.
What? So she sends me back out to the.
Yeah, because if you're taking too long, like you could be trying to rig it or something.
So she sends me back out to the lobby and makes me like a re wait for this test.
And at this point, I'm like, things feel like they're rupturing inside me.
Like I actually felt like I was dying because I had to pee so bad.
And I'm like sweating and shit.
And I'm like, I'm tempted to just go to the bathroom because I have to pee so much.
And I'm like, I can't wait for this anymore.
Like I've got to die, you know, and then finally she called me back again.
And I had to like pull my pants all the way off and like sit down and like angle
my dick right into the bottom of the cup and like push with all of my might.
Like it never, you know, a lot of the times when like if you're if you're
if you feel awkward in like a bathroom, then you might like it might take you
a minute to get started. But then once you start, you kind of ease up.
You're like, OK, now I feel relieved.
This was not like that.
Every ounce of it had to be pushed.
It was like me standing there like, ah, ah.
Just on the green mile.
It feels like I'm pissing glass, he said.
Yeah. Oh, God, that is what it what it felt like.
It was a fucking nightmare.
And I filled that cup up to the max.
And then I had to keep going into the toilet afterwards.
Oh, man, that's brutal.
That's hard. It was fucking horrifying.
But yeah, anyway, about not leaving your room.
It's all related.
So this is integral to the story of every need.
I guess so.
Well, let me let me let me tell you, I live in I live in a house with a bunch
of guys and they're all they're they're pretty cool guys that we're friends.
And for a while, I had what I would almost describe as an act of social life.
I would go out and hang out in the living room and have conversations with people.
Imagine that. Imagine.
But I've been living here for like six months now.
And I kind of feel like the honeymoon is over.
That's exactly right.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
Yeah, damn, like, like, like now we've hung out enough.
Like, I know who they are.
They're not surprising me anymore.
Like, I get it.
So I'm just like, OK, well, nice knowing you.
Have a have a good life.
You know, you know, just, you know, I'm now I'd stay in my room all the time.
I've noticed that all my friends are really boring
unless they're doing something new, you know, unless they're exposing me
to something interesting when it's happening.
I'll just, you know, I've I've known a bunch of people for my entire life.
And I don't really care about their shit anymore
because it's the same shit they've been doing for years.
I mean, I'm friends with a bunch of people that still come over and like,
I don't know, they we we used to share hobbies.
But now I've like, I've like given up all my old hobbies.
All I want to do is do my art and shit.
Yes, all I want to do is describing my life.
I like I used to I used to be into, you know, playing Dungeons and Dragons
and playing board games and Magic the Gathering.
Now I think that all those things are just big fucking waste of time.
And I hate them and I feel like I'm disappointing them sometimes.
And they're like, yeah, we're going to do this.
Do you want to like, no, goodbye?
Dude, just my co-workers invited me out to go see some fucking rom-com movie.
And it just sounded like the absolute worst possible use of my time.
And I was like, no, of course I don't want to go.
Why on earth would you even think that I would go?
I would go and see a movie.
We'll see. I thought about it.
And I was like, you know what?
I could put in the effort to make this relationship between us just a little
healthier, but this movie sounds horrific.
There's no chance I'm going to go watch this movie.
And what what is the benefit of this relationship long term of these?
The only way it could ever pay off is if I, I don't know,
like get some social group thing going where I feel a rewarding connection with.
But I don't these people are fine.
My co-workers are totally cool people, but we definitely don't share interests.
You know, so how many months of time am I going to have to like water
this little seed to make it bloom into a relationship
that I can get something out of?
I don't know. I don't have the time for that.
I got videos to make.
Yeah. You know, that's why the PCP is such a healthy group
because we stay interested in the shit that each other's doing.
I think that I think that the basis of a great and healthy friendship
is that the two partner, the two members of the friendship,
mutually benefit one another. Yeah.
And like if if hanging out with a friend is just you like
emptily indulging in like hobbies that you don't aren't interested in
or just like, you know, shooting the shit, I don't know, drinking beer,
waxing about the good old days. What do you get out of that?
Nothing. Right.
Totally agree. Waxing about the good old days.
One of the things I least like to do the only time I hang out with my friends
at all is when I like want to get fucked up drunk because it's not fun.
You know, which I also don't do anymore
because it's a waste of time and it irritates. Oh God, I did it yesterday.
It was the worst time of my entire life.
I never drank alcohol ever again.
You were very sick yesterday.
I sure was.
PSP had to be postponed. I mean, PCP.
So, um, me and that that friend of mine, becoming friends,
right, a huge part of it, like a huge basis of how we became so close,
was welcome to the NHK, the anime about Higikomariness,
which I still haven't seen it, but I want to.
I watched it recently and it changed my life.
One of the best shows I've ever seen in my entire life.
Yeah. And it was, uh, because at the time,
because this was 2007 and that show aired in 05 or 06.
I think it was in 05, but yeah, whatever.
I think it ran between them.
Either way, I saw it in early 07 and it was like my favorite show for a long time
because, you know, I was a heke, a borderline Hikikomori at the time.
You know, I didn't trust people.
I was paranoid about everything.
And so this show was like, man, this really speaks to my life.
But the funny thing is that, like, um, I think one of the most important things
about Welcome to the NHK is that even though Sato kind of gets out of it at the end,
yeah, the there's this implication that he's like, it's not complete.
Oh, dude, the little monsters are still there.
They're hanging around trying to get back in.
And if you read the original novel, which is a lot darker, every pony, baby steps.
Yeah, the novel is a lot darker than the anime.
And at the end of it, like, because there's like an afterword for the, you know,
like after like a year had passed since he wrote the novel.
And the guy was like, you know, all I've been doing is living off the residuals
from this book and sitting around and still being a Hikikomori.
He's like, he was like, I tried to write this like as a way to maybe
write my way out of it, and it did not work.
And since then, he's he's only written like a few books like for a Japanese
creator, he is not prolific.
Like most Japanese creators are obscenely prolific.
He is not at all.
He really did just like coop up inside himself and like remain a paranoid man.
And like all the books he's written are all about the subject of paranoia and stuff.
It kills me that anyone has to live like that.
When I know the problem is solvable, just with like that's how it was for me,
though, because I watched the show and like it was kind of because my favorite
moment in the show I've brought this up before is like when they meet the other.
Hikikomori. Oh, yeah, like I've read every self-help book there is.
I could probably write a self-help book, but I'm still a Hikikomori.
And the only thing that gets that guy out of the situation is when his lifelines
cut off and he has to literally get a job to live.
Yeah, that's what finally gets him out of being.
Oh, God, that scene is so fucking wonderful.
Everything about it rules.
That seems fantastic.
And like for me, I watched the show so I understood like the nature
of what I was dealing with and how to get out of it.
But there was no actual like thing making me out of it.
I was still in high school.
I was still miserable with my school.
Man, you can't do shit when you're in high school anyway.
Yeah, nothing could change it.
Because like all because I was determined to drop out at the time.
Like all I wanted was to drop out of school and be like,
I'm going to go become a director because school is making me miserable.
Yeah, like no one was going to let me drop out.
You know, people are constantly telling me no.
And I didn't have the balls to just like up and, you know,
leave or anything like that, because I would think about running away every day.
I was always like, I'm just going to fucking go out on my own and find my own path.
But I didn't know how to do that.
So yeah, I'm going to I'm going to go out with with a wooden sword
and slay and slay mobs until one of them drops a legendary artifact
camera so that I can use this rare camera drop to become a director.
That's the only way I can see it working.
So me me and well, I had a nice camera.
My dad bought me a nice camera for this purpose and we never used it.
So and then it broke.
So life. Well, I have one of my roommates is kind of a of a shut in.
And he he's a pretty nice guy.
But let me let me tell you two things that stick out to me about him.
One, if he gets even a little drunk, he starts to become like more open and more fun.
Yeah, like he starts to become like kind of a more outgoing guy.
But he also at the same time and in the same stroke,
starts to get nervous about the fact that he's drunk and it makes him worried
and he retreats to his room.
So as soon as he starts to get fun and loosen up, he's like, oh, no,
I'm loosening up and then he runs away.
The other thing the other thing is that like he goes out to eat a bunch,
but he has very specific things.
He won't he won't go to the same place twice.
Ever if well, like in too close proximity.
Like one time he went he went to this rest.
He went to stop and he doesn't want them to learn who he is essentially.
It's it. No, it's like it's well, sort of.
He went to Whole Foods and he bought a bunch of stuff and he came back
and then he was like, oh, man, I forgot the flour or something.
And I was like, you know what, I used to be like this too.
I would never go. I don't I didn't want I still am a little bit.
Like I feel like it's weird if I go somewhere that you wouldn't
ordinarily go twice in a row.
Yeah, and I'm like, well, if you need it, you know, you're going to go get it.
And he's like, no, I can't go back.
I was there earlier today.
Oh, man, you know, I can't know that I was there twice.
That's really like who fucking cares?
This really touches on something for me that I think is maybe
like a root cause of this whole issue.
Like having a life living and doing things with purpose,
like with a goal, with a mission makes like all these weird
like depression and like self-conference issues.
They all kind of just fly out the window.
I like have to do something like like example.
If like, I had probably needed that flour for something important.
Why would he care about what?
First of all, why would anyone care ever about what the employees
that Whole Foods think about? I'm like, oh, what a weirdo.
Well, that's a whole logic, you know.
Yeah, it's an emotional thing.
But yeah, but if there's something you actually need,
if there's an actual good reason that really would compel you to get that flour,
you would go back, you wouldn't care.
Some people rationalize, you know, whatever for whatever fear they have.
They'll say, well, I guess I didn't really need it.
You know, I can go. You know what? The weirdest thing.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. But if you really did, you would get it.
Right. Yeah, totally, totally.
Which is the same thing that made it. God damn it.
OK, go on, go on, go on.
The weirdest thing about my like brand of paranoia when it comes to that kind
of stuff, Ben, is that like I always say, like, I don't care what anybody
thinks about me, right? And like, yeah, it's weird because my sense of self
image is like, I'll dress however I want.
I'll look like a weirdo.
I don't like I'm not bothered that people think I look weird.
And yet when I'm out in public, I constantly am thinking about what
do people think I look like?
Like, yeah, yeah, I'm so fixated on myself and like because if I go out
in like any kind of My Little Pony attire with the beard I have,
I always think I look like a pedophile and you're right everywhere I go.
I'm like, does everyone think I'm a weird fucking pedophile?
Does everyone here think I'm like some kind of rapist?
Like when in reality, they're probably thinking nothing about me.
They don't have any opinion, you know?
Yeah, I got I got catcalled the other day.
No way by a pat by a driving bro.
Well, because I was dressed like a fucking clown, right?
I was wearing I was wearing like two different bright plaids,
like a bright plaid orange.
That's how I dress normally.
A button down shirt and a bright like starburst colors, like plaid long shorts.
I looked like it like, oh, we've also with long black socks.
So I looked like I was wearing stockings because the shorts.
Dude, you were rocking the you were rocking the cluster punk aesthetic.
I guess so.
Dude, I took it.
I took a picture of me with a giant with a giant scale model of Bender
from Futurama that we found in the trash the other day.
It lives in our house now.
Yeah, we have Bender. Bender lives in our house now.
He's great. That's awesome.
Yeah, it is.
I'll post a picture on Twitter sometime.
But anyway, the point is some guy slowed down, passing me in my stupid clown outfit
and he yelled out the window that outfit is on point, brother.
And I was like, that's cool.
And I just I gave him a salute.
I just gave him like a thumbs up because like I could have taken it like,
oh, I feel bad that this guy made fun of me.
But like, yeah, I don't know.
We'll see. He's just saying hi.
I hear what you're saying, Ben.
But like if you watch and I, you know, I don't really have much experience
with depression, but like the NHK guy, Satato, yeah, Sato.
Like when he he tells the story about when he first tried to go to college
on like his first day, like he he didn't even have an experience like that.
But he just like was out walking and just like felt so much pressure
from everyone's stairs at him that he just like completely panicked
and just like even though no one was even though nothing happened.
Yeah, that's that's what my that's like what I related to the most back then.
It was like I would go out and just and I still feel this way.
I always feel like people are like looking at me when they're not.
And like, I'll actually go out somewhere and like start to feel weird.
And I'll look around to see if anyone's looking at me.
I think it's like to confirm that they're not because I wouldn't do that before.
Like I'd walk into Barnes and Noble and I just look straight down.
Like I was always one of those guys who looked down everywhere I walked, you know.
And so I would just like I would just look down
and try not to like make eye contact with anybody.
And I always think like, oh, I look like the fucking of course
I'm going to the manga aisle because I look like a fucking weirdo.
Like, yeah, that's exactly who you expect to see looking at the anime stuff, you know, like.
And then I'd get there and no one's no one cares.
Yeah, no one cares.
It gives a fuck, you know.
Yeah, yeah, totally.
And even if they did care, it doesn't matter.
Even today, like when I walk into Barnes and Noble,
like my first instinct is like, oh, God, I look weird.
But then I have to go, wait a minute, I like looking weird.
I've chosen to dress this way.
I've chosen to have this beard and I'm proud of myself.
That alternative lifestyle like right.
Then I like pick myself up and go, like, did I say,
did I tell you the story one time about how me and Ben were driving
and he told me that he wanted to look alternative
and I've been giving him shit about it for years ever since he said that
because I looked like a weirdo and yeah, my rationalization for the fact
that I know I had like a weird haircut or something.
I think I like, I don't know, I had a weird haircut.
That's the point.
And Nate was like, why don't you get a normal haircut?
And I was like, if I haven't, if I look normal,
if I have a normal haircut, then people will see me and think I'm a normal guy.
Yes, that's not me.
I want people to see me and understand that like I am like a weird guy.
God, that's stupid.
That's what you told me at the time.
No, I'm with you, Ben.
Yeah, if a girl saw me, if a girl saw me and was like this guy,
he looks like he works a nine to five job.
I don't want girls that like guys with nine to five jobs to see me
and be like, I mean, I want girl.
I want girls who want a fucking loser weirdo.
That's exactly why I have that kind of girl to see me and be like,
now there's a guy.
Yeah, yeah.
I often think about like, hey, if I'm ever going to get into the dating scene,
I got to clean myself up.
But then I think about it and I'm like, well, if I clean myself up,
no, I'm just going to be selling a false product.
Like, you need to present what you actually are so that the girls
that actually like that can recognize it and be like,
exactly, yeah, like those girls might be harder to come by,
but they're the only ones who are worth having.
Yeah, there's no otherwise you're just going to the veils
going to come off pretty quick.
There's no point attracting a girl who's looking for something
other than what you are.
Well, there's a lot of girls out there who don't know what they want.
You know, that's true.
I guess so. Just saying.
But whatever. You see my point. I hear your point.
I do. I do.
I just think it's funny to say, oh, Ben's into that alternative lifestyle.
Well, but it's true, though, I do.
I don't lead a normal life.
I don't have a job. I'm a fucking artist.
All right, Ben, you've got to get in on the cluster punk aesthetic.
Here's how you become a cluster punk.
Yeah, tell me.
Every everything you wear has to be either pajamas or plaid.
Well, I am wearing all plaid, but
and or or an anime shirt or some kind of like video.
I've heard that I've heard that.
I've heard that what's in this year is Pail Wave.
What the fuck is that?
It's just like you wear like pastel T-shirts, just pastel colors.
Pail Wave is the movement, is the fashion movement.
I haven't heard that word for it.
But yeah, no, man, I'm all about like, because all I wear is pajamas,
either pajama pants or pajama shorts.
And then if you want to go full cluster punk,
which I do not have the balls to rock this in public anymore.
I have done it before.
But it's to put your plaid shorts over your pajama pants.
Oh, my God.
And the reason for this technique is that
the reason for this technique is
a lot of pajama pants don't have pockets.
Kids do not buy this at all.
If you want to have if you want to wear your pajama pants that don't have pockets,
but you want to have pockets,
they just put on a pair of shorts over your pajamas and they have pockets.
Why would you eat?
Why even wear the pajamas?
Why not just wear shorts?
Because it's maybe it's cold outside and.
Yeah, you don't want to wear pants.
Yeah, OK.
I mean, like I said, this is something that I mean,
there's enough ways to not do this that I would rather just change my pants
so that people don't fucking laugh at me openly in public.
But maybe don't be a scrub and get some pajama pants with dude.
But at the same time, if I wanted to go full cluster punk, this is what I would do.
I mean, because when you think about it,
because that's what punk is all about is looking like an absolute freak in public
and embracing the fact that people are staring at your crazy gauges
and giant spiky hair.
Yeah, yeah.
So if I if you really, to me, the moment it goes from just cluster fuck
to cluster punk is when you decide to go all out
and wear the the the shorts over the pajama pants.
That's when you've got cluster punk.
I kind of like it.
I like it, too.
Because that is, you know, that's that alternative lifestyle
that I'm always seeing that I'm always famous for quest questing after.
Back.
And no, but I think a lot of this relates to the peacocking of of pickup.
I was I was, you know, yeah, I was I was a lot better than blending in
if you're trying to get people's attention.
Yeah, standing out is better than blending in, just like you got it.
You got to you got to be noticeable.
The thing that the OK,
what you were saying before about feeling like people are staring at you,
even when they're not, I get that.
I felt that way before.
So in secure.
Yeah, I don't I don't really feel it so much anymore.
Now, the worst thing about going out and leaving the house is is girls.
I hate seeing them when they don't love me.
You know what? I'm completely with you, Ben.
If I see you, if I see a cute girl and I'm like, I see a cute girl
and I'm like, you idiot, you stupid idiot.
You've never.
How do you not recognize that I am the coolest?
Oh, yeah. No, you never know.
We've never said two words together, but that's your fault.
Whenever I see a cute girl out,
it's always when I become extremely self-conscious about everything
I'm wearing and what I look like.
That's when I'm like, yeah, because all I can think is,
like in this exact moment, if I looked right,
then I'd be able to talk to her and it would seem normal.
But at this moment, if I talk to her, I will look like a rapist.
So I don't want like it.
It's never a problem until I see the cute girl.
And I'm this is the exact emotion.
It's God damn it.
Like that's exactly how I feel, like the snap of the shit.
If I knew she was going to be here today, I would have dressed in pants.
You know, the thing about talking to girls in public
is you always look like a rapist.
You can't you can't not look like a rapist.
You just got to accept I'm going to go and talk to this girl
and look like a rapist.
And that's just part and parcel of the of the fucking thing.
I don't know. Somebody's doing the raping.
I, you know, I agree with you guys on both those.
I have, man, I I I hate talking about these things.
It makes me look not cool.
But yeah, these are these are real issues I have.
You know, but like, but there's no but there's no right.
I love that you're still concerned about looking.
I'm always concerned about.
Well, Nate is the only one that has
guys, let's make a podcast about not leaving your room.
His idea and he's concerned about looking cool
in the Hiccomery podcast, you can you can spin.
You can spin almost anything to sound cool if you say it the right way.
But it's hard to spin deep personal insecurities to sound.
You know, maybe, maybe deep personal insecurities are the coolest thing of all.
What girls are into these days.
Yeah, you know, damaged man.
Let me give you guys some more some more Hickey stuff.
So when I started hanging out with that friend of mine,
you know, both of us were super socially awkward,
but I was a little bit less than him.
Like I would I would often yeah, I would often say that, like,
in terms of personality, I was the Yamazaki to his Sato.
Like, I don't know what any of that means.
If you see the NHK, Sato is the main character
and he's full Hickey Comery, never leaves his house, never talks to anyone.
Yamazaki is his neighbor who is like borderline,
but he still goes to college and he's more like just angry at the world,
like less completely unable to talk to people and more like
has this burning hatred for everyone kind of thing, you know,
because of the fact that they that he's seen as abnormal or anything.
So and he's the one who in the end is able to totally turn his life around
as soon as he figures out what he's trying to do.
Yeah, he kind of just falls into it as it happens. Right.
But like he like my friend, my friend who
who is the Hickey Comery, like when we started hanging out,
because like I said, we I first met him because he just happened
to show up to school at the Lucky Star booklet.
And so I was like, holy fuck, someone else knows this is early 2007.
Yeah, that wasn't even the cutting edge.
A ring yet. No, it was it was done airing, but only by a couple months.
So like seeing someone holding a Lucky Star book was crazy.
And so I asked him for his Yahoo Messenger name.
And that was the last day he ever came to school.
So if I hadn't asked him for that then, then I never would have what a what a
what a painful meeting that was.
At some point, I started talking to him about Welcome to the NHK.
And that's how we became like good friends,
because we both like related to that like paranoia and everything.
You know, I like I was someone who completely understood
like all the stuff he was going through that to anyone else would have seemed
insane to me was like, yeah, man, I'm an otaku.
I know all this stuff because I've also watched Welcome to the NHK and Genshiken
and like I relate to these things, you know, so we sort of bonded over that stuff.
And then like I would come over to his house and then like at some point,
you know, we started hanging out.
So we would go out to like to go get food and stuff.
We'd like go to Taco Bell.
He could not order food.
Like he could not.
Yeah, a lot of people seem to have that problem.
Yeah, I've been talking to a couple of people who say they have that issue.
I don't.
Growing up, I had I had an issue with ordering food
not so much in the way that like it was a paranoia over talking to the people.
But because I was used to my parents doing it and it felt like anything
that like my parents had routinely done in front of me felt kind of more like
official or something like something that's off limits for kids.
You have to like be trained or something or that shit. Exactly.
I do feel stupid when I order food,
but not like an anxiety.
I love ordering food now.
I'm the best food order in the world now.
I love it because I am so good at talking because like I have a very clear voice
and I can communicate well with people and I can make sure because I have friends
who will get like really frustrated when someone gets their order wrong.
Like this this friend we're talking about like at the time,
he couldn't even order food like he wouldn't he wouldn't talk to the people.
He would have me do it for him.
So I would go up and like order both of our orders and bring it out to him and stuff.
And then over time he, you know, learned how to talk to people.
Now he's like pretty normal.
Like he has a job now.
He's living living a normal guy's life, you know, cured of all the things he had before.
So he's got lots of responsibilities and shit.
But he's still when he goes out to order food
and now he has a loud, clear voice because he trained himself to have one.
He's a big guy, so he can project really easily, you know,
he'll go out to order food.
But if they like seem confused, he'll just leave.
Like if it seems like they can't figure out what exactly he wants,
he'll be like, you know what, forget it and he'll leave
because he can't deal with like misunderstandings and stuff.
Whereas I will sit there and I'll sit there and like go through everything.
I'll be like, no, it's one quesadilla with beans, no rice.
You know, and I love doing it.
Like it's fun and hilarious.
So, yeah, like.
But so, yeah, for a while, like it was funny
because it actually helped me in a way because I would have to speak for him.
So, like, you know, I had to be more social
to compensate for his complete lack of ability to be social, you know, like I had
to start learning how to take orders or to give orders at places
for him because no one was going to do it for me
because he's clearly not going to, you know.
So we kind of had like a symbiotic relationship
where I started getting a little more out of my shell because of him
and then him because of me.
And I, you know, through hanging out with me, he became friends with all my friends
and eventually learned like to, you know, like people and talk to them.
That's good.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's how we got out of.
But that has not stopped the fact that I still spend most of my time in my room.
Yeah.
I want. Here's what I want.
I want my room to be cold, dark, dry.
I want it to just become a tomb.
I just want to live.
I just want to become a living corpse.
I want to be a list.
I thought you were going to say a list. OK.
I want to be a little more than anything else.
That's that's the fantasy creature I'd most I'd most like to be.
And I just want to live in like a fucking stone, cold Steve Austin.
Steve Austin.
Yes. And I just want to be fucking frozen in time forever in my room.
You mean you so basically what you're saying is you want to be able to do your
art stuff and not have to worry about the other bullshit.
I have a terrible.
I mean, I'm sure everyone can relate to this.
I have a terrible fear of the passage of time and the inevitable end of all things.
And what I would like more than anything else is just to freeze time forever.
For you guys, do you ever, for me, like part of my logic behind not going outside
much is fewer chances to die?
There's like because when I leave the house, all I can think about is like
like in my room right now, like the number of things that could kill me is
like I could choke on a few things.
I could trip on a few things.
And if you're maybe your entire house collapsed, you might.
Yeah. Yeah.
Or something some freak accident happened.
But like if you're just out driving, there's like hundreds of
way you use ways you could die every second.
You know, like all like all I think about when I'm out is like
or even when I'm at a place, I'm just like, what if this place gets shot up?
Or what if what if I'm walking in the middle of an area where a gang
fights about I don't I don't live in the nicest place personally right now.
Yeah. I'm I'm when I'm on the bus, I'm always picturing
like which one of these guys is going to be the or girl is going to pull out
the gun and just start just start blasting fools.
I had who is it going to be?
It's definitely someone.
This is the time.
The guns are everywhere.
There was a time in like my late teens where I happened.
It's like I was first getting introduced to like grimdark concepts,
like like or like realizing like how dark the world is.
Because I'd never grown up on like dark media.
And I saw like the ending of American History X.
And then I saw all of Boys in the Hood and after seeing Boys in the Hood,
I had this like long time fear that the way I'm going to die
is that I'm just going to get caught up in a gang shooting.
And I knew someone online who like had lost a brother that way
were like her brother walking down the road and like he was passing by a house
and the people on the porch and in this car that was like going to do
a drive by on the people on the porch.
He just happened to be in that spot when it happened.
So like a gang fight broke out around him and he got caught in the crossfire
and died. And I was like, this is how I'm going to go.
That's gay as hell.
Yeah, but I always thought it would happen at age 44.
I don't know why. We'll see.
I was like, I really thought I'm going to end up dying at age 44
in a gang in a game shoot out 20 years ago.
Even aside from the issue of death, I'm I'm very concerned.
Like, all right, in my in like the timeline of my life, I am very I really,
really want to never be maimed or mangled.
I really want to get to the end of my life without any kind of like
like any like limbs being severed or anything like that.
I know. Weird, right?
What a weird desire to have.
So, yeah, I'm like, I'm like, I got to say it.
I got my alternative lifestyle.
I got to stay home.
I got to not go anywhere because I would because that's the
safest way, you know, that's how I can make sure as much as possible
that I'll never suffer any catastrophic injuries
because they would hurt really bad, right?
They catastrophic even worse than the pain is the like, God,
imagine if your if your drawing hand got blown off or something, you know,
like, that's it. You're done.
Oh, my God, I would be done.
If I do often think about like the gamble of like which body parts am I
like if I had to lose anything, take a leg, take a leg, man.
Probably make it without the legs.
The hands would be a huge problem.
The eyes would be eyes or ears would be just complete done.
You know, if I lose my eyes, anime is out.
Yeah, exactly. Oh, my God.
But here's what I also do.
I also think a lot about like if I lose these specific parts,
what am I going to because if I lose my eyesight, I'm going directly for music.
Well, I'm going to learn.
Yeah. First, I'll cover music.
I'm going to learn Japanese, like how to like hear it pretty quick.
And then I can listen to like drama CDs and stuff.
Oh, my God.
Whole Avenue.
Like audio dramas and stuff.
Yeah. And anime tie ins.
Holy shit. Yeah.
I'll become a huge audio drama, audio book guy, like analyze those.
But the biggest problem is just that I have to have someone like hit,
record and upload for.
Yeah, you need people.
I would have to have someone to to do that stuff.
But that's what I would do.
I would become like an audio only guy.
Or if I lost my hearing, I would become like a manga guy.
Probably. Yeah, that's the smart move.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right. You've got all these contingencies planned out.
Oh, yeah, man. I think you hear that.
You hear that haters, even if even if you destroy Digi's eyes and ears,
he'll still he'll keep on doing it.
He'll never stop.
I dare you to do it.
I'll see if it stops him.
You know, this whole time, I haven't really said it up till now.
I've been been waiting for a moment to interject that I'm definitely like the least
by far, Hiki of anybody in the in the procrastinators group,
except maybe like Tom, because he's got a job now, too,
because I have a wage slave job that I work every week, nine to five.
And but but I very much feel, nonetheless,
like like like Hiki, because despite doing that,
I have no connection to anything I'm doing there.
And I'm only really good.
It's not like I'm uncomfortable at work,
but I want to say I'm only really comfortable when I'm at home.
That's when I feel like I get to be myself and I'm doing the things I want to do.
Typically leave the house at all.
No, not at all.
So there you go. You know, there's how often do you leave the house?
Oh, less than once a week, I think.
Oh, my God, like at all to get groceries or something.
Yeah, like at all.
Holy shit. There you go.
See, the funny thing about this is that I leave the house several times a day
exclusively to eat. No, I never do that.
Well, I'm a huge foodie.
So like I can't stand like just today I went out before we started this show.
I went out and drove all the way to a faux restaurant
and I got take out faux just because I wanted to try.
I wanted to understand what take out faux was like.
It's weird, incidentally.
I believe you.
I am thinking about leaving the house later today
because I'm all out of diet soda.
I haven't had any diet soda in like two days and it's making me very irritable.
There you go.
Yeah, I mean, that's another thing because I all I drink is diet green tea,
which I get from Wawa and I only buy like two or three bottles at a time.
So like every other day, I am guaranteed to go to Wawa to get tea.
And then, you know, while I'm there, I might get something to eat.
Like this weekend, I've just or I haven't left the house
because I just ordered food from Grubhub, you know, instead of doing anything else.
That's what I do.
You know, uncharacteristically, I did actually two days ago,
I went to the Cirque du Soleil.
Whoa, no way.
Yeah, which is not something normal, but just as it so happens,
we've got a temporary roommate subletting a room
and she is a roadie with the Cirque du Soleil and she got us all tickets to a show.
Yeah, I like I didn't want to go.
I didn't think I was going to enjoy it.
My housemates like banged on the door and they dragged me out of bed.
They made me come because they had four tickets and they weren't going to waste one.
Yeah, OK.
And I went.
How was it?
It was great.
I bet it was.
It was awesome.
That's awesome.
Yeah. And I realized on the ride home, oh, man, there was a.
I like now I want to do like hearing Ben just say outright.
It was great.
Like, yeah, Ben makes me like how I want to see Cirque du Soleil.
No, I thought I would be sitting there like, oh, this is dumb.
This is terrible.
Why am I wasting my time?
But no, they're like, I mean, not every act was a brilliant,
but like a bunch of them were really good.
You know, we've been talking a lot of shit.
He didn't look like a clown.
He was just a guy in a purple bowler hat.
But you could tell I could tell that what he was doing was clowning.
I think that guy may have gone to clown college because he had like he gave the air
of like having like an air of professionalism about his clowning that I yeah.
And that the fact that I could tell that he was a clown,
despite the fact that he wasn't dressed like one.
That's oh man.
It's very impressive.
And and also on the ride home, I realized this is important.
I realized that the Cirque du Soleil, the Carnival of the Sun,
must be the the mortal enemy of the Dark Carnival.
Whoa.
That's so true.
Oh, I think that Jesse isn't there.
Jesse be fighting truth and dare.
I wonder if that's why they named it that.
I wonder if that's why it's called the Dark Carnival.
I doubt it.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, you know, the final battle, the apocalypse comes.
Jesus and Satan, a Cirque du Soleil versus the Dark Carnival.
Yeah.
That's one of the many facts.
You know, we've been talking a lot of shit about like going out and how we we always
stay home and stuff.
But but you know, it's a lot of it is kind of in our little bubble.
We we kind of miss cool things that are going on outside because our focus is elsewhere.
I didn't hear about Brexit until it was happening.
Well, no, you know, there's some cool stuff going on out in the real world.
You know, I learned about Brexit all the way through because I watch a lot of YouTube videos
and sit on Twitter all day.
So I knew everything about Brexit.
But and I listen to the news.
Here's the here's the thing, though.
Like, yeah, I hate the NPR the radio every on my way into work NPR the radio every day.
It's great.
Yeah, I do kind of like NPR.
Like when I was like a teenager and like in my early adulthood, I like really had this
mindset like once I get money, I'm going to go out all the time.
Like I'm going to do all the fun stuff, you know, especially if my big part of why this
never happened is because my friends never ended up having a lot of money, you know,
but like I have enough money right now.
I could do anything.
I could go any day of the week.
I have the time.
I have the money.
I could just go somewhere.
And what I eventually realized is that I don't like any of the stuff you can go do.
What about music shows?
You like shows?
There's not no cool bands come here.
Like because I've done a lot of the stuff that like you just go to go.
Right.
Like I've done a lot of the like random events because for a little while,
like early last year, you guys might have heard this because you both listened to some episodes
of Digi Bros.
When Victor was working for this company called Yaloha,
where it was like they would send him to random events around like the area and like just have
him take little films and like make little two minute videos out of it.
And they would just they pay him like, uh, like what was it like 25 bucks a video because
it usually took him like an hour.
He would just like drive out their stuff for an hour and come back and send them the videos.
But like I went to a couple of those with him and it's like on the one hand,
it was really fascinating to realize that there's like always an event happening around here.
But all of those events are fucking stupid.
Yeah.
It would be like, all right, there's a little music festival happening in like what like a lot in,
in Norfolk, right?
It's the city next to mine.
There's literally like on the edge of a neighborhood,
there's just a spot where there isn't a house and they just like put a little like fence around it
and set up a stage and had like a little music festival there.
And it was that, that little lot.
And then the restaurant across the street and like the inside one was like metal and the outside one was like jazz.
And it was like, it was fascinating to know it was happening, but none of the bands were that good.
And, you know, it was hot outside.
It was a bunch of fucking hippies out on the lawn.
No one's doing anything.
You go inside and it's like, I don't want to pay for beer and tacos and I don't give a fuck.
Like it was cool to know it was there, but I would never go again because I didn't get as much out of it
as I would have got out of sitting at home watching anime for an hour.
You know, dude, I totally hear you on that.
And, you know, my life right now is kind of lonely because I really only do things by myself or online with you guys.
Like I would really love to have in my life a physical thing I can do with the people that I like.
And that's why the, you know, Horseshoe House, the Announce HQ is such a great dream for me personally because
being around people I like, just being physically around people, I think is a healthy thing that I don't do it all right now.
Yeah.
And that would be a life upgrade, as Christian would say.
There have definitely been times where like having my friends around is cool because like, you know,
when there is something that we all want to do, then we could do it.
But like, these days, most of my friends are either working all the time or they have no money or they're just fucking lazy and shitty and don't want to do anything.
So like, but I mean, my dad is a total outdoorsman, right?
And him and Victor will have periods where like, my dad goes on like 20 mile bike rides like every day, right?
And he'll be like, Vic, let's go for a bike ride and they'll go do that.
Or he'll, there was a while where he got into like paddle boarding and like every weekend he'd be like, let's go paddle boarding and they'd go do that.
And I'm just like, none of that in like, I don't want to do that because all I'm going to do, I know what's going to happen.
I'm going to go out or there was one time we went canoeing and kayaking with like my, like all our friends, like my dad took everybody out.
We all went canoeing, right?
And it's like we rode out into the middle of this lake and then we hung out there for a little bit and we rode back.
It took a couple hours and it was like, it was kind of fun and it's cool to have that memory.
And it was cool because all my friends were there.
But the end result was that I was in pain for days because not only did I get sunburned everywhere,
but like it was way more intense of a workout than like I was ready to handle, you know?
So like there was like days of lost productivity.
And I mean that one I would do again because it was everyone.
But like the idea of going out to do that every weekend is not at all appealing.
It was special because it was special, you know?
Right, it was a one-time thing and that made it cool.
But like that's the thing.
I feel like the only way to, like I think there's a mental image I had as a kid,
that there was all this stuff going on that was interesting or places to go.
Like you got like a, like I live right, less than 45 minutes drive from Bush Gardens,
which is one of the biggest and best theme parks in the country, right?
Phenomenal theme park.
I hate roller coasters.
I hate walking around.
I hate overpriced food, you know, like going there.
Like as a kid, it sounds, because it's such a big unique thing you can go do,
it sounds like a great time.
And there was a, there was a period when I was like 20 where I was like,
what if all of us, me and all my friends, what if we all got season passes to Bush Gardens
and we could just hang out there all the time?
Because like as a kid, you're like, I only get to go here once a year.
I'm going to ride all the biggest rides and make sure I do all that stuff.
But there's tons of like just hanging out stuff to do there.
So I was like, what if we all had season passes and we just hung out here all the time?
And then it was like, none of us really want to do that.
It's like a 45 minute drive and what are we going to do?
Eat some wiener schnitzel and we'll get bored, you know?
It's just, there's so many things that sound cool.
But if you do them more than like once a year, then it quickly loses its luster.
You know, dude, society has changed.
We're at a point where we have tons of stuff that you can do,
you can do whatever you want with your life for the most part.
If you're a lucky person, you're born in a good family, you have a good job, whatever.
So things like interpersonal relationships, they take energy.
They take effort and you need to work on them with the people that are in your life.
If you want to keep that healthy, which is an important thing about being a human
and having a good human life, which I want to do before I die.
Which is why I think something like setting yourself up in a situation
where you're kind of forced to do the things that you want to do,
but don't necessarily always make the time for is kind of a healthy thing.
So like setting up your business scenario, like what I hope to do with us guys,
similar to like the red letter media guys, they have just the perfect situation in my mind.
Like they're all friends.
They work together on these like funny creative videos.
They're, you know, they're successful on YouTube.
They're filmmakers as they want it to be.
They just released their first actual movie not too long ago.
Everything about that set up.
Side note, I bet it sucks, but go on.
I want to say, I haven't seen it yet.
I'd like to see it.
That wasn't their first movie.
They've made a few movies.
But they have been working on Space Cop for like 12 years.
There you go.
They made a bigger movie sort of thing and it came out.
And it's just, you have to put energy into stuff and you're going to get things out of it.
And these days, the way our world is set up, human relationships are definitely one of those
things that we have to like work on, you know, and that's why it's important to structure your
life in a way where you can get those things out of it.
And currently I haven't, I haven't put in like any work into getting any of that like human
relationship stuff.
I don't know anyone in the city.
I barely talked to my coworkers at all.
And it's because, yeah.
Housemates.
Yeah, you know, my roommate Ben is sort of a friend, but we never hang out.
And he's a pretty isolation-y guy, just like I am.
When I moved into my current place, yeah, I moved in with a bunch of, like I said before,
I live with a bunch of guys that are all pretty cool and are friends.
And yeah, I was, like you said, being in that situation did facilitate a lot more human
interaction social scenarios.
And like you said, it was good for a time.
In recent weeks, I've sort of gotten a little bit like, well, I've kind of had enough of
it for a while.
Yeah.
I'm not, I don't feel much motivation for it anymore.
If there was something kind of forcing you to mix with them, it'd be, you know, like there's
there's something good about that.
That is why I got forced to go to the Cirque du Soleil, which is, you know.
Yeah, right?
Like your life was probably better because you would do that.
I think for me, if you're passionate about anything, it justifies all of it, right?
Like I mean, I think if I was really,
into like skating, like my mom, when she grew up, was always at the skating rink, right?
Because it was a popular thing to do back then.
You went out to the skating rink, everybody skates in circles for hours and you listen
to music, you know, and we have one near our house.
And there was a while where my mom was doing roller derby, where you know about roller
derby, right?
I was going to ask if she was into roller derby.
Yeah, she got into it.
I don't understand it, but I like it.
I mean, she got into that like, this was like 10 years ago, like not as, like she was at
the skating rink all the time as a kid.
And then as an adult or as a mom, you know, she became a roller derby person until she
couldn't do it anymore.
Because, because she's like got injuries and she's too damn old.
Shit, hardcore roller derby.
Yeah, but she got into roller derby and you know, we go out there and like watch her
matches sometimes and stuff.
And like, my mom is the type who will never leave the house.
If there's not something to do, you know, like she'll go out if there's some kind of
social gathering or if there's some reason for her to be there.
But if not, she will completely stay inside for weeks on end, not leaving the house, just
playing Facebook games, you know, like when she was into roller derby, she would go out
to the skating rink all the time, you know.
And so like, she, so I think that for me, it would be the same.
We're like the times when I've gotten out of the house the most is like when me and Victor
were working out together.
You know, it's like we're going to the gym every other day.
So yeah, like it's, you know, it's, it's not so much that we're going out of the house
just to get out of the house, but because there is a thing to do out of the house.
Right, but when there's nothing like that, it's like, we create those things for yourself
pretty much, you know.
And if there's nothing like that, like for me, I have to be like passionately interested.
And there's been like, there have been sports and like things that I, that I would be interested
in doing that, or even just like a e-sports, like, because my friends are super into fighting
games, right?
And they have been for a couple of years now, like the main thing all my friends do is play
street fighter and shit.
And for a long time, I thought Brandon Tolentino was going to like try to go pro because he's
like incredibly skilled at fighting games.
But because there's not really much of a like pro culture around here and no one he can
practice with who's like good enough, then it's just never happened.
And he's still obsessed with fighting games.
But like for me, it was always like, man, if all my friends got into like, like trying
to do this professionally, then I would feel like a desire to get into it and like to leave
the house and go to tournaments and stuff and like do all this shit.
But as it stands, but ever they go to a tournament, like when they actually do, they're usually
not even to compete just to watch.
And I'm like, I don't want to do that.
Like, I don't want to say it takes work.
You know, it's about finding things that that fit into your life because, you know, it might
not, it might not be true for everybody.
But I think overall, like if you are in a situation that kind of makes you mix with more
people and be more social in general, your life is generally going to be better.
You know, it's going to shoot off endorphins in your brain.
It's just a rewarding day.
If I had one friend who maybe I'm just projecting because I want all these things in my life,
you know, if we all moved in together and just one one friend of mine was like, dude,
let's get really into tennis.
I'd be like, done because like it's kind of the thing is I would never do it by myself
because it's an expensive thing to do, right?
You have to rent court space a lot of the time.
You have to buy a racket, buy balls, buy it by a nice racket, buy some decent balls,
buy, you know, the right shoes and stuff, not too expensive.
But it's it's it's a costly hobby.
And it's not something that I see myself like forcing just myself to do.
Like if I was the only one who cared, it wouldn't it wouldn't be worth it.
But if I had a friend who was like, dude, let's the two of us hang out every Saturday,
practice tennis and just get really good at tennis and have fun playing it.
I'd be like, yeah, dude, let's fucking do that.
You know, but it has to be like that, you know, and I guess I missed the boat on this
because like my dad is really into running and cycling and he does all kinds of races.
Like he goes out every few months.
He goes out to a race, you know, like and that's something I like that's the kind
of passion I'd be looking for.
I don't like running or biking that much, but if my dad had that kind of passion
for like a sport I was interested in like tennis, then I'd be like, yeah, dad,
let's go out every weekend and do tennis, you know, like and I feel like I've always
wanted that. I've always wanted a friend with whom I could get into something
other than my job because like as it stands, I get so obsessed with my work
that I don't do anything that doesn't in some way pertain to it.
You know, and it's like as a result, my life becomes this
like living hell of just any time I don't have work that I'm doing,
I'm thinking about the work I should be doing, you know, which is I don't
I don't think it's a better use of time.
Like I don't think you find I don't think you find ideas more often
by thinking about them more, you know, like I don't think sitting around all day
like for like there's sometimes I'll sit around an entire day just going like,
what if I what if I did this, you know, if I did that, humans are funny things.
We're pretty much at the point in civilization where we really need to
trick our brains into doing things that make us happy.
You know, it's like we we've reached and it is like I think a lot of the
depression that people feel these days that is in things like, you know,
NHK and needs and stuff comes from like all your base needs are met.
But your higher level ones on the Maslow's hierarchy,
like you're just not self actualizing and it kills you and you're not socializing
enough and these things torment you.
So we have to figure out the ways to fucking, you know,
the only times like that's why I get I get so excited when there's actually
like a new video game that I legitimately love enough that I'm willing to say,
fuck it, I'm going to play when I played through Dark Souls 3 and like all the
Souls games, like yeah, like with Dark Souls 3, I was prepared for months
beforehand that I was like, I'm going to get all my work done before this game
comes out because all I'm going to do is play this game and it was glorious.
It was like three or four days of just sitting around playing Dark Souls 3
with no other cares in the world.
I did not give a fuck what it was going to eventually,
like I thought I would make a video out of it.
And then after I finished the game, I spent like a month and a half agonizing
over whether or not I should make a video about it and I didn't end up doing it.
Because in the end I was like, I'm just so desperate to make everything I do
a part of my work that like the idea that I spent three days just enjoying
myself is like a nightmare.
And Jesse talks about that all the time himself too.
He's breathed it out.
And then like I felt lucky when Doom came out because like I played through Doom
and I loved Doom and everyone else wrote a review of Doom.
And I was like, cool, I will never have to talk about this.
Like there's no possible thing I have to say about this game
that 40 other people didn't say.
So it was just pure, yeah, Doom.
You know, that's it.
It was no complication.
It's always interesting to me that you have this mentality about like somebody
out there has to make like the intelligent, you know, get the points
across about what makes Doom or any game or anime out there, you know, good.
I don't think about things that way, but it's interesting.
Like if someone if someone else has said the thing, I'm not going to write
a video that that other people have already written.
And like I watched because like with Doom, it was like literally the day
the game came out.
There was like a 40 minute Noah Caldwell Jervais video about it.
And then within the by the end of the week, it was like fucking.
Oh, who was the second person I saw cover?
I don't know.
There was someone else I saw and then like a third person and I was like,
these guys have already said anything I would ever want to say about Doom.
There's nothing left for me to say.
I read some more articles.
Then later down the line, like Aaron's signal made a video.
Super bunny hop just finally made a video.
And it's like there is nothing left to say about Doom.
Why would I ever cover it?
But he was surprisingly critical to I was interested by that.
His was I think he because he says in the video, he's like he said.
Everyone else has talked about this game.
So let's just play Doom.
And I'm going through all these hallways and killing all these demons.
And I'm just having so much fun with it.
I just it's a really great game and I'm really enjoying myself.
Good George impression.
He even said on Twitter later, like people were like being like like that.
He wasn't trying to like say it's a shitty game.
He's like, the game is amazing.
I just I just wanted to talk about the critical points of the game.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because everyone else has already talked about the game.
So why would I say what they're all saying?
Even then, the first half of this video when he was praising it was all
shit I'd heard before.
So I was like, yeah, get to the point, get to the criticism.
I just want to hear the bad shit, you know, like I got it.
But yeah, I will not.
I if someone makes a video and I watch it and it says what I would have said,
then I'm like, cool, I don't have to make the video because I can literally
just link people this one.
Like I could just make a video saying, hey, guys,
all of my thoughts on girl in the gun right over here.
Go watch best guy ever's video, you know?
Yeah. Yeah.
Which is not true.
I still have a few that I actually want to do on that show.
Yeah, it was never intended to be a, you know, summation of everything.
Let me tell a story.
Let me tell you a shitty story.
While you do that, I'm going to go take a piss.
I'll be right back.
All right, fucker.
I want to hear it, but I got to go.
Like two, like a year and a half, two years ago, I was living at home
with my parents and it was a nightmare.
And I could not wait to get out.
And then January of last year, I was, I got the chance to move in
with some friends in this house and like the Boston area.
And I was like, oh my God, I'm going to be living in like a city.
There's going to be social events occurring.
This house is like full of people.
They host, they host parties there.
They do things.
It's going to be a great time and I'm going to meet girls and bang them.
It's going to be.
That's any time you go into an event with that expectation, it's not going to happen.
Well, it wasn't a specific event.
It was the idea that there would be events and that at some of, at least some
of them, I would bang girls.
Anyway, I was so excited.
I was like, I'm turning over a new leaf.
I'm going to have an active.
You're going to be called a well laid.
No.
So I went.
I moved that.
And then in that January, I moved into this house and then there was the whole
thing I've mentioned before with the landlord and it was all, everyone moved out.
It was just me and like these two weirdos and there were no parties.
And, and they were occasionally invite me to like little mini concerts or
like screenings of obscure movies.
And I would always go.
I would be like, oh my God, a social event.
I will go and meet a girl and have sex.
And, and I always wanted that so bad.
Like I wanted, I wanted that life, but like it would always be shit.
It would always be, I would get there and it would be like, it would be like
some concert and I would get to the venue and there would be someone playing
and like this little gallery or something.
And I would just have to stand there and nod my head, pretend to care about this
music that I wasn't interested in, wait until the event was over, mill around
and socialize with a bunch of fucks and leave.
Or it would always be all guys or it would always be a weird crowd that would
make me uncomfortable or it would always be, there would always be something.
There would always be something that ruined it.
I mean, sometimes the movie would be good, but the band would be okay.
But the event itself would always, it was never satisfying.
And it really, it really got to me because I was there for like six months
and this was a consistent pattern.
And I just got so fed up.
I just got so fed up with the whole thing going out.
It was it when I was the other place with the landlord.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I, and I just, I just didn't, I just got burnt out on, on events and on doing things.
I was like, wow, the whole like socializing and going to things is not as fun as I fantasized
it would be back when I was stuck at home.
You know, I always kind of thought when I started disillusioned about that, I was never
really a big social gathering guy, but my senior year of college, I made man, my
damnedest effort to, to change that.
And I started doing a couple of things.
And at the time, I thought that I wasn't really capitalizing on them enough by just
like not being outgoing enough at the time.
But I went to a lot of those.
And you know, good things did happen at them sometimes.
But, uh, yeah.
Did you become well laid?
Well, no one's well laid like Ben St.
of Patreon, but, uh, no, there was a little, an acceptable
amount of, of being laid going on.
Actually, I'm really curious.
I feel like Jesse's probably the most well laid out of us, right?
He seems that way.
No, I think, I think it's me.
Yeah, I honestly think it's me.
In terms of frequency of having sex or in terms of, okay.
In terms of frequency, I'm, yeah.
Honestly, in terms of partners, it might be you.
I, it's, it's me.
How many girls have you slept with?
Uh, like 20.
20?
That's pretty good.
That's probably about double me, I'd say.
I catch up working on it.
You got two years, two years between us.
I'll catch up and then I'll mustard.
Nice.
Yep.
Well laid.
I'm never going to get over that.
That's the best fucking term I've ever come up with.
It's what was that?
That was a classic moment.
That was a classic, classic TVC moment right there.
All right.
It feels like this thing's ending.
Anyone got it on last?
Okay.
You got more?
This was supposed to be the end of that story I was saying before.
There was a very disillusion with going out and doing things.
And whenever I hear about an event, I always think like, oh, it's not
actually going to be fun.
It's just going to be some, some shitty, some bluster.
And it's all just some bullshit.
It was why I was really shocked that I actually enjoyed the fucking circus.
The circus.
It's a show, man.
It's designed to entertain.
Yeah, but like I, on the one hand, that's true.
But on the other hand, like that's the epitome of like corny, you know, like,
like kind of silly, sort of, sort of pointless entertainment.
Just, just spectacle for the sake of spectacle.
It really felt like it really felt like it was anathema to everything
that I would like, but I was totally wrong and it was a great time.
Well, I don't know.
I guess that goes to show people at home that even sometimes you just
got to, sometimes you just got to be like, well, life might suck and things
might suck.
And even if the majority of things suck, you still got to do things because
you got to find the ones that don't.
You know, this is, this is a real subject yourself to a, to a, to a lot of stuff.
It really is though, like, sorry, it really is a, like, uh, like a shot in
the dark of like whether a thing's going to be good or bad.
And I can't say that the number of things that have turned out to be
good have made it worth all the times they've turned out to be bad.
But no, it's not on the net.
On the net, things are bad, but you got to wade through that.
You got to wade through it anyways.
You got to wade through that quagmire so that you can find the things that are
good and keep them and then keep them in your heart and focus your life,
remember that scene, an episode.
I think it's episode one of NHK where Sato manages to like get out of his room.
He goes all the way to like the manga cafe to like apply for a job.
And then he just totally, yeah, it's first episode and he, he chickens out and
he runs and my God, like that, that episode is so powerful for me.
It's, it's insane.
Uh, but like that was, that was him taking an opportunity to try to do something.
And who knows if right then he had taken the job at the thing, uh, maybe he would
have, you know, right then he would have like branched out and things would have
worked out instead of having to spend, you know, the next 24 episodes or whatever
you're languishing in pain of being a neat, uh, yeah, I'm just saying that it's
about, it's about, and I can't, if you've got like a mental condition,
like a serious clinical thing, then I mean, it's not my expertise.
I don't know.
But if you're just a normal depressed kind of guy, then you know, you gotta
get out there and do shit.
It's the only way like Ben saying you got to wade through the shit to find the
good stuff.
I definitely got it.
Uh, sorry.
Depression is like, it's like a cycle and it feeds into itself.
And the only, the only way to make it any better is to kind of ignore it and go
against the, the instincts that it is telling you stay at home, don't do
anything, give up.
You, you got to like, you got to do something that feels wrong and just,
you got to, you got to go against.
Because you know, by the way, uh, I was just going to say, I know everyone
hates Zoe Quinn or I know that that whole thing was a big to do.
But before Gamergate ever happened, I played depression quest and I
thought it was really good.
Is that so?
Uh, and, and only later, only after Gamergate exploded and I heard about
Zoe Quinn, did they realize, Oh, she was the one who made depression
quest.
Well, holy shit.
Yeah.
And then I, and then I hear people being like, Oh, yeah, Zoe Quinn, she, the
game she made was depression.
Quest is not even a real game.
Well, fuck those people.
Because before she was even famous, I really liked it.
Hey, well, can't, can't argue with that.
Can't argue with that.
And you know, I was going to say that, uh, the reason that we feel pain is
because man is marble is both the sculpture and the sculptor and to reshape
himself will always cause him pain.
That's a metaphor people like that's never heard that one.
It's a big fitness.
So it's a fitness one.
So, uh, yeah, like I think up until like just maybe even not even two years ago,
I was absolutely the guy who would walk all the way up to the store, like get
the application and then never return.
And like that was, I've done, I've literally done it.
Yeah.
I've gone to places and like picked up an application and then just felt
so weird about I've done that too, man.
I've done that for a job or like gone somewhere to ask for an application and
then not like, you know, I go to GameStop or something and then just like look
at games and like then just put my tail to my legs and leave, you know, I've done
a lot of that back before, but like, I don't know.
It's not the kind of thing I would do now.
It's just cause like after having like worked in retail briefly, which with
target, it was easy cause the place wasn't even open yet.
So I, you know, it was like an online registration.
So like, I got the job before the place even was like, you know, operating.
Um, and, and like through having worked in those places and like kind of
understanding the mindset of the people who are actually there, which is they're
not thinking about you at all.
They don't care about the customers.
They're just thinking about the job they're trying to do right now.
And then like, uh, and then just having money has made it like, cause I go out
like I said, I go out to eat like almost every day.
So I, you know, I constantly am out talking to people and throwing money around
and like having this feeling like I belong in the place I'm in because I'm
spending money on it, you know.
So yeah, I think those things have helped me a lot to like, if I, if I had to get
a job today, I would just walk into a place and sign a fucking application.
Like there would be no to do about it.
You know, if I had to get a job today, I would sell drugs.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I would do, I would do anything to not get a job.
You know, I think the one factor that might be an issue for me trying to do
that would be, uh, like personal shame, like self loathing about like, oh my God,
I can't believe I'm going back to work at fucking Best Buy or something like that.
You know, like that would, that would be tough for me.
Definitely not Best Buy.
Well, I wouldn't go for something I was going to feel ashamed about, but I think
I could probably get a little better.
But if, if I had to get bottom of the barrel, yeah, yeah, um, like I've worked
some shitty jobs.
I worked in some back alley pizza places.
I worked at like, oh man, just like a bunch of Craigslist jobs and food, then
I'll fucking kill myself.
Like if I had my jobs, not that it's bad, my jobs came from Craigslist, even
like the kind of good ones like teaching physics and Poland and being that like
mirror coding, sputter engineer, those both came from Craigslist, mine were,
mine were pretty shitty for the most part.
For those days there are behind me now.
So it's sort of like sum up this podcast, because what I think is interesting
about this is the trajectory that we followed.
Unintentionally, we followed this in the way we told it, but like, I think all
three of us, when we were teenagers or young adults, we didn't leave the house
more out of like paranoia and like social awkwardness.
And then there was a period when all of us tried to fight that and realized that
we like, we could go out and do things.
And then we all came to the conclusion that we didn't, like now we don't
leave the house for totally different reasons.
Like, before it was, I hate, I don't want to be seen by humans.
So I won't leave.
And then we all went, you know what, I want to be able to do fun things.
And then we went out and did the fun things, realized they weren't fun and
went back into our room.
You know, kind of, yeah, I think, I think I'm in a little bit of a different
camp because I do, I mean, I know we all long for human companionship.
That's just a normal human thing.
I'd like to, I'd like to do more things.
And I could, I just, I just don't put in the effort.
I take the, I'm taking the path of least resistance really, but just keep
doing what I do every day and edit shit and, you know, doing that stuff.
I'd like to, I would like to get out more, but only if it's to do something interesting.
I don't want to get out more just to go with my friends to some dumb show or to
go sit at the beach, like asshole or something and do nothing.
Like if I'm going to go out more, it's got to be because we all decided like,
Hey, we're all going to like really start working out for real.
Let's all go to the gym.
Let me just tell you a quick story about this or even just me and one other.
Like if me and Victor didn't have the weirdest fucking job schedule in the
universe and he wanted to start working out again and he had money, then I'd be
like, Hey, Vic, let's go start working out again.
Cause that's a thing to do outside.
Makes me feel like a real human being, you know.
You know, the time when I was feeling probably the most low about myself was
after I came back from college, uh, I was taking like a class of two a semester,
just chugging away, trying to finish my degree, uh, which is almost done now,
thankfully, um, and was, was working these really shitty jobs and I was like 22 or
so before Tbap started or anything.
So I had no direction in life.
Um, like one day I was just like, I think I'll go skydiving all by myself.
And, uh, so I, so I did that.
I paid like hundreds of dollars, went drove out by myself to a Newport airport
in Rhode Island and just went skydiving by myself.
And the fascinating thing was everyone there was like in a group or like was
there with like their, their significant other of, of many years.
And like, yeah.
I mean, it was clearly like a group event, but the most interesting thing of all was
like the whole time that you're getting ready to go, they're pushing all these
things on you like, like, Hey, you want to buy like this recording of like the
footage of you, you know, doing the skydiving, you want to buy like the
landing photos that we take, we're going to take them anyway, but you only get
to have them if you pay like the extra hundred bucks for our like deluxe package.
So like this was so obviously what they were selling was like Facebook, uh,
page headers, no, they were saving Facebook headers that the, oh, look at me.
I did this kind of like, it was so much more about having like showing that you
had done this than actually experiencing it.
Everyone else was there for a different reason than me.
And I'm not saying that I was like a fucking hero or anything.
I was there because I was depressed and looking for something that makes me
not want to kill myself.
I'll fucking say, you're a fucking hero.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck all those guys.
All right.
Someone had to say it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Uh, and it's not about me.
It's just, it's just about them.
I thought it was really interesting what everyone else was doing.
Um, and our different motivations, you know, that's it.
That's all I got to say.
My parents are the type who every single time we even so much as go out to eat
as a family, my dad will take, he'll make a big thing out of like taking a
picture of everyone at the table together and then post it on Facebook and be like,
out with the family at this place.
I'm like, we literally just went out to eat.
Like there's nothing special about that.
The only thing that's fun about this is that we're doing it.
Learning about it online is not interesting.
Like I see things that I was involved with on Facebook.
And I'm like, why is this up on Facebook?
I don't care.
To impress people, did you?
It was only interesting back when I was doing it's all marketing.
It's marketing your life.
I don't really get the whole thing about taking pictures of stuff.
I feel like if something's important and meaningful, then you'll remember it.
Yeah.
And if it's not, then like when I see pictures of stuff that I don't remember,
then I'm just like, why do I have a picture?
Well, now hang on.
I don't want to, I guess there's a, I don't want to say the picture entirely worth
us because sometimes we'll come across like kid pictures and it'll be really
fun to be like, oh man, I was like a little, I was cool to do that.
It's cool to see like what I, to me, the most interesting thing is always
what I looked like at the time.
Like not what I was doing, but the fact that there was a time where I looked
that way, you know, I think they serve a function.
I can see the appeal on that level.
And if there is something that you don't remember, it might, it's
could be interesting and maybe edifying to be like, oh, wow, I did that.
I totally forgot about that.
I totally forgot about all this stuff.
This Facebook culture that we're kind of in now, like propagates the idea that
like everyone but me has such an amazing life.
And I think it could really be a, it could be a big pressure on people who are
like needs.
They'll be like, oh God, look at me.
What am I going to do?
These people, these are heroes out in the real world, you know?
It may be like that for some people, but for me, you know, for someone like me
living, as we've said, an alternative life, I've, I've, you know, I've, I've
just evolved beyond it.
Some, some idiot, some idiot like you, Nate, might, might see someone on
Facebook doing cool, doing cool things and be like, wow, that person's got a
great life.
I get it now.
Might see someone on Facebook right there.
That's the funny thing though.
Yeah, yeah, with their family or like doing something, doing something with
quote unquote, loved one.
No, here's the funny thing because I, I look at that and I'm like, man, that
looks dumb.
I don't want to do that.
I'm glad I'm not, I'm not that person.
I feel more like Ben.
I'm always like, this is stupid.
Why are they posting this?
But like the funny thing is I've raised this point with my dad because I've
seen people like very emphatically against like, uh, showing how awesome your
life is on Facebook for the reasons like what Nate's saying, like, uh, like a
nerd writer, um, before he became like big and popular, like he used to do
vlogs and he had a one whole vlog about like how, uh, Instagram was like slowly
being ruined because people were treating it like Facebook when it used to be like
artistic or something.
And he was like, we have to stop, uh, people from just posting like selfies and
stuff on, on a can't be done.
Whatever, can't be done.
And I, I thought it was interesting.
And then I, I brought this up to my dad one time where I was telling him, like,
you know that like a lot of the internet, like really shames this kind of
Facebook posting and he was like, the way I see it, I'm giving people something
to aspire to, like because my dad is the type who like a lot of the little
egotistical, but okay.
Yeah.
But like a lot of my dad's life improvement is from, he loves like egotistical
people and like reading books about like he has several Trump books like that
Trump wrote.
Cool.
He has a huge collection of nonfiction of like anyone who's successful.
He wants to read about them, you know, and like he, like he sees other
people's success and he thinks, I want to be that guy.
And so he tries to like, you know, learn about their success.
And like when he sees people like doing something fun and cool, then he's like,
Oh, I want to get to a point where I can do that.
You know.
And so he sees it that way, that people will look at his Facebook and want to,
you know, better themselves so they can do the fun things that he's posting about,
you know, yeah, man, that makes sense.
The thing when I see someone, maybe this is just my fucked up mindset.
But when I see something, someone doing something fun, my reaction is to be like,
well, it's probably not that fun.
Yeah.
That's how I think it's understandable.
That's why like I get my dad's mindset.
And I feel like that way about, you know, people who do like jobs I want to do,
like, you know, anyone who's successful at YouTubing, like I look at them and
I'm like, I want to be like them.
But like when I see, yeah, when I see like photos of people like, we're at
Disney World and it's awesome.
And I'm always like, it's like, it was probably awesome for five minutes.
And most of it's fucking boring.
You're smiling in this picture, but I know you were waiting in line for
like two hours before this and you paid $80 a day for cotton candy.
My dad is very easily excitable.
So like, I know that he legitimately has a great time wherever he goes.
And I usually am like just like, for me, because again, all I think about when I'm
out somewhere is like, is this better than what I could have been doing?
Well, see, that's the thing.
A lot of people don't even, that doesn't even cross their mind, you know,
like most people, I won't say most people, but like,
is ignorance truly bliss, you know, to just go through your life?
Yes.
Probably yes.
It's probably just like a better way to live a happy life.
Does the time reach your life?
We went to this place called Motor World.
And it was like, just like, it's like a place where you like ride around
like little go-karty type things.
And there's like a bunch of different courses.
And it was like, it was hot as shit.
No one else was there.
It was like, the place was pretty much desolate because it was like, you know,
relatively early on a weekday.
So like, everyone who was working there looked like they didn't want to be there.
The place is dirty and unkempt.
Everything's way more expensive than it needs to be.
Which, I mean, my dad was paying for all of it and he didn't care,
you know, that it was expensive.
But we were all just like, I'm the type who if,
even if someone else is paying for something I'm doing,
if I think it wasn't worth it for them, then it bothers me.
Where I'm like, I did not get a level of enjoyment out of this,
that you should have paid that much money for it, you know.
Yeah.
And so like, we were at Motor World and it's just like,
I mean, it was a thing to go do all day on a day when I had no other plans.
But like, I really left the place like, you, we have spent hundreds of dollars here
and I would have been just as happy not having gone, you know.
Yeah.
I remember as a youth when our family went to Disney World,
we went to like one or two, we went to Disney World I think twice.
I think so, I think so.
And I remember the second time I was probably like 14.
I remember my dad just being like, oh, we're having a great time.
You know, we're at Disney World.
And I remember just being a little shit and being like,
uh, I don't feel good.
I'm not having a good day.
I'm not having fun.
I was such an edgy teen.
Parents should just kill their kids.
You know.
I'm living, I'm living proof that you're totally right.
I was an edgy, I'm still an edgy teen.
I've decided I've recently come to the conclusion that I am as edgy a teen
as I ever was and I probably always will.
I think like whenever and any family event I see,
I always see it as being like vacation,
like National Lampoon's vacation where it's like the dad just desperately wants
to do something that he thinks will make everybody have fun and be happy.
But without an understanding of what anyone really wants to do.
And like because you're told it will be fun to go to Disney World,
then you want it to be fun.
But then you get there and it's not fun.
And as a kid, it's harder for you to like,
you know, like express that and like,
you know, because you know that it costs a lot of money
and that for you to be disappointed is, you know.
It probably could be fun if you go with the right people.
Right.
And if you're not, and if you're not like,
if it's not such like a rare and valuable thing that you feel like pressured to have fun.
Exactly.
That's why I know it's probably fun.
That's my favorite thing about being an adult is that I can now go and like spend all this money
on whatever and it's not a big deal because I was prepared for it to not be good.
You know, or like, when I was dating my ex-girlfriend,
like I really wanted to go to Disney World with her because she's a huge Disney fan.
And like there was nothing I could imagine that would have been more fun for the two of us
than to go see a bunch of cool Disney shit because she would have been like losing her mind.
You know, as soon as we broke up, I like,
I had this moment of realization that I was like,
I no longer have any desire to go to Disney World.
Because as awesome as Disney World sounds like it might be,
going with someone who likes Disney, it would probably be the coolest thing ever.
But without that, it's like, I don't give a fuck about Disney.
All I'm going to go is like, I'm going to look and I'm going to see like,
Oh, hey, it's Cinderella.
I didn't like that movie.
That's a strong six maybe.
It was a five.
Yeah.
Like that's, that's exactly how I would be if I was there, you know.
I'd say, Hey, Cinderella, your movie fucking sucks.
I, something, something seems, something is a little bit crass and gross to me about the idea
of a place like Disney World where, yeah, you're, you're told,
commanded really by the marketing that, you know, this is a fun place where you will have fun
and you like buy into that idea and you go there and you have fun just as you were told to.
I know that to a certain extent, all, all forms of having fun will all,
to a certain extent, all forms of having fun require you to buy into the idea that you're
having fun.
So it's not, so it's not like it's unique to this, but something about the fact that this is
like a marketed product, a place of fun to which you're like, yes, fun sounds good.
Let's go and have something is very weird about that.
In my career as like a horribly cynical anime critic guy, like in the last, particularly lately,
like after I went through that phase in like the early part of this year where I wrote a bunch
of negative videos, then like there was a period where like it finally got to me that
so many people were like, do you just hate fun?
And I'm like, do, and I had this moment of like, do I hate fun?
Like, do I, did you hate fun?
Do I know what fun is?
And it was, it happened when I was watching Myriad Colors Phantom World and I almost wrote a whole
video about this, but I ended up writing something else about that show instead.
I would, I would click on a video titled, Do I Hate Fun?
Yeah, and it was, it was because there was a moment in the show that I could tell
was engineered to be fun, but I did not find it fun.
And then I realized that I could identify a similar moment in another show that I did find fun
and compare them and say like why one word and not the other.
And ever since then, I now have like, when I feel legitimate fun, when I watch something and I
have fun, then I can truly cherish it because I'm like, oh my God, it's happening.
I'm smiling.
I'm watching something and it's just making me smile.
This is, this is what fun is.
I know fun.
I can see fun.
I see you fun.
I see you over there.
That's what it was like at the fucking circus.
There was like some big muscular dudes like bouncing each other on this giant
high wire like trampoline thing.
The suspended, they were, they were flying like 30 feet in the air and like,
yeah, I was just sitting there.
Like I was on the edge of my seat.
Like I cannot believe how high these dudes are getting.
How high do you even have to be just to do something like that?
And, and yeah, I mean, I think to have genuine fun, you have to, you have to, I mean, it's,
it's okay to be, you know, told to have fun.
It's okay that you're like, go in with the expectation of having fun, but you have to,
in that moment, you have to forget that you're supposed to be having fun, right?
Yes, mandated fun is not work.
I got to say one of the coolest things.
This has been one of the best things about the crunchy roulette game that I started the other day
on a DigiRaptor Dark, which I just put out episode two of, I think today,
because it's a game where I just hit the random button on crunchy roll and I watch anything that
I've never seen before.
And like in the course of this, I, because I never have any expectations.
It's all shows I know nothing about pretty much.
And like when I get a show that I have no expectations for and it ends up like being
a lot of fun, then it's like such a surprise that it's like, whoa.
Like yesterday, me and Shade did it together.
Like we watched six shows together.
And the third one was an OVA called Cosplay Complex from like 2002.
And I'd never heard of it and I had nothing about it.
And it was a fucking blast.
And like I was laughing the whole time.
Like I thought it was fucking hilarious.
And I never heard of this thing.
And I was just like, what?
This is fun.
This is what fun is.
When something's good that you didn't expect to be good,
it just makes it that much better.
Yeah, definitely.
In my opinion.
Well, man, these character designs are pretty tight.
Yeah, it was a three episode OVA.
We watched the first episode and it was just, I mean, I literally thought,
like I didn't know anything about it.
I was like, this could be total garbage and it was not.
It was a lot of fun and I liked it.
Awesome.
Yeah.
I guess that about wraps up this podcast.
Oh, we've covered a lot of topics.
We went from pissing to the concept of fun in general.
A lot of pissing.
There was a lot of.
Yeah.
It was just on the nature of sort of depression
and the forces that keep you locked in your room
and what you may or may not choose to do about them.
Yeah.
Good stuff.
This was a blast.
I've had a great time here today.
Yeah.
If only Hippo could have been here.
Yeah, true.
True.
Yeah, his shitty internet is fucking him up.
He couldn't be here today, but we'll be back.
You guys should get me your audio as soon as possible
so I can upload this tonight.
Since I'm not going to be able to finish the podcast
that we recorded last week until probably next week.
So.
God damn.
Let me say real quick.
I uploaded a vlog on my fucking YouTube channel.
Oh, yeah.
I've been saying and putting out YouTube videos now.
Imagine that.
Yeah, I'm going to actually have to like subscribe to you
on the Procrastinator's channel.
Yeah, good idea.
I think I already subbed me on there.
Anyway, yeah, go and click my little icon here
and go and listen to me talk about art and stuff, viewers.
Yep.
And buckle your fucking seatbelts for next week
when I'll finally drop the epic bombshell that was last week's recording.
Oh, man.
The three and a half hour argument over what is the color yellow.
I'll bug other things.
That was not the whole thing, but it was the worst part of it.
And the best part.
It was the worst and best part.
It depends on your definition.
It was it was just the worst.
All right.
See you next week.
Bye, everybody.
Bye.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money.
I'm supposed to be creating money.
Think that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius.
That's what they came for.
Instead, I'm tweeting hashtag repeating.
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah, it's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life, being a genius.