Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick I'm jerking.
Myself I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't wanna do it.
Hi, I'm Digibro.
Nate wanted me to edit this video because he's trying to edit his video.
And he doesn't want to procrastinate his video by editing The Procrastinators Podcast about procrastination.
So I put it off for a day and a half to play Bloodborne.
Now I'm trying to finish it up.
But I'm just gonna let Jesse's song do all the work for me.
Yeah.
It's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life.
Being a genius.
Hey everybody, welcome to The Procrastinators Podcast.
I'm Digibro and I am supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not doing shit.
What are you guys doing? Who are you?
I'm Guy. I'm the best guy ever.
You know, it's come to my attention recently that I've been putting a lot of work into these podcasts, eating up like all my weekend time.
So I've been literally, The Procrastinator Podcast has been causing me to procrastinate from my best anime evervids and all kinds of shit.
So how's that for a medic shit?
Likely excused. Hippocrite, what's going on with you?
That's me. I'm Hippocrite and here I am.
What are you supposed to be doing right now?
I'm supposed to. I'm supposed to be relaxing after a hard day's work, but I didn't do the hard day's work yet.
Isn't that the worst?
When it's like, the whole day has gone by and it's like, I don't know, like nine o'clock at night and you're like shit.
I kept pushing shit back and now it's nine and I'm supposed to be done and I still have everything I was supposed to do today.
I need to make an appointment to get my oil changed, my fucking car and I haven't done it for like four weeks now.
So it's not even like...
I guess I can't ask this question. You guys both take a lot of work on your videos, yeah?
Like your content takes pretty considerable...
I just work really slowly in the writing phase, but yeah.
But both of you guys are pretty infrequent uploaders, so that time has really felt strongly.
You know, I feel like guys who must have it good in terms of feeling like they're working all the time,
there's got to be guys like YMS where it's like, it takes them an insane amount of effort to put out their video,
but they still get out one a month, so...
Yeah, that's the dream.
It feels like the amount of work and the amount of time it takes are very equivalent and I bet he feels pretty fulfilled that way.
Yeah, and I bet he's really fucking busy.
I believe him when he talks about how Mahardi works and how he's fucking grinding away all the time.
At the same time, me and DeVu have talked about how we think that YMS possibly...
The way he schedules his work or the way he does it probably takes longer than it needs to.
He seems like his process is overly complicated and that's part of why it takes so long.
He has to do his research. It takes him a while to find all that shit.
It results in good things. Sometimes it goes too far with the Senecti thing that he admitted was bullshit,
but you know, it's a rarity.
YMS is what I say when I go to the doctor and they tell me I have multiple sclerosis.
YMS more like, what a mess, am I right?
Oh, zaydam.
Yeah, it's weird for me because my videos take very little time to make.
I envy that so much.
The thing is that everyone thinks I'm really prolific,
but I could be doing so much more that I always feel like I'm sitting...
The amount of videos I put out, people always leave comments like,
oh, this must have taken so much work and it's like...
I mean, you're talking about editing stuff.
You're pretty quick at writing a whole thing down and then recording it.
Yeah, well, it's that I just have a lot of general knowledge about things,
so it doesn't take me a long time to research,
and I know exactly where to research when I do,
so there are times when I spend more time on it when I go out and try to find interviews and stuff,
but with anime, there's not a lot of that in existence.
With YMS, I imagine he has to go through hours of behind-the-scenes documentaries.
He probably watches all these event...
The After Earth video, I was like, where did you find all this shit?
Yeah, I know, it's crazy.
He's got all these TV interviews with Will Smith and shit,
and I'm like, with anime, you've got the one translated interview that exists on the internet.
Anything that comes out goes through ANN, so it takes five minutes to find it all.
Yeah, I'm experiencing this now, making a video about a game currently,
but the reason that I focused on anime,
I think I generally have more of a historic attachment to anime.
I've got strong feelings for anime, but my point is,
when I was thinking about how to make the channel,
I was deciding should I focus more on anime and more on video games,
and the thing that pushed it over the top was definitely like,
I do not want to have to fucking play a game and get footage and record it and download it.
I'm like, if I could just tour it to show, that's a million times easier, way better.
And right now, I just had to replay to get the exact footage I need this game several times.
It's taken hours, so it's like...
Yeah, that's exactly why I don't want to do more game videos,
because it just takes so long, not just because games are longer.
Imagine you're making a Bloodborne video, and that game, if you make a mistake,
you have to play the whole game again.
It's like, Jesus Christ.
Well, the thing is, for me, I prefer, and I wish more game videos would be this anyways,
and we kind of talked about this in the review rules video,
that I want to see more game videos that are just about specific aspects of a game,
and I think you could get way...
I want to be able to play a 20-hour game once, and get all the footage,
and then make three videos out of it, instead of making one.
And then it would feel a lot more justified, and a lot less...
With the Dark Souls and Bloodborne video I just put out,
it was about very specific things, and it was very general,
so for a lot of it I just used whatever,
and I took 45 minutes of my own Bloodborne footage,
just of showing off all the weapons,
because I just wanted you to have a sense of how they all worked,
and getting a few of the mechanics that I needed,
and then other than that, all of the footage was either from the let's plays that we did
of Dark Souls and Bloodborne, or just cutscene videos,
because every cutscene in the game is online,
so I would just search all the cutscenes, or pull other people's playthroughs,
because those are games that people have a lot of let's plays of, and stuff like that,
so yeah, just sort of cobbling together whatever footage I can find,
but certainly if I was doing a comprehensive analysis of Bloodborne,
I would have to either play through it five fucking times,
and have 70, no, probably over 100 hours of footage to sort through.
Like at the very least, if you want the three endings,
that's three playthroughs right there, and you can't go back, there's no going back.
The whole recording a lot of gameplay footage is the entire reason why GRPG exists on my channel.
Right, right, because you have it.
Well, I mean, I don't want to record a whole GRPG, because they're like the longest games ever, for a review.
Oh, you meant because you don't have the footage, because that's the show where you don't show anything.
Yeah, I don't show any footage, it's an excuse.
Oh, right, okay, I see.
For other things, I would just play the whole game, and since they're not usually too long, it'd be like, I don't know, nine hours.
I do think a lot of people are being like, because I know that, and Nate,
I know you're the kind of guy who you really want every video to be like your perfect vision, and to be like a perfect video.
True, but that doesn't mean it's an all-encompassing thing.
Yeah, and I think it's overboard with a lot of people, because I think we've gotten to a point where YouTube videos,
they have to impress you, but they don't have to be perfect anymore.
I think there was a time where if you wanted someone to sit down for 20 minutes, then you had to be sequelitis and really blow their mind with animation and stuff.
But Noah Caldwell-Gervais, that dude does 45-minute videos with no editing in his audio,
and the video is like, you can tell that he'll just turn on a game, play it for 45 minutes, and then just slap the footage he has in there.
It very rarely matches up to what he's saying, which as a result for me, I don't usually watch the video,
and therefore I usually completely lose track of what he's saying, because it's so unedited that I just can't possibly give a fuck.
So what we're saying really is if you want to get your own obstacles out of your way, if you're going to do something like this,
my approach is obviously the wrong one for making YouTube videos.
I don't know that it's the wrong one, it's just that I'm just saying that these days you can do less and get away with it.
Ultimately, the reason you're doing your videos that way is not to do it smart, it's because it's what you want to do.
That's right, I got a job when I work at it, so that I can make the videos that I want to make.
Because if you just wanted this to be a business decision, then you would just fucking make 5-minute chunk videos.
And make fucking Digi Bro videos. Nobody wants to do that.
Well, that's the funny thing, because in the month of January, I finished writing and doing all the audio for my Asterisk War series,
and they're all being edited by the DeVue.
So in January, all I had to do was let him make videos for me, and I was going to make enough money off of those.
As long as he made 3 videos, I'd make enough, and I knew he would do that, even though I have to pay him,
and I made a decent amount through ad revenue.
I should be doing a lot more, because I should be trying to have a buffer of money.
I should be trying to make enough money that I can save some, or think about my future and put some money into my future.
But I was just like, eh, I can skate by letting DeVue edit 3 videos for me.
I put out some stuff that was all non-patron videos, stuff that wasn't deep enough for me to patron it,
because I'm very particular. I'll only patron something if I think it's up to snuff.
So then this month, it was like, alright, I gotta get back in the game.
I gotta actually make one of my own videos, and I wrote that Dark Souls in Bloodborne 1,
and I was so scared of editing it, I was like, oh, it's going to be a nightmare.
The video was like 12 minutes long, and the editing took like maybe 4 hours.
Oh, that's a dream.
But there was so much more of me putting it off, because I thought it was going to be so much worse than it was.
I was like, oh, I can't possibly, I'm going to need beer, and I drank half a beer,
and then did the whole first half of the video in one sitting, and I was like, oh, that wasn't so bad.
A lot of it is just starting is the hardest part.
That's definitely true.
It's a lot worse when you don't know exactly what the footage is going to be,
or what you're going to have to put in there, because when you know exactly what it's going to be,
because me and Davoo have both taken up this method where we download everything we need before we start,
and then it's helpful in two ways.
Firstly, that you can just plug everything in very easily,
and secondly, that it's incentivized for you to finish the video faster,
because you need to get all these fucking files off your computer.
For instance, the Hideaki-Ano video, where there was footage from everything he ever worked on,
so I downloaded every single thing he'd ever done, and I knew exactly which clips I wanted for which part.
So editing that didn't take very long, in spite of how long the video was,
because I had all the clips right there, and I needed them off my computer.
That is a very wise way of doing things.
I usually find myself downloading materials like that,
but I pretty much always just try to get what I know the base thing I'll need,
like game footage or the whole show, or whatever that's going to be,
and then just the way that I do shit, I end up editing in a lot of extra shit,
so I have to go through all that whole process of downloading and waiting.
That's what I used to do, because it used to be that I'd get to a point in the video
where it's like, okay, well, nothing in the show really reflects this,
and now I've got to go find something else, so now when I first start, I'm like,
alright, this clip, this line in the dialogue I know is not in the show.
Let's go find a clip before we start editing, because it really takes you out of the groove
of editing when you're putting shit together, and then suddenly you hit a roadblock
and you don't have the footage, and you have to go find it somewhere,
and it's like, you completely stop what you're doing to go make something else.
Man, it's just, I do that, my whole editing process is just a continuous series of that.
Yeah, that's what it used to be for me, and I'm glad that Me and DeVu sort of changed gears a bit,
and now the only stuff that he really has to, because he puts together a document
for all these Astroscore videos where he'll write down everything he'll need for each line,
and then me and him go through it and find all this shit, so if there's a bunch of shows that he...
because there's a lot of, I make references to lots of things that he doesn't know,
because he's not an anime fan, or not a long time anime fan anyways.
I've been wondering how he dealt with that, not really, yeah.
Well, in the early days, because a lot of the older videos he did for me,
it was interesting because he would use stuff that I'd never even seen before.
Like, in the one where I explained what is anime and what isn't,
he brings in all these Tizuka clips from shows I'd never heard of,
because he was doing his own research.
I would write the video, and then he would have to go re-research the video
and learn it all for himself, and it had some interesting results,
but for these Astroscore ones, when there's parts where I'm like, you know,
there's, I'll say something like, in other generic anime of this type,
you know, and then he has to ask me, okay, what are other generic anime of this type?
I'll give him a list of like five shows, and he'll go download clips from those shows.
I'll come to you sometimes, and be like, did you, I need like a super robot moment,
like what can I use? I did that a couple times with the grown login one.
Yeah, for the getter robo clips.
And the G Gundam, which was actually one of my favorite moments in that whole thing.
Man, the fucking King of Hearts, holy shit, that was like the coolest thing that ever happened.
That was amazing, yeah.
I need to watch that show, and I don't want to sink fucking, what, like 24 hours of my life
into watching that show.
Yeah, it's fucking long, it's like 50 episodes.
It's 50 episodes, so 16 and a half hours, probably, 17 hours.
That's a long ass show for not needing to be.
You can skip a lot of it, like, there's a lot of episodes that if you can tell early on
that it's not going to be, like, because there's a lot of just stupid one-off episodes.
Hey, this is a good example of something that incentivized procrastination,
because I'm the kind of guy who is really uncomfortable with skipping anything in a show
when I'm going to watch it.
And as a result, I keep being like, I'll do it later, I'll get to that.
I wish that I'd seen G Gundam by now, but I haven't, because I've got this obsession
where I'm like, I have to watch it all, it's 50 episodes, it's a long ass time.
For me, it's all about measuring exactly how much do I give a fuck
and how much am I going to miss out on, because unlike you, I spoil myself for a lot of stuff.
And a big part of that, I make it sound sometimes like I just go out of my way to spoil myself,
but it's more like I hang out in the community for long enough
and you're going to get spoiled for everything.
Like, there's not a gamer alive who doesn't know about Eris dying in Final Fantasy 7
because it was spoiled like a week after the game came out in a magazine.
So if you even read gaming magazines, you'd know.
A bunch of cock knobs, we'd do that, fuck them.
And it became like a really infamous spoiler that everyone knew it.
So like no one's going into that game not knowing that.
And like, there's a lot of stuff that I just glimpse on TV, because I grew up,
G Gundam was on Cartoon Network when I was like 13.
So like I'd seen a bunch of it, I got the point, you know.
And so when me and my friend finally like marathoned the whole show,
then there was a lot of episodes where we'd be like,
oh, this is an episode about Neo-Mexico, which is never going to be relevant again.
Yeah, let's skip that, you know.
Because a lot of them are like...
That's racist dog, that's racist.
Well, a lot of them are like really corny sob stories.
You know, it'll be like, oh, Neo-Mexico's sister was captured by the cartel
and he has to fight and then it gets all emotional.
Oh my god, Jesse Wood joins us.
Wow, that's really funny.
Oh, hey, what's up?
Alright, Jesse.
Now we got to sync our audio with Jesse Wood.
Alright, on the count of three say procrastination.
One, two, three.
Procrastination.
That sounded terrible.
Jesse, what have you been procrastinating on joining the podcast by doing?
I want to die.
You can't escape the dream through death.
Is that an answer?
No, I guess it's not.
Are you saying you're procrastinating on dying?
Yeah, just do it already, faggot.
Procrastinating on life because I'm dead inside.
I do like the idea of, you know, I've been wanting to kill myself for years
but it's just so much effort to load the shotgun.
Well, that's not quite exactly the reason that guys like Sato and NHK don't do it.
But at times they're like, man, I just want to die but it's such a fucking bother.
I don't want to go through all that shit.
That's a different sort of thing, I guess, though.
Man, let me tell you guys, I have been the least motivated to do anything that I've been in years.
It's been swell.
And by swell, I mean it's been hell.
Hell in a swell.
I've been pretty unmotivated myself.
Well, you know, I was telling that story earlier, Jesse wasn't here,
but I was talking about how in January DeVue had all my work covered, so all I did was play.
It was kind of cool because I finally got around to playing all the Souls games
just because I didn't feel like I had to do anything and I was like, fuck it, I'm just going to do this.
It wasn't even like, I thought I was just going to play Bloodborne and then play the Witcher 3
because those are the two games that I really wanted to play.
And then I got so hooked on Bloodborne that I was like, I have to finally do Dark Souls.
And then after I did Dark Souls, I was like, I have to finally do Demon Souls.
And then you got to Dark Souls 2 and you're like, I do not have to play Dark Souls 2.
That's exactly what happened.
I'm still struggling with it.
I kind of want to try to play the PS3 version and see if it's less frustrating than Scholar of the First Sin,
but I suspect it's not.
I thought they'd have made it better because it was already pretty shit in the original version.
Yeah, well, they tightened up a lot of things, but they also added a lot of enemies.
I don't want to talk about Dark Souls 2, it's stupid.
Yeah, I do want to talk about what I want to talk about.
What I want to talk about is a better game than Bloodborne, which is a piece of shit.
Oh no.
How can you even say that shit?
How can you say that in my life?
Jesse is an advocate of, he's a star.
It'll be okay.
Jesse will beat Bloodborne one day and he'll like it.
You know what?
I don't even want to argue.
You're right.
It's the best game ever.
You were singing about how tough the heart it was and how much you loved it,
raping you in your face constantly.
Who are you?
What happened to that handsome young man?
Shut up.
Who is this guy?
No, but Jesse did make a good point earlier,
because I knew the answer to that when I said,
we were arguing earlier for the people listening to the podcast,
and I said, what happened to the guy who sang the song about liking games
that are hard in the Demon's Souls video?
And I know exactly what happened to him.
He got older and doesn't have time for shit anymore,
and isn't into doing that, which is the same for me.
That's why I've always said that I don't think any game is hard if it's a good game,
because the only thing that makes a game hard is that you have to learn how to play it
and do the same thing until you know what to do.
The hard thing is just having the patience for it and wanting it.
I guess there's some games that are probably just so hard in terms of dexterity
that if it's a certain kind of platformer game
where you just have to be able to move your hands fast enough.
DDR is hard for really fat people.
Yeah, I'm completely uncoordinated, so DDR is really difficult.
I mean, I guess I could eventually learn it,
but I don't know if I'd ever be able to move my legs that fast
without literally beefing up myself and getting strong for the sake of DDR,
which again would make it easy.
It's just a matter of what you're willing to put yourself through.
I no longer have the patience for anything.
I hate exerting any effort whatsoever for anything.
I hate doing anything or having to do anything.
I can't stand learning new things.
It's like poison to me, the concept that I might have to learn something new
or read a set of instructions or work my way around something.
Just for this very podcast, I had to go figure out how to make audio
two keyframe transitions and animate that thing.
I don't even know what that is.
I taught Demu, I showed them the shit.
Look at us, Jesse, we're all learning things.
You gotta get out there and mix it up.
With Bloodborne though, because I didn't play Bloodborne for all that time
because I thought it was too hard.
I played it when it first came out and the loading screens were really, really bad.
Every time I died, I was just like, I don't want to play this anymore.
The loading screens are way too fucking long.
The reason I ended up playing it was just that I learned everything about it
from watching Victor play and watching other people play.
I was like, well, what I came to realize is that that game is so much fun
just to play that I didn't even care if I made it anywhere.
I figured that I could just play every level over and over again
and it would always be fun because the combat is fun.
That's kind of what I did.
I just played through the first area until I was so overpowered
that there was nothing that they could do to me.
Then I went to the next area and I played that until I was so overpowered
that there was nothing they could do to me.
Then by that point, I was so overpowered that the entire game was easy.
I never had to fight a boss more than three or four times at the absolute most
and just kind of steamrolled the whole game.
There was a guy in a...
No, go ahead.
Well, what I was trying to talk about ages ago
is conversely to all of you who are all feeling very unmotivated.
I have recently become...
I'm not feeling unmotivated.
But you said you were.
You said you were unmotivated for stuff.
I never said that shit.
They were saying it.
I never heard that.
Jesse, I think.
Whatever hippo.
I don't...
I have become much more motivated to do stuff
like progress in some sort of work every day, much more recently
than I have ever in my whole life.
I've been going into...
I've got a university and I'm doing an animation for my final film.
For my final year.
You know what I...
And I've been going in every day to the library to work on it from,
I don't know, like 12 to 6 and then coming back and then playing games
and it's been cool.
Oh, that's the dream.
You know, hippo, I remember a few years ago
when you were always talking about how unmotivated you are
and a lot of the problems you had.
And I kept saying, you're going to turn 22 or 23
and then you're just going to suddenly be motivated.
Yeah, yeah.
I am 22 now.
Yeah, because I remember having this conversation
because I felt the same way.
And then you'll turn 26 and you'll never be motivated again.
Well, because when you're up until your early 20s
your brain is just not finished developing yet.
And for me, when I was a teenager and when I was 20 and 21
I just had no desire to do anything.
And then it just kind of clicked and I was like,
oh, now I want to do stuff all the time.
Now I don't ever want to not be doing something.
Well, it's not that I love doing stuff.
I do love doing stuff, but it's always been difficult
to get into that groove.
Yeah, the mindset.
So I've just been figuring out how to force myself into that mindset.
Getting into a pattern like that is the best thing.
The most productive time of my entire life, by far,
was when me and my brother were doing T-Bab episodes
every Saturday morning.
We would crank those motherfuckers out.
And we were highly motivated.
We were fucking achieving our dreams.
It was awesome.
As unmotivated as Jesse is,
he is still producing a lot of content without even trying to.
I should rephrase it.
It's not that I'm unmotivated.
It's that I'm sick and tired of being motivated.
And I wish I could be unmotivated.
It's like an addiction.
Creativity is a serious addiction for me.
I can't stop it.
That's kind of how I felt when I played all the Souls games.
It was like I had to physically rip myself away from that obsession
with I have to be making something.
It just gets me to a point where I just realize
it's too much effort to organize my thoughts
because my thoughts are like a swirling ball of chaos.
It takes effort to organize it into concise little videos and shit.
And I realize it gets to the point where
I'll never be able to make videos as fast as I can write videos.
So no matter what I do,
I'll always have a backlog of 50,000 fucking ideas that I want to do.
So eventually, I just got to say,
someone come here and kill me.
Come to my house and put a gun in my asshole and pull the trigger.
If that really is an issue,
you should consider getting an editor or something.
I don't know how that would work.
For me, for all the time you see videos coming out on my channel,
all the time I'm not making them is me obsessing over what I should be making.
Every time I finish a video, my immediate thought is,
okay, what's the next one?
And then it's just this long period of figuring out what the next one is.
There's no celebration when you post a video.
There's a window of a couple hours after we're at peace.
There's a window where I...
For me, it's as long as the comments last.
Because basically, comments typically last about two days
before you stop getting new ones or they slow down considerably.
And there's that initial point when you post a video
and then you get a couple hundred comments,
at least for me I do because I get a lot of comments on my videos,
and that early period where I'm just reading all the new comments
as they come in and responding to them really actively,
that's the big come period where it's just like,
okay, I have finished this thing, it's done, now I get to enjoy it.
My sense of peace only lasts until I see the first comment.
That's a window we can believe in.
Well, most of my comments are positive,
so for me it's always like...
Because by the time I'm done with the video,
I've always totally lost faith in it because I've now heard it 20 times
and I'm questioning it already.
So with the Dark Souls and Bloodborne one,
I guess another way to put it is that I become so familiar with the idea
that it doesn't seem like a revelation to me.
It seems like something I've known forever.
All the time.
So I put it out and I'm like, what the fuck?
Everyone knows this clearly.
And then it's not until people start commenting
and they're like, wow, you really opened my eyes.
I never thought about this and I'm like, okay, cool.
Yeah, that's a relieving thing to say.
I legit thought my both girl and Logan videos were complete garbage
when I released them.
My friends are just going to make fun of me.
What was I thinking releasing this piece of absolute trash?
No, they were great.
It came out okay though.
But I don't feel like I'm the arbiter of if my videos are even good.
I guess nobody is.
Yeah, I mean, we all kind of feel like that.
I feel like that every time I make a video.
It's one of those things.
You just got to have people reassure you that it's actually cool
because they haven't seen it yet.
You got to gaze into the void and then hope it gazes back favorably.
You've been spoiled for your own content.
I definitely have a lot of...
I am the arbiter of whether or not my content is good
because who the fuck is going to know
whether or not I achieved my goals better than me?
That's true.
It's not like I trust anyone else's judgment over myself,
but I just don't trust my judgment either when it's being released.
Who's opinion am I going to take on my videos?
My commenters? My commenters are fucking scum.
They're idiots. They're morons. I hate them all.
I have two different types of videos
that I have the ones that I know are good because I like
and I have the ones that I'm okay with because everyone else likes them.
All of my really long videos, I deeply love
and I don't care what anyone else thinks.
My psychopaths videos never got a whole lot of attention,
but I thought they were the best things I'd ever written
and I still think they're better than anybody else's content, you know?
I make no qualms about judging my own stuff against everybody else's.
I wouldn't do that in a video because it would look incredibly arrogant, you know?
But like...
I've made videos right now.
Yeah.
Well, it's not like a top ten video.
Like when I did my top ten videos, YouTube videos of...
Top ten people. Did you think sir? Shit.
Right. If I had done that and I included my own work,
then it would have had my psychopaths theories in it.
It would have definitely had the Hidey Ikeano videos in it.
It probably would have had my Evangelion analysis in it.
You know, maybe even my Nanoha one.
I almost wish that you had done that just so people could watch that
and be like, wow, fuck this guy.
Right.
Yeah, it would have been funny.
Maybe you should release a corrected version with just your videos.
I mean, I make my videos because I want someone to make something that I want to watch.
You know, it's like the whole point of me doing them is
no one else has done this idea yet and this idea is what I want to exist.
So I have to do it.
You know, I've had plenty of videos that I...
I've had plenty of videos that I didn't do specifically because someone else did it.
You know?
Right.
Like I would never want to do a video on Aldenoa Zero because
between demo and anime addicts, they both did great ones.
Although anime addicts channel has completely been taken down by YouTube.
So I...
Because he was a guy who like, he did a bunch of great videos
and then like quit because real life got in the way and he went off to go become an engineer.
And then I think in the time since he stopped doing videos,
he got three strikes and his channel got taken down.
Just didn't pay attention or something.
Yeah, while he was gone.
So yeah, like we've lost the best breakdowns of Aldenoa Zero
and what's it called?
That fucking... that Watanabe show that wasn't good.
Zankono Terror.
Oh yeah, yeah.
He had great videos on those and they're gone now, but like...
Too bad.
I wouldn't want to cover something that someone else already did a great job on.
I cover it because I don't think anyone else has said what I want to say.
And so it only makes sense that those would be some of my favorite videos
because it's something I wanted to see.
That's true.
Yeah, generally, I generally don't look at the reviews of the games that I want to talk about
because I just want to talk about them.
It's never really... I want to, you know, make a big splash with this one
or I want to blow people's minds.
I just want to talk about the games I like.
You got to shoot for the moon because even if you miss, you'll land among the stars.
Oh, I never thought of that.
Yeah, yeah.
But, you know, it's just...
Something about the way... well, never mind.
I was going to make a Bloodborne reference, but you're not far enough in the game.
Nothing is...
I've seen the whole thing.
Relieving to me, then when one of you guys is going...
says you're going to make a video on something that I also want to make a video on
because I feel like I can trust you all to make a good video on it, and then I don't have to.
Oh, I've had a lot of...
I've told Nate...
I've told Nate that he's going to do a fucking Undertale video.
I'm like, thank God, take all my Undertale notes, throw them in the fucking trash, throw a match in it, because I don't care.
Yeah, no, I told Nate before that, like, uh...
I mean, that's also why I didn't do an Undertale video, because when I played it, I was like...
Oh, man. All this pressure.
It's going in the trash.
When I played through the game, I was like...
I feel like I could knock something out on this really quick, and it would be...
It would get a lot of attention, but I didn't want to undercut Nate,
because I felt like he would say all the things I said, but do a better video.
I promise it is coming.
I'm working on it all the time.
So, like, immediately...
I'm never going to do a Girl in the Gone video, because you did the perfect...
I mean, I already have one where I compared it to Kill Out Kill, but...
I don't think anyone else could do one without at least acknowledging the king in the room.
Who could follow that up? Nobody.
I did my one where I compared it to Kill Out Kill, which is a great video on its own,
but I would never try to do a full-on analysis, because you covered everything.
And when you said you were going to do Ghost in the Shell standalone complex, I was like, cool.
I don't have to go in depth on that show, because he's going to do it,
and I could go do something that you will never do.
Yeah, please.
I guess when it comes to, like, things that you want to see exist.
Because, like, I don't know.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Well, I was just going to say that...
I've said this several times before, but when I was making the Girl in the Gone video,
I did watch, like, every video I could find about it,
and found them woefully inadequate.
So I felt, you know, the need to do it.
I mean, I've done it both ways.
Because, you know, I like watching analysis videos all the time.
So, like, inevitably, if a good one exists, then I'm going to see it.
But usually, I have to do a video because I haven't seen a good one.
And if I haven't seen one at all, it's very unlikely I'm going to find one.
Because, like, I follow all the people who I think are doing really great work.
So even if, let's say, I was going to do some show and, like, a bunch of people have reviewed it,
but if it's not anyone I follow, then there's a good chance there's not any good reviews of it.
Or any that I would want to see.
So, like, yeah, it's not like I'm going to cancel my video just because a lot of people covered it.
It has to be someone good.
I have notes for my Japanese anime, Girl in the Gone.
And all the notes say, it just says, Gundam Lagann.
Nice.
And then under that, it says, fuck it.
And that's the whole...
You should release it as that.
So, apparently, between the first joke and then Nate made his video.
Now, let me tell you, you were on to gold with that first line.
You should follow that and see where it logically leaked.
Did you already do Attack on Gundam?
Yeah, he did.
How did you not watch Girl in the Gone in, like, ten years?
It's been, like, ten years.
Every show about big dudes just eat Gundam Axe.
It was going to be, like, a running joke that everything is Gundam for my Japanese anime.
Which is great.
I like that joke.
But I hardly ever make them anymore, so it's taking a while.
Especially because, like, I can't tell if you...
I should just make the whole video.
It should just be Gundam Lagann, fuck it, at the end.
Yeah.
My favorite thing about that joke is that I'm not sure if you've ever seen any Gundam before.
I've never seen Gundam.
Any of them.
Perfect.
Even better.
No, I saw a little bit of Gundam.
And I never will, because if I do it, I'll ruin the joke.
Yeah, you don't want to know.
Yeah, no, you don't need to.
Like, I don't see you ever trying to wrap your head around Gundam.
It's a bit much.
Does Gundam stand for something?
Is there meaning in that word?
Uh, I think the Gundam is made of Gundaneum.
It's just got a damn gun on it.
Oh, it's named after Gundaneum.
Okay.
Yeah.
Of course, of course.
I believe that's the case.
It's when you see the gun, they go, damn.
Damn.
Gundam.
It's a gun.
It's a gun on a den.
They shoot the den.
The damn gun.
None of us are going to get that, because I don't watch weeb shit.
Uh, so, I mean, so, like, what we're saying is, I think, like, the whole point of this
was, like, content is, there's all these obstacles.
You gotta pick your shit.
Yeah, the point is, we are doing our best just to wait.
Yeah.
Videos are coming, guys.
Well, I think this is something everybody can relate to who's done creative work.
Yeah.
We all procrastinate.
Or even not creative.
Just, like, you gotta do your homework, and it's like, fuck it.
I don't want to do that shit.
That's happening to me, like, just last week.
I'm taking this class forever.
I never did my homework.
Me neither, dude.
Actually, that was the worst period of my life.
Like, procrastination was really the cause of my, well, I don't know if it was the cause,
but it was like, what was perpetuating my depression back when I was in high school?
That's interesting about that, though, because procrastination really does just, like, okay,
what is procrastination at the end of the day?
You have goals that you want to accomplish.
If you just don't do them, that's procrastination, really.
So, like, yeah, if you aren't doing in your life what you want, then, yeah, you're gonna
be depressed.
Well, what drove me nuts back in high school was that, because I would fall into this loop,
and I'm sure a lot of people are gonna be like, oh, my God, you're making me cry because
this is my life.
Yeah.
So, back in high school, you know, I'd get a lot of homework, and then I'd come home,
and I would have that feeling like the homework is the only thing I should be doing.
Yeah, yeah.
But I wouldn't want to do it.
But as a result, I wouldn't do anything else, because I felt like I should be doing my homework.
Oh, shit.
But I wouldn't do the homework.
So, every night, I'd come home, and I'd just sit on Instant Messenger talking to my friend
on who was a Hikikomori at the time, like, full-blown, like, as in not in school, not
in anything, just in his room, pissing in bottles.
Has he seen NHK by any chance?
Oh, yeah.
We bonded over NHK when we first met.
That's sort of how we became friends was by talking about that show, because he was a
full-blown Hikikomori, and I was a borderline one.
I was still in school, but he had to drop out because he had a medical ailment where
he got headaches that were, like, insanely intense every morning.
Yeah.
That sucks.
So, we would sit there on Messenger, and I would just tell him, like, you know, I wouldn't
watch any anime because, like, because to me, I've always regarded watching anime as,
like, a goal.
Like, that is accomplishing something to me, because it's always been, like...
It's better than doing nothing.
It's better than just jacking off or something.
Right.
Well, I've always been writing an anime blog, and, you know, even back before it was my
job, I was very passionate about doing it.
So to me, watching an anime was always a part of doing my job and, or getting things done,
but I wouldn't do it because I'm like, well, I can't really watch anything because I should
be doing my homework, and I just sit there all day and do nothing and just be super depressed
and fucking want to kill myself by the end of the day.
That's a very familiar feeling, and I think every person here can probably relate to it.
I resent the idea that watching anime is better than jacking off.
Oh, a lot of the times it's the same activity.
Sure, you do have something physical to show for it at the end of jacking off.
I'll give you that much.
Yeah.
Talking about jizz, people.
Talking about jizz.
Don't even get me started on jacking off as a method of procrastination.
Yeah, it's...
I actually, I think I jack off more to procrastinate than to actually satiate my human needs.
Well, I'd say jack off once a day is probably, like, the maximum you need to do to get yourself.
Oh, man.
I...
All right.
I'm just saying need.
I'm saying need.
Okay, yeah.
There is no maximum.
Let's stop that kind of thought right now.
I'm saying to satiate your needs.
I actually think there is, like, I mean, there's obviously a physical capability maximum where
you jerk off so many times you can't anymore.
But I've actually had that moment in the song Long View by Green Day where he says, like,
when masturbation's lost its fun, you're fucking lonely.
And I've had that moment where I jacked off so many times that it just wasn't actually fun anymore.
And I was like, I'm done.
Like, this is the most bored I've ever been in my life.
I mean, you've got issues of chafing to deal with as well, and you know, there's all kinds of shit.
If you're going to go long, you've got to prepare.
Well, it's just like, when you go, like, two days in a row and all you really did was jack off all day,
that's when it gets to that point where you're like, what is my life?
What am I doing?
See, I haven't actually done that yet.
I don't jack off all that much.
Hey, no more procrastinating.
I procrastinate on my jacking off.
I have made by working on a goal before.
I've had several times where I've tried to hit the 12 in one day.
Oh, okay.
I procrastinate jacking off by joining a church.
You know what?
I think jacking off might be the only activity that I do just for fun, not trying to make something out of it.
Yeah, okay.
It's pretty often the one I jump to.
And well, because there's a line in there.
Because everything else, like, I can't do anything unless in my brain, I'm telling myself that it's for a video.
If I want to sit down and play a video game, I have to tell myself, well, I'm going to do a let's play,
or I'm collecting notes for a review.
Oh, shit.
Text just pledged the best guy ever, five bucks.
Thank you, text.
That's how it is for me too, Jess.
And it was a true revelation when I managed to play the Souls games and not feel that way.
And it was only because DeVoo was doing so much work for me that I felt like I had time.
And I was able to just sit down and enjoy all three of them.
And then, of course, I had a bunch of ideas for videos anyway.
So I was like, no, I got to make the most out of the three weeks that I spent playing video games
because it's a healthy process, I think.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a lot better than if I hadn't played them at all and was sitting around for three weeks.
But even Jersey Office has become...
Unless you're no longer some asshole who says it's his favorite game and hasn't even beaten it.
Right.
Even Jacking Office has sometimes become a thing that I did to try to accomplish a goal.
Because in The Venture Brothers, there's an episode where there's this group called The Sphinx,
and Brock Samson was a part of it.
And they're all like...
The guy is like...
The leader of the group's like, we don't keep any secrets here.
Men sound of them.
They're all like saying things that they did that are like secretive.
And Brock Samson goes, I once jacked off 12 times in one day just to see if I could.
And I was like, 12 times, huh?
It's pretty hard.
That sounds pretty rough.
Never have actually made it.
It's a lot harder than it sounds.
It's probably above most human's capability, really.
I think I made it to 10 months.
Do you have to take like a five minute break in between?
You can take whatever breaks you want.
If you came, that's what I would count.
This is why everyone should play Starless.
Yeah, this is very related.
Go play Starless.
I don't think I could jack off to that game.
You never know until you try, my friend.
Well, yeah, okay.
Well, I guess if I was actually trying, I could probably do it.
I mean, some of the scenes are very pleasant, you know?
That was kind of my prize for putting up with all the food.
Now I've just got in my head the idea of playing games while jacking off
like as a skill thing.
Like a speed runner would jack off while playing.
That's why they made Bayonetta playable with only one hand.
You can just play that game.
Better yet, Dead or Alive 2.
I've been there.
You can play Dead or Alive 2 entirely.
Well, the problem is you can only do that with the right hand.
You can only play it one-handed with the right hand.
Luckily for me, I'm left-handed.
It's more of a you did it to say you did it thing
than it is an actual, like, I'm going to do this as a regular activity thing.
What I meant, though, was like, you know those speed runners and those live streams?
Yeah.
I bet anything Lobos could beat Dark Souls while jacking off.
I would bet anything on that.
Can you do it with only one-half and eight-press?
Have you ever heard of Lobos, either of you?
Yeah, I've heard of him.
He's like a famous speed runner guy.
He's the guy who does challenge runs of Dark Souls.
And he's done, like, every retarded, insane, like, you know, level one, no items, no weapons,
fighting the final boss on level eight plus seven.
I think I might have seen his YouTube channel if he has one.
Yeah, he's...
Because I saw him do, like, a run where he was level one and he had that, the, you know,
the chest helmet thing that drains your health slowly.
And he played the entire game like that with no weapons.
Yeah, he will do any retarded challenge you can come up with.
Because I'm pretty sure, I mean, when I thought about it, it makes sense because I'm sure he gets,
he's a sponsored Twitch player, so he's getting paid to just be on Twitch.
So it really doesn't matter how much time he wastes fucking around in a game.
Like, yeah.
Because some of those runs, like, you'll see the final, like, you'll see the video on YouTube
where he beat it, and that'll be a 45-minute video.
And then you're just thinking, think of all the times he died with one hit left.
So many.
And how many days this must have taken.
But if he gets paid just to play the game, then it really, it doesn't matter.
He can play it all day and it's his job.
That's true.
What's up with...
If you were a professional streamer, you know, like, I get the feeling that, like, streaming won't last forever.
And what...
I mean, how much money do these people make?
Are they making enough to, like, save for the future?
I really don't know.
Are they hoping to, like, transition to something else?
Or maybe streaming will just last forever, and I'm just being a Debbie Downer.
Let me ask you guys, have any of you ever watched the YouTube channel Crazy Russian Hacker?
Once or twice, yeah.
So Crazy Russian Hacker is a guy who does these really terrible life hack videos.
Yeah.
And he's, like, this Russian dude, his motto is,
safety is my number one priority.
Right.
He's, like, partly it's the accent and partly he's, like, borderline retarded.
Oh, that's not true.
He's a football.
He's definitely an idiot.
There's videos that reveal that he's probably an idiot.
Okay, well, I haven't done the research, so maybe...
He also made a whole video about how the proper way to eat a, quote, muffin, and it was a fucking cupcake.
Wait, who are we talking about?
He's Russian.
Maybe it's a language barrier.
Crazy Russian Hacker.
Anyway, this guy makes these terrible life hack videos, and they're all stolen.
It's all ideas from around the internet.
He puts out a video every fucking day.
He just finds a life hack.
Is it someone's intellectual property, though, to, like, have a method of how to do it?
Not really, but it's, I mean...
I'd like him to get credit, though, I guess.
All right, here's the thing.
Look.
Yeah.
I don't think he gives credit.
He just makes life hack videos.
It's just obvious that he got them from other places.
I mean, and who the fuck can come up with a life hack every day?
Most of them are stupid and repetitive and dumb, right?
Well, my friends have been watching him, like, ironically, for years.
They, like, they'll make, like, they'll just send each other his videos as a joke and stuff like that.
Sure.
Because it's so stupid.
Well, the thing is, he's huge now.
Dude has five million subscribers, almost, right?
Yeah.
Puts out a video every single day, and all of them have half a million views.
Now, recently, apparently, you know, my brother Victor's been watching him for years, and he
was, like, originally, he was doing these in his mom's kitchen at her house, right?
Well, he'll have this intro where you see him going into a house, and Victor's, like,
it's this really nice house in the mountains, and what I gradually realized is that that's
his house.
He has bought a really nice house in the mountains on the back of this YouTube money,
and I was, like, I was, like, show me his channel.
How much is it?
Let me try to figure out how much he's making.
Now, I know that a thousand views is about a dollar.
Yeah.
Five hundred thousand views is about five hundred dollars, and he puts out a video almost every
day, meaning he makes almost five hundred dollars a day on ad revenue, and he's bought
himself a house in the mountains with that money, from which he does life hack videos
that probably cost ten dollars to make in his kitchen, and I thought, what are we all doing
with our lives?
Really?
That's the...
Being stupid.
Yeah.
I mean, we can't all be that guy.
We can't, like, emulate him and hope to achieve that kind of success.
Those sorts of things just happen.
But, I mean, I have no problem with him profiting off such a thing.
I just wonder, you know, how far is it going to go?
It just makes me wonder, what are we thinking when we're putting so much into these videos?
Right.
Yeah.
Totally.
And, like, all we really need to do is, every single day, look up something on the internet
that sounds like it would make a good video, spend ten dollars at Walmart buying water balloons,
and then, like, explaining how a water balloon can be used as a tampon or something.
That's all you have to do.
I'll tell you what it is.
It's entirely ego.
I make the kind of videos that I make because I see myself as a smart guy, and I'm like,
of course I'm not going to make shitty videos.
I'm going to make the fucking best thing in the world, and I am directly financially hurt
by making that decision.
Well, the sad thing is that, like, I've had a lot of times where I've sat there and gone,
like, it would be so easy to open up an alternate channel and just not associate it with my identity,
or even if I don't even care, fuck, associate it with my identity, use it to promote me,
and I could easily be cranking out videos all the time that were just, like, cheap,
but it's, like, knowing that it would take away from the time I spend on my main content,
or that it could eventually, because, like, you know, because we've all seen what happened
with Game Grumps, where it was like, they didn't think it would take away from it,
but then once it was the main revenue stream, then it was like, well, we might as well
spend more time on Game Grumps, because it makes a lot more money.
Why the fuck wouldn't we, you know?
And so, like, there's always that fear.
But then at the same time, I would totally love to have Game Grumps positioned.
I'd love to have some easy fucking job that prints money, and I could just do,
I could take my sweet time on the passion projects, you know?
I shit on Game Grumps a lot, especially to you guys, because I think it's lazy
and not particularly valuable, and, you know, we've all got our different feelings about it,
but, yeah, there's no doubt that...
I mean, you've kind of taken the...
You're basically doing that because you have a real job,
so you're basically doing another job, you know?
I like to think that my life choices were made based on this core belief
that I have then, you know, extrapolated into how I live my life.
So, it's not like I decided that, then decided the Game Grumps were shit, or whatever.
Yeah, but I just mean that, like, if I could turn YouTube into a job,
because it is my job, you know, but I don't handle it like a job,
I handle it like art, and there's times where those conflict with each other
where, like, I can't make a video that would take a month to make
because I just won't make enough money, you know, it can't happen.
I mean, how you told me right after I released my GERD Live video,
like, you wish you could make a video that would one-up it,
but, you know, it would take four or five months to do, so it's not even worth it.
Ben, my problem, my whole career, is the videos, the kind of stuff that I'm interested in making,
I know it's not the kind of stuff that is successful.
Yeah, and you have to ask yourself, like, is that wise?
Like, are we just being stupid by making these kind of decisions?
Even if it weren't successful, it would just...
The most important thing that I'm looking at right now is I've decided to make a whole concept album
about my friend Pete for no reason, and that's more...
That's not gonna make a lot of money.
No, no one's gonna get it, people are gonna think it's retarded,
but it's way more important to me, artistically, than anything else that I could be doing right now.
And that's exactly why I don't make a lot of music, because, like,
if I wanted to really, like, sit there and just polish an album,
and I mean, I make music really fast when I do it,
so even if I just set aside a week, I could probably make a pretty decent rap album,
but I had to set aside a week, you know, and I can't necessarily do that.
And, you know, that's why I was saying earlier about, like, YMS,
that I kind of envy getting into a cycle where, you know,
people are paying you enough that you can make one video a month and make it perfect, you know, and...
Yeah, that's the dream.
Well, I'm very envious of these guys, like, I kind of look down on them in sort of a snobbish way,
but I'm also envious...
Who have YMS or the...
...of guys who you watch their channels,
and it seems like they're only interested in making one specific genre of video or one kind of contract,
because that's good for them, because that's what works.
People like consistency.
Yeah.
But I can't help but look at it sort of snobbishly, like,
how can you call yourself an artist when you're just making the same shit over and over again?
That, I think, is overly simplifying.
Like, you're like always studying in Philadelphia, right?
Like, that's the same formula.
Yeah.
It's not, like, the highest art, obviously,
but I don't think it's fair to just say that, out of hand, it's a lower form.
Well, I'm saying I'm envious of it, because I kind of wish that I had that,
because I can't do things that way.
I'm incapable of focusing on one thing.
I've told a friend of the show, Mother's Basement, who we had on a few weeks ago,
like, that I'm...
Because he...
I'm envious of him because he likes everything to be a series.
Yeah.
Like, he does what's in an OP, now he's doing, like, he's doing a bunch of different types of analysis,
but they're all a series.
What's in a scene?
What's in a level?
What's in an OP?
You know, like, and he wants it all to be these ongoing things.
And I'm like, man, if I could do that, it would be so much...
It would make my life so much easier to know, at the end of every week,
that I can, you know, that the same video will come out.
And it's like, I just...
There's never been a concept that I wanted to do for that long.
And I tried, at the end of last year, I've told you guys about this.
I don't know if I've mentioned it on the podcast,
but at the end of last year, I tried to come up with a plan, like a syllabus,
to have one video come out every week, all year, for 2016.
And I had eight different series, which would come out bi-week, bi-monthly, rather.
And so it would be like, you know, you'd get four series one month, four series the next month,
and then you get each series again.
So each one would only have, like, four videos for that series coming out, or, no, six.
Six videos per series each year.
But it would be eight different series.
But, like, even within that structure of those, I kept boiling it down to, like,
well, I don't really want to do this one, or, like, I don't have enough ideas for this one to last.
So in the end, I was only left with, like, three that I still kind of want to do.
And even then, just a prospect of making something, and then knowing that in two months,
I'm beholden to make the same thing, is, like, too much for me.
Because, like, what if two months from now, I want to do something else,
but I have to make this fucking series, you know?
Yeah, put yourself in that position.
Do you have to have, like, a series with a time release schedule?
Uh, I guess not.
But, like, the concept at the time was that I was going to try to write all 52 videos before the year started.
Like, just write them all at once.
And I wrote, like, four of them, and then just kind of gave up, but, yeah.
I'm kind of actually trying to do that as well.
I want to write a bunch so that I can have one come out every month.
For guys like us, Kim, who have a harder time writing, that's probably a wise way to go.
Yeah.
Writing is hard, and I hate it.
Writing's easy for me.
Editing's hard.
And for me, the hardest thing is caring for a long time.
Like, the reason my videos get done so fast is because as soon as I'm done writing it,
I don't care about it anymore, so, like, it stops being interesting.
Like, those videos that I did write for last year, um, you know, I have them all,
and they're still good scripts.
But the idea of trying to make videos out of them now,
now that I'm, like, not that hype about it anymore, is, like, really difficult,
where I've got, like, a few that, um, like, one of them was the Top 10 Directing Tricks in Avangelion,
which is a great script, and people really want me to do another Avavid,
but, like, I put it in the editing bay, and I was just like,
Why did I write this months ago and not, I should've just edited it immediately as soon as it was done, you know?
As soon as I wrote it, back when I was still impressed with myself that I had written it, you know?
I have had times where I caught a second wind where I read an old script and, like, forgot how good it was
and wanted to make it a video again.
That is nice, but, yeah, it's good to capitalize on your creative spark when it hits as best you can.
I never have, like, ideas for scripts.
I always just go into thinking, like, I want to talk about this because I know I like it, but why?
Yeah, that's interesting.
It's sometimes really difficult to understand why, because I'm not very good at analyzing, like, myself and games and stuff,
but I just, I don't know, it's fun to talk about, so I still do it.
Well, I need to write a video for this.
What happens is that, like, I'll be, I'll just get something in my head and then I'll go, I gotta go and write this down before I forget it.
Then I'll write it, and then as I write it, more just pours out, and it goes, like, really easily.
And before I know it, oh, great, I have another entire fucking video I have to make.
Yeah.
For me, it's always having the, sort of, the first sentence, like, there's two ways that the videos come about.
Yeah, well, yeah, like, for that one, for instance, it was that I was bothered that the discussion on what is anime and what isn't was always being had,
and then I thought, like, here's how I would approach the argument, and then once I've thought about that, I always construct the first sentence,
and then I go from there.
So, like, yeah, with the anime as a Japanese colloquialism, like, that line was stewing in my head for days.
That's just a meme now, that's a hilarious line to me.
Yeah.
And it's often times that what'll happen is, I'll get the phrase, and then I'll go take a shower, and then while I'm in the shower,
I'll spend the entire shower just constructing the first sentence, or the first paragraph.
Oh man, I do that too, but I'm always scared that I'm gonna forget things before I get out of the shower.
It's anywhere where there's, like, no internet or no distractions.
You know where my sanctum of inspiration is?
Toilet, it's the toilet, right?
No, no, it's Walmart.
Cause, like, that's a good one.
Walmart is, like, where I go, like, it's usually, like, four in the morning when I go there.
No one's there.
Cause you have one in walking distance.
Yeah, and whenever I'm there, I'm just kind of an autopilot walking around.
And when I'm in Walmart, like, I'll wander around Walmart aimlessly for, like, 30 minutes, or 30 minutes to an hour,
not by anything, but then I'll have, like, 10 entire videos in my fucking head, and I gotta go home and write all of them.
I have a road next to my house that's, like, a mile long, and I'll walk down it almost every night and have a cigarette,
and, like, and that's where I usually try to come up with concepts.
But what happens is, if I don't have an idea for a video, then all I think about is, like, stuff about my life,
or, like, drama, or something I've been into, or something, like...
Yeah, yeah.
Like, a lot of the times it's just me thinking about how pissed off I am at somebody on the internet,
and, like, running through all the social reasons that I would be mad and, like, what it says about society as a whole,
and just getting so, like, angry.
And that's the kind of stuff that becomes...
You should, hey, everyone's making beef videos these days. Let's capitalize on that now.
Well, all of that stuff becomes Digi Bro's discussions, you know, like...
Yeah, yeah, that's inappropriate.
Anything I think about that can't be made into, like, a good video just becomes a Digi Bro's discussion.
But, like, when I'm in the middle of writing, then I'll often go for a walk to figure out what the next paragraph is gonna be.
The one that I did that the most with was the PsychoPass videos,
because there's, like, there's parts in there where I just drop, like, all these heavy concepts in a row,
and it was just, like, I write a paragraph and then go outside and walk around, have a cigarette, come back in,
just, like, keep walking around my house and doing laps and shit, like, trying to think of the next sentence.
That was the most, like, I ever felt, like, a writer, you know, like...
Yeah, yeah.
Because it comes so naturally to me that a lot of the times it's just I sit down and I pump something out,
and I'm like, well, okay, but then, like, that was the one script where it was, like,
I really had to struggle to think of how I'm gonna put this idea to words,
and it was the biggest come in the universe to actually do it.
Whoa, you said you sit down and you pump something out, and it was the biggest come in the universe.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Yeah, it's the PsychoPass and the Kaon videos.
Those were the ones that I had, like, the most, like, like, revelations when writing it,
where it was like, how do I put this?
And then I'd come up with the perfect phrase and be like, oh, my God, I finally did it.
I can finally explain what's so good about Kaon, you know?
Like, with Kaon, it was the phrase I kept saying throughout the whole video.
I kept saying, the more you watch of it, the more you like it,
and I said it so many times because it was such a revelation to me at the time that I was writing
that that was, like, totally how I felt about it.
I get so self-conscious of, like, my big lines whenever I'm going over a script,
especially after I've recorded it, and it's like, oh, God, I hope people don't hate me for overselling it.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a few lines in the Astroscore series where I either, like, if I think it's a corny line,
then I oversell it on purpose to show that I acknowledge that it's a corny line,
and then if I think it's really cool, then I just, you know, play it straight and...
Yeah.
Like, the lines that you did in part nine were definitely good,
but just, like, as a guy who makes kind of dramatic videos sometimes like that,
I just, I pictured myself doing that, and I was, like, projecting myself.
I was like, oh, I hope people don't think this is great.
But it wasn't at all. It was deserving.
Oh, apparently it was haunting and deep, and I got so...
Yeah, that was good.
I got, like, a few hundred comments about how...
Those marks.
I got, like, a few hundred comments about how that was my best video ever,
and it made them so emotional, and it was so depressing, which is great,
because that's exactly the intention.
I told DeVue, I was like, part nine has to depress people,
and I actually redid all the audio on it,
because the original one I did was more in line with the rest of the series,
and I was like, it has to be, like, really sobering and dark
and make you feel like shit afterwards,
and a lot of comments said that that happened, so I'm glad.
A lot of them, specifically because they were eating McDonald's when they watched it,
I got, like, ten comments to the effect of I was...
Or I ate McDonald's just before watching this, and now I feel really self-conscious,
and I was like, perfect.
I bet there were quite a few Monocles dropped at that moment.
Yeah, and then I had to point out to those people, like,
I ate McDonald's in the video.
You know, I wrote this video, and then I had to go buy and eat McDonald's,
and, like, and do that for the video, you know.
I felt just as bad as anybody.
Yeah, man, it's funny, it's just that that exact sort of thing
is really what I plan on doing with my...
And I've already got footage for it to do, like, a bunch of shit like that,
so it was probably my favorite moment of anything you've done in your entire filmography.
The live-action segment.
Yeah, just to, you know, make a...
You know, you've seen a million Digi videos.
He makes this change.
It's this related thing, the speech, the music.
It was just, yeah, good stuff.
Fun fact about that, it was totally half-assed and last minute.
That's great, that's great.
Because it was like, Javu went,
I don't have any ideas for this segment.
You should do a live-action segment, and I said,
okay, then I got Victor, and like...
Because Victor hates doing live-action for me,
but I was like, dude, this is the Astroscore,
it's my best video series, we have to nail it, you know.
And he just took a bunch of random shots of me.
Also, you're probably just like, you're going to McDonald's buying food,
so that's what, like, ten minutes, you know.
I was amazed by how many people were like, legitimately impressed with the filmography of that,
because it was not like, it wasn't staged or directed or anything,
it was just like, Victor just pointed a fucking camera at me while I got dressed,
and it just happens to be a fairly nice camera, so the visuals look clean, you know.
I happen to think that my filmography that I did in my, what was it,
like that little update, or the Final Fantasy 7 one where I was filming me driving,
I think that came out great, and that was me nearly killing myself driving in my car.
But my point is that I did actually set up a bunch of stuff,
like I had my DS at home, like paused on the exact screen,
and then I drove out to get footage, and yeah, so it worked out really well.
But it's like, just even doing live action footage when you're guys like us who do a lot of editing,
I'm not saying that makes it look better, but it's, you know, if you do even these, it's going to be...
It's just unexpected, and it shows up cool, and I told Victor like,
the only shot that I really care about is that we see the golden arches coming up in the distance,
which I didn't even end up using, because it didn't come out right,
because I thought it was a much taller sign, but the one that we went to had one of the little signs,
because to me it was so important, because what I'm trying to evoke there is that the reason...
Right, you see the arches and it recognizes you.
Well, to go in deep a little bit, the reason that so many places like that are they all look the same
is because they want it to be the same no matter where you are, where it's sort of atemporal.
Actually, one of the only good idea channel videos of the last two years was the one he did on hotels
and how they kind of exist outside of reality, because it's like you're always going to the same hotel,
like they're all the same place, because they try to be, which would have been an even better video
if he had done it about Walmart or something, because that's explicitly what they try to do.
They want it to be so that no matter what town you're in, you go into Walmart and it's always reliable,
and I've been to a lot of conventions or to concerts in other cities,
and when you do that, you almost always eat at McDonald's or Wendy's, because you recognize it and you know what it is.
There's probably a thousand great local restaurants near you, but you have no idea what they are,
so you're just like, oh McDonald's, yeah, but we didn't even really get that shot.
I really like that you had one shot in mind, because I don't want to spoil things for the future here,
but I've got the one piece video I'm working on, and I too had exactly one image and went out and got it
and then just got all this other shit, so when that comes out, listen back to this,
and this is me telling you how great that's going to be, and it was all from just one image in my head.
And you recorded it like a year ago.
At this point, it's probably been seven months, and the Ghost in the Shell footage has got to be almost a year now,
so it's one of these days.
Every best guy ever video is like the product of like an entire film pre-production cycle.
Pretty much.
I mean, Guru in the Gaon itself...
Guru in the Gaon, the video took four months to make, and Guru in the Gaon...
It took four months to edit, it took months and months before that to write.
But Guru in the Gaon, the TV series, had like, I think four years of pre-production,
and then it was made in like six months.
Because they said...
I remember Imaishi saying they'd spent so long pre-planning it,
and they had like way more ideas that just kind of got left on the cutting room floor.
They originally had done all this research into what an underground society would be like.
I love what they did with that, but they definitely could have done more if they wanted to.
They said that they had done all this research into moles and how they see,
and like what it would be like if people lived underground,
and like they were gonna flesh it out and make it this whole world,
and they were like, eh, they just get through all that.
Yeah, and then like he said that actually making the show was like really fast,
because they had everything planned out, so it's just like they zoomed through it,
and it took no time.
I like that a lot. It's good stuff.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
I actually just remembered that this is a podcast, and we're recording.
Yeah, we're about at the end of it.
Yeah, I figure we can wrap it up soon.
This is about procrastination.
Well, let's finish it later.
I don't wanna.
Well, date was demanding that we keep these shorter than the last one.
I got an Undertale video to edit, alright?
I think I had time to suck my own dick like the rest of you.
Alright, last time was too long,
but it was also a topic that I was really passionate about,
and I kind of wanted to do that podcast for a long time,
so that's why I wanted to let it run long.
Jesse's list just...
And Jesse had a million things on his list.
And since last week, I watched a video by the Nostalgia Chick.
She actually did every single thing on my list that I hated in one video.
It was honestly inspiring.
Your message needs to be heard.
The people, hopefully they'll...
Oh, by the way, there's something else that I wanted to touch on.
Some wonderful commenter last week
went through the trouble of giving us all individual ratings
for our performance in that podcast.
And you know, he gave everyone else...
You know, did you got like a 9?
He gave me a 2 out of 10.
Really, motherfucker?
I thought he gave you like a negative 2 out of 4.
He gave me a negative 2.
2 out of 10.
Yeah, I was so horrible in that podcast.
I only carried the entire conversation
and made everyone laugh constantly.
You piece of shit.
Oh, the horror that I carried the conversation.
I made everyone laugh constantly.
The horror, the agonizing horror.
I'm so bad.
I'm like power glove bad, right, dipshit?
You piece of shit.
I thought not only that Jesse did the best in that podcast
because he actually had a list,
but also that it was the best he had been in any of the podcasts so far.
Yeah, that's the thing.
It was definitely his best performance thus far in this...
I deserve a 12 out of 10.
And yeah, he had lots of hilarious moments.
I legitimately lost my shit watching the video back at parts.
Anyway, alright, each of us,
let's sign off by saying what we're gonna stop procrastinating
and get back to doing.
Jesse, what are you gonna get back to doing after this podcast?
Finish your Adam's Family retrospective.
Make some bloopers.
Don't spoil it, it's gotta be a secret.
No one can know about it.
We can bloop that out ourselves.
No one can know my secrets, because if they know about it,
then I'll never finish it.
Well, you just gotta finish it before the video comes out.
Before this video comes out.
That's fucking impossible.
Well, did you just editing it?
Who knows how long it'll take?
Like five minutes.
I think I edit a lot faster than you guys.
Cut that out.
That's because I put in an effort.
Take that out of the podcast.
I'm not getting back to doing anything.
I'm gonna be procrastinating forever.
As soon as this podcast is done,
I'm gonna get back to playing Honey Pop
and jerking off forever.
Hi, Hippocrite.
What are you gonna get back to doing?
I'm gonna get back to writing episode,
or not episode two,
but the Ratchet and Clank 2 review,
which I've been working on.
Fun fact, me and Victor just recorded
five episodes of Ratchet and Clank 2.
Let's play.
Oh, shit.
Wait, but seriously,
what's up with that Kingdom Hearts video?
I don't know.
I'm gonna release that later
when I've released an actual video.
Okay, fair enough.
Because of my last few, just been whatever.
Alright, Nate,
what are you gonna get back to doing?
I'm gonna edit the shit out of everyone.
It's...
When is this fucking video gonna be done, Nate?
It's coming, god damn it.
I work hard every day.
How much can possibly be left?
I don't understand.
So hard for my money,
so you better treat me right.
How many hours does it take you
per minute of editing?
I'm curious.
Because this video is like 25 hours to do 30 seconds.
Oh my god, what the fuck were you doing?
I was editing.
I have a vision.
I can't see what was your vision.
This guy was giving me shit.
I was like, oh man,
this is gonna be the best blue glow ever.
He's like, oh what, it's like a 6 out of 10?
This is coming from a guy
who makes like one video every three years.
He's sitting there doing nothing.
Everything the world ever needs or wants.
Bull.
Do they criticize Da Vinci
for taking a while in the Sistine Chapel?
I don't think so.
I crap out a Sistine Chapel every two days.
A poo covered Sistine Chapel.
I actually have to go crap out
a Sistine Chapel for real.
In the toilet.
That wasn't a metaphor for my next video.
I just have to take a shit.
I have nothing planned tonight.
I'm probably gonna,
I honestly have no idea.
I have no idea what I'm gonna do tonight.
So that's it for this episode.
Everybody say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Fuck you.
We did it.