Yesterday, I had the Thomas the Tank Engine theme song stuck in my head all day.
Why?
Now it will be in your fucking brain throughout the entire podcast.
Well, maybe it will be in your head.
It's always in my head. My name is Thomas.
Percy was such a cunt.
Hum that again. I haven't heard it in so long. I need to go back.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, Thomas. You're my first love. My only love.
Hey Jessie, we're starting.
Wait, we started recording, but we haven't started, started so-
We haven't synced. Can you hear us?
We hear you.
E. Hello?
Oh.
Hello?
Duh.
Wait.
Sorry.
That wouldn't count.
Is Jesse like ten seconds behind?
Oh, no.
Poor Jess.
Okay.
I mean, if you feel that's appropriate, then fair enough.
Fair enough.
Okay.
Take care, Jess.
All right.
See you later, dude.
Later.
For the viewers at home, his internet is bad.
He can't do it.
That's why.
Okay.
Cause this is all stand-in.
I mean, just cut that out.
No, no.
This is all stand-in.
This is all stand-in, dude.
This is what the people want.
They want inside baseball.
Confusing messes.
I don't think they do.
Uh, but that's just me.
I have no idea.
I can't wait to give this to our new editor and just be like, here's the mess of the
beginning.
You have to try and find a way to sync it up.
Yes, Zach.
Good luck.
Beautiful.
Perfectly fine cutting it.
No.
Okay, whatever.
On that note, I guess the episode started.
Uh, welcome one and all to the inaugural episode.
Really organized, well thought out content cluster.
The PCP, the piece of crap podcast, back at it again with another episode.
All of the life and soul is drained from you, Nate.
You just look like you got to have a wood chipper.
I feel like I'm climbing into a wood chipper and I can't wait.
Here's the deal, people.
It's time.
Jesus.
The time is finally here.
The time is now.
The time is come and so have I.
I forgot what I was talking about.
Oh, right.
Uh, the editor contest.
So you, okay, here's your challenge.
Here's your challenge.
I'm getting my life back.
Do not scroll down and notice in the description where it says you edited.
Don't do that because as you probably could tell, we got the new editor.
Got a new editor, baby.
And it's time to announce it.
What'd you say?
What?
We got to say some, some honorable mentions.
Is that the plan?
Oh, okay.
So here's what we're doing, people.
So we got it.
We're going to let you know who did well, everybody who entered.
Thank you so much.
We're sorry to keep you waiting all so long and jerking you around.
But we are going to tell you some of the people who did a fine job in this here contest.
So here's our 11 top picks, our top 11, because we're like the nostalgia critic and we like
to go that one step further.
One step beyond you fucking fake fan.
Is that what he says?
We, we, we used a, we used a first pass the post voting system or something.
I don't actually know what that means.
Something like that.
It was a point, a way to point system.
Yeah.
We use social credit to determine how much each vote was worth.
So, okay.
So this is what we did.
These were our top guys.
Um, okay.
So, so, you know what, uh, this is not in point order, uh, specifically because I have
to obscure who's the winner and who's the loser here.
So this is totally unordered.
Uh, here we go, uh, John Kano, Donasaur, you Caterpillar, unusual Caterpillar, Ed, Kulik
64, Alden, Green Fleshy Flowers, Calazar 321, those Tismis, those, those Timmy's, those
Timmy's.
Oh, those Timmy's.
Okay.
Right.
And Eleazar and Oblivionfall.
Those were our finalists, ladies and gentlemen.
And if you are on that list, um, get ready because you're going to find out whether or
not you edited this episode.
Indeed.
Fingers crossed every point.
You know, we, we, we could announce that right now, you know, we could let them know
like the landmark announcement of their entire youth, you know, let them know, you know,
what will define their lives for the next like 10, 20 years, but you know, you know,
what if we just, we'll just dilly-dally for a little bit, you know, what if we just twiddled
our clip for, you know, um, 20 more seconds right here, you know, what, what, you know,
why, why be too hasty?
You know, why do you be too hasty?
Well, you're going to give some honorable mentions, right?
And even want to shout out your peeps you liked.
Um, no.
I'm 64, your pizza-chan, therefore I hate you.
Yeah.
Sam.
Um, oh, Pete, you, I don't know.
There were a lot of like, I don't know, I don't fucking remember any of them.
I voted in a drunken rage.
Everybody on that list could do the job as far as I'm concerned.
So that's cool.
Yeah.
Um, definitely, definitely.
The people who gathered to, to, to choose the finalists, we had such a hard time to
choose who.
We, indeed we did.
That's why it took like three years.
Um, it was a nightmare.
We had to have one of these patented, awful, Nate, quote unquote, fair processes no one
likes.
Exactly.
So, you know.
It wasn't a dictatorship and that was truly our downfall.
Man.
Okay.
So there were a lot of like really creative like layouts and like art styles that went
into a lot of these.
And personally, what I would like to do and what I plan to do is, um, okay, well, what
we did was we recorded like a 15 minute sort of test script or a test episode and gave
it to the editors to edit together.
And what I plan to do is take a bunch of those hang on, Ben, if you say it, maybe you'll
never make it.
Do you want to just hold on and make the thing?
Or do you want to let people know?
No, let them know.
Like I basically, it'll be like piece by piece, putting the episode together, but composed
out of like what everyone made.
I think it was in particular, I had like a really cool like layout and like, even though
we didn't end up picking it for the winner, I think it deserves to be shown.
Wait to spoil.
Ben, you just spilled the beans about shot him down.
Okay.
He's, it's all right.
He's a smart boy.
He figured it out.
Sensor that.
Oh my God.
No, it's okay.
Sensor everything.
All those.
Okay.
All right.
Let's re-sync.
Let's start over.
No.
No, we're keeping it in.
Sensor it will save us.
We're keeping that in and we'd censor it.
You hear that editor?
You're censoring those things.
It's crucial.
It's like the worst way could have possibly have gone.
We spent like literally an hour just like, like dictate exactly like the minute details
about how we would announce it, win, and what like order we would announce the finalists
and the winner.
And we're just, oh, fucking, you know, there's some people here.
Keep all that in.
Sensor that.
Look, it was not my fault.
I fought for a real start.
You people overthrew me.
You people.
Yeah.
All right.
I was just saying, he's not the only one.
Hey, a bunch of them have like really cool layouts and I want to show them off and I want
to let people see the work because a lot of these, a lot of people put a lot of work
into the submissions and I'm going to, we're going to, we're going to feature them in a
thing.
I am committed to this.
Okay.
Well, cool.
We'll hold you to it then.
And so will they.
Yes.
Please hold me to it.
Ha ha.
Anybody, anybody else want to shout any honorable mentions that you liked?
Oh, by the way, there was like 50 entries, I should say.
I believe there was exactly 50.
Were there?
Yeah.
I think so.
It's hard to say because some of them were questioned like oblivion falls was in particular
was like, we didn't think it was a real submission until we like specifically asked
like, Hey, do you want us to consider this like for real?
I mean, yeah, that's true.
That's true.
And there was another one too.
So another guy finished his and submitted it and said he was doing like when we said,
when we did our hilarious update and said like, Hey guys, you actually feel free to
like make fresh visuals and whatnot.
This person kind of, it's on the charts on the bottom.
Like they said, like, I'm going to make a new one.
And then they're like, I actually don't have time.
So please just don't count.
Like day one, he turned in a submission and they just didn't, you know, then he realized
I don't have time to do this, which I totally respect.
That's totally cool.
Better to realize it now.
What the fuck is it?
I've got it right here.
It is, it is scroll down.
God damn it.
Fucking one spar.
That's who it was.
A good old one spar.
Oh, that guy.
We all know that guy.
Yeah, that guy.
He's iconic.
Whatever happened, whatever happened to one spar, whatever happened to one spar weekly.
I had my finger on the pulse and now I don't.
Good question.
Are one spar and center point 3000 the same person?
I think so.
I don't think so.
I don't think it's distinct, but similar.
Might as well be the same.
Well, center point was another contributor.
He was another entry, so unless the same person entered under two different names, I don't
think so.
Unlikely.
Rest in peace, center point.
Center point starred in my hit video, feeling closer to death, so appreciate that.
One spar is struggling right now with multiple systems, you know, he's got multiple personalities
in his head and they all have different Twitter handles.
You know how it is.
I thought you were going to say multiple sclerosis and I was going to be like, oh, and
tug my collar.
No, no, did not.
Was not going to go that dark.
Guys, my joke that we that we wouldn't get to the finalist was turned into reality.
I should have known.
Listen, we can't give the people waiting any longer.
That's true.
Wait, let me just say the other honorable mentions.
I just had a fellow human.
I picked top 10 whatever.
Fellow human person was good.
Everything was moving a lot, like almost too much, but there's a lot of movement.
I appreciate that.
It stimulated my lizard brain.
So Dell, Dell was up there and also zero and hoodie.
Those are all my top 10 in addition to the others that were picked.
But OK, that being said, let's move on.
Let's actually announce the real winner, ladies and gentlemen, prepare to be eviscerated.
And the winner is Oblivion Fall wins Oblivion Fall came in with the animator chops, the
editing, audio quality, copyright strike, just so people know the full story with him.
He made his submission said not to be counted up front and he made it just to flex on everybody
else.
He said it was just a flex to prove that he was the most powerful and he was the most
powerful from the start.
It's very true.
And then when we're at the end, we were like, Hey, are you sure you don't want to because
this is really good.
And he was like, No, OK, I'll do it.
So yeah, I told him I knew it.
I knew he was a filthy liar.
It was almost unfair.
Yep.
So Oblivion Fall, welcome to the PCB family.
Bring, bring, bring, bring.
Yes.
Hello.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Call from corporate guys.
The contest is canceled.
We still have to edit ourselves for another eight years.
Also you're adopted.
Uh-oh.
We didn't make enough on patreon.com slash the procrastinators to pay an editor.
So looks like you're on ice.
You're on ice, buddy.
Yeah.
That's that's support us.
Please.
Please pay us more.
I'm just saying, if you feel bad about editors not getting paid enough, give us more money
so that they get a larger share.
If you don't want to give us money, think of Oblivion Fall.
Think of poor Oblivion Fall slaving away, you know, like whittling away at his podcast
episodes, slaving away on his cuphead animations, like, like, like a, like a, like a, like a
pro.
Indeed.
Just trodden under the boot of society.
Uh-oh.
As our newest ward soon Oblivion Fall will blossom into Oblivion Summer.
Wait, after fall comes winter.
Don't say that.
No, don't say that.
Oh no.
Winter is approaching.
I think, I think you gotta, you gotta admit though at the end of the day Oblivion Fall
being the winner does make the most sense thematically because because he procrastinated
the entire contest and then decided right at the very end he was going to take it seriously.
And in a way he procrastinated, although he made like an amazing entry, you know, early
on.
But okay, I get your point.
I get your point.
It's brand recognition.
Right.
Good point.
Yeah.
Although you could say that he fulfills the other spirit of the procrastinators by perhaps
procrastinating on his many other like animation jobs to take the time to make the editor submission,
which is the spirit of procrastination, you know what I'm saying?
I think the real winner of the editor contest were the friends we made along the way.
I was, I was, I was expecting that.
That's fair.
It's just so true.
And you know what?
It's unironically true because a lot of great people submitted.
Eleazar, I think Eleazar learned how to edit apparently for this contest and I'm just
going to tell you, he was tied for number one with green fleshy flowers.
Eleazar overrated.
Green fleshy, for me, there's no, for me, it's all about that green fleshy flowers.
Just for those who are curious.
And that unusual caterpillar and that Q like 64 baby.
Indeed.
I'll give you the top 10 according to our voting.
Okay.
Eleazar and green fleshy tied for first.
Alden in third place, unusual caterpillar in fourth, Donasaur in fifth, John Kano sixth,
Ed seventh, Kula 64 eighth, Kalazar three to one and ninth and those Timmy's in tenth.
Oh, look at those Timmy's baby.
Oblivion fall wasn't on it because he said it was a joke, but then just.
So what you're saying is that after we procrastinated all that time and like try to do all these
things and spend all this time dividing like a voting system, none of that mattered in the
end.
Of course it mattered.
100% mattered.
I mean, if it didn't matter, it was because oblivion fall, you know, misled us with his
liberate.
It's just a prank, bro.
So you know, get mad at him if I fucking got us good.
Shit.
I feel, I feel pretty pranked.
You know, a lot of people or a lot of the submissions were pretty much, they didn't have a lot of
like editing per se, like a lot of motion, but a lot of people did have like a just sort
of do like a cool sort of their own art style interpretation of it, like they just sort
of drew our heads in their own style or like did like a pixel art style.
I remember a chuck chucklehead 95 had like a cute pixel aesthetic and like retro PK.
So just drew us in his own little thing.
I don't know.
This is why.
PK his art was great and I love the layout of that.
It was really nice.
Big, big, big fan.
I was pretty impressed by Dona sores just like really pleasing like, I don't know, there's
like a video of like plants in the background with like some waveforms going on and stuff.
I thought that was real neat, but very Zen unusual caterpillar and some cool like eighties
aesthetic thing going on.
I think that as well.
I think unusual caterpillar and Qlex both did like an eighties like vaporwave kind of.
Yeah, I think so.
Which I really liked both of I forget Alden's off hand.
What was Alden's again?
Alden's.
Oh, he didn't he do do do like the drawings and like I was a butterfly, wasn't that the
one?
Yes, that's the one.
Oh, yeah.
That was weird.
That was just weird looking.
I don't know about that.
You guys all loved it, but I liked it enough, but I didn't like the air raid segment.
I just in my notes.
Oh, yes.
I remember that.
In my notes.
I put down just like no more of that, please.
Green fleshy flowers had like a really cool thing where like it was it was it was in like
a basement or like a room full of like TV monitors and the TV monitors like turned on
with our faces on.
I like that so much.
That was a really cool idea that we may rip off.
Yeah, it's great.
Who was the one who there was one where like the whole screen was like a soundboard and
it had like our waveforms on it and like in the waveform you could see our like logo.
I can't remember who that was.
I remember that.
God damn it.
I really liked some like green fleshy definitely did this where like there were multiple screens.
So like if you have images to edit like big fat mama as she was, you know, famous in
that episode, which I've heard a thousand times now, like, you know, images like that,
like there was a designated screen for them to like go on to.
It was a cool touch.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The like front screen.
But then again for visibility, the thing about green that was interesting was like I didn't
actually know if that was necessarily for the best because those are kind of small and
there was a lot.
I don't know.
I liked it and I was impressed by it obviously.
But some of the layout choices were conflicting.
Now, now of course, if like green was our only.
Oh, wait, it was John Cano.
John Cano was the one where everything was like the whole screen was like an audio mixer
layout.
Oh, yeah.
Pretty sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Again, like all of these things were great and we could have worked with any of them,
but yeah, just lucky to have very talented people.
So, you know, it was it was truly an embarrassment of riches we were faced with picture me with
that DJ Khaled holding my head and with suffering from success across the top of the of my new
album.
All right.
Is that what his album is called?
Yeah.
Does he even make albums?
He's a producer.
So, I think so.
I think he raps a little.
No, I think he's just a producer.
I don't know if he raps.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anyway, any final thoughts because I think we're ready to move past this forever and
be done with it.
I'm glad it's finally over.
The fucking Herculean effort that I observed and did not participate all that actively
in is finally behind.
Indeed.
But I'm sure it was really stressful to watch other people try and really hard on.
Yeah.
Because like I was just watching from on high.
I've been like, do I have to intervene and fucking save these peasants from themselves?
You all know with Tom's guiding hand, it would have been done with a slickety split in a
smack.
Exactly.
Well, he did have to listen and vote on them.
So, fair enough.
Well did.
Uh, except.
Except me?
I think.
Except me.
Munchies didn't give a shit.
I didn't vote at all.
Completely abstained.
Yeah.
Munchies spat on every participant individually.
That's 50 spits he did one at a time.
Because deep down, Munchies still mad because from if we go rewind all the way back to like
PCP episode like 10 when we talked about the redesign and Munchie was always saying he
was going to do it.
And now it's out of his hands and out of pure spite.
Oh God.
Remember that?
Time for me to give my top three overrated editor submissions that everyone liked even
though they sucked shit.
Eleazar Alden, Donasaur.
Get fucked.
Everyone else voted for them except me.
Wait, no.
Digi didn't.
Jesse didn't.
Okay, it's not entirely true.
I didn't.
Uh, whatever.
Okay, so there's other people of good taste as well.
I just, I just resent.
Oh, wait, wasn't true.
It was actually just needlessly mean for no reason.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
No, I just, I just, I resent everyone who made it into the top 10 who I didn't personally
vote for.
I'm a pained appearance without some shade being thrown.
You're, you're encroaching on my safe space.
Uh, and I just wanted to thank our top six guys.
We sent them all questionnaires to give us like extra info.
I very much appreciate you guys doing that for us because we, we took you guys all seriously
and we're really thinking about who'd be the best choice.
Yeah, we did.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Appreciate all the effort.
We did not underestimate you.
Yeah, like I said, it was very difficult to choose between the finalists.
Yup.
And don't, we appreciate all the work.
Which is why, which is why I procrastinated on brands so long before I voted.
took me forever to get around to because I just didn't want I didn't want to crush the dreams of
all those those delightful shining faced young people out there who just who just want to who
just want to you just want to reach out and be a part be a part of this grand project known as the
procrastinated listen uh listen to Ben's new album that's uh suffering from kindness that's him you
know sadly looking down he's too kind just too kind to help anyone uh well oh you also
DeVoo didn't vote but he's been AWOL so yeah that's fair you want to talk about how DeVoo's dead
I mean there's not much to say he's just doing other shit I guess mayor may come back one day
I don't know it was just literally AWOL well he uh you know he he tweeted about it I don't know I
think it's interesting I think it's relevant okay talk about here sure apparently he whoa hold on
there buddy boy what what what did he say in the tweet because you might be about to say something
he didn't say in the tweet no I'm not gonna say what you said what I'm not gonna I'm not gonna
reveal your secret cache of knowledge just saying he's like he's like just going yeah just just going
completely AWOL it's not a huge change from the internet to work on his stuff or is it just his
game in hardcore with his game or not he's he's focusing on on other aspects of his life other
he said he's going to go he said he's gonna work on getting a real job and okay and something in his
tweet longer said something about like trying to use that experience to like hopefully build
like a game dev career in the future that's like more sound sounds like he's going home
to be a family man now go home to be a family man I've always put forward that it's perfectly
I mean it's easy to do the PCP and you know anything else it's a once a week commitment
and I guess the not even you don't even have to show up to all the episodes yeah but I think
it's more that he just doesn't want to you know he wants to get his baggage out of behind him and
I don't know be a real person in the real world or something hey god bless him you know whatever
fair enough sure whatever man I mean I don't want to do it but if he does cool whatever makes
him happy yep man more power to him well although I know I know every every every once in a while
there's an outcry there's an outcry in the comments of where's DeVoo I mean that's true that's
true DeVoo does have a he has a loyal a vote is a vocal I wouldn't even say a vocal minority
because it's not even that small yeah there's a vote there was a segment of the PCP population
there's a vocal community yeah that is vocally that vocally craves craves more of that DeVoo sauce
they think back to the virginity cast and they want get me some more of that sir I want an
extra heaping of that business over here and I don't blame him no it's fascinating indeed indeed
he's doing well you know I've at least talked to him and he's doing well uh so this isn't
they're sad enough this isn't uh you know he's not leaving on a bad note here but just you know
can we get a lowercase o and seven in the comments a little salute he talked he talked to me on
discord very briefly about uh eating too much sugar and I advised him to look into stevia
or sucralos and that's like that's how much I've interacted with him in the last like six months
yeah get a ping over here and then we talk briefly that's fine hello yeah oh no oh my god
you recording hippo I'm recording I'm sorry I'm late I just had we announced the winner of the
editor contest oh hooray what's that bread doing in your mouth get that the hell out of your mouth
hey it you guys can't chew in class I finished my chewing it's all done I had an I had a baked
beans on toast oh the what's that your cheek what's that on your little bit of a cheek right there
you got a little bit of a chip on the cheese did you put cheese on it did you have cheese on it
uh no that's not just cheese it's not good ew and beans and toast gross do you put cheese can
we just like ban cheese cheese is illegal uh as far as I'm concerned uh I've learned to love cheese
I've learned to love cheese because it's keto it shouldn't be it should be banned is what it should
be what what do you got against cheese Nate there are two states of being for things in this world
keto and ban this one needs to shift to bang what's right tell me tell me your cheese grievances
your cheese while while cheese may while cheese may be keto and those with the correct uh knowledge
and power to use it effectively I'm sure it can do good things but that's not how it's used especially
out in Ohio where you buy fucking chili you buy a fucking salad and it comes piled high there's
like more cheese than salad yeah on that fucking thing this is it's a misuse of the power of cheese
and it's fucked up and I'm just ready to cut the cord you know when I when I used to you know before
I got into keto in the times in the past when I tried to like you know lose weight tried to like
do a traditional diet like a low-fat diet like cut my calorie intake I would always for go cheese
because I was like well okay yeah like I'm gonna eat a burger right well I can eat a hamburger or
I can eat a cheeseburger and the cheeseburger is like an extra like 150 calories and it doesn't
like huge you know some people will fight me on this but I don't think that like adding cheese to
like a burger like hugely increases the enjoyment of it I don't think it's like a game changer or
anything so I was I was always fine like I'll have the normal thing cut the cheese that cuts like
you know a third of the calories cut the cheese guys am I right in what I'm saying I'm losing to a
bird but now but you know now that I'm keto now that I've got the all the powers and privileges
associated with that I've got a flipped a flip the script on cheese are you like are you like a vegan
man from scott pilgrim with your superpowers I was yeah exactly only only with vegan man
you get weird like psychic powers with with keto with keto you just get pure kidney stones it's
just pure kidney stones ladies and gentlemen at light speed would you like to relate to us that
story then well yeah so the way I found out about this is we were going to record a stream
on rowdy fuckers cop killers and then you message me early that morning say I can't do the stream
today I've got another kidney stone oh my god I didn't know there was a second one there was yeah
on Friday you know you know first you know fool me once shame on you fool me twice shame on
kidney stones slash keto so what do you have to what how are you going to repent this obviously
terrible lifestyle you're leading um listen I might have kids drink more water yeah yeah I'm
gonna drink a lot more water I think that's okay like I people say like soda people say
energy drinks people say caffeine I've here I've heard these things I you know I gotta look more
into this because I did some cursory googling and not exhaustive by any means but I actually
found an article saying that caffeine intake is actually linked to a lower instance of kidney
stones so caffeine sure but maybe it's like the so isn't it sodium deposits generally so I mean
well the caffeine might help maybe the sodium could be calcium calcium I don't know see I don't
know enough I need to find out more before I could form like a really solid opinion but I
definitely should be drinking more you should you should check to see if if the articles that you
read have sources that are like to oh like coke by bang like this one this this one this one I'm
talking about was specifically like an academic like journal was it peer reviewed the association
of modern-day potion chemists yeah yeah it was pretty good this was very official but I need to
buy the point that I need to find out more um anyway so yeah I woke up on Friday at like 5 a.m.
feeling a certain pain being like oh god oh god and it got worse over the course of like half an
hour and I'm like yep here it is again and I'm like okay I'm gonna go to the doctor no because
going to the doctor is really expensive and I don't want to do it and all they really did last time
was give me some well they gave me morphine for a little while and then they just sent me home
with some percocet and I was like well I've still got a bunch of that percocet so I guess I'll just
try that and I did so for the rest of the day what I did was I would take a bunch of percocet
try to sleep fail like 15 minutes later the pain would be too bad I'd wake up however I discovered
that taking a hot shower made the pain mostly go away so I would take a shower for like 40 I would
sit in the shower for like 45 minutes try to sleep for like 15 minutes not be able to take
another shower for another like 45 minutes and then I just repeated that cycle for like 26 hours
straight um perhaps some sort of warm compress would have you know been a good water bottle maybe
not it's not a bad idea it could have worked maybe but uh the shower was good trying to sleep
through it made the time pass faster and it only lasted I think at around like 3 a.m. the next morning
or no maybe like 6 a.m. the next morning I woke up feeling a little better and I was like I think
it's over I think it's done well Ben I got some sad news for you because the pain was the least of
your problems your kidney stone has depreciated in value oh what I'm gonna spend what 40 grand on
this keystone he's gonna pop out another one next week no well see I didn't I didn't catch I didn't
catch this one I didn't have the mesh so so this one this one was lost to the ether oh but now the
great hunt begins through the sewers once you've made six kidney stones then you can put them in
the keto gauntlet and then you'll be you'll be all and if you get seven you can summon the keto
dragon dragon one wish you know when I stamp my fingers half of all carbs on earth can we make
that a hundred percent can we get that up to a hundred percent please Ben just starts snapping
furiously I gotta get rid of all of them I guess I gotta get rid of all this fucking the Zeno's
paradox I keep half you didn't have it I can't get zero there will always be the the primordial
carb will continue to spawn you gotta fucking take it down we gotta track the fucking car broaches
you can't every time you squish one more just keeps showing up no hey speaking of Thanos I'm just
curious please no spoil please as anyone seeing the new avengers I'm probably seeing tomorrow morning
is the plan oh I want to see it I want to see it as well I'm going to uh team up with a local friend
and I'm gonna see it as soon as possible apparently it's it's already made 1.3 billion dollars of course
it has it's just like destroying life as as totally expected uh tywin lannister comes in he says Thanos
I'm very disappointed in you and then he cries you're my gay son can can someone can someone
please upload it to the internet for me thanks oh that would be legal mage oh no or if a pastor
finds out mage what would have god smites us for our sins mage then smite you know speaking
speaking of this though I just I think we've talked about this before but uh movie theaters have
become such a luxurious experience they're pure decadence so I'm gonna fucking get my lady dress
her up in her finest whore's makeup and we're gonna go out and we're gonna hit the town and we're
gonna get like a fucking pizza delivered to us in the movie theater while we sit there just you know
pure decadence movie theaters have fully shifted from like cheap bullshit to just like complete luxury
like they've got like like recliner chairs yeah that's got like they got it okay okay every single
movie theater just has like bars in it now there is everything I've had like fucking liquor in it now
okay but here's something even got the notion to put liquor in it man that's a waste of watermelon
you see it's interesting that you cut all the guts oh my fucking god you know what I'm talking about
I remember the video I can't remember it's like the guy you're talking about pdps pd greens
washington I want to hear what Tom has to say guys nobody listens to me mage it's fine no it's not
fine no it's not fine like this is a weird special occasion where you actually talk we need you need to talk
it was way too long it's only suey guys that's what I got in pain on the new day
sorry oblivion fall I'm sorry you have to edit through this mess this is your inaugural episode
I was actually interested Tom uh in your discussion of movie theater well well the
interesting thing I was going to say is that I'm going to go see the movie tomorrow but I'm going to
the theater in my hometown which is like a fucking time machine because you go in there it hasn't
changed in like 20 years I've been here so it still has the shitty seats it has none of the
recliners has none of the new services like you you still have to like bomb in and like hunt for a
seat you don't get to reserve your seat or any that shit so it's just like going back to like the
90s and it's just like disgusting you know when I was young we used to go till it was like the
it was like uh I forget what it was called but there was a movie theater that would specifically
play like movies that were like out of the main cycle Patriot cinema Patriot cinema yeah Patriot
cinema there was like a dollar fifty oh yeah we went to the zeotrope that they did that the
zeotrope the zeotrope that was called but did the same thing were they growing like were they
growing aliens and like tubes underneath uh no well maybe they're gone now so maybe they
went home uh they were just fun trying to fund their reason I haven't been to the cinema in like
over a decade no no less than a decade hippo tell me tell me how are theaters nowadays made you
goddamn neat get out of your house and go kill Thanos like the rest of us don't do something useful
like go to the movie theater something productive I haven't been to a theater uh I think since
star was the force awakens and uh back then it was just like your average like reg you know
the the normal sort of theaters where yeah there's no big I mean I think I've been to one cinema
where they had the big funny chairs the big funny leather chairs I have only been to yeah the the
last cinema I remember going to was with my friend and it was like it it was like in this
really small building that was like someone's house at some point I feel it was like the
tiniest cozy little cinema and it was pretty neat I wish I remembered one movie we watched though
I don't remember I only ever went to one theater that had the big cushy chairs and stuff and it
was also the last time I ever went to the movie theater and it was with it was with uh digi
and and May and Tom Tom did you come to see Princess Mononoke that one time yes yes I did oh
yeah Kazi was there yeah yeah and uh that was pretty fun um hey too bad he's dead I just confirmed
with my main bitch we're going to see Avengers today and it's gonna be sick damn what a sensual
date though yeah we got her fresh collar and chain so she's gonna be the talk of the town let me
tell you Nate Nate's going with his main bitch but he's really there to date Thanos his his love
his lord and savior she's my she's my beard she's my beard for sure or is there an anti-beard is
there an opposite beard what do you mean bitch she's my pussy she's my pussy you know you're gonna get
the the weird lines your chin is a tattoo uh I love a life of duality you see because like most
things outside I'm only gonna do it if I'm with someone else right like I'm not gonna like go to
the movie theater alone like I'd rather kill myself than do that than face the consequences I've
done that multiple times I don't give a shit fuck it so there are two there are two circumstances on
which I go to the movie theater one my local friends are back in town from a back a back uh
from being away from their college dorms or I'm in Boston oblivion please play the boys are back in
town and no no you said same are you pro or anti going to the movies alone uh well I generally go
with people but I'm absolutely if no one wants to go I will 100 go myself I don't give a shit I
mean I wouldn't be against it if like I was really into movies just I can't remember that last time
there was a movie that I was so excited about that I would go see it without making it without it being
like the thing we were doing that's another question the embarrassment was a cover-up and a joke and
not real the real reason is because it would be boring and I would have no reason to do because
I hate movies no I disagree fuck people I'm there for the for the story in the mood okay anyway sorry
go on anyway so so I'm either in San Diego or I'm in Boston when I watch a movie and San Diego
experience is far different so with Boston you got you know you got the liquor you've got the
watermelon rind you've just got people zigzagging and bopping and fucking just all over the place
semen drenching my eyeballs when I'm at the movie theater in Boston you get to watch like
jibbly movies there it's crazy just the height of luxury well they were doing a thing there was
like a that was like a national a national event it was an event unfortunately it ended I was
I was really hoping to see porco remember that that classic jibbly line I just don't understand
how we black people starting I went to a party these nice white folks they had slices
one white woman she said she said to me oh I didn't I didn't think you black folks ate watermelon
like that no more
link below I said lady you just trying to get me to cut up all the guts so you can keep all the good
part for yourself oh pete green where'd you go pete green uh so so in San Diego there is a
there's an iconic mom it was a staple of san jacan culture and all you locals choose a man
friday I'm talking to you hoarding plaza iconic getting torn down our place with office buildings
so this dilapidated once iconic mall is just in shambles and in there there is an amc and it is
a huge theater but no one gives a shit because their days are numbered and last time I think I
just tried to have spider-verse I snuck into the theater with my friends and then stole the 3d
glasses from the trash that's what every experience is like watching movies there of course you know
just walk in you you don't ask anyone you don't pull out a ticket you just walk fucking in
fish whatever essentials you need out of the trash like you do and then watch your movie in peace
walk out the door and you know it's it's sticky it's terrible I have a photo I have a photo that I
took I forget even I think it was the Grinch CGI Grinch that I took and it's my friend just in front
of like a completely empty row of seats I'm gonna try if I can get out put in the show notes link
on screen right now to look at it just no one's here it's my own personal playground to just fucking
suck and it's great but you know it's a fast and different experience and then you know it's fine
I try when I go to the movie theaters I try to optimize the time that I go so that nobody will
be there like that's why I'm going yeah I'm doing Q&A's at the point you know I love at the movie
in general what's up guys just defeated Thanos I'm ready for a Q&A yeah they're asking questions
about what movie you're watching and what's going on and you're just like live commentating just
live instagraming during the movie and that's why I gotta make sure nobody's around because I can't
you know gotta have a little bit of respect on the sub on the subject of yeah on the subject of
pete green uh-huh I just want to let you all know that pete greens autobiography laugh if you like
ain't a damn thing funny was published in 2003 and he and green was portrayed by Don Cheadle in the
2007 film talk to me which was inspired by his life and career wow yeah that's great I don't actually
know what his career is I mean I know he had he had like a Washington DC area like like morning
talk show and that that clip of him getting really angry about people eating watermelon the wrong
way yeah is the funniest thing I've ever linked in the show notes I have placed it there yeah okay
excellent um and yeah and apparently you can see Don Cheadle play him in the 2007 biopic so there you
go uh munchie who's this modern day ghoul that you've posted in the person when I saw uh Grinch
2018 with the best movie ever made by the way Jim Carrey's Grinch how could it even compare to you
know story anyway so I saw it with this guy and uh I uh I took during the entire you know when you
go to the movies and you get there like early because you know you're a good boy you're a good
you want to see yeah you know Roman Catholic uh and they just have like the bizarre like please
god by our procs movie theaters are dying do all this weird gimmick shit so uh there is literally
an app that was advertised in the previews of this no there weren't like movie previews there were
just like app previews and this was for an app called new v not joking new v for the in new
movies wait a minute audience uh well the first there was new goal now we've got new
v's left right and center it's just like was was like this app bought by new goal just like
youtube was bought by google they just try to mirror their movements I can only imagine so what it is
it's do you guys remember face Raiders on 3ds yeah no no so literally face Raiders but for movies
so there would be like on screen and be like without your phones without your tm new v's
app and start clicking right now three two one go I don't know so maybe you could like
choose the ending like do you want the Avengers to a no no no so what will happen is there will
just be like a like a stock photo of a movie theater you know where you are right now just a
sock like of the concession stand and I'll whip out new v to see the creatures to see the critters
run and you look at the new v app like of course we did we scrambled we like we like ripped out our
phones we almost broke it like like fidgeting with it tried to open it as fast as we possibly could
desperate to get it open and then there and there were like little creatures little UFOs little
aliens tried to invade get into our ears maybe plant some eggs you know to shoot them yeah they
were like AR what I'm trying to say they they were right right right okay objects that were in
your phone screen you had to shoot them you don't only see them if you're pointing them at the screen
would this like pause the movie to happen no this happened before the movie okay so so is this
are you saying there's there's there you're in the movie theater right i'm just trying to paint
the picture for myself so the screen is displaying a generic movie theater that's empty and then if
you point your phone at the generic picture it will show items on top of the generic picture but
not in the actual environment you're actually really sitting in the actual movie theater it's only
the picture of the movie theater indeed indeed in AR i'm very confused that is the most retarded
thing i've ever heard in my life no no it's engagement it's it's entertainment god damn it
i was entertained and i was engaged can you imagine one isn't enough but both this sounds
like this sounds like the ubisoft presents dog pals rip off of nintendox which is face raiders
all right this sounds like a blame it sounds great something gets way better so that's what the
movie theater experience is like in in horn plans are just decrepit literal mummies mummies
roaming about like actual dead people i saw some dude piss in the movie theater uh like
i said rummage through the trash or there was a lot of like you know birth control in there you
just not a good time just not a good time but you know it's worth it as long as i got to see
Superman spider-verse fucking suck uh hey i've got a thing of note now i do not
want to make this overly political however it is interesting but i hate the current president
no i don't want to yet i want to call out everyone in the comments like okay what do
everyone in the comments ever on the show everyone in the world who's against this i was
trying to avoid this okay me me and you talked about what was it last week we talked about some
like slut oh we were just we were talking about the um marcess man versus peterson debate
yeah that's right very briefly briefly and everyone's still in the comments like it's too
political we were i think it's a mean we were barely even talking about because people are tired
of any mention of politics i think they have a negative association which you know what their
fucking brains are broke and they need to fix it ironically unironically i think because you two
are like on you know somewhat on opposite sides politically um and and you like talking about it
with each other i really think you should bring back t-bap but replace ponies with politics
you know what literally the name doesn't have to change i don't even think that's a terrible idea
it would be really funny do it so you don't have to do it here look i yeah i get that okay but
none of what i say will consider this none of this has to do with what i was about to say which
is just that so like an hour before we started recording or whatever pewdiepie uploaded a video
called ending the subscribe to pewdiepie meme and i watched this video before and basically this is
this is troubling implications for me personally um basically what he says is like hey guys so
subscribe to pewdiepie was really great it was really fun i never expected to last as long as it
went but here's the thing i got like 90 million subscribers now and some bad apples have crept
in and like you know only now only with that last couple million did a few bad apples creep in
that's exactly the point i mean i'd argue he's not response okay but okay let me finish i mean
okay whatever go on okay the point is he just said like so and obviously he addresses like
the christ church shooter yeah who says subscribe to pewdiepie and so obviously this he said like
this is really weighed on me like personally this has been like an issue and i didn't want to
acknowledge i didn't want to say anything publicly except on twitter his disavowal because like i
didn't want to like draw any attention and it wasn't about me so like you know we didn't want to do
that okay but now he's saying but like but i want to end the subscribe to pewdiepie meme whatever
t-series has passed me and i don't want to make hitting a hundred million be like because i'm trying
to beat someone else so okay now look the message is fine the thing that troubles me about this and
i'm curious if you guys agree disagree or whatever is that like basically what i'm taking away from
this among his perfectly reasonable points is that all he takes is one bad apple and like i know
there's more than one but like he really drew the christ church guy if you have 90 million followers
if you have one bad follower it's your like you bear responsibility like you are the guy who what i
don't know encourage this like you have to stop what you're doing like oh this is just it reminds me
so much of like if there's any accusation of any wrongdoing by anyone to anyone today that enough
seems like that seems like that's enough these days to like stop any like campaign whatever
approaches tracks but i don't think he bears that responsibility is there anything i don't i think this
is more of just a personal thing the pewdiepie is like some killer was spouting a meme that had
his name in it and that's just sort of fucked within a little i don't think this is like people
are campaigning to destroy pewdiepie because he endorses killers because he obviously doesn't
maybe it's not you know that could be true but however like i'm just saying if i agree that like
pewdiepie can allow or anyone you can let a meme be tainted by some bad actors then like every meme
has bad actors like i don't know pepe obviously has tons of like racist stuff about him but like
do you have to let that be the way that you appreciate the joke or the character i mean i don't
you don't have to let subscribe to pewdiepie be tainted by what if your pewdiepie yeah like
imagine your pewdiepie and you know the tea yeah dude yeah pretty sick dude pretty sick
fist bump um so your so your pewdiepie and this this t-series things happen and you know it's
kind of it's like a fun thing it's like healthy competition it's growing your channel by a lot
and it's really exciting you're like yeah you know what this is cool i didn't like do this on purpose
but it happened organically and i'm just gonna run with it yeah it's fine and then at some point
this thing happens and now like you're seeing the same meme and you're seeing you're seeing your name
be you know propagated in with you know with with association to this horrible thing that like people
you know whether you didn't do it but like people are associating you with this thing now like
i could i can understand why he'd want to be like let's not let's take that let's try and take that
element out of it like maybe maybe not like yeah maybe maybe if i pushed the subscriber
pewdiepie i mean even harder maybe i'd hit a hundred million faster but yeah isn't it better
to hit it later and have like less of that poisoning the water yeah i think you know that
this was like maybe he was kind of getting tired of it and and like event and this was sort of
like the last straw because he did you know it's sort of like said like you mentioned a few other
reasons why he's sort of stopping it uh that that was one of you know one of the reasons but not the
main reason um i have a somewhat similar experience like on a very much smaller scale and not as you
know so uh horrible i guess um back in my pony days i used to do like this whole touch face thing if
you guys remember and it was like oh how could how could we forget how could anyone in our audience
everyone touch face for mage down in the comments time for the simpler days it was it was touch
facing in the comments oh no no stop no the point is like i i started doing it because i thought it
was uh funny and kind of cute and it's just like something weird you know um people took a liking
to it and it sort of became a little bit of a meme in my sort of circle of friends in the community
a bit and whenever people started seeing me online and so the first thing they would say is like hey mage
touch face and like it got really annoying after a while because that's all it was to those people
that's all they said to me in like group chats and stuff and yeah and like people assumed they knew
me just because they knew this one meme that related to me and like i stopped doing the touch face and
i think it took like maybe a year almost maybe two for people to sort of caught on the caught
catch on that i'm not doing it anymore because they kept doing it yeah and i i feel like pewdiepie
and you know the subscribed to pewdiepie isn't going to die just because he said to yeah that's
what i was gonna say like the fact of the matter is he can't stop it like if you know but i think
if people want to keep doing it they're gonna people i think people who do respect pewdiepie
and his wishes and pay attention they will stop just because you know he asked nicely but people
who don't care and just want to meme on people and be mean i guess will continue to do so but
eventually i don't think you have to even be mean like i straight up i mean yeah you certainly don't
have to have malice to choose to not like agree to end a meme because i mean that's pretty artificial
anyway to go to your main point about like i think it's just the nature of the world and the
interconnected nature of the society that we live in um that words change um things get hijacked
and you know labels and and stuff like that gets tainted and it's i feel it's naive to just ignore
the fact that the public perception of those things can shift to something that you don't like
or don't agree with it's it's unfortunate and it sucks but like if you use a word and then like a
year later the word means something completely different stubbornly continuing to use it in
that sense is just gonna be confusing when you have when you make a meme it can easily grow out of
your hands as it did for touch face as it did for you know subscribe to pewdiepie and when you know
if that meme which you've started has you know turned into something else and he's used primarily
by people that you don't like that can be a discomforting fact that can be even if just in
the hands of a few people who you disavow i don't it can still be like you all this all of this point
is assuming that these things are tainted and like it's just so easy just let's just seed ground forever
just give up everything god like i don't know it's it's a personal there is no objective amount of
which something needs to be tainted for it to be like quote unquote tainted i think it's really
just down to public like a perception of the word in who you know whoever's thinking about it if you
don't believe that varies between bubbles though i mean yeah i mean i don't know what's what's your
objection they well here tom did you want to say something i'll say that afterwards um i mean i just
think in my perspective i don't think it's about like being tainted or anything i just think it's
pewdiepie has been the punching bag of the mainstream media and like like for what like four
five years now like he's just the guy they point to of saying like he's this problematic guy causing
all this fucking shit and like you read it like i haven't read it but i've heard like people summarizing
the christ church shooters manifesto and like all of this was designed to increase tensions on purpose
like he didn't actually give a fuck about subscribe to pewdiepie he said it to piss off liberals you
know because they knew they hated pewdiepie and they had this whole nazi agenda against him you
know and he's he just the entire thing was constructed to increase tensions between the
left and the right and it worked perfectly like he fucking played everybody you know that that's true
but when people when people have raised that point as like a way to like like you silly sjw i'm not
even really i kind i basically agree but like when people say like you silly sjw's like you're playing
right into his hands i mean like yeah but like what's the option here just the sjw's it's everybody
you know like every everybody on both sides but like that's my point is that like even i'm part
of the pro i wish i didn't even have to say it because like that's what i would do except that
pewdiepie himself has basically given ground and says that he agrees it's problematic now i don't
even think that he's given ground at this point i think it's just the fact that like because he's
been in the crosshairs for so long like this is just a way of like trying to like get some of the
heat off of him yeah i think they've beaten him down i need to broken his spirit a little bit
that would be my argument i mean even if even if it has nothing to do with it like i if putting
myself in his position like even if it is just for the memes like and and like was done you
know as like a way of like manipulating culture to have yourself even like you know remotely
connected to a shooting is fucked and like that of course it doesn't it doesn't matter like what
the reasons were that will make you feel like ass and i'm sure like that feels like shit yeah like
i think i think the discussion you sort of want to have maybe pewdiepie wasn't like the best
to be to to choose because like i feel like his situation is a little bit it's a little bit different
due to the shooting it's kind of been loaded loaded of a situation so it's a little hard to
that's just an extreme version i mean now fuck that i don't associate a subscribe to pewdiepie
with that guy at all i mean that guy is trying to latch himself on to a movement uh but i mean
look i know the guy because i read the fucking manifesto he doesn't believe it at all like i
don't know he probably loves that pewdiepie is white but like i don't know that's not pewdiepie's
fault that's uh you know it's all in this guy's head and and like here's the thing like i i have
such a reject i feel it burning inside this feeling of like like i was saying like giving
ground and just allowing people to just take and take and take these ideas and like okay right now
let's say another shooter whatever shoots up a church somewhere and says like i love pcp baby
i was high on pcp i listen to the pcp haha uh it's like we're the reason people are dying baby
black black black you're describing the wildest fantasies right now real real situation that
happens that could happen we've got thousands of listeners we've got tens of thousands one of them
could be a shooter absolutely but do we like what do we do then is our brand tainted do we need to
shut down the show because one person is insane it's not about like shutting down shutting down
that's not what that's not what pewdiepie is doing either he's shutting down the meme the idea is being
shut down he didn't he didn't even make the meme in the first place he didn't engineer subscribe to
pewdiepie like if if somebody just likes the pcp we're not going to stop doing the pcp because we
obviously don't rebrand though like let's say the entire mainstream isn't even rebranded he's just
look he's ended he's ending a meme it's the same way that the guy who made pepe basically disavowed
pepe and killed the character and you know i don't even blame it he can do whatever he wants it's his
character pewdiepie doesn't want to do this but he's being forced to for damage control purpose i
mean that's the nature that's the nature of being an incredibly famous individual that has to
like compromises have to be made i'm not saying any of this is like the best way for the world to be
i'm just saying it makes sense for him to do that and i don't begrudge him that i feel like i just
i feel like roar shock from watchmen i feel like i'm just witnessing bad things happening
and everyone's like yeah you gotta be pragmatic dude okay i'm just like but it's wrong but it's not
right so is your problem that what pewdiepie is a coward for for killing the meme is that your
problem he he gave in yes he gave in and i was i don't like it but it was his choice in the end
to do it he was i'm guessing like this i'm just guessing but i think he was just tired and he
just wanted it to end uh like if something bad similarly happens to pcp and like if one of us
decides to not associate with the pcp it's not i wouldn't blame me how about this name maybe the
cat's argument the cat's yeah let the cat speak um i just want to say uh look i'm aware if i was in
his position like there's a distinct possibility i would have broken long ago i just hope that people
who are you know who who value like i don't know not seeding intellectual ground just because
there's like a fuss that you might not agree with like i hope i would i just i just disagree generally
that this is like intellectual ground like he's not he's not changing his whole world he's just
like tired of the thing it's not about world it look they could do this about anything they could
take any meme any of us make ever and someone if they want to they could do a school shooting
and associate with that meme are you if you give ground on this you have to say that any meme can
be corrupted by one individual doing something extremely black and white about this of course it
can be corrupted i do not agree there's not a it's not a fucking light switch like you flick it and
then it's corrupted and if you say you are a school shooter it's not as drastic as that you're accepting
the principle that i don't i just don't i mean look yes it can happen but you shouldn't give it
it's wrong you don't you don't think that meaning can be changed by the addition of context i believe
very much in performative meanings no one has to say that subscribe to PewDiePie is like evil
or bad or associate with shit if you just don't associate okay but i think about it you you can
choose to believe whatever you want but that doesn't change the fact that lots of people out in the
real world now do associate that phrase with the new zealand shooter how do we square that with the
fact that those people have been fucking duped they've been okay because it doesn't matter it
doesn't matter if they've been duped the point is they they have the association is there now
it can't let's correct them one by one it can't be gotten rid of it's like i said earlier it's just
it's just naive i just want to quickly shift like the um we can use a similar um
hold on overwatch overwatch did like a ban on something on like the okay sign recently or
something like that because like one person complained about the okay sign and they just
someone flashed the okay sign during an interview yeah exactly and they censored it because this is
what i'm talking about yeah exactly like and i it was me it was me i was dog whistling i admitted
and like i think in that in that context that was dumb of them and i like sure and overall i do
agree with you nate but like with pewdiepie's case like i said i feel like it's a little different
and it's just like it's i mean are you aware that the christ church guy did the okay like obviously
he was doing it to play into the racist you know the newly formed like not actually the real meaning
of the thing or not the historical meaning of the way he did it when he was in like uh at court
or whatever when he was being tried or something right yeah so like i mean yes he's a hundred percent
i guess quote dog whistling but it's just i from what i heard he just did a lot of things to piss
off as many people as he could uh right yeah and he was a memer for yeah yeah absolutely i don't
agree with the whole okay sign being censored because people are taking over uh the meaning of
it despite it actually i just think it's the same logic i think those are like very similar
i mean it's the exact same thing it's someone taking something that's benign and trying to inject
poor beliefs yeah that's that's what's happening yeah but like i don't know like it's not like
pewdiepie saying like now it's bad it's just like i'm kind of over it now the difference in the
response he's agreeing it's been corrupted the difference between these two things is that like
with with the overwatch thing that was blizzard making a decision for someone else's actions
whereas with pewdiepie he's making a decision based on something revolving around his own brand
yeah so i can like i understand pewdiepie's position on a personal level even if i disagree
with it on a philosophical i mean that's and you know what i don't want to be overly critical
gib here you go well yeah i'm just the the the thing that's annoying me about like your argument
is that i like what do you suggest we do like i'm saying that that's the way it is and i don't like
it and you're saying the same thing but you're just i don't know like what like if i think it is
really stupid and naive to imagine that you can just tell each person individually by the way that
word doesn't actually mean that because language like in general is it shifts all the time words
start to mean different things and people don't like it people don't like that literally doesn't
necessarily mean literally anymore it just it can mean figuratively as well and that's just the way
language is like how how would you go about how would you go about changing something
that has been changed in a way that you don't like the thing is there's a lot of retroactive
continuity going on here like like i don't know people show like obama's made the okay symbol
has that word changed was he dog whistling all along do we need to give like time stamps to when
words meant certain look i i know this is all muddy but like i mean here's my solution whenever
you like you do an okay sign and someone says uh hey you know that's uh racist or something you
say no it's not uh that's you know i'm not using it that way like i i'm aware that some people do it
i don't think about that there i mean it's kind of like the same argument is like back in the day
like using gay you know it's like gay doesn't mean gay it means stupid like it's it's just a different
way of using the word and this is a different way of using the symbol and that's always gonna
have pushback because you have people who look at everything uh with like a certain context and
other people looking at it in a different way you know because like you have people who are taking
like modern day sensibilities and projecting them on the entirety of human existence and you're
obviously going to run into problems with that whereas you have other people who take a more
nuanced approach and it's just the different ways people look at things i just think like
if if something as big like the okay sign that is very ridiculous that is like you make a circle
with your hand right that's that's what it is um that being turned into a no you make a w and a p
for white power dog right of course like what i read like you're like the actual white pyro sign
involves two hands rather than one yeah there's like a historical one that's like so you take
both hands and you form them into a blod and it's you guys know how to do that i'm doing it right
now i i do yeah uh it's all right go ahead get uh fucking lost my train of thought this is this
always happens when i'm in the middle of a point brilliant blood comment ben way to go no it's
everyone everyone's like it all right real funny though i apologize uh the okay symbol right the
okay symbol it gets changed um changed as in like quote unquote changed like some people start using
it as a meme how many people in the entire world is the majority thinking of this as a racist thing
now it's really just like you give it a couple years until it is guaranteed yes everybody knows
this thing to be to be like culturally insensitive or racially insensitive or something and then once
it's like pretty clear then you don't use it just to out of respect because like if the if you've
lose if you lose the battle and the word now means something else then what are you gonna do are you
going to constantly fight the rest of your life over this one thing that you just nobody you're
never going to convince everybody that it used to be something else and you're going to continue
using it the old way because at some point it it's just changed it's like words change their
meaning i mean i guess i don't think that we're there i guess i think that it's not you big yeah
not not for the okay sign or it's changed that meaning and you can't just say well i'm just not
gonna accept it or you're just gonna end up being wrong what are we actually we're actually talking
about subscribe to PewDiePie which is obviously not inherently racist i mean if you think PewDiePie
is a racist terrible person like okay well i don't think that what do you mean it's obviously not
inherently racist it means whatever you think it means well okay we can say that for literally
every word so let's not yes we yes we sure sugar can my my friend like and and we will it's it's just
it's just like i'm coming at it from like a perspective of uh you know if i find out that
something is racist then well i'm gonna stop doing it if it you know in the context in which
that would be you know that would get me in trouble or is just be a stupid thing to do for no reason
like i wouldn't go out of my way to say something that i don't think is racist but people have
have decided is racist i i just would like well you know i can do without that word if every word
in the english language was suddenly you couldn't say it then that that would be something different
but like i i don't i don't inherently find losing ground as like like a terrible thing
like i i understand like if the the subscribe to PewDiePie thing it's not that old so like
i can see just still using it like innocently enough so i wouldn't demonize anyone for using it
using it in the in the the more innocent like interpretation of it it's just like once you
know once you are aware then there's a certain level of responsibility that comes with knowing
when to say it i i sure didn't i wasn't saying subscribe to PewDiePie all the time but i sure
would have thought twice about it you know after the whole well well here's the thing right like
what you have you when you're in a transition period like that you know because like you're
we're asking like when does the scale tip or when does the the switch flip and all that kind of
shit and like it really just like for a while things just have dual meanings like right now
like the okay sign means okay or white power depending upon your intent because like a joke
got out of hand on 4chan and now it has two meanings and while i can understand on the one hand
saying like well if something changes we have to respect that new meaning because things do change
over time the way they change over time is doing what Nate's mad about and giving that ground uh
yeah and look i know there's people who aren't clued into like it might i don't know your fucking
grandma or whatever like she'll be like oh my god they're using this symbol and it means a horrible
thing uh i didn't think it meant that but okay i guess it does oh better not do it like they're
not clued into the whole fucking back and forth here i i get it but i don't know i when you when
maybe i'm being conspiratorial but when look i'm not even saying i sense an agenda of like a force
that's not what i'm saying i'm just saying that like we this guy for example said he was trying to
make people you know more angry and divided and all that stuff and like and that's what's happening
so why i mean we just feel like well look obviously this doesn't mean what do you think well the thing
is with that is that um what he's trying to do is like the easiest thing in the world like it only
takes well you know it takes like a sentence to ruin any friendship you have uh yeah i suppose so
a friendship that can last for that can be built up over years like if you say the wrong thing then
it's all over so like causing discord and and disruption and making people fight each other
is like not not even slightly a challenge so it's not like he can it's not like him manipulating us
is some feat that we you know i mean anything he said like like he used the he used the um you
know the marine copypasta right he said the whole like i'm a i'm a such a such a marine was so like
that's tainted now too maybe not oh that is fucked up ben that is fucked up well here's the thing
shut the fuck up and let me finish the point is that it has an association to that guy
just like anything he did is now associated with that guy and there's just no helping it
and like yeah he said the pewdiepie thing so of course that connection now exists and it was a hot
topic at the time it was like a hot meme at the time so of course it's got you know it attracted
a lot of attention along with the in association with the story and and that's just an unavoidable
thing like hippo was saying it's the easiest thing in the world to connect two things like i'm not
saying i would love if people could just disregard that guy or if he got no press whatsoever it would
be even better it would be it would be nice um but the fact of the matter is information travels
really quickly and now people know those things and it's like you did he leave oh no we lost him
nate nate what nate nate uh rage course oh he's back oh no he's back no he's back oh we had five
glorious seconds of no nate what happened uh uh yeah sorry about that um i'm sorry i guess i just
looked at you were saying this discussion's like fucking sick and all and like talking about politics
that aren't actually politics being political uh that's great uh but but i want to talk about uh
i played dark souls let's talk about trees in dark playing fucking dark souls i'm playing dark
souls in bloodborne let's talk about that instead it sounds way more calm tell me about all the trees
in in in dark souls the dark the trees in dark souls actually my sister was laughing at them
yesterday because they use the uh the cross textures they just take a flat image and put it
in like a cross shape to make it look like 3d oh yeah she thought that was funny uh because it's
an old game and she's a child you guys understand the graphics used to suck i can't believe dark
souls is an old game it feels like just yesterday i just i got the lord vessel and i killed i killed
two two of the boss of the big goss of the big souls so far uh nice i don't know dude i'm trying
i've got 40 something hours in i still can't i can't get into dark souls it's just sick real on
switch what secaro is not the new one on switch not yet i think secaro is not on the switch dark
souls i'm playing dark souls on the switch i guess it's like not the remaster it's just the vanilla
version at a higher frame rate yeah it's just the older isn't that isn't that just what the
remaster is that it's just the remaster changes some visuals and stuff i guess and people are
like bent about that like yeah the the visual the visual changes i've been watching the digital
foundry visual yeah there's none of those in in the switch version because i guess i can't run them
or something so it uses all the old i have a question to y'all have y'all played like this um
old bioware game called jade empire i played some of it yeah oh did you like it it was pretty cool
it was it was i liked it more than kotor because it actually had real-time combat i always thought
it was dumb and kotor wearing like i pull out a lightsaber and i'm ready to fuck people up and
then just freezes and i got to like do turn based stuff i was like oh yeah jade empire was like
bioware's first like not their first original ip but like it was their first of that generation
because i did star war stuff and then they finally made their own shit it was pretty cool and there
was like kung fu and it was cool yeah it was basically my childhood and i loved the game so
much i could never do the bad route i just felt so bad you had to be so mean that's that's that's
bioware's shtick yeah but like i really liked how when you were evil like like the shadows would
just sort of like start like slowly yeah yeah it was so cool not enough people played jade empire
yeah it's weird like it's like it's the redheaded stepchild like people remember kotor people remember
mass effect really fondly but jade empire was there and it was like the stepping stone between
you should you should play it on iam games uh i should yeah i'll have to wait i'll have to get
isn't isn't iam games done isn't it isn't it season season one is wrapped but uh uh once i get my
injury figured out i will hopefully be reviving it and continue so so you so you got that in the
divorce yeah yeah it's not even that i got it in the divorce it's that did you never gave a shit
about any of this shit surrounding iam games and so i'm the only one in the discord you know that's
i have the power i'm so so it's all mine you know i was i was uh organizing my room the other week
or last week and i don't know where my iam game shirt is i know i have it and i it's buy another
one don't you have to like you'll be both games it's different though that was that was a handmade
one that was the original run oh it's gotta be somewhere it's gotta be somewhere please find
faith you'll find it i i've been dying to get back in the video games i'm notoriously well like
have not played single player games let me let me tell you my sheet all you got to do is just
injure your spine and then you just have no desire or drive to do real work because every moment of
being awake is i've noticed you've been tweeting a lot about video games lately i've done nothing
but play dark souls and bloodborne for the last two weeks and uh it's been and i can tell you're
having a real shit time of it and you hate dark souls and i don't understand it makes me mad is
so miserable it sends fortress is so hard guys well it is i can't what is what are all these
fucking snake men doing here like uh why do you want to kill me so bad yeah like i wanted to give
him a hug why they sell all these traps for me what the fuck yeah it's pretty it's pretty it's
pretty not fun and i was i was really upset i'm beating it out of pure spite right now because
every time i say like i'm treating like twitter right now is just like i'm live tweeting dark
souls like you're just like i'm just playing it i got my phone in one hand those topical games of
playing yeah yeah exactly um but the reason i'm playing it is because i want i want because
everybody in this chat fucking loves dark souls and i'm like all right i gotta i gotta i gotta
figure it out i gotta get to the the meat and never play dark souls everything about this new
from soft game and i don't really understand what the deal is i mean it's it's just dark souls but
again like there's literally no difference like i don't understand so live tweeted yeah so i'm playing
playing fucking dark souls and i don't know i guess it's because like it started back in iam
games because like did you was always talking about dark souls and i was like i don't really like it
and then we got neo because he's like oh neo is like a dark souls s kind of game but by team ninja
who made ninja guide in one of your favorite games so maybe you'll like that and i started not really
liking it then i got into it and i played way too many hours it but like neo is way harder than
dark souls and it's way harder than blood boron it like fucking beats the shit out of you so then
i started playing blood boron again because i had that since i got my ps4 and just couldn't get
into it but this time for some reason it clicked and like i played it just on stream randomly to
kill time i think it was when digi wasn't there he was like away getting his house shit sorted out
i needed something to play and then i packed up all my shit to move back to my parents place while
i got my spine fucking surgery done and like the entire time i was like getting my shit packed up
like man i just want to play blood boron right now it's kind of weird so i got into it and i
bought the dlc and i fucking destroyed that game it was pretty fucking cool and i was like all right
i've done it now i can play dark souls and get it and i played dark souls and i still don't get
i mean dark souls and blood boron well actually demon souls and blood boron are the most like
divergent in terms of the type of gameplay and yet also the same yeah and i'm having tons of
arguments on twitter about it and i'm trying to be respectful and not mean because i don't i don't
think dark souls is a bad game i just think dark souls does nothing in terms of like what i really
like in games like it's pretty fucking cool and there's like some little interesting bits but
like the core gameplay loop isn't enough to like keep me invested because like that was a thing like
i got to father gas coin in blood boron and then that's when i ended the stream and i started to
pack it up my shit up and i was like thinking the whole time like man i want to like take that hunter
axe and kill more shit because it feels fucking great and that's why i went through and finished
playing everything and that like fun of the core gameplay loop got me through all of the
frustration of playing blood boron um dark souls is combat and just like core gameplay loop isn't
as engaging for me personally uh because a lot of it's just like waiting because you have to
like keep your shield up and like you know wait for openings and stuff where blood boron was way
more aggressive based which i kind of enjoyed that was like the idea behind it there's nothing
there's nothing but hatred driving me to beat this because i just because every time i say something
uh i don't really know if i like uh this part of the game it's not really doing it for me like
i'll just get a response it's get good so i want to get good i want to beat the game and then when
i go on twitter and be like guess what i got good and it's still gay and i still don't like it sorry
bro i hate get good so much it makes me sad i just went from playing securo jumping into playing
dark souls on switch which by the way calls itself dark souls remaster so i assume that it is but i
mean maybe there's more to the story securo calls itself dark souls remaster no dark souls the dark
souls on the switch says dark souls remaster right on the thing which is brand it is dark souls
remaster because they the changes of like uh being able to change your covenant from the
bonfire and like a couple other mean little tweaks like that are there but the graphics engine because
it was developed by it it was ported by a different company than the ones that did the ones for ps4
and xbox they just took the base uh the base xbox 360 well shit that's probably the best version
then because the dark souls normal remaster looks like shit on on pc possibly i don't know i thought
the flame still looks shitty on the bonfires this or whatever maybe uh but uh jumping from that from
securo to that game was like stepping into you know you know when you're in dark souls and you go
into the swamp and you start moving at like you know quarter speed or whatever yeah that's what
going from securo to dark souls feels like all the time and it's it's you know it's more deliberate
it's more you know whatever you gotta think about yourself as someone who plays devil may cry all
the time like that's what playing any from game feels like and and like that's understandable
going to dark souls one just like overemphasize that like even you know i'm like uh i think i mean
playing dark souls now it's good i mean i i got like i respect it as like an art piece obviously
and i'm a huge fan when i played it back in the day but having played dark souls two three blood
born and securo now it's hard to go back and i feel like a lot of the joy of the game is actually
about like the multiple playthroughs and the different play styles well that's why i got dark
souls on switch because my idea was like everyone because i watched i watched all of hippo's dark
demon blood videos before i bought anything uh because i wasn't sure if i was gonna get demon
souls or not and based on your demon for any video i was like i don't think i'll probably be able to
get into demon souls if it's even slower um so i kind of passed on that maybe i'll go back to it
at some point demon souls i think is like the they they got it right the first time sort of game
like it is slow but like it's so much about it is so good yeah it's great maybe maybe maybe i'll
get to it maybe you should go go to the voicemail ralph pete green was a comic genius who spent years
quote clowning around and spiraling to life's lowest depths then he conned rhymed and quote
speechified his way to heights he hardly dared imagine using lessons from his unconventional
grandmother on national tv with pete greens washington he'd end with a signature rhyme
i'll tell it to the hot i'll tell it to the cold i'll tell it to the young i'll tell it to the old
that had viewers asking who is this man laugh answers and introduces two characters destined
to capture hearts that's it that's the description for laugh if you like ain't a damn thing funny
the life story of a ralph pete green as told to lerma wrackley which i am really coming out you
obviously message pete pete white pete green and and he's late on you yet again lerma i messaged
lerma wrackley i messaged lerma wrackley but she's too busy playing skyrim and she won't make an acx
account so we can make the fucking audio book together god damn it i'll do the accents and
everything i'll fucking do it i don't care oh that that'll go over really well that that everyone
man that's a waste of watermelon oh god hey guys uh that's just what he sounds like i
everyone in this chat it just loves dark souls comes on it i've got come on the mind today you know
i guess that's what you get when you bathe in seaman anyway guys it's me uh i'm here on the pcp
i forget what i was oh dark souls i everyone likes that's all you were saying something though
no no let let my cheek go okay oh i i uh and i tried to play on pc i thought i was uh i don't
want to say boring uh i think it says this is the house but i just assumed that everyone was right
that was a good game i just stopped playing it's like you know i'm sure they're right you know it's
okay all right and then i stopped to save time but uh bloodborne has always seemed really appealing
to me it's always seemed like a game that i would really enjoy but it's on a ps4 and like are you
joking me like ha ha is what i say to someone saying the words playstation 4 to me like there's
no way i would ever acquire one at all but like what i like played at digis house was so good and so
fun i just craved and knew it but unfortunately i'm blocked by by the tools at my disposal and makes
me upset every single day yeah hey you know bloodborne that's surprisingly good it's definitely
the worst thing about all of it is that they're on lockdown consoles i really wish bloodborne and
demon souls you could just play on pc well actually i was gonna mention one of the things
i wanted to bring up was that playing dark souls actually kind of like sort of meta ruined some
of my appreciation for bloodborne and the reason for that is that it it became very clear when
playing dark souls how bloodborne came to be um because it was clearly like like sony rolled up
to from software it's like hey that dark souls thing pretty big we had a thing with demon souls
and we fucked it up sorry about that why don't you make us another exclusive kind of game like
that but like you know gaming's like bigger and more mainstream now so maybe like uh make it
more accessible for stupid people like maybe take out a lot of like the weight restrictions
and uh and a lot of that should maybe make it simpler maybe pare down all of the rpg stuff
make it so that our dumb console install base will be able to play it a bit more so we can sell
a couple extra million copies thank you very much and that's definitely what happened with
bloodborne i mean yeah and i'm a stupid person and i like sounds like they made a better game
that i would like to enjoy yeah i think i think exactly i'm one of the dumb peasants that liked
the streamlined simplification i mean all right i i hate like the the the whole like get good
atmosphere of the dark souls fanbase more than anyone um and yet i love those games and it's
it's always annoyed me how like there's this elitism about you know all that stuff well i yeah
it's it's just like all right i am a casual gamer i i don't play games a lot and when i do
i want to win all the time and so for me dark souls is just sort of inherently interesting
uh because i want to play it despite i get mad and throw the controller across the room
maybe i'm just mentally strange that way i also really like the swamps i don't know why i like
the swamps but i really like uh the the it's all that mud it's all that mud like this it's all
that good gloopy bubbly mud it's it's the sort of like grossness and the depraved like sludge
and and and you know blood monsters and flies and you're making me hungry and it's like all all
all coagulating at the bottom of the world and it's like yeah that's what i want to go into i want
i want to trundle through that stuff and kill everything um speaking of hunger uh uh and
swamps uh what do you call a white girl with a yeast infection michelle cracker with cheese gross
got them oh no i was googling what do we do we do we want to do we want to do we want to duck
back real quick to that shouting match we were having a minute ago and see if we can't just
smooth that over the entire reason i brought up dark souls was to end that no but i know you're
well i'm being transgressive by suggesting we dip back i feel like i feel like we got the end to
the end of that conversation i don't think everyone dislike that but also i have a new thing to talk
about um please god i i'm a web comic guy and i do web comics and my newest web comic is red
man and the things he says in four panels over and over again i love the red man this is a slice
of live comic yeah the slice of life he is he's just sort of he's such a simple wholesome you
know blood beast was this was this intentional did you did you like sit down and make this
like with a plan in mind or is just something that you did dry all right and decided to make a
thing i had in the past i had in the past uh drawn a four panel or a three panel like garfield
comic i took the garfield without garfield without john and um i had jim davis written there and i put
blood man i put red man and gun girl uh and gun girl shot red man and that was funny um oh no she
just sort of didn't like him and that was the whole comic he just said hello and i i just liked that
as the the you know a tiny panel comic and i was thinking red man and gun girl are my two ocs in
rowdy focus cop killers universe and i was thinking i could do like a garfield uh comic with them as
the characters and one day i was thinking hmm i should really get around to that garfield comic so
i just drew some really crappy red man thing of him saying i just drew three three lines in a small
document drew red man and then i put some text on it and uh it was it was just really funny and so i
thought this reminds me of dinosaur comics i was gonna ask if you were influenced by dinosaur
comics because it was like the format's like identical of like the art stays the same but
you're changing the captions yeah it's it's the it's the coolest idea i've ever i've ever seen
and you know that those dinosaurs are so funny we gotta we gotta get red man syndicated in the
slime times munchie yeah the slime times needs to come back we gotta revive that just for him
yeah the blood times it will be called was the perfect chroma keying green background done for
pre-emptive uh uh memification purposes no that was just because green complements red as a color
and if you'd pop out of the screen and also it was garish which is very rfck core that's true we
should be our endless war should saturation all the way up yeah it's it's it was really funny the
first few times i was like ha yeah i could do this i could do this as a little side comic and now
whenever i have something that i would otherwise make a tweet out of i make red man say it and it's
suddenly a million times better damn that's good way more yeah that's really that's really good
got it you gotta figure out it's a good scheme you got going there yeah it means blown up immediately
upon posting it everyone's just latched on to it like a baby to a tea yep exactly in the back of
my mind i'm thinking hmm what if i make a million of these and then i publish a book and have them
all in there and ruin everyone's goodwill yeah i'm imagining like a hardcover book that's like
really big like one of those like novelty books you get if you're like a kid it's just like the
big book a fucking suckin dick and then uh it's you know a huge book that's like the entire like
width of your tour so but it's just is all like a red bang comics for like hundreds yeah how funny
would that be i i would buy that and put it on i would i would buy that absolutely you gotta have
the format it's just one strip per page and then like huge white borders so the maximum thickness
yeah i would sign each page individually yeah yeah oh do you gotta have a you know you gotta have
like hussey style like uh author notes at the bottom of each page explaining each one they'd
be unbelievably like like orders of magnitude longer than the comic themselves it's like no no
it's like half the pay like like the top half of the page is the comic and a huge white border
in the bottom half is just like a long like paragraph but all the art all the commentary has
to be about the artwork even though it's the same artwork every time yeah it's like i was going for
i was really trying to emphasize the motion of this of this one uh you know 10 out of 10 i want
this to be real you have a long-term goal now i just really like the way he smiles at the end
because yes and the fact that like it's binary brush and it's all very small so like that every
pixel that sort of adds to his smile sort of like makes it hard to discern exactly what he's
thinking so it's just it could you could interpret it it it's literally like the money by the
content who knows what who knows what's behind that like that smirk can mean anything just
depending on the panel before someone said it's it's fucking brilliant i did so now that you've
become a mean a meme hippo do you want to continue to melt your viral viral worth for all it is worth
do you do you plan to make more memes in the style just let it come naturally are you an
artist about this or is gonna be your new career path your patreon one dollar pledge get new red
band comic no i think this is gonna be like as long as i can think of something funny to put
i will put something and then uh my i mean it takes like one second to make one of these uh wait
really it looks really involved the end product
don't don't don't don't stare this when you're when you're just that fucking good you know just
makes the rest of us look like we're moving in slow motion i really like how people have taken to
to making their own yeah that's the way to win would you say i think you should probably bring
litigation against those people yeah you think i should destroy them yeah i think so welcome for
all their work here's the scenario hippo uh blood man becomes real and start feasting upon blood
do you disavow the red band comic what the he like a person becomes real as red man and is the same
guy no no red no no listen you're making the technology that every child wants the technology
to enter the side of the tv to jump right in like you're dived into a swimming pool you get into
the cartoon world but what's this while exiting red man himself comes out and says his favorite
catchphrase blood and continues to beat the blood of in a sense do you say no rayman that's a bad
stop or do you say well you know that's just his prerogative and then keep and then crank it keep
crank it out your red man comes i would probably um uh set him loose or against uh the uh the the
farm animals instead of the people but then the farmers would be mad farm animal blood is that
okay is he okay with animal blood i think he's pretty i think he's pretty happy with it like he
gets a chicken and he's just so squeezes it until everything comes out and then just shows that
in his mouth animals to red man let's be honest i like it i like it dude draw draw draw that now
i'm slamming black blood the other day let me just tell you the bars tab grew sky dude red
dude red man's gotta make a uh a beverage to compete with fuck energy he's gotta release
blood energy he would never sell it that's the that's the problem he has like a whole thing
like it's canned and bottled and it's got a custom label but it only for him it's not for sale
anywhere it's like cunt corona selling his like kool-aid man but he shows up to the blood bank
and bursts in the walls and takes all the blood he wants that blood man and he and he unlike most
good dealers you know he definitely is partaking of his own stash so so red man played too much
blood born got all those blood vials he's like i want to do this in real life he's blood drunk
he's one of those he's one of the fat guys from blood born but real shit red man and gun girl would
be a great like actual like like like short on youtube like five minutes every like six months
that'd be great yeah i would need to get like a voice actors for that put that shit on new
why
yeah you got a perfectly good voice cast right here right here yeah right here hire me hire me
all right munchie you can be red i'll be gun girl i volunteer to be gun okay all right well
my people will talk to your people and we'll we'll sort something out send us send us a
people racist much yeah high five all right voicemails yes such a short episode no yeah what
white white white voice we've been going for an hour and a half also i said i have to go at four so
we got half an hour voicemails i might be able to scratch it a little bit taking like an hour sometimes
sure is nate is nate alive i'm yeah i'm here i'm here let's do voicemail you fall asleep you
went catatonic after we stopped talking about politics all the energy drained from his body
oh no more drump no more nate he said leaving as fast as he could i mean i had all this rage and
then i was just had nowhere to put it so it just turned to ashes in my mouth his soul left his body
and floated up like Winnie the pooh you're gonna ashes in your mouth get in an ash tray dumbass
see i'm not mad about politics anymore because i'm just so mad at dark souls all my rage just goes
to dark souls now i don't i don't get just something happens trump says something elizabeth
warren says something i don't care i'm still mad about blight town it's fine dammit i wasn't
trying to make it about politics it's about basically in blight town right now i'm my right
fellow man i hate politics first voicemail first voicemail i want to talk about fucking politics
and shit i'm gonna talk about it no you're not i'm gonna talk about something else no i don't give
a shit anymore i don't give a shit either no politics go start teabap again voicemails go that's
not how that works no nate nate nate nate why are you mad why are you mad i'm not why may
why is mage mad because i'm tired of politics i took a break from pcb for like three that's a
that's a weak that's a weak opinion philosophical discussion that is that is a weak commenter to
your opinion oh it wasn't about politics i mean politics technically if you if you widen the
brush to involve anything social commentary there are not modern you know us politics yeah okay okay
what would just would annoys me is when people especially in the comments but anywhere will just
they'll use they'll call it like oh i hate all this talk of politics when like it's not even it's
really just like an opinion i just want to i just want to move to voicemails that's all i want i do
i mean i do too i do too i just all right people just just we'll just throw that word around like
a general dirty word it doesn't mean it's been diluted it doesn't mean anything anymore i just
sense that may spend me in exchange they they think the word politics mean i'm not going to
apply the new concept we have to disavow i guess okay the final point we'll move on yeah i'm just
saying that like i think that that particular discussion could have been decent but perhaps
it went on too long we got too into it and expanded to too many categories and perhaps that was
inevitable because i'm aware we're making a product here i don't want to make this unpleasant for
people to listen to i want this to be a good thing but i mean there has to be some room for some
amount of discussion of some of these things sometimes yes there is we were we were getting
into like the fundamental nature of language though and you know you yeah once you're there you can't
wrap that up on a podcast that's fair that's fair so sorry major didn't mean to yell at you that was
a built up frustration about things so okay all right let's sorry i yelled you i was just doing
a funny because mage yelling well i was not doing a funny i was doing an angry for sure well the
well that's that's that much is clear i'm trying i'm trying to make a joke and be like oh you can't
do it it's impossible funny is funny is just depends on what the individual believes it means
why do we have to disavow they make jafar like a business like a fucking salary man he sounds like
don't get me the lamp please i beg of you he sounds like a fucking faggo sounds like a twink
please anything for a lamp and it's just it's just not right i just don't agree with it at all
fetch me the lamp a ladder no it'll be your last sunrise he's saying that no but i mean he should
it sounds like something he'd say that fits into my generic employee jafar jafar's awesome
jafar's the coolest he's such a pussy now yeah he's oh he's great he's great but they ruin them
they ruin a new one well i mean give him a chance maybe oh the new Aladdin wait what do you mean
there's a there's a live action one with um will smith as the genie is now live action Aladdin
oh god is that out it's coming out soon it's gonna be at soon hey is there a toy story for yep
yep that's also coming soon i think okay it's coming soon okay all right great it stars a spoon i
think yes that's right i've seen the spoon it is spoon getting into the fundamental nature of what
is it to be alive what is it to be a toy what is it what is it to worship a capricious god
up around whom you define your entire identity on their on their approval of your of your existence
was was was woody just indoctrinating buzz into the into the andy cult the whole time yes
should we really look so fondly upon all this pure projection of andy's homosexual urges uh
but that being said uh let's check with our boy sex rex for our first voicemail yeah uh all right
here we go commands hey guys it's me there's sex rex um i was uh listening to the pcp big
mistake uh last episode while i was having sex and i just uh what's what's your guys favorite
say oh god oh his favorite you know a sex rex uh male i think that his name is latin and rex
means king so he's actually the sex king oh i thought it was like sex rex as in like sex rex
live sex rex home rex no sex sex rex like dino sluts if you remember that oh dude remember dino
sluts yeah i do i saw it recently wait you did i was looking at old i was looking at yeah i was
looking at old twitter things and uh i saw it wasn't that like wasn't that like well like when we
were thinking of things to name the podcast or something i think it was i think this was gonna
be the dino sluts podcast why didn't we call it the fucking dino sluts that would have been so
much better once again there'd be a divided community the dinos versus the sluts you choose
your side ladies and gentlemen we got a rebrand okay we got listen ever since we made that we're
the reason people are dying shared our brand has been tainted and we've got to walk it back we've
got to roll back the brand we've got to come back out as the dino sluts there's still time i think
i know jessy'd be on board for sure i drew like a little i drew like a little icon it was like a
like a banner that said dino sluts and it had like a t-rex roaring but it had like big tits
can we get that in the show notes that's gotta be a bit all right fine i problem man i don't know
i feel like i can i can i can get the the tweet that i saw it from okay great all right put that
in the show notes assuming whenever possible uh but okay let's move on uh that that was a good
question that unearthed some deep lore uh like primordial lore of the pcp stuff that i'm not sure
anyone anyone listening would ever have heard before yeah damn that's probably the juicy
shit they want to hear but uh let's move on baseball that's that inside baseball i'm talking
about episode two here is keto punk kitchen checking in so let's let's see what they have to say
maybe pure kidding stones indeed oh wait i pushed the wrong button uh okay go here's a
needle keto treato for you dudes who are elita take some cocoa and some splenda mix it up like
you're a blender then stir in some heavy cream oh that tastes just like a dream
that's it is that it that's it that's the whole thing okay because i literally make that all the
time wait what is that what is that concoction exactly is that a drink it's it's just keto hot
chocolate oh okay or i mean you can blend if you blend it in like a blender i mean i put ice in it
and then it's come like a milkshake but you can dilute it with a little milk and then heat it up
in the microwave and then it's hot cocoa it's great sounds good i drink that i i want i want a keto
milkshake like right now it's fucking it's great it's fucking great ice cream cocoa stevia or splenda
blended drinking excellent okay thanks we appreciate the rhymes and whatnot keto pun that was great
that was those rhymes were actually pretty good yeah i was actually impressed just like a dream
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna tape that up on a on my wall and i post it now good idea
print it like a haiku you won't be saying that 24 hours when he's uh in a hot shower for the
third time as he as he's sitting in that hot shower desperately slurping at his hot keto
cocoa the one thing that sustains him through his pain uh but also would cause it that's the
joke okay anyway uh fat cock 69 uh we've got a message from you let's hear it
so my friend recommended me this podcast the pcp podcast yo listen into that shit this is
pretty fucking entertaining bro yo this is a funny shit anyway thanks this is your podcast
i was listening today the best guy i ever talking about and fucking that we're taunted bitch that
was pretty interesting to me that was pretty entertaining anyway so i listened to that i
was thinking about it i was thinking about the concept of having sex with we're taunted
bitch so i was thinking about that concept and i was hearing that with the concept that you
discussed the engagement concept to jim davis jim davis's idea of engagement and so i was thinking
our city here i was listening to this podcast with my friend and i was like hypothetically
hypothetically hypothetically would fucking we're taunted bitch be considered engagement you see
let me explain this to you entertainment because you're having sex and sex is inherently entertaining
it keeps you engaged also yeah it's engaging because it's sexy you're having sex you're going
for that not but you see there's a lot of entertainment and it's on top of that because
the bitch is retarded that's interesting that's an alternate experience that's interesting yeah
that's real good and i'm retarded so i'd like to i want to experience the other side of that
that's what i was thinking about anyway i appreciate you listening to my voicemail
back off 69 thank you i love you guys so much
okay so so i'm pretty sure so i'm pretty sure he answered his own question there yes
having sex with the retarded bitch is enter gauging however i want to ask another question
nate did michelle hear the podcast last week oh you know i don't think she got that far i don't
okay i was gonna ask what did she think of that whole thing shit you know what i i told her that
there'd be a great part that she should listen to but i don't think i'll have to remind her to do
so okay i'll report back with results um i was here yeah okay well blasted on the car stereo on the
way to the adventures good idea good idea make a twitch highlight okay next one we got uh hell no
fresh uh calling it yeah let's see what this is about i just don't even want to what am i do
that's not from hell no fresh are you retarded or or don't know how to cook of course you are
listening to this podcast oh it's recipe we're gonna be making peanut butter ramen i know that
sounds a little wacky but if you're ahead something like peanut chicken it's basically the same idea
whatever fuck you dude flavor wise as far as packets of ramen go for this i'm gonna go ahead
and recommend something like pork chicken chili oriental would probably work something like
creamy chicken you probably got a little bit too much going on i'd be a little bit of dubious
selection but that's shit you my man you're gonna want to get two or three green onions
chop them up into little little little sections uh take the tentacle looking bits off the bottom
and fucking chuck them bitches into your yard next time your dad knows the grass you can sift
through the clippings with your greasy little peasant food you might find some free green onions
that's pretty dope take that shit on the stove throw your fucking noodles in there throw your
fucking water in there empty the sauce packet in there put 75 percent of your green onions in there
and then a dash of sesame oil and a sprinkling of red pepper flakes and once that shit gets going
you want to take a scoop of your peanut butter and just toss that shit right in there it'll get
on nice and emulsified it's fucking great you want to take the remaining 25 percent of your
green onions and sprinkle those along some red pepper flakes on top of your sunny side up eggs
that you've got going on medium heat cover that shit because you want to ensure that the yolk
remains raw right so when you put the nice crispy eggs on top of your fucking soup you can bust the
yolk into the broth and your dick would be crackling with sexual energy hey hey hell hell no fresh
that's actually the the the sesame oil and stuff like that is sounds incredible it's actually a
somewhat similar concoction to a thing that I make with ramen all the time it's ghetto carbonara
carbonara is a spaghetti uh dish sort of thing with egg in it and I make ramen with that so I
put uh I put I put also as well the chili flakes and like some a lot of like ground up red pepper
and then I put on an egg on top of it and I make sure to keep the yolk bursting on that as well
like a sunny side up yolk and I burst the egg into that shit and it's delicious if there's not that
much water in the ramen so it just kind of like the egg just coats the ramen without like yeah
the water sort of like you know alleviating that and it's just like carbonara it's just it's just
eggy noodles and it's delicious doesn't make that hey by the way I want to make that today
you know why am I the first because my kitchen works literally congratulations my kitchen was
fixed and I got groceries and I'm finally gonna be able to do my fair day in the world and fucking
cook again for the first time in literally months I'm so excited that's wonderful I feel an urge
to push back on mr hell no fresh because it seemed like the main component of his dish was like
instant ramen is that really like I mean can't you do better than that if you're cooking well
hold on shit out of instant ramen I mean it's not I mean it's not keto so it's obviously a zero out
of ten sure you can do it well I don't understand I mean it's an agree it like any other does it
taste the same as normal ramen no not really I mean though the the noodles in in instant ramen are
fairly low quality compared to other stuff I mean can't you you don't have to have a good dish with
like high quality ingredients that doesn't necessarily I'm just saying if you're making you
I mean are they are they any worse are they any worse than like regular pasta that's great because
it's easy to make and it's simple and it's you know you can make you can make it pretty reliably I
would say almost anytime you want to make top ramen I mean it seems like you're not even I mean okay
obviously there's other shit going on the peanut butter sesame alright it all sounds cool but I'm
just saying like the fundamental here like that's I don't know it feels like a cheat it feels like
it's not or it's not as good as it can be to make ramen noodles every single time you I'm with
munchy I'm with munchy and the instant ramen noodles are an ingredient like any other I I suppose
that's true and like you'll get it you'll get a different tasting dish if you use them as opposed
to I don't know a linguine well yeah I mean isn't there any kind of like raw ramen noodles you can
get like on its own and then like add you know spices and shit just of your own that gotta exist
somehow right like not just are you talking about the packet you can't just not use the packet
now well I'm saying like we're gonna get ramen noodles that aren't like the instant kind that are
you know like better you gotta go to knee home you go to where they sell the pasta you just boil
noodles in a you know they just come in packets similar what are ramen noodles I guess is the
real question I'm asked well instant instant instant ramen goes through a strange process that I saw
on TV once that involves something and it may or may not be good for you good but normal normal
ramen and pasta noodles that are not like instant and you have to like boil them for a number of
minutes those are just normal I've seen videos explaining how to make like real ramen and the
thing about it is that it is like a really complicated thing where you have to like steep
multiple like you have to do like multiple steps of like steeping different like herbs and ingredients
and like flakes of stuff and okay it's like it's like a it's like a pretty complicated process
that's how a lot of Japanese stuff it's like the katana food you gotta fold that yeah the invention
of making an instant ramen is like cutting out a million steps so yeah I guess there's no wonder
it's popular I think you can at like an asian market or something I think you can just sort of buy
like new like bundles of new of ramen noodle like you're not in like an instant pack but just sort
of tied up in like a like rolled up in like a ball sort of huh yeah okay that's kind of what I'm
talking about that'd be cool but maybe that's slightly more complex than I remember this recipe
involved the flavor packet it might it did it did okay he gave a couple of choices okay well
whatever fuck that he did say it was a ghetto dish so you know he did that's exactly kind of dish I
want a millet taste good is involved but doesn't make you want to kill yourself after the price
okay next voicemail let's do it it's uh Duke Nishimupil let's see what he's got for today
Mike my first son all right what does he need uh hello hello yes hello hi welcome hi hello this is
uh Duke Nishimupil I'm here to call in for my application to the teen cp um I went to your
website and I tried to find a location however you only had this number posted so I'm calling this
number now okay anyway what you got I would like to apply for my podcast job um my qualifications
are that I am literally biologically the son of munchie uh I am I'm I'm under the age of 18 so
that's important that's important um you can check my medical records and you can check that I am
indeed autistic uh let's see here what else uh I have been on two podcasts before so if you
want to check my credentials just go to uh see me on there uh is there anything else uh I avoid
political talk like it's the plague so you don't have to worry about that that's uh I am literally
retarded so well autistic and retarded um whoa all right well that's about it I I unfortunate
podcast if need be I'll do that yeah pretty good to go so um if you need me just uh give me a call
talk around talk to you around talk to you later talk to you later um yeah uh bye
pretty oncoming uh pitch for you and and unfortunately Dupati you listening to me
accept your application right now on this pcp will be a week after you're already accepting
clicking invite on discord right now you're gonna hear me live the moment that you were
sent this is the exact moment that I'm referring to right now on this oh my god episode right
now that's a moment outside of time so wait what's going on with the teen cp have you have you
have you got together yet yeah give us the update are you retarded yeah of course the teen cp
has contacted me and we are in a group together called the teen cp and we are here and we're
and we're just we're getting more members we're slowly you know occurring more and more teens
and we'll record our first episode soon muchy are you gonna go through some horrible like
eviction when they hit 20 and they are no longer teens they have to be like memory wiped
like kids next door style to no longer be in the teen cp is this the inevitable fate of all members
yeah munchie's already aged out he's 18 saying that i that i'm i'm well i'm well within the
age bracket yeah he's 18 so you know he'll be 19 but then when it's 20 that's why i'd be worried
i'd protect my neck and my back well you know it's like i'll just send off you know
my second command will then become the new munchie and then yeah and just keep going okay fair
fair enough fair enough there was there must always be a teen cp indeed there must always be
a munchie i'm surprised munchie's still eligible because as we've all heard first hand munchie
does not have a teen cp if you
yeah yeah yeah tom i do remember when i showed you my penis
guys what the fuck is going on
all right moving on uh how many how many more do we got uh like six like six more
all right tom so choco taco you got one go toms or taco choco everybody i just wanted to correct
something nate said last week yeah you actually still can download stuff from emu paradise it's
just you have to download an extension called uh tamper monkey and run a script through it
this is pretty easy to set up you can just google it it works fine i disavow any kind of
illegal activity this man might be engaged in here uh i heard i heard that you just need a link
that like the the emulators are still there you just need to find they don't have the direct
links to them anymore so you need to find the direct links elsewhere like there's a subreddit
or something like well you know the links to download emulators are legal emulators themselves
are generally legal there's there's i'm i'm talking about the roms though i'm talking about the games
yeah um but i haven't actually tried it so i don't know if i mean there's an even easier way than that
friend all you have to do is buy the game purchase them on your nintendo switch yeah that's a stupid
idea it doesn't sound that something doesn't sit right about that to me on a moral grounds
get in contact with your friend andy activision and he'll hook you up with any game andy activision
did a hell of a job with securo so you know what i'm on i'm on his side right now uh but okay let's
let's listen up to uh lost tape archive number three
nate well it's by time i guess uh time to face the fire go i was blitzing through the cosmos
the other day in search of the holy bludge i crashed into a remote aquatic planet called florida
it extended its watery arms a wet tape in its clutches it whispered
take me take it my darling take it for nate
i am a being of pure utilitarian bliss sounds like it i hail from the holy nation the nation of
hydration drink your water drink your water i drink florida with a straw i now have the mass
of ten moons
i mean i think is the canon lower behind these like these are our private recordings
that this man stumbles upon we're like 12 and i still don't know i mean there's a
there's lore being unearthed here uh maybe in like a past life or maybe like at my core being
i'm like the reincarnation of a pure entity of pure utilitarianism and hydration who also wants
cochi that sounds about right but uh you don't sound like you've been drinking your water i've
i got well i got gatorade for my electrolytes with me right now which you mean in in that
recording in that recording it sounded like you needed a drink i need my water i need my water
peter the problem that's the problem the more water you drink the more you need the next time
to quench your thirst next true it's true best to just avoid it to begin with agree are we talking
about cutting down our carbs because believe me i would love
no we would never talk about doing such a thing keto squidward get out of here remember that time
the squidward bought canned bread the least keto food in existence next time yes i was upset
a boycott of the episode i drank the florida and you know have a large mass but okay uh let's
you need to drink your water need no there's no you have to drink your water everyone's
get a squidward pass a kidney stone and and spongebob bought it for 25 cents i okay i breathe
it wrong but the good news is we got poo easy rectal cleaner unit 2148 series is calling in
and let's get into it right now go this is a public service announcement we'll
let you know that you are all shit my voice modulator is bigger than your voice modulator
you suck balls especially fat but bag it you can die go down to the hole of anises where you
will be pooped on for eternity fuck you he wants to flex his voice mod I have the biggest he has
the biggest voice all right worst voice modulator that no like I like that because it's so over the
top but I could understand everything I want that voice it's true I could let me tell it too yeah
please email me you're probably just like six voice modulators on top of each other yeah maybe
that's what it is maybe we should do a bonus episode where we're all using this
speaking of bonus episodes possibly we recorded one recently oh there's there's a new one that
should be out by the time you hear it I missed it because I had my fucking kidney stone I had no
idea what was going on oh yeah well let's understand so if you hate then you'll love this episode
yeah it was uh without spoiling too much we get to the core of our personality and understand
things about ourselves that you know that there was there was some light spots the episode there
were some dark spots the episode but you know mostly dark honestly mostly dark not gonna lie
not gonna lie pretty dark uh okay moving on we've got a voicemail from uh voicemail housekeeping uh go
what happens to the old voicemails did he just get deleted is there an internet archive does Nate
download them all what happens also if I make a voicemail for a specific member of the podcast
and they're not on when I record it if my voicemail just doomed to never be played you have to spam
the folder that same voicemail over and over and over again or can Nate just download the voicemail
and then play when it's actually relevant and when the member's on the podcast also why aren't the
mp3s uploaded earlier doesn't think less time to just edit audio files and not edit audio and visuals
why not it wouldn't really hurt the viewers okay that's it all right bunch of questions there
so okay so they get deleted because they're on soundcloud we only got so much space uh this is
just this is just a utility question I happen to get back to them on uh and like so I have
all the voicemails downloaded right now on my computer I have them maybe maybe we should make
them available in the google drive we just we have the raw ones that have ever been been submitted or
are the ones that have ever been played they've ever been played ever been played only and they're
all they're in order too I think for the vast majority of them anyway so like maybe I can put
them on on the drive but then that'll take up space on the drive and really take up that much space
though you know they are really short let me see how much is a file not big it's not big I mean
you could make like a video that houses all of them and unlist it so they they'd be around
like if you made a super long video with all of the voicemails in them and just have it on the
on the channel unlisted and then link people to it if they really want it you have to keep
making more though right I mean yeah we have that's that's uh adding a lot of extra work well you
know you could just do like one for 2018 one for 2019 make a disposable or a straight email account
that says a separate google drive or something indeed well here's the I think I think they
could just go in their own file on the drive since they're small that's a reasonable idea
yeah I like that they will stuck up eventually though yeah but like I mean one pack of them
is maybe one megabyte is like one megabyte for like all all 10 or 12 for a thing yeah so we got
we got space and um uh to the other question the the last one about like uh what if I have a voicemail
that's first specific person like why doesn't Nate just like hang on to it until I got fucking I don't
make any extra money for doing this shit with the voicemails uh I'm sorry but if it's part of your
admin fee my money did not go up when I started doing this extra work so explain to me again why I
should continue to do this when I get nothing for it because you want to it well it is the admin fee
but the admin fee did not rise when this extra responsibility it's the admin fee didn't I'm
saying that it didn't I'm saying that it didn't go up and you didn't make any more money did the
show notes get rolled into the editor fee I mean they like they just get given to the editors but
there's a separate payment for uh doing the show notes that people get when they edit so I don't
want to hear any of this fucking Nate needs to do more work shit I mean if you want me to propose
me extra money and then I'll put more effort into it all right well then I guess the voicemails are
dead and we all know who to blame it's been yeah I'll take it all right yeah just nail me to that
cross Tom so to the practice for you less humble listeners out there submitting your voicemails
sorry but you just got to keep submitting shit uh you know if you got a if you want one you want
people to hear honestly it's amazing that the voicemails are still working because we're not
paying anything for the voicemails we're only supposed to get like 20 a month on the free account
and for some reason it just doesn't enforce yeah it just keeps working so I'm pretty thrilled about
that hey okay anyway moving on from that so sorry guys but the burden's on you you gotta you gotta
keep submitting shit and we do not what was the last thing about the mp3 is going up late was that
the mp3 for the voicemails oh I think I think that was about I think he's talking about the mp3 of
the podcast um if you're talking about like the itunes feed the reason it goes up hours later
than the video is because when I make them go live at the at the same time that the episode goes up
but then google and like itunes they have to do like a check and it takes like a couple hours for
it to get like approved yeah yeah I could do it earlier but if I do it earlier it risks it'll go
up before the actual episode yeah I think I think maybe the last several episodes the uh the mp3
link has not worked I don't know if that got fixed at any point but I think there were a bunch of
episodes there yeah where the mp3 download link was not I usually check it but uh I mean if anybody
has an issue with that for a while I was seeing comments being like the mp3 link doesn't work I
know there were two episodes that had the same work because it wasn't changed and I did go back
and fix that uh all right but people keep an eye out basically maybe it's maybe it's anytime there's
a problem like there are tons of people who just bitch at me I'll be out on Twitter and I go and
fix them so oh okay well great I don't get paid for that either Nate that's not true you literally
do get paid for that that is your job that you get a fee for so no no I get I get paid to to upload
the stuff to iTunes but I mean like when there's things in the description people come bitch at me
and I fix those as well I don't get paid oh well I mean yeah I mean you have no responsibility to
do that yeah but I do it because I'm why do they bitch to you of all people uh because I've just
become that guy I guess uh well okay I mean you don't have to it's it's fine I don't like it's the
editor's responsibility to do that shit so who's the editor for the last like two months I mean
well okay so it is your responsibility is the point but because you're the editor that I don't
do well then it's not you okay whatever it doesn't matter it doesn't matter what I'm saying is I
get no ground on this point I suffer just as much as you that's what I'm trying to say even
it's not it's not true at all but I'm sticking to that's a hill I'm dying on for no reason
other than I feel like it well good news uh we've got a mail from best baby ever
and this is gonna be good I can already tell I can't wait here we go well this is the best baby
area and I just wanted to say that food is too fucking hard to make I'm tired of I'm too weak
for to follow instructions I want self cooking food I want to cook to be caught I want a baby
mode I want an easier than easy mode food should respect me as a consumer and give me an easier
than easy mode I I can't follow a youtube recipe I just it's too fucking hard I can't I can't
don't even find the the ingredients in the supermarket but I cannot do a shit I want
that a self cooking food I'm entitled to that if I pay for my ingredients I should have a good
a good meal in my head I this is a straw man I just shot myself oh he shat himself he shat
okay okay you know what I'm I'm just gonna say I'm just gonna say it guys based on popular
opinion which is the only measure of truth yeah I definitely won the hello fresh debate
you definitely did I don't everyone is everyone is on board with me I am the king I am the reigning
champion because everyone who listens to our podcast is poor and can't afford a service yeah
exactly everyone but no I think that our viewers are are intelligent capable human beings who are
more than able to fucking google a recipe and when we get a fucking flower at the supermarket
except when they shoot down political discussion then they're fucking retarded that's right then
they're fucking stupid okay as long as I always I found I found listening to that quite interesting
especially specifically with Nate saying that like yeah organizing ingredients and making a
meal is like so much of an extra hassle that you can't deal with and you want to be a baby and
you know spoon fan right no no no you were saying you were saying that words to that effect right
you're saying that sort of like you're phrasing in a very critical way but I mean I'm just saying
I'm just saying you don't want to have to think about it right you don't want to have to think
about it yeah but then at the same time you are like a calorie counting gain guy that like does
all of that other stuff that which pertains to food which is like why couldn't you also do that
when buying ingredients well okay but I mean to me that sounds like like uh you know a person
you're carrying you know 10 stones like what's the big just carry 11 stones and I mean like okay I
get it's not that much extra work but you don't want more stones to carry you want the least amount
possible I mean I think it's just that you have like the capability to to like regiment yourself
in that way already it's like a skill you already have you just don't want to apply it to this other
thing which is very very similar I I mean I guess so I've never been a cooking guy I mean let's be
fair though if there was something that Nate could just like use to just automatically count his
calories he would just do it like it wouldn't do it if he didn't have to that's true like there was
like some service I could sign up to that like scan whatever food I ate and just added it I mean
that'd be fantastic that'd be uh you know that'd be what I want just put an implant in your cheek
that scans everything that goes in your mouth and automatically you fucking counts all the calories
that'd be great that being said though you kind of want to you want to the point of some of the
point of counting calories is to like like not choose the things that are bad because you know
they're gonna be bad so it's a little bit of it'd be like by the time the food hits your lips it's
kind of too late sometimes but the thing about cooking for yourself is that it's modular in
that you can you can tune it to be whatever you want it to be like I've been making I've been
making a lot I've been using Arlo's crust recipe and I've been making a lot of keto pizzas lately
and you know I know I know exactly what goes in them you have wait you have two
I have no I want to get it on it sounds good oh it's it's great I made a I made like a pesto
with like I made like a pesto pizza with tomatoes and onions a while ago I ate that and then the other
day I made one with a salami onion mushroom and more sliced tomatoes with like a red sauce it was
really good it's really delicious it's really great okay I and and and but the point is I know
exactly what goes in them and I can make exactly how much I want and I can do if I want to not
cook for a while I can just make a much bigger one and it's it's it's it's convenient I I find
it more convenient like getting like that even even if Hello Fresh was like okay we'll deliver
three meals a day to you for like you know every day for like the rest of your life it's like yeah
well you'd still have to cook each one of them individually you know and that and da da da da
I got you the only thing is I've never operated that way in my in my life where like I've like
even when I was at my best calorie counting and you know most regimented with my diet and all that
stuff counting every single day and counting every calorie eight and stuff um like even then I would
like I had like designated meals that were just designed to meet the macronutrient goals of the
day and and that was by far the most important thing I was never I never like I just don't think
in a modular way when it comes to cooking I mean maybe I should that would be better but like I've
always been like ingredient like calorie first and then everything else is far secondary and so I
just like found you know recipes that allow me to you know mix those calories in a you know palatable
way for the day or whatever so just different way of thinking yeah but you can't you can't do that
with Hello Fresh though uh you get whatever they send you that's true that's true uh those those are
I I hate this topic more than life itself because I have such a non-point but I'm forced to play
devil's advocate about it all the time I don't recommend Hello Fresh I think it could be good
if you know if the things that we've talked about on the podcast seem like they're attractive to you
I don't think that if like if someone came to me and said I want to learn how to cook I would not
say get Hello Fresh I wouldn't say that I will say that the like I enjoyed Hello Fresh because
with stuff like that when you have you wouldn't like Nate you've never like branched out or tried
to have that creative spark and learn new recipes on your own the most appealing thing about Hello
Fresh is that it forces you into these boxes that they have like meticulously made to be fast
and easy and even though it's easy in the sense that it's not hard to do it will still help you
branch out because they're varied meals and they have various different ways that you can prepare
it with various different you know cuisines and and genres of food so the point of Hello Fresh in
my eyes was to be a a bomb in a way a bomb that would go off in my fridge if I did not cook Hello
Fresh well then that was wasted money and I didn't want to waste money you know buying Hello Fresh and
then just not even cooking it so it right the purpose of it was to force myself to do things
that I would not normally do that that was the benefit for me that was probably the sole benefit
and after I was like okay you know what I feel good that I've branched out I don't need to do
this anymore because I just want to do these things because I've realized that they're not that hard
to do and I can do them reliably on my own that's the point I that's the only thing I that's the
only goodwill I have towards Hello Fresh is that it's easy and it forces you to do stuff that you
would not you know would not normally do that's the convenience and that's the service that I want
I don't think that it's the best thing that you could do with your money it's not economical all
right it's not the best you could do for the price I don't agree with this before not to rush
I just want to say that I mean we're not that different Ben we're not that different I hate
being on the other side of this argument I don't like yeah yeah yeah I agree I just wanted to say
that I won and I beat you okay that's fine I have the mind I have the mind of a child is my point
but let's let's move on to uh oh chilling chocolate chilling chocolate has a message for us uh let me
say okay we got two left uh okay and oh shit I'm in the wrong chat I don't want to mean this one up
with a bunch of bullshit okay here we go all right chilling wow us impress us go
hey guys sorry I haven't made a voice mail in a while ever since uh rubber
redacted she killed me and hide the podcast robots sucked out my spine I've been rotting in hell
since uh it turns out being a pc patron is enough to damn your soul for uh eternity uh talking to
mage's dad was fun but I wish that I could watch something other than filler episodes of fairy tale
speaking of which turns out the voice down here will give me a month of crunchy roll
for everyone I can get to patron so uh let me sneak you disgusting normie swine some of the
delicious content you're missing out on from the bonus episodes 17 specifically so go to tiny url
dot com slash pcp voicemail uh no capitals no spaces and uh just drink in or eat oh the beauty
well uh episode nine is starting again so uh see you later wait what was the url what was that
link to I think was also please let me join the teen cp okay well add me on discord and you're in
buddy you're in by the way this is really weird that I'm like letting people envies it's someone
it's the teensy pieces like his pocket you know what you're in you're in just just discord me
wait wait tiny url dot did anyone catch it wait okay I click on this link I think I got it it's this
tiny url dot com slash pcp voicemail delete it delete it oh that's no good uh okay deleting this
okay no what are you talking about it's great uh link in the show notes ladies and gentlemen
go click link in the link in the show notes I got hacked for you delete that and then I'll post it
and then I'll post it better uh okay I got a life hack delete delete that all right I'm deleting it
I'm deleting it all right there we go I mean it's fine I don't want you to talk okay fantastic
okay don't all right yeah everyone it's great go click on that link uh yeah no no it was really
good yum I'm getting hungry if you know what I'm trying to say that no that's a that's a yum brand
if ever I've seen yeah okay uh last voicemail let's get to it we've got uh previously on riddle my
ass batman yes uh oh should I'm waiting for this all week and here we go commence previously on riddle
my ass batman munchie crashed a batman bill through the wall shot batman in the eye batman
gave munchie a stern talking to do the batman's injuries munchie was forced to temporarily assume
the identity of batman munchie best of the riddler was a single word suicide from that he deduced it was
tom oliver the pcp's resident suicide boy now along with ben nate munchie debu and made tom oliver
is safe this just then we regret to inform you that there will be no new pcp rid of my ass batman
this week but for the time and next week we're gonna be a real hunting or I assure you now tune
in next time to find out same pcp time same pcp channel again we're ready for me there will be no
new riddle my ass batman this week this is an outrage this is a fucking outrage this is the only
reason people come to this show and you blow it for us well you know he got more time prepared these
these are getting higher and higher production you know this is this is unacceptable this is at the
he should I'm saying he should have made a clip show episode out of the previous one I mean he
should have made a highlight real yeah that would have been good I'm thinking of it as a clip
show which everyone hates by the way I I haven't been keeping well I kind of forgot whether I was
freed yet am I still in no you're still captive oh no you're over a water full of dick eating
piranhas I believe oh something like that okay wait I'm safe right you're safe you fell in but
you don't have a dick so you were fine well technically you were dropped the dick eating
piranhas but you were safe for yeah that's correct they were harmless to you yeah um so
we have our best scientists figuring out figuring out what it is and the hopes that they can provide
an antidote to the rest of us uh well fuck that's it I'm still waiting on tenterhooks for the next
installment tenterhooks yeah waiting on tent tenterhooks what's a tenterhook I don't fucking know
sounds like a like a blood-borne creature tent tenterhook a hook used to fasten cloth on a drying
frame or tenter so you're waiting on that yes what does that mean beast me but it feels really
good am I right let's ask let's ask mariam webster let's ask mariam webster what does it mean to be
on tenterhooks I think it's similar to like being the edge of your seat it is yes uh okay good because
you're held up by cloth things so you're like gonna fall soon it's like right close to okay all right
similarly on tenterhooks is to be similarly tense as one waits in suspense thanks mariam webster well
thanks webster appreciate that thanks maryweather didn't even get to the comics oh we didn't talk
about oh man we didn't talk about how maryweather tried to get he's given me a whole bunch of life
advice on how to be a successful comics boy like him yeah whatever rfck which is better it's it's
we did talk about an rfck go listen to our 10 hour long pokemon xd stream i'll be x but actually
time i've no doubt oh yes more actually i was more dxing honestly oh that's rough if you if
yeah if you catch my drift i do it's a great game all right that's it are you guys done have you
completed your your quest because i mean as i recall as i recall we're going to you and i
have a certain engagement once you reach the ending of that uh yeah um i'm not looking forward to that
no um no because our team is a nightmare really good really really good yeah they're really great
as long as you have six you'll probably be okay in general they got real great moves and
you know what i mean are you thinking of it that you have to use the exact moves they've
gone in the same levels or something because i figured we could i was i mean i thoughts i don't
know i mean okay if we have to play one of those rules all right all right well we can just okay
we can we can iron out the terms okay we'll do it we'll do something uh no we're all done people
patreon i gotta get out of here slash the procrastinators give it up for how did oblivion
fall do how do you how do you this edit this episode did he make it good because this episode
was terrible so if you made it good then you did it was did he make it good did he make it finally
good at last cp finally good we've been craving it for so long the tall order to put all on oblivion
falls shoulders but one out of apples we did it that's that's one more apple than last time uh
all right patreon.com slash the procrastinators people one dollar you know patreon lounge all that
good stuff be a supporter of our beloved brand and don't let the haters get you down and then five
dollars there might be a large contingent of moms against pcp you know the map crowd we they're
redefining the term map they're making a more positive image these days and uh you know i don't
ever since ever since misanthropony tainted the tainted the phrase indeed they had that negative
association so we had to move past it as a dog whistled i don't know fuck whatever uh yeah so
five dollars bonus episode it's out it's out now should we should we tell them what it is should
we tell them what the bonus episode is we should it's out it's out right now we should tell okay fine
yeah it's quizzes we all took quizzes personality quizzes people whoa go get it on it you'll learn
the deep secrets you'll get to find out very deep secrets about us maybe indeed we get to the heart
of the matter uh the dark spoils so the one of the things that we that we came up across uh if you
want to share if you want to give them a teaser well uh the we uh we finally found wait wait pause
pause hold on we have a dedicated editor now can't we just make them bring back the previews we
used to have when we cared more remember we used to do you know we can do that should we do that
yeah that takes a while is all i'm saying oh well you know what uh this episode won't be at or that
episode won't be edited i think by the time he's editing this so it might not exist yet uh okay
that one's a maybe but in the future we definitely can do those sorts like next episode we could
definitely do that a preview in that one or something it's okay good good thought good point
good point um okay well that being said uh at tpcrasners on twitter for more updates and things
and that's it editor contest in the bag oblivion fall confirmed for brawl yes finally we did it
congratulations and thanks everyone who submitted um we really appreciate everyone
congratulations we appreciate it we're gonna we're gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna put together a little
thing uh to show my appreciation showing off all your hard work and you know thanks again
good man uh great great stuff we had a lot of really talented fans absolutely true and we could
have used most of you and you would have been great so keep it up people hope you used it and
you channel the positive vibes keep making your own shit so good luck everybody and we'll see you
next week
oh
what the hell is wrong with me