Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever and today we've got Hippocrit, are you?
We've got Ben Saint.
I'm a lumberjack and I'm okay.
We've got Lethal Aurora Mage.
I regret to inform you all that I am once again addicted to Animal Crossing New Leaf.
You swore you'd never do it again.
I'm sorry.
I needed my fix.
And we've got Endless Jess.
Endless Jess.
Hey, it's Franklin.
Come into your house.
Come into play.
You ever see that level one mafia grunt as Caillou and the level 100 mafia boss as one punchman?
Was the middle one Charlie Brown?
I guess that would work.
Caillou's so fucking retarded.
Anyway, hey everybody.
Welcome to another episode.
Yeah, fuck that guy.
Today we're talking about Fuck Caillou.
It was the worst child show I ever watched.
I never watched Caillou.
I don't think.
I guess it was for like actual infants.
Yes.
Well, yeah.
It was for actual babies.
Well, the plot lines were frankly patronizing.
I know I have to wipe my butt after I take a shit.
Thank you very much.
I didn't need to be a lower yourself to my level.
I'm glad you brought up that topic.
This is the topic that I want to touch on.
I'm sick of wiping.
I'm done with it.
I hate it.
I hate shitting.
I hate wiping.
It's a fucking nightmare every time.
You know, I have somewhat evolved my handling of that situation.
I'm doing a lot of washing after wiping these days.
I've just upgraded and I think it's better.
There is no after wiping for me.
Something about like I've got the poopiest shits and the slimyist craps.
I'm just never done wiping.
The wiping never stops.
It's a curse.
I can't get off the toilet for hours.
It's like they say, it's like they say, wiping is never, oh fuck, a wipe is never completed.
Only abandoned.
Right.
But it's abandoned and then shown and that's what matters to people.
Cut all of this.
That's the biggest difference.
Take this out.
Hey, speaking of, let's talk about, let's talk about cartoons featuring bald people.
Like Steven, after he, Rebecca snatched his wig off in that finale, is that what you're
talking about?
After Rebecca Sugar made him come out as a skinhead, like she meant to all along, and
become sands.
Yeah, I was going to say come out as sands, have you seen the video?
I've seen the image.
Yeah, I was going to say.
Okay, okay.
You guys ever see a cartoon called Fillmore, exclamation point?
Yeah.
No.
Okay.
No question.
I'm googling it.
I think I saw it like once.
Like one time on some channel, I was, I watched this cartoon called Fillmore and it is about
a kid.
It's about, it's like a high school, it's a high school cartoon, but it's like, it's
like a noir, it's like framed as like a noir detective kind of story.
And I saw like one episode of it ever and I thought that was the coolest thing I've ever
fucking seen.
And then I never saw it again.
I was like, for the rest of my youth, I was like, when, what the fuck was that?
Like when will I ever see Fillmore again?
Like I want to see more of it.
Are they even allowed to put black people on TV?
This is weird, man.
Watch out.
Yeah.
That's you, Ben.
Wainhead.
I didn't say anything about him being black because it totally doesn't matter.
And he doesn't, it's like, you know, I think I was watching some, I watched it.
What are you denying his racial identity now, Ben?
You're in a hot water, son.
I saw some YouTube video.
It was, it was called like, I think it was called how to black.
Oh, I saw that.
Yeah.
It was recommended to me and it was a guy talking about like how to write black characters.
And this, you know, the guy making the video was black himself.
And he said, like, you know, in his opinion, like you don't have to, you know, it's tough
because like, I think some, some of those, some certain like white, guilty type people
would say like, you know, you got, you can't just, you can't just write black characters.
You don't know the black experience, but like, you don't have to.
The story doesn't have to be about them being black.
Like it's okay if it's okay sometimes, maybe even most of the time, if a character being
black or white or whatever doesn't really inform the story much, it doesn't have to
be with the stories about that film or like film or could have been whatever.
He's just, he just looks like Morpheus and it rules.
He does.
He does remind me of Morpheus.
You ever see Wayne Head though?
No.
Wayne Head is like, there was like in the nineties, there was this entire genre of cartoons
that were like, like made by black people specifically for black children.
Like they were like these really ghetto, like urban, like all the characters looked like
really racist.
Like Fat Albert?
Like if a white person had drawn the cartoon, it would be considered racist as hell, but
because they were made by, they were all made by the Wayne's brothers or something, like
every different Wayne's brother had their own shitty cartoon series with like these really...
How many, how many Wayne's brothers are there?
I don't know, like fifty?
Three?
Hundreds.
Okay.
But Wayne Head was like this, like urban, just like weird.
They're breeding.
The whole show was about this kid with a club foot.
God, this character design.
That's the point.
This giant foot.
And that was like, he was like, oh, yeah, yeah, he had like a, he had like, he called it his
big shoe.
Um, I remember that one.
I don't remember what it was called, but yeah, he had like a foot brace because there was
something up with his leg.
Yeah.
And the theme song was like, Wayne Head, Wayne Head, the party's just begun.
And like the theme song actually has a part in it that went, hey, ho, hey.
Like, like...
Alright.
Okay.
So this is the realism of the head and foot exclusively.
It's pretty freakish.
You ever notice how black people make art that's like really racist against black people
and don't seem to notice that they're, that they're being racist against themselves?
Well, but that's not racist then.
Yeah.
Well, for them, it's just like, it's like, you know, isn't it funny how people do this?
You know?
Which like, you know, everyone does that.
But you know, if you're white...
I'll just, I'll just...
Listen, listen, if you're white and you're watching a cartoon by a black person that's
about like black kids living in...
It's already racist right there.
No, shit.
They're like living in the, living in the streets or whatever, not like homeless, but you know
what I mean.
You might, you look at that and be like, huh, wow, this is, this is, this is weird in what
it says about black people.
But like, you know, this is like, there's, you know, they're just writing about people
they know, writing about their, their life experience.
I don't know if it makes me racist.
I hope it doesn't, but I hated all of these black people cartoons.
Like they're just...
They were all like the proud family.
The proud family is a fucking disgrace.
I did not enjoy that show.
No, I did not.
The worst thing ever happened to the sequel was pretty decent.
You know, I wasn't, I wasn't particularly into the proud family either.
The whole, like the, like the whole proud family is like, there's like the dad and like the
grandma is like super abusive to the dad.
And it's played for the last cause she's like, you know, she's sugar mama.
She's like, it's, it's cool.
She's like a sassy black lady, but she's just like an abusive monster who like has
ruined the dad, his entire life by treating him like garbage and continues to treat him
like garbage and emasculate him daily, even as a man in charge of his own family.
She's the breadwinner.
She's the, the guy.
I hate, I hate sugar mama.
I want her to fucking die.
I want her to just, I want it.
I want, I always want an episode where she succumbed to dementia and ended up in a hospice
and died slowly.
And all of her family was around her and the last person in the room with her as she was
dying was Oscar.
I think his name was, was, was the son.
And he's just like Oscar Langley.
And like just as she's about to die, he's like, I don't forgive you.
And she just, she flat lines and that's it.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I think I would have enjoyed that as well.
He did get abused, but I think they were trying to paint him.
I mean, as they always do, like he was a fuck up, like everyone around was trying to help
him and he just couldn't take their good advice and just was a fool through and through.
Was the proud family dad a fuck up?
Yeah.
He was like, he remember he was an inventor, but like he didn't make any money to support
the family.
What?
He was all the, the mom who was like a newscaster.
Wait, he's an inventor?
No.
Stu Pickles is an inventor.
Was he like a tinkerer?
Yeah.
Stu Pickles is the inventor.
I was thinking like, is he, is he like Stu Pickles again?
Okay.
I might have been confusing that.
There's no way.
I don't, I don't remember what he was or did.
Yeah.
I don't know these American cartoons.
Stu Pickles, now there was a cartoon dad.
I know that.
He was up, he was up at two in the morning making chocolate pudding.
That's, you're not wrong.
Yeah.
Let's go back to criticizing Caillou and these nice white families that I feel comfortable
talking to him about.
The only media I saw with Caillou is like with those go anime atrocities.
Yeah.
Have you seen, have you seen Giles theme goes with anything Stu makes chocolate pudding?
Well, of course.
Of course.
Da da da da da da.
Stairs, stairs.
That's some time with the music.
That's good stuff.
Classics.
But hey, okay.
Remember that episode of Rugrats where there was literally a time machine?
Is that Sprues?
Yeah.
I'm sure it was an imagination.
Boo Boo Rooms.
No, they go to the toy store and one of the, the brand new hot toy that all the kids
want is a literal fucking time machine.
Okay.
That's very cool.
You know what I realized is like a-
Wait is it actual or did they just imagine-
They they they activate an evil toy gorilla that's chasing them around and the way that they defeat it is they lure it into the time machine and send it back and
Back in time to fucking George Washington crossing the Delaware River
tape
I liked it that much imagine. I'm glad it's not just a fever dream. No, it's real
Okay, hang on. Are you sure that the that the the actual narrative was not that there was a
Playtime machine that was really fun to like pretend you were time-traveling
No, you literally see the gorilla materialize on the river as George Washington is crossing with his troops and they're like
What's that pretend? I don't think the kids were making believe
One-year-old kids making believe about George Washington in the Revolutionary War
Does it like happen where like a painting changes and not like there's a gorilla in the in the
One of the founding fathers gorilla
No twilight zone ending twilight zone ending they get the toy they go to the cash register and stew's like here
You go keep the change hands him a one dollar bill and it's
That would have been they should have gone for it. We should have committed to the bed
Everybody welcome to the cartoon podcast where the reason cartoons are dying. Yeah, that's true
Speaking of dying cartoons
Like I could have sort was a fever dream for like I don't know like ten years of my life or something
And when I was little and I was watching pop-up girls
I saw this episode once and only once and I don't know why they stopped airing it
But like it was something about like but a cup of bullying some kid that kept eating glue
I think and then he turned into a giant glue monster and then she had to
Yeah, well, why did she apologize? She was doing the right thing by bullying this because he was stronger than her now and he could be
Her up. Yes
He was a giant glue. So she actually yeah, you know, I think I do remember that
Um, I don't know that I watched a lot of power
But yeah, like that I only saw it once on TV and I have no clue why they never aired it again
Was it was it like banned like the like the gnome episode? Maybe it was encouraging kids see glue
Maybe people complained maybe oh man, okay
What we need is a be careful who you make fun of in high school meme of like nerd kid is a powerpuff girl and then giant glue monster
That's what she learns. That's a good lesson to prevent future school shootings. That's a big reason why well
We really need we need these these white boys to get laid. That's what we need
We need heroic women out there who are willing to put out to save our children. That's the number one thing that'll do it
Why are my words why I volunteer I volunteer to be one of those women
To be one of those women. That's right. Why didn't the powerpuff girls just fuck all the other kids?
Think of all yeah, they were missing the greatest superpower of all heightened sexuality an ounce of prevention is a pound of cure
We've all learned a lot here today. Thanks for joining us everyone on the procrastinating cartoon cast
Okay, Steven Universe. Let's talk about it. There was there was the new special. I think everybody here watched it
I have not seen the new ones, but I don't care about spoilers if you want to
A blot black cartoonist just putting their own worst stereotypes and cartoons this black character amethyst is just such a
disgusting
Hittiest freak. He's I don't know where I'm going with that. She's even doing things
These episodes anyway amethyst is growing. No, I'm like amethyst a lot. Oh, I was just I was just I it was black people
I was making fun of not amethyst. Oh, okay. That's fine. Yeah, that's good
So so there was a whatever a couple of episodes and a big special like a 45 minute finale episode
Season some backster did the last shot with the I knew it. I yeah, I was yes
Disney guy hell happened in this part it got all good, you know, okay
What was interesting about that? So there's a moment at the at the emotional climax of this scene a lot of crazy
Shits happening with a confrontation with white diamonds going down and all that stuff
And all of a sudden the animation goes from piece of shit flash garbage animation. It's not flash
unbelievably beautiful
like fluid Disney level Disney movie animation
They're
Proportions and sizes wouldn't change so drastically. I don't I guess that's true
I have no idea what I'm fucking talking about
But I do know that this got super fluid. No, I liked it a lot
but I was watching this with Michelle and
She actually kind of hated it because it was such a jarring transition from what Steven universe normally looks like
That you said like it really just threw out of it. She wasn't able to absorb the emotions of the scene
You know itself I really liked it
But yeah as a whole it was quite a jarring jump like I immediately saw the shift in animation
It was kind of weird. It took me out of the experience. Yeah, it does make you think of like
Okay, this is the part where the people making the cartoon really want to blow their load and make me feel something. Yes. Yeah
Like it I like the way James Baxter was used in adventure time because it's just he animates a horse because he's good at that
And it's a silly horse and you wouldn't even tell me who James Baxter is though because I don't know
I didn't look into him, but he's a guy who has worked for Disney's done a lot of like really good
animation for Disney and
recently oh
You know the bit in the Gravity Falls opening where Mabel is rubbing her cheek on the pig and it's really smooth
That's him. Yeah, the bit where
Scar and is like a fighting off with Simba at the end of the Lion King with it like a 360
Shot where he's like no scope around him. Three six. There's sixty no scope
Yeah, that was him dude. Yeah, and and he's like a
What's the the punchback of Notre Dame?
He's done a bunch of he does a lot of like really
Impressively animated motion scenes like yeah, the reason he did the thing with the
The white diamond in 3d like whoo like you just drew that because you can because he's good at that
What if right thinking thinking about scar a 360 no scoping Simba
Think what if like what if like voice actors, right?
Like like Jeremy iron like for example Jeremy irons just starts a twitch channel and just starts like streaming games as
Scar, but he's just like do that. I think yeah
Like not actual voice actors, but I kept being recommended like a few years ago
Like by a person who kept doing Fluttershy voice and pretending to be Fluttershy and just playing games
I've seen that the the the scout voice actor for TF2 has done that. Oh, yeah, that's cool
It's like the evolution of like an ask blog or something instead of like drawing this character
You're just are peeing him on on twitch
I'm not sure if he's streamed or recorded, but I heard like the voice actor for
One of the overwatch characters the high noon one. Oh, what's what's it the McCree? Yeah McCree McCree
Yeah, he he he would troll a fellow players and would just scream high noon in voice chat
So we play that was like just they'd be like oh shit. He's using his ult, but no it was in fact a ruse
Respect to them a lot more before I knew that he also plays the game
Yeah, let me tell me to maybe he only plays it to troll people who knows
So, okay, let's talk about the the the ramifications of this this Steven universe special
Because the big thing I saw a lot of people talking about it and I feel this to a degree as well is like
What is there even left to talk about now that this is done?
I'll just be able this is spoilers. So if you don't want to know fair enough skip ahead or whatever
It's done white diamond is redeemed. She's on our team now
Here's the most thing what I think because I'm way behind. I'm totally behind
Yeah, the last thing I saw was the white diamond reveal. Yeah, okay, fair enough. I mean that looks good still
So cool looking the thing with like all of Steven universe is like combat is part of it
But Steven is like as a person is always like I don't fight
Don't do it like a pink diamond would fight
She had a war going as like rose quartz, but Steven's like
Never and he has a shield and it's like, okay, so this is not really about like solving problems with violence
um
And I guess I guess the thing that happens next
after like white diamond is redeemed kind of or definitely is uh like
Changing home world like I think instead of having the climax be a slug fest
Which would go against like the the point of Steven as a character
It would be the finale would be you know changing the universe for the better making home world better
You know doing all this stuff because all they've done really is they've they've uh
Like what do they do? They got the gems that were like fucked up and they healed them
And then that's it
The cluster yeah, they've got to do something about the cluster
Or like turn it into a big giant guy
um me and byter joked that like
Because I heard that there might be a uh six season and we were like well
What are they gonna do because everything's so wrapped up?
And so we joked that like the whole six season is just just them separating and piecing back together the cluster
Every episode is basically them
And yes, it's minecraft it's minecraft you go in there with a little pickaxe you chunk chunk a bit off turn it into a guy
Keep going. Please fact check me people
But I believe what I heard was that we know there's a movie coming in I think September of this year
And I believe that there's also a sixth season. I that that's what I was
Yeah, that's the rumors I've heard, but I'm not sure if it's true
I don't know. I don't know if there's any like confirmation of anything other than the movie. Okay. Okay. The movie's for sure though
So let me just say my thoughts in general which are
That so I I never expected like I mean would I have liked a little more fighting? Sure never hurts
But I was satisfied with what we saw we finally saw I think it was was it obsidian the fusion of all of the
Obsidian was was it final we saw the four fused?
Dude, did you notice did you notice obsidian was the temple?
Yeah, I used the temple that was I was expecting it to be the temple because I I knew the moment stupid
I I heard that temple is like oh it has to be I'd heard that theorized on like way back like you remember like season one
Damn, I guess everyone was ahead ahead of the curve and I was the only one who was excited about that
I know I I liked it a lot too. I thought it was really good and I liked her coloring
That way though that was yeah black with lava under it and all that dude's stuff with a big old sword
That was it was dope. It looked really cool and I was very happy with it
It doesn't get to do very much, but you know that that's okay
And and like like we were saying the like emotional climax or the climax wasn't a big fight
It was literally Steven like talking to white diamond and convincing her to be a good boy
But but beyond that, um, I mean it was it was convincing white diamond that whatever like people are imperfect. Nobody's perfect
So you shouldn't be so
Strict on everyone like you have to accept people's imperfections like okay fair enough whatever
Yeah rarity if you just you just opened your heart a little bit you let people into your your worlds
We can help bear your burden. You don't have to be perfect all the time
Yes, and that was a good that was fine. That was fine. I have some today. I learned that i'm steven
Well, let's just let's before we get to that. Let's just say that so when when white diamond she she she fucking kills everybody else
It's only uh, steven left. She fucking pulls the diamond out of his stomach
She pulls it. She rips it the fuck out and he's gotten up and there's blood everywhere deeply horrific
He was freaking out on dying
Out after she pulled it out. It was uh, it was fucking that was that was the um, okay
Can I can I say that i'm kind of disappointed with corny or rather how she was uh
useless
I'm over conny man
I was I was hoping when she entered the temple and every and and all the gems were getting zapped of their color and stuff
And it was like oh well conny's a human she won't get that maybe she could do something
And no she immediately gets caught like she has like a small battle, but that does nothing and then gets caught
It's like well, what's the point of you being here?
Yeah, that was a weird build up or nothing to happen like the whole conny thing like oh, it's cool
That steven confused with her and he becomes tall then the sword looks the right size
And the and the shield is in his other hand and he rides line or she
Schlier schlay or schler rides lion
And it's like oh the coolest like that's the final battle mode, but conny was just there
And she didn't do that
I don't know why I kind of built her up. It's like oh she learned how to fight and and stuff. Well, what's the
Okay, okay. Let me just get into my point here. Okay, so everything about steven universe every single conflict has been predicated on
The fact that they're what there's okay
What why do people fight in the real world people fight in the real world because they want things from each other
And like they can't just get it given to them instantly
They have to take it by force and they like they can't come to a compromise or they just don't care to
That's why people fight in the real world at all. So okay. Why are they fighting in steven universe?
They're fighting because like white diamond insists that like humans are shitty. I don't care about them like they're worthless
Gem life is good. We're going to spread gem life and whoever gets in our way including humans
Like we will fuck them up including like the you know the the crystal gems who fought back
They had to fucking destroy them because they were getting in their way. So this all makes sense
um
As to why why they're doing it. They don't recognize like the importance of the fucking differences of what makes them special
So when so white diamond is convinced finally that that is not the case by the big emotional climax
Where she rips out the gem from steven and the gem itself of pink diamond like she was expecting to just become actually
With me and michelle were thing was that oh now we're going to get steven and rose quartz. She's not even dead
She's just coming back. This is going to suck
But no the the the pink diamond itself had been changed by the existence of steven
We thought she was back
But uh it like so pink diamond really is permanently gone even having to remove the gem from steven
And it like its nature has been changed and now it's like it's a weird pink steven thing
And then it refuses with his body. It's a big emotional thing. Yay. I'm myself again. Okay, that's fine
So so what I just want to cut in just before you get to that that bit. Why why was uh pink steven the diamond
Had no emotion at all like the other diamonds have emotion. I don't really understand what that means
Well, I mean, okay, so that was a blank face pink steven
I mean, I mean was it really with no emotion because it yelled really loud that one time that seemed like something was going on with it
Uh, I just think it was a weird like
It was it was a weird like
Like choice to have it be so
Because like what else are you supposed to take away from that other than he has no emotion?
No, no, I think it was just sort of a shorthand to say it to show that it's incomplete without steven
Like two two halves of the same thing
And that's why when steven got happy. So did the pink steven got happy. They all got in sync
Yeah, I think I think that's right brain left brain. I think uh
The episode was kind of shit on the whole. Yeah, the more I think about it
um, because uh
Like a lot of a lot of the the dialogue and ideas in this episode seemed like like weirdly on the nose even for steven universe
like
It felt like like all the criticism
That people have given the show like how it like shoves like it's lgbt thing down people's throats
it it felt like
They heard the criticism and then doubled down on all of it
For this well, there's no way that we change that shit. That's what the show. No, I know they're not going to change it
And I've never really had a problem with it. I've been a stalwart steven universe defender
But some of the dialogue in this episode was like excruciatingly on the nose
Like when they go she prefers to be called steven now and it's like just shut off. Yeah, I know top
And there was a bunch and like they're like the part we're fucking the
The steven and garnet fusion
Sunstone, I think like breaks the fourth wall
Looks at the camera and says remember kids if you are dealing with a bully tell an adult
What the fuck was that that was horrible?
I don't I couldn't believe what I was seeing. I could character
It was a joke, but I don't get the joke like I really don't I can't understand what the joke is that literally that literally happened
What steven fused with garnet and made a new gem sunstone
Sunstone was like oh, she's wacky and like she says her and then she goes to the camera. She breaks the fourth wall
So like oh her joke is that she's
She's dead. She she breaks the fourth wall
And she says she says after school
I mean, I guess like commercial if they hit. Oh my god. Sunstone is fucking awesome
It looks great, but god damn like if they had done that bit if they had done that bit twice
Then I would have accepted it like okay. It's like her thing. Maybe it's because
Sapphire is in there somewhere. She's like aware of things
But like because they only did it once it was so insanely jarring and weird
Like she's just giving this like they're literally fighting first of all
And then in the middle of a of the fight like she's going. I'm gonna beat you up
I'm gonna beat up white diamond and then looks at the camera and goes but kids if you have a bully tell an adult
And like I wanted to shit. I just wanted to empty my bowels
in an instant
and uh this whole like arc of like
Of steven being there and being forced into the role of pink diamond
like
Like again, everyone is criticized to show a lot for a long time and I've always defended it
But this arc like right when he gets in the pink diamond outfit. That was the moment where I finally went
This is gay
This is gay. It's like he's just like he's in this like really to to with his midriff exposed for like four
entire episodes and like I'm not
Like I'm not being close-minded. I'm not offended by it. I don't know. I didn't mind that at all
It's just so fucking lame. I mean, I'm still looking at the wiki. I can't fucking believe how cool sunstone is
It's awesome. All right
You know, we're fucking angry
That thing with sunstone when she looked at the camera was
particularly like annoying
Uh, I was totally blind and that was just like oh just that was like them just like planting a sign like editing
Like a still image onto the middle of the episode and it wasn't in character wasn't anything
It's just like by the way, like we support children not being bullied
Just please call this number in the real world
It just doesn't make sense because sunstone isn't is way smaller than this giant robot. She's not bullying the giant robot
I don't understand what is yeah, but but that thing was the bully right like that thing was bullying them
Like the whole like I just don't get like why this episode like as the finale was so like weirdly
On the nose and in your face and like obnoxiously like
um
It felt like they were not subtle at all ticking books is like oh, we haven't seen Steven and pearl fuse got to do that
Steven that's true. They were trying to like really
Cramming all the different themes of the show all at once in this episode and throw them at you with no subtlety to them at all
like um
The part where it's just the the the finale fan service
Yeah, yeah, but like
The best part of Steven universe is like
Getting to know the care like really getting into them like I think like one of the best episodes is
Mr. Greg
where
You like
Get an idea of like any pearl episode is great because like she's kind of the most rich character, I think
But like delving into like her insecurities and stuff
But in this episode there was a moment where
White diamonds starts running down the crystal gems and she just like flat out says
Uh, your flaw garnet is that you're fucking
Retarded and your flaw pearl is that you're insecure and your flaw amethyst. No
Your flaw amethyst is you're insecure and your flaw pearl is that you're obsessed and it's like
It was better when you like stating yeah, like the the characters seem so much more three-dimensional when you
Like are seeing that instead of like it's really weird for a character
To just like it's kind of like another break in the fourth wall thing almost where the characters just yeah
This is who you are as a character pearl and this is who you are as a character garnet and this is why you
Gathered yet. These are the flaws
How does white diamond even know that?
Yeah, that's also a good. Did she say that did she did she say she said she she said like
As she was zapping them and turning them gray like oh, you're all flawed
You know and she said like the word obsessed to pearl and insecure
I forget what she said to garnet, but was was did we was it confirmed that pearl was white diamonds pearl?
That's still not confirmed and it's infuriating. Yes. Just confirm it for me god damn it. Well, well white diamond would have met pearl
Plausibly, but she wouldn't know anything about amethyst, right?
Well
Because she kind of brain washes them
I think she has some sort of way of getting into their minds and knowing
That's it's it's revealed that
um white diamonds pearl
is pink diamonds pearl
Because she turns pink at the right
so
Like and and there was that line in an episode a long time ago where jasper says something about you being a defective pearl
My theory is that our pearl
Like at some point pink diamond fucked up and pissed off white diamond
So white diamond took pink pearls pearl
And said this is my white pearl now and then like
Pawn and like gave pink diamond like a crappier like an off-color
Defective pearl which is why our pearl is not pink as she like logically should be she's just pearl colored
That's so I think that our pearl was a replacement pearl for pink diamond after losing her original pearl
to white diamond. Yeah, most likely
All I'm saying is if it is in fact revealed as I personally suspect that our pearl just was straight up white diamonds pearl
Although like are there more than four pearls in the universe? I would imagine so, right?
Um, but anyway, like assuming that our pearl was white diamonds pearl
There are many many many times when it would have been relevant for for our white ish pearl to say by the way guys
I was white diamonds pearl. I have some information about her
I can like tell you some info on her, but she has not done that which is weird if she is in fact her pearl
I don't think I don't think I don't think she was white diamonds pearl
I think she was just like a literally a defective off-color. Yeah, like a spare piece of shit
Okay, I'll just say for the record. She would have been destroyed because there's no tall there's zero
Zero tolerance. I guess that's also true. That's true. That's well. Never mind. It makes no sense. It's stupid then
I'll point out just for the record that so every pearl has their pearl on the same place on their body as their
Corresponding diamond and white pearl or our pearl does in fact have a forehead pearl just like white diamond as a forehead diamond
So it seems well likely that they are in sync, but again not confirmed yet
Maybe she was uh cursed to not be able to say anything
Like I mean that is established that that is a thing that happens. So one thing about the episode that I did really appreciate
Is that a pearl pearl our pearl the real pearl
Has now permanent cool jacket
That's true big old shoulders
Yeah, so now she now she can dress up now. She can drive around and fuck that less and I like that because
Finally, I like that because you know every time that they regenerate they their outfits do change
But this is the first time that it's looked like to me or seemed like
The physical change is like a tangible manifestation of actual character development because that episode where she wore the jacket
Was an episode where she actually developed as a character. So now that she has a jacket as part of her
Permanent look. It feels like sick
Is the jacket is cool. Peridot has prominent glasses that she doesn't deserve and dead
And also and also a fucking
Peridot has come in a glasses. Well, that's what I'm saying. That's she's the one she's the one and garnet they both
Oh
Garden has like Simone glasses, I guess
And uh and uh fucking lapis has like a lad pants now
for some reason
God damn it lapis. You looked way better before go back to your dress. What what what what what's the deal with lapis
What the heck is she and why lapis is the worst character in the show
She's so she's so strange and I don't I still don't really understand who she is
Agreed me too. And that's a problem
I kind of like her lapis, but that's the thing is I can't describe why
It's like she vaguely depressed and confusing. I wanted to like her. She looked she looked really cool
I I was I was on board like when I first saw her I was like oh lapis. Oh cool
Uh, it was just sad. Nope. Nobody else on the show is sad. I'm into it
She was just written like a bit different a few too many times
I don't even feel like lapis should be a crystal gem
I just feel like because she was a character design that like had been in the show. They're like, we got one
Let's bring her into this because like I felt like she was just a one-off
Like side character, but then she gets all wrapped up and
She's so weirdly outside the the circle of what I consider the real crystal gems
Which includes paradox, but it does not include lapis and it does not include bismuth either
I don't like that character. No, it does not. I don't she should go away. Also guys, did you
When they all fuse into like obsidian or whatever
Notably, they just are like, we're let's just not use with bismuth. Let's like she we don't want her like mixed up in our
Like obsidian thing. Why why didn't they do it?
You know when I I looked up obsidian and like she she's like a lava creature and she like forges her greats
Out of like the lava in her third mouth, which is fucking awesome. So I saw that I assumed that bismuth was in there, but no
No, no, no, they just
You would think that would be bismuth's bag
I mean, maybe there's an easy answer to this but like like so the temple has like five gems or whatever for the five crystal gems, you know,
whatever
diamond rose quartz
Amethyst a garnet who is two gems and then pearl like how can bismuth didn't have a room?
What's up with that? She was there. Did she maybe they built that up before they made it? Yeah, afterward. Yeah. Yeah, I guess that's fair
I guess that's fair. Okay. Well whatever
Is the worst
Yeah, she sucks
We all agree on it. I just don't like it
The thing with bismuth
Is that like I was talking about this with some some art people and they were like really annoyed about how
Boring and terrible her character design is when the gem bismuth is the coolest looking gem in the world
Yeah, like she's just got sort of like kind of colorful dreadlocks
And it should be it should be like a wild like super rainbow
Cool like angular hair and it's just some lady with dreadlocks
And I don't know she's like the most bloodthirsty of them all but she doesn't like do anything with that
She's kind of boring and she's fat
Yeah
I don't care for it
Yeah, I guess so were those uh one of those really good designs
Like at the end when when all those gems are getting reformed so many cool little designs are like weirdly vaguely humanoid
Are just really neat
That was one of the best parts of the show just watching them all being uh reformed and being able to guess like oh
What gem do you think that one might be?
Hey, do you remember the the chip sky from the very first episode the one that likes
Yep centipede man centipede
It's like the cutest one. I loved her
She's I do like I do like her and then jasper was there. I forgot that jasper was bubbled and then there she is
Bubbled and fucked up permanently uh with troll horns. They're they're saying she's a troll now you guys
Oh no
Yeah, they got they got back the friends that they mentioned like I don't remember what the names were but like they mentioned those friends
And they were like, oh no, they're gone. They're corrupted and they got them back and bismuth pounced. You know, okay
You know what I'd like to see I'd like to see all right
This maybe this has nothing to do with anything
But imagine off on homeworld they got like babies
But they're coal so like coal babies and you crush them into different gems. That's how they make them
You put a baby in the crushing machine. It comes out
Let
Okay, on the subject of saving all the corrupted gems at the end. Let's talk about like consequences
For white diamonds genocidal campaign throughout the stars that the other diamonds that by the way, nobody even cares about like blue diamond and yellow diamond
absolutely
Uh participants in these genocide crusades. Um, let's okay. What have they done as part of their galactic uh conquering empire
They have 100 destroyed planets wiped out populations
Mind all the resources in like an expunged all life plant or otherwise from planets
And we can only speculate as to how many planets this was done to many many systems many many planets. Um
Okay, yellow did say like thousands didn't she thousands? Yeah, I think so
I'm not I'm not too sure but yeah, she mentions a large
And now so big dick Steven slams his cock on the table in front of white diamond and says
It ain't gonna suck itself
Stop being evil. You're good now and white diamond says okay
And whatever she learns that it's okay to be flawed. I guess that means, you know
I look I get the whole I get what they're trying to say socially in the in the meta text of that message
What I don't understand is how that's in any way a sufficient apology
For the genocides that white diamond and her and her cabal have committed across the universe
And how it's just okay for them to literally come to earth and say like hey guys, we're here. We're good now
How is that?
Acceptable. There are some crimes that you cannot be forgiven for and I think they've crossed the threshold
If they're doing more episodes that might be addressed
Okay, let let me finish one point though on this and it's it's just that okay. I am I do not believe in like, uh, like
What's the word?
Like repudiation justice like like punishment justice
If someone has if you've got a thief and he steals a loaf of bread and like okay, maybe the punishment for that is chop
Off his hand. Okay, like that's not gonna help anybody if you could instead
Explain to this guy why what he did was wrong and he could make it up to the person he stole from
And like he doesn't need to do any jail time or even be punished at all
He just needs to sincerely change his behavior like that's obviously what we want
So if white diamond has been like redeemed then like okay
I'm willing to accept that like maybe it's not even doesn't even make sense to punish white diamond for this
But they don't talk about that what I think is that literally white diamond is too important to jail
Because she and it's it's literally only her political and actual physical
Might that prevents us from even thinking like oh this person should be in jail
Just like we do with big bankers in the real world
We're like obviously, you know, it's fine that they're not in jail. They're important
Like a president just can commit war crimes because like I don't know. He's the president. That's fine. And uh, I just feel like we're using some weird
Systems to judge these guys
Shouldn't we be more mad shouldn't the characters be more mad about what's going on?
um any comments here, I don't know I
What on the one hand? Yes, they should be more mad. I guess but I think they're just more relieved that
They they have stopped her from destroying everything and so they're just getting caught up in like
Ah victory, you know, we did it. We've solved the problem for now
And then you know, they they can sit on the beach with a ukulele and play a little little song
Like for one second
That's fair, but okay, there's a couple of issues still at play them. Okay, it's
So what we are led to believe about white diamonds redemption
Is that it was that white diamond was a perfectionist and she like okay
She was literally like a bigot against like uh, and I understand what all this represents the real world like okay
White diamond thinks that fusing is icky. Why does white diamond think that fusing is icky? I don't know tradition
It's it's new and different and weird. It's the purity. It's not pure or something like oh, okay
Yeah, it relates to off color something like okay, that's fine like obviously that's just something that should go away
There's nothing really wrong about that
Like uh, I'm not someone in the real world who thinks that all traditions are necessarily worthless
But I'm happy to examine any of them and you know toss out the shit and keep only the good stuff
So this is one that doesn't seem to make a lot of fucking sense
And you're literally way more powerful if you fuse anyway, so wake up white diamond. Stop limiting yourself
I was almost hoping to see a blue and yellow diamond fusion
I wanted to see stuff like that
Dude, they gotta like it's okay that they've got a gay son now
But they're gonna have to work up to actually trying any gayness out themselves
What if all four of them fuse and they become big diamond?
Big diamond big big big big diamond
Um, okay, okay, so that's all that's all fine. I get what they're trying to say
But here's the thing and this is okay. This this is a moral for babies and like okay. That's fine
A galactic genocider with a big diamond on his head when you've got a galactic genocider
Most people who commit galactic genocide
Are not they didn't just like fall into this position. We all know one
Okay, all right
Like I'm trying to really take the story and give it all the credit that it's due like okay
Why was hitler like a bad man?
Uh, probably things like he was he was poisoned uh into thinking that like the world was persecuting the german people
After their experiences after world war one like he had had I think personal run-ins with jews that made him hate them
And make them think they'd be a great scapegoat. Okay, like fine
So he he had like some baggage that made him an evil guy understandable
Like what makes white diamond like an evil person uh one she like wasn't accepting of like new thoughts and
You know what people wanted to do with their lives
Um, but also let's not forget the fact that homeworld is literally falling apart
We we see homeworld and it's like being destroyed
I was kind of under the impression. Okay. This is this is how you write steven universe in like a like
I'm not even saying it's better, but like a
A more realistic thing
It's a thing where like what what I was hoping white diamond would argue and this didn't happen at all was like, okay
I'm white diamond the reason that I'm so strict in everyone is because homeworld is literally falling apart
Like our society is crumbling right now
The way that I maintain structure and order for like all my billions and trillions of like children that are like my
Under my command and like they're my responsibility is I impose these rigid social structures
To like keep things in line so that things don't like spiral off like they did when I gave pink diamond too much leeway
And it caused that whole crystal gem shit and then we had to go mop up that
Like people don't just become a dictator for like no reason they do it because they
Generally either think that it's for the best whether they're right or wrong
Or like they they just crave power and they find whatever way they can get it
If white diamond just crave power she would be evil and they would like have to fight her
So obviously they weren't going to do that
so
Like I just think it would have been way more
interesting of a of a story if they deal with what like actual dictators do
And it's a thing where like she like this is just the way that she
Controls her society and makes sure that I don't know it runs fucking smoothly
But like that and and then it would be harder to convince her
But no, it's just that oh, I just like I have just this purity thing
Like oh like but then she sees oh wait, I have emotions sometimes too. Even I'm not perfect
Maybe I can allow these people to be different
Well, I I I'm wondering about that because like they blue and yellow we're talking about you know
Oh, do you remember white diamond when we used to have fun picnics and we were all happy friends and like
They didn't necessarily mention a thing that changed
That's like I feel like there is a thing that would have changed like oh
And then the event happened
But we don't speak of that event was was the pink diamond
Well pink diamonds quote-unquote death or like the crystal gem rebellion
I like because they say that before pink left like they used to have fun together
And it's that's the only notable event like in gem history that we're aware of so it's kind of a guess
But it seems fairly reasonable. I think
Um that like something about pink diamond leaving and like quote-unquote
Well, I guess being murdered and like gems betraying them in their eyes. Anyway, maybe it just made white diamond think of like
Maybe this plays into what I was saying it like ah when I give them too much freedom bad things happen
So let's fucking you know, even tighter than before it could be that or it could just be the like
White kept pink around and didn't let her go on
Uh, you know taking over a planet missions
um
Because she liked having her around and when she was gone. She just sort of well, it's it's weird
We just don't know enough about white diamond
I'm imagining that they were all younger and like white diamond was the eldest and so she took up the mantle of being perfect
So that she could set a good example
There was like a line or two. I don't remember what the lines were but it was
The white diamond said and because of that I assumed for a split second that like
Pink diamond and maybe the other diamonds other color diamonds are kind of like parts of white diamond that got separated from white diamond
So she could be perfect
Let's talk about that because that was a little confusing and I was also wondering about that white diamond does say that like
She doesn't say things like literally she says that like blue diamond yellow
Like are part of her and that pink is also part of her. I think that was more metaphorical
In the sense of like they are aspects of myself
Like emotionally, but I like like whatever blue is like sad and I white could be sad
But I like control that in myself yellow is I don't I don't even know what you're angry
Angry and I you know repress that in myself. I'm just I'm calm all the time
And then and then like the thing that happens to me
Isn't yellow diamond isn't yellow diamond all about having no emotions like
No, she's actually pretty
Well, okay, okay
Yeah, but remember there was that episode with peridot
We're like she like she loves yellow diamond
But then she talks to yellow diamond and she sees that yellow diamond isn't as like perfect
Like she sees yellow diamond get mad on the communicator and she's like, huh?
She's not as cool as I thought she was she's not perfectly logical after all
Well, I guess I well white diamond does attempt to make everybody like logical and not
Overly emotional I guess but I suppose yellow attempts to do that
But you know isn't as good as uh as white diamond yellow is trying to follow white
Orders to the tea, you know, she's she did say like I I did everything and did everything perfectly in your name because you requested it
So she's sort of like trying to be like white diamond, but she's obviously not why I'm I'm still wondering
We this has not been addressed or even close to answered. Where did the diamonds come from?
What is the origin of the gem civilization to begin with the coal babies they started as the coal babies you get crushed by
um, you know, I don't even I don't even really minecraft steve
and his and his galactic
Craft and bench. Well, I don't even need like a real answer
The only reason I ask is because I literally want to know more about white diamonds backstory as a character
Like that's why I'm asking not because I I need all the lore all the fucking time
But like uh, so so in in in various things up to this point at the end of the special
We see a preview for the movie and there appears to be a red gem
Like rotating and and people theorize. Maybe that's red diamond
Like maybe this person is the one even above white diamond. Maybe this person is the real origin of everything
Or maybe it's just a split off diamond all the way or maybe they're not a diamond at all. I mean, who knows who knows
Um, could be anything could be diamonds all the way up
diamonds all the way down
And uh, like so so I guess I'm just gonna say that so so far I'm not really uh
It's not that I'm not satisfied with the story. It's just that oh
I have unfortunately recognized that this story's moral is just something that I kind of already know
And isn't really for my age demographic and that's fine. It's just unfortunate. So it's not that it's like bad
It's just the the thing I'm most interested in they don't really want to touch on and that's okay
It's just a different story. I guess then from what I want
But maybe with the movie and this possible next season there will be some of that because because just to be clear
Steven universe is actually like the only show that I go back to and just watch episodes from randomly
Because I just really enjoy the atmosphere and those queers can make a goddamn show when they put their mind to it
And make a comfy-ass atmosphere and I really like it
Uh, so this is not I'm not even trying to be that critical of the show
It's just when it when it comes to like intergalactic conflict and like the origin
Of like why civilizations act the way they do that's when my star fleet senses start to tingle and I get a little excited
Who would have thought that this show that I value so much for its comfy down-to-earth atmosphere would would would
Stumble out of the gate when it comes to intergalactic politics
And war crimes. Well, I mean that's the time when like, you know, they can expand the scope a little of that choose
And they chose not to and that's okay
But yeah, yeah, that's it. That's all I got. I want to fuck pearl
I want to check out her pants. I want her to regenerate with no pants on. I want to fuck her
It's me the best character in the show the guy who fucks him
That's my name. I guess that's the guy who fucks him
Greg's my Greg's my name, but the guy who fucks him is my middle name
Fuck a mom the pussy. I think we've confirmed that Greg literally did just come on her gem
And it butted off into some kind of steven growth. I think that's the most disgusting thing I've ever heard
There can be no other
Do you see like a do you see like a like a zoom down like a house like a house?
Kind of like style like zoom in by into the body biological close-up and you see his no absolutely not
Okay, just one other solution could there be nothing nothing
Um, I guess that's it. I mean so september's the movie. Uh, I don't know
I there was actually some pretty mixed feelings here on how things are going. Um
Yeah, I don't know. I I still like steven universe a lot and I'm looking forward to more
Um, I should probably catch up. I want to see more white diamonds. I want to see sunstone
Cool-looking. Yeah, and she got some great animation and uh
She's got a cool star cloak with all kinds of cool stuff in it. I'm so fucking cool. You guys
Yeah, I want to fuck her. I want to stick it in her fucking
hole
If you okay, if you came on white diamonds, uh diamond, would it grow like a white steven universe?
Is like that what you would get same with you know bluey and yellow. Would it be the same sort of thing?
I think they would have to do it on they would have to decide
Like only if they wanted it to happen. Yeah, you can't do it by accident doctor. Help me
I cut my cock on a diamond cunt
What if what if it does happen and they don't have to opt in like what if it's like semen is just to a gem as like
Water is to the wicked witch of the west. Yeah
Like you confirmed that pink had to grow grow a womb
To actually I mean she did have a womb. We saw her like pregnant with steven
There was a thing I refuse to believe that the gems don't have vaginas and I meet you
They have to be able to fuck it's the like I think like because it's a whole episode like one of the earliest episodes
When steven tries to fuck amethyst that was a crazy. That was a big life lesson for me the earliest episodes
Pearl has that line where she's like I don't like eating because I don't like digesting. It's gross
Which confirms for me that they got you know pearl's been around a long time. She's like a million thousand years old
Right. She's so you know, she's but she's done things. She's pooped
She's peed and she's probably been porked a few times that sex and didn't her like it rose quartz
Absolutely requested and enforced and demanded that pearl develop a vagina for her pleasure
I have no doubt that happened
In real I think she went even further than that. I think I think that she is a definite degenerate
I think that she gave the order
She said pearl go out there and find male human boys and men and fuck them so that you know what people are like
You gotta go fuck them
Holy shit, you know those like you know those like saudi arabian and you gotta eat food and you gotta poop it out your shitter
Well, yeah, that that's my order. I'm that's an order from your fucking
Fucking diamond. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so wise diamond
And she had to do it. She had to do it
She had to go get fucked. She had to go shit and pee and she didn't like any of it. She didn't like it
She's like sitting on the toilet just sitting and she's just looking up out the window teary. I had like oh great time
And what what is your what is your plan? What is your life almost a shit? I can never stop wiping the wiping never stops
Oh, it all coming back together. We have to get off of it
Wiping so yeah, so this is steven universe episode four now
Uh, I think this is three universe. Isn't this our third one? It's only three. I think so
I think this has got to be at least three and a half
Well, okay, I'm glad that I'm glad that I was able to make that wiping tirade come back and have a purpose later in the podcast
Me too. Uh, we did not get any steven universe voicemails. Thank god
Do we want to talk about anything else or should we just go to voicemails?
And this has been steven. Oh man. If people aren't talking about pearl poop, and then I don't want to hear it
We need we need a we need a new top we need something to jostle us out of the steven universe rut where I say voicemails. Let's do that
Um, how many do you have? Here's a uh news fact news fact a relevant thing
By this the time this episode comes out
Uh kingdom hearts 3 will be out in the real world. It will be released. It's already out in japan right now
Uh, and people have copies because some people are just getting it early finally something gayer than steven universe
To satiate my lust for homo bullshit
I'm happy to say that nobody has even attempted to spoil me on things which is very nice
Um, and by the time they hear this it's going to be too late. So you can't even do it now motherfucker
I'm gonna be cock deep in that game by this point. Uh, maybe I'll take some time off work
I don't know. I might uh, I might call out sick
mischievously for a day or two. Oh you rascal. I'm such a rascal. Um
I don't know. Maybe I maybe you're just putting a day. I don't know
The point is I'm going to be playing a lot of fucking kingdom hearts
And uh, I just want to take a moment on on our platform here on the procrastinators
And uh, please play uh the the fucking main theme of titanic in the background
No one uh, just to play it in your mind ladies and gentlemen as uh, we recognize the friends we lost along the way
By that I mean the people who used to care about kingdom hearts, but are completely fucking out of it
I have several friends who said they would buy a ps3
Specifically for kingdom hearts 3 when it inevitably came out on the ps3
And we are like we are like a year or two away from the ps5 right now. It's it's right around the corner
Um, it's been but they they man, they did it. It's been 13 years
13 just for the meme and at a certain point they were like okay for the past 10 years
Let's just go to the meme. Let's make the meme happen here
Uh, and I guess they did it, but uh, there's no way that's a coincidence, right? That has to be intentional
I I can I god. I hope so
Well, I don't know. I obviously I haven't played the game yet. I've been avoiding it. I just thought that uh
Man, I don't know. I just fucking say how fucking crazy it is
That and you know what this game is way more important than final fantasy 15
Um, because I mean whatever I played 15 didn't love it very much
Uh, but but this game is an actual real continuation of the same story that I started playing when I was like 11
And I feel I haven't played a kingdom hearts game since uh since chain of memories
But you haven't played two. You never played two. Well, oh wait. No two was after okay. Yeah, then two
I guess then two I haven't played a game. I haven't played a game since two
My my child self is screaming at me. You gotta play three
But like I haven't played any of the other games in between would I I mean, I'm gonna play it and I haven't played any of those
games. I don't forgive you shit. I
probably
I mean, I don't have
Well, I think I have a ps4. I mean, I have no hope or delusions that the story matters in kingdom hearts at all
I basically feel I mean like the the the part of the kingdom heart story that matters is like the emotional part of it
Like in the first game
He's just trying to get back to his friends and in the second game
He's still trying to get back to his friends in the third game, you know, and probably still I don't fucking know
That's the part that matters. Everything else is just just bullshit
Kingdom hearts too. I mean, yeah, they could have ended it at kingdom hearts too and just it was a perfectly clean ending right there
But you know, they wanted to do more and that's fine. They had they had things to explain legitimately
So they planned that the real story of kingdom hearts is that uh
Sephiroth
Is standing on a cliff somewhere being gay for cloud and waiting for him to show up so they can have a
Gay fight and that's true a sword fight with their dicks. That's every game
Since okay since the game is not yet and I haven't played it
This isn't really a spoiler, but just I heard I heard that there just is no sephiroth boss fight in kingdom hearts 3
That's what I heard and like that makes me I don't know if that's true
That would be so weird because like don't they want to push the remake?
Okay, well here's the thing and this is where things get a little bit scary. Um,
I think that they're planning that as dlc
Um, that's my fear. This is my fear
and
You know like okay, so I would I would still I still find that weird because I would think they would want to push the
The remake I would think they would include that just for that. Wait, what do you mean the remake? Oh of seven
Of course, of course that that makes a lot of sense makes a lot of sense. Yeah. Yeah. Good fucking point. The you know
Uh, that re that fucking remake is in rough shape right now. Um, they they recently like completely scrapped all work
I think and started over no fucking way
You know what? I might be confused that with another story, but uh at the very least we have not heard any positive
updates and the only the only dlc that kingdom hearts 3 should have is fucking like
Sora goes to disney world and he goes in the princess room and else is like do you have magic hands?
and he fucking
Gets a a cold hand job. I don't know that sounds good. That sounds good. Um
I I don't know I've uh, I've just heard a couple things in the over the grapevine
But like when I you know kingdom hearts 2 was weird
I mean because they they released kingdom hearts 2 right and then that was that was a standalone game
It had all its stuff then they released final mix not not in the west
But eventually it came out in the west years like 10 years later. Um, but they did in japan and like I'm like
Is it worse to buy dlc or to like buy an updated version of the same game?
I like like the idea of buying an updated version because it feels like real commitment
As opposed to like slapping shit out and just rolling it out whenever it's done
Uh, which just feels sloppy, but maybe that's just an emotional response. You know
I don't know. I just can't stop thinking of like weird stupid gay people sex jokes and fucking
everybody's
Is that related to kingdom hearts? I don't know. I'm just on I'm just I'm just on her
I'm on a real gay thing this week. I can't stop
All I want to talk about is like and then sora goes up to donald and he's like, hey, I'm gonna fuck you donald and
Then goop. I'm gonna fuck you when you're in your pillow out there
Then goofy is like well, I'm gonna fuck myself and then mickey is like nobody will fuck me
Not even mini he's getting cut by peat. That's the thing that happens, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was actually the first steamboat willy
Actually the first one was called uh, what's it called the the charlie steamer, uh, but they they they thought that was not good for the cleveland steamer
The cleveland steamer. That's the one. That's the one
The fuck is happening. They revamped it before release. Historians agree. It was the right decision
Walt Disney really was a marketing genius
This episode is weird guys
This is a weird episode, but you know
Uh, whatever. Well, welcome first time viewers to the procrastinators podcast
Um, this is gonna get like this is gonna get linked on some like steven universe subreddit
Like these guys had a really in-depth conversation about steven universe and all the steven universe fans are gonna click on it
And the first thing they hear is gonna be like, oh my shits are too fucking greasy and slimy
I can't stop liking my poopy bong ball
Please everyone post post this on the steven universe subreddit
Let's get it get it to the front page get it to the front page
Who has been an integral part of steven universe lore since the beginning anyway, so it's not our fault. They they made us do this
Um, well, all right. I mean fuck it. Let's go to the voicemails. I'm all de steven defied
Do not do what they said do not spam this on the steven universe
I don't want I don't want to be known as a villain in the steven universe community
I do I fucking do how cool would that be?
Oh
We're the real bullies. Oh, listen. Oh, listen. I already burned. I already burned all the bridges with my with my fellow pony tubers
And my fellow pokey tubers. It's time to burn it with the steven universe
I disavow everything I've said on this podcast except the funny things and the stuff about fucking pearl
One day I'll burn all my one day I'll burn bridges with the with my with my fellow poo tubers as well
The steven universe fan base has been inoculated already with uh instructions explicit instructions from sunstone
To not deal with bullies to just say no to bullies like us. So no matter what we do
Uh, they're fine. They're gonna be fine. Hey steven universe fans. We're the bully sunstone was warning you
Not me. I'm just the guy who fucks all the gems. I just fuck them. I'm not a bully. I'm just a sex man
That's just bully with me. Hey, all right, let's go
If every pork chopper perfect, I wouldn't fuck pearl. Oh, they rolled they rolled out that line. They rolled out the
Every pork chop like that because like it means nothing to why diamond was she does not know what a pork chop is
But that was I think that was that was for us not didn't she watch dug?
Didn't she watch seminal nick tune dug? Hey, remember that episode where him and roger bought all the hands on the wall
Remember this christmas special where they're gonna kill pork chop. What no why
He like bite
Someone's being an asshole or doing something dangerous and pork chop like bites him and a totally justified act
But the guy's like he's a wild dog. We got to put him down. They're gonna do it. Yeah
What why didn't they do it? What's that? Hey, remember? Hey, remember that episode where skeeter gets banana putting on their
Oh
Okay, all right, that's enough. Let's let's just float on to our fucking voice next episode of the procrastinators podcast the dug
I mean at this point it's the new
Utilitarianism we just need to get it out of our system. I guess just uh
All right. Okay. This is our first fucking voicemail. Here we go. Okay. It's from
Everyone's going crazy for this pizza
I was getting the foot off the pee. All right. Okay. Go. You're currently reading camo. You're on deck play
I know it's a meme, but I really hate the phrase friendship simulator
A one-way audio tracks doesn't really equate
To a friendship and what a friendship can mean
On the other hand, I really like the phrase simulator and it's kind of fun to think about what you can apply it to
For instance, you could consider a movie an experience simulator
Or you could call a book a thought simulator
And that one really rings true for me because when you're reading
it's almost like the author is
Instructing your mind to think in a certain way and to follow along with the specific thought process
I don't know just a thought
Okay, first of all fair enough. Uh, that's generally true. Second of all the friendship simulator is designed to be
Generally insulting. I think uh, I think we're all in agreement here that we are not your friends
I hope so. I hope we're in agreement about that. Of course
Nor are we each other's friends
Well, absolutely. Absolutely. It's yeah, I feel genuine. I feel genuine. You know, I'm
Viewers, uh, I'm a well-wisher and that I wish you know specific harm. Yeah. Yeah, shoehorned in a simpsons reference. Good
Wait, is that it?
I thought you were like building to something with that. No, I just wanted to quote moe. I guess that's how moe
Is like
In the in the one where in the one where the where he eats the chili pepper and the spirit coyote tells homer
He's got to find his soulmate. He thinks he's he's misled for a moment that marge might not be his soulmate
So he goes to the bar and he starts asking everyone there if they're his soulmates
And barney's like no, I'm more of a chum and Carl's like I'm an acquaintance and what he's like
I'm a something and moe says I'm a well-wisher and that I wish you know
Specific harm and then our dad would say that to me all the time. He really liked that quote. He really liked that quote
That was his uh, that was my I was our dad's um, the sun is shining the kid or the birds are chirping
But kids like you should be burning in hell
He wished us no specific harm and you know
All right next one from cheesy. Um, what what?
Um, I was gonna say the the bit at the end about experience simulator. There's a there's a video
There's a video by innuendo studios where he talks about um
Uh, this is not it's like this is not a tomato is what it's called
It's like he does like a big like metaphor explaining like what art is and he there's a part he talks for a while about like
Stories actually I think it might be the his video on the beginner's guide whatever doesn't matter
The point is he's quoting some he's quoting like an unauthor
Like a writer. I forget who he's talking about stories and he says that like a story is like you use words and language to
To to stimulate like a series of micro memories of your experiences, right?
So like you have memories of like what a tree is like so in a story
He might like describe a tree and then you pull up your version of a tree and that's like a little
Many experience you're having from the description in the text and it strings these micro memories together into a sequence that creates
Like an extended false memory and that false memory is what the story is and I thought that was neat
I thought that's a neat way to think about it. Yeah, okay
By the way, I'm just looking I'm sure this will be in the show notes, but this master slimelint is a very
Absolute unit. He's just colossal. Yeah, he's to scale 72 feet across
Why then what what what in treats you to such a massive individual? Why do you get such a big lad?
What's makes you special?
I look I spent I spent years I spent years in my slimewood lab slash dungeon in the basement of saint ben's cathedral
Just like just just concocting them concocting them out of goo and ooze and whatever raw materials
I had at hand
I guess that's fair and and the result was a massive success
But there was a lot of there was a lot of byproduct
There was a lot of runoff and it all collect it all collected into the being known as master slimelint
Oh, I see by the way whose name he's really based on the bubble from uh mermaid man barnacle boy, right?
Uh, well someone someone suggested I give him that face. He doesn't actually have a face
It's pretty fun. It's pretty funny though. So after the image his name is a reference to the master. Um
The the elemental masters from ululilias book
Yeah, legend of the 10 elemental masters because they all have names
Although the elemental masters are like the fire one is the master lavalent
And the the water one is the master lavalent. Um and stuff
So he's the master slimelint because because all those are just big orbs of whatever element they are and so too
With my boy here
Sick, okay moving on. Here we go voicemail from cheesy man fraydo. He's back again. What do you got?
Hey ben saint, um, I just came back to
apologize about
My last voicemail
It's kind of really shitty of me just to use it to secretly show my web comic and
I don't know. I just been thinking about it a lot. So I decided to come back in to apologize, you know
All right, just kidding bitch. I got a patron on that fucking voicemail. Take that honky bongo luna forever
Oh, no
What a heel turn the joke of that man has gone too far
I got I got a he he challenged me the bongo and luna guy challenged me
He sent me a challenge on twitter. He he added me with something
And I wanted to respond, but I didn't know how I guess I was just really intimidated. I guess I was really
I guess I was just scared into silence. I was just scared into silence. Um
Well, that's been for you cowered through and through there we go. There we go. Okay
Next mail I guess
Uh j clark 98, uh leon on us
Good evening pcp
I am jogging plug from sub world
Japan
Long time listener
First time caller the other week night said taxation is theft
And I just have a few words
Did you know the top one tenth of one percent?
Owns as much wealth as the bottom 90 percent. It is an outrage and it's time. They started paying their fair share
I'll leave you with some readings
One the communist menu festo by carl mox
True mind calm by adult
No, no stop you're ruining rainbows from a snowflake a collection of 34 essays by tumba users
Thank you for your time. Well adding those to my recommended reading list, of course
I'll let you know how I think you have a lot. I think you I think you can learn a few things name
I think I have many lessons to learn. I think you could I think you could expand your horizons
In all I think I think you need to I think you need to be more sympathetic with the plight of the working man
Indeed indeed and of the uh, I guess
Uh, the poor oppressed german by those damn jews. Yeah
Yeah, exactly. Okay. I'll open my heart to that
Yeah, if you were talking about it before you were talking up, you know, how uh, yeah hitler oppressed
Um, oh right, right. He was a deeply. This is what happened. Yeah. This is what happens
This is what you know, you got one too many jeff bezos and you get another hitler. That's all insane
All right next one the enlightened communist. Oh, okay. We're keeping right along. Let's see what he's got
Hey, guys, sorry. I haven't sent in a voicemail in a while
I was really busy jerking my gherkin and I've been wondering that's my favorite opening
You still get messages about pony stuff and how hard was it to transition away from
MLP related content and has your pony past had any effect on your current career?
Any thoughts, uh, well, I don't remember any pony voicemails
Not voicemails. I think he's talking about like, uh, pony messages
Yeah, anybody at young twitter say fuck off clopper, you know, shit like that
Everyone every once in a while someone will someone will obliquely reference uh, phantom horn
Yeah, and you know sometimes people ask me where's the where's the t-bat max revive, which is uh fair enough
I definitely view it as one of many black marks on my life and reputation that will never leave me and will forever follow me to my grave
Yep fair fair. I suppose that's fair to say I get very little of it once in a while get like a keg standard
But pretty much like Ben. I mean, I almost I almost got I almost had to get beat up by misanthropony that one time
But uh, but uh, I mean I managed to uh, I managed to talk my way out of it
I um, it's it's weird. I haven't really got any of that from anyone
Like my old like pony videos occasionally still get comments about like ha ha. They said the word know a lot
No, there's really old ones. Yeah, those great ones, but I don't get like current fans saying ha ha give and take
You're you were a pony your pony ha ha like I don't get any of that
Well, it'd be mostly I feel people, you know, whatever people who uh dislike or hate pony stuff for whatever reason
Like trying to like be like hey remember this embarrassing thing you did
I
The only people I get the only people I get doing that is you guys
Making fun of me for being rightfully making fun of me for being on analysis anarchy indeed. That's true
I I I've come to accept that that is just really funny and I don't
It is. Yeah, I don't even mind it that whole comparison of like Danny DeVito being you ben versus me being our old swarzenegger
And that like brothers. Okay, class. The thing is that's true
But in an intellectual capacity
Exclusively when it comes to specifically the choice to be a part of or not be a part of analysis anarchy
That was it that that was that was the mo that was the defining moment of my arc
And you know, I I picked I picked a side. I picked a side and I could never go back. That's it. That's it
But I I mean I guess for me, uh, like I really did just make a hard
I mean, I remember agonizing about like oh
Should I like use t-bap to like put I put videos on to like be like I've got a new channel guys come watch me
I was just like fuck it. Nah, whatever you you you I think you made like a point like
Ben like don't like don't link to my stuff. Don't like my other stuff from from t-bap
I was very concerned about my ability to like not just be a pony guy forever. I was concerned about that
Um, yeah, but it worked out pretty well
I suppose it's fair to say what had just gone better
What had just been a faster growth like what did you did if I like had used that?
But yeah, no, I'm maybe I'm not worried about it now. Obviously. I doubt it would have made like a big difference in the long run. Yeah, yeah
I think actually if you had that pony like back backing you may not have started we agua
Like you why you say that like
Because it's it's sort of like you have like but the pony stuff you have like an
An easy street like a bunch of subscribers that are already there like the algorithms already working in your favor
Starting from scratch is a lot harder. So like making
You know a month of regular content me and you know may not have been like a thing on your mind as much
That is true. But you know when it comes to like there was really no chance
We were gonna like I would even like because it was a shared channel with me and ben
I was just like uncomfortable with the idea
I mean, I didn't want to deal with the complexity of like making this my channel now
Like I was just like I can abandon this like this is a
Whatever ben could post on it. Would you like to preserve that channel for posterity just with the stuff on it?
I mean, maybe one day we'll update it. We'll see there's big things coming. There's big things coming on that channel
That's you're not wrong. You're not wrong. There's a big thing coming on that. I wouldn't have a big monetized
We'll have to check
I want to know dude. We got a post we got a post max revive tbap to the patreon and get that sweet like
Definitely doing that that like eight dollars of people that are still the tbap patreon. Yeah
Yeah, the tbap the abandoned tbap patreon
It's it's alive. It's alive and well. It's going going strong
Um, okay. Well, anyway, I haven't made it. Haven't made a dime off it in what years now. Yeah, absolutely probably three years or something
Hell, yeah, uh, okay next one. Here we go
Well, what about you mage? Have any thoughts on this? I mean, you don't do pony stuff anymore
But like in in your circles
Every now and then like I get comments on videos or messages or whatever like, hey, are you still on the pony fandom?
I'm like, no
Think you're the only one think you're the only one of us still dealing with that
I think it's because of the whole alethel halloween cola because people
Find it over and over again. And that's a big one. I get comments like oh, I watched this one. I was little
Oh, I remember I was so scared
I get comments. Oh my god. Oh, that's kind of nice
Dang, I want. Yeah, I watched this when I was just a kid. Yeah, I'm 14 now
God damn you guys talked over each other
I said, yeah, I said, yeah, I watched this when I was just a kid. Yeah, I'm I'm 14 now
Yeah, pretty much pretty much. Yeah, I was I was just saying like how long is it going to be until like I'm a nostalgic property
Like the hypocrite videos be like, oh man, I remember watching those
I'm already nostalgic for those like compilation videos at the very least
Even the next episode
The animations you did I really liked those
The water glass glass of water. Yeah, it's probably been what like two years since you made those or something
Yeah, well like I'm I'm thinking like like
Like a munchy level like oh, you were a baby when you watched me and now you're a human being and you're talking about it
Like I like the things I made are like
As important to you as like anything else. Yeah, well, you know, it's what's youtube. That's true
But you know, it's gonna be interesting. We're a generation that basically all of us
Even munchy probably for the most part. Although no because homestuck was this big thing
Oh, well, I was just gonna say that like we all grew up and basically our media stuff like was
You know produced by like big companies and like it was like shows and stuff
And well, those are obviously still big and what game of thrones and whatnot
Obviously things are skewing more towards like the youtube and a little granular like, you know
Middle-class creators who were you know individually successful. Yeah, I suppose as we just get further and further
It's gonna be like a generation that like they are biggest nostalgic thing. There's I don't know the Logan Paul vlogs or something
Oh, yeah, something like that. I mean, there's so I mean so many kids so many kids watching that stuff
You know, there's gonna be a whole generation of like boy. Yeah. Remember Logan Paul from when we were kids. Remember
Remember Spider-Man and Elsa remember a bad man and wait
Spiper man and bad man. You know what I'm talking about those guys
Batman
That's the life. Oh, I love chomkin
Must be my favorite. I mean, I'm already like, uh, you know, remember
Metal Gear awesome. Yeah
It's so cool. Isn't it so cool how the internet the internet has allowed like
Yeah, like individual creators to make stuff that made a huge impact like Homestuck. It's so great. Yeah, like
So many kids like the fact that munchie like grew up in like Homestuck was his thing
Is like, wow, it's pretty great. It's pretty amazing 10 out of 10
Oh, what did I have what I have fucking um, and a man adult swim. I don't know
We need to lose what you had. I had Winnie the Pooh. Yeah, I had Disney shit. I had Arthur
I don't get I don't get Disney heads
They're babies. I don't know. Arthur was uh hippo. I said I said in
Oh, wait, no, this wasn't this was cut. This was cut from my script of the first poo video
But in the first poo video originally I went on a digression like comparing poo to Arthur
and how like for me
Arthur was like like baby books in my like
Elementary school library and I was like, oh, these are like baby books. I don't know the real shit though
And and then but then like Arthur was a tv show and it seems like people think Arthur was pretty good
Like people remember it pretty fondly, but it was already tainted like I was like, oh, that's a baby
Franchise for babies. No, no, thanks. I mean, although I might have been a little old for Arthur when it came on tv
I forget exactly. I look back on when Arthur punched EW with much fondness and
blowing
Remembrance
Oh, yeah. All right. Next voicemail. Let's do it. This is from um
Nyan Kwan. Nyan. That's not a real name. Get the fuck. So I'm a member of the inferior species known as the female
I've never had the joy of having a big fat
shlong dangle in between my legs
I just want to know what's it like having a dick
Like
Why do some dicks curve to the left or to the right? Which way does your dick curve pcb boys?
I want to know I want to know everything about dicks. All I know is how to put them in my fucking mouth
I suck that dick all the time
Yeah, but yeah, just I wanted all the dick facts. What's it like having a dick? Okay, bye
Guys before anyone answers this is a trap that girl's 11 years old. Do not answer her questions
Do not engage do not engage
Yeah, it's pretty good. It's fine. It could be
Uh, it's sick. It's fucking I imagine it's like easier than not having one because you have like control
But it is, you know mass that is, you know, in existence control like the patriarchy
My dick my dick has a my I'm going for I'm going for guys. You can't fucking stop me call call the cops
My dick has a my dick has a very slight leftward. It's a very slight leftward curve. I think you're a left leaner
I am I am a bit of a left leaner. Yeah, me too
See it's funny Nate because I was thinking oh, it's because you because you jack off all the time
And it's like, oh you're bending it because you're like applying all that force like
But hey, but you're a lefty. Yeah, you're a lefty and I'm a righty, but our dicks curve the same way
I guess it's not the jacking off that take that atheists
All right, I I remember like like finding out like
That it was starting to bend in one way. It's like, huh, is that bad?
And I think it was just literally the way that I put my pants on
Oh, that could do it. I mean and that's like the way it was just resting it
There was I had to go one way or the other. I wouldn't like force it down like the middle path
Just cut it in two. That's what you got to do
So it just it just like naturally would be squished in one direction or the other and then that's how it grows
Yeah, yeah, and it really doesn't matter because it it's it's a floppy thing
Here that's true. That's true. You can bend it right back
Throw it over your shoulder. Uh, you know all the good things like a continental soldier
That's true. I've been an industrious young lady could figure it out too though
If she yeah, I suppose you could employ a funnel perhaps or something along those funnel like like a garden hose
Girls can pee standing up a thing. Well, yeah, but drawing while peeing, you know, that's uh, oh, yeah
It's gonna take some skill some some maneuverability
You'd have if you saved up a lot like you had a lot of pee you'd have to write really big like you'd have to like
Take steps right and like walk. Yeah, that's the way to do it
Well, you could just do it. You have to use a big font
You have to write some like show card gothic or something. Yeah, I was gonna say try peeing and show card gothic next time
All right, and do it in bold too. Okay. All right. Oh next another voicemail from no, thank you commence
Hey guys, so I haven't made a voice message in a little while. I was wondering if anyone in the procrastinators
Has has been interested in the subject of new tropics if you don't know what new tropics are
It's a fancy name for mind enhancing drugs
Not like creation or but things that will make you
More able to concentrate or focus or reduce anxiety, you know, the the good and
Pragmatic and utilitarian kind of drugs
Yes, yes, if not why you can tend to just
Especially the transhumanists on the podcast and starfleet
future starfleet officers
On the podcast why you consent to just let your brain
Be how it was biologically made and not make any attempt to improve it
With with any means necessary including buying
Illicit substances off of strange chinese manufacturers on the internet
Why what's wrong with you? Especially since most of these things are perfectly legal. I swear officer. They're perfectly legal
So yeah, that's my question anyone have any experience with new tropics or other
Smart drugs brain enhancing drugs and no, you know, it does not count. Did you boy? Oh my god?
We did not count as a new topic. We'd makes you dumb
I just kidding. I smoke weed every day
I I feel like
We we we have collectively had trouble with new topics on the podcast
Yeah, we just can't come up with them. We abandon them the idea entirely
You're right
Well, um
What counts? I mean does cath to something like caffeine count as a new topic? I take stuff like I take stimulants like that
Yeah, maybe technically
Caffeine's a hot topic. I I do find I do find that like I focus I mean he said like when I'm a little like
I'm a little buzzed on on on something like caffeine. It's like I don't know
I get I can like get like really invested in something and like, you know
A little bit of tea
Goes along we well the way that he clarified it as like not being mind-altering drugs or whatever. I'm just
Confused it like I guess the criteria of it like what constitutes it because like
Yeah, for example like lsd or whatever mdma like all those like psychedelic drugs
Like yeah, I don't think that those would fit into his criteria
But like I know people who've done them
And everyone who does who who has ever done them has always like said the same thing like
Changed their whole outlook on life from doing it once or whatever. Yeah, so I think that should count as like a mind-strengthening thing. I guess
I could have you what he I could have used like a list of like some examples of what
I could answer the question a lot better. I mean did he say yeah, he said Adderall was I've been on I've done Adderall a few times
And I will definitely say that when I'm on it
I don't know why anyone would ever not be on it because it literally makes you a better
smarter person
Uh like in every way. It's like it's like
It's like a kaioken technique in like a pill form
Like multiplies your strength times 10
And
Our uh, our I mean our dad our dad got me uh got me a little in very briefly at one point
And uh, I ended up kicking a hole in a wall
While under the influence of it. I don't think that made me a better or more effective person
Well, I took it for like two. I took it for like two weeks. I've always
Jesse if if if Adderall is makes you a better person
Why don't you take it all the time because I don't know how to get it
It's like it's like you you can't just get anything that you need everything is impossible to get your hands on
Because you like have to go to a doctor and like I don't know like where do you get that shit
All I know is that someone gave it to me once or a few times and like I don't I don't know where you fucking get that
Like I'm not well, okay someone surely someone someone on your local street. I'm not jumping through hoops to get anything
I would rather be stupid and miserable and depressed than jump through any hoops to get or do anything
Anything that I have to work for or put in any kind of effort at all
That could be time better spent like wrapped up in a blanket hiding in the dark
Fuck you know
I you know if you're on Adderall wouldn't be saying that's also true. Yeah
At Adderall Adderall Jesse you'd be like man. I better you know, I gotta I gotta start I gotta start branching out
Yeah, it's time to do my fucking taxes. It's time to fucking get a real job. It's time to go back to college
And I would do all of that in like in one hour. I would
You know
Okay on on the general subject here, I'm happy to answer why so I have the versions
They kind of creep me out doing drugs in general and even things like surgery because they're like they're like fucking with your body
And like okay, this guy's right that like utilitarianly whatever pragmatically
There's nothing that says the default state of a human is like the best or correct or like will definitely go flawlessly
But it's just when I when I think about messing with that
I get nervous and like to take a step like that makes me think like, okay
I really want to make sure what I'm doing is like, I know I'm not gonna fuck myself up or like, you know
I don't know like if I take they say that like lsd
I think they say gets embedded in your spinal cord when you take it and then like years later when you're like moving or
Benning or something it can release that like
Encaptured bit of lsd and you go on a trip whatever you're doing at that time
And I know that's just one small thing
but those are the sorts of things that I think about and
And on the other hand, I am a pretty damn effective human being so like I don't really feel the need to
Boost myself in those ways
But it's it's always possible that things would just be better if I like took Adderall or any of that stuff
But you have to weigh the risks the risks are why and I don't know the risks. So you know, that's it
I was yeah thinking about that. It's like
Surgery specifically if you have like um, say there's a new surgery to like to add your brain power plus one
um
You would get surgery when your leg's broken because you have a broken leg and that's painful and it's terrible
Yeah, if you have a pretty fine leg, would you get surgery to improve your leg if it was fine?
Probably not. So it's sort of like if you're in a really bad spot
Um, and you're like, uh, I'm gonna die
You know through suicide because I'm so depressed and I can't do anything
Uh, and then there's this surgery to like give you a brain happiness thing
Like it would be a better idea
When you're in like the lowest point and like you're you're already broken. You may as well fix yourself
Adding to yourself like improving something that's fine
Yeah, it does have a risk to it
Just generally I just yeah, I feel okay. So like I don't feel the need to
Take drugs in general and that doesn't preclude our all our lives from just being better if we did
Like I don't know explore some of this stuff like sam harris and first of all, I do coffee
I mean, I you know, I drink coffee. So that's caffeine. That's a boost
Like sam harris talks all the time about how he is like he's a smart guy. I respect his intelligence
There's been a couple times in life where he has like done something like uh, like like mdmt or whatever it's called
And he did it in like a safe environment and like what he says he got out of it
Or like is like a transcendental experience, which for him was an awakening to like some of his
He argues a lot of things that I agree with that like consciousness is an illusion. There is no self
It's an illusion and like when he took mdmt
I think he was saying that like he was very aware that like we are all everything in the universe is connected in the sense
That it's all like matter
Being operated on by the same forces in like a unified system
Not that there's any like higher power guiding it just you know, the laws of physics or whatever
And this also like killed his ego in the sense that he felt just like
Part of the stardust of the universe like had no self
Uh had no personal identity
That was all stuff that comes from like our you know, like our programming and our brains and whatnot
And I I agree with that and maybe taking mdmt or something would help me to also experience these higher level
Ways of thinking or maybe great make great art great music or whatever
But I just don't feel like I need to and I worry that it would fuck something up
So I guess that's it. That's why that's why I think about it though sometimes
Well, my goal is to do every drug and every activity possible until I'm god
So like I believe that like
I don't know like the more experiences I
Absorb into me the more powerful I become
No matter what so like I just I want all knowledge inside my brain so that I can shoot lightning from my fucking eyeballs
And stop wiping my ass once and for all with the knowledge that I've obtained
You just you take a drug that turns your poop into little rocks and then they come out all dry
That sounds good
You don't have to wipe anything
And that's how the first uh gem people were created at the beginning of steven universe
That's what that's what some guy in some galaxy somewhere
Just did all the drugs until he became a fucking gem
And then like turned in it like made a body and became white diamond
It was originally just a guy on drugs
A lot of fucking drugs
Uh
He turned into a crack rock dude. Who's the who's the crystal meth gem? That's when you see he's out there somewhere
Um, all right. Let's do another call here
This is from oh, wait. I'm in the wrong chat. Uh, all right. Here we go. This is from um
Kishin slayer. Oh, yeah, our old sword guy buddy. Let's see what he's got
go
I'm finally able to totally work on the swords, but I need a deadline
Mage asked for something out of my current abilities
Nate you said you need some time to think about what you wanted me to make
Digi gave me enough to go on but never totally specified what he had in mind
Davoo is silent as an overlord should be but I would still like confirmation if he doesn't want anything
I like jesse too much. So I'll still give him a pirate sword even if he doesn't contact me
The deadline will be when the next episode goes live at that time all requests are locked in
With digis unless otherwise told I'll just do whatever the hell I want
Also go play meow by bubble one games. It is literally the comfiest game that has ever been made
That's good image take note
No, no, it's gonna be completely clear. I didn't ask for anything. I back when we he first asked about us
I thought we were memeing and I just I just said I just said, uh, oh no
No, this is the most serious man's ever let
He's gonna make a real fake sword. Yeah, but I don't I don't know. I feel bad for
Requesting something like that. I mean, I mean this guy comes into our thing and is like hey guys
Give me information to make you a sword, which is a little presumptuous
But you know
We don't owe him anything and I don't really care that much
But you know make me a fucking vampire hundred d sword like d has in vampire hundred d. There you go
You got my order. That's it
I don't I don't even know what to ask
Here's what I like I like the fucking yeah, I like I don't know what this guy's level of skill is or if it's possible
You know what sword I fucking like I like the glass swords from morrowind the fucking
They're like green and shiny and they're got like fucking they look cool. Make me a fucking morrowind glass sword
What about rose quartz a sword?
That's a big pink one big pink one. That's the site the site
Make that for
also me, I don't know I
I guarantee that my sword is the coolest and will look the best
Did you give him detailed specs and whatnot? I gave him a little I gave him details and I made it like a like a
Like not ridiculously difficult so that he would you know be able to focus on making it as as good as possible
Yeah, all right. It's I am I've been he he messages me on discord once in a while and uh
Tells me like
Man ben making this flamb as you asked for is gonna be really hard and I'm always like hey
You remember all the remember how every time you say that I'm like
I told you like a fun s stock is fine, too
And he's like no no no i'm gonna do it it's gonna be a challenge and then a couple other days later
He's like man this flam this curved blade is gonna be really hard and I'm like hey remember man
I told you you don't have to do that. It's fine. He's like no no no it's gonna be good
It's gonna be tell I'm buying all this extra equipment just to make it possible
I'm like okay. You know whatever you want to do just remember. I said an s stock was fine
I'm telling you right now. I don't want you to have this weird emotional leverage over me like you're doing me a big
Fucking favor so just forget it. I don't want anything. That's that's what I have to say
Well, you guys are stupid. He's making a sword. It's gonna be cool. I don't want to have to look at this guy anything
I don't maybe I don't suck. I don't fucking know
I don't know maybe I'll maybe I'll get it and I'll sorry
I feel like I'm coming off because it was a little mean I'll still fucking keep it
I'll still but then I'll have a sword and you won't that'll means I can kill you
Let me just quickly say like I appreciate it
But like you would have nowhere to send it to so don't make a sword for me though
I really appreciate the sentiment problem. Are you homeless?
No, I don't want to give out my home address and I don't have a p.o. Box. So
You could probably have him send it to you at like a nearest post-op or maybe maybe you would need a p.o. Box for that
Yeah, that's what p.o. Boxer for oh, you know what he could send it to me and then uh, I could just give it to you
In person. Yeah, that's true
You know what guys this is really boring. Let's talk about these details later because who cares
I agree. Okay. Let's let's next move on to our final voicemail of the day. By the way kitchens later
No disrespect. It's just this is another chore and I have enough chores as it is
So there you go arrested if we carry swords around though. Oh my god. You are in britain. You are in britain
These are not like sword swords. These are like
Yeah
If I were on adderall right now, I could really draw this guy up some schematics of precisely what we all want
If I was on adderall, I could forge this motherfucker myself. I could forge the buster sword single-handedly
All right, let's go on
We've got our final mail of the day and this is from Nate's body anxiety
Um, I'm not looking forward to hearing from him. Well, let's let's go
Run just go now. Listen. You don't have much time. You're not hot yet and you're not getting any younger
Gotta get on that cardio train or the calories that kind of catch up to you
You'll balloon up and then at that point, so
You might as well just be dead
So on that note Nate, how's the running going? I've been trying my hand at cardio, too
But I just kind of feel like
How are you dealing with that
I okay, first of all, it's going like ass. I'll have you know
No, I'm running after this episode as soon as this episode is done. I'm going for a run
Okay, red. It was back on people today. I'm starting again
I completely forgot that was a I know because I've been deliberately avoiding talking about it because I'm embarrassed because I fucking it up
Uh, but
To to your interesting point though how he has trouble doing things after he works out
If if I go to the gym and it's like late when I get home
And I only have like a couple hours to do anything for I have to go to sleep for work
Then I have trouble like getting work done. Uh, and also the tiredness is also relevant
But like if I just go for a run, I generally feel better and feel like wow
I've accomplished something time to just jump into my next task and I usually get more done when I exercise
So for me, there's no excuse to not exercise all the time. It's just better in every way. It's just laziness
Joe Rogan calls it conquering your inner bitch to just get to the gym or get running into your thing
And that's what I'm gonna do today folks. You should do the same
Fucking shit. Yeah
Hell yeah
My man Joe Rogan my favorite fucking dude shit
Take a fucking pee and then you'll see
Um, I I think I think it's time to wrap it up folks right on that note. Uh, was that the last one that was the last one? Yeah
Oh, thank god
Yes, uh
Um
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators, uh, give us five bucks for the bonus episodes
There will be a new one out by the time you hear this. Um, and uh, they're uh, uh, there's like 22 now
I think I think that's the number at so it's worth the five bucks uh per episode so fucking do it
You've cowered, uh, but one dollar and you're in the discord. So that's pretty fun, too
That's a good place. Uh, anyway, uh at tpcrastinators follow us on twitter updates and shit and do the speak pipe
Come on people more voicemails. Keep them coming. They're our favorite. They're good. I'm sorry. I'm full of gas right now
Uh, but uh, that's it for the episode
I'm gonna go run immediately after this and crush my body anxiety. It's gonna be great
So thanks for being here to see you next week or on the bonus episodes
Oh, oh, is this it? That's it. The end. Here we go with the end. Bye
Yeah
Right now, I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick I'm jerking
Myself, I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
You