I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Nope.
What a good intro, well done.
Thanks.
I gotta get my folder open.
My voicemail folder for some reason.
This boy taking notes.
Yeah, a little bit.
Doing what you might call a thorough analysis.
Do you have your soundboard up?
Do you have your white woman in the room to go, oh my god, that is crazy.
Now I got no bitches.
God damn, how is this a podcast then?
No bitches.
No fucking maidens.
No maidens, touch grace.
It's like that video game that I played that made me very angry.
I don't even know what it means, I just picked it up through the cultural osmosis.
I barely know what it means.
I don't know what the fuck it is.
I got to wait two years before all the lore videos are out.
It's something about fingers, I know fingers are involved.
Are they?
Yeah, fingers.
Fingers that are like actual just giant like hands that are just two fingers that talk to God or something.
It's a major element of the Elden Ring lore.
Oh, like a ring goes on the giant finger that talks to God.
Fingers and rings.
Oh shit, I didn't think of that.
Have I made a connection here?
You did that I didn't.
Oh my god.
Alright.
I mean it's the Elden Ring.
So alright.
Yeah, so clearly you weren't paying attention when you played fucking 200 hours of the game, idiot.
No, no.
Alright, I guess we've already started.
I guess we're already going.
This is the show.
Is it?
Yeah, I think so.
It's the worst.
There was like a full minute of dead air while you're looking at your folder at the start.
Eleazar, cut that dead air out.
Eleazar, boost all the background sound in the dead air and then leave the whole thing in.
Eleazar, pull stretch it and make it twice as long.
Eleazar, insert sound board.
Sound effects.
Make me sound like a morning radio DJ.
Word up, it's Whittlerly Wazzle Benzane.
Benzane in the m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-morning.
With his co-hosts, Jimmy the Fuckface.
Yes, Simsie, aka Jimmy the Fuckface.
That's my real name.
People always ask me what's my actual name so they don't have to call me fucking Simsie
because it's terrible and I just always tell them Jimmy the Fuckface.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Good old JTF.
My first name is Jimmy.
My middle name is that the there.
You see that? Yeah. Last name. Fuckface.
This is fucking shit. Move on.
I have an announcement this week.
I was going to.
It's a bit of a shame it gives not here
because it would be relevant to her as well.
But she is at a
Thundercat concert, which I gather from the context of it
being a concert that I guess Thundercat is a band.
Maybe that that question mark.
I don't know. Maybe it's a concert that plays the soundtrack
to the original animated series, Thundercats.
Well, she didn't say Thundercats.
She said Thundercat.
So I mean, it could be a typo.
I don't know. Maybe they only had one of them.
What? Only one of them showed a new liner.
Hold on. Hold on.
Let me I mean, let's let's let's interrogate this.
Thundercat band.
Does it do I get any?
Yes.
Oh, he's a no, he's a musician.
He's a guy.
He's one guy.
He's a guy with a guitar.
Does he dress like a Thundercat?
No, he's got the pink dreadlocks.
So that's cool.
Hmm.
At least that's acceptable.
And some of these pictures, he does.
That's a solid level of cat energy, I guess.
Sure.
Yeah, floats your boat.
That's just like just he's got pink dreadlocks,
just like a cat would have.
Just like my cat, Crunchy, he has pink dreadlocks.
Crunchy.
Oh, what a sweet boy.
He's good.
Leave him alone.
I was paying him a compliment.
Learn how to take a compliment, lady.
I was just I was just grabbing your sweet asses
and he doesn't come.
What are you fucking homies and Jesus Christ?
Excuse me, sorry.
I had a dream before I woke up to record the PCP.
I had a dream and I remember it unusually well.
I don't usually remember dreams very well,
but this one I was in a bar and I was with a woman
and I don't remember, I don't know
if we were like on a date or something.
I don't remember like, did I know this woman?
I don't know what our relationship was,
but she was there and she seemed to be excited
about it being like a manly bar.
She was like, yeah, this place is manly.
Yeah, that's cool.
I'm manly and I was like, cool.
So I ordered some manly stuff from the bar.
I was like, give us a plate of, give us pickles
and a cheese tray, please.
So like those are things that like,
those are bitter, salty things
that a man would like, thinking about it now.
Actually-
Not like red meat or anything.
Women love cheese trays, so that might have been a mistake.
Women like candy, they like sugar,
they're like little babies.
You like schnapps.
Schnapps, yes, schnapps.
And they like flowers.
In that order, those are things that women like.
They like schnapps, flowers and Sailor Moon,
those are the three.
All women do, they just drink schnapps,
watch Sailor Moon, eat flowers and lie.
So, Bird, what the hell is this announcement
that you've got?
Oh, it's the most important game changing thing
that's happened ever.
Since Radcon 4, everything will never be the same.
Are you ready to hear what has transpired?
Yes.
I finished, I caught up on one piece, I did it.
Holy shit.
I fucking did it, yes, this week.
Perfect.
I know, I know.
I thought I was gonna have to dance around it
because I wanted to bring up Nate
having a panic attack every stream.
I have heard some mention of people talking
about his stream pirates thing.
He's not happy bunny, he's not a happy bunny
with what's been happening.
I've heard, yeah, I've heard people complain,
I've heard complaints about it.
But anyway, everyone's people saying that like,
this is the worst thing ever.
One piece is ruined, made me do it and I caught up
and now I know what's going on.
I know everything.
I know you're verdict, what do you think?
You're talking about Nika?
Yeah.
What else would I be talking about?
It's pretty weird, but I think I'm okay with it.
I think it's fine.
I guess big spoilers, big spoiler warnings for one piece.
For chapter 1044 and 1045, I believe,
are the two chapters.
Yeah, that's as far as I've read,
I don't think there's any more.
Luffy is a wacky, silly boy now,
like even more so than before.
Okay, if you are sticking around for spoilers,
I mean, I'll give you the condensed version is,
the big revelation is the gum gum fruit
is not actually the gum gum fruit.
It is a mythical Zohan type fruit.
It is the human, human fruit.
What is it, mythical model Nika?
Yeah.
And Nika is some like sun god?
He's like the god of freedom or something?
He was a hero of slaves, sun god Nika,
and he always had green on his face.
Yeah.
So it's like the, who is, is it Son Goku?
Have the hitohitonomi mythical model Daibutsu, right?
That was the other one.
Not Son Goku, Sen Goku.
Sorry.
Oh, not only that,
not Son Goku is from Dragon Ball.
Yeah, and Gens of the West.
Sen Goku, the former Admiral, Fleet Admiral.
Now he's just an old retired guy, but that's not good.
Good for him.
Well, yeah, I think my take on Nika is like,
on the one hand, on the one hand,
like it is disappointing that it's another,
it's not my favorite when characters are like,
oh, actually they have a special destiny.
Oh, actually it turns out they kind of have
the best power in the world.
They kind of have the biggest advantage
one could possibly have.
On the other hand, I mean,
that's kind of just been one piece for a while now.
It's just sort of been revelation after revelation of,
oh, actually this guy is so-and-so's long lost son
or whatever. Exactly.
So it's not like this is a new trend.
Yeah, there's like stuff there like,
with the giant frozen straw hat in the capital.
It's like, if that didn't annoy you-
Wait, giant frozen straw hat in the-
Do you remember that?
What do you mean in the Wano capital?
No, in the Mary Joie,
the place where all the celestial dragons live.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I don't remember-
I don't remember a giant frozen straw hat.
Okay, so during Reverie,
they show like a guy who's just like a silhouette
called Im, do you remember Im?
And he's like looking at bounty posters.
Okay, this is one of the big things
that people complain about in One Piece.
Like I just, I am?
Yeah, I am One Piece, just Google that.
One Piece and Im, okay.
Do you have any recollection of this whatsoever?
Oh, look at this, look at this.
Is that just like a big Hollow Knight crown?
Yeah, I don't know what he's trying to do.
Yeah, no, no, no, I do vaguely remember
this like shadowy dude.
Yeah.
I mean, okay, no wonder I don't remember him.
Well, what happens is he like looks
at some bounty posters and it's Luffy
and then he goes into like a back room
and there's a giant frozen version
of Luffy's straw hat there.
What?
That was like, yeah, that was the big like,
oh, destiny, I guess,
because that must have been there for a long time.
For sure, for sure.
I have no idea what the fuck that means.
I think people think that Joy Boy had a straw hat
and he was a giant or something, maybe.
I don't know.
Hmm, okay.
But like if that doesn't annoy people a lot,
then why would Nika, you know what I mean?
It's on the same level of what the fuck?
The thing, I mean,
how, when you really think about it,
how long has the Luffy's powers have long since ceased
to be that he's made of rubber, right?
Yeah.
So basically ever since Gears started being a thing,
it's like, well, what is this?
Like this is not.
It became like a bizarre fucking second level of,
okay, so he's using, he's made of rubber,
but he's using it in like a really weird way.
Really highly specific way.
It was fun, yeah, it was fun.
But both of them don't make sense.
Like Gears second, making your blood move faster
doesn't do anything.
It wouldn't do much to help a human move super fast.
No, it wouldn't.
And like.
And Gears third is he just like puts air into his bones
so his hand is still has like the same mass.
It's just spread out.
So it wouldn't, you know.
It doesn't make any sense, but that's okay.
Exactly, I'm doing the thing
that I've seen a lot of people doing recently,
which is trying to apply logic to one piece and like rules.
But like, there comes a point where you remember
this is written for 13 year olds
and to be exciting every week.
Yeah, and like in hindsight,
I guess maybe it's like, okay, all that was bullshit.
Right?
Like all that stuff about making your blood flow really fast
and he's blowing air into his bones.
That was what Luffy imagined it to be.
Yeah.
Tapping into the gear five.
Which is almost a more elegant explanation.
Like, no, that was all stupid.
Like you, the reader are dumb for thinking
that that's really what was happening.
Yeah.
So I know in Nate's one piece lecture,
you guys had a discussion about how the fuck does gear second
like make any sense whatsoever?
And like this sort of, no, of course not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I always just went, ah, it's one piece.
Like he like fucking, he drinks milk and his teeth regrow.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's a stupid comic.
Yeah, yeah.
And like, I guess, I don't know,
it's sort of in line with like,
I think didn't Oda like start,
isn't the reason that he gave Luffy rubber powers
is just because he wanted to draw him like doing wacky
stretchy cartoon shit?
There's like an exact quote where it's something like,
it's the most free, crazy power of the world.
Right.
You can kind of go anywhere with it.
Well, it's just more creative, isn't it?
It's, it's, yeah.
So, I mean, so literally it's like,
like Nika's whole thing is like,
he's just like a cartoon character.
He's like a squash and stretch cartoon character.
And that's what, so it's sort of,
it's not like a rubber thing,
but it's, it's not a Gomu Gomu thing,
but it's sort of a continuation of the ethos
that is what made Oda want to draw Luffy in the first place.
Yeah, I think regardless of the reasons
why he has that power now,
I think that power is very fitting for Luffy.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
I think it's like the perfect extension
of him fighting as a character.
I agree, I agree.
Also, it's funny when he does stupid faces
and hits Kaido real hard.
It's, it's funny when he does stupid faces.
This is unrelated.
I was a little bit,
I was a little bit surprised to realize that Kaido is blue.
Yeah. Although I know that a blue,
I know that a blue dragon is like a thing
in like Chinese mythology.
Did you think it was red or?
Black, I think.
I imagine it has like a black,
maybe maybe with yellow highlights or something.
Yeah, he does have like black tattoos
of like dragon scales on him, doesn't he?
Something like that.
Yeah, he, he, I was, I was like, oh, he's blue?
Really? Okay, okay.
I know, I love that feeling where you have no idea
what the fuck a manga character's color scheme is.
And then you say it and you're like, what?
But I, you know, I know that a blue dragon is one of like
the four, I think it's like a Chinese mythology thing.
There's like a blue dragon, like a red monkey,
a green parrot and a yellow answer or something.
Oh, I've got no fucking idea.
And it's like, if they represent like the four directions
north, south, east, east, west,
they're in, they're in that one video game.
Xeno, Xeno, Xeno blade, I think.
It's a thing, it's a reference to something.
Okay. But speak, yeah, I don't know.
Clearly I know all about it.
I have no fucking idea what the fuck you're talking about.
It's a reference to something.
It's probably, it's probably in Journey to the West.
But on the, on the subject of color,
every time I've seen, I did see images of,
I did see images, I guess Nate is calling him
goofy Luffy.
Yeah, I could do goofy.
Yeah, I did see images of Nika Luffy.
And I, and I, every time I've seen him colored,
he's drawn like he's like on fire,
like he's orange or he's gold.
But in the translation that I read,
Kaido explicitly says he's white,
like his hair and his clothes are pure white.
Well, I think that's because the chapter
that's before the most recent one,
they don't, he doesn't say anything
and people just assumed,
oh, it's shown in character with spiky up,
whiter hair, it's got to be yellow.
Right, yeah.
He's doing it, he's dragon ball.
He's dragon balling it.
Or he's on fire or something.
But I guess he's white.
I guess he's white.
I guess, I'm trying to picture it in my head
and it looks strange.
It's like he's old.
It's like he's a ghost,
like he's an old ghost or something.
What I really like is if it was like,
he's black and white,
so he just looks like a manga character
even like in the context of the universe.
Oh, yeah.
Like if the, once the anime gets to that point
and he's just black and white,
you know what I mean?
He looks like the manga version.
The, I think-
But there's no way to do that in a manga,
like to have the distinction, you know what I mean?
Yeah, to just think, like, wow,
he looks like he was drawn with ink.
Say the characters, yeah.
The, I think, I felt like the penmanship
in the Nika chapters is like rougher and sloppier.
Yeah.
And I think it's gotta be on purpose.
It's-
Oh, yeah.
It's got-
I mean-
Yeah.
So honestly, I wouldn't be the craziest thing
if that were just true.
Like if he were white
because he's meant to be black and white.
Yeah.
That would be my favorite thing.
Yeah, that would be great.
It's like he went to Kingdom Hearts,
Steamboat Willie universe.
Exactly.
You got it.
I like it.
I hope, I kind of hope you're right.
Well, I don't know.
I'm sorry that's not gonna happen.
He'll just be, he'll just have a white shirt
and white hair and-
For some reason.
And like glowing blue eyes or something.
I don't know.
God.
Why not?
There's no way they'll be cool enough
to do something like that.
We'll be disappointed, don't worry.
So I guess, damn it.
I guess I'm gonna put my,
I guess I'm gonna throw,
what's the phrase I'm looking for?
I have no fucking idea what you're talking about.
I'm pro, I'm pro-nika, I guess.
I'm pro-nika.
I guess I'm kind of a little bit pro-nika, yeah.
Like after I'm okay, I'm okay with it.
I'm good.
I'm pro-nika in terms of what's actually happening.
I just hate the reasons behind it.
You know what I mean?
Which ones?
I just, you know, the whole destiny.
Oh, it's actually the most important fruit in the world
that the world government's been looking for for 800 years.
Yeah, yeah.
It feels a little-
Yeah, sure.
It's not like Naruto where they explicitly say,
Naruto isn't special apart from he has a nasty fox in him.
And then it turns out he is special.
Like nobody's ever said Luffy isn't special.
It was, yeah, I mean, it was sort of implied.
It was a fun element of his character that-
An element of his character?
Is he's just some kid?
Yeah, he's really determined.
He has a fruit that's like would be useless
if he wasn't so creative with it.
Yes, that's a fun element.
But I guess it's like, well, we've done all we can do with that.
Yeah, I mean, all they ever really did with it
was he tried to fight Ace when he was a little kid
in the flashback and he couldn't throw a punch properly
because he was all rubbery.
I mean, that's the only time it was ever
like a drawback to him and then he overcame that.
I get you, I get you.
But like special destiny wise,
everybody's getting a special destiny.
Yeah.
Sanji, Sanji's the son of this like,
he's like a science freak.
He's a Nazi scientist.
He is a Nazi science experiment gone wrong.
Zoro, I guess they're about to they're revealing
that he's like the son of like the old Shogun or something,
right?
Maybe.
It seems like they're implying he's the,
he's the lost son of like the old,
like the former someone from Wano who was like a great.
They, they, no, they're saying pretty heavily that like,
oh, he looks just like this guy.
It was the guy who was in the cave.
He was in the cave with Yamato.
I was about to bring that up, but I don't,
he wasn't like a Shogun, was he?
I thought he was just like a known samurai.
Maybe he wasn't, he was someone important from Wano
who was like the best swordsman of the last generation.
Maybe he wasn't the Shogun, but he was someone important.
I know the guy you mean, I see people saying,
he doesn't look enough like Zoro,
so he's got to be his uncle.
And it's like, why?
He kind of looks a lot like Zoro.
He kind of looks exactly like Zoro,
so I don't know what the people are talking about.
Yeah, that's a stupid thing.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So what have you thought of the Wano arc like in total,
overall?
What have I thought?
Hmm, what do I thought of the Wano arc?
I guess I've enjoyed it.
I'm trying to think like, do I like it more or less
than like, maybe I don't like it as much as like the,
I've complained a lot about the Fishman arc,
but I think, I think there were more memorable characters
in the Fishman Island arc.
Yeah, Wano's been all right.
I'd say Wano's just a bit overstuffed.
There's just too much going on.
It's, I mean, it is really stuffed full of shit.
It's, I always bring this up when I'm talking to people
about it.
It's like, did we really need two little girls
whose lives were ruined by Orochi and Kaido?
Could they not just have been one character
combined into one?
You know what I mean?
Do you mean?
Like Tama and Toko, those two characters.
Toko is the laughing one and Tama is the one
who can make the disgusting little rolls out of her face.
Disgusting.
It's cool.
Shut up.
Did those really need to be separate characters?
I had honestly forgotten about face roll girl
until she reappeared at like in the end.
And I, she had the power to make people change sides
in the battle with her face food.
Did Kaido really need like four tiers of like guys
on his team?
Couldn't it just been like two?
Did he need the flying six, the headliners,
the other ones?
Did he need all of those guys?
The all stars.
Yeah.
The, yeah, I mean,
I guess it just had to fit all these character designs
in there somewhere.
It's true.
Just had too many, yeah.
I forgive him because he put giraffe man in
and stuff like that.
Oh, the guy who's, yeah, the new giraffe guy.
Yeah.
The smile users are pretty, are pretty funny.
Yeah, they're good.
Hey, why did killer become like a serial killer
for a minute, but like now he's good again?
I don't know.
He, yeah, I don't know either.
He ate a dud smile, didn't he?
Which is why he wears the mask
because he's always grinning.
No, no, no, no, that's not why he wore the mask
because he had the mask before.
Okay.
Nevermind then.
I don't know why he just decided to kill random people.
Do they ever say like that the guys would,
he was killing with like specifically Kaido dudes?
He, yeah, yeah, he was working for Kaido.
He was like, he was doing it for Kaido.
Oh.
But now he's just not.
Yeah.
Was it because kid was in prison
and he was doing it to try and make it
so he doesn't kill kids maybe?
I don't know.
Oh, wait, was it Basil Hawkins?
Was Basil Hawkins making him do it?
Maybe.
I don't remember.
All of those characters are completely uninteresting to me
so I forget about them as soon as they're not on screen.
I know, because I know he just beat Basil.
Yeah.
And that's fine.
And I don't know why.
And you know, it being a continuation of the theme
of Basil has like people's lives in his little wicker dolls
and he uses it to blackmail people into stuff.
Like, I guess that would make sense.
So it's the best theory I've got.
I mean, I could look this up,
but I really don't care it's killer.
You know what I mean?
Well, it stands out to me as a baffling moment
in the story.
I guess so.
I mean, I guess.
I completely forgotten about that.
That wasn't, that's the one that was like,
I don't understand.
I don't understand these characters' motivations right now.
And there probably is an explanation.
I can't have just completely.
Well, he was killing people because his name was Killer.
Right, at the end of the day.
He was like a serial killer,
but actually he was working for Kaido,
but they were calling it serial killings
because they didn't want people to know
that it was Kaido, or no, it was Orochi.
I mean, he was working for Orochi,
but like Tomato Tomato or something.
He was a street murderer in Wano Country,
secretly acted as an assassin working for Orochi.
Yes.
They were trying to get him to kill Toko, apparently.
Toko the girl?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was chasing after Toko and the...
Grandpa?
Was it grandpa or uncool?
No, it was, oh, I don't remember her name.
Something of the, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't Kiku of the lingering snow.
It was one of the siblings, one of the two.
No, Kiku is one of the two siblings, right?
There were the two actors.
Yeah, it's Kiku and Iso.
I think it might've, no, it wasn't Kiku
because the girl who was holding Kiku Toko
was useless, like she was not a fighter.
Yeah, it's Comrisaki, the heroine, Odin's daughter.
Was it her?
Oh, wait.
Odin.
Yes, Odin's daughter, Momo's big sister.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, boy.
Momo, Odin's big, his big sister who I don't remember.
Oh my God, there's like, there's fucking...
There's like 900 characters in one or alone.
There's, there's Momo, okay, there's Momo's big sister.
There's, there's the other one.
There's Odin's wife, Odin's wife,
who is like the same age now.
Toki.
Toki's wife.
Wait, no, Odin's wife's dead.
Odin's wife is dead?
Yeah, she died when she sent them back to the future.
Not back, but when they sent them to you.
You remember that Odin flashback, it ends with after Odin dies,
they raid his castle and his wife is there with the two kids
and he sends them 20 years.
He sends Momo and the rest of the samurai.
You mean she sends them 20 years?
Yes.
And she doesn't, why doesn't she send herself?
Because she...
I forgot that she died.
Because her husband died and she was sad,
so she didn't want to live no more.
And then Hiori doesn't get sent to the future.
Which one's Hiori?
Oh, is the...
Hiori's the daughter.
Yes.
Momo's sister, brother, yeah, sister.
Sister, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She escapes and is looked after by a little kappa guy.
What's his name?
The frog, Kawakami or something like that?
Kawamatsu, that's it.
Kawamatsu, I think.
Someone like that.
Kawakami?
Yeah, it's Kawasomething.
I'm literally looking at the wiki now,
trying to figure out why the fuck he was murdered.
My killer was murdering people.
The Basil Hawkins theory is compelling enough
that I'm just going to assume that that's the case
until I'm corrected.
Okay, yeah.
Orochi offered killer a chance to save his captain
by giving him a smile fruit.
So, like, he was going to kill kids.
Kid.
And then...
Unless you eat the smile.
Yeah, and he did.
And he turned into a pleasure,
which is the crazy people.
Okay.
And then he started killing people for some reason.
So, I guess they were like,
it must have just been,
it must have been I'm going to kill kid
unless you eat the smile
and you got to work for me.
Yeah.
It's got to be.
I don't think he was working for him.
I think he just, like, went off
and then just started killing people
because he was mad.
Okay. I don't understand.
My impression was that the people
he who were being killed
were people that Orochi wanted killed,
but they called it serial killings
to hide the fact that he was...
But maybe he was, like,
supposed to be working for Orochi,
but he went rogue
and he's just started being a serial killer?
Yeah.
I thought maybe he was killing Orochi's guys
as a street murderer.
But I don't know.
And then Zora beats him
and then he turns to a killer again or something.
I guess that does explain why when kid shows up,
he just immediately stops being a serial killer.
Yeah. Maybe he thought kid was dead.
I don't know.
Hmm. Yeah.
So he went nuts.
Okay. Something like that.
Sure.
We'll go with that.
Everyone was talking about...
Everyone was talking about Yamato being trans.
No one was talking about Kiku being trans.
Yeah, I know.
I didn't hear anybody bring up Kiku.
I thought...
Because Kiku isn't the...
She doesn't hit people as hard.
So people don't talk about her.
That's true. That's true.
But Kiku is just actually, like,
straight up, like, proper trans.
Just straight up? Yep.
Just there's...
They just say it.
Faced.
It's like, okay. All right.
And then her brother, Iso, isn't...
No.
But he kind of looks like a girl anyway.
Yeah, but he's also very cool.
Yeah.
I like those two a lot.
Uh, yeah.
Kiku's under-discussed.
Very cool character.
I think so. I think so.
I mean, I remember...
You know what it was?
Okay, this was...
Maybe I'm just stupid.
I felt like I was stupid for needing this help.
But when Kiku...
Okay, because there's all these similar-looking women...
Yeah.
I appreciated that, commonly, when things happen to Kiku,
she would talk about snow in a way that I was like,
oh, it's Kiku the lingering snow.
Okay, that's the woman I'm seeing right now.
Was that a thing?
A couple of times.
Like, I think when she got wounded, she said like,
ah, the snow is melting.
I'm like, okay, I wasn't 100% sure who that was,
but now you've removed all down.
Thank you.
Okay, that's cool, but I never noticed that.
It was... Maybe it was just one time that it happened,
but I remember, I was like, few.
I guess it's because I... I was confused.
I've been reading it weekly for ages now,
so I guess I didn't...
There's some stuff that I just don't pick up on,
like, because it happens like one week
and then it's not addressed again.
I just liked the name.
I just thought the name Kiku of the lingering snow was cool,
and so when they mentioned snow again,
it reminded me of the name that I liked.
It sounds like a Sekiro boss.
It's exactly the type of energy that those people...
Hmm, I wonder... I wonder why it kind of sounds...
Is that racist?
Yeah!
Hey, yeah!
Could they have been pulling on a similar cultural mythology
to create these two settings?
I don't know.
Because I've been reading weekly since,
like, the very end of the Odin flashback,
like, the first chapter I read as it came out
was the He Laugh Chapter,
when they actually reach Laugh Tale and find out what it is.
It's funny, I read that like one day ago.
That was, like, three years ago for me.
That's awesome.
It's crazy.
It's crazy to think that the raid has been going on
for, like, a full two years now.
It's insane, which is why I don't remember anything
that happens in it, because so much happens.
I feel like I kind of feel like I made the right choice
not reading it weekly, because, like,
I've read the entire Wano arc in, like, three days.
That's good.
It is good.
There was long stretches of just when it was everybody fighting,
where I was like, oh...
Yeah.
I hope next chapter something funny happens,
or something character-y happens.
Yeah, for sure.
But I'm pretty happy with where it is now,
and it's clearly headed towards the end of Wano, finally,
unless it's some other fucking insane twist happens.
We've gotten to the part where Luffy has revealed a new form.
This is the final battle.
We're at the part where everyone else has stopped
having on-screen fights, and Luffy is fighting the main bad guy,
so it's getting towards the end.
We've arrived.
So are you going to be reading it weekly going forward,
or are you just going to let it build up again?
I might read it weekly.
Yeah, at least while this fight is going on.
I think I'm going to follow it weekly.
Maybe I'll stop at some point, but for now, I'm planning on keeping up.
What day does the new chapters come out?
Is it Wednesday?
Yeah, like, the fan transit ones come out,
like, the leaks come out Wednesday or Tuesday.
The fan transit ones come out Wednesday or Thursday,
and then the official ones come out on Sunday.
Yeah.
It just all depends on chaos.
I don't know.
Chaos, who I've maxed out my affection meter with in Hades.
Oh, yeah, you've been playing Hades.
But I still haven't got...
No, I did.
I got Chaos to try to talk to Nix.
But I think I have to do something
to unlock the rest of Nix's little heart meter
so I can start giving her ambrosia.
I think you get an option for her to go to see Chaos on one of your runs.
I just think that's what happens.
I don't remember it's been ages since I played it.
Yeah, yeah, that sounds right.
Have you talked about Hades on the podcast?
I haven't seen him on the podcast.
A little bit, yeah, a little bit.
So you've played it.
I like it a lot, it's great.
I played up until like the true ending,
but not the true, true, true super ending.
The true ending went on the river with the song.
Yeah, the true ending when you get first credits,
I think is how people talk about it.
Yeah, OK.
I played up to there and then I sort of fell off and dipped.
I played up to there.
Yeah, I didn't play any Hades this week, I don't think, or not much.
I don't think I played this week.
But yeah, I've seen that one.
That's the only credits that I've seen.
Yeah.
And I didn't do like any, I didn't do like any nectar gifting.
Oh, no.
No, that's not true.
I did.
I didn't do any nectar gifting with the with the Olympians.
OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was saving for the people that I liked.
Yeah, exactly.
You do get like preferential inclinations going on in that game,
I find.
Yeah, I don't want to give fucking nectar to what's the name?
Artemis, pardon me.
I don't give it to fucking Artemis.
I don't care about her.
She doesn't say funny things.
I don't care about her, but I guess you got to do it for the true, true ending.
So whatever.
I'll give it to the boulder, though.
I didn't I didn't start talking to Bouldie until after.
Yeah, after the credits.
Yeah, it took me a while to realize that you could and just give him
and you can just waste nectar on him.
You you you can't you definitely can't until Sisyphus mentions him.
OK, yeah, because I because I try.
I heard that he was a thing and I tried talking to him
and it wouldn't let me until until Sisyphus brought him up.
Who's the who's the guy that is like
friends with.
Percy, not Perseus.
Perseus Jackson.
No, who's the guy who's the old guy at Spawn
at the Hades House who like trains Agrius?
Oh, Achilles Achilles.
Yeah, who's the guy who's like Achilles's old bro or boyfriend?
That first of all, they're definitely boyfriends.
OK, I don't remember if it was explicit or not.
It's pretty it's pretty explicit.
It's Patroclus. Yeah. OK.
Whenever I like Patroclus, he's like I like he's like
he's like you are sitting on his hill watching his clouds.
Yeah, I just remember every run I did just hoping I got him
because I wanted to fucking restore death defines
because I always fucked up somewhere in the other run.
When I when I the first couple of times I found Patroclus
and I realized he would restore my death defiance.
I was like, oh, my God, I can't I can't believe it.
Like we've got we've got the run back boys.
But then it's but then I realized that really what you want
is to not lose your death defiance so you get to him
and you can take the other upgrade,
which gives you the 60 percent attack damage boost for like 10 rooms,
which makes the frickin the frickin thesius fight
like take half as long.
God, what a fight. It's cool.
But it is as great the first few times you get to it.
You're like, what? What do I do?
Took me a lot of time.
I died a lot of times on that fight for for a while.
Now now I've kind of figured it out.
Do you have any idea like how soon into the game
you got your first kill on Hades?
I know.
Yeah, it was probably after like 40 something.
Yeah. Attempts.
It took me, I think I.
I probably have been playing it for maybe like 30 or 40 hours.
Maybe something something like that makes sense.
That's about when it feels like there's like a tipping point
once you have enough upgrades and it starts to turn in your favor.
Yeah, there's.
I like it's it's so it's so gradual.
It's so gradual, but it's it's gradual, but definite.
That's what I would say in a review on YouTube.com.
I OK, did you I didn't realize that there's an entire other set
of Mirror of Night upgrades.
Yeah, that I think I did figure out.
I just never tried clicking them.
Yeah, because you see that button,
it doesn't like register in your brain.
It's just like a little arrow pointing to the thing.
Yeah, no, like, sure.
OK, that's just part of the UI.
And then you go, oh, oh, there's a whole other set.
Yeah, it wasn't.
But like most of them are worse.
Like most of them, I think, are bad.
I'd say all of them are worse.
I don't think I've ever like there's one or two.
OK, I like the the green one that lets you reroll.
I would rather reroll.
I have been using the the reroll items from the mirror
from the the Well of Charon because it gives me more
because it gives me more chances to get a kiss of sticks
and get my death defiance back in the last section.
Yeah, I I suppose there is ways you could use it.
But is that the one that swaps out for swapping rooms instead?
Yes, because I think rooms I never get anything good
when I try to swap rooms.
Yeah, whenever I play Hades,
I get so obsessed with collecting like permanent upgrade materials
like the treasure and the the nectar and stuff like that.
Yeah, yeah, like I've started runs and then just quit them
because I was getting no nectar and stuff
because I just wanted to progress the quest lines.
Yeah, I mean, though, there's literally no reason to stop a run.
Like you get something out of it every time.
Yeah, I mean, the way that you get the most of that stuff
is like by getting the furthest.
Because like the most like the most gems
you can get is the boss after you buy the upgrade
from the contractor is the boss rewards for like for killing
for killing these CS and killing Hades.
Yeah, that's the like the most gems you can get.
So, yeah, pressing on is the most profitable thing you can do.
Most of the time.
But I'm impatient and stupid and don't think about things like that.
If I waste all my re-rolls and don't get a nectar,
fuck you, I ain't doing this.
I have been. OK, I don't know if it actually makes a difference.
But it feels like after the true the first credits,
it feels like I have fewer opportunities to fish for the good fish
on the surface, and that makes me upset.
What? Like once you beat Hades and you can fish
like yes, because you can't because you yes,
because you you don't you no longer make the walk to Persephone's cottage.
Oh, yeah.
And there's and there's ponds on the path and there's ponds at
there's several different places at her cottage that you can fish.
And I don't get to see those poop those puddles anymore.
And so I don't get as many trout and bass.
And what the fuck?
The thing is, I feel like I miss the only reason I even liked my mom
is because I got to get fish.
I felt like I only ever got like two fish,
like I only ever saw the same two fucking things and I fucking.
I don't know. Did you ever did you ever fish in chaos?
No, I don't think I ever even saw a fishing point in. OK.
It was funny.
One time I got to chaos and I was I'm going like I'm like muscle memory
like bubble bubble bubble grab the thing, choose the thing, go get the portal.
And I do that.
And as I'm I'm getting the like leave chaos thing as I'm leaving,
I get Zagreus's voice actor comes and goes, is that a fishing point?
And I'm like, wait a minute, what? No, but I'm already leaving.
It's when you realize that you can fish there.
That was when I realized.
And so further and so for like the next like 20 runs,
I'm just like just keep my eye out for a fucking fishing point.
Turns out the way that I got a fishing point in chaos, finally,
I've seen one or two and generally the way that I get them is by buying things
at the pool of sticks, you buy the one that guarantees a fishing spot
and the one that guarantees you a portal to chaos.
And then they both proc at the same time and then you get a fishing spot in chaos
and you fish up these little cosmic jellyfish things.
Sweet. And I think you trade them for a diamond and did you get annoyed
when you realized like when you were like, I hate that in games
where you realize that you could have been getting something for ages,
but you had no idea it was there because I had a moment like that
with Elden Ring where I was about 30 hours into the game.
And I realized that there were invisible walls in this one, too.
And that did that did damage to me when I found that out
because I had not been thinking about it whatsoever.
Yeah, that's unfortunate.
And there's more flaws, too.
I think that was probably I probably had not missed any chaos fish before that.
That was probably when he said it, but it was too late.
That was probably the one that I missed.
You could just pretend that it was and then you won't be annoyed.
Yeah. Yeah, for sure, for sure.
But a real good game.
It is a real good game.
When I I was a bit.
I was going to I was underwhelmed.
I was I thought I was underwhelmed by the the quote unquote romance options.
Mm, but then then I got an extra cut scene.
I maxed out my my Meg.
I don't even like Meg. No, no, I don't I don't like Meg.
I know people who really, really, really like Meg.
And I'm like, no, I don't really love any of the options.
I guess if I had to pick one, I would say Dusa is my favorite.
But like she's fine.
That's like a gag one more than anything.
She's the only one who's like, I don't remember who is Romance of all.
OK, Meg is I mean, Meg is a it's Meg, Fanatos and Dusa.
OK, so you got it.
So it's like, OK, I mean, I don't really I mean, he's all right as a guy.
Like he's a decent guy, I suppose.
So it's so you got that the extent of my feelings for him.
So you got that bro.
He is that bro.
Yeah, he is that bro.
I yeah, that's true.
You got step bro mean lady and floating heads.
It's got to be the floating head.
She's nice.
I just I'm sorry.
I'm a simple man.
I just like her because she's nice.
I like her because she's friendly to me.
Yeah.
Is that so hard to understand?
And she's not my step brother.
I didn't even think about it, but he's totally your step brother.
Yeah, exactly.
People forget that.
But it's great because it's fine.
I guess I yeah.
Oh, I mean, I guess I guess these are Greek gods we're talking about.
I mean, they were always up to that stuff.
Yeah, I mean, I had forgotten, but I was reminded recently
yet Hera, Hera and Zeus are just siblings as well as married.
And that's fine.
God, I didn't realize that.
They didn't bring that up in Percy Jackson.
Geez, that's it's true, although
they might be siblings in the sense that like they both like congealed
out of like a pool of blood, the same god goop.
It might it might be like that.
Yeah. So it's like, yeah, it's a bit like.
I mean, I guess if you conceived like that, all the characters
and homestuck are siblings because they all spawned out of the same
communal spawning pool, but that's just how their species is.
So I guess it doesn't count.
Our robots built in the same factory.
If they fall in love, is that interest?
If they if they're the same model, if they were designed
but or they were designed by the same.
Yeah, by the same by the same use the same blueprints.
Then that's like DNA, I think so.
Yes, I think so case that's and if they fuck and have a little robot
children, they'll be too similar and they'll get you know, he be
him a few acts or whatever.
Oh, Jesus, you know how it is.
What was it? What was I talking?
Anyway, step step rose.
He's all right. He's OK.
I don't dislike him.
My friend was really obsessed with him.
Really? But that's fine.
That's his type of character where it's like a pretty handsome boy
who is mean sort of and sly, you know, I would say.
I guess you can see one of the things
in Hades is you can see exactly who each character is for.
You can see the demographic that they aimed at.
Yeah, I feel like Dusa is for someone who doesn't like either of the other two.
Exactly.
And Nick's is for me.
Yeah, Sam. Yeah, Nick's is the best.
Electo is unfortunately you can't romance your stepmom.
No. Sadly, cowards, cowards.
Why can you do the gay one but not the mum one?
Right. I mean, I mean, slippery slope, I guess.
Just let me let me slide all the way down it.
Big, big, globo homo agenda.
God's sake.
You can't you can't romance Cerberus, cowards.
Yeah, he's he's a god.
It doesn't count.
It doesn't count as agristers by things.
He's God's mother.
So I think Cerberus could consent.
Yeah. The narrator.
Well, the thing is that the thoughts.
The tongue, the tongue head would consent, but the other two won't.
So. No, yeah.
Yeah, there'd be issues around that.
Yeah, they could convince one of them to give them enough ambrosia.
Everything would be fine.
You can't romance Skelly.
And you stand out shit characters that you hate when I.
I love Skelly. I love Skelly.
Yes, Kelly's good when he I actually I said this in the last episode
when he gave he was the first keepsake I got and when I got it.
And I realized I could summon Skelly to show up in my runs.
I was like, oh, my God, he's there.
There he is, my friend, my friend.
I have a family with me.
Yeah, I don't think I ever figured out how to progress Skelly's quest
or whatever he or I just didn't happen to give him enough nectar.
You you just I think you just give him enough nectar, I think.
And I don't think there's I don't remember doing anything else.
I think it plateaued at a point.
And maybe there was just something that most people do that I didn't do
and didn't realize. Well, for me, I never looked anything up for Hades.
I went in like fresh.
I. I barely.
I think I looked up one or two things about the Mirror of Night,
like when I got confused about the switching.
I looked up like one or two things.
I didn't look up very much.
Skelly, all that happened with I think I just maxed out his nectar.
And then at some point, he asks you to he asks you to kill him permanently
by fully upgrading the Zagreous aspect of the Stygian Stygian blade.
OK, yeah, I never did that.
Yeah. And then you do that.
But then it's just a joke.
He's just like, well, I was just fucking with you.
We're in hell. What the hell's going to happen?
Yeah. And then I think it's a dumb ass.
And then I think after that, you can give him ambrosia
and you give him like three ambrosia and he gives you the skeleton keepsake.
And he's just.
And like I said, he he does in battle exactly what he does
outside of it, which is he just stands there and lets the enemies away.
It's awesome.
The writing in the writing, the more I played it,
the more I I wouldn't say it was annoying, but it sometimes came off
a little too cutesy.
The writing in in in that game is just a little bit cutesy sometimes.
And I know what you mean.
It's on purpose.
I don't think it's a mistake like they did it on purpose, but sometimes I feel
it's a bit much that like
Skelly the Skeleton, boldly the bolder.
I don't know.
I don't know. There's a lot of good stuff in there,
but there's some stuff that borders on and I hate to say it, the C word cringe.
There's a little there's a few little things or I was like,
eh, I can't. I would.
I don't know if it ever goes into full on cringe.
Occasionally, it feels a little like a Redditor wrote it.
Yeah, that's not even that often.
It's mostly good.
Just one or two moments.
I'm like, you tried to be cute and I don't know if I appreciate it.
Would rather you be quiet, please?
Yeah, the fat guys who look like Donald Trump.
They do.
Louts.
Is that what they're called?
Yeah, they're called louts.
I never looked at the best year, even though I knew it was there.
He thought I don't remember what the name of the enemy.
I also did not look at the best year.
He says he says more louts when you go to a room with them in it.
I just assumed that would be a he's just calling everybody a lot.
I don't know. It's again, again, it's been like two years.
That's so silly.
He know he occasionally will say the name of the enemy and some of them.
Actually, no, this was one of the first times I was like, really?
It was when he says it about, you know, the skeletons with the bombs in
in Asfidel. Yeah.
Some of them have goofy names like slam dancer.
The skulls, the floating skulls that come out of the piles in Tartarus.
They're called knuckleheads.
It's like, oh, yeah.
These names are so goofy.
They're so cutesy, like, what about learning that the learning?
Yes, learning.
Yes, learning, the learning in Hydra.
Another another moment.
I'm like, all right, OK, cute.
They're being cute and it's fine.
Serbi and Hades, Hady.
I that's they would do it.
They would do it.
They have no shame, no shame at all.
Hades is cool.
The character, not the guy. Game sucks.
Game sucks. Obviously, the game sucks.
I played it.
I played it so I could fuck the
monster floating the floating monster flying head.
I haven't filled out her gauge yet, but I think I'm like one away and
when you give her the second gift of Ambrosia, she literally is like,
Prince, why are you being so nice to me?
Look, we both know I'm just a floating monster.
Yeah, I know.
Got to fill that gauge, though.
Yeah, you need to do that.
Yeah.
It's a good ending to that one.
I'll just say that I like that one.
Oh, you did it. OK. Yeah, I definitely did that.
Well, I think she was the only like summon I got.
By the end of the game.
I have gotten her summon, but I have not used it yet.
I've only used Skelly's and Meg's.
Yeah.
I got Thanatos's, too, but I have not.
I haven't haven't used.
I haven't finished his gauge either.
I'm going to do it.
I'll I'll fuck them all.
Whatever. I'll fuck my brother.
Who cares?
It's not related by blood.
No, no, no, no, don't worry.
No, no, no, don't worry.
Don't worry.
It's OK.
I can I can get my I can get my stepbrother pregnant.
And it won't be weird because we don't share DNA.
So it's fine.
It's true.
Yeah. It's fine.
Absolutely fine.
Mm hmm.
That's right.
How are we going to get out of your game?
I can't fuck Hypnos.
Why can I fuck Thanatos but not Hypnos?
I don't know.
It's the game just doesn't respect Hypnos,
even though he literally did nothing wrong.
Hypnos like is Haiti's son, though, isn't he?
No. Is he or is he just Nix's?
I think he's I don't think he is.
I don't think he's Haiti's son.
I think he's just Nix's son.
OK.
He's him and Thanatos.
He's your stepbrother as well.
He's also your stepbrother.
Yeah. OK.
I don't like Hypnos.
You didn't like him?
No.
It's all right.
I think he's fine.
I think the games really mean to him.
Everybody talks about him like he sucks so bad,
but he's like slight.
He's like slightly silly sometimes,
and that's the extent of it.
Like he like sleeps.
He sleeps on the job and like there's nothing.
There's no consequences for it.
And everyone's like, ah, what a fuck up.
God, I can't fucking stand Hypnos.
Come on, eat them all and fuck her.
I'm sat there with my little control of my head going, yes.
Fuck you.
Yeah, kill him.
Yeah. Get his ass.
I wasn't mad about Orpheus either.
Orpheus, music, man.
It's Orpheus a trans man.
That was my read because I feel like
he's got a female voice actor.
Yeah.
And then I thought, and then I thought,
maybe I'm thinking too hard about it.
I don't know.
I don't really care.
Yeah.
He just got annoying and old.
The joke of him being scared and sad.
I don't know.
I got tired of his character.
That's just his personality.
I don't know.
But I mean, by the time by the time
I got him and Eurydice back together,
I like his little question mark,
like stopped even propping.
So I basically stopped even having conversations with him.
So I didn't really get.
Walking straight past him, poor man.
I mean, he's not saying anything.
So like I didn't get tired of him.
Like he was done.
He was done having things to say.
I forget.
So that was it.
Does he just stay with Eurydice
or does he come back to the House of Hades?
Like half and half.
Like half the time he'll be hanging out
in his little Hades chair and half the time
he'll be singing with Eurydice in Asphodel.
Can I just say Eurydice is the coolest fucking name ever?
And it's so fun to say.
I don't like it just because I see it written
and I want to say Eurydice.
Yeah, that's true.
But once you know it, you can be the cocky asshole
who says, actually, it's Eurydice.
And you get to say Eurydice and it's fucking sick.
I like that name.
It's fine.
It's all right.
God damn it, Ben.
Clap for the things I clap for.
Ah, please clap.
Trying to think.
Trying to think if there's anything else.
I'm working on doing, I think I'm getting close
to finishing Sisyphus' quest line.
Think I'm almost there.
Sisyphus is the goodest boy.
He is the sweetest cinnamon roll.
As the writers of the game would probably say.
I like his dumb fucking face.
He does have a dumb fucking face.
He does.
Oh, Prince.
But it's like a friend dumb face.
Good to see you.
Oh, oh, oh, Prince, I'm having a banger week.
The lashings were mild today, Prince.
Yeah, that stuff works.
I like that stuff.
He's delightful, yeah.
Who's your favorite god to talk to?
My favorite god to talk to.
My favorite god to...
I guess I would say, I guess I would say probably Poseidon.
Poseidon's a little shit stirrer.
I like him.
Because he's goofy.
Yeah.
He's the one that I have more of a reaction to, I guess.
He's the wacky uncle who takes over barbecue duties
at the house party.
Yeah.
He's, I get him, and Haiti's just calls him dumb.
He's just like, yeah, he's just an idiot.
I mean, it adds up.
He's kind of, yeah, sure.
I'm trying to think if there's any others that I particularly
like.
Artemis seems embarrassed when you give her stuff.
And that's kind of cute, I guess.
Just like, what?
I love all their designs so much.
I think they're all some of the best versions of drawing
those characters I've seen.
They're all beautiful.
They're all gorgeous.
Yeah, they are.
I love Athena's design so much.
I like that she's just gray for no reason.
She's just gray.
It just suits her color scheme perfectly.
The colors are nice.
Her color is blue, yellow.
Not green.
Blue, gold, and gray.
Blue, gold, gray, silvery color.
It's like, yeah, cool, cool, man.
She gives you all the best powers
because you can just live through anything.
She gives you, I mean, divine dash is like the best.
It's like the Runsaver.
When you have divine dash, you just spam dash.
I mean, you should be spamming dash all the time.
But when you have divine dash, you just spam dash
and nothing can hurt you.
You just got it.
I don't like any of Aphrodite's powers that much,
to be honest.
You know what?
Aphrodite does good damage.
She's a big damage booster.
And I like, yeah, she gives you like,
I mean, maybe not as much as like the who's,
I mean, she gives you her weapon upgrade,
gives you more of a damage boost than what's her name,
than Athena does.
Yeah, but Athena shoots bombs back to people
that kills.
That's, yeah, I guess that's fine.
That's cool.
I mean, if you want to shoot bombs back,
then just dash.
True.
You should just be dashing.
What do you need?
I don't need everything to deflect.
I just like the ones that do the most damage.
And I think.
Yeah, Artemis is like summon thing.
No, not summon thing, like super attack.
Oh, the arrow?
Yeah.
The arrow.
Yeah, I didn't use that one for a while.
I eventually did.
And then I realized it just like,
takes out like a third of a boss's health.
I know, you can just like shred Hades with it.
Okay.
That one ability she has that like summons an arrow
whenever you do an attack.
I, I didn't, honestly,
I didn't use a lot of Artemis stuff at first.
I kind of looked at the numbers.
I was like, what, 3% of my hits will be critical hits?
Like, okay.
Do you know the one I mean?
Yes, the one that every time you cast
or hit with an attack or hit with something of special.
She's, you just shoot a little arrow.
That one's fucking great.
I love that one so much.
I've only used that one like one time.
And it was, it was pretty good actually.
It's so good for like crowd control in the,
what's it, the Labyrinth bit?
The Labyrinth, but you mean Tartarus?
No, what's the fucking, the bit right before Hades
where you have to go through the randomized rooms.
Oh yeah, the, the, the temple of sticks?
Yeah, that one.
Yeah.
There's some, there's some real dicky enemies in there
and there's lots of them.
And that, like some an arrow thing is fucking perfect for that.
Uh, man, when I'm in the temple,
when I'm in the temple of sticks
and I'm fighting one of the stupid fucking bosses
in the final rooms and I get poisoned by a fucking Seder.
Oh, bang, bang, my fucking desk, like, no.
Why are they in this video game?
I hate them so much.
Yeah, yeah.
At least there's always the poison cure thing nearby.
Did you, did you unlock all the weapon aspects?
I don't think I unlocked all the aspects by lockable.
I have recently unlocked all the aspects.
All the unlockables are like,
they're all like slow and strong.
In a way that, like they're not bad.
They're kind of good.
Some of them are kind of good,
but they all are similarly like slower,
tankier versions of the regular weapon, which is fine, I guess.
I think what mostly I did with Titan Blood,
which is what you used to upgrade those, isn't it?
Mm-hmm, yep.
I think I mostly just like traded that in
to get Ambrosia and Nectar.
But, ugh.
Because I wanted to do quest lines.
Oh my God.
You know, I guess, but then, but then like...
That's why I got no aspects.
But then you got no fucking Titan Blood.
But then you got no Titan Blood.
I know.
You'll eventually finish all the quest lines
and you'll be like, okay, great.
Well, now I've got all this fucking Ambrosia and Nectar.
I think the only one...
And I just need Titan's Blood.
And I have none.
I think the only one I upgraded
was the one that just like makes the gun have more ammo.
And the gun is the most boring weapon to use in that game,
but it's the winner.
I got my first two wins with the rail.
Yeah.
That was the one that I found.
That one, and then I think I have the...
Other than that, I have the most wins with the spear.
I really like...
I think probably my best weapon
is the aspect of Hades spear.
Cause you just spin it.
You get the Daedalus Hammer that gives you massive spin.
You just spin it and hit everything in the room
every single time you do huge damage
and you debuff them with a 150% bonus damage debuff.
And that's just it.
You just win every fight like that, yeah.
I really like the Daedalus Hammer for the bow,
which makes it rapid fire.
And you don't have to charge it.
It feels cheaty, but that one's real good.
I don't know if I have that one.
I did get the Daedalus Hammer that makes
the rail continuously fire, no ammo.
Yeah, there's ones for each of them, I think.
I'm pretty sure there's one.
Or is it like an explosive shot I'm thinking of?
There is an explosive shot.
Yeah.
I haven't gotten all the upgrades for every weapon.
I'm still working on the prophecy list right now.
That's my thing is to get...
I'm like really close.
I actually know, I think I just got all the legendary boons
and I am really close to getting all the duo boons.
Oh, I got nowhere near fucking the duo boons.
I think I have two more to go.
No, wait, no, now I remember.
I did.
That's the one thing I looked up was,
I had one duo left to get after playing the game naturally.
And I looked it up and then it was like,
you had to get a Zeus, some Zeus one before some other one.
There's one?
That Zeus thing just never dropped for me.
Probably the one that's gonna be last.
There's one that you need.
It's like the most complicated one.
You need a Zeus upgrade.
You need like a regular Zeus upgrade.
And you need a...
I think you need a Zeus upgrade that gives you
like lightning or chain lightning.
And you need an Aries upgrade that gives you doom.
And you need some ability from someone
that gives you like a deal damage
when you get damaged ability.
And it like all combines into like a revenge,
lightning, doom thing.
That's probably exactly what I was thinking of.
And I have not gotten that one yet.
Yeah.
I got a great combo.
The unlocked aspect of the rail,
the aspect of Lucifer, it shoots like a laser.
And I got, yeah.
And I got the Hades attack buff that inflicts doom
when you hit with the laser.
And the laser, it does like no knockback.
Enemies don't even like react to being hit with it
but it just does like, it just does damage tick,
like did, did, did, did.
And the number increases for like every consecutive tick
that you remain focused on them.
And I had, but I had the doom.
And so I'm just like spinning the laser around the room
and just like hitting every enemy with the doom effect.
And then just running away and letting the doom just like explode them while I'm not even looking at them.
I do really like the doom power.
Sometimes it's really good, like on fast weapons.
There was one run where I got... On slow weapons it's bad.
Where I got like no boon. No, no, like, boons are the like specific powers that the guys give you, right?
Yeah, when you get the glowy orb with the god in it.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
I got like none of those apart from a doom one for the like the shield throw with a doom.
It's good. It's good. It's...
And I just dumped fucking tons of the...
The pomegranates?
Yeah, the pomegranates into it.
And it was fucking just killing everything after like two seconds. It was amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
It bounces between like 10 enemies.
And I think I got one that the hammer that made it bounce between like even more enemies
and then do like an explosion when it comes back to you or something like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
And it was absurd and I loved it.
Yeah, there have been... I have definitely...
I have definitely had runs where I've just been relying on doom damage.
It's pretty good.
I had one.
Maybe it's kind of cool.
Oh man.
Oh, I did that with... It was against...
I really... You know what? I really like the shield.
I really like the shield.
Yeah, I do really like the shield as well.
Because there's a lot of bosses who you can kind of just set down the shield and like hold it and ready a bull charge.
And the boss just can't hit you through the shield and then like they'll attack and then when they're done attacking you just bull rush through them.
Get on their other side and just like repeat.
Yeah.
And it's fun. It's fun to win that way.
Most of my friends said that they didn't like the fists, but I really liked the fists.
They're okay. They're not my favorite, but they're fine.
I think just because they remind me of the fist weapon in Devil May Cry.
They were the last weapon that I got the final upgrade of.
Actually, I don't think... I don't think I've unlocked the last aspect of them, but I haven't used it yet.
Because I always go with the weapon that has the...
The darkness buff.
Yes, the dark... I always... Yeah.
Because otherwise you just leave in darkness on the table.
That's free money.
It is. That's permanent. That's permanent progress.
You churn credit cards. You're not going to turn down a darkness buff.
Yeah. Although it's more about the gems now.
I've got all the darkness I really need.
Now I just want to buy new chairs for the lounge.
I do really like doing money builds.
Getting upgrades and stuff that just mean that you get a fuck ton of money.
Oh, obons or gold or whatever.
Yeah, and then just dumping it in Karon's shop and becoming absurd by having a million powers.
When you get the Chaos Boons that gives you plus 93% gold.
Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
And then there's Dionysus ones that give you 15 gold when you exit a room and you can stack those together.
That's a Hermes.
Oh, okay. Yeah, they're Hermes with gold ones.
Side hustle. Side hustle gives you 15 gold every time you go in their new room.
God, it rules.
It does rule. What a good fucking game.
It's just a good ass video game.
Unlike Elden Ring.
I don't think I'm going to play it for an entire year like I did with Noita.
Although I did boot up Noita again this week and I got a run going and then I died and I was like, I don't care.
I don't care that I died.
I'm sort of glad that the run's over.
I was bored.
I've told you that I've still never beaten Noita at all this time.
Well, how many hours have you played it for?
Let me have a look.
I've probably played it for like 800 hours.
I know Spork beat it a lot quicker than I did.
Well, Spork beat it.
Do you know why Spork beat it?
Why?
Because I was walking her through a run.
She was streaming it and I was just kind of like observing and telling her like, oh yeah, go for that.
Go for that.
Or like, try this.
Or like, wait, wait, wait.
Try to build the wand like this.
Okay, so I've played 40 hours and I haven't gotten a single win.
That's fine.
I had kind of penis envy with that and I was like, I'm embarrassed.
My penis is small because I haven't beaten Noita and I've played it 40 hours.
It probably took me longer than that to get my first win.
I don't remember, honestly.
It's something I dip back into every now and again, but I don't play it for like explosive bursts.
I have occasion.
I'll be like, I don't know, wasting time fucking opening up Metal Gear and then playing one mission and being like, cool.
And then I'll just go, Noita, okay.
And I'll do that.
It's when I'm like bouncing between games.
I have occasionally been watching.
There's a new guy I've been seeing on YouTube who does Noita like info videos every now and then.
He's called Dunker Slam.
He has made some videos recently that have...
I actually didn't know some things about...
Okay, here's a weird thing that I found out.
You ever found a spell that's just called like water or oil or blood?
Yeah.
And it's just like a ball and it just squirts out a little squirt of whatever it is?
Okay.
Well, you can use...
I knew that people use those along with the like crit on wet, quit on oil, quit on bloody, or crit on those things.
Like when your enemy is wet with something, you deal an automatic crit.
Well, so I knew people did that.
I thought what you had to do with that was to put the material spell on a trigger.
So like spark bolt to trigger so that the material would spawn on them when the trigger spark hit them.
Wouldn't that be like after though, logically, just triggered by it?
No.
Well, I think because normally when you cast that material spell...
I guess after the first shot it doesn't matter.
Well, when you cast the material spell, a bit squirts out of your wand.
But if you cast a trigger, spark bolt with trigger, the spark bolt would hit and then it would just cast out of the trigger,
which would be, you know, on the enemy that it hit.
Yeah.
So I thought that's how you had to do it.
Turns out, no, if you cast a block of spells that includes a material spell, all projectiles in that block will have the property
that they will inflict that material wetness status on anything they hit just automatically.
So if you cast a double spell with a spark bolt and a water and you shoot it,
like a little drop of water will come out of your wand and be like,
but also the spark bolt will hit them and make them wet.
And so if you have a crit on wet, it will do an automatic crit.
And that's not like a specific like modifier that just happens if you have that in like a block of spells.
Yeah, you don't have to get like a does this effect spell to add to it.
No, it's basically like it.
Wow.
Yeah.
Like that, like the material spells are not modifier spells.
And yet they sort of have this hidden thing that they do where they sort of give this secret modifier to projectiles in their cast block
that makes them make enemies wet.
That's so cool.
It's it's sort of cool because like it it sort of feels honestly,
it sort of feels like the developer just throwing you a bone even though it doesn't make sense.
Yeah, like it doesn't really make sense why that would happen.
But like, they're just like, did it to make the crit on material spells good?
No, it's just like those things.
It's just like, I can't imagine like even starting to make a game like that.
You know what I mean?
There's so much like just the way the system of the ones works.
It's so clever and so complicated.
I I can imagine I can understand.
I can understand the like seed idea and having like like like what if the world was built of pixels that were materials and they were simulated
because, you know, the sand game or whatever.
The one thing.
Yeah, the one the one building stuff.
It's pretty it's pretty nuts.
It is impressive.
It's very it's very robust the way that.
Yeah, but also it's pretty janky.
Like when you like the way that the spells interact like you can learn them and you can make use of its quirks,
but like its quirks are really weird and don't feel designed intentionally all the time.
Like spell wrapping kind of just seems like it happened by accident and they just left it in.
That's when you'd like fill an empty slot with a light or something to just make it so it recharges quicker.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's when you put a modifier at the end of the cast at the end of the ones casts.
And so it tries to cast the modifier.
But because it isn't modifying anything, it loops around and casts the first block in the wand a second time.
And the fact that you can do that to effectively do like you can just have you can just make like a mana refresher spell just cast twice per block,
even though you only have one.
It feels like an accident, honestly.
But it's the kind of fun accident that develops.
It's a fun.
Yes, it is.
It's a fun accident and I don't think it's bad.
But I also don't think they knew exactly what they were doing.
But that's OK.
But I think I was going to have.
So was there another example of like the material, the wetness thing, the way that shit, I was going to go somewhere.
There was one other example that was similar.
Oh, the.
Yeah, those material spells.
Another thing about them that is maybe not immediately obvious is they're actually just fucking awesome.
Even if you don't have a crit on material spell, they're awesome because they cast they cost no mana, but they give a huge cast delay and recharge time reduction.
Oh, so just just put them in a block like and like, yeah, you'll be squirting water or oil or whatever.
But you'll also just cast like way faster angels turn it into a machine gun.
If you if you don't mind having water everywhere, like you can just make it want way better.
Like it's actually they're actually really good modifiers, just just because.
Yeah.
Dunker slam is I don't know.
He's pretty good.
He's shown me some shit.
I didn't know about it.
I had I had fucked around a little bit with the material.
Like I'd put him on the trigger and gotten them to do the like the material crit like that did work.
But it turns out I was like over complicating it.
It's actually way easier to achieve the same effect.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Okay.
Wait, I got to tell you a little while ago I got a run and I got a I built it so that do you know the thing about bouncing burst?
The secret thing.
There's a secret thing.
Yeah.
No, I didn't think so.
Bouncing burst is the is the green one that like bounces around.
Yeah.
Well, it has a secret property that it actually does.
It doesn't always do the same damage.
It's damage actually is a like it's based on a like comparison of its initial speed to it's the speed at which it hits the enemy.
So if you can get it to start slow and hit fast, it does like it can do like thousands of damage with a single shot.
Yeah.
So if you have heavy shot, which makes it slow, but you have accelerating shot, which makes it accelerate, you can cast bouncing burst and it will start really slow and get faster and faster.
And if it hits an enemy like that, it will do like thousands of damage.
And does it still like bounces for?
It does bounce.
Yeah.
It bounces the same number of times, whatever that is.
So you can sort of like set up like a few like slow moving bouncing ones that get faster and then do a lot of damage.
I had a build where I had a one that was a spark bolt with trigger and then on the trigger, I put, you know, like a big multicast and I had a bunch of bouncing bursts that were all heavy shot and accelerating shot and homing shot.
Oh my God.
So my every and bouncing burst is not expensive.
It did not take much mana to do this.
So every shot I did would have like, you know, eight bouncing bursts would come out that would all be slow heavy shots and then they would accelerate and then they would and then they would go everywhere and they would home in on enemies.
And they would do like thousands of damage for every and I was and I was literally like machine gun shooting out spark bolt triggers that were all just exploding in these like unbelievably deadly accelerating homing bouncing burst that just sought out enemies and killed everything.
It was awesome.
That was probably maybe the most impressive just like kill everything on screen like without even thinking about it.
Build the damage was off the chain.
I love stuff like that.
And that's what makes Hades appealing as well is figuring out little tricks and just find the perfect little combo.
I get I get the same feeling.
I get a similar feeling in Hades when I find because in Hades, the best defense is a good offense.
So when you when you get a bunch of like when you get like an epic boon, like an epic or heroic boon on, you know, on one thing, like usually it's my attack.
But sometimes it can be my cast or my special.
Usually it's the attack, but like you get like, you know, a good attack boosting boon on your on your base attack.
Plus you get a day a good Daedalus pair of Daedalus boons that just boost your attack.
And like is everything comes together and it's all stacked on like your base attack.
And it's like, OK, all I got to do is just spam my base attack and it just like choose through bosses health bars and just the damage is so good that like nothing can stop me.
I love the point in a game where you find something and it feels unfair, but you don't care anymore.
It feels so good.
Yeah.
The Elden Ring was pretty good about that.
The whole system that they have set up where you can like add a special ability to like any normal weapon.
I have not played Elden Ring.
Basically, you can like mix and match different powers on different weapons.
So you can just have like a normal longsword and then put like an ability on it where if you hit left trigger, it will just shoot like a basic sorcery spell.
And with a trick like when you attack.
Yeah.
No, it's just it's a separate attack, but it's just on the weapon.
But the way that those work is they scale with the weapon level as opposed to your stats.
So you can you can be like an entirely strength character.
But if you put like there's a spell called Glintstone Phalanx, which summons four swords and then they shoot at the enemy.
It's like the homing soul mass from Dark Souls.
Okay.
Yeah.
But it scales with your weapon level.
So if you have like a plus 10 sword, but you don't even need the intelligence to cast that.
So you can do you can just be like a crazy strong guy.
So your normal sword swings do like super damage.
But then also you have this backup range attack.
And each one of those does like a fuckload of stun damage.
So you can cast that once and then four swords hit a guy.
And if that doesn't start, you can just do one basic jumping attack and that will stun him.
And then you can do like a repose attack.
And there's so many little fucking.
Oh, oh, it's good.
I admit I have felt some pangs of like, I'm missing out when I see some some of the Elden Ring discussion.
It is a real good game.
I'm not a I'm not a huge souls guy like it's I'm okay.
Yeah, like souls is fine.
But the Elden Ring seems really big and kind of fun.
I mean, like if you like Breath of the Wild and you like Dark Souls,
I haven't played Breath of the Wild, but it I've watched someone play a bunch of it.
And it also like is another one.
I would play it.
That is all about player experimentation.
Yeah.
It rules.
Elden Ring is good until the last spot.
The last phase of the last boss, which really pissed me off.
Then it sucks.
Yeah.
There's some there's some shit in that game that really does feel like Dark Souls 2 where it's like.
I've been I've been spoiled on like one or two of the bosses.
Yeah.
I've seen I've seen Radon.
Radon is is insane.
I know about Radon.
It's fucking like the weirdest idea to put in one of those games, but it kind of works.
Yeah.
But also made me very angry while I was doing it.
And then immediately afterwards, like that was the coolest thing I've done in a video game.
There's lots of movies like that.
I saw Radon and I was like, OK, I kind of see what the game's doing a little bit.
Yeah.
I feel I feel bad for anyone with a sense of pride when they play Dark Souls games,
like the people who are like absolutely no summon ever.
Oh, sure.
Like you're not going to be Elden Ring unless you just absurdly good.
I mean, to be honest, that's how I played.
That's how I played Dark Souls was no no summoning.
I felt like I was cheating if I summoned.
I've always been that way as well.
But with Elden Ring, I got it got to a point and then I just fully committed to the win as a win mentality.
I mean, it's I mean, it's in the game for you to use.
So yeah, sure.
I just feel lucky that there's so many absurd like combos that you can do.
I mean, there's there's a whole system of like a flash that you can mix like different effects in,
which just give you temporary buffs.
And one of them is you can cast unlimited magic for 10 seconds.
You can combine that with another one that like triples your magic damage.
And then there's also a spell that puts a rune on the floor that triples your magic damage.
And there's a there's a spell which is just a giant Kamehameha laser beam.
Which usually you can only cast for about four seconds, even with like really high like magic.
Because it just it just eats up all your mana.
But with that combination, you can cast it for like a full 10 seconds and you can just straight up kill like most things in the game.
The problem is you can't redirect it.
So it has to be like a slow moving enemy.
Otherwise you're fucked.
Right.
Now you've sent the people I've summoned, like because I did a little bit of like,
Oh, I'll summon some people fun and you talk about summoning from from online like real people.
Yeah, most people just use that fucking ability.
Kamehameha beams.
Yeah.
Because I feel like people are like, Oh, I'm so clever.
I figured out how to cast it like you're like an insane person, but like everyone's doing the same thing.
Yeah.
I mean, we have when I played, have you played Lisa?
No.
In Lisa, like Lisa has a thing where there's a drug, the main character is addicted to this drug called joy.
Right.
And you can use joy in the game and it makes you super powerful for like the battle that you use it in.
It's a really strong and good item.
Yeah.
But it gives you, well, I mean, your main character is addicted no matter what he'll have withdrawals.
But like, you can use it on other characters too, but it will make them addicted and they will get withdrawals.
Right.
And basically you're, I think to get the good ending, you have to not use any joy.
Then, but then in the sequel or the DLC or whatever, there's joy.
You're expected to use it like it's technically possible to beat the game without using joy, but you're expected to use joy.
And if you don't, you're punishing yourself.
You won't have a good time.
There's no consequences for using it.
Exactly.
Because I guess, narratively, it's canon that the character is using it, so just fucking use it.
It feels like Frozoff sort of decided that that sort of mentality with summoning, but they've done it another way because there's NPC summons now.
Yeah.
Where you can like summon any, like you can find the ash of basically any enemy in the game and then summon them to help you.
And it rules.
Oh.
It's real fun.
Like, I mean, there were NPC summons in Dark Souls.
No, yeah.
They're not like character NPCs, but like you can literally just have like Pokemon stands from JoJo.
It's great.
So you can just have like a particular ghost that you will summon over and over again.
So say you really like the imp guys who, they're like little gargoyle men who hit people really fast and do a lot of bleed damage.
You can find their ash and then that means that you can summon them as ghosts to help you.
And it's balanced pretty well because there's only certain areas you can do it.
You can do it in pretty much any boss fight and then like certain areas in the open world.
There's a fuck ton of enemies.
You can call in your boys to even the odds.
Yeah.
Calling the boys.
There's a really good one, which is just it summons like, you know, the basic bitch zombies that like do nothing in Dark Souls.
Sure.
Yeah.
Like in the first area, there's one that just summons like 10 of those.
You mean there's a ghost summon?
Yeah.
They're useless, but they're just meat shields.
I was watching.
Like Skelly.
Summon Skelly.
Let the enemy beat the shit out of him.
I was going to bring this up when we were talking about Hades, but like German got obsessed with that one.
And every time he used it, he would just go, boys.
And there's one moment where he's like walking through like they walked into a room and he sees that he's allowed to summon like the symbol on the side of the screen appears and he goes,
right, boys, and summons them.
They step forward and they immediately get crushed by a chandelier and all of them die.
And it's the most amazing thing I've ever seen.
Gentlemen, gentlemen, we have no choice.
We must summon the boys.
And of course, the best one is a summon that is you.
So like towards the second half of the game, you can find there's a boss fight, which is called the Mimic Tier, and it turns into you and uses your build against you.
Which is a fun idea.
And then you can find that as a summon later on.
And if you summons a copy of yourself?
Yeah, summons a copy of yourself so you can sort of just have to trust no one but yourself.
It's great.
That's awesome.
And what I did was I leveled up my strength enough so that I could carry two greatswords.
And then I would switch off the greatsword.
So I was dual wielding greatswords.
Summoned the Mimic Tier, he would appear with the two greatswords and now I'd switch back to my seat shield.
So I could sort of be, I could be the one that lives and he could be the one that goes nuts.
It's funny.
It is funny.
It sounds like a really fun game.
It is.
It's on Steam, right?
Yeah.
I guess I technically could get it if I wanted to, but I'm scared of commitment.
But Ben, the horse can double jump.
I know.
You've seen the horse double jumping.
The horse is cool.
He's a goat horse.
He jumps.
And there's a cool Welsh witch girl who talks to you.
I might.
Damn.
I almost feel, this is stupid.
I almost feel like it's too late.
Like Elden Ring was the hot thing for like a week or two there.
It feels like everyone's beat it now.
Everyone who bought it at launch has gone through it now.
Yeah, I feel like I've, I mean, it's not a good reason not to play it.
No.
But I do feel like I've missed the moment when it was like the thing everyone was doing.
There was a great, like the first two weeks of just talking to people.
Oh, have you found this yet?
It was one of those games.
Yeah.
Have you found this yet?
Did you find that?
Oh, did you know you can do this?
That looks like fun.
Yeah.
I'm sure there's aspects of that.
Like you could still always have a friend who knows a little bit more.
That's the way it is.
And I feel like the game is definitely designed around that.
Like with the message system and everything.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
It's pretty great.
Yeah.
Just some, just some real bad balance issues towards the end of just how do we, how do
we make this boss fight hard?
Oh, that kind of balance.
Just hundreds of AoE spell attacks at the same time.
Sure.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
Fun.
And that's when you summon the moot here and let him dangle the damage so you can
I might, I might get it.
I don't know.
I might get it at some point.
Maybe when you burn out on Hades.
Yeah.
Maybe when I, if I either burn out or just like exhaust everything there is to do in Hades,
maybe the next one I would consider might be Elden Ring.
I'd recommend it.
Good game.
Yeah.
I'm thinking about it.
I have to, I have to pee.
Me too.
Okay.
Let's take a, let's, let's break for a minute.
All right.
Sick.
Hell yeah.
I've returned from urinating.
Hey, Elis, make my audio five times louder and with a big echo sound.
I'm back.
Hell yeah.
Me too.
Nice, nice.
That was a clean break.
We did it.
I definitely didn't say anything into my microphone after I came back.
Don't worry about it.
Good.
There's no secret audio.
Excellent.
Yes.
I love when there's no secret audio.
Let me look at my stupid notes here.
I had one other thing on my things to mention list.
I asked, this week I asked CC, the Tails gets trolled guy about if I could, if I could
draw a page for Tails gets trolled.
Nice.
I'm going to, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do a page.
I'm going to do it.
Do you have like a brief or anything?
Or is it just, yeah, you can do that at this point?
No, they gave me, they're a factory.
They're like a well oiled machine.
From what I've seen, it seems very organized, alarmingly organized for something called
Tails gets trolled.
It is shockingly organized.
So I asked CC, can I do one?
He was like, yeah, sure.
And then he said, I think he said, ask Embergram.
He said message Embergram.
That's a laser bots brother.
Yeah.
He said message Embergram about it.
So I messaged Embergram.
He was like, I was like, hey, CC told me to ask you about doing a page.
He was like, did you, I think he asked me, like, did you submit, did you submit like
a resume or something?
Or did you submit like a sample?
And I said, no, but you know, CC knows my art.
He told me to just ask you about it.
Yeah, I'm kind of a big shot, you know.
Well, he said, can I see your work?
And I said, sure.
I have comics on my website and I linked to my website.
He was like, he was like, yeah, looks good, looks good.
And then I think he said, I think he said, by the way, like, I know who you are because
I know your video.
I just, I didn't know you made comics.
I was like, all right.
That's great.
Yeah.
So they got me into the like artist server and they put me in my own little room.
So I have my own little sub channel, which is specifically about the page that I'm, oh,
no, I asked him.
I said, hey, I was the voice of Satan in the audio book.
So if there's a page with Satan on it, could I draw that one?
And he was like, funnily enough, I'm finishing writing the script for a Satan page right
now.
I'll give you that one.
That's great.
I was like, hell, yeah, I was like, hell, yeah.
So yeah, there's a, there's a, there's a script in there.
And I got to draw, I have to draw it by, they gave me like two or three weeks to draw it.
The deadline is like April 14th.
No, that's fine.
Yeah.
It shouldn't be too bad.
So I got to do that.
Actually, I've been sitting on that for like almost a week now.
So I should get on it.
Never mind.
Get to fucking work.
Yeah.
So maybe not, maybe like four days.
So I got to do that.
But I thought that was a pretty funny.
Cool.
That's lovely.
I know.
Yeah.
It's a great little turnaround on now you were saying, now you make Satan.
They're going to pay me something.
I don't know.
I told CC, just give me the standard fee.
Just give me whatever is normal to pay someone for an artist.
And I don't, and I don't know what amount that is.
If it's hilariously low, then that'd be funny.
I don't know.
It would be funny if it's like 10 bucks.
No.
I mean, I don't know.
I will report back when I know, when I get that and find out how much it is.
There's got to be one chink in the armor of the insane organization of the Tails gets
rolled team.
Perhaps.
And it's the payment.
I mean, I'm not doing it.
I just wanted to do it to do it.
But also, I don't believe in working for free.
I kind of would do it for free, but I just don't want to.
I'd rather do it in a professional capacity.
So just give me whatever is normal.
Also, you like money and money is good to have.
Yeah, I mean, sure.
At the moment.
I mean, I imagine it won't be.
I mean, I'm not counting on a huge amount here, but we'll see.
I mean, the pages are long.
You've read.
Tails.
Yeah.
The I don't like nowadays a page is not like one.
I've read the early stuff.
I never got too far.
Well, I think it varies.
But like now, like a page is not one comic page.
A page is like a long column.
Oh, so it's probably the equivalent of like two or three.
It's sort of like a webtoon page.
Yes.
So it's longer than almost a chapter, but like not.
Not a chapter chapter.
No, yeah.
Yeah.
So it's it's a bit it's a bit long, but you know, that's all right.
I was imagining when you said I've got to draw a page in three weeks.
I was like, well, don't bend way faster than that.
Even even I am faster than that.
Yeah.
God knows.
I mean, depends depends on the drawing.
You turn out.
I have ups and downs.
Sure.
Big ups and downs.
Man, actually speaking of being slow, what I have been doing this week, and I may have
mentioned this previously a bit, but I've continued to do it is I've been taking.
I'm trying to do the book format for slime and punishment.
And what I'm doing is I'm taking screenshots of the game.
I'm trying to organize screenshots of phantoms revenge and organize them into like a readable
sort of sequential comic.
I see.
Put that on the page so it's in.
And that's very tedious because otherwise you would just have to have like you turn the
page and then it's a URL and it says go play phantoms range.
Yeah, which I could do that, but I don't want to.
I wanted to be in there.
So but it's not it's not just as simple.
Okay, first of all, to get those screenshots, I didn't want to like play through the game
and like hit print screen every time I got to a scene that I wanted.
So I had I fucked around an OBS to get a screen recording that was that like, you know, a
lossless quality so that I could just have perfect screenshots.
Oh, no.
So I so I record it was pretty big.
The file size.
I could imagine.
But but I could handle it.
So I have this master file that is like a high resolution play through of the game.
And I've go through that in VLC doing like screen, you know, frame capture this frame
this frame this frame.
And then I'm putting them together.
And sometimes I'll like take two images and like combine them like in a room where like
there's a bunch of attacks instead of showing like every turn of the game.
I'll show a few images that are like phantom and Virginia like, you know, attacking together
like multiple like killing like multiple enemies in a single shot or whatever.
Yeah, just to make it try to not make it drag any more than it needs to.
But it's very tedious because like, I'll have to put two images over each other and
like, you know, erase parts of one to include bits from the other and then I'll have to
go and like, oh wait, the blood splatters are inconsistent.
Okay, I got to like fix those.
And you got to make sure all the pixels line up because sometimes there's like a screen
shake and I got to account for screen shake to make the images match each other and stuff.
So it's like in a movie when there's two of the same guy on screen, except it's attacks
in your brony game.
Right.
And you got a green screen, the screen to when you apply green screen because there
were two of the guy and you got a green screen to make them out.
So there's only one.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like that.
Or like Jack and Jill by Adams, by master filmmaker Adam Sandler where it's the reverse.
Yeah.
It's the reverse of putting, taking two images with two guys and putting both guys in the
shot.
We got two guys in the shot.
We got to get one of them out.
We got two guys.
We got a green screen one of them.
Just too many guys.
We got two guys.
I've only made 14 pages.
It sometimes takes me like several hours just to like put together screenshots from the
game and just line them up and get them all looking right and be like, yes, the formatting
is good.
It looks clean.
Yeah.
I guess with the exact pixel stuff, you definitely don't want any overlap or anything.
I'm trying to hurry it, but like, yeah, because it's pixels, it can be very finicky and I
just want to get one and be like, oh, wait, he's in slightly the wrong pose.
It's the wrong frame of his animation.
I'll go back in and be like, get the same shot but like at a different point in his animation
cycle so that like two images will go cleanly over one another and stuff.
To save myself the work of like, you know, having to like manually edit it.
So that's been tedious.
At least you don't have to make new stuff.
Honestly, I've been a little surprised.
Like, sometimes it's like, damn, this can like, feels like it takes longer than just
drawing a panel would take sometimes occasionally.
But it's come along.
I've got 14 pages done.
I'm probably like almost halfway through bookifying that.
So that's good.
Yeah.
Sweet.
And then I got it.
It's going to be writing the index, writing all the notes.
Oh my God.
It's going to be really fucking long.
And what's actually going to be quite maybe annoying is going to be like, I think I'm going
to write it in like a notebook file and then like copy paste the text into like an image
like like manga studio or something in like a text box because like I have not finalized
what page size I'm using.
I haven't I haven't chosen a printer yet because there's too many freaking options.
And some of them are more cost some of them are more cost effective at like printing 100
copies versus some of them would be a better deal to print like 500 copies.
So I might print like one or two test copies from a couple different printers and then
show them in the Kickstarter and just be like, listen, I just don't I don't know which of
these I'm going to go with whichever one of these is most effective, but they're all mostly
the same except like ever so slightly different dimensions.
That might be the thing to do.
I might just have to not settle on one.
You know, but I have to be open to the possibility that the page size will change slightly in
which case the formatting of the text would ideally be a little different.
Yeah.
So so I'll probably have to write the text in its own file and then when I know the final
page size, put it in the file.
Stick it in there.
Get it out there.
Exactly.
Get the money.
Get the smiles.
Get the fucking money.
I hope someone buys the book.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of books, I got my copy of Lord of Ghosts.
Yeah.
Lord of Ghosts and my little pouch.
Oh, hell yeah.
I do not have mine yet.
It's very surreal that the plush is just like real.
It's like it feels like it like I went to a shop and bought it.
So so nicely made compared to what I imagined.
Yeah.
Very nice.
So you bought a plush of a Pokemon and you know how they usually like really good quality.
It's like that.
Wow.
I did not expect that from a Kickstarter for a tiny book.
Yeah.
She did a damn good job.
I haven't read it yet.
Oh, I mean, I've read it already on on on the internet.
I was saving my reading for the physical version, but now I'm sort of in between reading other
stuff and watching other stuff.
And I I've sort of had to come piece.
Yeah.
I sort of had to come up with a rule for myself where I'm going to finish things more instead
of like having tons of things like almost like, you know, how you'd like to start a project
and then you start another project and you never finish anything.
Sometimes the project is reading something.
Yeah.
No, I got in that with media in general.
So I'd be I was like, like my brain was spread between like Elden Ring and like reading Bleach
and watching Seinfeld.
And I decided, right, I'm not going to do anything.
Right.
I'm not going to do any of the other things until the other things is done.
So I finished Elden Ring.
I've nearly finished Seinfeld now.
Oh, wow.
And like when I have free time and I'm not working on commissions, I'm doing one of those things.
Are you still reading Bleach?
No.
Bleach is on hold until Seinfeld is done.
But I'm in the last season of Seinfeld.
So we'll come back.
We'll come back.
I've never read Bleach.
I read up to where it gets bad.
Cool.
And like last year.
But you're committed to finishing.
Yeah.
Now there's like the anime coming out later this year.
And I'm like, I kind of want to watch the anime with people and like be hype because all my
friends have already read it.
Yeah.
And even if it's bad, you know what I mean?
That makes total sense.
Yeah.
So I'm going to power through because I know I dropped it last year.
Like I read all this because I watched it when I was like 14.
And I got to the end of the Soul Society arc, which is the bit everyone likes.
And then I just didn't watch anymore.
And then I read up to that point last year.
And then I got to a bit and it's like that story reveal happened.
I was like, that's fucking stupid.
Stopped reading it.
And now I'm reading it again.
And it feels like like this.
It feels like the manga isn't already out.
It feels like it's come out for me now.
It feels like I've been waiting for the sequel since I was a kid.
It's a really weird feeling, even though that's absolutely not what's happening.
It's just my brain tricking itself.
But it looks good and it's stupid.
So I don't care.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I've never, never read it.
I'm vaguely aware that it's about like.
Swords.
I think they like, are they grim reapers or something?
Yes.
They're death ghosts.
They're Shinigamis.
Death gods, ghosts sort of.
Yes.
Excellent.
It's got all that delicious fucking edge.
It's so fucking wonderful.
But also kind of bad at times.
Is it better or worse than Yu Yu Hakusho?
I've never read Yu Yu Hakusho.
I've never read it.
I've seen it.
Or watched it.
Is that by Rumiko Takahashi?
Is that by the Ranma?
Lady or is it a different?
It shows by the Hunter X Hunter.
Oh yeah.
No, no, they're not married.
Hunter X Hunter guy is married to the Sailor Moon lady.
Yeah.
Not, not the Ranma lady.
You gotta, yeah, no.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Did you see?
No, go on.
I read Naruto two years ago now.
And that was like completely raw.
Like I knew nothing about Naruto.
And I just said, you know what?
I'm going to see what all the fuss was about.
And I read the whole thing.
And I was like, that was good for a while.
Then it was less good.
But it was still entertaining, you know what I mean?
Overall positive.
I never read Naruto.
Like many people, I watched it until a little bit after Shippuden.
At some point I fell off of Shippuden.
That's the general idea.
Because my housemate, he was like his kid thing when he was a kid was Naruto.
And he was obsessed with it.
And he's watched it like four times or something.
Ridiculous like that.
Yeah.
It's got its moments for sure.
And it was really interesting to have like no outside perspective of it.
Like it wasn't still going or anything.
So nobody was talking about it.
Like I had nobody to talk to about Naruto apart from that guy.
Did you read all the like Boruto stuff?
No.
I watched the Boruto movie.
Which was okay.
And it's just like the start of Boruto basically.
Right.
People seem to either really, really like Boruto or really hate it.
Which is really strange to me.
I didn't think anyone would like it.
I would assume it would be really bad.
I would, yeah.
I would assume that it's just like, well, we got to keep this cash train chugging along to the next station.
So.
A Dragon Ball Super.
Right.
I read that for a long while and now I just can't.
I just can't do it anymore.
I really, really, really gave up on that one.
What's bad about it?
I don't like, what is wrong with it?
You know how Dragon Ball is very formulaic?
Formulaic.
And it's like new bad guy, new bad guy's minions.
They fight new form maybe sometimes.
Yes.
But Z sort of had twists on that with like Gohan beating the final bad guy.
Or Goku being dead for half the arc and then coming back.
I only saw like the latter half of Dragon Ball Z.
Okay.
You sort of get what I mean where it's like all the same thing, but like.
Yeah.
The tweaks and changes that keep it fresh.
Dragon Ball Super is if they didn't do that, if they didn't tweak it at all.
And it was just the same thing over and over again.
Oh, okay.
Okay, cool.
Nice.
And just he flubs it at the end of every arc.
Every single one, it just always falls apart and it turns into nonsense and it sucks.
I don't know how, there's only so many ways you can say everything about this is bad.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, sure.
There's the occasional.
It's just not, just not having a good time.
Yeah.
There's the occasional idea that I'm like, that's the tick and then it doesn't capitalize on it.
Or it ruins it in some way.
Like the villain Zamasu, I thought he was really good.
I thought he was one of the genuinely, not that this is high praise, but he was one of the best written Dragon Ball villains.
Zamasu.
Oh, the green guy.
Yeah, he's the green guy.
Is he a Saiyan?
No, he's a Supreme Kai.
Do you remember those?
I remember a Supreme Kai who was purple.
Okay, he's a Supreme Kai from another universe.
Oh, so he's like an alternate universe version of that guy?
Yeah, not specifically.
Or is he just one of his race?
Like the Supreme Kai's, yeah, their race is just sort of in charge of universes.
Yeah, sure.
So he's one of those and Goku meets him and he sees how strong Goku is and he's like, that's fucking scary.
I better kill all the models.
Okay.
And I like that as a motivation because it's not the same thing that most Dragon Ball is where it's like, I need to take over the world or I need to kill all these people because I don't like them.
I'm scared of him.
So that's why I do it.
Yeah, okay.
And then there's interesting, like he's the guy who steals Goku's body and becomes evil Goku.
I'm sure you've seen maybe images of him Goku Black.
I have not.
I have not seen Goku Black.
Have you not heard of Goku Black?
No.
Wait, Goku Black.
I'm scared of what I'm going to get.
Okay.
He's just wearing black.
Yeah.
See, there was a time where if you typed in like a few years ago where if you typed in Goku Black on Google, you would have gotten very different results.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
That's the green guy in his body.
Okay.
And then with time travel shenanigans, he meets the green guy.
So Goku Black, which is Zamasu in Goku's body, meets another Zamasu from the past or the future.
I don't remember.
And then they fuse into a super one.
So he fuses with himself in Goku's body.
Is that how he turns pink?
No.
And get the mask?
The pink doesn't make any sense because it's just like he steals Goku's body and he tries to go Super Saiyan blue, I think.
And it just comes out pink for some reason.
All right.
Yeah.
Just so they can sell different toys.
Is the other...
Okay.
I see there's a Zamasu that has big Goku hair and there's a Zamasu that has like a side cut shaved head like Mohawk.
Yeah.
The Mohawk one is his base form.
It's Zamasu normally.
And then when he fuses with Goku Black, he becomes the one with the Goku hair.
I see.
Yes.
And then...
Then Goku and Vegeta fuse and they fight him.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
What?
How is he...
He's in Goku's body, but also Goku is still around to fuse with Vegeta.
He went back in time in another timeline and killed Goku and told it took his body.
No, no.
He didn't use the Dragon Balls to wish to steal his body.
And then he killed Chichi and Goten in that timeline.
So, okay.
Different timeline, Goku.
Yeah.
See, what I was trying to get that is I really like the idea of that villain, but they use
time travel in the worst fucking way possible and it gets so confusing as to what the fuck
is happening.
So, he's Goku...
So, he's...
Okay.
So, he's Goku's body from another timeline with an evil God inside of him.
Yeah, inside of him.
What also fused with a different God?
What's the point of fusing?
Fusing makes you stronger.
What's the point?
It makes you stronger, then.
Okay, yeah.
It's your number times his number.
I guess you're right.
It's bigger number.
And the worst part is they can't beat him.
He gets too strong, right?
Right.
Naturally, because he multiplied the big number by another big number.
And so, even Goku and Vegeta fused can't beat him.
And then some real bullshit happens and fused...
I think people refer to him in that form as fused Zamasu, which is a terrible fucking
name for a character or a merchandise or whatever, but whatever.
Sure.
Yeah.
He does the most insane...
He fuses with the universe or something.
Okay.
And tons of his face start appearing in the sky.
So, it's like he's become the...
And they don't explain how he did this.
He just does it.
That's awesome.
No, that rules.
It's a cool idea, yeah.
But like...
Yeah.
What?
How?
And the way that they write themselves out of this corner, because...
Do they punch the universe?
No.
Earlier in Dragon Ball Super, they introduced the real God of actual everything.
Like the whole multiverse.
He's like a little bean guy.
He's got a head like a football.
So, because they're in the past while they're fighting this fused Zamasu, Goku has a button
that you can press because he's friends with God of the multiverse, right?
Yeah.
And the God of the multiverse appears and he's like, hey, Goku, let's hang out, let's play.
Let's play tag or something.
And Goku's like, can you get rid of this Sky God man?
And he goes, no.
What I'm going to do instead is I'm going to teleport us out of this timeline and erase
the entire timeline from existing.
Oh, oh God.
And it just so happens that that timeline was the same one that Future Trunks comes from.
Future Trunks is wrapped up in all this shit as well.
That's the timeline that Future Trunks is from.
So what happens for Future Trunks?
You know the basic concept where the androids came and killed all of us, everybody, yeah?
Yeah.
So that was a dark timeline.
So he came back in time and entered a new timeline so we could kill the androids and
that's the real timeline.
Yeah.
So following on from that time, after he kills the androids in his own timeline and they
try and rebuild Earth, Goku Black shows up and he causes another apocalypse, basically.
And then all this bullshit happens.
But wasn't Goku already dead in that timeline?
Yeah, but they jump between timelines.
Okay.
See, that's one of the...
That's one of the...
What?
Moment.
All right.
So yeah, God of the Multiverses erases the entire Future Trunks timeline and sends Future Trunks
to just another one, I guess.
Sure.
So he's fine.
And then before they go, he goes, I'm coming with you to your timeline and he goes back
to the present.
Goku and Vegeta is like normal timeline.
And now there's two of God there.
Which God?
The God of the Multiverse, Zeno.
Wouldn't...
Why is there more than one of him?
If he's the God of the Multiverse, shouldn't there just be one of him that oversees all
the other timelines?
Unless you time travel him and then he can have a best friend who is himself.
Okay.
Yeah, that tracks.
Sure.
Hang on, I need to show you him.
Hang on, here they are.
Show me.
Show me the little bean guy.
I'm curious.
That's good.
I need a sparkling water.
Sparkling water.
Strawberry Kiwi.
I'm back.
Very nice.
All right, show me.
I just posted a little gif of him.
Oh, let me see.
General.
Oh, this little guy.
Yeah.
I've seen.
Oh, Stewie Griffin.
Yeah, Stewie Griffin.
Haha.
What the deuce?
Because there's two of them.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
I'm super so good.
I love it.
Man, animation is cool.
It's kind of weird.
Kind of weird sometimes.
Wacky Japanese.
I feel like if I ever put a gun to my head and made me do a lecture, it would be on how
stupid Dragon Ball Super is.
Honestly, honestly, yeah.
Like, fair enough.
Can I hear my favorite fact about Dragon Ball Super?
I'm sure not going to watch the entirety of the Dragon Ball continuum.
Yeah, favorite fact.
Lay it on me.
They established that there are only 27 populated planets in Goku's universe with life on them.
27, huh?
27.
Exactly 27.
In the universe.
In his universe.
I'm okay with it.
I'm okay with that.
That's, like, I don't know why.
Frieza had a galactic army of, like, thousands of aliens.
Yeah.
Wait, so we only conquered, like, six planets?
His whole thing with the Saiyans is that he sent them out to conquer planets.
But there's just not that many of them, I guess.
Hmm.
It makes his job easier.
That's the bullshit reason they have for rank, because there's a big tournament between all the universes, right?
Naturally.
And you expect, oh, Goku's universe is going to be, like, in the bracket, they're going to put in one,
because it's got Goku in it and he's the strongest, yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Nobody's going to be stronger than Goku.
But it turns out that their universal power level is much lower,
because they only have 27 planets with other people on them.
All the other universes have, like, millions of populated planets.
Oh.
But to balance out Goku being, Goku and Vegeta and everyone being so absurdly strong,
they have way less, like, global, like, universal power.
So that they're, like, ranked number six or something instead of being number one.
So in other universes, there's just way more people.
People, yeah.
So that adds up to bigger number.
Yeah.
So just so that they could say that and have you go,
oh, no, those other universe might be scary after all.
They retcon it and say that there's only 27 planets with people on them.
I mean, I guess it makes sense.
Sure.
Why not?
And people complain about Nika Sun God, Devil Fruit.
Right, yeah.
You should try being a Dragon Ball fan, mate.
I'm just kidding.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nika, Nika base.
Yeah.
My favorite.
My favorite guy.
Yeah.
He is pretty fun.
One piece lore is pretty, pretty fucking, it's a little goofy.
It's a little dumb sometimes.
But that's, it's mostly, it's mostly all right.
Yeah.
I don't think there's anything in there that annoys me too much.
I'm not one of those psychos who is screaming about Nika and saying,
I'm not going to read the series anymore.
Oda has ruined everything.
You know what I mean?
I've seen a lot of that.
About, wait, about what?
You cut out for a second.
About, about Nika, all the Nika reveal would go,
Luffy being the Sun God, people are not happy about it.
Some people, your brother in particular.
I've heard that he is upset.
I've heard, I don't know, I got the impression that everyone hated it,
but I've also heard that like, maybe that's just more like,
the like two online crowd really hates it, but like, maybe not.
You see.
I don't know what the general opinion is.
There's two extremes.
There's people who have been like picking vague things that Oda has put in the manga in the past
and saying that it was direct foreshadowing of Nika.
Honestly, I feel like there might be some of that.
There's some that I can believe, but there's a lot that are just like,
what the fuck?
No way.
Sure.
There's, there's been a lot of people like making up their own foreshadowing.
I mean, they've been, they've been talking about Joy Boy for a while.
Like Joy Boy got mentioned, maybe not that far back, but like before like,
maybe not pre-timeskip.
He was Fishman Island, I believe he was first.
No, it was, it was pre-timeskip.
Yeah.
They may have, I would believe, yeah, Joy Boy got mentioned that even that far back.
So there's that.
I mean, I'm sure, I'm sure it wasn't planned from the beginning,
but like nothing was planned from the beginning.
No, exactly.
There are people saying that there's clues in chapter one that have led to Nika.
It's like, no.
I can't give a specific example because I looked at the post and said,
you're stupid and then stop looking at it.
I just, I just don't.
I simply don't care or no.
There's, I mean, I was reading, I read the Wiki article about the
Hitohitonomi mythical model Nika.
Yeah.
And it said like, I rolled my eyes because it says like, it talks about,
you know, the history of the fruit.
Oh yeah.
It was stolen by the shanks by the red-haired pirates.
Yeah.
And then it was eaten by, you know, Monkey D. Luffy.
It's unknown whether the shanks knew the true nature of the fruit or not.
And like, that's just a little dumb because like, first, like, there's no way,
like the only explanation for the way they behave.
Like it would sort of make sense that they, like, if they didn't know,
if they just thought it was the gum gum fruit.
Yeah.
If they knew that it was like the ultimate power in the universe,
I'm sure they would have reacted a little more strongly.
They probably just wouldn't have left Luffy to just live in his little town.
It makes way more sense to think that they didn't know.
So like, why wouldn't you assume that they didn't know?
And why would they know?
No, like the point is, you know,
The point is the government has scrubbed the knowledge of it.
They've suppressed the knowledge.
Yeah.
It's perfectly reasonable to assume that they wouldn't know what it was.
But like, maybe they could they have known about it.
I don't think so.
But whatever.
Fine.
There are a lot of people that are thinking that the Nika reveal confirms evil shanks.
Do you want me to take you through this?
Sure.
Why not?
So like, there's a scene in Reverie where shanks shows up and speaks to the five elders
who are in charge of the Navy.
Do you remember this?
Is this pre-Fishman Island?
Or post-Fishman Island?
It's a long post-Fishman Island.
It is...
I can't remember.
I think it's in Reverie.
Like the mini-arc between Wano and Holcake Island.
Wait, Reverie was between Holcake and Wano?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought it was before that.
But okay.
I think it's then.
I mean, we see some of the Reverie in Wano, and I thought that...
Yeah, they flashback to it.
I thought maybe that a new Reverie was happening now because it had already been a year since
the last one.
No.
Wait, wasn't the Reverie immediately post-time skip?
Am I crazy?
No, you're crazy.
That doesn't happen now.
All right.
It was very recent.
Because Shirahoshi's there, the mermaid princess, so it's like after everything's been
set up.
All the dressers and people are there.
Okay.
Yeah, I remember...
I'm pretty sure it's after Holcake Island and before Wano.
I know that the flashbacks happened during Wano.
Yeah, I think Wano, they show the characters because it's like there was some kind of disaster.
They're kind of vague about it, but there was some kind of disaster that happened at the
Reverie, and we don't really know what that is yet.
But anyway, during Reverie, there's a bit where Shanks shows up and he talks to the five elders.
The five guys who were talking about Nika in the research.
The Gorase.
Yeah, those guys.
Yeah.
And he says, I need to talk about certain pirate, and people think that means that he knew that
Luffy had the Nika fruit and was warning them, and that's why they sent a guy to Wano to
get him or something.
I mean, oh, like Shanks was there to inform them that Luffy has the Nika.
Which I guess can kind of make sense because he's probably seen on like the news that like
Gear 4.
I don't know if Gear 4 is like public knowledge, but you could probably see that and say, that's
not rubber.
That's something weird.
You know what I mean?
I mean, I could believe that Red Hair would know secret things.
Yeah.
And it wouldn't shock me to know that he has become aware of the Nika, of the Hito-Hito-Nomi
Nika.
I can't say the whole fucking name every time.
Yeah, I mean, it sounds plausible enough, maybe.
Yeah.
Evil Shanks could be, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's just one piece discussion recently.
It's just been chaos.
I saw it trending on Twitter.
It was just that the tag was just like one piece 1044.
It's like, oh boy, something happened.
Now I know.
I don't know.
I'm just going to roll with it.
Yeah.
Sure.
Just like much like Nika himself, you know.
Just go with the flow, man.
Just sprint, save slaves and be rubber and be wacky cartoon.
Hey, in the new chapter, was Luffy like punging through Kaido's eyes?
You see that?
Yeah, it looked, I think he was doing, because they say Kaido says like, hmm, looks like
you can turn everything around you into rubber.
Yeah.
Does that mean you've awakened your paramecia?
Hmm, but this transformation seems more like a zone.
So I think he was just doing a goofy thing.
Like he was like turning Kaido into like rubber cartoon physics.
And he was like wearing him like a glove.
He like punched all the way through his skull.
Cause there's like a funny rubber way.
There's a really weird panel where like Kaido swallows Luffy and then he punches
out of his eyes.
Do you remember that?
Wait, he swallows him and he punches out of his eyes.
Like Luffy's inside of Kaido's mouth in dragon mode.
And then he like punches his two fists out of Kaido's eyes.
And it just looks like Kaido's eyes have turned into Luffy's hands.
And then like the next panel, he's like coming out the mouth and it's like,
what happened?
Did he pull himself out through?
What?
I don't understand.
Wait, this is in 1045?
Yeah.
Oh, oh God.
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't, I see it.
I'm seeing it right now.
Yeah.
I didn't even think about it at the time, but he's totally just punching.
And if you look the way he like grabs onto Kaido's nose and then pulls himself out,
but he comes out the mouth.
I don't understand how that works.
He's like swinging.
Yeah.
He like grabs the nose.
Okay.
I think it doesn't make any sense.
His arms would have had to go through his snout, but I think the idea is he's like
grabbing the nose and using it as like a fulcrum to swing himself down and out the
mouth, even though it doesn't make any sense because his arms are coming out of his
eye socket.
What's really weird is it doesn't look like Kaido's eyes are turning into like a glove
and like stretching around his hand because you can see his like fingernails.
Okay.
Let me, let me, let me, uh, you can see his.
Yeah.
It just looks like they're just puncturing the eyes, but they're not.
Is he just, is he just phasing through?
Yeah.
I don't know if he has phasing powers or something.
It's, uh, it's a little hard.
Hmm.
Well, maybe.
Okay.
Look at this.
Look at this fucking panel.
Look at his head.
He's great.
Look at his fucking face.
If you turn your head upside down, he looks like a Charlie Brown character.
He totally, he totally does.
Maybe, okay.
Maybe if he really is, maybe if he really is like all white, like he's a drawing.
Yeah.
Maybe the white of the hands and the white of the eyes combine.
Maybe he's just got whiteness powers and any white that he can just, he's just part
of anything white.
And because it's a manga, that's everything.
Yeah.
Sure.
Why not?
Fuck it.
The rules are all out the window.
The panel you brought up as well.
Whereas hand is going through Kaido's face.
Hang on here.
It's this one.
Yes.
It's like, for a second I thought it was like a cartoon thing like where like, uh, uh,
Jerry hits Tom with a hammer and then he like cracks and then it goes through.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like cartoon logic.
Yeah.
But like, no, like immediately after Kaido is like fine.
But he's like wounded.
And but like, it's really strange.
He just, he just reacts.
If I remember correctly, he just reacts as though he, you know, he got punched in the
face.
Not that like he was fully, you know, impaled through his skull.
Like you can see his face in the next panel and it's like, there's no like hole.
So I don't really understand what the phasing through stuff is going on.
Like, like Kaido's skin must be stretched thin like rubber around his fist that has
punched like gone through and the eyes must be doing the same thing.
Yeah.
It's just the lack of like texture on it.
You know what I mean?
It is.
Yeah.
It is confusing.
It doesn't really look like that's what's going on, but that's just the only thing.
This is the only thing that makes any sense.
I'd love to see the anime try to make sense of this.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, look at, look, look at this panel.
Look.
Oh God.
This has become what's, what's even going on here.
Ben and Simsie scream about one piece panels that he does.
Look at him.
I can't even tell what his body is.
I guess that's his leg sticking out black behind him.
Yeah.
It's like his leg like shadowed in the back.
And then his front leg is bent and his knee is sticking out the bottom and then he's just
like loud.
Is that, is that just a wisp of cloud floating in front of him there?
What next to Kido's hand?
No, to the right, like under his body and sort of.
Oh yeah.
He just sort of has that in gear five.
He just kind of has little and like around his neck.
He's got like a weird like wreath of like flame cloud.
Gear four has the same thing.
Cause you know, like gear two was he, he like shoots a, he gets like loads of steam coming
out of him.
Yeah.
It's, it's like, it's like in gear four, that just becomes like a permanent thing and it's
like in a specific shape.
Maybe that's why he's white.
Maybe it's like steam, steam cloud.
Okay.
Sure.
Whatever.
Look at, look at this.
Look at this panel.
Look at these like scribbles.
I don't know how anyone could hate this.
I.
Yeah.
Like it's, it's very weird.
I mean, there's so it's very weird.
It is very weird, but I like it.
I don't hate it for sure.
I don't know if I would say that I like, I'm committed to like, like, it's so hard.
It's mostly just, it's mostly just strange and curious.
Yeah.
I guess I'm the most emotion you have reading this chapter is what the fuck.
What the fuck is happening?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
I feel like maybe you're supposed to be like, oh God.
Yeah.
I don't, yeah, I'm not sure if it, if that's intentional.
I've heard a lot of people saying this is going to remove the stakes from the rest of
the series because he's just too strong now.
He's always been.
I know.
That's always been how it is.
You've always known he's going to win every fight.
The stakes.
Give me a fucking break.
One thing I've said is just like, well, it's not like he's, I feel like he's going to,
for some reason there's going to be some reason why he can't use this power all the time.
You know what I mean?
In this fight, in this fight, he like gets tired and he like stops using it and he's
like, I can't, it's like, I can't keep using it forever.
It's too, it takes too much out of me.
There are people who saying like, well now Luffy's all part, he like literally is a God.
But that's like, not what's happening.
He has a, he has a God power fruit that is just takes a lot, takes a lot of energy to
use, I guess.
Sure.
We see, we see that he can't maintain it forever.
Yeah.
I don't know what people are worried about.
Oh, well, we circle back to one piece because everything always does.
It's, what is, what really is there to say other than to just gawk at some of these fucking
panels?
They are insane.
They are.
I mean, the, him getting his head like caved in and curved by the, by the back.
Yeah, and it stays that in the next like few parts.
Yeah.
I really like when Kaido hits him on the head and he gets really flat and then springs off
the wall.
Kaido hits him on the head.
Hang on, this one here.
Oh yeah.
He's just like.
Yeah.
It's great.
It's, it's, I, I, I do think it feels like a, a continuation of the sort of ethos of like
why Luffy is a rubber man to begin with.
Cause this Oda wanted to draw shit like this.
Imagine how much Lama gear five could be like in, in terms of like any other version, like
where they make it like serious.
Like there's the, there's this classic image of someone's fan made version of gear five.
I've never seen this before.
Imagine if we got like this instead, how much worse that is.
Honestly.
Yeah.
At some point, at some point, I mean, this is like, you know, all the, the new like super
new Sands where like, oh, well he's blue, he's blue now, but like blue means he's like
stronger now.
Like it's better.
And pink.
He's got more.
Well pink's even better than that.
Yeah.
It's at some point, it's like none of these like mean anything.
Like you just, you just, you're just making number go up.
So I'm glad Nika is, it's not that.
It's different.
He can do different things now.
It's not, he's, he just does things in, in, in the same way, but stronger.
Yeah.
So that's good.
Sure.
I'm with it.
We'll see.
Yeah.
That's a good thesis.
Do you want to go to voicemails?
Sure.
Hang on.
One last thing.
I want to mention that I saw Sonic the Hedgehog 2 in cinema.
Oh, yeah.
And it was a perfectly serviceable kids movie.
Knuckles was pretty funny.
Nice.
He acted like Warf from Star Trek, which I thought was strange, but I liked it.
That seems about, that seems about right.
He was all about honor and he, he was Idris Elbert and it was great.
He was the best.
Yeah.
He's an honorable dude.
He's got to carry out his sacred task.
I do not care about your mission, Robotnik.
He was like that.
And I was like, this is strange.
Jim Carrey, that man's got a lot of energy for somebody who's like 60.
Yeah.
He's getting old, but he's still doing it, I guess.
God bless him.
He put all the effort in.
Like there's clearly scenes in the movie where Jim Carrey just did something and then they
made an entire like effect sequence around it.
Well, that's awesome.
Yeah.
That sounds great.
Cool.
The best thing about the movie was me and my friend were the only adults there without
children and I felt like a pervert.
You know, I don't know if I've ever told anyone this, I don't know if I've ever mentioned
this, but when the hype was building, like early in the hype cycle for the first Sonic
movie, that was during, that was during the hilarious fall of Monkey Jones.
That was during the whole like Lou the Kitty arc.
Or it was after that.
I mean, it was after, it was during the fallout from that.
I talked to him a little bit.
I think I reached out to him because like, I don't remember who reached out to who actually,
but we talked a little bit and I was like, man, I don't think he's doing that well.
He asked if I would, if I wanted to see the Sonic the Hedgehog movie.
And I was like, yeah, I guess.
And he mentioned like, well, you know, when it comes out, you know, come out to North
Carolina or whatever and we'd go see the, you know, you can come out and see the Sonic
the Hedgehog movie.
I was like, yeah, I guess I could do that and it didn't come up again.
So I did not do it, but it was the offer was made to see the Hedgehog movie with a monkey.
Oh yeah.
The weirdest thing, I never saw the first one.
So I just went and saw the second one with my friend because he asked me, I said, sure.
You've never, you have not seen it?
No, I haven't seen the first one.
I just went and saw the second one because fuck it.
People said it was, people said it was okay.
I can imagine.
I can imagine exactly what it is from what happens in the second one.
Yeah.
Because it like starts out with Sonic living in like two, the two human characters house
and they're like, oh, come on, buddy.
I ain't your dad.
Come on.
Get it together.
And I'm like, oh, I know exactly how the first one ends.
Wait, he's not Sonic's dad telling Sonic I ain't your dad.
No, no, Sonic goes, you're not, you're, you're, you're, you're supposed to be my friend, not
my dad.
And it's like, oh, he's like a cop, right?
Doesn't he like hang out with a cop?
Yeah.
Nice.
He's a cop with a hot black wife.
All right.
And they, they like can't kiss on screen because it's a kid's movie.
So they like hug awkwardly whenever that something good happens.
It's great.
There's like a 10 minute section of that movie that turns into like an Adam Sandler.
Like Sonic is on screen for like a good like 15 minutes.
And it just turns into like an Adam Sandler movie with like goofy shit happening and like
normal people.
You should have got the studio notes that said, whenever Sonic isn't on screen, everyone
should be asking, where's Sonic the Hedgehog?
Where's Sonic the Hedgehog?
But the best thing about that was that none of the kids in the cinema laughed at a single
thing Sonic said or like clapped or like seemed happy.
But when there was the spit that I said felt like an Adam Sandler movie, it's like a, there's
like a fat lady and she's like running around and going, oh hell no.
And like running after fiance, who's actually like a, a secret agent or something.
I don't really remember what was happening, but and then she like drives around in a golf
cart and throws tales as it explodes without him.
And then all the kids were laughing and clapping for that, but they shouldn't react like to
a single thing that Sonic did for the entire movie.
They were just too, they were just too enraptured by their hero, Sonic the Hedgehog.
They were probably scared of him.
You see John.
Brought to life on the silver screen in glorious 4k.
Anyway.
60 frames per second.
Sonic movie, sure.
Yeah.
Go see it if you want to.
Okay.
Well, if I want to, then I will.
Like any, like if you feel like you're going to enjoy it, you will otherwise, you know,
you know exactly how you're going to feel about it by just looking at it.
You know?
It's one of those.
Yeah.
And for, for me, I'm, I'm good.
I'm good on that, but I won't judge.
I didn't even care.
But I got, I haven't seen my friend in a while.
I was like, yeah, fuck it.
Obviously Sonic.
Sure.
If I, damn, if I had a friend, and, and he invited me to see the Sonic the Hedgehog
2 movie, I'd be like, yes, please.
I'd be like, sure, I guess.
I'd be like, sure, buddy.
Why are we friends again?
Oh, well.
Come on, man.
Go see it with Munch and Kazi.
I don't know if they'd be, I don't force them to.
They watched, um, like last week they watched, uh, that Pinocchio movie.
Oh, no.
Because they were, because that trailer had come out where he goes, father, I have the
whole world to see.
I love that video.
And they were memeing on that.
And they were like, ha ha, what if, what if we watched it?
And then they were like, yo, Ben, you know, we're watching the new Pinocchio come over,
we're watching the new Pinocchio.
And I'm like, I don't actually want to watch that Pinocchio movie.
I'm not actually going to do that.
I have not found, I have not heard whether it was any good.
No feedback.
We'll have to, we'll have to see, wait for their, wait for their review.
Oh, well, well, I'm drained.
Voice mail time.
All right.
Uh, listen, if at any point it becomes too much to bear, I won't blame you.
If you, uh, just have to dip and leave me to it.
Okay.
You said that there's a lot of them and I'm betting that there's going to be one person
who sent like 10.
There's, there's, there's about 50 of them.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going, I'm betting a bunch of them are going to be from the same person.
Yeah.
That's, that's a safe bet.
All right.
I'll post them in general.
This one is called with killer, killer Prince 930, three, two, one, go.
Hey, I feel talk so I want to discuss.
I was going to clarify about wolf girl, but it seems like somebody I already searched
for it.
Uh, Ben, because of you, I watched even lock the movie of the guy on the card.
Yeah.
He's only on the card in the car.
Look, he's really, really good.
Thank you.
And you started to play a Hades.
Yes.
Do it.
Hades is the best.
Based.
But watch out.
Uh, doesn't matter who you are, Hades, you come out of it, gayer than you were before.
So it's kind of dangerous.
I mean, I am going to, I'm probably going to fuck.
Why do you think the implications in society would be if everybody had just big as wings
like this through structure, transportation, you know, what probably architecture would
be different.
We probably wouldn't have stairs.
Yeah, I suppose so.
Probably nests.
Nests.
Nests culture would be bigger.
You'd see a lot more posts from Nest Twitter, I think.
Probably probably wouldn't probably wouldn't have cars, probably wouldn't have roads.
No need.
No, yeah.
I reckon planes would still exist because then they'd be much more efficient.
Would they?
Well, we don't really need cars, do we?
Oh, I guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I feel like flying your, I feel like walking versus rolling, like cars are much, cars are
much faster.
Well, I guess planes are faster than birds.
Yeah.
Never mind.
I win.
All right.
You win.
Point to sin too.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's it.
We wouldn't have cars or stairs and that's what would happen.
That's it.
No other changes.
Everything else would be exactly the same.
Oh, you know how like people, like some people, like fetishized angels, it would be the opposite
where people fetishize people without wings.
No, that'd be like amputee pulling.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
What if we didn't have wings?
Ew, gross.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Oh, you could sleep on your back and it'd be comfy.
Damn.
Okay, next one is called Admit This Is Funny, 3, 2, 1, go.
I just made a video on it, so I don't have a video.
I just made a video on PCP7 or what I feel about it, whether it's like, I don't know.
It's hard to say.
It's just, it's just so complicated.
I need that man.
I need that man to cut through bullshit.
I need that man to put his hands together.
When you look at comments on like the lectures, like specifically, I look at the animarts
and we can see the lectures obviously, the ones I share.
And there's just tons of people being like, are they serious with misogynists?
And I'm just like, can you really not tell?
It's a joke.
Like, I don't even, I don't even remember.
Like, what are they talking about?
Like, there are some times when, like in the animarts when Nate was like saying, like,
I'm not a woman, wrote this law, but like clearly as a joke, and it happens like twice,
I think.
And it's just like, yeah, I don't know.
Like, uh, yeah.
So yeah.
So what, I guess, what is the, are they, are they really misogynist?
They really can't read the room at all.
And I'm like, I don't know.
I don't know.
It was funny. I'm a funny guy. I say funny things.
I would say that was decently funny. I'm an entertainer.
You got to recycle a full minute 30 of material there, Ben.
You didn't even have to do anything.
That's free content. That's free.
You know, when you're this funny, you don't even have to come up with new material.
You just get them to tell you to play the old stuff and you just do it.
You just do it.
Why not?
And it's good.
Next one is called Patrick Star. 3, 2, 1, go.
Fuck you and Saint. If you ever get with a woman, I'll be there.
The shadows waiting to cuff you. If you ever climax their self-stimulation,
I'll be there to collect your summons, which leads to fertilize a bird of woman.
Then you'll be on the Hooper Child support. That would be putting justice.
Thanks, Patrick.
Please don't do that. Please don't do that, Patrick Star.
Patrick, keep it up. You're doing great, buddy.
Okay. Well, he's just following orders, Ben. He's just following orders.
Who's orders?
Never you mind.
Okay. Wait, there's a YouTube...
There's a YouTube link in the next one.
Oh, boy.
This is the video, Secret Tips on Watching a Puppy That You Don't Know.
Should we watch the video first or the voicemail?
Yeah, it's seven seconds.
Okay.
Hey, guys. It's your boy, Brad Brad here. Today, I'm bringing you a secret on how to take care of your dog.
You play a lot of Call of Duty, then you take care of your dog.
Because every time you pet her, you'll go,
Sorry, man. Things got fucked up.
Subscribe to more tips on how to take care...
That was a cool dog.
Cool dog. Good dog.
Yeah, sure.
Sorry about the cone.
Let me see. All right. The voicemail, let's listen to it. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys. It's your boy, Brad Brad here.
Just letting you know that my videos are starting to get more views.
So, if I ever become a YouTube game, it's always sure to tell me audience to go
subscribe to PCP, BenSaint.com, no, Patreon.com, BenSaint.com.
Yeah, BenSaint.com.
Just give and take and play Fan of Revenge and to play Pumpkin Alley.
Oh, also, as usual, no Tom, no watch.
Okay.
Well, he won't know.
This guy's just shilling his channel.
Yeah. Yes. It worked. We watched the video of a dog.
Yeah, I guess.
Well, thanks for that, man.
I'll use that next time I watch it puppy that I don't know.
All right.
Next one is called Heat. Three, two, one, go.
All right, Ben. I got some, I got some heatwave.
Okay, thanks.
I think we found the post.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly. Okay. Next one is called Big News. Three, two, one, go.
Okay, next one is- That's right, everybody.
Keep wearing masks.
Keep wearing masks. Yes. Get your fourth booster.
And I'm not kidding. I will get it.
Ben, we don't need to watch the video of someone explaining that the Breath of the World has been delayed.
We got to watch the whole video.
No, we don't. Otherwise, how will we react to it?
I'll tell you, I knew it comes on screen and he says it's delayed.
That's it.
Okay, but I just think we got to watch the video.
Okay, watch all of it.
No, you're right. No, no video.
Watch the title, bro.
Uh, next one is called-
It's a minute 30. We don't need to watch it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, next one is called High Ben New Fan Here.
What do you think of plants versus zombies?
I've never played it.
Oh, it's kind of cool.
It's got a good song.
It looks fine.
Zombies go-
I know that the Shamblers and RFCK are plants versus zombies based.
Yes, good.
Next one is a YouTube link.
Nathaniel Bandy.
So, I got hacked.
What happened?
And it's eight minutes long and I'm not going to watch it.
Probably someone got Garling Houseed.
Yeah, you had a channel.
Oh, yeah.
You mentioned a channel that got Garling Houseed.
There's a channel called Lenors who did funny edits of a weird 80s video of a guy dancing.
Anyway, they got hacked by the exact same people that you guys did, the Ripple RFCP.
Yeah, like literally they got Garling Houseed.
It was the Ripple people.
Yeah, exactly.
I was like, no, no.
Yeah, that sucks.
Hope they fix it.
It's funny now in hindsight, but it sucks so bad.
I know.
I checked their Twitter and they were trying to get in contact with YouTube.
I hope they're all right, but Lenors, cool videos.
Maybe I should reach out and be like...
Yeah, maybe I'll send you a link once we're done.
Yeah, why not?
And then he'll be like, oh, this happened to you?
Oh, how are you guys doing now?
And then he'll look at our channel and be like, oh my god, it's a graveyard.
Oh my god, it's a wasteland.
Oh my god, no, this is my future.
No!
Next one.
Okay, well, there's a short voicemail to go along with this video link.
I'll listen to the voicemail first.
Three, two, one, go.
It looks like Trixty's doing rants again.
Evan, you should make a video where you expose her and be like, yo,
she didn't fulfill the most of her fucking rant.
So you guys shouldn't support her and fuck her.
What do you think?
I think it's genius.
I mean, I don't know.
People still think they're going to get what they pay for with Trixty.
Then like, I don't know, they've dug their own grave.
Yeah, I mean, anyone who can't see the pines for the fields,
what's the expression?
The pines for the fields?
Some of that, yeah.
Anyone who can't see, you're missing,
you're really missing the pinewood for the derby.
I was trying to be clever, but like anyone who's still like hanging around the yig stuff,
like you can't help them.
They're like flat earthers.
You can't convert them.
Honestly, true.
There's, yeah, I saw this, I don't know if it was this stream,
but like there was another yig stream and I saw,
there was a brief moment in one of these recent streams,
I think the latest one, not this one.
The one with Thu's thumbnail is the girl in the hat.
She, I forget how it came up.
Someone, some weirdo in the chat was saying like,
was saying to Trixie, like you just seem like a stupid ripoff of best guy ever.
And I'm like, okay.
And that was a weird thing to say.
And then later that same person was like, and this is great.
At least, at least he doesn't, you know, you're like,
you just seem butter, you just seem jealous.
At least he doesn't rub his gender in your face.
Oh my God.
At least, at least best guy ever doesn't rub his gender in your fucking face.
So this guy was based, obviously.
But somewhere talking about that, the subject of me came up.
Oh, no, no, it was someone said, someone mentioned Munchie.
Someone was talking about the PCP.
And Bird said like, Munchie, yeah, he seems all right.
I don't know about him though.
Because like he hangs out with Ben Sain, right?
So that came up.
He mentioned that.
And then the two of them, they sort of like nervously chuckled.
They're like, hey, yeah, that's not a good look.
Like, that's never good.
That's never good.
Ben Sain is bad.
Wait, it's not a good look?
I got to get out of here.
You got to get out of here, man.
You're looking a little sus right now.
But so they said that they did not elaborate.
And then some guy in the chat,
and this blew my mind.
I could not believe someone would actually say this.
This is like a parody.
If I was imagining like the dumbest, tricksy head take on me,
they said like Ben pretended to be not problematic.
Like Ben masqueraded is not problematic,
but really he was like the worst of them all.
Man, you didn't even pretend once.
Because I don't love tricksy.
I'm actually the most problematic at all.
I could not believe a person said that in like genuine whatever.
So that was great.
That's all that was, I don't know.
Just thought that was funny.
It was funny in like a tragic way.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's what I have to say about these streams.
Whatever.
Streams means the low on money, which is funny.
It is funny.
Give her 10 bucks if you want her to like mumble some shit
about something she doesn't know what she's talking about.
Oh, did you remember the tweet that was like,
oh, I need to make a negative anime video or something?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
She said I need to criticize something
because I'm just so good at criticism.
And that's why all my negative criticism videos
do better than my positive videos.
It's because I'm just so good at criticizing stuff.
It's not, yes, it's not that like,
that's always the case and everybody knows that like
hating on a thing gets more views than praising a thing,
like always.
It's not that.
I'm just such a genius at negative criticism.
I'm so good at it.
I just want to shout out Veil's response to that tweet
where he said, we have forgotten hate.
I thought that was funny.
I know that I made a whole video
where I sort of like vaguely alluded to the fact
that I'm like changing my whole personality
so that I'll only be positive now
because we need to remember love.
I know that I made a whole thing and like said that
and implied that about myself.
But actually, I need to like do like some clickbait.
So that's actually like at the window
and it didn't mean anything, lol.
It's time to start dumping on stuff again
because it's the only way I can make any money.
Ooh, I hate her.
She's so dumb.
Simsie, she's so fucking dumb
and people actually watch her and they nod and they go,
this is smart and they go, this makes sense.
I'm on board.
I'm on board with whatever this is.
This is a comprehensible.
She's so dumb that it's like,
it's like it just makes everyone else dumber
and they're with it.
It's a seeping dumb curse.
It is.
I don't know, is that an Elden Ring thing?
Sort of.
There's a seedbed curse.
I was close.
Okay, we'll go with that.
Seedbed curse.
That was intentional.
I didn't accidentally reference Elden Ring.
Does it turn you into a garden?
No, there's a man called the Dung Eater
and he infects corpses with the seedbed curse.
It sounds like Hollow Knight.
Yeah, except his name's the Dung Eater,
which is funny because it means he eats poo.
He does.
He really does.
Good for him.
Anyway, is the YouTube just a link to the whole stream?
Yeah, it's just a link to the whole stream.
Should we watch the whole thing?
Yeah, I think so.
It's only like three hours.
Oh, that rant was so stupid.
Well, I'm sure it was.
Hey, Trixie, can you rant about Dragon Ball Super retcons?
She would.
She would take some money.
Says, oh, actually, I don't really know anything about that.
I haven't watched it.
I think I don't watch shows anymore.
Thanks for the money.
There's like six people.
There's maybe like six people who are like
more invested in Trixie and Yig than a person should be.
There's like six people who will just throw $20.
You should just be like, I just love you.
I'm just so glad that you're playing Elden Ring.
I've been waiting to see you play Elden Ring for like,
I'm so happy to see this.
Before you said the throw $20 thing,
I was like, there's six people who are so invested in Trixie
that it's unhealthy.
And I was like, well, two of them are me and you.
Okay, eight people, but at least I don't give money.
I give money to the other people.
But I was just in like a sick way.
I was in like a cool go.
Yeah, yeah, sick, but good.
Sick in the head, but sick in the bed.
You know what I mean, homie?
They're sick in the head in the bed.
We're sick.
No, scratch that reverse it.
You're missing the pines for the fields here, man.
We're sick in the bed, but not with each other.
We're not, we're not gay.
We're not like Thanatos.
I was sick in your bed.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to fuck Thanatos later, but not in like a gay way.
God, you give him ambrosia and make him my boyfriend.
You keep bringing that up, but you seem pretty excited about it, man.
No, I'm just dreading it.
I'm like, oh, I got to do it.
Oh, I got to kiss that handsome man.
Fringe, am I right?
That handsome gray boy.
So look at those pecs.
Look at those, that Serratus anterior just bulging
out of his ribcage.
Disgusting, am I right?
There's a part two, actually.
So let's post, there we go.
Part two, three, two, one, go.
I might be wrong because I didn't watch those videos.
I watched a shit fucking content, but who knows?
Nobody knows.
You're not wrong.
Don't worry.
Nobody, nobody knows.
Nobody watches a fucking content, bro.
Those views, those view counts, we're cracking like 4K on a good one.
She just keeps putting them out and they just keep doing like 3K views, 4K views.
Any day now.
Next one is called, it's a YouTube link, whatever, three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, that's my my favorite YouTube videos here.
Make sure you like it, subscribe, and leave a comment.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to...
If you were right, it's the same guy.
Guest privileges and say voice jail.
I'm, I'm, if, he's on thin ice.
He's, he's on thin ice.
Anymore plugin.
And I think any more plugin and yeah, we'll just have no choice.
I'll have to become a cop.
But Benny's blowing up.
He said his videos are blowing up and he's gonna give you a shout out.
Well, I hope he does.
You know, I wish him, I wish him the best in that endeavor.
But if you fucking come around here again.
Yeah, I wish he, I hope he does it elsewhere.
Next one is called, best guy ever, isn't getting any more PC Patreon money.
Glad.
Speaking of PC Patreon money, I forgot to upload those bonus episodes that are in the can,
but I will, I swear I will do it soon.
Oh, Ben, you silly boy.
I know.
I am a silly Billy.
Anyway, three, two, one, go.
Now that Nate's not getting any PCP Patreon money,
expect the donations from us over at Trump Tower.
Yes, Nate.
No, watch.
Come on, thanks, Donnie.
I picked up like halfway through and I was like, is that Trump?
Hell yeah, my man.
Thanks, man.
Did you see, he made a, I saw a screenshot of him, you know, because he's off Twitter.
He's banned on Twitter.
So now he does these like email, like press releases.
Oh my God.
Like, and I saw one fairly recently and it starts out with just like an entire paragraph of him.
He says like, yes, it's true.
Yes, the rumors are true.
Yes, I golfed, I golfed a three under par on like a certain, on a certain, like playing,
playing with like such and such PGA tour.
It was three under par, it was wonderful.
It really happened.
Yes.
So the wind was against me too.
It was beautiful.
It was a beautiful shot.
It was almost a hole in one.
Absolutely.
Would have been a hole in one if the wind was with me instead of against me.
But yeah, everyone was very impressed.
It's true.
You've been hearing about it.
I'm here to confirm.
You've heard the rumors.
You heard them.
It's true.
It's all true.
Every single word of it, every single word of it is true.
I'm golfing.
I thought that was pretty good.
God bless that fucking monster.
Living it, living his best life.
Just a, just, just golfing, golfing with the stars.
Next, next one is called, wait.
Oh, the next one is just a YouTube link.
Oh, I saw that Cybershell put this video out, but I did not watch it because I have not seen
the first Sonic movie.
Me neither.
But if anyone is interested, yeah, Cybershell put out a video thoughts on the first Sonic
movie, so watch it perhaps.
I'm sure he was like.
I might watch it anyway.
I'm sure his opinion was it was a perfectly serviceable kids movie because that's everyone's
opinion of the Sonic movie.
It would make, would make, would make sense.
Next one is called, Trixie's Pride.
No, no.
Three, three, two, one, go.
I don't get why Trixie doesn't just change her channel name back to like Digi or Diginae
because like there is no more Yugi Studios.
Everybody's left and it's just her now.
And she's gone back to just making the exact same sort of anime.
Who, who could have seen it coming when she was Digi Bro?
Only, I think the recent ones are a lot worse.
IMO.
Nevertheless, like she would, she gets no views.
And I think she would get views if she just changed her channel name to Digi probably,
but she doesn't for some reason.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I mean, there's lots, I'm sure there's lots of people that see that logo and are like,
I don't know what this is.
Unsubscribe.
Uh, I won't, I won't unsubscribe or just, I'll never click it.
So you're probably right.
Well, the real.
Yeah, she had.
Yeah, yeah, go on.
The real answer is she's not playing that character anymore.
That's true.
Yeah, she's not.
Digi was a character long and she's not playing it anymore.
Digi was a character.
Trixie has remembered love until she needs to make a video shitting on something popular to make some money.
So, yeah, you fool.
Trixie has remembered love.
If she, if she were to rebrand to Digi, it would be admitting,
it would be admitting that by going back to making the exact same content as before and
everything else that she said she was going to do with Yeeg Studio failed,
it would be admitting that she's doing the same thing.
It would be like,
And obviously she's remembered love, so it's totally different.
It'd be like at the end of Avatar season two when Zuko's like almost turning good,
but then he betrays Aang at the very last second and goes by it again.
It would be, it would be precisely like that.
It would be exactly like that.
What would Riley say?
It would be, it would be a betrayal of Riley.
Yeah.
Riley's got, he's, he had Yeeg in his bio and now like,
I don't know.
He didn't have, he didn't have Digi in his bio.
They still make podcasts with each other.
I mean, they're basically still a thing.
I mean, it's not like Riley did anything in the first place.
They basically, they basically, yeah, they have their, right,
they do the podcasts that get like 200 views on Riley's channel.
I haven't, I mean, I haven't listened to anything.
Have we, have we talked about that?
I'm sure they're riveting.
Mint's art tutorials and specifically the comments on those.
Um, maybe, but like, I don't remember.
So I mean, I've seen one or two of those videos and they're very embarrassing.
Yeah.
But like, they're like, I was looking at the comments on them recently
and it is literally just all people saying like,
Oh my God, you're so cute.
What are you wearing and stuff like that?
Yeah.
So strange.
I think she looks like there's something wrong with her, honestly.
But that's, yes, that's just me.
I don't think she looks like she's got all her chromosomes.
Then she's got a low view count.
So she can't fucking say that, by the way.
She's got a low view count, which means that she's mine.
That's probably what they're thinking.
That's probably their brain process.
I, I, I, is, I mean, is that true?
Is it all just like comments about like, you're cute?
Yeah.
It's very funny.
And like some, it's like good episode and things like that.
Right.
Yeah.
I can't imagine the kind of person, I can't imagine the kind of person
who's like invested in like Riley's channel.
They, they uploaded a movie review every day for like a month.
And I have no, can you imagine?
I saw that that, well, I mean, I didn't see all of them,
but like I saw that someone mentioned that that happened.
Yeah.
Can you imagine being the kind of person who would watch every single one of those?
The kind, it's, it's not, I mean, I'm imagining that sort of person and it's not,
it's not a flattering.
It's not a healthy person.
It's probably someone who I would call them the lowest bottom feedingist,
like a social climbing like cloud chaser who like is below the floor.
Is at the very bottom and is like, I need to start somewhere.
Well, here's a guy who has like a third hand connection to a, to a famous podcaster.
So it's, I'll start by sucking up to him and then maybe I can climb the ladder.
I mean, that was always my plan with you,
like getting me friends with you, so I could be friends with Nate instead.
Right.
It was my, right.
And I mean, it was my plan with Trixie.
I was going to use her to get to Jeff and, and then, you know,
and then it all fell apart at Radcon and things were never the same.
Um, you know, I get it.
Like I get it, but, but that's, but that's, that's it.
That's the only kind of person I can imagine who's like commenting,
like nice, like nice upload, like good video.
I love those comments.
They're funny.
Yeah.
I'm glad they exist, even though I'm scared.
They're ubiquitous.
Yeah.
You always see them.
Uh, anyway, next, the episode, I mean, is called, uh, Forg Wizard.
Virginia Beach is bad.
Three, two, one, go.
So, uh, did you always use to talk about how much she loved Virginia Beach
and how great of a fucking location it was?
And I'm just going to, maybe just because I'm a Midwest boy,
but, uh, Virginia Beach fucking sucks.
I agree.
I've been there a couple of times now just visiting family or traveling there.
I've spent quite a bit of time there and God, it's hot.
It's sticky.
It is a tourist trap nightmare.
There's no reason to go there.
Did you, you are wrong.
You suck.
You are bad.
Also, the best city in this gosh darn country is Minneapolis, Minnesota.
I've never been.
Boston is up there.
It's pretty close.
You know, there's some good cities, but name a better city than Minneapolis, Minnesota,
and not St. Paul.
Fuck St. Paul, but Minneapolis.
The fuck is St. Paul?
Goddamn boys.
It's a damn good city.
I don't even know where St. Paul is.
I've never been to Minneapolis.
Um, I've been to San Francisco.
Easy answer, but I think New York is cool.
I've never been to San Francisco or San Diego.
It was neat.
Hmm.
I went on a tram and I was, I was too scared to go to Alcatraz because I was like seven.
So I went on a tram with my mom instead.
Wait, you were too scared to go on what?
Yeah.
My, my sister's two years older than me and her and my dad went to Alcatraz and did like a tour there.
Oh, right.
And I was too scared.
So I, I went on a tram with my mom and she bought me ice cream.
It was great.
Are you talking about like the trolleys like you see at the beginning of the room?
Yeah.
It was cool.
Those seem, those seem pretty nice.
And then we went skiing.
Seems like a nice thing.
Somewhere in Denver, I think.
I hate skiing.
I like skiing.
What a hassle.
I was really bad at it.
I always hurt myself really badly.
I almost beat up a cliff and died.
My, my cousin like, my cousin like went to the hospital one time that like we did
went on like a family ski trip.
He like, I think he like plowed into a tree or something.
I don't know.
He indeed, he had to go to the hospital.
He hit something.
I mean, I think he was fine, but uh.
I landed in a tree well upside down and almost, I almost drowned in snow
because snow was like sliding down my body because I was upside down in a tree well on a slope.
And it was fucking gonna kill me and luckily some random man saved me.
Jesus.
What do you mean a tree well?
A tree well is like, you know, when it snows and then like a tree, like around a tree,
there's like a funnel of snow.
It doesn't settle as much.
Oh, sure.
It's like a, like a dip in and I fell into that like backwards upside down.
So my head was pointing down the slope and I was in a tree well and then like the snow was like,
like soft powdery.
So it was like sliding down towards me.
And I was only like a little, I had skis on.
So I couldn't fucking move.
I've never heard of such a thing happening.
No, every time I've almost injured myself or almost died, it's always like such a hyperspecific
like stupid nonsense thing that takes like 10 minutes to explain.
Like fell into a big snow hole and the snow was too powdery and it just kept flowing in your face.
You couldn't just like push it away from your face.
Yeah, I was doing that, but I was getting tired.
I was there for like 10 minutes, 15 minutes, something like that.
And just screaming because there was like an offshoot of the ski slope where you could
like ski through the trees and like weave between them.
And I fucked up because I was bad at skiing and I fell up because nobody was going through it
apart from like the reckless kids looking for fun.
And I was just screaming and like nobody could hear me.
Fuck.
It was wild.
It's horrifying.
Yeah.
Oh well.
Boy.
Wait, what was the...
Oh, I don't like Virginia Beach.
It's not walkable, so it sucks.
It is a tourist trap.
It sucks.
Trixie just like decides she likes something.
She doesn't know anything, but she'll just be like...
She'll talk about it like an authority, but like it's just all she knows.
Like all she knew was Virginia Beach.
So she'd just be like, yeah, it's the best city.
I've decided it's the best city.
And here are my reasons and lists the only things she knows about it.
I don't know.
It's on a beach.
It's probably got a Wendy's.
It's probably all right.
I guess if you like the beach, sure.
Everything else sucks about it.
Mostly it's just not walkable.
I'll take your word for it.
Why would you live there?
Huh?
I'll take your word for it.
I don't know.
There's no...
I mean, there were some light rail.
There were some buses, but like not really.
So, uh, Boston, you don't need to own a car, so it's perfect.
Sure.
One more.
One more do you need?
Yeah.
Next one is called Yummy Yummy.
Did I already posted it?
Yeah.
Three, two, three, two, one, go.
It is the same guy.
They're all the same fucking guy.
I told you.
All right.
Cool.
Next one is not a voicemail.
It's a Twitter link.
Oh, I saw this.
Yeah.
I retweeted this on the endless war account.
That's a slime.
It's a robot made of magnetic slime.
I guess it's...
I don't know if...
I don't think...
Okay.
I think that it does not actually like contain any like
circuitry or computers.
I think it is controlled by external magnets.
Exactly.
That's what I thought when I saw it.
Yeah.
So it's this, but it's this slime that they use external magnets to manipulate into basically like
the idea is that it could like worm its way through your body and like remove foreign objects and stuff.
So it's just this gross little slime monster.
It's real.
And it looks, looks delicious.
It says in the video that like it needs to be tested to ensure...
Like it's, it's like the, it's made of a material, like the metal it's made of is toxic.
It's coated with this material that prevents that like toxic metal from, you know, getting into your body.
But like they need to test it to ensure that like it remains coated and it doesn't like leak the toxic stuff that's inside of it.
Is like why it's still...
Good, yeah, it's pretty neat.
I think this is going to be one of those things that just doesn't ever happen, you know what I mean?
I, I don't see it ever like becoming like widespread.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's pretty, but it's neat, but it's neat for sure.
It's funny.
It's green.
It's green slime as well.
It's a little bit green.
You've got to address it.
Yeah, it's greenish.
I, I, I retweeted it on the endless work.
What more do you want from me?
The community, no, the community has been made aware.
The next one is called God She Is Still Making Videos Help at gmail.com.
And it's a link to one of these Trixie videos that's got like 4k views.
Yeah, as I mentioned, she just, she'll just keep putting them out, I guess.
Sure.
I, I guess, do you think she'll give up eventually?
Will she just be like, it's just not working?
I don't think she has any other options.
I think she'll just stick with it.
What little she can.
Yeah, I think so.
I think, yeah, I think, I think.
For the foreseeable future, it would probably just be living off of the Patreon, like losers.
And whatever, whatever real job Bird has, if he still has one, I don't remember.
He used to have a job driving.
I don't know if he has one now.
Yeah, yeah.
Probably Bird will just pay for stuff and then Patreon will pay for stuff and she'll,
yeah, you're right.
Like what else, what else is she gonna do?
She's got nothing else to do.
Are they living in someone else's place?
I don't remember.
I don't know.
I know that they're living in Virginia Beach.
I am not sure if they're, I know they, I know they've historically mooched off of people.
Yeah.
But as of now, I'm not sure if that's, if that's the case.
Whatever.
I mean, if Bird has a job and she makes like, and she's still making Patreon money from people
that just have not checked their Patreon account in like four years, I think they could afford a,
they could afford some place in Virginia.
Yeah.
So I, but I don't know.
I don't think she should stop anytime soon.
Yeah, you're right.
She's got nothing else to be doing.
Yeah.
Human content machine.
The human content machine.
No, DigiPro is dead.
The DigiChannel is dead.
This is, this is a rap studio now.
YigStudio, it's going to be, we're going to be featuring like local musicians.
We're going to be on tour around the country, featuring rap artists.
We're going to be doing interviews.
We have an anime in production.
We're making an original anime, Simsie.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Actually, we're going to put those on Branches of Yig, which is another channel, by the way.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, those didn't work.
Those are going on Branches, but we're still making an anime.
Okay, and we're still the, we're still going to have, we still, we,
we got the colored thumbnails, right?
Oh, we, we, we're going to have, we're going to, we're still going to have music
movies and cartoon movies and movie movies.
I say we give up, we give up with the color thumbnails for now.
Oh, how about a music review show?
Okay.
Yeah.
But, oh, we got to put that on a different channel.
We got to put that on the other channel.
That's fine.
Okay.
So what are we left with?
Oh, anime reviews.
Anime on Yig Studio.
Yeah.
And then.
Okay.
But it's, okay.
All right.
This is the Yig Studio.
Yig Studio is now guys, guys, drumroll please.
Yig Studio, I am announcing that as of now I'm deleting all my old content, right?
All, I've got three weeks in three weeks.
I'm deleting all my old content.
It's going to be gone forever.
All my Yig content, I'm going to, instead, I'm going to be re-uploading all those old
Digi videos that I said I was getting rid of.
They're all back.
And Yig Studio is now drumroll please.
An anime review channel.
We're rebranding, boys.
God bless.
We're going for it.
We can make it.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's going to work out.
You know, I'm taking a big bold step into the unknown.
We have remembered, hey, everybody.
We have remembered, hey.
But I believe in my, I believe that with God at my side, with the power of God and
anime on my side, we shall prevail.
Hey, Trixie, review this.
Put some middle finger.
Hey, yeah.
Yeah.
Let there be carnage, bro.
Carnage, bro.
Next video.
I mean, YouTube.
I mean, next YouTube video.
Next YouTube link that we're not going to fucking watch and just talk about.
No.
It's, it's, it's called what?
It's short.
Thank God.
Here it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Looks like you're treating a cancel again.
Whatever you say, buddy.
Yeah.
True, true.
Next one is called, it's just text.
It says, Ben, you should do a lecture on T-Bap.
Unironically, I think a lecture on phantom horn slash T-Bap is not a bad idea.
And I might do.
I think I've had this idea before.
Yeah.
Either a lecture or maybe just a video explaining it.
Somebody has to explain it.
And nobody's going to do it if it's not me.
Um, so yeah, I agree.
I agree with this, uh, yeah.
Cause I mean.
At ride code five, we're announcing it here ladies and folks.
I mean, you know, much the idea behind the lectures is that like the best sort of lecture
is explaining a piece of media that is inaccessible for one reason or another.
What's more inaccessible than T-Bap slash slime and punishment?
Nothing.
Uh, it's, it's the most inaccessible thing I knew how to make.
So, so it's great lecture fodder, perhaps.
Tell you.
Next one.
Do it.
Do it now.
Okay.
Well, the, well, no, no, no, no, no, I would just, I would just read out the, the story so far
on the itch page of phantom, phantom explaining how he was just a mild mannered
somepony with a, with a YouTube channel until, until an inciting incident occurred
and she, and turned his world upside down.
Act one of the narrative began.
That's correct.
Uh, closing in on 400 downloads.
That's cool.
Or I think I'm at like 360 or something.
Once I've read Lord of Ghosts, next up is slime and punishment and then the game.
Oh, oh, I did, um, I did a poll.
I did a poll on Twitter.
I don't know if you saw, but, um, I asked people like what they're like, how, like,
whether they've played phantom's revenge and stuff.
The, the results were about 15% have played it and beaten it.
Another 15% have played it and not beaten it.
Uh, almost 50% haven't played it yet.
Uh, but if that's, okay.
But implying that they will play it or they intend to play it.
And then another 20% said they either aren't going to play it or they can't.
I assume some of those are just like, they can't play it because they don't have like a Windows
computer.
Uh, so some of those would hopefully play it because I'm planning on, on making, um,
I'm trying to pay a guy on Fiverr to, uh, to fix it for HTML and hopefully Mac, maybe Android.
Uh, I'm going to put it.
Yeah.
I don't want to do it myself.
I don't want to do that.
Yeah.
I'm just going to, I'm going to try and get a guy and just do it for me.
Uh, Matt, ideally I would get it on, um, working on Mac and Linux and Android and
in HTML.
HTML is the most important because that's how I've calculated.
Yeah.
On a TI 83 and switch on a black, on a blackberry, uh, get it on switch.
Obviously, obviously he's got it.
Everybody who plays fantasy event says this should be on switch.
Why isn't this on switch?
Yeah.
All right.
We are getting, we're like more than halfway through.
Okay, sweet.
We're probably, we're probably about halfway through.
Well, half of them are going to be the same guy, so it's fine.
Probably.
Next one is, uh, let me find my place here again.
It's called Masha Tick, Tick, Tick, Tick, Venova three, two, one, go.
Is this, is this in Russian?
I do not know.
Oh.
Is that your baby in the background?
No, that's not the voicemail.
I feel a jump scare coming.
You won't take when saying they aren't real.
They were real, but they left after trips left.
Oh, I can't follow it.
I, I feel like I could understand it if I really focused, but I just,
I just can't.
I just can't pay attention.
Somebody transcribe that, put it in the comments.
It's too annoying.
It hasn't, why does it have intentional background?
To make it feel real.
That was surreal.
What the fuck was that?
There was like a concept going on there.
Good voicemail.
And it just totally failed, just completely failed at whatever it was trying to do.
There was a cat that got shot by a Gatling gun, and that's all I could really tell.
And they said Ben saying.
There was work put into that voicemail to absolutely no end whatsoever.
Next one is called, where am I?
Where am I?
Oh God.
Well, there's an image to go along with it.
Here's, here's the image.
Okay, this time, this time listen to the voicemail.
He says, listen to the voicemail first.
Okay.
Oh God, I got a couple of L's.
Here's a voicemail.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
So, you were wondering why it is better to have nothing in the code affect anything else.
Same reason, you want to have different colors on different layers when drawing.
To have control in case something doesn't work out as planned.
Yeah, I looked up tight coupling and I understood.
To fix one bug doesn't snowball into a bunch of other bugs.
Expect trouble to prevent trouble.
Speaking of trouble.
It seems Twilight Sparkle voice finally died.
I am unbelievably sad, yet you can't even hear it.
I guess I will just have to create my own deep fake.
Um, who should I pick?
Someone with bright and emotional voice, yet thoughtful and competent.
Oh, I think I know just a person.
Just listen to their voice.
Music to my ears.
Hey folks, how's it going?
Today I am talking about the newest film from Pixar called,
Turning Man.
Yes, this is perfect.
From here on out, call me.
Liquid, Saber Spark.
Ah, okay, I see.
Okay, I see now.
That was a lot though.
Yeah, it came together.
The image is Liquid Saber Spark.
And it says.
Wear shades.
Yes, bitches.
Wear shades in the dark.
Trench coat, naked body in Alaska.
You are a loser.
Doesn't wear a mask, doesn't need to breathe.
Hairs are literal, sun, plasma.
Okay.
Liquid, sure.
I hate Saber Spark's cadence.
Honestly, I don't like it, but I don't, I don't,
I don't honestly feel that strongly about it.
This is the strangest movie I've ever seen.
All YouTubers sound like, well, not all of them.
All bad YouTubers sound like that.
Okay, next one is called, Biden weighs in on the
trans-racial question.
Yes.
Three, three, two, finally.
Three, two, one, go.
Look, fat.
Transmortialism is ridiculous, believed me.
Raises the social construct arbitrarily categorizing
certain verbal things.
Weak sex.
And now social construct degrades new arbitrary categories
on a thinner gender.
Senior truth of blackness.
It's like, senior trends, amen.
Thanks, Biden.
Thanks, thanks for waiting.
Ben.
Thanks, Biden, for being against all those fucking psycho bills they're trying to pass
right now.
I appreciate it.
He said, look fat, which is the one thing I know about Biden is that he said that.
Look fat.
Yes, it's the one thing I know.
Well, he hates British people.
Yes.
Thank God.
Yeah.
Woo.
He's Irish.
Genuinely same.
He doesn't like what's going on with you guys.
No.
I wonder if that's why he's being a little, he's being a little cool about trans stuff
right now.
It's just because he hates GK rallying so much because she's British.
I clout.
Thank God.
Next one is Ben's weekly reminder play Delta Rune chapter two.
I will one of these days.
You've done one piece.
Now you have to do Delta Rune.
I did one.
Yeah.
I can only do so much.
I read one piece, which is the hardest thing in the world.
It sucks and it's been ruined.
It sucks and it's bad.
And Luffy, it's not it.
What do you mean?
It wasn't the Gomu Gomu No Mi.
I was only reading it because I thought it was rubber.
Now everything's different.
Oh, now you hack.
You've ruined the story.
Oh, do you hack?
I was reading for the rubber.
You took it from me.
Ben, you're turning it to your brother.
If he wasn't made of rubber, then why couldn't Enel shock him with the lightning fruit?
Oh, no.
What do you mean?
He's a son.
What?
Get it.
Sure.
That's every talking parts stream, by the way.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I have not seen any of it.
I just have heard that Nate does not like goofy Luffy.
He does not.
Why?
He's not keen.
Just the destiny shit, really.
Just the destiny shit?
I mean, sure.
I don't like that.
I don't love that either.
Yeah.
It's just this is...
There's so many...
This is such like just one more in a long line.
There's so much more to life than you could have been.
There's just one more thing in a long line of things where I've been like, oh, so they've
got a special destiny, huh?
Well, all right.
Next chapter.
A thousand chapters later.
Me reading chapter like 200 or being like, wait, so Shanks was one of the four emperors
the whole time?
Oh, Luffy had a special destiny this whole fucking time.
He knew one of the four most important people in the world?
Honestly, honestly, yeah, even that, even that, it's like, oh, so Shanks.
His brother was the son of Gold Roger?
What the?
That's...
That sucks.
Oh, genuinely, yeah, that does suck.
Honestly, yeah, finding out Shanks was like this really important guy instead of just
like a cool dude that he knew when he was a kid.
It's like, boo, boo, boo, genuinely, I don't like it, but like that ship has sailed, no
pun intended.
Dad is the leader of the Revolutionary Army and he has like no lines of dialogue in the
entire series.
He's got no what?
He's got like no lines of dialogue.
Dragon doesn't do fucking anything.
Has he?
Yeah, he's spoken like once, yeah, I think.
I'm sure we'll see him, but like whatever, it's fucking funny.
He'll hug his baby boy and explain the law to him.
He will probably, yeah, I think so.
I think that's probably right.
The Revolutionary Army must be a pretty big fan of Joy Boy.
Yeah, sure.
That's kind of good.
That's probably going to work out well for them, I guess.
Whatever.
Whatever, yeah.
I'll just consume product and then wait patiently for next product.
I don't want to think about it, I just want to see it and go, mmm.
I remembered love, so I like Nika now.
That's right, that's right.
I remembered love.
Nate just has to remember love.
He does.
Like me.
Next voicemail is called Tom Part Two, three, two, one, go.
Okay, I got an idea of what Tom's actually doing in Virginia.
He's there to start the Lazy Guy's podcast, in other words, the new PCP.
Just in spite of you, Ben, he's going to invite Gibb to it, he's going to bring Jesse
back, Taboo's coming back, what's his name, Mother's Basement's coming back, aw yeah.
Why is it called the Lazy Guy's podcast then?
Because they don't make any things.
Jeff is a hustler.
Oh yeah, Jeff is a hustler.
He can't be on.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know about that.
Gibb can't be on either.
Gibb is also, wait, why would you move to Virginia to start a podcast with Gibb?
Yeah, what?
I don't think you thought this voice mail through Ding Dong or whatever your name is.
Next one, silly boy, silly lads, who's the Lazy Boy now, huh?
Next one is called Message to Mr Slim Time, three, two, one, go.
Hey, to the guy, the slime time guy.
Prince.
I don't know, you're down to my trap sucker.
Fuck off.
Well, honestly, I'm thinking voice jail.
Yeah.
What was that?
What are you talking about?
Shut the fuck up, I'm done, I've had enough, I'm up to my fucking eyeballs.
I'm over it, he's a total loser, get rid of.
That was good.
Take him out.
Even the, Merry Christmas, what is it like, Merry Christmas to everyone, yes, even the
losers and haters.
I like what he called that guy a proven loser, that's a good phrase.
Who did he call a proven loser?
I have no idea who called it, but he says like, he's a loser, he's a proven loser.
That's a good, that's a good thing to call someone who loses all the time.
A proven loser.
It's the next one just a drill tweet.
Yeah, the next one is just a drill tweet.
I have, oh, I see, oh no, no, no, there's a caption.
It's called YIG colon, and then the drill tweet, oh, I get it, I get it, yeah.
So it's like, this is, this is, this is the, the rebrand to YIG.
It's as though Trixie said, so long suckers, I rev up my motor, motor slice and create a
huge cloud of smoke when the cloud dissipates, I'm lying completely dead on the floor.
This is one of my favorite drill tweets.
I love this one.
Solid.
Yeah.
I'm keen.
I like it.
Yeah.
Okay, it works.
Next one is, next one is called Autism Speaks She-Her, she slash her, okay, 3, 2, 1, go.
Trixie, from my amusement, tell me your deepest, darkest trauma, or simply flounder, lamal.
I'll just flounder, thanks.
One time, I pooped my pants at school, and everyone laughed at me, the first day of primary
school, a bee flew in my ear and stung me inside of my ear and I've always been terrified
of bees and wasps, like horribly, because of that.
I would also be terrified.
And also school, because that happened on my first day of primary school.
Jeez.
I'm trying to think, is there anything that I'm afraid of because something bad happened
with them?
No, nothing bad's ever happened to me.
Sorry.
Yeah, I'm kind of a cool guy like that, nothing bad ever happens to me, you know.
I guess you're just a proven loser.
I guess you just took the L with that B, you little child.
I suppose so.
Yeah, that happens, I guess.
Next one is called, oh, here we go, The Ben St. Dream, from hardpissaprilatdustydumps.com.
Good name.
3, 3, 2, 1, go.
I had a dream that Ben St. bullied me over my tiny Tokyo apartment.
Why would he do such a thing?
Because you're a bitch, because you're a proven loser.
Because it's small and that sucks.
Nice tiny apartment, nerd.
How many tatami mats he got in here, like four and a half?
You fucking biatch.
Why don't you commit harakiri?
Oh, boom.
Which means hurting yourself in Japanese.
This is the guy who does the songs and stuff.
He was also the same guy who sent me that torturous voicemail about how to upload a podcast to Spotify.
So I would say that those two things cancel out and he's neutral now.
Um, suck it, nerd.
Remember the pig?
Freddy Krueger.
The pig?
Yeah.
I kind of missed the pig.
I thought the pig was coming on that Russian one.
I thought there was going to be something.
I see what you mean.
It was so boring.
It's going to shock me with something, but it didn't do it.
No pig.
Next one is called In Defense of Ben's Bad Programming.
I have not done the thing where I post my source code on my Patreon yet.
I'm going to do that.
I just haven't gotten around to it.
Three, two, one, go.
There's a voicemail last week calling Ben a dunce for tying the damage checks in Phantom's Revenge to the animation,
and they're right in that it's good practice to avoid that sort of thing,
but like 90% of game development is about recognizing what shortcuts or concessions you can take
to avoid stretching your time and resources too thin,
lest you never end up finishing the project.
And this is doubly so considering Ben started out knowing basically nothing about his development environment or the process.
Of course, you have to take the needs and scope of each project into account,
but he did that and all it resulted in was a bug so minor,
it was only noticed when I documented my run in extreme detail
and double checked all the math to make sure I wasn't making any mistakes.
So I think we can afford him a few lines of spaghetti code in exchange for a finished game.
Also, hey, hey, hey, now that the PCP is officially a game development podcast,
I've said before and I'll say again that you should organize a PCP game jam.
It's really easy to create one on itch.io.
Maybe it could be like a week or two instead of 48 hours to be flexible with people's schedules.
You could do a shekels for heckles where you played jam entries.
It could be themed however you like or with no theme at all.
Maybe nobody will participate, but hey, I'd like to at least.
Those are some good ideas, actually.
That was a well-presented voice mail.
I'm impressed by how eloquent and fast that was.
Yeah, I think, and I don't mean to toot my own horn,
but I think you were correct that like, yeah, maybe my code's not optimal,
but it works, so like whatever.
I did what I had to do to get it working and guess what I did.
If it works, it works.
I think this is I'll Die.
I think this is...
I think it was I'll Die who found that bug, so I think this is I'll Die.
Sure.
I hope I'm not wrong.
Good voice mail, I enjoy it, even though I have no idea what you're talking about.
Organizing a game jam.
Honestly, honestly, that's kind of a compelling idea.
PCP doing something outside of recording podcasts? Who would it be?
And I've never even considered it before,
but since we're all gamesmen now, it kind of makes sense,
and maybe we could do it.
I guess you can just do it on itch.
I don't always have to look into how you do it,
but I'm listening.
Good voice mail, if you can believe an actually good voice mail.
Oh my God.
In the sea.
In the sea of utter crap.
In this utter garbage.
That's a fucking filth.
Next one is called,
and also video game more like video come.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, I left the voice mail last week about Pyre,
but I want to second the other person's voice mail about Transistor.
It's the game that turned me into a super giant stand.
It's super short, it's super dense,
and everything about it makes me come,
and it will make you come too.
Sounds good. Maybe I should try it.
I was thinking about playing Transistor.
I saw it's got a lady in it,
and it's by the Hades guys.
So I was like, yeah, go on.
I didn't know hardly anything about it.
You know, I saw Bastion, and I was like,
okay, it looks all right.
And then I saw Transistor, and I was like,
oh, it's a new one by those guys.
Yeah, it looks all right.
It means I like Hades a lot. That's cool.
And you describe it as short and dense,
which are two of my favorite things a thing can be.
So that's good.
You're talking my language right now.
All right, I'm thinking about it.
Hell yeah.
You're giving me a lot to think about this week.
I'll die. Well done.
Next one is called Transracialism
from Sonic3oST at gmail.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Michael Jackson is pretty much transracial.
How could you forget about him?
Yeah, I guess so.
They said is instead of was.
That's true.
I don't know if he ever said anything to that effect
or what his opinion about any of that was.
I'm not sure.
Maybe he would have said something relevant,
and I just don't know.
Did he claim to be white or something like that?
I don't know.
I think I heard something about it just being trying
to distance himself from his family.
I know he wasn't too keen on his father and stuff.
That's why I remember.
God, that is horrifying though.
Okay, serious question.
Why is he the only human being I'm aware of
that did that to himself?
Why is he the only one?
It is really weird, isn't it?
Super fucking weird.
If he didn't exist, you wouldn't know it was possible.
No, that's right.
Same with Elon Musk and hair transplants.
Face, face, face.
Yeah.
Damn, when you really think about it,
it's a little weird and horrifying,
and I'm confused now that I think about it.
I don't know how it happened or why.
I remember when I was a kid,
somebody just said he got in a big patch
of big tub of bleach inside there for a few hours.
Like Too Faced, but he fell all the way in.
Yeah, yeah.
And he did it on purpose because he hated himself or something.
I don't know.
That's what I heard when I was like six.
I mean, sure, I guess.
Anyway, what was the question?
I don't know, whatever.
Why didn't you bring up Michael Jackson as a transracial person?
I don't know.
I didn't think of it.
Stupid.
Why do you think I didn't think?
Okay, next voicemail.
Listen to the baby's words.
They will not be repeated.
From Gibby, you are just the cutest
at kissybwisseykissue.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, mate.
The baby says first words.
Oh, god, the baby.
Now he won't shut up.
Nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh.
Fuck you, bin.
Here to summer.
Fuck the name of bin the saint.
It is a samurai of the Kawasaki clan.
I was born of revenge.
Excellent disguise.
Revenge, I will enact on you bin the saint.
For stealing scroll.
Had you double checked, they find the print and scroll.
You would have seen this technique
of being reborn
through a baby.
Now I will exact my revenge on you bin the saint.
Son, in the body of a baby.
Until next time.
Fuck the name of bin the saint.
Nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh.
So the samurai's powers have been expanded
to he can be reborn as a baby
and also return to the baby form at the end.
He is, he is, okay, I guess in real life
May and Ethan's baby is canonically the samurai.
Oh, I didn't even catch that.
That's, okay.
Yeah, that was Ethan, that's Ethan.
Okay.
So I like it.
Yeah, okay.
The baby is fucking, he's back for my ass.
And I don't know how, I don't know why
I thought I was gonna get away with it.
How's the samurai saga been going on now?
Gotta be more than a year, maybe two years.
Yeah.
Something like that.
I'm not sure.
I don't think that's the same samurai.
I think there's an idea of a samurai.
There's an idea of a samurai.
I know the original samurai is like,
has like COVID and pneumonia right now.
So I feel like maybe that wasn't them.
But I think I like this lore and I'm just gonna roll with it.
Did you see, I mentioned it in my discord,
the new goss about Ethan.
I think they just got married.
I think like they just got married.
Yeah.
Also, I saw someone punching him in the face.
I saw that somewhere.
I didn't watch the video, but I heard there was a video
of him getting punched in the face.
I know they were gonna get married at a bowling alley.
So I assume that that video is from the wedding.
Yeah.
So I guess they're married now.
He was wearing a cowboy hat that said fed on it.
No, no.
He's wearing a cowboy hat and a shirt that said fed on it.
That is wedding, I guess.
I just heard that he date raped somebody.
Yeah.
That's the big one.
And that just came out like a little bit before the wedding.
But like the wedding just continued.
It's like, fuck it.
But apparently he date raped a woman in Vegas
while Mae was pregnant.
So...
But that's fine, whatever.
We'll just get married.
So life marches on.
Life marches on.
The show must go on.
You got to break a few eggs, you know?
To remove some samurai's.
Exactly.
Next voicemail is how do you get good at Hades?
You just played a lot.
Anyway, three, two, one, go.
You beat it already, I heard.
How do you deal with the fact that everything you do
creates a huge right wave of energy?
What?
Be it waves with Poseidon or blades with Aries,
no matter how you play.
By the end you literally can't see enemies,
so I die from something I could never see coming.
No.
I reject your hypothesis.
I don't think that's true.
I mean, I kind of know what you...
I mean, by the end of the game, I am often not really like...
I'm usually not like focusing on an individual enemy
and like fighting them.
I'm usually like jumping into a group of enemies
and just exploding all my abilities as fast as I can.
Do as much damage in as many places as possible.
They're just dashing to not be hit.
Yeah, late in a run there is definitely a lot of visual clutter,
but at that point you're putting out so much damage.
If you've built it well enough to not be able to tell
what the fuck is happening, you're probably doing alright.
The only time I'm really worried about like,
oh, where are the enemies,
is usually in Elysium against the Great Shields
because I have to make sure I'm behind them.
But other than that,
I'm just jumping into the fucking pack.
I guess I try to keep away from like the chariots.
And the game has pretty good lock-on,
like most of your time to build land unless you're playing with mouse and keyboard
in which case you have to be a bit more precise.
Not every...
I mean, a lot of the times my best builds are not like shooting energy everywhere.
A lot of my best builds are just about like,
put everything, put all my boons,
just buff my attack.
So I just spam my basic attack.
That's how you get good.
Yeah, I'd say focus on either special or attack
and dump everything into that when you can.
Just pick one, depending on what you're using.
Cast maybe sometimes, but I don't really...
I don't really like casting Hades.
I don't know. I used to get to do that.
Usually the most useful thing about casting
is that it embeds the Bloodstone, which gives me the damage boost.
That's usually what I use.
I use it on bosses, but like during normal gameplay, I don't follow it usually.
Sometimes I like it when I have...
When you have a good thing like Trippy Shot or the Zeus,
like cast like Bouncing Chain Lightning,
sometimes I like to have that...
It deals pretty good damage and a lot of times it can clear out a crowd pretty easily.
So sometimes I'll use it for that.
I've had one or two runs where I've just done focus casting,
just buff my cast as high as I can.
It works.
Yeah, fair enough.
Anyway, just focus all your boons.
Try and focus your build on something and just go really hard
and buffing that thing and then just spam it.
Yeah, don't spread out your stuff.
Keep it concise and make one thing real good.
Yeah, that's the way to do it.
Also, just grind darkness if you need a bit of a boost and level up at the mirror.
Grinding darkness, important.
Also, get the Hades aspect of...
What's the Spear's name?
Val something, the Eternal Spear, whatever.
Get the Hades aspect is the best.
Use the Spin Attack.
What he said.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Fucking...
The Arthur aspect.
It's so cool.
It's just so fucking cool.
He stands different.
When he has the Arthur aspect of the Stygian Blade,
he doesn't have his usual stand.
He stands perfectly straight and he holds the sword up with a great sword
in a different stance.
Like guts.
Yeah, kinda.
Sweet.
A little bit.
Okay, next voicemail.
I'm losing my place.
That was 39, so number 40.
Oh, it's a Vokeru.
It's called Agree or Disagree.
Here's the link.
Wait, are you ready?
Yep.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
What would be nice if Ben was gay?
Well, we got good news.
Ben is gonna go on Hades tonight.
I'm gonna fuck Thanatos eventually.
Fuck his step, bro, so you got your way.
And I do agree it would be nice.
It would be nice if only.
Well, it's like I always say, you know,
I've always preferred men sexually,
but unfortunately I'm just not gay,
so I just can't do anything about it.
So it's sad but true, you know,
so I'm with you, voicemailer,
but some things are just not meant to be.
Some rules were meant to be broken though, Ben.
I don't necessarily know if that's true.
I think some social...
What's the phrase I'm looking for?
Some...
Expectations?
What's the constructs?
What's the thing that they call...
Some social constructs are meant to be
abided by unquestioningly.
True!
Sleeping in a bed?
Everyone does that.
Pooing in a toilet?
Now we're talking.
Go goblin mode.
What are you gonna poo in a sink?
I'm gonna shit in my bed and sleep in my toilet.
Yes!
That's the way.
Next one is called Sad Man.
Three, two, one, go.
I have just broken up with somebody.
Give me advice to feel better.
Is this a shrimp guy from laughing, smiling friends?
Sounds a little bit like him,
but I think that's just what English people sound like then.
Oh, fuck.
That's racist.
You broke up with someone.
Consume media you have previous attachment to
that gives you the one-fuzzies.
I don't know.
Yeah, that is that.
Just fucking do something cool.
Do something fun.
Yeah, do something epic.
Do a cool skateboard trick and then...
Yeah.
Do some shit that you didn't do.
Do some shit that's cool that you didn't do with your
former partner and then be like,
well, they sucked actually.
We never did this stuff.
Do something that they tried to do,
but they were really bad at it,
but then you do it way better and you go,
yeah, they did suck.
Why do I even care?
Yeah!
That's what you do.
Just make yourself hate them.
Just convince yourself they're the worst fucking person in the world.
That's what Ben did with Trixie.
It seems to work.
So, when we broke up, we ended our passionate romance.
Just fuck a bunch of whores.
That'll cheer you up.
Fuck a bunch of whores.
Yeah, I mean, why not?
Take a load of drugs.
Sure.
Drive to the wrong side of the road with a whiskey bottle.
Now, hold on.
Now, hold on a second.
We're getting far afield.
Buy a load of amiibos and then sell them for an exorbitant price.
Have you considered committing suicide in Minecraft?
Cheers, yeah.
And then you go, that doesn't feel good.
That'll make you feel better.
I wouldn't do that in real life.
If you're inconsolably unhappy, you know,
the sweet decor of the grave beckons.
In Minecraft.
The sweet oblivion.
Not in real life.
In Minecraft, of course.
If you ever feel really sad, let yourself lose a run of Hades right at the end
and then you'll be like, damn, why was I sad about that other thing?
Yeah, just, you're stupid.
You're stupid ex never fucking built, you know, an all Artemis.
You know, just critting everything.
There's so much damage on that fucking Artemis' call, you know.
It's insane.
Just eats Hades' entire health bar.
Read chapter.
You think she could do that?
They could do that?
You never, never.
Read chapter 1045 of One Piece and go, look at it.
Get online and then get online and go, I can't fucking believe it's not rubber.
That'll take your mind off.
Yeah, there's lots to be, lots to get excited about right now.
It's a good time to be single.
Talk to a friend, I don't know.
Yeah, I mean, I guess if all else fails.
If you fail to distract yourself with product and media.
We covered all the bases there.
Yep, that should be all you need.
And that's all you need.
In that order.
You should be all set.
Okay, next, we have about, I think we have about a dozen to go.
So, we're getting there.
Next one is called, how are your three, two, one go?
Hey guys, how are you doing today?
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
I'm actually, I'm actually starting to feel very strange about this man.
At least it was short.
But next one is very strange about this man.
That's how I feel about Thanatos.
That's what I said.
Every time I see his bulging trapezius muscle just exploding out from behind his muscular arm.
He goes, hello, Zag.
That could hold me if he were so inclined.
Sure.
Hey, Zagman.
Hey, how are you doing?
Hey, drink some wine, bro.
Why don't you drink some wine?
My bro.
He says, you're a proven loser.
I won the competition.
You know, when you go in the room and you have to kill more enemies than him?
Hey, yeah, yeah.
He calls you a proven loser.
He does.
Yeah, I remember that.
It just made me want to date him even more.
He want to turn the game off and then can play about one piece of Chapter 1045 on the Internet.
He just gave me something to prove.
Next one is called, did I post it there?
Yes, I did.
It is called, my evil plan is underway.
Three, two, one, go.
I can't do it.
I can't fucking do it.
I'm doing voice jail ding dong for voice jail.
It's over.
No more.
Goodbye.
The end.
I'm not laughing.
Put a wax seal on that and smell it to the king.
An ignoble end for this nonsense.
I'm irritated.
I'm in a bad mood.
Is that what?
Yeah, ignoble.
It is a word.
It is.
Ignoble.
Yes, ignoble.
Like a noble from the gig studio.
Yes.
IGN, OB, whatever.
How would you say the opposite of noble?
Unnoble.
Im noble.
No honor.
Non noble.
Ignoble.
There's a word for it.
Oh sure.
Go on.
Lecture me some more.
About the life which I invented.
And we perfected.
Next one is called, I don't know, it's a link studio project image made on cap, cap wing.
Is it a video?
Okay, it's me.
Oh, it's me from the documentary with my like face that I didn't complete shaving correctly on.
Where you just have just the neck beard.
Yeah.
And it's Obi-Wan Kenobi looking at it.
Is that Obi-Wan Kenobi?
Yeah, that's from the trailer for the new Star Wars TV show.
Listen, I know I look terrible.
I don't know why I only shaved half of my face that day.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm not trying to make excuses.
I can't even tell what this image is meant to convey.
Like is he like upset?
Or is he like what?
Yeah, he's not.
I think he's probably saying what?
Yes, in that you and the Gregor sort of way.
What?
Ben Shave hasn't shaved his face.
He's right.
It's confusing.
I agree.
You should have used the picture of naked snake with the binoculars.
We're smiling.
Idiot.
Oh, yeah.
We scroll.
No, image.
Liquid Saber Spark.
Yeah, use this image.
Oh, wait.
That's you.
Sorry.
Okay.
No, that's yes.
There we go.
Much, much better.
Next one is called great artists steal greater artists outsource.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben St.
So I think you should publish your game.
That'd be a fun exercise.
Yeah, I think you should just take care of your copyright issue.
So, you know, just go on Fiverr, you know, get someone to make a legally
version of the song when it's like Bobby Prince.
You know, it's still sounds like it.
So it hits the proper beats.
Yeah, I know what a sound like is legally distinct.
Yeah, boomed out of being done.
Anyway, peace out.
So lame.
It's so lame.
Like, uh, make a song that sounds exactly like this other song.
Please.
It's like, it would be bad.
It wouldn't be as good.
Like when you get commissioned, they send you a reference image of the character
in the exact pose that they want.
And it's like, well, what the fuck?
What do you need me to draw it for?
What do you need me to draw it again?
There, there it is.
You have it.
It's probably better than what I can do.
Uh, sure.
Um, this, I, yeah, I mean, you're not the first, you're not the first person
to give me this advice, but I, it's stupid.
So fucking stupid.
I don't know.
I, I think, I think I might just say fuck it.
And just like make an account, like make a new steam account.
What's the worst that would happen?
What's the worst that would happen if I like put it on steam?
It gets taken off steam.
They don't let me post it.
They get, it gets taken off of steam.
Like, okay.
Well, I guess I could just, that if that happens, then maybe I could make some sound
in the like songs and re, re-post it.
I guess.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Uh, I don't know.
I just seems dumb.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to do this.
It seems, it honestly seems more dishonest to be like, hey, some guy make me a song that
sounds exactly like this other song, but is legally distinct.
And then put that in the game versus just putting that song and then in the credits
being like, yeah, I stole this music from this other game.
It feels more like stealing.
Because it's like, it's like when you make a forgery of a famous painting.
Yeah.
Replace it.
It's so dumb.
I mean, I understand that maybe this is the kind of thing that you have to do to get around
copyright issues.
But this is why we should just abolish copyright.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
The next one is from son of Marowak.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
I just watched an aesthetic critic video for the first time in two years.
Nice.
Big mistake.
Sorry, man.
Yeah.
Hummer.
You don't get better.
This is not, it will not improve.
Uh, next one is that Tommy Oliver voicemail was pretty funny.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So, you know, it's a little bit like a voicemail.
That's your good, huh?
Maybe.
He may be even boys.
What do you think?
Okay.
Bye.
Thanks.
Whatever.
What was that?
The five notes of Freddie's ambient fan noise in the background?
Why?
Was it like, was he meant to be like jacking off?
I don't know.
Was he, was he trying to give the impression that he was jacking off while making this voicemail?
Good for him.
Or them.
Or they them.
There you go.
Much better.
Now, now you're learning.
I'll get there eventually.
Now we're learning, understanding, finally, you're becoming human.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about that, but sure.
Story, story from North America.
What the hell is North America?
Here's a story from North America.
There's both cup and taken outside.
No.
Okay.
Give knows what I'm talking about.
Sure.
I'm sure she does.
I don't.
I don't even know what Digimon is really.
I'm sorry.
What?
It was a media property.
That's it.
Thanks.
That's the answer.
Now I'm informed.
Okay.
Now you know.
Next one is called, I was kidnapped.
Someone please help.
Oh God, I can't take it.
Three, two, one, go.
I think, I think they left.
Please, someone, they kidnapped me.
Please, someone come.
I thought you were my friend, but it seems we have a snitch.
Okay.
Then you will be with my pet and pets need training.
Engaging the one protocol.
No, no, no.
111.
What did I just said?
Okay.
So I guess that explains why the fan, I guess.
No.
I guess that explains something.
He was kidnapped.
No.
Let him out.
Okay.
There was a DS again there.
I guess.
Come on.
Just be cool.
Was that Twilight?
It was Twilight Sparkle.
Okay.
I'll take your word for it.
Next one is called, what about sponsors?
Three, two, one, go.
And finally, I want to give a big, big shout out to Surfshark for sponsoring this video.
If you've been living under a rock or something and you don't already know, Surfshark is one
of the best Nord VPNs out there.
So if you're ever looking to learn the skill or build a website, head to the description
of this video and hit the link audible.com slash CJDX and you can get started right away
with hundreds of champions from 14 playable factions.
I've already saved $50 on purchases just from the last month.
It's genuinely my favorite pair of headphones now.
I really recommend them.
So yeah, thanks for watching to the end.
Let me know in the comments what you want to see me do next.
No promises.
I can't do everything, but I do read everything and I love hearing from you guys.
I guess that's it.
Try to be nice to yourself.
I'll see you next time.
Bye.
That's great.
Is CJDX a real YouTuber?
I have no idea.
But if so, that's a good bit.
I like that.
It's a good bit.
It was that guy, CJ...
CJ Something.
What was the full name?
The guy who made that...
He was making that history of the PCP series and he made the first episode.
I don't think he's CJDX though.
I think it's a different guy.
What's the opposite of an X?
A Y.
It says Pokemon.
Yeah.
CJ the Y.
That was the original username.
Next one is called IHOP.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys.
How are you getting on today?
Fuck off.
I hope you're doing well.
I hope.
Fuck off.
Yeah.
Next one is called Cybershell.
Three, two...
No, I didn't load it yet.
There we go.
Three, two, one, go.
I hope you're having a good day to give a guest or no, Tom.
Tom, I hope you're fucking on this time.
I'm gonna...
He's not.
Haha.
I can't...
Also fuck off.
Fuck.
God.
Waste my fucking time.
I hope.
Also fuck off.
Fuck.
God.
Waste my fucking time.
Why don't you?
I'm so glad I said before we started.
I bet you half of them are gonna be the same person.
You were...
I expected you...
I didn't expect you to be this right.
No, me neither.
Yeah.
I'm never confident in anything I do, but maybe I should be.
Next one is called Cybershell.
Three...
Wait.
No.
That last one was just called Cybershell.
And it had nothing to do with Cybershell.
God, you're right.
What the fuck?
It's clickbait.
Next one is called...
Next one is called Opening.
Three, two, one, go.
No.
I'm not listening to it.
I'm not doing it.
Voice jail means something, and it means I don't listen to your stupid voicemails.
You've lost your fucking voicemail privileges.
Ben, what if it's not the same person?
We have to give it a chance.
What if they just have a very similar microphone setup?
Well, they're...
Well, after listening to the entire 12 seconds right there, which I won't play,
Eleazar, don't play it, but I can tell you that this person has the same ethos.
Has the same MO.
I will agree.
That is a similar energy.
Yeah.
Next one is called...
I'll have to administer another fuck off.
Next one is called Well-Ben.
These are all the same.
These are all the same guys.
You could just tell by the titles.
I can tell by the title.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, what?
No.
Next one is called...
Next one is called Well-Tom.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, in fact.
Nope.
Okay.
Next one is called...
Not this time.
Not today, Satan.
Next one is called Love You.
Three, two, one, go.
There you go.
Nope.
Okay.
That's it.
That's the end.
That's the last voicemail.
All right.
Bing Bong or whatever your name is, you're in voice jail forever.
No more.
It's over.
It's done.
We've had enough.
Everyone else, thanks for your voicemail.
At least I hope we play one second from the start of all of those.
Yes.
That's what I heard and that's what I want the audience to hear.
I want them to follow along.
Oh, God.
That was cool.
That got a little bit fun at the end there.
I guess I had some fun with it.
Yeah.
That was fun.
I suppose.
I guess I enjoyed myself.
Well, I can't wait to go and make a nice ham, and cheese, and mustard, and tomato, and
lettuce wrap for myself on a low carb, and a Bandarita wrap.
And fuck your stepbrother in a video game.
Yeah.
Well, you know.
Just one of those days.
What are you going to do?
I mean, they put it in the game.
I can't not do it.
That's free content.
You can't skip content.
It's free content that I paid for, but it's more content in the game.
Yes.
It's already paid for.
It would be pearls before swine if I didn't indulge myself.
You're wasting the pines for the edge of something.
I thought it was disappointed in the sex stuff.
Well, because like I gave Meg the last gift, the last ambrosia, and it was just like we
just had a drink in the lounge.
And I was like, are you joking me?
Like, is that it?
Like, that's what happens when you when you max out their heart.
You just have a drink in the lounge and you go, hey, maybe you're not so bad.
And that's it.
That's how you fucking date these people.
But then I got a cutscene later where it's sort of implied.
What are you not going to fucking put out, baby?
Jesus Christ.
You're not going to put out what?
What are you?
What are you not going to?
Let me fuck you.
You whore.
But then it's implied later.
Whip a Madonna, a Madonna.
They do a little fucking nasty in the past.
They do a little, they do a little, there's some whip sound effects and you go, aha,
I knew it.
Sure.
I knew she was into that.
She's into that stuff.
My suspicions confirmed.
Thanks, game.
It's fine.
I was like, okay, that's it's something.
At least at least it's something.
I clapped.
Excited to see what deuces is like, I guess.
Good.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
It's funny and sweet.
I hope so.
It'll be good.
And then I guess I'll do Thanatos afterwards just because purely out of obligation, not
because I'm gay or anything, voicemailers.
I think we learned a lot today.
I've learned nothing about myself or anyone else.
I'm going to keep it that way.
All right.
Keep telling us.
Any final notes before we end the episode?
No.
Me?
Yeah, me either.
I'm Simsie.
Go to my Twitter account.
Look at my pictures.
Check out Simsie Fart on Twitter, right?
That's the app.
Yep.
Check out Simsie Fart.
Check out Simsie's art.
It's almost like.
It's almost like a pun.
The name.
It's almost like Simsie art was taken.
Okay, that's it.
That's the episode.
Ending recording.
Goodbye.
See you next week.
I'll put those bonus episodes up.
I promise.
I'll put that file on Patreon, my Patreon, my game source file as well.
I'll do some stuff.
I'll do all kinds of important things that I should have done.
Okay.
It's my birthday.
Oh.
This week's my birthday.
By the time.
What day?
It's Thursday.
So by the time.
So this episode will go up the day after my birthday.
I think I'm going to get new glasses.
I think my parents are going to get me new glasses because mine are like really old.
Why don't you ask for like an Xbox or something?
You fucking idiot.
I don't want that shit.
I've got Noida.
That's all I need.
Sure.
But you don't have Elden Ring.
I don't have.
I should have asked for Elden Ring.
You should have asked your parents for a copy of Elden Ring.
Honestly, maybe.
They should.
Maybe they'll get me something else besides new glasses is not.
It's not that.
What's that?
Like a hundred bucks?
It's chump change.
Sure.
More, please.
Give me more.
Anyway, I just wanted to let everyone know what that's happening.
It'll be too late by the time this goes out to wish me a happy birthday.
You fucking losers.
Happy birthday, man.
You proven losers.
Thank you.
See, I remembered.
Nobody else remembered by this.
You're not a proven loser, Simpson.
You took the W.
I took the facts and I put them on the table.
That's right.
All right.
That's it.
Good night.
God bless.
See you next week.
Peace.
Bye.