Hello everyone and welcome back to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best guy ever.
I'm doing what I do here on the YouTube as you do. And we're joined today by the usual boys Ben Saint.
More content grist for the mill.
Indeed. Gibbontake. There he is.
I got a comic content that you read right now. The lord of ghosts chapter six is out.
Call me when it's been converted to anime. That is great though. I haven't read chapter six yet.
It's all great so far. And today we're joined by a guest friend of the show. We haven't seen it a
while, but welcome back everybody. He's been doing great lately. FitMC. What's going on? How are you
doing guys? There he is. The oldest Anarchy Minecraft server in the game. In the world.
All time man. Good to see you man. Really YouTube. I think the last time we spoke might have been
in the in the chat during Radcon 4 when I think you popped in for one of the live streams. But I
think yeah like the last time I was on the podcast wasn't it like three years ago already?
Something like that. I think so. That's crazy. At least a year ago. Have we even been a podcast
for three years? I think we're over three years now. I believe so. We did the math the other day.
It was end of 2015. I think is when we started because it was a little bit after I started
BG. Just bury me. Yeah. I agree. End of 2015 pretty sure. Maybe I'm wrong but I think that's right.
Well let's just say for the record. So Fit has recently hit the legendary one million subscriber
mark. It's pretty great. I'm amazed. You'll still waste your time with folks like us down in the
slums. You can't forget where you came from you know. I always had a great time hanging out with
you guys. He owes it all to the progressives podcast. We basically invented FitMC. We invented the
old standard server in Minecraft. Yeah. That's right. You know and believe it or not I always
thought like there's no way like once you reach a million there's no secret YouTube Illuminati.
There is. Yeah. Really? Yeah. Is that so? Yeah. And it's like you actually get to talk to actual
YouTube employees. It's crazy dude. Oh sure. You know I did discover after I hit 100,000. Now I
wasn't the first of our group to do so. Did you had long ago but did you just a bit of a fuck up
when it comes to I don't know like engaging with the platform and talking to I don't know like the
employees and whatnot to solve problems. But the second that I hit 100,000 I was like let's get this
plaque going boys. Let's get that silver shit in my room. So I just logged in to the like the contact
the YouTuber help or whatever immediately got like connection with a person and we like instantly
sorted out like how to get the things sent out what form I need to fill out something that Digi
said was like a real hassle and he struggled with and he couldn't figure out or that there was like
some issue in the way. My instinct is that while the tools were available he was simply not capitalizing
on them in the appropriate way. So this is another call out to you Digi. I think you still have not
gotten your silver play button which you were certainly deserved or owed or whatever. So my
experience was that as soon as you hit that the tools did in fact open up to a degree and I could
only imagine that at the million mark it opens up you know even more so. The Illuminati is deeper
and wider than we ever thought possible. That's right starting to get to the inner circle man
like it's crazy all these conspiracies it's wild. I could go on for hours but I don't want to bogart
the podcast so. Thank you. Appreciate it. Did you have you filed for your gold play button out of
curiosity? They haven't sent me the code yet because normally like after a few weeks they'll
give you a code which they send it to you in the mail but I haven't received it yet but I know
there's been an issue with like YouTube verification like normally you know when you hit a hundred
thousand subs normally you get that little check mark. Well apparently no one's been able to get
that for like the past I want to say six months. Like a really popular Minecraft YouTuber Dream
just hit two million subscribers and he still doesn't have his yet. So it's it's yeah I mean
there's a lot of really strange things happening at YouTube right now. Not everybody is a Digi Bro
and by which I mean un-incompetent. It is possible he hasn't talked to the folks that
created support but maybe he has and he would he would you know just clarify. Yeah I don't know.
You know Nate I got to say I watched your entire lecture on One Piece and it was
phenomenal. I mean now I talk to my friends and I act like I've seen One Piece. Right.
Right. You never actually have to do it. It's fantastic. Save you the trouble. Did you hear that
guys? Fit likes my content. Oh my god that reminds me of there's a reason I'm having audio glitches
today and it's because guys fits at something nice about me you know how that makes me feel
a little bit like this. Yes I'm doing it. Easy money.
I did it guys. I figured out how to pipe the fucking soundboard into my audacity and so that
everyone can hear it. Congrats. Oh it feels good. That's the real celebration. Thank you. Thank you.
I gotta get one of those. Let me give you one of these. Dude it's it's it's good. I got my Elgato
soundboard that I've been using for a year or two. I absolutely love it but just this very day
I have figured out how to get it for podcast so I can do things like this.
It brings me so much joy every single day of my life. Oh Ben Ben tell us one of your really
boring stories. Tell us a really uninteresting story of your life. I well I was playing Dungeons
and Dragons. I hate this already. I was a little frog and I I missed I missed the pond
and I went to a cave and I and I and I killed a goblin and I had some some bore
from a mine. Come on. I spent it on on the wizard to make water for me because I needed
to live and breathe. Dude make sure to stay hydrated. You know what I'm saying. Oh yeah guys
mage is back. She's such a normie. I do Ben. Thank you. Thank you. Did you get the water that you
see? You're welcome. I did. I was very happy. Give it up for Ben everybody. Give it up for Ben's
D&D story. Thank you. This can't be how it is from now on. This is how it is from now on.
This is the world. He lived in a post soundboard world.
Yeah well now what were we saying? Back to the praise of my lecture which was great. Thank you
very much. What else was I going to say about that? Oh I didn't just want to take the opportunity
while the lectures came up to again shame those people who have not released their lectures
specifically Munchy because this is the one that I want to watch again the most because it was so
good and you get so little Munchy content day to day. I can't believe it. What is he even doing
with it? I'm just sitting on it. Just sitting on it. He's just shameful. He's doing his school
work. He's doing his homework. He's doing his little you know what was his lecture on? My comic.
That's true and are you aware of this fit? Ben's been his ode art by some of our members and it's
truly shameful. I am all right. I realize everyone hates me. Everyone hates me now because my
comic's not out. My book's not out. The reason why is because I waited until the school year
started to get them the the shit and then they all had because they're all little babies. They're
all in school. They've all got homework to do. They've all got to be on Zoom or whatever and
talking to their professors. Some summer vacation babies. Summer vacation finally
six month overdue book can be made at last. I will no longer be a liar.
Oh yeah it's the end of May so that's going to be like any day now that summer vacation will be
upon us right? I mean it's practically already summer. I mean imagine you're a student in school
right now. Do you actually give a shit? Oh god. Absolutely not. It's got to be a true nightmare
and you have more, what's the word I'm looking for? More history with this than others. I was
watching your million subscribers special with great fascination fit where you talk about you
were an elementary school teacher when you got into Minecraft and you started playing it in
college and all that good stuff and you basically I just want to point out for those people who
don't necessarily think of this life path that you pursued a trait. You pursued a relatively
stable life path of being a teacher and whatnot doing something obviously you're interested in
and then you had a hobby that you loved and pursued independently and then once that
got to a point where it looked like that would be economically viable then you made a transition
and when you had already like developed your love for this your your skills in creating the medium of
YouTube content and whatnot and your your wit and witticism and also had developed the
bald head polishing technique that really gives your videos the edge that the kids crave and they
come running for. So just want to point out to everybody this is a very good life path to take
one that I would recommend to a lot of people and yes it is what I did so you can have a little bit
of bias in there but I think it's just a good idea. So looking back on it is there anything do you
feel any perhaps any any desire like looking back on as I compare myself to some of my contemporaries
online and whatnot that you should have like dived yourself in like as soon as possible sooner
and and weaned off of your job faster to get to a career that's been so great for you and so nice
and hopefully rewarding and all that. Any any wishes you've done sooner? Well for me I mean so
on June 1st that will be one year I've been YouTuber full-time and I would say the timing
worked out exactly the way it was supposed to because I had a very unusual rise to YouTube
fam I mean I went from zero subscribers to like 80,000 in like three months and that is right
not typical and it just I've been looking at your rise to a million was in the last couple months
from like 300,000 or something insane exponential growth. I know and it's just like with that first
initial explosive growth I didn't know how to maintain an audience so I needed to spend a few
years in algorithm hell to really learn how to be a YouTuber so I mean the timing it just kind of
worked out perfectly I would say you know. I'm still figuring it out myself I'll hopefully one of these
days it'll work out for me but you know interesting you say you'll be like one year officially being
a full-time Uber on June 1st my anniversary of being a YouTuber full-time will be on July 1st
exactly one month later isn't that isn't that fun that's awesome man yeah yeah hopefully I uh don't
die of starvation see how it goes the most important thing to to do in the YouTube I think is to
do it just my inner thoughts coming out
you know you you're a piece of work you are maybe I was just gonna rib you for not uploading videos
you're taking a real long time in that final fantasy lecture okay not like totally understandable
thing actual video right right oh where's the video I can't wait to hear your thoughts on this
Nate I cannot wait I won't spoil it for you if you haven't heard my rantings this far I'll keep it
completely out of this episode I'll let you I'll let you guess and then one day you can see when
the video does come out hopefully the world will uh you know just accept the argument for for the
points that are being presented there without bringing any too much baggage of things I've said
elsewhere um yeah yeah what do you feel fit have you played it any investment in the series
so well I watched since I don't own a playstation I watched a full playthrough of the remake
and I'm afraid to say my thoughts on it because I know it's just gonna piss you off man
uh okay yeah I'm saying I'm a fucking consumer I fucking loved it no more as a
fucking genius man you know I've got to say this uh the approach of just not playing this
movie game and just watching it on YouTube that's really the perfect experience that's the best way
to consume any video game I would say I mean I feel like I've played 2b2t more than anyone
because I just leave the videos on autoplay in the background and just impassively gaining the exp
of a real gamer uh so frankly I think I'm probably more of a Minecraft veteran than you could ever
hope to be because I have 10 screens going at once all the time and I'm absorbing the information
gameplay was a was a fun footnote in history it's time to just devote ourselves to movie games
and uh let's just cut out this wasteful middleman of actually playing video games
gaming via osmosis man that's right that's the future I I've been playing Minecraft recently
like uh I'm just some server and I've been I've been grinding away I've made like a castle on
the sea and I've been making a moat in the ocean uh of the sea like it goes this scene and then it
goes down as a moat of the right yeah it's very cool very epic but it's really time consuming
because I have to like put dirt under the water then fill it with sand and then delete the sand
and I'm just realizing that nobody comes to this part of the map nobody it's not a very populated
server I'm like why am I gaming right now what am I really getting out of this that's a great
question if I was watching somebody just like do a speed build of this it would be like how cool
but I'm doing it and I don't like that I have a I feel you very foggy memory last night of trying
to log into Pixelmon I I can't I couldn't do it yeah I couldn't type the password I couldn't
write my name like your Minecraft password yes my I I think the last thing I remember
before blacking out was just trying to fail to type my password into the into the Minecraft login
screen I couldn't manage it I wasn't up to the task no no there's a new version it said you
need 7.2.2 and I was like oh fuck and I struggled right right to obtain 7.2.2 didn't didn't manage
it couldn't do it it's pretty pretty simple gave up had you committed yourself to the drink
and now I'm hungover now my head hurts and so your soundboard is really doing me a lot of
favors today I'm really loving it yeah that feels good the point is I can't play Minecraft it's
impossible it's it's the hardest game ever made because logging in is just impossible
can't get over that initial the initial hurdle the skill floor is just too high
right right uh you know hey I have been playing just a just a little bit there there's exciting
news in the world of a little game known as good Minecraft aka Terraria which just said it's final
update yesterday time of this recording journey's end I played it for like an hour or two just to
get the usual building stuff done make a house for the guide and dig a little bit of a mine and
stuff get a couple iron me and munchie have to like I think we have to rebuild slime base
in the new in the new game or something I don't know I think we're gonna write it does the old
map not work I don't know he says there's been a lot of changes he said something about how we
would need to like redo I assume we're just gonna transport the old map and maybe something
changed about it I don't know I haven't seen the new updates is it uh is that the name of the world
slime base or just like no we built no no it's our we built a little a nice little slime cove
a nice little bubble in the ground it's full of is there a name for the server does have a specific
name I think it might just be called rfck rfck oldest anarchy server in terraria
endless war is the oldest anarchy server in discord in discord it is it is it's true uh we
that's true I would say and um we've said a bunch of times uh fit that like what what endless war
are you familiar you're familiar with endless war rfck all this shit okay it's a it's a it's a
disc well me and munchie and some other people made it it's a discord server but it's a game
it's like an rpg and it's and it's for cool kids who love slime and um it is what what it needs it
has lore it has like it has existed for like two years it has like a rich and storied history of
like legendary events committed absolutely true by the player base and what it needs is videos like
what you make uh about a 2b2t it needs that same kind of like like a narrative you know like like
take the events that happened construct them into a narrative make a video about it so anyone can
be like oh I get it oh so that's what happened oh so that's why you know this character that character
that user is like you know famous for whatever like that's that's what the meme is all about
that kind of lore at least from my opinion is kind of the main draw of rfck in general
that's the real uh attachment that I feel to it we of course I've enjoyed the game we made a um
there's there's another lecture I don't know if you've seen it uh there's another lecture on the
the lecture a playlist that is the me and munchie doing an rfck lore lecture and you know it brought
a big like influx of new players now who all threw money at the kickstarter and stuff it was great it
was great I was gonna say uh fit if you had to guess if you had to quantify any kind of
guess as to like how much the popularity of 2b2t you think has increased specifically due to you
know your work on youtube and whatnot I mean I know I first heard of it due to your videos
uh I would say I was probably probably the primary catalyst for new people coming in for a while but
now there's actually a russian invasion going on where a bunch of russian youtubers have like
been making videos and they're getting millions of views I used to be able to log into 2b2t at
five in the morning and get right in but now like at five am I have to fucking russians I gotta wait
like 20 minutes man it's bullshit it's it's we're gonna have another cold war dude and it's gonna
be a minecraft okay it's just that like clogged with traffic yeah and it's because that's when
they would all be logging in because that's their oh god you know fifth vodka shot of the daytime
yeah they're squatting at their uh dull laptops and just going crazy what are they what are they
doing like they just fucking around or yeah they're just walking around just fucking falling in the
holes it's those pissy russies oh man oh yeah russian a hole and watch them fall in that's
that's the way it goes tear down the minecraft wall but what I've been doing recently is I've
been trying to like sort of diversify my content a little bit and I've been just talking about
broader minecraft topics like I did a video about this server called the uncensored library
and it was a minecraft server for news articles from countries without freedom of press fascinating
it was really crazy shit yeah so like there's a lot of real there's like there's so many communities
in in minecraft because it's the best-selling video game of all time I mean you've got the pvp
community you've got the shrek erotic role play community you've got all these communities
and that's that's real by the way I wish I was down yeah I believe it it's ridiculous man I think
you'll find a few members in this very call thing every joke is now a double joke you just hit it
with one of these when you're done I will eat your ass this should not be as funny as it is
so much I know I love my son he's like a pig in shit yeah you're right okay you know you know
call the comedy police all right I'm ready cart me away I hate him I hate him
okay all right what are we talking about I don't remember something about minecraft
shrek erotic here's another minecraft thing my brother the the infamous coder of run away
from snakes the video game not the winner of the most recent pcp royal rumble which is the sound
samurai aka hgb guy yes younger brother right yeah my youngest brother um the chas has been
often on he's like he's he's a coder boy he likes doing coding and he's recently got into
really into a coding and minecraft server with unique things in it and it's he's looking to
to like spread it around um I just wanted to take a little minute to explain how cool this is because
it started out like this one mini game called a rabbit catching where there are multiple different
maps and you you go to this area you teleport to this map and you and whoever else is playing
has to try and find all the rabbits and click them or stand on them and you get points and it's a
fun little game like that and for as a reward you get like a bunches of blocks and you would go to
build this island and then build stuff and so it was like a different way to play minecraft rather
than doing survival stuff and over time he has built so many great mini games like like with really
rich um uh I don't know I can't think of the words it's like really deep um well there's this one
mini game which is a king of the hill tf2 like slime rfck endless war thing where you choose a
pink team or purple team and you kill each other and you collect slime in a in an arena
wait what where's this where's this it's a server that my brother's working on I can send you a link
us royalties yeah we own pink and purple no no no I told him it was okay so it's fine you
all right well you pay palmy you can pay the price yeah I'll pay you in slime um
but yeah there's that there's um this pirate world which is my favorite basically you get on
this little boat and you whack this bell that's on the boat and suddenly you are in control of
this player owned boat and you have like a golden rod that is a navigation rod you right click the
navigation rod and your boat teleports in that direction and essentially that means you have
a pirate ship and you can sail around and like occasionally there's like random treasure chests
appear like buried treasure and if you have a compass it'll point to the treasure you go collect
the treasure there'll be like blueprints sometimes in the treasure chest you could take the blueprints to
like the pirate island in the middle of the map and you can change that in for like making your
ship bigger and it's it's like it's like a real pirate game it's really cool I'm really proud of
work ethic how is this possible it through lots of lots of Minecraft coding and programming
and smarts and it's really cool and I he needs more people to play on it so that it feels like
it's you know worth his time because at the moment he's just got a few friends and me
so I'm just shouting that out that's a little bit like uh you know fit you probably haven't
heard about this but we in fact have our own PCP Minecraft server that we have a patron for
to sustain the livelihood of and we've got like two admins we just brought on to work on it regularly
and they're constantly expanding and making like more features and stuff we're having a
Pokemon tournament it's it's a Pixelmon server primarily right now on uh on the 20th that you
if you want to stop by you should you should come check it out it's going to be at like 3 p.m. we're
all just going to be fighting Pokemon boys in the server so I don't know they're the invitation
look version come hang out some time oh you know I should know that offhand I don't remember
generally newer ones though generally more recent ones I can get you that later though
that's all good yeah I definitely want to check it out yeah yeah sure sure we got a lot of dope
stuff and um one of the things that they're building there's a bunch of ideas for like
unique stuff that we plan to do in the server it's generally Pokemon themes since that's
overall the the point of the server in general that we're thinking of expanding but but one of
the things that our boy Marenpan uh one of our admins is working on is like hey you like the
one piece lecture right well Marenpan is working right now on a like large-scale recreation of
the grand line from one piece uh like converted to like a Pixelmon progression system where you go
from island to island yeah what the fuck on the the board it has it's surrounded by borders that
function like the calm belt that prevent you from entering any place except from the beginning
of this area and you start on like you know I don't know like the twin capes or whatever it is
fucking what was the first one um oh what's the big cactus whiskey peak I don't know whatever island
it is I think they're just using the ones they visit in one piece and you're gonna go and like
fight trainers there and in some way that's still being worked out progress from island to island
going through the red line or through the grand line until you get to the end where there will be
something and it's we're still working it out but I haven't even the theory is sound I haven't
even fought my way to the top of endless war yet neither have I that's how much baby I am I just
haven't spent the time grinding up a team or anything though I do have only I could just type
my password into the freaking login screen it would be all uphill from there uh so but anyway
that's just one of the things that we're working on just the other day and I think we're gonna use
this for the tournament our boys built um like a new stadium like a Japanese themed tournament
stadium where we're gonna have like most of the battling for the tournament or something I don't
know it's just a great time those guys are killing it uh patreon.com slash peace be minecraft only
five dollars a month come play with us oh and it's it's free oh okay it was free but when you hear
this episode it will no longer be open to the public for like that five day event or whatever
but there will be more of those coming there are there we're planning to do more like every month
or something just to give people a chance to play well my my brother's minecraft server linked
the thing there's that's the ip uh that's free forever just just play the game it's it's fun
just hop in that he's recently made a like uh survive like resident evil survival horror
like pvp thing where like a button what everyone goes into the spooky house and then everybody
gets like the blindness effect except for one person uh who gets like a pumpkin on their head
and a scythe and they have to kill everyone and he's invincible and it's like that's pretty good
it is pretty good uh so it's really cool do things like this it's it's i mean yeah it's it's
basically you know he's not using any pre-existing mods he's coding all of this himself he's having
ideas and he's just doing it and he's just like really into that and i'm like i want people to
play it so that all of this time is not wasted that is way cool and i love it i've been uh i was
going to say that uh like in my recent experiences exploring the depths of various games specifically
like final fantasy seven i talked about this on my stream the other day so hopefully uh i don't
know most people haven't heard it but uh like as i was digging into just a bunch of features about
the game uh i noticed one interesting feature when i first started up like the pc version of ff7
which was the easiest to to get my hands on um like i noticed first of all that the music was
like horribly wrong and then like what is going on here and you do a bunch of digging and it turns
out that like first of all ff7 was a buggy mess that has notoriously been very hard for like
sort enix to like make updated versions of just for like ports to other systems and stuff so like
there's actually an extensive history of like all the problems with uh like the re-releases and
whatnot the like probably the biggest one being that the soundtrack is different and weird and
sucks uh on like all versions except like the original version so of course what i do is i
turn to the heroes in the modding community to just save me from this awful music so boom use
a mod and get the correct soundtrack in there thank god thank god now it isn't terrible bullshit
anymore um but beyond that there was like the next issue that i've been like looking into
and i i'm definitely going to touch on this at least a little bit in my um my ff7 remake video
and stuff but but uh to say it in a little more detail here because i want to have an opportunity
in that context it's that in the remakes of ff7 or rather the like the remasters the re-releases
and stuff characters in the field model they're they're lego models they have visible mouths
and they did not in the original i saw i'm talking about did you link that the video that was like
comparing all the different versions or did i just find that somewhere that is a popular
video that's making the rounds yeah i saw a video it's like yeah comparing all the the
different re-releases like the pc version yeah yeah but it those mouths look so bad like it's
insane yeah that i the first version i played was the pc steam version i saw the mouse i was like
okay that like for at first i was like are they is that part of the thing but then i saw like
yeah it was just in a in scenes that were very inappropriate the way they look right i was like
okay it's a glitchy thing i'm playing a different version of the game so i sort of ignored it but
it was still kind of like that sucks oh my god if i had known that like when you play oh sorry
were you saying something yeah i was gonna say i can't i can't believe i haven't told you this
nate the first time i ever played final fantasy seven was when the drummer of the plain white
teas was babysitting me when i was a kid yeah okay so a long time ago my cousin dated the drummer
from the plain white teas because you know my cousin's a lot older than me um and they were
babysitting me one night and he's like hey well kid check out this game final fantasy seven for
the playstation i was like what the and like they didn't have a memory card so i could only play
through like the midgar section like and i loved it man but like that's one of those i mean it's
it's good shit man that's it's no no no argument here it's one of those stories where i tell people
they don't believe me that's you know it's just one of those weird stories that is a weird story
but hey uh sometimes weird stories are true oh man look at this oh and wilson looking motherfucker
they did hey there delilah yeah yeah they're the ones yep that's oh my god you're right
it is it delilah delilah baby look at this light look at this light yagami looking ass
look at this uh look at this uh two-faced guy who's the guy who played two-face uh
aron something you sure i love he looks like all those three people that i just mentioned
go watch thank you for smoking yes hey there delilah what's it like in 2b2t what's it like in
midgar i was playing ff7 with my new best friend the friend fit mc the oldest anarchy server in
minecraft beautiful beautiful thank you thank you um what was i saying about that oh right so if i
had known give at that time that like the version you were playing of ff7 like on the steam release
or whatever had like this glitch which i didn't know existed i would have screamed and cried like a
pussy baby about how no you need to play the real version you're playing this shit i i couldn't find
i couldn't find like i went to my local game store that still existed at the time um i mean
they still exist but they don't have like old games anymore um and i i found final fantasy seven
no final fantasy eight and nine i thought oh they're really cheap some reason i'll get those
uh but i couldn't find seven so it was like whatever steam's fine i wouldn't know i don't
blame you at all i'm playing the steam one right now look at these fucking crisp polygons why are
they so shit why did we ever move past crts i i feel you we don't need any more bits than 32
everyone beyond there's a waste and a dude is fascinating i had my mom send me the the
playstation one and like some of the games just to fuck around with and like the memory card is 32
bits meanwhile i just purchased for like to transfer files for my ps4 whatever i needed a
micro sd card like a i think it was like a 256 bit in you know a little micro sd and i'm like
micro xd over here bro this is like crazy the technology you know what i'm saying that's
incredible it really do be like that sometimes yeah but uh on this model thing i so i looked into it
and i was gonna play the steam version i still am playing it and stuff the the sound thing
intolerable oh you probably played with like the shitty soundtrack to give oh i'm crying i'm crying
inside uh i do vaguely recall like a weird sound thing and i think i may have got a mod to fix it
okay that would be like if it was like yeah if it if you had seen it heard it and it was like
painful i i feel like i did something about that well that's that's great i mean to be fair it's
not like it's literally like broken and fractured i mean i'm aware i've been listening to that soundtrack
for like decades and it's like my favorite when i was a kid i didn't listen to albums i listened to
the soundtrack of final fantasy games oh wait no a little bit stuck in my brain yeah i do remember
because i downloaded the soundtrack and it sounded the same as i remember it from the game so yeah
okay great that's that's fantastic oh my god um i just want to say yeah i'm so glad i'm not alone
i used to feel like am i the only one that listens to video game soundtracks like when i was growing
up and like i fucking loved them man i'm glad it's a very i used to burn final fantasy soundtracks
to cds to play in my walkman cd player so that i could have them on the go and listen to the main
theme of final fantasy 7 whenever i damn well pleased and uh it was great i i had my mp3 player
which i still own and it's filled with like the entire okami soundtrack and things like that
fucking let me just like this is you i wish that were me
man all this remake talk i played through the original like all the way once i got a little
older like i was in high school and i just hope they keep sid smoking in the remake
oh that's one of the things that's one of the things that i fear fucking dynamite with his
cigarette for his limit sure does buddy he sure does i mean wait it's not a game for babies they
wouldn't take the cigarette out well i i certainly hope not but if they do i will scream and cry
like a little baby i would be which i am i will wet my diaper the game has guns in it it has guns
so it has to have cigarettes as well imagine if they had the guns with the orange plastic tips on
the end you know i noticed that'd be simply epic dude i mean for example i believe heitiger
but definitely president shinra has a big honkin cigar but he's evil so it's like oh yeah that's
okay the heroes can't smoke because winners don't do drugs forgets that absolutely right but hey
forget um the smoke and the cigarette will sid still be a literal wife beater or a girlfriend
beater because if they don't keep that i mean i'm just gonna say this is no longer our god this
is not the man like his assistant she's girlfriend too and there's there's a specific line in the
original where uh they say because it's okay to be your assistant it's not going to be a girlfriend
if you start dating or you have to stop beating her it's great there's a line at the end or in
what when you first meet number seven where i think tifa says like oh it's weird that you treat your
wife like that he's like oh god my fucking wife don't i'm gonna fucking puke i would never marry
you like a disgusting fucking piece of shit like her man so based so that sounds more
sincerity than than sincere no no he really hated it's not like i hit you because i don't
like you or anything he hit her because he really hated her and resented her on a deep level
amazing which is somewhat understandable heart or a hot take shara was 100 in the wrong she
should have known she was trying to saddle sid with the baggage of having murdered his assistant
to go to space no that's not that wouldn't maybe i'm remembering incorrectly didn't she find out
like the ship was gonna blow up if it took off and so she was trying to like save sid and that's
kind of his whole character arc you're absolutely right it's just in the the full series of events
is like yes sid was downplaying like some issue that could and probably would have like killed him
when trying to launch the rocket it would have been like some coolant was leaking it was like a
serious problem some of that star trek techno babble technical issue okay sure fine true
and shira was like i need to fix this because i want the launch to go off without a hitch
but her quote unquote solution was to put herself like in the cargo bay or whatever to be fixing
the problem which was going to be like flooded with radiation or space rays or something and
she was going to die in there and when sid says oh hey i'm about to take off you're gonna die if
you're in that room shira says just do it like that's fine i will die and i'm just saying
she should have known that no person is just gonna say sure yes i will just kill you shouldn't
achieve my dream she have just like not been in there i don't you know what i'm think the more
i'm thinking about the less sense this makes why didn't she fix it it's a very anime situation
why didn't they just put the launch off why didn't they launch like the next day that's exactly
i think the general idea was like shinra was getting frustrated the project was going to get
canceled soon if they didn't have results and also like sid was not listening to shira he was
like blowing her off and dismissing her as you know because he's the captain blah blah blah i
want to go do the space stuff and i don't want to delay this anymore because there's financial
issues she was backing us etc etc uh so like they concocted the situation it was rough sounds like
maybe final fantasy seven bad game oh yeah hard to agree gotta agree hate to say it i feel like
you'll have an easier time getting cigarettes in final fantasy because it's a video game it's not
like a movie like dude do you know how strict they are with movies like if you put a cigarette in a
movie yeah automatic r rating automatic really yeah that can't be true so if you have ever seen that
movie about walt disney you see him a tom hanks yeah you see him put out something and they don't
show what it is but it's a cigarette because disney was a huge smoker but they can't show disney
smoking or else the family friendly film gets an r rating so they had to be super clever about how
they did it Jesus fascinating she you know you can see the logic behind it but does seem a little
bit to seem a little bit silly yeah um anyway to make my final point here about this i was looking
into this mod situation uh to like fix the music and then when i noticed in the pc version the first
thing i saw was like oh my god big's his mouth and wedge and jesse are like horrible barrett and
cloud look fine or whatever um but then i i was like looking online or i remember that video that
puts the details together or something where uh you see that sephiroth's mouth is just like a
gape like jesse big's and wedge i can somewhat understand but sephiroth is like the most important
character outside of like literally cloud or maybe your main cast or something so they really should
have fixed that luckily for me there were two mods available online that people had made to fix this
issue one simply disabled all mouths to make it like the original and that's that's okay that's
acceptable you can see that one working but i did find that like because now everything is so much
more high resolution it kind of feels a little bit weirder so instead i found another mod that just
adds like better looking mouths to all the models to make them look better so like sephiroth no
longer has his horrible gaping o mouth or whatever and it's funny to think that like i don't know i
kind of feel like the mods solution in this particular instance is the most appropriate one
in keeping with like the spirit of the original it's like uh i don't know i don't know since like
fidelity has increased just due to time marching onward and everything looks so much more polished
it's almost kind of weird now to not have mouths but so you have to turn to the modding community
for the solution to this particular issue um and i don't know maybe this is obvious to people
who are experienced modders i haven't really done too much of it messed around with like securo and
oh i just installed uh the the cinders mod for dark souls 3 that my boy uh limit breakers just
advertised in one of his big old beautiful videos that you guys should all watch if you at all give
a shit about dark souls content or just you know good videos which he always makes uh yeah anyway
they made like his videos are too good they are too good they definitely are too good and i don't
know how or why he is one able to make them that good and two finds the will to put in the kind
of effort to make them as amazingly good as they are because the the full hit i would love to get a
behind the scenes scoop on like how he makes his videos because it must involve a complicated series
of like installing the mods he needs to make the particular like camera work and stuff happen like
in some way either green screening or like magically cropping to like an amazingly competent
degree the models out of like things to do is like super imposing animations and attacks and
stuff for like his various pans and fades and combining different footage of different stuff
i don't know he's one of the most amazing editors uh in the game in my mind and i love his style
so uh let's let's be best friends limit breakers i think you're the coolest guy
and his whole channel is final fantasy seven themed so he's a he's a good guy uh in my book
anyway mods are cool love to love to sip and uh you're welcome for fixing your shitty work
square enix i have found solutions that the community has found to uh improve your bad work
oh you know what last interesting thing i found on that was just that i was i was looking around
at different versions i noticed that uh the switch version which is like the most recent
port that exists anywhere i think their solution to this horrible mouth problem was like okay some
mouths work like cloud and tifa and barrett they look perfectly fine most of the time but like
sephiroth has the big o and the pc so what do we do they simply keep mouths for some characters
like cloud and tifa etc and they just like turn them off for other characters so now it's like a
new thing where just some characters have mouths and others don't have broken mouths they just
have no mouths and that's weird and doesn't seem quite right anyway anyway mods are great
they're uh the heroes we need in this world to save us from this hellscape of imperfect mod work
or imperfect developer remasters and whatnot so thank you boys and girls out there for all your
hard work i love mods right okay so this week i made gummy worms oh i saw my sweet
i missed it i have to go look it's so no listen i spent i said this on twitter i spent like
hundreds of dollars buying weird shit um right the key the key to the perfect gummy worm the
perfect keto gummy worm is iso malta oligosaccharides aka soluble soluble tapioca starch um it is a
miracle ingredient but they they they're out i bought one jug of it and i made the perfect
gummy worm i perfected the formula and i said i'm gonna do this for the rest of my life and then
i went back and the manufacturer's like now we're out now we don't make it anymore now that's there
it's gone i don't know i don't know i need it back i need it back listen listen i i was in
i was i've been like a mad scientist that all my all my roommates keep seeing me like making weird
goop in the kitchen making just cooking up some gels and jellies and slime and and and but you
know what they they can't argue with the results they can't argue the fact that this is not some
jello horseshit this is not some bullshit this is like this is this is candy like you'd buy in a
plastic bag on your corner store i even got i've even got the crystals i've even got the stuff
you know like you know you eat like a sour gummy and it's got the christly stuff yeah i've got that
i've got that stuff i made those you know what it is it's pure it's pure malic acid pure i have
big bags of pure crystallized acid that i eat now you can just eat it raw you can see the spoonful
of it if you want is it good to enjoy it well i wouldn't enjoy that much but you can you can
just tap tap your finger on it you just coat your finger on it and lick it off your finger
and it's actually kind of nice it tastes i mean it's it's very sour but it's very pleasant it's a
nice look at your work here it looks good did you get worm molds to do this specifically so many
i made like hundreds of them and i ate all of them and these were the last three that i had
to take a picture i was like i have to save these to take a picture with yes that was wise that's
wisely done but you've got the recipe now you have the secrets i've got the recipe but there's like a
there's like an x factor there's an x factor and that is xanthan gum because when i add xanthan gum
strange and mysterious things happen sometimes it like doesn't change the outcome at all other
times the same amount will make it like super thick like taffy like there was one time when i
couldn't even pour it into the molds because it was just too sticky i just had to like take a big
glob of it and glob it onto the mold and just kind of rest it on top of the mold and some of it sort
of went into the molds and then i had to just peel the entire lump off and sort of cut the worms
out of it right it was so rubbery but it was delicious it was just a taffy mass and i think
maybe because i i let someone else whisk at that time who's stronger than me because i'm a weak boy
i think maybe he just whisked it really hard and it stretched it like taffy in it and it gave it
that consistency um interesting anyway this has been this has been what i've been doing this week
this has been my project i succeeded um you know i am a miracle worker um yeah um every each
shit everyone fuck you you'll never make a gummy worm like me fascinating you you know you got me
beat you got me beat uh i don't know i am impressed and i see that you say here that you've invested
hundreds of dollars yes on all your your tinctures yes i the the commitment the oh the isomalta
oligosaccharides are pretty expensive maybe yeah how how are you supposed to mass produce these for
so cheap um i guess is it really just like a quantity makes it worth it um possibly well i mean
this is like because it because if i were just doing like regular gummies with sugar it's like
sugar and gelatin like non keto they would be much cheaper of course right right like these
i've been i was i was going broke bankrupting myself buying this brand at Whole Foods called
smart sweets and i was like i can't i can't spend four dollars a bag on these i'll be dead i will
die so i have to spend hundreds of dollars instead um um but i just looked at the ingredient list
and i was like hmm a lot of weird shit i don't understand on here let me just so i went on amazon
and on like net nettrition.com where you can buy just bulk food chemicals and i bought bags of shit
they ran out after after a while there i i don't know what i don't where did it go
how do they why do they not sell it anymore and it's not just them like every distributor i was
fine that sold from this i think this brand this uh uh uh fiber yum is what the brand is called i
think they just like died or like like stopped existing or decided like this this product
wasn't profitable anymore because that is the only kind is the only brand of it that i can
find anywhere and it disappeared and was made unavailable on every like retailer
shit man i don't know maybe it's these maybe it's these tough economic times i might be able to get
a powdered kind we will we will god bless we will god speed yes uh this has been ben's gummy time uh
please thank you thank you yeah i'm honored
oh that feels good one day also ben to his gummy worms i will eat your ass
i will um i will i i i will let you taste them one day one day oh yeah yeah i would love to i would
love to this is gonna be my thing whenever i have guests over i'm gonna be like all right welcome to
my house here's gummy worms i made them myself yeah i was gonna say here's happy have these gummy
worms and then then you eat them and it's like ha ha your keto now long got them i was gonna say
that uh there's probably some potential to like uh like selling these you know since you have such
labors to make them i want but it is food so maybe that's like i think i might i think i might like
get like custom molds made and make like rfck gummies you could definitely do it i could make
like slime corp gummies i could make uh you know i could just make slime i could just make a big
bag of like could make podrans i don't know make i would make them real sour make them real sour
green that's all super cool i love it i think it'd be pretty i think that'd be pretty fun and you
know now that you've devised the alchemical circle necessary to summon them from hell
it's the possibilities are endless it would probably much like the war selling them such a
thing would probably be really hard i would probably have to get like licenses i'd probably
have to get like my kitchen surveyed by the fda which like it certainly wouldn't pass because
it's filthy um right but you know whatever perfect environment for worms to grow filthy delicious
delicious well that's it that's my gummy story i will eat your ass your wealth your wealth good
i look forward to trying some one day when i'm in the neighborhood
yeah or maybe you can sell them at the next radcon i will give them away for free much like our
uh put them in um the piece of cany's could we could we get away with making them like backer
rewards you know food seems like i mean i think you the only way to do it would probably be to
give them away for free because i think if you charge them you open yourself up to like some
kind of i wonder if like um if like Kickstarter would be like please don't make your backer
rewards like food like please don't send food in the mail yeah we will be i mean if i can uh what
was it the the drill andrew hussey kasey something kasey yeah those guys a collaboration like sweet
bro and hella jeff the book came with a backer reward which is you get hot sauce it you get a
bottle of hot sauce i didn't get that one because i didn't want a hot sauce i thought maybe that would
be sketchy but yeah apparently people had it wasn't bad they said it was food was it did it i'll
believe it did they just bottle it themself did it come with like a nutrition information and like
like you know labeled for retail sale and whatever i i don't know i think it may have been just a
funny meme bottle with like lol it's it's food it's sauce let me let me look this up
well that is dope because we've talked about the possibility we've talked about me and once
you talked about making fuck energy uh yeah but like and i looked a little bit into like how you
would do it like you there are machines that you use to do like the canning they're very expensive
obviously and like i i assume they would i can't when i when i consider when i consider what it
must take to like get your shit approved and like get them onto like store shelves um it sounds it's
it's you know it's probably probably take years i wouldn't be surprised if it would take years
all right here's the bottle um i think this is the entire label this is for the high rollers
out there exclusive premium gourmet barbecue sauce sweet brown and hella juicy yeah dinner
flavored sauce dinner flavored sauce looks normal it looks normal ingredients it is 100
sauce i would use that i would definitely use that uh maybe maybe because it's not
considered like intended that you probably put a thing like not intended to be consumed like not
a nutritional supplement or you know some shit like that i don't know maybe maybe something like
that would get you past the guards either way this sounds awesome and i want them all uh in my
mouth and stomach it sounds like i should have i should have backed i should have backed the
friggin book i didn't have any money at the time yeah i still want it i've got my my fidget spinner
from it hey oh you did it bozinga fuck yeah dude bruh bruh based based based
bruh bruh yes all good things
you know what uh you know what radcon needs though guys what's that you know how when i was popping
in the live stream i was like we need a royal rumble i wasn't talking about your normal royal
rumble we need an actual fucking royal rumble at radcon with a wrestling ring i want munchie to put
me through a table like let's let's make it happen we've got boys with some wrestling experience
but with that i mean jesse that time he jumped on a table and broke it wait was that video was that
in um plebe and the weeb yeah did that did that right yeah that's the radcon to plebe and weeb
stuff i think that was the last episode when they the last episode where they trashed everything
and it was very confusing was this did this i'm and you were there i wasn't there i think somebody
broke a sword who broke the sword i don't know it's been a while i always forget like which of the
plebe and the weeb content got released and like i feel like some of it like never got out or like
was still like premium content or something there i mean i think it was all released okay i think
you're you might be thinking of like the whole blu-ray debacle about how they oh and there was a
second season promised that was not filmed or like i think they tried and it got like the
footage didn't work or something there were issues right so um one day one day hopefully uh we'll see
that happen uh don't hold your breath boys and girls um i do remember jesse going through the
table i he did it like twice right because he's like oh the first one wasn't good i have to jump
through the table again it looked like it really hurt he seemed to be in like very brave way afterwards
yeah you got to like dead in your nerves to be able to endure uh such such blows
listen i am weak if we do a live royal rumble we so we have to build we have to build a platform
i will get in there i will cower i will go down in one punch i will i will crack fall uh i will
you know sure but i'll but i'll be but i'll make it funny like i'll just i'll make i'll be like a
joke character i feel like the joke wrestler who goes in there just i don't know whether you're
aware but um germa who was the original royal rumble with stupid characters guy the already has
done a live action royal rumble where he and a bunch of people act out uh him and and you know all
of his stupid characters beating the shit out of each other on a real wrestling ring and it was
really funny but obviously extremely difficult and expensive to to make let me see what kind of
venue they're in here it's it's technically doable i mean we'd need a lot okay they got a whole
facility yeah yeah i mean a whole bunch of people to do it this is the sort of thing that we could
make a stretch goal on a kickstarter for rad gun five or something but it would be like
in of itself this would be like i don't know like a five ten k kind of price point to rent out a venue
get all the costumes get like the production stuff up i don't know big productions doable
i do let's let's just tone it down let's just do a street yeah right well we'll buy some knives
we'll kill each other now that that's something i'm down for uh i would love to do that uh there's
only six of us though so maybe we could maybe we need guests to come in we gotta get uh fit
flying out there we gotta we gotta get all all of the all of the guests and all of the voice
grail voice jail people oh for the villains and heroes yeah that's a great idea let's get
fuck die buster in there so i can fucking kill die buster fuck die buster that sounds great
oh you know uh speaking of physical activity and whatnot you know fit i you maybe you didn't
see this but i when i was in hawaii most recently visiting my girlfriend's parents i finally did
the thing i've been wanting to do which is go surfing i did it in real life and was super fun
and i absolutely loved it and every day more than missing the ocean i miss specifically being able
to surf which i now want to make my life's purpose uh because it is a better way to be alive than
being a piece of shit landlubber or any of that stupid shit yeah man first of all i'm curious
as a as a floridian do you spend much time in the ocean around the ocean on the beach
or do you find yourself you know mostly just doing land type activities um well i'm kind of biased
because i live on an island you do oh shit that's right that's right i'm i'm one block away from the
beach usually yeah when there's not a worldwide pandemic i'm there like right four times a week
and something because i'm on the golf side the surf it only like happens we only get like good
surf waves like twice a month so like i always am watching the beach cam and if i see some good waves
i drop what i'm doing and i head out there like instantly oh that's the surfing lifestyle man
it's a better lifestyle one i want to be a part of uh unironically uh i don't know i i talked about
this like months ago when i when i did this but like i like i've been skateboarding for last like
i don't know year or two or whatever and those skills applied perfectly to surfing basically
same same kind of shit and uh it really just feels better than just not doing that to be doing it
and like feel the momentum i don't know i feel like you're tapping into like a primal
aspect of like a human psyche that just loves to move fast and do cool shit yeah and it's i think
a big part of it is that it's mother nature that's getting you to go this fast it's a force that you
cannot control you can only go with it you know it's exactly true it's it's sort of like a feeling
of sliding down a hill really fast on a toboggan or something yeah it is like that true and i only
went the one time but i did manage to catch some waves on my first outing surfing then and it was
awesome and you know it actually reminded me of as you said like it's a natural force that's doing
this shit um yeah i felt like it reminded me of the time when in my last apartment here in
Cincinnati when the street was just flooding and i was completely powerless if the rain just kept
coming it would have submerged my apartment and the basement was already flooded and there was
a car down the street that was 100% immersed underwater and that car is definitely in the
trash right now and i would just i in that case i was terrified and felt helpless and like i was
going to die uh but when you're surfing it's like you feel i don't know like uh like you're using
this force for good it's like weaponizing the thickness of the wave for the forces of good or
something like that right right and uh i don't know the other thing is i've never seen a surfer
who isn't hot so i think that's just another real benefit you will be a hot person if you surf
regularly and also you know i'm thinking of moving to virginia pretty soon and they you know they got
they got summers they got waves virginia beach is right in the ocean so like i could potentially
go surfing in the summer or whatever but you can't surf that's one part of the year i don't know
i don't you can't do it it's impossible there are no waves there is a surfing ability in virginia
beach i looked into it a little bit but as you said like like fit over here is talking about like
once or twice a month the potential is there to go surfing this is like there's a block of time during
the year like one month or two months out of the year where potentially that might be the case
that there's like decent waves sometimes the month but that is just a very limited time
and you can hardly define your life around that sort of shit or live the sexy surfing lifestyle
of exactly as you said dropping whatever you're doing and going to surf which you know in hawaii
is like massive culture out there and i want to be a part of that it seems like a good way to live
i want to do something that's more interesting than just going to the gym and lifting weights
because that's on the schedule i want to actually kind of be excited to go do so because jesus christ
the workout i got i surfed for like three or four hours or something and it was like probably the
most intense workout i've gotten of like my upper body just paddling out and out and out
and killing my arms hurt so fucking bad the next day uh point is this is a great workout great
exercise and you just are a cool person uh when you do it so it's all benefit and uh i want i want
to do it more that's that's the point of what i'm saying right now good man good man yeah it's good
for the body it's good for the soul yep yep never we've never done it i'll become a master ben
and then you can double board with me we'll go out there t-bap lives again rides again rides again
on the waves sounds fun sounds fun um all right well that's that's all the shit i had to say
you guys got more you want to talk about or we certainly can go to voicemails if you want to
i'm ready for voicemails yeah i'm down for whatever i got a bunch of them so we can we can
spend our our sweet time on that all right fuck it yeah let's do it oh wait wait uh uh ben before
i press play on any of that uh i wanted to let you know that i did some animal crossing stuff
and i want to see what's going on with your life with animal crossing stuff i was and to that to
that end let me okay ellie's are literally cut this because i have to find i have to find this
thing he said uh don't cut this ellie's are no cut it please this is good this is cut me
double it i like man here we go double it just play this twice please play this twice please put
on the reverb quick nick hit the sound board about the animal crossing but first oh yeah
yeah all right now it's content all right there you go take it away this is the ben
st jingle talk about a c n h go there it is
yeah
how can you see
well i i mean i guess i could probably take a picture but i have like so many black roses now
i have excellent infinite of them i gave them i was playing with a
kazzie yesterday and i gave i put a bunch of pink and blacks on her island because she wanted them
i have i have them to spare now i'm i'm excellent i don't even want my pinks i have them by accident
i do need i have a bunch of purples but it's not enough it's not even close um yeah uh uh
oh man i went to another island i went to a separate island from one of
kazzie's friends and i saw what a five star island looks like and i realized what does it
look like amazing and like imagine like everything like the entire island like cobblestone with like
little like parks and like pathways and little like gardens like just immaculate um i did hit
three stars the other day so i did unlock the thing so i've been making paths and feel much
better about my life and it really goes a long way so that's an improvement i gotta move some
shit around you know i feel like i've been unambitious um you know lots of flowers is
fine but like you gotta you gotta arrange them you gotta put them in just the right place for
them to really be worth anything um you know uh it's sunday morning the day we record this
i was awake and i totally forgot but i happened to be wandering around doing my daily rounds
i found that little stock motherfucker yes a little piggy-wiggy yeah and i bought 200 000 uh
dollars worth of turnips for there were 92 bells each that's pretty i feel will give a great return
on investment i i forgot this week last week i bought 500k worth and i had a spike i it wasn't
as big as the last time i i was on like the last time i sold at like 400 it was amazing
this time i sold it like at like 200 something so it was still pretty good so what what should i
aim for if i see like a 200 or a 300 one day i mean to jump on that well yes but there's
okay should i just give like the full explanation of how it works right now yes the yeah all right
here's here's everything everything you need to know everything you need to know about uh uh
turnips and the stock market um you will like you know you buy them at whatever price it's
usually around 100 and then in on any given week there will be one of four patterns that occurs
it will either be random or it will be um a just a steady decline or it will be a small spike or
a large spike and there's a there's a website called turnip profit as in p-r-o-p-h-e-t you can
type you if you're checking your numbers consistently you can put in like what are they
throughout the week you need to check twice a day and if you do that this algorithm will predict it
will like read it and be like okay this is the pattern you're on and it will predict like what
your turnip prices are likely to be and if you're on a spike week it will tell you okay it will peak
here like here's when it will peak this is when you should sell because like the the the the the
small spike is like four rising prices that go up to like somewhere around 200 and then they drop
off the large spike is two rising prices and then the third one is like a big spike and then after
that it goes down so sometimes you might see a good price like if you're on us if you're on like a
if you're on like a large spike the price might go up and it might be kind of good
but then if that third spike is about to happen it will like skyrocket so like if it's more it's
if you want to really maximize it it's not about just like sell at this point you got to like
know what trajectory you're on and know like how yeah just just use turnip profit it'll it'll
it'll pretty much predicted for you most of this is my first week doing it i want that money back
i want to return on investment so i'm gonna do that i'm gonna track it get on turnip profit
commit to checking prices twice a day put in the numbers it will predict you you'll see it you'll
see it the first question it has here is is this your first time buying and the answer is yes this
is my first time i think on the first time you buy it's guaranteed to be a certain pattern i don't
know which one but i think that's it because otherwise there's like a probability of which
pattern it's going to be and it's affected by like what did you have last week because like it's
unlike you're less likely to get the same pattern twice in a row okay okay um we'll see so that's
that's my primer on that the long story short just use turnip profit
i definitely will uh for this time see how it goes all right well good uh that's settled hopefully
you will be a smart investor ladies and gentlemen out there in youtube land uh but let's go on to the
rest of our voicemails speak pipe link down below and uh let's see what the people have to say
we've got like 10 or 11 or something today we'll just motor on through them as fast as we please
god uh they were they were quality uh in general i can't speak for them uh you know one was just
saying like yay fit is on happy happy joy and i was like that's good but i get the idea and i
don't need to play this whole thing uh so the rest are all very critical of fit the rest are very
negative very nice very nice um uh they're like no i'm the oldest anarchy server in minecraft
it's me sir you're stealing my my crown all right all right let's hear this first one this is simply
from why why why are the ads for mobile games so bad like it's clearly not even the game that
they're advertising i don't understand what the fuck was that okay i know what he's talking about
any all i can say the mafia city ads are fucking kino have you have you actually like
watched the montages they're incredible man i'm all about that afk arena no that is good share
i'm getting a lot of ads for afk arena uh i mean they are because mobile games are bad
across the board none of them are good we all know that when you say it's a good mobile game
you're talking about in the context of mobile games which are all bad like when i did my ad for
that game whatever it was that i played the other day for whatever we agile episode that was that
game was fine uh i can't even remember it was it was fine it was just a spin-off of concolay or like
you know kmart brand concolay and it's fine you can play it there are cute anime girls in it that
cannot be denied can you guys hear the kids screaming out my window but a little bit yeah i've been
hearing that very now okay okay good leave it in lezard he he's probably screaming because he just
got sniped in mafias city and he's just having a real tough time with that oh my god playing his
favorite mobile game i'm gonna post an image in general of my favorite fucking scene from mafias
city and it's just like please it's unbelievable i gotta see if i can find it real quick okay all
right is that the one where it's like you know the level zero something and then like the the
level 100 boss yeah yeah yeah yeah it's good shit but the afk arena has taken the the you know level
one brain mafias city format and turned it to a level 10 anime version of that which is obviously
superior i've never seen an advertisement in my whole life i don't know why actually i do have
ad blocker on my on my desktop it's on my phone i always get ads for this shit because i cannot
use ad blocker on my phone yeah yeah that's my favorite one man a level 10 hit man you can my
favorite part is the extremely low res texture in the background tractor this is what a level 10
hit man looks like in real life this is tools of the trade uh congrats he did he earned that 25
thousand dollars all right go look at that lays gents uh all right next up okay okay we have
another voicemail uh this one is called radcon five idea uh take it away go relevant voicemail
since you guys have a guest hey fit i'm thinking guest lecture at next radcon maybe i mean a two
b two t is like the perfect topic for a lecture now i think it's a really good idea it could maybe
get you guys a lot of views and she you know oh my god there's actually there's a lot of
wall cows on two b two t that might be worthy of a full on lecture really sure sure man i yeah
your videos are very much in the same style well i would watch a video about that i would sit in
the front of somebody doing a lecture about that i me too i um hey possibilities there doors open
yeah our people will call your people we had uh we had zen we had zen visit uh uh yeah very briefly
yeah stretch goal stretch goals hey possible we kicked him out as soon as we could but he did
manage to weasel his way in there briefly that's true he was in the tarantino cast and uh one or
two other things as i recall uh well there you go uh agreed even if fit didn't do it or anybody
the two b two t lore stuff is exactly the kind of thing that i think makes for a great lecture
and his his videos his story had been kind of about that exact shit all right next voicemail
we got tectonic improv go so you guys like fully cooly right and nate did that video on lucifer and
the biscuit hammer um i have a question what in the hell is a biscuit hammer the reason i bring
up fully cooly is because the pillows obviously did the soundtrack to that and they have a song
called biscuit hammer but it came out in like 2002 or something and then lucifer and the biscuit
hammer came out in 2005 so what's the connection here because i tried looking it up and i couldn't
get anything i only got like stuff on lucifer and the biscuit hammer is it like like an actual hammer
that you use to like make biscuits with or something i have no fucking clue what this is can you guys help
me uh this is you know i hear people ask questions about this sometimes or be confused very simple
answer it's just that lucifer and the biscuit hammer is it just it does what jojo does jojo
just names things after albums or songs or whatever lucifer the biscuit hammer just named a bunch of
stuff after pillows songs uh that's that's that's that's a full extent okay follow up question is
why is there a pillow song called biscuit hammer i was gonna i wish i knew the answer to that
alas i do not i don't know since it's this uh an original song and songs mean you know usually
do this don't mean anything there's titles that is yeah like you could just be like hey what if
like there was a hammer specifically for smashing biscuits that'd be funny
i'm going to genius page on internet it's all in japanese though i somebody translated it
i'm sure there's some meaning i'm sure some simple googling would would determine the origin of this
but i don't know how they translate japanese people will will have a lot to do with it
maybe it means something else i don't know because biscuit means something in america and the uk
that's true that's what you call cookies maybe in japan maybe in japan it's something else
you know which even we know that there's two definitions of the word biscuit at least between
our two countries or whatever which one are these japanese individuals using i don't know is it a
cookie or is it a kentucky southern biscuit kind of thing yeah getting the gravy and whatnot i don't
know i would love that uh okay here we go oh you know what i was gonna say uh fit having you around
and your name being fit always makes me self-conscious about if i'm being fit or not and i am glad to
say that i ate a delicious prepared meal by my loving significant other uh that was full of greens
and grilled chicken and cauliflower and white rice could have been brown it was white hey not the
end of the world you know that's a eight out of ten could do better next time that's really impressive
name i'm impressed that's really nice well what's what's impressive is that i have a fridge full of
like 40 of these all stacked up have a fridge full of 40s like i'm gonna drink them that's right i wish
now there's a healthy breakfast uh anyway i ate a good breakfast that's my story thank you god
mate you are a literal god i will accept your praise i feel good about myself
friend every day is a battle man that's true so true love love is a battlefield as well
unfortunately just in case you weren't aware oh okay yeah i appreciate that all right next
we have uh a friend of the show suck my underage dick nibba's is calling don't play this one let's
hear what you have to say no no no this is gonna be good all right go all right bitches i'm listening
to one you have every day of quarantine i would like some recommendations preferably some obscure
shit because i'm not very well versed in music and i will not have heard of it it can be literally
any genre because i do not care and i'm trying to broaden my horizons thank you and fuck you
hey short and sweet i like it um it was albums the only only good album that has ever been made
is aeroplane over the sea in the aeroplane over the sea right right uh listen to we like it here
by snarky puppy jazz fusion there you go very good that's a good one okay i haven't actually
listened to it but yeah i mean gibb says it's good i believe him uh i'll throw out things listen to
anything in joanne annusam's discography how about a short one divers that's a good album
you could enjoy that potential or east also good uh i don't know fucking pet sounds by
uh the beach boys everybody loves that album sergeant pepper there you go recommended um listen to
um listen to lemon demon lemon demon's pretty good oh my god i haven't heard lemon demon in ages
man yeah he's got some good shit on his discography captain beef heart be an intellectual titan
people know him for people for his uh mashups more but his originals are good as well yeah
i've heard a few of those through his youtube stuff i like the one where he's an arcade machine
that's a good one shit i forget what it's called anamana gucci's endless fantasy that's
you know that's an album love that album love prom night baby it's a classic you know i don't
know microtonal banana is pretty good link kink is in lizard was it oh watch in watch cello 555
if you've never heard oh or yeah that that punk album but if you're gonna listen to the album just
watch the movie right it might as well fit we were we were saying so the founder of vaporwave
vecroyd under the like label macintosh plus so like the username is coming out with a new
album sick and panic and they just released the first track and it's it's godly i love it
also i recently this is music related i recently discovered middle-aged white woman youtube and
there's a bunch of live streams with just like relaxing music like to ocean waves and shit
that's yeah i unironically have been enjoying it word word wait middle-aged white women youtube
what does what does that mean so it's just music yeah so i'll post the link in chat real quick but
like yeah it means youtube for that demographic or youtube buy that demographic uh both here i'm
going to post the link right now like this kind of shit uh yeah yeah i i yeah hey man don't
oh i don't like it until you've tried it i i know i like the occasional like uh rain sounds like asmr
um yeah i put on i've been putting on rain sounds every night to sleep it's good i have
one i have one particular i'm like i'm very picky about my rain sounds because if like it's too muddled
or like if there's thunder or if like it's yeah i have to be able to hear the individual drops
if like the drops have to be heavy or it's worthless so you know i got mine here under
particularly too yeah like a like a rain sound that it's like hitting a tarp and it's going
this is it this this is the one this is the one this is the sound of my life
except no substitutes okay cool cool i'll i'll listen to it i know that feel although the sound
of rain on a tarp does take me back to my boy scout days when i heard a lot of that and it was a
very relaxing time i think i would enjoy rain on a tarp sounds if they aren't too well they will
there at it there you go she's flashing oh wait this isn't a tent oh okay okay he's gotta be on a
like if it's if it's not if it's not raining on a tent what are you even fucking doing
what's even the point what's even the point of rain that's not on a tent
sure mine for rain is actually pretty good yeah like like on iran yeah that's our video that's just
like 10 hours minecraft rain that probably definitely oh my god gotta be i'm here yeah uh
fits next video rain and thunderstorm rain and thunderstorm at night 10 hours minecraft asmr
there you go oh god you know i missed the days of 2016 youtube where videos trended based on
how long they were watched for right like those types of videos were like insane for growth but
yeah it's not the same anymore our lecturers would have done even better in those days but
they still do very good oh man five hours imagine or imagine uploading like a 10 hour like a 10
hour like rain video you put ad breaks every like 15 minutes it gets millions of views yeah yeah
generates hundreds of dollars in revenue every single day that's the good shit people wouldn't
stand for ad breaks maybe like text ads oh they'll stand for it oh they'll watch what i tell you
they might it depends on the algorithm would force it in front of them right the whole point of an asmr
like two thing that happened like interrupt like hey you buy a product okay yes that's what i want
listen they'll do an advertisement asmr just like constant advertisements like layered on top of
each other reverbed not a bad idea appreciate although you know they will they will watch the
ads to support me the creator one person comes to mind i think her name's gb asmr she's she's
very well known one of the famous people who does it and uh i think she does a thing called sponsored
saturday which basically just means it's a whatever normal asmr video but at the beginning
she doesn't add but she just does it talking softly about whatever she has to say for the ad
and it it doesn't break the you know it works it works just fine for for listening to person talk
the you know i've been thinking recently the thing that annoys me the most about asmr is
i don't know because i mostly listen to people talking specifically i prefer the male voice i
find it relaxing and it's they they really are just fill in time man they will just find words
to say and they will just say those words and it is annoying i wish that there was a little more
substance to what people are saying the amount of like filler content that is stuffed in there
just to justify the runtime you know it's the game they're playing so i get it but when someone's
has said in 10 different ways like how i can't even think of of anything specific like you are
like a beautiful majestic creature and like everything is good and nothing is bad and they
just go on loops well it makes you feel better in like 20 years they're gonna have like ai
generated asmr and all the problems are gonna go away nate it's gonna be fantastic as will we
as we're phased out as a species and i look forward to it i can't wait for the ai generated
youtubers who have ai generated drama with other ai generated youtube
that's exciting stuff all right let's go on to our next voicemail but by the way two other albums
that are great go listen to you these are also famous mu core loveless by my bloody valentine
the essential shoegaze album give it a listen you probably love it and also prince's gold experience
yes it is le jo jo reference you are welcome uh great album great album more voice all right
yes all right here we go here we go this one is simply titled escape the voice jail all right go
it's been one week since i've been imprisoned in the voice jail for crimes against die buster
or not if i got this recording in too late it's been rough every time it's warden nate best
been shift he calls me dumb and gay which is really messed up because i'm not even gay
it's okay though i find solace in the dramatic irony of nate saying we'll never hear from fuck
die buster again and then immediately playing my next voicemail it gets me through the day
that and warden hypocrite the only member clever enough to see through my disguise and not altering
my monotone at all it gives me crayons and we doodle together chill dude can't say the same for the
rest of the wardens though then saint has been trying to convert me to communism indigibro keeps
placing me on various charts bad autism going insane in here need to break out nate i can't
believe you would give him there is a core the suck core yeah playing the satisfaction of playing
his his his male nate it's supposed to be that's true and that he's solitary that's true that's true
but i find this to be something to live for he what see what's the point of imprisoning someone
in the voice jail if not to have his story be available to others as a cautionary tale so his
suffering soft is being put on display so others can learn you think so remember what he said about
die buster he said he said he didn't like that's a bad thing he said i don't like that themes were bad
no that is a criminal offense you're absolutely right about that okay i will live and learn uh
forgive me let's try uh okay hey some helpful notes uh more cruelty less mercy less forgiveness uh
right okay okay uh relevant male here i think i like asmr now no what that's the voicemail
that's the name of the voicemail okay let's hear what he has to say so i never understood
nate's love for asmr i always thought it was weird and creepy and yeah his love for it was
probably sexual in nature yeah but i recently fell down a youtube rabbit hole of this channel
called cracking the cryptic in which a very nice and calm british man solves really hard
sudoku puzzles and all you hear is his nice calming voice and the quiet clicking of his
mouse as he gets more and more excited about finishing a sudoku puzzle over the course of
30 minutes or so and it's awesome so shout out to cracking the cryptic and also i i guess i'm a
freak who likes asmr now that's fucked up that's not asmr that's just a quiet man that's just a
bob ross asmr yeah like would you classify bob ross people say that all the time like a person
who is not shouting constantly i someone who is not usually a youtuber on youtube must be the bob
ross of whatever they're doing look asmr is different but a little bit like sexuality in that
you can be doing nothing or just standing there and someone can just find that attractive or
arousing or whatever like it could just be like your voice or something about you or it doesn't
have to be a person it could be anything um you know some drawing or art or whatever that you didn't
intend to be that way but people just interpret it that way so like what is bob ross asmr most people
believe that he is but like that wasn't the point um no that that has to be a fringe opinion
bob ross i mean i'm not saying he's a paint man he is a paint man i would never say that like he
was an intentional asmr guy but i just think that like nobody you don't get the head thing
about from bob ross nobody does it's impossible i mean i never have either but still i find it
relaxing to listen to it seems like it i don't know i don't think that being relaxing to listen to
makes it asmr i don't know it's just a definitional it just sounds like this guy's trying to commit
honorable sudoku and that's what his channel is about
oh wait wait if you go through i really like sudoku i'm i'm really into sudoku there was a
there's a video like i made where it's like a sudoku with only four numbers huh and uh there
was some stipulations like the the night's move like a number could not be in an l shape to the
same number and the center square had to be a magic square where each row had to add up to the
same number and diagonal and stuff it was like using those stipulations it was actually possible
and i paused the video at the beginning and i figured out quite a lot of it i ended up failing
because i missed something halfway i couldn't remember where but it was so fun like i would get
stuck and be like oh dang it i clicked back on the guy and he's like hmm well well because this
and this and this therefore this and that and i'm like wow yeah yeah he's so smart now i'm smart
because i learned from him oh my god i see there's a comment on that rain video this guy says i
like this one because i can clearly hear the raindrops it's not blurred into white noise there
you go cj wonder struck 25 gets me i'm not the only one you know this this just reminds me that
the other day in my nuzlocke i was playing poke no i keep thinking pokeball flip but it's voltorb
flip the whatever the fuck it is oh shit i've got a video playing stop stop anyway voltorb flip is
the most brain breaking uh ahego inducing uh dojin you know mind break experience in any pokemon
game and i i'm way too stupid to do it reliably and eventually i got better but it was kind of
a nightmare and that game is bad and basically what i'm saying is i don't enjoy logic puzzles
because they're too hard and i'm stupid and that's just the fact jack damn there you go love logic
i'm so fucking smart i put a number in the right way so many things in your head i can't do it
you have to know like oh because this probability exists here there's like a probability cloud
that it now exists and there's like a totally separate probability cloud and you have to recognize
where those things intersect in logic brain functions and it's too hard i can't do it
nice my brain works very well i mean in sudoku at least period end of sentence there's there's a
few things where it's like sometimes i'm like i've got a lot of uh like things filled in but
there's like one number i can't i need this number to figure out everything else and so i try so
hard to find this number and in order to do it i need to like say okay so i do like a hypothesis
a hypothetical situation if the seven is here right that means the seven can't be here which means
the seven can't be there which means the seven can't be there which means that needs to be a six
this needs to be a five and that doesn't work so i have to go all the way back and put the seven in
the other spot and then it works and it's it's fun i it's really fun i get so scared physically
terrified of all the like maybes and i can't keep track of all the things that are definite versus
like probable versus we don't know oh god that's what the little notes are in sudoku where you put
the little number yeah you're right you're right possible it's too scary i'm already scared just
thinking about it all right well if you like it go check out crapton the cryptic everybody
all right next voicemail is called ellie is our fix it take it away i don't know if the last voicemail
sent about this topic uh went through because the uploading was kind of weird but anyways i'm just
going to speak fast to make for it uh so ellie's are the editor of the pcp fucked up in last week's
episode because he has a timestamp of this in the description there's a part talking about the final
seven spells that was a voicemail that i sent and then right after nate talks about his fucking
pokemon streams because there's another voicemail talking about these pokemon streams and he fucking
flipped the goddamn voicemail audio uh so it's like wrong they have the wrong reaction to each of
those two voicemails ellie's are you cuck idiot fix this oh man rest in peace ellie's are oh god
we're in the chat ellie's are typing right now oh no he just says the fuck that guy is what he
says in the chat i'm just gonna ask him is this accurate either way don't care pussy bitch
i think um even if this guy is an accurate i like i think it was it was true and ellie's are
noticed it in the the comments of the video and somebody said it and he replied like um
that was just the order that they came in which says to me that he didn't listen to it so it's
still a bad it does that's no excuse that's no excuse and i think we're gonna have to lash
we're gonna have to bring out the whip this time oh my god fucking ellie's are he is saying it's
true but i put them in the order that you sent me do your job ellie's are uh listen to the episode
bro okay but this is one minor flaw in a stellar history of ellie's are editing work so who could
be who could be too mad but hopefully he knows it could be uh they could be out of order on occasion
all right next one we got oh yes excellent uh we've got i'll die groveling
begs and pleads for mercy that is the full title okay let's hear what he has to say go
me a little less than a year ago i'm working the hustle making an amv i think hey i could
advertise it in a voicemail why not oh overstepped my bounds got sent straight to voice jail that's
okay i can respect it's reasonable but what's not reasonable is that like two weeks ago you sent
someone who thinks that die buster is shit in there and listen i love die buster that's the
problem i can't stand it in here anymore i've done my time now it the punishment far outweighs the
crime at this point you may i she's my favorite fucking director i can't i can't be seen in the
same list of names as this creature i gotta get out of here please please first of all his name is
surumaki who directed fully coolly and fucking uh die buster so oh embarrassing embarrassing moment
right there truly a bra moment um he may she wasn't maybe he was involved maybe he was like
producer or something i don't fucking know uh okay but but ben what do you think do we have any
policy for forgiveness or allowing people to come back into a polite society after they've been so
excoriated for such a long time i think ben's muted so he might not answer this so give
any any feelings about the should we forgive those who are repentant after some period of time
nah you don't get out of jail by just saying please let me out please that's not our words okay but
normally with jail there is like a time you you go in for a certain number not this is this is this
is the worst jail of all it's a meritocracy you have to be cool enough to get out that's i
suppose yeah you have to not just say i'm sad that i'm here with fuck die buster uh even though i
fuck up the director in bed truly embarrassing um you have to in fact just give us something cool
and then perhaps you could be saved like your old i'll die corporation stuff that we all enjoyed
but then that's funny he made a bunch of great voicemails we'd made one minor infraction after
contributing to the show and forever is in jail and there's no hope of redemption uh unless
uh who knows who knows maybe one day maybe one day all right anyway let's let's just move on to
our next one we have the notorious f a g calling with a voicemail let's hear away i'm back what did
i miss oh yeah yeah okay bed you can weigh in quickly let him uh did you hear the voicemail
did you hear that um no mercy no i did hear no mercy no no mercy but do you have any thoughts
on an eventual potential redemption plan for anyone in voice jail um he uh um no no never
okay no no one we're all clear understood understood uh has there ever been anyone who
has left voice only way to get wait the yeah i think someone went from voice i think someone
did voice grail or maybe the other way around but like it didn't we say i know the other way you
are in you can sacrifice your voice grail status to rescue someone from voice jail right oh so you
know who would ever do for leet strats you know what if you were if tactically i'll die you could
have someone else uh like call in work with them on a production to make it good so that they get
into voice grail and then they could use their status now as part of the voice grail to to free
you or you could just use them as a patsy you know to get uh to get the name on the on the board
and they could use that there's one plan do with it what you will all right anyway let's listen to
the norious notorious fag i've been dying to hear from all right go hey pcp the notorious fag here
so how do you guys feel about the fact that my little pony is on the official evil lineup
also what are your thoughts in general about them fighting herbs
and if you haven't seen it's a pretty cool fighting game i recommend that a lot sure yeah yeah yeah
um yeah i know i know about them fighting anyway this is i have no opinion i don't know how to end
this i don't know how to end this shut up just stop that doesn't know um wait wait so okay yeah go on
so what was that about like my little pony is the official evil list line okay first of all if you
don't know what evo is oh he's like the biggest yeah the biggest fighting game way event so he's
oh evo so he's saying that them's fighting herds is an evo okay but but hang on like the i played
this because there was an interesting thing i went to the evo website and looked at the games
first of all it's not among the games being played at evo so i don't know what that's about and
second of all at the top of the thing it says evo 2020 has been canceled so double
not happening wait hold on i just found something posted three days ago that says evo 2020 will be
all online features four new games and it's this says one of them is uh uh them's fighting herds
well shit i guess they're just main website hasn't been updated which is their fault not mine
but uh okay how cool how long ago did they say it's canceled this update you know it doesn't say
exactly when this was posted uh i mean probably the last you know month or two i don't know um
even maybe this happened like yesterday or something i don't know i mean there's not
much to think about it them's fighting herds was like it used to be a my little pony fan game and
then yeah hasbro said no you can't do that and so it became an independent project and now it's just
about animals beating the shit out of each other designed by lauren fast which is pretty cool yeah
and it's like it's a it's a cute little game and i i don't know it looks all right the like it being
in evo means very little um i agree i mean i guess it means it's got a like community around it and
it's considered to be like balanced enough that it's a it's a worthwhile game to compete at so good
i guess i i guess i think it's cool smash bros melee is it in that list of added games because
i'm still pissed that melee has been removed from evo which is by far the game i'm most interested
in fuck modern smash don't care melee is way more interesting to me i mean i don't follow it follow
any esports at all but that seems strange because it's so big isn't it melee still uh yeah at least
maybe i'm like not in the scene and it actually is just like a vocal minority group or something
but to me it seemed like the most popular fighting game like period except maybe for like street
fighters and maybe modern i think maybe i'm incorrect on this didn't they get like pressure from
nintendo to drop melee at evo i think there was some something like that going on keeps selling that
game and i think it was a big issue for the evo staff because you needed like the crt televisions
or whatever and they were fucking heavy to like take in and out maybe if they hit the gym instead
of their pillow with virgin rage every night then they could lift those crt tvs and it wouldn't be
an issue plus if it got added i'm curious how they'll do it because there's no net play on the
game cube so they'd have to use an emulator right that is true which could introduce concerns and
issues and yeah you know okay okay but but they only did the online thing recently they cancelled
it i think like last year is when they announced it before we knew any of this online stuff you
know those concerns are reasonable they cancelled having to use special technical stuff uh yeah
yeah it was like months and months ago why why was it cancelled i think some other i mean maybe
because of fitz reason i a lot of people were wondering that i think i saw a video talking
about it um i can't remember exactly but it was just sort of like management is bad evo bad
you know there are reasonable concerns like technically like he was saying and if nintendo
is like breathing down your neck about it i mean they should have no right whatsoever but excuse me
that was uh e3 i think so it was it was some big thing that nobody cares about anymore that sounds
like e3 definitely all right we've got one last voicemail we might as well get to and this is um
riddle my ass batman i r l okay take it away my my hero my favorite he's back baby okay
so i'm taking a shit real man shit the kind of shit that means it sounds like
like digit i enjoy reading on the shit 20 minutes passes i'd rather kill and jump for
the thousands of time i'm done with my business reach over to clean up and i riddle us i'm completely
out tp and i'm like damn you coronavirus i got a couple hours to take a shower i've already taken
a shower today so my skin will feel dry i couldn't use my socks my feet would get cold scoop and drop
method maybe then wash my hands like a doctor by the point perform surgery um burritos tonight
half touch my hand with my food no go then look at my comment i've already read it i've owned two
signed copies a special edition a black and white edition eventually i decided these hard times
sacrifices must be made first in his rip one page then i soon realized combo paper is thin
and i'm scratching not absorbing of all either really just smeared it all around my butthole
pointy two i'm bleeding out my ass long story short i use the entire comic for my business
and it's like i had to hear i had to go to the store shortly after and buy two things
tp and a frame for my new most prized possession now the joker really has a shitty grin
absolutely astounding absolutely epic they said they said he was a one-trick pony they said he
was all washed up they said he had nothing left in the tank but then he hits us with one of these
you know uh thank you it's what's what i hate most about the story is how relatable it is
what i hate about is how much it reminds me of my daily action it's just it's just too damn good
is all this is what i hate about it it's a comeback time baby riddle my ass batman i'm ready
terrible i'm ready for the revolution terrible shit all right that's it that's the end of our
voicemails hey do you think we're gonna leave on that note you think we're gonna get like a big
i think we're gonna get do you think we're gonna get a million all fits one hundred or one million
subscribers watching this episode i think we're gonna get a hundred percent conversion i think
from him to us let me let me tell all right all you all right all you all you fit heads out there
yeah all you two bt we're like shitheads yeah you better watch better watch now like go to subscribe
watch the pcp uh watch the lecture playlist check out the lectures are great what's the endless
war lecture get get get understated you you think you know anarchy uh you have you have no idea new
los angeles city aka new milwaukee educate yourself yeah agreed agreed good point oh and not only that
i i hope to convert you from fit to us but then also have you unsub from fit to have the full
transplant experience that would be the ideal situation for me i i just want to watch his
the procrastinator's podcast the official home of fit mc don't worry about that
it doesn't exist don't worry about it uh yeah that'd be nice i would i would also like uh everybody
listening to go to gib and take dot site and read the lord of ghosts as i said at the beginning
chapter six is out there's like uh i don't know like eighty pages it's the only thing i like on twitter
it's a manga i draw it's really good i'm really good at it it is legitimately great you should all
read it you all are like where's the good content when everything sucks there it is that's it go read
it that's all what were you expecting uh let me see what else do i got to plug i don't know just
go watch the fucking lectures and stuff youtube videos one of these days you know you'll see them
sometime learn something um that's it that's it leave more speak pipe stuff link down below
leave more voicemails and whatnot uh what else is going on hey new bonus episode join the freaking
minecraft server join the minecraft server that's right uh you'll be a little bit late line i guess
is it one of these days we're working on it it's impossible but you will have already heard
you will have already been able to join for free the uh pz minecraft server you already missed your
opportunity to join for free but there is future opportunities on the horizon if you're skeptical
of if you want to spend five bucks for a month or whatever that's okay there's going to be more
events probably like monthly or something where you open it up for a day or two and let people
filter in because on the you know on the one hand we want to tease people get them invest in the
server and then all the fun stuff we're doing and then the other hand it's just more fun for people
to have more people on the server to play with so it's all it's all good stuff base and uh yeah
so come play with us gonna do that big old play with us well you have already missed it okay yeah
saying something am i am i talking over you okay right they understand uh lipp point go play minecraft
just go play minecraft that's all we're saying just go play minecraft the details don't matter
what else okay patreon.com slash pcp no it's patreon.com slash the procrastinators that's right
minecraft is the other one you can't do it sometimes i fuck it out i just can't type the
password into the freaking password i can't type my name in my email address go go sort that
shit out ben so that you can be there for the tournament which is in our future but in their
past actually wait a minute maybe now that i'm sober i can figure out how to update minecraft
indeed indeed and how to open pdf yes as well yes which would be essential um let me see right
right so bonus episodes patreon.com slash the procrastinators 38 bonus episodes are recorded
but the new one will be out in like two weeks or whatever after you hear this we were ahead of
the game this time and it's gonna be good it's gonna be fun you'll like it and uh what else is
going on that's it that's it play just more money on the patreon that's all good stuff and of course
our guest is a youtuber if you didn't know of course we should introduce our epic subscribers
to fit as a gesture of good faith we forgot nothing wrong with that good stuff man if you
thought this channel is videos you ain't seen nothing yet now those are videos uh for everyone's
enjoyment audio visual entertainment on that's right imagine it imagine it uh it's legitimately
great shit uh obviously so yeah imagine a platform where anyone can upload video to be viewed by
what is the twilight zone imagine if you will a platform uh uh content made of visual and audio
inputs data ones and zeros in a line working together to make you entertain incredible uh
i love when that happens it is very exciting uh and also hey updates on the twitter uh at tp
procrastinators uh more rad con stuff is coming we're working on it fast as we can good stuff coming
ben is currently holding us up on some things so ben finish those things you know what i'm talking
about yeah i know what you're talking about good good shame him shame him people i guess
good guess i'll do it we're also waiting on munchie but he said he'd do it i think tomorrow
we're the day after something so there okay there you go and uh that's it that's it we'll be back soon
feel like this outro is lasted like longer than the podcast i don't know why but i i agree i agree
it's been far too long but for real fit it's been great to talk to you subscribe to the patreon
but hey did you know if you join the minecraft server no no no there's pokemon in there well what
the pokemon yeah okay it's this video game right imagine i don't imagine if you will a program
a program that displays visual data and auditory data that you can control with inputs through your
keyboard wow okay last actual point about that is that maren pan did actually make a really cool
video that just teaches you how to play and what you need to do to sign up for the pcb minecraft
server there will be a link to that so it's not open for free right now but soon it will be so okay
there you go go watch that so you can join us next time i'm sure for people who are cool that will
be interesting uh okay there you go there you go fit great seeing you dog thanks for being here yeah
thanks for having me guys it's always a great time on the procrastinators podcast yes hard agree
thanks for being on our program it truly was easy money thank you bizarro flame for that
sterling endorsement the greatest ganador player who there ever was or ever shall be
all right we'll see you next week everybody thanks for being here all right done