Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're back. I'm back. I've been away for two weeks. I know y'all miss me, but that's okay.
We're here again. Did you guys didn't show up either? I'm really upset. I invited all of you and everything.
My name is Tom Oliver, and we got a whole brigand of disgusting people with us today, starting with the man himself, Digibro.
I'm gross. Indeed. We have the Hippocrit Gibbontake himself.
I thought you said Barum. That's why I didn't come.
Oh, well, you were right, actually. I fooled everyone. It was a very awkward time for all. Nate is here.
Every side of the dreidel is represented here.
Indeed they are. And Ben Saint.
Yo, I'm back from Anthro New England, baby.
Ah, yes. I got pictures. I got proof. It's true.
Hell yeah. I saw teeth from that all weekend, and I was sad that I couldn't go with my lowers but my brothers regardless.
I'll be interested to hear. You want to tell us about it? I'm very curious.
Did you get it on any sick furry orgy's dog?
That's the most important question. I'm afraid I didn't get to weasel a single person.
Oh, what the fuck? Everything I know is a lie.
Actually, most of my, I mean, I was walking around with Kazi in her new Colby Jack suit, which is fucking, is baller by the way.
I've seen it. It's a well-made unit.
Does someone want to post a picture? It's on her timeline.
I'll find one.
But most of my experience was weird drama, friend drama of some people.
We went to one of their friend's hotel room for a bit, for everyone to get suited up.
He didn't confess he was maybe thinking of voting Republican in the presidential.
He wouldn't do that, right? I mean, he wouldn't tank his whole career doing something like that now, I hope.
I mean, I hope he would have more sense than something like that.
Don't we all.
By the way, there's the image you can see in the show notes.
And then we all left the room and we were going to go to a restaurant to eat.
And then we got to the restaurant and suddenly a bunch of these people are like, we have to go.
And they leave and we're like, what the fuck was that about?
And then we find out when we get back that all these people, all these friends of our friends who had their own hotel room,
they all got fucking weirded out and had anxiety attacks because there were too many of us in the room at one time.
And then they were like, we don't want to see them anymore.
They can't be in here anymore.
They didn't say anything about it. It was only later after the fact.
They're like, we have to fucking form a coalition against these other people.
They can't be allowed to intrude on our personal space any further.
Fascinating.
And so they were like, all the stuff was sort of, they gave us the stuff and were like, take this, take this,
you got to give it back to the other people, take this and go.
And I'm like, yeah, cool, whatever.
That was it.
Were you one of the offending intruders or were you part of the core group?
No, I was just a friend of a friend of a friend.
Okay, okay.
And I don't know.
Like, Kazzy and Munchie, their stuff was in the room.
They were just like, here, you know, it's fine.
We had like a mutual friend who was like, she wasn't mad at us.
She was just like, hey, I'm sorry.
You guys, could you just, you know, like these guys are like these other people, they're having a fucking attack.
They're having a fucking episode over here.
Here, I'm sorry, just here's your stuff.
So we had to take all our stuff.
Anyway, we had to leave the convention early.
But I did get, I just, I got to the convention and I just walked in the front door and I asked someone,
I'm like, hey, where's the con?
And he's like, oh, you're going to want to go to a registration.
You're going to go on a ticket.
It's right, it's right through there.
And I'm like, thanks.
Had an exactly the opposite direction.
Just walked directly into the main hall with no tag.
Find them, sit down, watch the end of the furry dance competition.
No ticket required.
Paying for things is for losers.
Well done.
I've always wanted to do that.
Like every year, I mean, aside from the fact that a lot of the cons I go to, I get into for free anyways.
But like, anytime I see a con where it's like the security's not that tight, I'm just like, did I fuck?
Am I a Rube?
Like, should I?
I mean, just for example.
They might have checked my tag, not to go in at all, but to go into the hall where the dance competition was taken.
That's what I was going to say.
They probably would have checked it if I'd gone in at the beginning, but like, it was almost ending anyway.
So I think they just didn't care anymore.
They didn't even, they didn't even ask me.
At Bronycon, the only time you were checked is if you went into like the dealer's hall or I think like any of the main events,
you could 100% wander around and get 90% of the experience.
I've been, it's been that way at a few of the smaller cons I've been to.
And yeah, particularly at Bronycon, I remember it being like, what the fuck?
Like there is no reason anyone should have paid for this convention.
Like the only time they check you is if you go into the main events hall, which none of us did.
So.
I mean, I don't even think that's, is that even frowned upon to do?
I feel like it's almost supposed to be that way to attract lookie-loos to, I don't know, make the event seem more...
Yeah, like anime, anime New England is like that too.
Most conventions they go to, getting into the convention grounds is not hard and does not cost money.
It's, they only check your tag for events and for panels and for the vendors hall and stuff like that.
So for any of you, any of you thrifty would-be con-goers, just consider not buying a ticket.
Well, make sure you know how the con works.
Because there are plenty of cons that do check you at the entrance.
If you're gonna con the con, do your research.
That's fair.
I went right into the main event.
I watched the last like three dancers, including the one who ended up winning.
So I guess I've seen the best dancing that Anthony New England has to offer.
I only, I enjoyed the finest, the finest things in life.
What does a fursuit dance look like?
It's pretty tame, honestly, because like, there's not-
Tame like an animal?
I mean, they can't get, I think they can't get too extreme with it.
Because they'll fucking puss out.
Because their suit will fucking explode, yeah.
Right. I wasn't sure if you meant can't get too extreme, like, they can't do jabberwocky fucking dance maneuvers?
Or like, is it a raunchy dance? Like, is it a pole dance?
No, nothing. And there was nothing raunchy about it.
It was just, there wasn't even any cool like break dance spins.
It was just like, I don't know, it was just-
Being in a fursuit would make break dancing easy on your back, at least.
You just wouldn't be able to slide around, people kick you.
Your friction would be so, you could spin on the ground so much.
Anybody, I mean, I've heard of the like advanced nanotech like water cooling fursuits that they're rolling out.
They're really pioneering like the battle armor technology, the fursuit community.
I'm looking forward to it. Keep it up guys.
Incidentally, Kazzy's fursuit looks like Barney the Dinosaur got fused with Super Eye Patch Wolf's avatar.
I've been seeing her make it for like months, like every time she would come over to my house, she would have like a paw.
And she'd be like, yeah, I was sewing it on the bus. Old women commented on it.
I've seen it come together piece by piece.
This is like actually pro.
Is it supposed to be like a, like what animal is-
It is a fur dragon.
Okay, so it is just like a dragon with a wolf's head and paws basically, right?
It's a dragon.
It's a furry.
It does have kind of a somewhat canine snout there.
Yeah, but it's a dragon with paws and fur.
Pretty dope.
That's it.
Congrats to all involved.
Looks like a triumph.
Seems like a triumph.
I think she's going to start selling them.
I think she's going to start doing this like for money.
Damn.
I mean, it looks like it's quality work.
Yeah, you got the skill.
I think this suit is probably like between like 500 plus hours work.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Remember, what is it? Violent J's daughter received a shitty cosplay costume from some shitty seller.
Next time, look up Kazzy.
Kazzy will do right, but she'll look it up.
Yes.
So, anything else go on there?
Anything else?
I didn't spend that.
I was supposed to go-
Okay, this segues into-
I was supposed to go to it at noon.
I was supposed to get there in the middle of the day, but I overslept.
I slept through my alarm because the previous night I had heard such disturbing news that I could not get to sleep
and I was not able to sleep and I slept through my alarm because of it.
I learned that due to some kind of clerical error or something, I'm not going to be able to vote in the fucking primaries on Super Tuesday.
I fucking registered.
I fucking registered before the deadline.
I went on the 31st.
I checked the box.
I should be registered.
I'm calling the registrar tomorrow.
They're going to get a piece of my mind.
This is bullshit.
This is voter suppression.
This is not democracy.
I'm white.
I'm supposed to be able to vote in these things.
God damn it.
Did you try turning it off and on again?
Maybe.
Yeah, turn the DNC off and on again.
It'll work.
Sir, is it plugged in?
Is your vote plugged in?
I don't know.
Whatever.
I'm going to call the registrar.
That's fucked up, man.
It is.
I did everything right.
I did everything right, but it's still-
I would have assumed you would do everything wrong, but no.
I thought so too.
I saw it.
I checked my status, and it's not registered.
I'm like, oh god, I fucked up.
I fucked up.
I let it go by.
I wasn't paying attention.
I missed the deadline, but then I remembered, no.
I was at the RMV weeks ago, and I filled out the form.
I should be registered.
I registered.
What is this?
What am I looking at?
I did not fuck up.
Is there any hope of remedying this, do you think?
I don't know.
I'm going to call the registrar, and I have no idea what he will say about it.
What is the RMV?
It's the Massachusetts form of the DMV.
It's the Registry of Motor Vehicles as opposed to the Department of Motor Vehicles.
We have a BMV in Ohio.
That's the Bureau of Motor Vehicles.
I didn't know all this.
All over the spectrum, everybody has different ideas.
We have a BMV, the Building of Motion Vehicle.
So I might be cocked out of voting on Super Tuesday, which makes me very sad, very upset,
very frustrated.
But it's okay.
Is Super Tuesday this Tuesday?
It is a week from this Tuesday.
It's March 3rd.
So it'll be the next Tuesday after you, the listener, are hearing this.
But it's okay.
But it's okay because Bernie fucking blew out Nevada.
Bernie obliterated Nevada.
He did.
That snake warren, not even viable.
Not even a single fucking delegate.
Pete Buttigieg scrabbles with his little rat hands just barely over the precipice of viability.
He'll probably get like one and a half delegates.
Biden will get a handful.
He came in.
But Bernie fucking blew it out and got almost half.
He almost got more than everyone else combined.
Ben, did you watch Pete's speech he did after Bernie won Nevada?
I didn't watch the speech, but I saw the tweet.
It was pretty funny.
He was like, congratulations to Bernie.
I'm glad that we agree on so many things he did so well.
I will now proceed to shit on Bernie and tell you how bad he is for the next 20 minutes.
Everyone is just, oh, Pete and Warren, they're all just like, oh, Bernie's so mean.
He yells so much, though.
Like, what a nasty man.
I wouldn't hang that man in my kitchen.
I find it off-putting.
It's a big cope.
Did you see Chris Matthews on NBC?
He compared it to the Nazis.
He compared Bernie blowing out Nevada to the Nazis.
The Nazis blew out the Jews?
The Nazis are conquering France by running over the Maginot Line.
Odd comparison, but okay.
In slightly bad taste, considering Bernie's family was killed in the Holocaust.
Yeah, but that's true of like every Askenazi Jew.
So, I mean, what are we going to do?
We're all day worried about this.
What are we going to never compare Jewish people to Nazis?
I mean, come on.
Once in a while. They build a hell of an Autobahn out there.
There was just a recent struggle tweet about that where a guy was like, he said,
it's like the Holocaust, both parties fault.
The Nazis for killing Jews, the Jews for being Jews.
Wait, yeah, who tweeted that?
I remember that.
Oh, shit.
It seemed like a joke, but then I wasn't sure.
Damn.
Was it like Richard Dawkins or something?
It was. It was somebody who would say that, I believe.
Yeah.
Richard Dawkins isn't like woke on the JQ.
That can't be right, is it?
Well, what he is is a liberal.
And liberals are stupid because liberals, this is what we're seeing.
This is what we're seeing with the mainstream media melting down right now.
Liberals like fascists more than they like socialists.
This is what's had.
They're going to have to fucking learn to deal with it.
People like fascists more than they like socialists.
People do like order.
Sure.
Did you like order?
Well, so, yep, they sure do.
They love it and they're going to cry.
I'm going to drink their tears.
Listen, I know I'm not supposed to say this, but yes, in my heart of hearts,
I do want to see heads on spikes.
Yes, I am the toxic Bernie bro your parents warned you about.
I am one of the bad ones.
That's no secret.
I'm owning it.
Okay.
That's good to know.
But they're not all like me.
Okay.
I'm I'm the bad one.
It wasn't Richard Dawkins who said I knew it.
I knew it.
Both sides to blame.
This has to be a joke.
Let's have a little bit of charity here.
It has to be.
Let me I don't.
I mean, is it like a parody account?
But he's made some pretty fucking.
He's made some like recently he unironically tweeted about how eugenics.
You might not like it, but you can't deny it works.
Okay.
Come on.
That was taken way out of context because his point was like, yes, of course, you can
manipulate the genes of a population if you choose to, but morally, obviously you don't
want to.
But you know, you could if you wanted to just don't do it.
Which is true.
Yes, it's true.
But why would you say it like that?
Why would you say it works?
I don't know.
Every there's no like nobody contends that you cannot manipulate a genome through selective
breeding.
Nobody needed that pointed out to them.
As always.
Okay.
Were you in the none of us were in the fucking conversation he was responding to and we're
just taking the thing.
Let me look.
I'm going to look right now.
I'm going to look up the content.
There are just so many stupid people on Twitter that you probably would have to spell out
something like that if you like start talking with all the dregs, you know.
I don't really know anything about Richard Dawkins.
Other than I've heard his face.
Richard Dawkins.
His name.
I believe in God.
A relevant writer who a decade and a half, who a couple decades ago was pretty big because
he wrote some books about how atheism is kind of cool actually.
The God of delusion was him.
The God of delusion.
Yes.
I've heard all of that.
He was one of the four horsemen with Sam Harris and the other guys.
In any case, I mean the thing you're referring to Ben with him talking about eugenics, he
does in his follow up tweet say, I deplore the idea of a eugenic policy.
I simply said deploring it doesn't mean it wouldn't work.
Is it a dog whistle, Ben?
Does he actually support it?
Work to do what?
Is this his position?
To eugenicize humanity?
How much more clear can he be?
Obviously it would work.
I'm just saying, look, I'm not saying Richard, I didn't say Richard Dawkins made these tweets
to unironically promote.
It's just a weird thing to say.
And here's another.
This Jew thing is even weirder.
I don't know.
That's all I have to say about it.
Bernie Rondavada, Deb.
It's going to be okay, America.
Okay.
No, it's not.
You think the DNC is going to fuck him?
What?
Hey, what's the position of Steve?
You think the DNC is going to fuck him out?
They have super delegates, don't they?
I don't really still have the chance.
They have super delegates, but they do not come into the vote until after the first
until after all the pledge delegates.
So if he were to win a majority, or anyone were to win a majority of regular delegates,
the super delegates would not be allowed to vote.
Okay, I see.
Oh, do you know about like on the last debate, the last question, they asked everyone like
should the person who gets, even if there's no majority, should the person who gets the
plurality of delegates be made the nominee?
And everyone but Bernie said no because they don't believe in democracy and their shitlibs
and they have no values.
Hmm, I did see that.
Okay, I see your point.
Although to be fair, if Bernie has a plurality but not a majority, can it really necessarily
be said that he like, you know, is in fact the winner?
Shouldn't they pair things down and decide?
Because that's not like the 51% has decided that they won.
Pair things down to who?
Well, you know, like to do like that, it's not first past the post, but that voting system
where the weakest candidates are limited.
Like democracy isn't just there's one thing, there's one way of doing it specifically,
and we know that's real democracy and every other voting system is bad.
There are different ways to do it, including the like the CGP gray model of like everybody
wants if there is no majority.
Yes, that's fine and all, but like that has no relevance at all to the super delegates
and the convention.
There is no alternative vote.
It is, yeah, the super delegates just are a secondary block of unpledged voters who
just get to vote whoever the fuck they want.
I don't want that.
That should go away.
I don't know why that exists.
That seems wrong and not good.
You know who else thinks that that's bad and shouldn't exist?
Elizabeth Warren and Pete Buttigieg, who all said that it was bad and undemocratic
until suddenly it was their only chance at the nomination and now they all support it.
Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben, don't you understand once they have power, they will make things good.
You just need to trust them.
Yes, that's true.
This is what you don't understand, Ben.
You have to trust them.
They know what's best for you.
I do.
I do trust them.
They are standing out with a podium.
I mean, I'm not standing up with a podium.
I'm on team P now.
So, better listen.
Warren's the immoral after a plant position of power becomes moral once you are in power.
I love it.
It's fantastic.
That's my plan too.
You can't argue with it.
Or you go to the fucking vote room.
Anyway, it's all very upsetting.
Anyway, the point being that, yeah, if Bernie doesn't get the majority, it's possible the
super delegates will screw him out of it.
They'll come in and they'll be like, uh, we're actually all going to vote for Bloomberg, so
he gets the nomination instead because he paid us too.
I'm ready for the Bloomberg.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to...
I'm ready to hashtag vote bloom no matter whom.
That's...
No matter whom he is, if he changes himself.
The delegates are going to vote bloom no matter whom.
So Bernie changes his last name to Bloomberg.
He gets all the votes instead.
Oh, sneaky.
But I don't know.
There's a possibility that it might not come to that.
Bernie might end up with a majority.
We don't know.
He's going to start winnowing.
Elizabeth Warren needs to drop out soon.
Pete Klobuchar, even I would say Biden at this.
Honestly, nobody else even has a chance.
Just get them all out of here.
Just get them out of the country.
Leave them out.
Just throw them into the ocean.
I don't know if I want the field to narrow down for Bernie to soak up more support, or
if I like that the center's vote is split between all these fucking nobodies.
That's the question, isn't it?
That's the X factor.
I'm not sure.
Did I mention...
I realized that I didn't mention...
Before New Hampshire, I was making calls.
Did I say that I was making calls for Bernie on the PCK?
You mentioned it at some point.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I was fucking in there.
I was in there because I was really worried about New Hampshire, and it turns out I had
every one...
$1,000 to our next Kickstarter to get a personal Bernie Sanders endorsement phone call from
Ben St. who will convince you to vote for Bernie.
Yeah.
That's what my reward is.
I will convince you to vote for Bernie Sanders, no matter what.
We'll be here all day.
We'll go over all the facts and logic until...
Oh, boy.
Do I have anything else to say about...
Do I have anything else to say about that whole charade?
I don't know.
South Carolina's coming up.
Biden might win South Carolina, but the gap is narrowing.
Bernie might actually be ahead by the time they do the poll.
I don't know.
Open quit.
If Biden doesn't win South Carolina, he needs to fucking drop out.
He is dead in the water if he doesn't win South Carolina.
He's probably dead in the water anyway, to be perfectly...
Yon!
You bore us, Ben.
Yes, yes.
Collectively.
All right.
Let's do something else.
I've said all I have to say.
I'm not following it.
I have nothing to add to this.
It's fine.
Here's the thing.
I'm following it, and I have nothing to add to it.
Fair enough.
I'm really excited for the debate on Tuesday.
Join my discord where every time there's a debate, we all get in the discord and are
like, oh my god.
Did you guys watch the debate?
I only saw a little bit of bloom getting up.
This last debate was unbelievable.
It was by far the funnest debate.
There's a part where Pete Buttigieg and Klobuchar are literally just screaming at each other,
and the moderator cannot quiet them down.
They just keep going.
That happened a couple of times.
Klobuchar's barely contained rage is palpable.
It's so uncomfortable.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
Considering that she probably views him as an upstart guy, she's like, how is this fucking
guy questioning me?
Well, it was about a thing in a recent interview.
She was not able to name the president of Mexico.
Oh, right.
The people, the moderators asked her about it, and she was like, you're right.
I hate Mexicans.
I don't view them as human beings.
You got me.
You want to understand my position.
She's like, it was just a slip of the tongue, and Pete Buttigieg, fucking psychopath, is
like, I don't believe that that's true.
I don't believe like, are you, like, how can we trust someone who would forget something
so important?
And she gets fucking like really defensive.
She gets, she's like, I'm sorry, we're not all as perfect as you, Mayor Pete.
Are you calling me stupid?
Are you saying I'm dumb?
And he basically just goes on and says yes.
I think I speak for a large portion of our audience when I say I couldn't give less of
a fuck about anything in the world possibly.
So fair point.
I was fucking on the edge of my seat.
I was on the edge of my seat.
I was edging on my seat.
I was edging the whole time.
And then at the end, last thing, and then at the end when Bernie just does literal fucking
Marxism to Bloomberg, that was when I had the coom.
That's when they're like, do you deserve to be a billionaire, Bloomberg?
And he's like, yes, I worked very hard for it.
And Bernie's like, don't you think your workers are the ones responsible for that fortune?
Don't you think they deserve some of the credit for it?
Just literal fucking Marxism, literal class consciousness.
Bernie's a hero.
He's my hero.
I mean, Bernie's a millionaire though.
You're such a fucking moron, Nate.
Your IQ is fridge temperature level.
Let's go on with that, Ben.
Yeah.
With you being ironic, I can never tell.
Who knows?
Okay.
Yeah.
A great point.
A great stupid point, also made by fellow stupid low IQ moron, Michael Bloomberg, on the debate
stage, which is why he's basically out of the running at this point.
Good job.
Let's move on.
A fellow bloomer.
How exciting for all of us.
Finally, we'll get the bloomer representation, the most oppressed minority in the White House,
looking forward to it.
We need more.
We're all about to bloom.
We need more voter suppression.
When you think about it, who is a bigger minority than billionaires?
Just saying.
It's true.
Right.
Just saying.
It's true.
They're guillotines way more often than non-billionaires are.
You should join the guillotine, Ben, when the guillotine, when they are rolling out through
the streets.
I will be the first one.
I will be the first one out there.
And I'll probably be the first one that they turn on.
I've had enough of this crap.
Yes.
I said let's move on.
I am talking about the artistic creative process because I'm having art problems, artist boy
problems, anxiety about things I do, always being not good enough, no matter what it is.
Tell me about it, bro.
You can take-
Sounds like our democratic process.
You can take any multitude of potential reasons.
I felt bad about this because I didn't use a reference and you're supposed to do that.
Or I did use a reference and I felt like I was cheating.
I used something and it didn't work out the way I wanted it.
Any potential reason for upset with the art.
And the core reason is always the same.
And it's just that I'm afraid of death and everything that I'm doing with regards to art,
when I'm trying to get good, when I'm trying to improve the quality of what I can draw,
what I can create, what's going through my head is this feeling of every moment I do something,
it has to be working towards being good because I only have a limited amount of time on this
earth and I'm going to die if I don't do it fast enough.
I need to be efficient.
I need to be making the most of the time I have.
And as that's going through my head and I'm drawing something and it's not perfect,
I'm thinking, okay, what could I be doing wrong?
And I'm thinking of all the tutorials that I didn't fully watch or the things I could have been doing,
the techniques that people have told me about and I've kind of forgotten how to do.
And I'm like, oh shit, my knowledge banks are too low.
I don't have the capability to be efficient.
It's a lost cause.
I'm a lost cause.
This drawing, which admittedly is fine, is terrible and I've wasted my life and I'm a worst person ever.
And it's all downed to the whole death thing.
And I'm trying to figure out how to not be scared of death.
That's my goal.
I'll tell you.
Tell me if you want to.
Well, I can help to some degree because you just got to think about the fact that death will come
suddenly and there's no way to predict it.
Oh, that makes me feel so much better.
Thank you.
Well, there's no point.
We're in.
Right.
That's kind of the way I look at it.
It's like, I don't see much point in considering it because it's like, well, I know that if it happens,
it's going to happen suddenly or it'll be obvious long before it happens.
I fear death a lot, but I fear disability significantly more.
That's my...
Well, it's not literally just about death.
It's that death is the cause of my artistic anxiety.
Like the reason I hate myself through my art is because I'm scared that I'm not getting
fast enough, good enough.
Right.
I think like, for me, it's kind of like, I understand that fear in the sense of like,
oh, I don't want to, you know, what if I don't get good enough before I die?
But it's like, you won't.
You won't get good enough before you die.
It's just not going to happen.
Like you'll never, because there's no ceiling on it.
You'll always want to get better.
At no point will you look at your stuff and be like, okay, now I can die happy, you know?
True.
I do feel like though there are like very obvious milestones and I am currently in the
mediocre artist point where I can't easily sketch something that looks okay.
I need to spend a long time on anything.
I mean, like, if you...
I mean, all artists spend a long time on things.
I know that, but like, you see how like someone who has a very good grasp of, you know, drawing
can, you know, sketch a little cartoon character, a little doodle.
And it can be like clearly, you know, if you put lines on the line art on that, that would
be a great drawing.
And they didn't think about it too much.
It's sort of on autopilot.
I maybe wouldn't realize when I hit that point, which is the reason like you would always
be aiming higher and higher until you're dead.
But I know of certain things that I need to improve about my drawing.
And once I feel like I've conquered them or like I can conquer them in individual drawings
without tearing my hair out, I will know that I have gotten to a good point.
I think it's a good idea to just, you know, I mean, obviously practicing all the time.
But like specifically just like doing as much different stuff as possible because I feel
like the best way to get through, like to make breakthroughs in any kind of art is to
stop trying to force the thing that you're trying to do and just go do something else
and come back later and see if you've figured it out by then, you know, because like you
never know where the answer that's going to unblock your understanding might come from.
It's like maybe you're like, oh, why can't I get these colors right, you know, and then
you go and draw a bunch of other shit and then while you're working on something else,
you're like, oh, this color, this is the one I needed for that other drawing I was trying to do,
you know, just like maybe it's just a good idea to, you know, if you hit something,
you're not sure how to fix this problem you have, just go do something else.
Well, here's the thing. I'm aware of like certain practices and tutorials, things I can go to
for like information on how to do specific things. It's not a specific thing necessarily
that I'm having trouble figuring out what it is. It's more of a getting past that initial
like death spiral way of thinking. As soon as you start a drawing, you open up the program,
you're looking at it and you draw the first little bit and you're like, oh no, this isn't
going to work and that stops you. I don't let that happen to me. I try to just power through
the whole thing as fast as possible. Sometimes I'm not thinking and that's the thing that always
seems to work is that when I'm not thinking about getting better, I draw and therefore get better
and I really want to know how to stop thinking. I need some sort of way to make myself an idiot
while I do this stuff. I was thinking, hmm, let's just drink profusely, but I'm not sure
that's a really good idea. That doesn't seem like the best solution. Just get into marijuana.
It's worked for me so well. I mean, it's not legal in the UK and I really don't want to talk to teenagers.
It's not legal where I am either, but... There's a guy I know. This is in no way a solution to your
problem, but what it is is another example of a guy I'm currently mystified by the insane amount
of talent that this person has. Do you guys know who Mark Rebele is? Or Rebele? Nope.
Does this sound familiar to anybody? Okay, Mark Rebele. I've never actually heard the name pronounced out loud.
I've just seen it on YouTube and stuff. So he's a musician and what he does is he has made a career.
He quit his job a while back and has gone pro like doing sets where he will set in coffee shops
and restaurants and on stage. He's getting more and more popular these days where he will set up his
keyboard and he will have zero set list and he will go up and he will improv, but he used loops
and samplers and stuff to capture his own voice and to in real time mix full on songs that he 100%
improvs based on audience submission and stuff. So okay, here's a link to, in my opinion, the
greatest work of art of the 21st century, which is a song called Work That As For Daddy.
Yeah, this song. It's an eight minute long, jazzy breakdown song just built around the
concept of Big Booty Black Girl. That's it. And he just makes up all the lyrics based on that.
And it is an absolute journey to go on. And I've watched this so many times, once I love the song,
and two, because I know that like, okay, he has to have like his keyboard, his sampler, he has to know music
and how to loop things correctly. But I'm so in awe of all the skills that went into in real time.
He did this on a live stream one time. This is literally what I want my life to be.
It is so amazing. He's bought all the equipment that I dream of having.
And he's just rapping, he's just literally saying, yo, give me that ass, give me that fucking booty.
And he looks like Anthony Fantano when he was 18.
I'm sucking your booty and ass in the same place. Whatever the fuck it was.
Oh, I'm sucking your pussy and ass in the same place. Gotta work that ass for daddy.
And he looks like a Anthony Fantano who's in shape with hair. It's nuts. He looks like a pedophile and it's great.
He's a monster, but I love him. And I'm just in awe of this.
And as a guy who has just dabbled a little bit into music and music composition here and there, total, total amateur shit.
Like, I've talked about this before. It's like this man's casting a fucking magical spell.
He knows the Harry Potter runes and glyphs to just do magic in front of me. And I don't get it at all.
It's funny that you're so impressed with it just because I do get it. I get like how this, how you do this.
I mean, okay, answer this question. I've had one question about this.
The hardest thing about this to me seems how to get the loops to sync up perfectly in real time.
You gotta press the button at the right exact second, you know?
That seems so hard to do that consistently.
It's the same as playing notes on the beat consistently.
But that's hard, though. It's kind of the most basic skill you need to have.
If you can tap your feet to a beat, you can eventually, you know, transfer that skill into doing something.
And the fact of the matter is, there is some, you know, margin of error allowance.
Like, I'm thinking about, like, times I've seen live bands where they have to, like, Agiloch,
which I know, Hippo, you listened to, like, the whole Agiloch discography the other day, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah. The, uh...
Yeah, what'd you think about that?
I liked it. There was a lot of, like, the deep, screamy...
Well, not a lot, actually. There's just bits of it.
But, yeah, it was very moody and very cool.
Good background music for working.
Yeah. When I saw Agiloch live, because they switch back and forth between a, like, unplugged-and-plugged-in sound,
in order to, you know, switch between guitar tonalities, they have to, like, press a switch with their, you know,
like, the kick down on a little switch.
But there's often moments in the songs where it, like, dramatically transitions between, like, acoustic and electric.
So you have to hit that thing on the floor just at the right time to...
You know, and you can see that it's, it definitely seems like a bit of a struggle to remember to do it at the right time.
I definitely had trouble with guitar pedals and stuff.
I never seem to... I mean, it was years ago that I've been using guitar pedals and, like,
when I used to be in, like, a school band playing, like, little rock things.
And you're doing the thing with your hands, and then you go to, like, okay, lift, like, your foot up and land on something.
Anything involving your feet, like, what this guy is doing in this video is, it's funny.
This is exactly... When I said, like, this is what I want to do, I'm not exaggerating.
I literally want this equipment because I have a habit of banging on desks, like, making desk beats and stuff
just out of not being able to sit still.
And, like, those pads, the synth pads, like, what he's got there that he's doing his beats on,
ever since I saw the Kanye West video for Runaway where he's playing the beat pad to the Phoenix,
I was like, oh, I don't have to learn how to play drums.
Drumming is so hard. Like, to me, this looks easy.
Drumming where you have to time your hands and legs together is nearly impossible.
I cannot coordinate my hands and feet.
But if you just press buttons on a pad with your hands, it's so much easier to control and time your hands.
So, you know, something like this, this seems like a way I actually could perform music that, you know,
would be less difficult than any other method.
Every day, every time I stream, I'm getting more and more of a master.
I'm acquiring these skills via my soundboard, which I would mash right now,
but none of you will hear it in the recording, so I'll do it for myself.
Heh, heh, epic. Bruh, bruh, bruh, bruh.
You know, music has also been one of the things I've been trying to make on, like, a garage band on my iPad.
Just simple beats that, you know, they loop, so I don't need to think about time too much.
And I'm just trying, desperately trying to make something that sounds like it could be on a Gorillaz album,
and then I'm gonna sing over it.
But every time I make, I make the beat, and I'm like,
I think I have a trouble, like, figuring out how to structure the song.
Maybe Digi, you could help with that.
Like, like advice, because I have the beat and it loops,
and then I add a thing, and now it suddenly, there's too many things, and it's too cluttered, so I get rid of it.
I can't figure out how to visualize the entire song before I have something to sing to.
If you're having trouble with too many layers, like too much sound, is that what you mean?
I don't know, I have a few things where they just sound like amateur, doesn't know what he's doing, sort of beats.
I would say that part of what I've learned is that the EQ matters a lot,
in the sense that a beat is usually prepared out of elements that don't exist on the same frequency as your voice.
So think of a rap beat, usually bass and hi-hats are the main focus,
because it's either way super deep or way super high-pitched, but your voice tends to fall into the mid-range.
So as you're customizing a beat, a professional producer would try to create the beat around the singer's range,
try to figure out where do we fit your voice in there,
or make a good singer, of course, will also know to fit their singing to the beat,
but for me, I try to seek out beats that I will sound good on top of.
I more or less know where my voice falls in the range from just looking at my singing through an equalizer.
So I just try to make it so there is space in the beat for that sound frequency that nothing else is on that exact spot.
And granted, I don't do this very often, most of my music just sounds like shit.
It just sounds like a garbled mess, because I can't avoid these problems,
either because I didn't make the beat or whatever else.
But when you're actually making your own, it's very nice to get to go like,
I will sometimes create a beat just by thinking,
alright, let me find a low-pitched noise and a high-pitched noise and something in the middle that doesn't counteract my voice.
And if you have those three things, you're done, essentially.
You just got to arrange them into a song.
I guess I just got to work at it a bit.
It always annoys me. I'm getting close. I have a bass line.
I play that and it loops and it's like, that's pretty good.
I add some drums and it's like, yeah, it's pretty good, but it doesn't feel like a song.
Well, it also helps remember, especially if you're doing a guerrilla style thing,
that most of it is sample-based.
Rather than just making it out of the sounds that are built into the program,
it might help to go and just go find drum sounds that you want to use
or make your own samples or even something like that.
I'm sure that a lot of...
In the case of guerrillas, the album The Fall, I think he literally made that
in a week on his iPad while flying to new places or something.
When I learned that he made it on an iPad, I was like, okay, well, I have an iPad.
Maybe I could try. Maybe he could make something.
It's funny because I used to fuck around in GarageBand way back when I had a Mac,
and that makes that kind of thing a lot easier because it comes with a sample pack.
A lot of those guys, I don't know if Damon Albarn specifically uses GarageBand,
but I will hear the sounds that are pre-packaged with GarageBand in all kinds of music,
especially TV shows.
AudioJungle.com.
Even Yuki Kajiyura, who's my favorite anime soundtrack composer,
I know she uses GarageBand just because some of those loops come up in her songs.
I'm like, ah, there they are. I've played with these myself,
but it's also a little embarrassing when you hear it too much.
I'm watching House Hunters or something, and I'm like, okay, I know all this music is made out of three loops.
The soundtrack was crafted in 30 minutes, and I could have done it myself.
I mean, I don't really mind that it feels...
The thing that I've always had problems with in music is just having songs that have beginnings and endings
and hooks and stuff, like a flow.
I don't really care what I make it with or how it sounds.
All you need is 8 bars of intro, 16 bars for the first verse, 8 bars of chorus, 16 bars for the second verse,
8 bars of chorus, some kind of bridge for 4 to 8 bars, 8 bars of chorus again, 8 bars of outro.
That's every pop song, so...
Okay, there you go.
Write that down, kids.
Yeah, let me actually write that down.
She delivered for you.
Clickety-clack down the track.
And at 130 BPM, that almost always equals a 2-minute song, which is why nowadays,
rap music, you'll notice that there are so many songs that are almost exactly 2 minutes,
and it's just because if you just do that structure I just described at the minimal level,
it will always come out to 2 minutes.
You'll see that on a lot of my albums that I did with Shade,
because he just builds a song to that structure, and it's just like, okay, done.
Is that going to be the Radcon rap?
Is it going to be exactly 2 minutes?
No, it'll probably be much longer, because there's 6 of us on it.
We've got a lot to cover.
There's a lot of garlic to butter, a lot of bread to slice, you know.
Gotcha, gotcha.
Obviously, we're in the middle of the show right now, but what do we want this track to be?
Do we want it to be an epic length of this track, or like a cool, in and out, more of a hit song?
I was thinking, for the purposes of the, you know, it's a story.
The PCP got hacked, and we're dissing Brad Garlic House.
I think it should be a storytelling song, instead of just a fucking view.
I think that the music video should tell the story, if there is one, and the song is just...
Well, I mean, there's one of the same.
You can't really tell a story with a song that isn't telling a story.
I mean, of course you can. Music videos hold the time of stories that aren't in the song.
Usually in the song, maybe you don't pay attention to the lyrics.
Usually the video is like an interpretation of the song on some level, but...
I'm not literally saying, like, let's start with a story time, of course.
Like, once upon a time, the PC... I mean, we could do that.
Well, I don't care what we do with it, honestly, but if we don't tank Ripple XRP when the release of that song comes,
we will have failed our mission, so that's my one thing that I want to have happen.
My one thing is that we're on the PCP channel right now.
That would be nice. That would be nice, Brad.
Help us out.
Where's this going?
No? Okay, never mind.
You're gonna upload this episode on your channel, Nate?
I don't know. Probably not, considering I already said I don't want to.
Yeah. Why is that?
There you go. Because my channel is for very specific content.
Okay. So, like, it wasn't in the plan or anything.
It wasn't in your plan or anything that, like, any of these PCP episodes might go up on your channel.
But the rest of us, though, that was our plan.
Uh, fair enough.
No, I'm saying that ironically, man. Being sarcastic.
I'm saying you're being selfish for not wanting to upload this on your channel,
when the rest of us are totally willing to do it.
That's what I'm saying. Fuck you.
You are welcome to have that opinion.
I do. Fair enough.
Okay.
Well, result.
Excellent.
Hey, Tom.
Yo.
What's going on with you, dog?
Uh, I made a cell shader, and I'm really proud of it.
That's what I did while everyone else doing PCP the last two weeks.
I figured it out.
I made in Blender a shader that looks just like a cartoon,
really easily, and it looks good, and it has line art that, like, scales.
It doesn't get distorted as a bunch of 3D nerd shit that most people don't understand.
But it looks great, and it's crisp, and it's perfect, and I love it,
and I put an animation up on Twitter.
Uh, it's great. 10 out of 10.
Unlocked full potential of doing cartoon style in Blender.
Really proud. 10 out of 10, good times.
What if we used 100% of our brain?
Oh, we have the answer. We have the answer.
Yeah, you get perfect cell shading. That's what happens.
I saw... I was reading political articles.
Oh, no. That's nothing to do with cell shading.
I got accidentally redirected to some article,
and it was like Jeff Bezos talking about...
No, no, it's like Trump says to Bill Gates,
like, you will not ban this invention. The American people need it.
I was like, what the fuck is this?
And it was talking about some, like, breakthrough.
Like, Bill Gates says, we can now access 100% of the brain.
It was just a fake article for, like, some brain pills.
It was just, like, some fucking brain pills of advertisement.
Thank you, Alex Jones for bringing those to our attention.
Yes, it was Alex Jones' tear shit, and I had been had.
I've been having those every day, and I can tell you they don't affect me very much.
Sorry, my internet...
I already had 100% of my brain, I guess. You know, what are you gonna do?
My internet cut out for a second. What was being said?
Brain pills.
Thumbs up or thumbs down.
He's a genius now.
He bought and invested.
Here's, I'll just run this by you guys.
This is a thought I was having earlier about a potential video I might make
about different types of level design and game design
and storytelling and game design.
And I was thinking about it because of Dark Souls.
I started playing Dark Souls 3 again, which is fucking bay.
It is.
I was thinking about how Dark Souls 1 is definitely way more open-ended.
There's a lot more you can do, a lot more variety in the ways you can play it.
But how Dark Souls 3 is so opulent and tightly crafted,
and it's like every single moment of it is really memorable, to me at least.
I was thinking about the trade-off between more modern and older games,
and how most modern games are trying to create a very linear, tightly crafted experience,
but with a lot of depth, at least in the visual and graphics department,
where they're trying to make it so that there's a lot of verbosity to the storytelling.
That's the term I've come up with.
The way I would describe what is verbosity in a video game setting is
if you were to translate this into a book, how many words would it take
to convey everything that's on the screen?
That's just a normal word, Digi. That just is a word that means that.
Yes.
Well, I'm applying it to game design, because in the case...
So to give an example of a game that I would consider to be not verbose,
but also extremely nonlinear would be Dwarf Fortress, right?
Almost anything can happen in that game, but the way that it will happen,
the way it will be described to you, is just a sentence telling you that it happened,
whereas in say like...
I think I've heard this video.
Yeah? Are you saying somebody's already made this point that I'm making here?
No, it's you. Didn't you talk about Dwarf Fortress in that big,
old or autistic something or other something?
I don't think so. I don't remember.
You were talking about all the different forms of our mediums and then how they...
Oh, I don't...
I don't think I did talk about Dwarf Fortress in that video, but maybe.
I don't remember if I did, but...
Anyway, point being that in that game, like, tons of things can happen,
but they will not be described in very much detail.
It's just kind of telling you that the thing happened,
as like in an uncharted game or something, even just like Nick Drake jumps and grabs ledge.
Like, that story is told in like an obscene amount of detail through the visuals and graphics and all that.
So, like, the question becomes, like, what makes...
I don't know if I agree with this at all.
Like, the game's state of Dwarf Fortress is so much more complex than any of these other games you're talking about.
We're talking about raw graphical representation, though, right?
To fully...
Well, that's such verbosity.
To fully describe the game's state of Dwarf Fortress would take so many more words.
Yes, well, that's the thing.
To describe the current game's state, but the game's state should be...
If I'm playing uncharted, for instance, like, if I were to say that, like,
describing this one moment, all that simply is happening is that Nate Drake is, you know, climbing up a wall.
But, like, that is in the middle of the ongoing story of what's happening.
Like, in Dwarf Fortress, one thing is happening right now.
But, yes, to describe everything that led up to that point would take a long time.
Well, one thing is happening, but, like, one thing is happening, like, everywhere simultaneously.
Like, a separate thing.
Like, every tile of the map has its own state and, like, every entity that exists has its own state
and, like, also history of everything that ever happened to it.
Would you say that that state is, like...
How do I put it?
Because, like, I agree with you that, like, keeping track of what's happening in Dwarf Fortress would be, like, a much more complex operation.
I'm just thinking about, like, if let's say that one of the stories being told in this game is, like, Dwarf goes too well, you know?
Like, there is nothing to that other than that phrase in that game, you know?
Whereas, like, Nate Drake Goes Too Well has a visual representation that tells another conglomerate of stories
through the art design and everything else like that, you know?
And this is...
I mean, there is information conveyed in...
I mean, I think both games have certain information that they do convey and certain information that they don't.
I mean, visually, in terms of, like, what it looks like when he does this thing, yeah, there's a lot more going on in Uncharted.
Are we talking about Uncharted?
Whatever game, it doesn't matter.
Uncharted is just the first HD, visually focused, you know, experience-driven game.
It was just making me think about how, essentially, you always are going to have to kind of pick where on this slider you want to be,
because there's, like, limited time and resources to get anything made.
And so, the more nonlinear an experience is going to be, the less verbose it necessarily can be within the same, you know, same resources
as making something linear but super verbose, you know?
You're talking about how you can't have a character progression and a story arc in Minecraft,
because it's Minecraft, you know, to have that, like, randomly generate would be impossible.
Yeah, that's...
Yes, that is partly what I'm saying as well.
Like, in any game where...
I guess I'm thinking more about, like, Asset Generation, like, the sheer complexity of Dwarf Fortress,
you can't, like, the reason it doesn't have a visual interface is that you'd have to just account for so many possibilities,
it would take fucking forever, you know, to create, like, an actual visual interpretation of what's happening.
So, you know, the way I see it, it's just like, any of those games, like, the games with the super complex systems almost never have super complex graphics, you know?
That almost always comes down to a more linear experience.
And, you know, on that point, it ties into the video I've long been thinking about making, which is this, like, whatever it is,
I've yet to find a satisfying teleport, but it's like the, like, cap or, like, the curve of, like, intellectual...
Like, the ceiling of intellectual complexity, meaning, the more, like, take your Final Fantasy XV, that game is quote-unquote complex,
but it's complex in many superficial ways that don't tie into, at least superficial in terms of gameplay,
but in terms of, like, rendering and graphical representation, like, all the complexity is there.
When it comes to gameplay, you mash X to attack. And there's other options, too.
And that's part of what I kind of want, like, the takeaway from this video idea I have to be.
And it's something I've been saying in a lot of my videos lately, is just that, like, I really think that when you're crafting a story,
you should always be asking yourself, like, what story am I telling right now?
Not so much in, like, the broad sense of, like, everything has to fit into my grand narrative,
but just that whatever you're doing, it should be telling a story.
It should contribute to the telling of a story, and if it doesn't tell a story or contribute to the story,
or it's not an interesting story, then just try to get rid of it, you know?
Like, if there's parts in a video game where, let's say you're just walking through empty space
and maybe that could be because, let's say you're playing Xenoblade, right?
And you're in a gigantic open field full of monsters and it's, like, really epic
and you feel swept up in the moment, like, that's a good story about wandering around through an open field.
But usually, wandering around through an open field is not a story and it's not interesting,
and, you know, you would want to cut down on how much random wandering there is in your game
unless that's, like, core to the point, like, Skyrim. And even then, it's boring.
It's just a connection, the connecting thread that needs to be there for the story
to feel the way that it does, you know?
But, like, overall, like, you know, trimming the fat is a good idea
and I think that the biggest problem with these AAA games that go all in on the graphics
is that they don't always tell the story.
They're not always contributing or at least not contributing enough
for it to be worth the extra effort they're putting in, you know?
It's like, how much, at what point does the verbosity become purple prose?
It's just fill in, you know, extra detail that really wasn't necessarily
and doesn't contribute to the story, you know?
That's nearly all of graphics. Like, how much does it...
The way of rock is rendered with, like, perfect lighting
and it's like, oh, it's glistening with water and it's also dynamic
and graphics intensive and computer intensive
and that rock, like, slightly more sells the realisticness of the location
but it's so redundant at some point.
Like, it's been redundant for years.
You can feel like...
For a game that isn't redundant, though, would be Dark Souls.
Like, Dark Souls 3, everything you see tells a story in that game, you know?
I was going to mention Bloodborne, but yeah, the same thing with that.
So, like, and even just the random things that are used to sort of spruce up the environment,
like, I think about Deus Ex Human Revolution, right?
That game has tons and tons of random, like, papers and stuff on all the desks in everybody's room
and it's almost all repeated.
Like, you can recognize the exact same assets in, like, every room in the game
but they're just there to make it so that every room feels like somebody lives in it, you know?
And I'm fine with that. Like, obviously, it's a little distracting that the same stuff comes up over and over again
but do I think that the game looks better with the clutter than it would without it?
I do kind of think so.
And, like, in the case of Dark Souls, like, there's all these random bodies strewn about all over the place, right?
But, like, you know, they're placed in ways that look good.
They contribute to the feeling of the setting and the story that has been told before you got there, you know?
And even if a lot of it is just obviously the same clone-stamped bodies, it's the way they're arranged,
the way that, you know, meaning is derived from putting a character next to an object
or putting it in this location or the story of, you know, going to this one random platform
is interesting because of the item layout and the enemy layout.
It's just the game is always telling a story.
Every single encounter is a story, you know?
This gives me a really cool idea.
Imagine a game that the story is about things being copy-pasted.
So it would be, you know, like mass-produced, like, everybody, like, there would be the same clutter in everybody's house,
but the reason all the clutter is the same is because everybody's being fed the same information
and they're sort of like a hive mind of people.
You could make the, you know, having to copy-paste things for saving money into the story of the game,
and then it would make more sense, and it would be like, oh, yeah.
That is a good idea.
I think, you know, this, tell your time.
Why don't you try and say something before I'll go after you?
I was just going to say, I think that the problem that you're talking about comes from just, like, intent and laziness, right?
Because, like, all these big AAA games, they want to be filmed.
Like, they're trying to be filmed.
That's why they have, like, these narrow scopes with this really, like, crazy amount of detail and stuff,
and also because, like, it's easier to sell to people,
especially when your entire industry is kind of based on technological progression.
So it's like making an uncharted game that has, like, basically no depth, but, like, is a visual tour de force,
is A, more filmic, which is what the normal people kind of understand.
Like, oh, it looks like a movie.
And it's easier to iterate on technical aspects than to be creative and build story.
And, like, the money still flows.
Yeah, I mean, in the case of Uncharted, like, I think they really, they base the Uncharted games around the set pieces for the most part.
So I think they look at it as, like, what's a crazy, exciting set piece we can create
and what is necessary to make that happen.
And, like, I do think that the realism of those games adds to those scenes where some of them are really well done.
Like, this comes down to a problem of, like, for instance, Tomb Raider in the new Tomb Raider series,
all the times where it, like, changes controls for a dramatic scene and, like, becomes a movie.
They all suck. They're horrible.
And, like, every time one of those scenes happens.
Because they have to be incredibly easy so you can do it instantly.
Or they're not incredibly easy to do the first time, but it's completely fucking just asinine.
Like, it's worse to fail it than it is to get it right the first time.
But those scenes, I hate them.
And every time they would come up, I would just think, like, man, this game had such a ludicrously overblown budget.
Because Tomb Raider 2013 or whatever, it was, like, it sold, like, six million copies
and was still a disappointment for Square Enix.
It's just like, why did you put all these fucking expensive scripted sequences that don't contribute anything to the story?
They are not interesting stories in and of themselves. They are dull, generic.
They're all the same story.
A lot of cruffed slides down a fucking hill.
That's, I mean, like, it's totally true, but Tomb Raider 1 or the 2013 one was critically acclaimed.
Everybody loved it. It got praise from everybody.
It is a great game, aside from those scenes. That's the thing.
Like, everything else it does, it does right.
But I think most people, I think there are a lot of people, like, the mass market,
that enjoy the spectacle of those scenes and don't care about the lack of complexity.
Maybe. But those are definitely true.
That is what I think is the biggest thing that hurts modern games is that they throw in too much frivolous shit
and one frivolous thing in a game that costs millions to generate, like, a second of gameplay, you know?
It's a lot of fucking wasted money.
Right.
Here's an interesting example about that.
So I've recently, I replayed Kingdom Hearts 3 recently on Critical Mode.
The game is a nightmare. It's a disaster, like, through most of it.
The only times that that game is good is some amusing, like, engagement between the Disney stories,
like the characters and the original Kingdom Hearts story.
Sometimes that's good, like in Monsters, Inc., a little bit, and in Toy Story.
Like, the ending of the game is an absolute nightmare, makes me want to kill myself.
Absolute fuck up.
But the DLC, well, first of all, Critical Mode was added, so now fighting is actually kind of fun,
and the DLC data boss fights at the end are actually good.
None of that was my point.
My point is that as I was playing through the game the second time,
and this is the first time, but whatever, there's a...
Have you guys ever played the game The Witness by Jonathan Blow?
You know what that game is?
I've heard of it.
I know it.
It's a...
For anyone who doesn't know, it's a perspective-based game where you walk around in a 3D environment.
That's correct. That's correct.
And it has...
That game, The Witness, has a unique feature about a lot of things...
Real quick, I would recommend actually...
Yeah.
It was Joseph Alexander who did a 45-minute review of that game, right?
And Joseph Anderson.
Joseph Anderson.
Yeah, I believe that's right.
That was a pretty good video.
That's the only video by that guy that I really enjoyed, so check it out.
Yeah, that's his best one.
Well, check it out.
Because interestingly enough, there is one thing that's...
I was wondering if it was maybe copied in KM3 from that,
and there's lots of these...
In certain positions in The Witness, things will line up in...
There's a thing you look for.
It's a dot with a line after it.
And it could be things like in a certain position on the island you're on,
the clouds will form that position.
You have to look at it in this perspective,
and then draw a line with your mouse, and it'll do something.
There's a mechanic similar to that in KM3,
which is these Mickey emblems that are scattered throughout the world.
And as you play through the game, you can find them.
And if you're very keen in looking for things...
For example, there's these three pillars of rocks
that don't look like anything as you're climbing Mount Olympus.
But when you get to the top of Mount Olympus and you look down at them,
suddenly they form the shape of Mickey's head,
which is the Mickey emblem, and you can take a picture of it,
and that gives you the achievement.
Stuff like that was cool.
And the thing to tie into what we were saying was that
one of those things, which actually didn't involve the perspective thing,
but as I was playing through the game, I got to Monster's Inc.
and I was fucking around doing stuff.
I beat the level.
One of the things they do in Kingdom Hearts is they recreate
places from the Pixar worlds in now an explorable 3D environment
in the Kingdom Hearts world.
And a lot of people just enjoy that,
even though they have to partner with a company and recreate every detail.
Blah, blah, blah. It's a whole big thing.
But one of the things is, if you remember on the scare floor in Monster's Inc.,
there's just desks where Mike Wazowski and Sully would work,
and Mike worked at his desk and had papers and stuff,
and Sully would go scare in the doors and then come back out.
So they've each got desks covered with paper.
As I was playing through the game again and getting all the emblems,
one of the desks, written on the paperwork,
has a unique thing, which is like a bunch of wires in a circle,
and those wires are a Mickey emblem.
They're in the shape of a Mickey emblem.
And you have to look for them specifically and find them.
And when I was going through and finding that,
at no point did I ever give a single fuck about anything that was on any of those desks,
as I was like blasting through the world,
just killing the Heartless and the Unversed as fast as I could to get to the end,
actually good part of the game.
But then I was like, as I got to that,
it made me suddenly take stock and kind of appreciate the environmental design
that had gone in here, which is something that I just absolutely would not have done
if I wasn't a completionist who wanted to get every little mini-game in the game completed.
And to tie it back to the point, it's just like they put so much work into all these details
that 99% of people will want 100% just blast by and not pay any attention to.
I mean, it's really funny because there's some places where you want to praise that,
and then other places where it's like, why did you bother?
Why did you try?
There's a give and take.
Obviously, most people will never see Ash Lake in Dark Souls,
but those who do will be like, this is a life-changing moment.
In Kingdom Hearts, I'm not sure if you will feel much once you finally do observe all that stuff
other than, oh, they put all this here? Why?
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
That mini-game is one of the more enjoyable actually gameplay things that was in the game from the start.
But I mean, it's true.
In the grand scheme of things, did that save the game?
Absolutely not.
It's a complicated thing how good that game is, but yeah.
In terms of the money and time, the 13 years to get the game done due to various reasons,
obviously it wasn't all that they were just building out specific stuff like this.
I'm just going to go ahead and call that, I mean, obviously what it is, bad project management,
which is just Square Enix in a nutshell.
The fact that they have had all of these issues, like the whole Tomb Raider being considered underselling
because of how much it costs, is just the kind of stuff you look at and you go like,
how fucked is your corporate structure that you can make this mistake?
Because I know that Square, obviously Square Enix isn't the studio that developed Tomb Raider,
but they are the publisher, so they were obviously part of it.
The fact that they agreed to like,
Well, and that they were having this issue on all their games,
because that year it was also like Hitman Absolution and fucking, what was it, Sleeping Dogs.
Those were all three games that they had published that all had sold millions of copies
and all were considered financial disappointments.
And all were just way over the top with the graphics.
And it's like, there's no need for this.
I don't know if this makes you as...
The reason they're all doing it is because I think it makes them competitive to have better graphics,
but it's like, you're being competitive with games that are selling 10 million copies.
You're not...
Only one in every so many games that even attempts to reach that audience is going to do so.
So it's just not worth the risk of trying to even do that.
I agree.
There's an aspect to this as well, which is games that go for a heavy stylistic approach
where the heavy computer processing power is not required in any way.
And the art...
I was playing Okami, right?
The best game ever made.
And the game, if you're not aware, is about a dog, a wolf.
And you are the dog, and you are the wolf, and you are a god, and you have magic powers.
And because...
And it's like the graphic...
Graphical design is supposed to be that of like a Japanese painting, watercolour or calligraphy
and all that sort of cool, non-realistic looking shit.
And because of that, they can take massive shortcuts with things in the background.
In the background, there's no skybox, there's just a big blank colour and calligraphy mountain.
Just a big black line of just a mountain and a tree or various mountains.
When you're in the city, you can look up and you can see completely solid black silhouettes
of almost like paper cut out tall Japanese buildings looking things.
And that's all they need to give you the illusion that this is a huge city with loads of stuff in
and then the mountain is like this world is vast.
And it's really smart to go with something like that,
because not only did that game come out like a million years ago
and is still one of the best looking games I've ever seen in my life,
but they were able to make it back then in the same way.
They made HD versions, but nothing has been changed.
It's just the fidelity, the resolution rather.
So it's a time saver, it's a money saver, it's a graphics saver and it's just better.
Just don't do realism.
I just wish that the AAA market was what I think it should be like an enthusiast niche.
Right now it seems like games are dominated by people,
games that work as hard as possible to be the most technologically impressive.
I wish that was like with technology that the most advanced stuff is for that group that wants to get it
and be pushing the envelope, but that's not what it is.
Here's what I think happened and this is based on, there's a great show called What Happened on YouTube
by a guy called Matt McMussles where he breaks down games that flopped
or that had trouble developments, he goes through what happened.
And a lot of the time what he's talking about is how the seventh generation of consoles
basically killed everybody.
Making games for the PS3 and Xbox 360 just because of the fact that all the games
were trying to be the most expensive, most broad reaching game possible
and that's what the publishers wanted.
And so every promising game developer that starts to spring up, EA or whoever else comes in, buys them out
and gives them a shit ton of money to make a bigger, crazier game and they can't do it.
Making games on that scale, especially when they keep getting mandates from the publisher
for all these different things, oh now you gotta add multiplayer
because this game came out with a hugely successful multiplayer and now we all have to have it
and it's just like well it doesn't go in our game and it's expensive to implement, doesn't matter
now the game's uneven, it's gonna get seven out of ten scores, it's not gonna sell
more than one or two million when it needs to sell six or seven million
and the developer gets shut down.
And it just comes down to I think all these publishers looking at GTA and Call of Duty
and saying we have to be that successful.
We all want to be super rich giant corporations
and when you go in with that mentality that it's just like you're not thinking about how to make good art
you're thinking about how other people have made money trying to copy it without really understanding what they did
and then failing and it's just like this is not the environment to do creativity in
like if you want to make stories you have to think about the story you're making
what is the appropriate size of this project, what is the appropriate amount of effort and budget to spend on this
so that it can make profit you know and I think that with a lot of these triple A games
with all the crazy graphics and stuff really the problem is that the price of games has never increased
but the expectations have you know that like games keep being six well it's not that they never increased
but you know going into the seventh gen it became $60 was the standard but it's like you know $60
I could spend $60 on Dark Souls and they will be making way more money off of that $60
than Tomb Raider would have made off the same purchase you know and it's just like that's smart business
and that's why even a small developer like FromSoft by just not bloating their process
can keep making these games that feel like magic because they
I'm not even sure that they count as triple A but they are the only triple A company I trust
like only one I don't trust anybody else anymore
least of all Square Enix
well let's hope Elden Green is fucking baller
indeed
you have been playing Okami I recall you saying on Twitter
hell yeah it's fucking great
talk about how cool it is
it's the fucking shit I mean I just I find myself I constantly getting lost in Okami
just trying to figure out how Clover did all the fucking things they did
I don't understand because like a lot of the stuff in the game is just sprites to cut down on the poly count
because I'm playing Okami and like it's funny because you're saying like it's not very graphically taxing
and now it's not but I have a strong suspicion that at the time this was pushing the PS2 to its limits
maybe it was
a lot of the things they do
it never chugged on my PS2
yeah it's because it's like because the way they're doing the outlines for all the characters
they're doing what I'm doing it's called the inverted hull
it's where you duplicate the mesh and have it the back of the faces be transparent
so you can see through it and then you make it a little bigger
so all you see is the outline of this like duplicate shell around the main mesh
and so that doubles the poly count of everything in the game
and when you're working with this low headroom like the PS2 that's a problem
so the characters are all really simplistically designed
like the characters don't have any mouths that articulate or anything like that
the head just kind of jingle around when they're talking
and like there's like a poly count limit in the engine
because there's no enemies on screen you always go into this little tiny arena
when you encounter one of those scrolls and then the enemies spawn
so they don't have to draw the background
so there's tons of little like shortcuts they're doing
but it all just looks aesthetically gorgeous
because like it has like considered art direction from the very beginning
and like it's really interesting because like Okami originally was going to be a photorealistic game
like there's an old ass fucking trailer and screenshot of like a realistic Amaterasu
running in a realistic looking field
and it just wasn't feasible with the PS2
so they completely changed the art direction
and once they got the painterly style that's when they added the celestial brush
because they started like thinking of other ways to use this art style
reflected in gameplay
and there's just so many fucking cool things that the game does
and it's just so brilliantly considered
and the way the aesthetics and the gameplay blend together
it's fucking great it's like
Kamiya's the man dude
he really is
and the fact that like all these characters referenced
Devil May Cry and Beautiful Joe is fucking badass
every time you fight Wakka he makes a reference to one of Kamiya's other games
and it makes me lull
it's great
are you excited for a
probably for Okami
are you excited for the wonderful 101 ports
coming out
yeah cause I haven't played it
even though I have a Wii U
I never got around to buying it
cause at the time I didn't even realize that was a Kamiya game
cause I'm a fool
you know that's cool
I don't know if any of you saw it
the Matthew Matosis talking about the Kickstarter
where he straight up called Wonderful 101
his favorite game of all time
he did
damn
he said that Rain World
might be vying with it for domination
that was interesting
Matthew has a very specific taste
I know that his best favorite game of all time
is not going to be something that I would like on the same level
um but
maybe
like he's into that arcade stuff
Wonderful 101 was like oh yeah it's basically
beautiful Joe, Devil May Cry and Okami
all wrapped up into one game
so like the biggest come in the universe
I mean maybe
I have like very specific desires
and it's really just
I want to be in a three dimensional world
and have autonomy to turn around
anything that is like an arcadey version
like oh 2.5D makes me
you know that's a big trigger
that's a big no-no
where you have 3D but
you've taken it to the two dimension
and you're just fake 3D
I can't run around and jump on things
fuck you
but actually it's fine
I did beat that game
years ago
on a Friends Wii U
and I did like it a lot
uh
but I don't really care
that it's getting remade
but I'm happy for those who do
so Godspeed everybody who's
who's interested
I'll get it
it'll be sick I'm sure
I already have it
I prefer Devil May Cry
what can I say
I'm positive I'll prefer Devil May Cry
because it's my jam
and it's my favorite forever
for all time
I mean the fact of the matter is
that the reason the wonder
other than the fact that it's on the Wii U
I think the reason the wonderful 101
was always poised for lack of success
is just that it doesn't look
cool on the surface
like it looks deliberately
lame in a way
and I think that
whatever it is going for
obviously once you actually understand it
and you you know engage with it
then you'll appreciate it on its own terms
and I think that
Matthew Matosis is very good at that
and
like it fascinates me to see
the different reasons people like things
because like I tend to be of the opinion
that like I like it because it's good
you know and like
I like all kinds of things that are good
that appeal to me in some way
but like the main appeal
is the fact that it's good
whereas I think most people
the main appeal is on a conceptual level
more so it's like
that is like 80% of the battle
for most people
it's like I get to play as a cool guy
and slash things
it's like most of it
and then the fact that it's good
is what keeps you coming back
I think it's because most people's
like occupation isn't exploring media
and so they have to make choices
well it's funny because
that gets brought up every time I think
about this but like the reason
my occupation is exploring media
is because I love exploring media
like I made that my occupation
so not everybody has autism like you do
so that's another thing
well that's and it's sad because
everybody who I have ever known
who has experimented
it makes your life better
because you eventually find things
that you didn't know you wanted
it's like if I had never started
eating Asian food
I imagine my life would be very different
you would never love Japan period
right
it's just funny to me to think that
like because there's lots of people
especially when it comes to food
here in America
almost most of the people I know
or encounter have just never
even tried experimenting with other stuff
and I always come away like why
wouldn't you assume there are things
that you will love that are out there
that you haven't found yet
won't you be like so fucking hype
when you find out about those things
but I don't know
most people don't seem to care
they're just like I'm fine with what I got
and I'm like alright
there's a guy I know out here in Ohio
this doesn't speak highly of this
place in the country or the world
but who as far as he knows
has never eaten anything except
I believe it was fries and chicken tenders
his entire life
and this is just how he survives
that's it
my dad knew a guy who lived off hot dogs
so I guess it's possible somehow
fair enough
you're just
by the way that reminds me
I am glad that this
remaster is coming or whatever
release for PC or whatever
because I'll probably play through it again on that
because I always want to take notice
of Matthew Matosis
and he's the guy who's made me
like Matthew Matosis introduced me to the idea
that like I should go back
I've beaten all the Devil May Cries
but like I should play them again
and find out why I don't get them
because I still don't understand
I mean I just haven't done this yet
I've been saying for a while
I need to find out why
the point system
and the trying to like master combat
is like particularly enjoyable
whatever I talked about this before
I don't get it yet
and I'm gonna make some effort
and Wonderful 101 is absolutely one of those games
where like the real goal
is to get pure platinum
unlike every mission
that's when you really beat
that's well I think there's a
I think that one of the biggest problems in game journalism
is that not enough people approach games
on their own terms
and it's because
every reviewer is reviewing
is trying to appeal to everybody
they're trying to like
imagine like the layman
like the perfect just gamer
who is generic
who will like the same things
whose opinion is predictable
you know like they're thinking
okay most people only play a game once
so let's review this from the perspective
of having played this game once
and it's like okay but in the case of
like Beautiful Joe
or any of Kamiya's games pretty much
like the point
is to play it more than once
like the game is not designed
with the expectation that you would play it only once
most of his games are like two to six hours long
you know wonderful one-on-one
I understand is much longer
but like you know the
yes you will have a good time
playing Devil May Cry through once
and that's kind of a testament to how great
the design of the game is
but like can you really review it
if you're not having the experience that
the game is meant to
to provide and will provide
at its best like
shouldn't we
shouldn't some reviewers
like make sure that they get to that point
before they really talk about the game
and that's why I appreciate Matthew Matosis
and Super Bunnyhop
so much as well
right they'll 100%
they'll go to the highest difficulty
and a lot of the times
you don't really get to experience all the systems
of a game until you go to the highest difficulty
because it will push you to have to learn
those systems especially Metal Gear Solid
where you know as he
put it in the MGS3 video
where he says like low level play looks like this
and he's like
looks like a super serious action game
and he's like high level play looks like this
and it's like five guys standing around a porn magazine
that then like spews out knock out gas
and knocks them all unconscious
and it's like yeah
just mastery of the systems completely
and just you can do it everyone
oh it's beautiful
and it's like obviously the average player
will not do those things
so reviewers don't try to account for it
but like what if the reviewer tried
to push you to do those things
like Matthew Matosis
he didn't just beat
like do a perfect run of Devil May Cry
he's like hey
why don't you challenge yourself
and try to get this good at some game
like surely there's a game
that you're passionate about
and like you will learn so much more about it
if you play it this way
so like if you really want to develop
a real relationship with your video game
like you know
just try some things
try some kind of challenge
absolutely true
I got to plug this thing real quick
because with the DLC release
for Kingdom Hearts 3
remind DLC
with all the actual good bosses
at the end of the game now
there has been an influx
of what's called
something like Kingdom Hearts 3
versus any of them
like Marluxia
level 1
no hits
and then with style
the rise of these with style videos
has been exactly what I've been hoping for
we would get
and it's all these people
doing insane
like you were saying
with Metal Gear Solid 3
just having such mastery of the system
and knowing exactly
every single thing you can do
you think that fighting Terra
or whatever
back in the day in Kingdom Hearts 2 Final Mix
was like
hard
the people who have mastery
they just
they can make them look like a child
it's almost embarrassing to watch the bosses
try to fight back
against truly masterful players
and there's one thing they'll do
the with style thing
I just want to say
the with style thing they do
the number one thing is that
there is a selfie mechanic
in Kingdom Hearts 3
and there is nothing more embarrassing for a boss
that when they are charging up their super weapon
and this player just knows
so they just do a pose with Sora
and do a big like little like
making fun of him
gesture with his fucking hand
and take a fucking selfie
while they're charging up their death beam
that they know
is going to do no damage
because they know how to deal with it
it's
it's a performance art
like the game
it is
the game allows you
the game is a template for you
essentially any video game
is a canvas for storytelling
that you participate in
it's like
how are you going to
contribute to making this story good
are you going to
you know
if you play like shit the whole game
it's a shitty
it's probably going to feel like a shitty story
you know
but if you master it
you can make the story
into something very different
and like
like you were saying
I'm imagining Dark Souls players
who will use the emotes extensively
and just how fucking funny
some of the videos are where
you know
they're doing all this crazy stuff
in the game
or fucking with other people
and then using the emotes
and like it
it allows you to have charisma
in as a game avatar
you know
see that
that's the kind of review
like I want one of those people
to make my reviews
of my video game
and that's why
when I made my first
Kingdom Hearts 3 review
that's why
Seth Zenak is the best game reviewer
yeah that's right
I was so clear on mine
like this is the first one
I will get back to you
I'm going to fucking
master the DLC
so I can be
I've been dreaming of this
for years
that I will be the guy
even if other people have done it too
who does the equivalent of
you know
fucking
super bunny hops
100% middle of your solid 5
I'm going to be the 100%
Kingdom Hearts 3 DLC guy
just give me 6 months
and you know
I'll be there
it's going to be good
wait
shut up
wait before we go to voicemails
I have to talk
what's the matter Ben
you don't like video games
oh I want to talk about politics
I'm super
yes I am
super bored by this
well I have to call
I have to have a
a discussion
I got to reconvene
with Ben and Nate
because
when this episode comes out
it'll be the end of February
and if you recall
in the beginning of January
we all made a pact
oh dear
about being healthy fit boys
and I just want to say
that since that day
every day
100% keto
no carbs
down almost 20 pounds
how are you guys doing
very nice
that's fantastic
I have been keto
for the last several weeks
I haven't weighed myself
but diet-wise I'm doing good
I'm on track
dope
okay
I'll be
that agreement was for one month
and I definitely failed that month
I'm back
obviously it's the end of February now
I have
failed
oh no
failed is the short version
okay
yeah just be super clear
but
gonna
gonna do my best
I had free pizza thrown in front of me
multiple times
I did resist
now that's Will
you know what
I'm glad this exists so that Tom
you represent
the good aspect
like what one could aspire to be
well done
I am probably the worst
I gained a couple pounds while I was away
I'm the guy who's getting really good at Kingdom Hearts instead
instead I was really good at Kingdom Hearts
yeah I didn't even do that
I was just on vacation doing nothing
ooh what a waste
we all have our strengths and weaknesses I suppose
I mean I haven't picked up lifting again
which I wanted to do
but I didn't do that
yeah
I will make a vow
I'll go today
people listening
be inspired
even if you're in the hole
fix it
I'm gonna go to work
Jim
it's never too late
I'll go there
that's right
we got
by the way
11 days till Radcon 3
so
better get beach body ready
real fast
it's impossible to do that
or Radcon 4
after that
you could lose 10 pounds easy
in 11 days
it's not about 10
it's not about 10 pounds
it's that I have body hair
and it looks bad
you could shave it
that's a doable thing
I'm gonna shave my whole body
it's weird
why not
literally why not
that's what people do
I'm gonna give
having the body hair
or shaving
that's the question
both are gay
both of those things are gay
yeah
he's right
the problem is
there's no getting around
the
Radcon body is
gonna be gay
no matter what we do
so
it doesn't matter
how you want to
everything you do is gay
yeah
actually
you know what
I think
I mentioned a long time ago
I have a fitness
wall
around here somewhere
or like I've got
like a chart
did you saw this
when he came to visit
all my fitness goals
one of them has long been
for like
the five years I've had the chart
shave your entire body
from the neck down
maybe Radcon 3
is the
Radcon 3 is dead
Radcon 4
I mean okay
because bodybuilders do it
a lot of them are just like funny
like
be like a bodybuilder
yeah you want to be funny
yeah I see
it's a joke
but
wait wait
I'm laughing
before we go to voicemails
I did want to say
one last thing about video games
sure
talking about like the whole
with style thing
I feel like
I come on like a different
like if there's two sides to this coin
one is the Devil May Cry
play the game over and over again
to get mastery of it
and the thing I like
which is more
to play a game
what I would consider
Devil May Cry side
would be like arcade
like part of
the fun is performing well
in front of other people
in the arcade
looking at you being the cool kid
playing the video game
and the other side is
just living
in a video game world
and just having autonomy
and doing things
and then existing
I don't really feel
the need to perform well
and so when a game is like
you have to be incredibly good
otherwise it sucks
as in
with the case of Kingdom Hearts
if it's like
you're playing it casually
you can play on easy
but
it's not
on easy it's just boring
and you have to
you have to play
on the harder difficulties
for it to be fun
which is why I didn't like it that much
the game is only good
I would argue
at a high level of play
when you're
so like
when the baseline
enjoyment is
the arcade thing
I don't really gravitate towards it
but something like
Minecraft
or World of Warcraft
where
it's just
you
can escape from the world
and play a game
and be a game character
doing something
I mean Dark Souls
I would consider this as well
because
you don't need to
necessarily be very good
you can put loads of points into
the OP thing
and just
run around
and be powerful
it's interesting you mentioned that
with Dark Souls
because of the fact that
like
if you know how to
make it easy
then Dark Souls
can be a game where you run around
like a
good
one of the main reasons
to play Dark Souls
is kind of as a horror game
which obviously
the more you master it
the less you get out of that
I was explaining to May the other day
that the funny thing about Dark Souls
is that people are always talking about
giving it an easy mode
or whatever
the reality is that the game is too easy
yeah like
there's no way to make it hard
is really like
you have to make it hard
by your own volition
you have to do things to yourself
to make the game harder
there is no hard mode
New Game Plus is not significantly harder
and it only
becomes harder
you know
for a certain amount of time
so it's like
yeah I think that
that what makes Dark Souls
so fascinating
is that it can be
both of those games at once
you know
that it both is a game
where you can just hang out in the world
and do whatever
and it's also a game
where you can do the most
crazy flamboyant
challenge run
you know
and like
a game like Devil May Cry
only has one of those two
aspects really
you know like
when I watch people play Devil May Cry 5
it's obvious to me that like
a huge part of the appeal
to people who love the game
is how complex the battle system
or the abilities you have are
and how much shit you can do
and like for me
it's like
I appreciate that at high level play
you'll be forced to do all those things
and therefore
the game does kind of require you
to get good
for the game to be good
but you can play it on normal
you can just spam
the same attack over and over again
the game just not nearly as good
and it's still good
I mean I like all the Devil May Cry games
even though
I've mostly just kind of
you know
played them in a boring way I guess
or Bayonetta for a better example
I got a stone statue
on almost every mission
still beat the game
in like eight hours
you know it's not like a
the only thing that makes the game
super hard is trying to do well
but that's also the
you know for me
Bayonetta is like an 8 out of 10 game
I completely understand
why it would be a 10 out of 10
to somebody who
does want to engage in those systems
you know but like
Dark Souls can be a 10 out of 10 for me
without being any good at it
in fact Dark Souls would 10 out of 10 for me
before I fucking played the game
Remember back in the days
when Digi hadn't played Dark Souls
that whole saga
I remember that
it was a good time
I enjoyed it
Alright let's
go to the voicemails
voicemails okay alright
everyone you know
the link is down below in the description
to the speak pipe link
leave voicemails
make them good etc etc
okay where is our first one
right
oh wait sorry
gotta click on the actual one here
right okay the first one is from
alright this is from a filthy
Radcon 4 Parasite
I think this is from a
particular time and place in history
let's see
what he's got to say for himself
okay and
go
oh my god you guys
I'm so excited
Radcon 4
$30,000
it's real
it's happening
it's
it's it's a
it's a
ahhhhhhh
remember when we had only
earned $30,000
Redcon
I feel so bad
for anyone that wasn't watching
one of our streams live
when we
it was
it was a great time
we were all just like
streaming each other's streams
yea that's right
this guy left a second one
after we hit 33,000
but it was pretty much
just the same thing
oh 33
three I think I get the idea to discuss that on this episode I oh somehow days
ago I thought that would be the entire episode but it's been a few days and now
it's boring now it's lame it's boring now now I'm just now I'm just back to
being mad that YouTube hasn't given the channels back yet sure sure human
happiness is a fleeting thing we want to see the biggest come you've ever seen
your life go watch one of the recordings of the live stream if people
want I tweeted one out on my on my Twitter it's because I private the
live shows would have been the one that went the longest so if you want the the
entire thing you'd go to him but uh yes but I read my chair go most your
head is red in my stream because you were on my yes well but everyone else
could hear me saying it was read more than Nate's by me yeah that's true all
right well I mean shit what is there anything else I mean we funded what do
we fund on that stream we earned over one one one one one dollars more than
that we earned like the Kickstarter ran until noon that day between midnight and
noon we earned like $12,000 so we earned like a thousand dollars an hour that
whole day and like like ten thousand hours yeah those last two hours are
worth a week for sure we put the the the gruff showing the spike yeah yeah show
notes will link the the tweet with the chart okay yeah I'll get it right after
this okay well yeah what do we find we got we got over the 2222 which I don't
even remember what that was we because we were sure that at the start we were
trying to get genome was 25 25 well remember we had already hit the 2222
by the time we started the live stream then cuz that's right trying to get
genome mm-hmm there was an animated we got him he's confirmed there's an animated
OP there is there's a dojin to go along with the OVA we missed we missed the
ultimate stretch goal of did you making a funny face on Twitter yeah by less than
a thousand dollars which means I was thinking that blur out his face and
every whenever did you make a funny face in the OVA we should censor it saying
funny face you didn't pay for it so you can't have it yeah that's right he's not
allowed to make funny faces how will we know if I'm making a funny face or not
well you know when you see people hey rate these faces and then we'll blur out
the funniest one it's always funny so we just can't show it at all it makes
sense all right next voice mail we funded all kinds of great stuff it's gonna be
correct and just FYI when you hear this literally when you hear the next one one
day one week from now that is the start of radcon one week from when you are
hearing this Jesus seven days from two days I should probably start working on
my fucking yeah yeah yeah we all should I have to figure out what I'm gonna
lecture about because I don't have enough time to do the research for the
other ideas I had fair enough fair enough and let's do faces it would
faces for a straight hour and I'm okay all right next voice mail this is from
21 means I am immortal okay and go hey PCP let's give me my birthday today
before you're listening to this so it's gonna be my 21 birthday and I just
really want to get smashed so what should I do and how should I do it thanks
what do you think we get smashed by drinking alcohol straight vodka shots
it's the cheapest way to do it why spend your money go to your local game
store sign up for the smash tournament get smashed oh god no just jump into a
river just just end it all that's what I would do although do you think he meant
maybe he said before you hear this I'm gonna turn 21 maybe like before like not
even on the day that we're playing this but like some period beforehand maybe
he's like already 21 that's why I was confused by the question beer before
liquor never been sicker drink yeah yeah take shots first and then switch to
beer that's what you do have sex okay let's move on that's my recommendation
oblivion rent a car okay let's go on right well driving off a bridge that's
a birthday to remember rent a car drunk drive drunk kill yourself all right
we've got another voicemail from tarbuck transom everyone's favorite belt
Smith on the go that is tarbuck yeah that's him yeah okay good good let's
hear what I say all right take it away go all right like he's no offense enough
waiting around it's time for coordinated action the slow burn method isn't
working to get the channels back and we all know YouTube only responds to bulk
pressure if you can hear the sound of my voice you are compelled by justice to
message YouTube on Twitter next Thursday if you are truly a blessed night like me
you'll be doing it every six hours by the time they record the next podcast they
should have the channel back safe and sound you know your mission get at it
boys email email the YouTube support and in addition to the tweets because
sure in my experiences mass email gets people's attention the most because it
feels really serious and scary the mass tweets they hit the whoever like that
PR HR person is who's managing that Twitter we've been helped on Twitter it
just hasn't helped so it's like we gotta we gotta be we gotta they said on
Twitter they said like we're ready to restore the channel like you just need
to do this and then Nate you went and you did the things to it's almost like
every time we raise a stink they try to get us to stop by telling us that they're
doing something about it and then they don't do anything about it here go we
need to just consistently be reason raising a stink I guess yeah live update
okay this was like this morning and I need to reply to it I think we got one
more update let me see what we also we weirdly got like access to the can
tent like email address back but not the channel or something right okay didn't
you not lose the email address and like didn't they just go into the email and
transfer the channel to another yeah that's not exactly correct as did you
said like they said something about how they've detected like spam like videos
are being posted or like they know it's not us and they can see it was hacked and
they said like they were gonna give back the Google account okay so like things
are wrong we have the Google account there is so much confusion by dealing
with it they obviously do not know the specific issue if you log into the can
tent Google account there are two like listings of it like as though there were
you know both the channel and the non-channel version of the email anybody
who has a YouTube account probably knows what I'm talking about but or YouTube
channel but the the thing is they both say no videos neither one is the can
tent channel so you can sign into two different versions of can tent and not
have access to the channel and I'm like well what how do I get into the channel
like who has that there's that second channel is here's the way they restore
it they ask you to make a new brand account which is different from like a
user account it's you know it's like right it won't ask for like first and
last name this is just the account name of like can't enter whatever and then
like once you make a new brand account on whatever Google account you say they
and then you give them that link they will like port the channel to that brand
account that you have created they'll like stick everything on I'm waiting for
it that will become I gave them all the information I don't know what the fuck
they're waiting for by the way just just here's a little update I'm gonna
respond to this after we're done here but it said like so the team responded
they have confirmed that the PCP was hijacked on January 23rd okay do you
hear that they have confirmed their hijacked after this happened they start
remember how they were streaming today on the fucking PCB channel after the team
confirmed they were fucking hacked what the why haven't you stopped them from
doing shit if you know it was hacked I think they might be hacks over at the
YouTube support I don't understand okay anyway I'm gonna touch base with those
people but hey I don't see any reason not to spam them with emails what's the
probably do a lot of good honestly be respectful people and I would encourage
you to list all the channels I think Nate you have all the channels listed in
your Twitter bio right I do I do you know can't attend a podium cast tea bath
and so on there's like seven of them or something that we have you know it seems
to me like we're close to getting the PCP back but I said that first like a week
ago so you know slightly won't give them back until we harass them into doing it
and they get sick of it and they won't give us they'll just give us back one
channel at a time we're just gonna have to keep harassing them until we get every
chance like we're gonna have to do the same thing for every single one so let's
probably just commit to doing that works for me so as Tarbuck said
Thursday I retweet on the TP Crasinators channel I retweet everyone that posts
hashtag save the PCP with you and that adds team YouTube I would encourage and
like I would encourage everyone to tweet hashtag save the PCP with all like list
all the channels that we want back and then and at the YouTube and then go in
and like everyone else's tweets so they're just getting like a flood of
sure sure yeah god I hope we have the channel back before the Thursday he's
talking about cuz that would be me a long time from now don't wait till
Thursday just do it all the time yeah whenever you like it anytime's a good
time to email and like and message and make and at the fucking team YouTube we
want PCP back in particular it's urgent but we want all of them back and I won't
take no for an answer Nate how many more voicemails we got two there are two
more excellent all right here's one this one's just called a sweet listen up
here we go
scrum deli umptress I have to say but you know much to my chagrin when I went
to the Washington Monument I did not see a speck of Brad or garlic in sight no
but you know it's hard to stay mad when you're drawing a nice a juicy a sweet
a grapefruit with loaves of bread loaves with L O A F S Nate look I know
you're a big chump supporter and all but that doesn't mean right not see
especially but I will not leave you guys alone I'll be coming through your
windows and snatching your grapefruits up but I'm gonna leave on a bit of a
positive note here's a picture that you may find a little appealing monster he's
pouring sweet and directly on to the grapefruit voice jail voice jail voice
straight to voice jail what was this guy's name for okay whatever we'll look
it up on on fucking DVR it's quandary poser so like a splatter on the ground
it's absolutely horrendous he's gonna you know as a matter of fact that off the
black the asphalt you know but before this I couldn't get into the DVR like I
saw this linked on the thing and like I tried to click on it it was literally
locked because it was said like contains adult content this image so I had to
log in to fucking like the t-bap DVR for back of the day cuz it's the only one I
knew how to get into and yeah anyway quandary poser you are a fucking monster
for a number of reasons by the way I just realized not only did we forget to
talk about our extreme success with our thing but we also forgot to talk about
the fight this episode is on reserve it's on reserve what is that on hold
no just just isn't we can bleep just the number nothing else sure then bleep
that bleep it all bleep no bleep this everything we're all saying I want a
solid minute of what's our position then on what this episode is canonically this
is 201 obviously okay so we're not coming out let you live from the future this
is just 200 okay great got it all right that moving on okay right we have one
last message one last fucking voicemail okay here's the thing this one is very
long and we can cut it off anytime but what it is is that one dune coon made a
a PCP something like a radcon fanfiction and they converted it to audio and we
have it here it's like four minutes long anytime we can cut it off anytime but
let's just listen to a snippet of it and if we like it we can listen the whole
thing but we'll we'll see how it goes okay here we go and take it away dune
coon impress me go you're listening to an abridged version of radcon the
untold story by dune coon duji bro was sitting in front of his work computer
desperately trying to thrust his uncircumcised seven-inch penis in between
the thighs of his shinobu oshino anime figurine when the knock came out his
door he'd almost managed it when a second knock rang out breaking his deep
concentration what the who the fuck is here did he asked shinobu he rose from
his cum stained office chair and hobbled towards the front door peeping
through the peephole and readying his 3d printed gun which was a dick show
preaching on reward and opened up what's up nigga Nate greeted
saying the n-word is funny it wasn't a lie he had spent the morning trying to
figure out how to fit more of his fetishes into the story maybe I can make
shinobu like some fairy things like yui from sorda online then I could fucking
even smaller version of her I mean talk whom I could fucking even smaller
version of her yeah that's what I meant with that out of the way and all
pleasant not into many girls with no obvious direction to steal the
conversation they stood in silence eyeing each other up did you bros overwhelming
fatness was rapidly escaping from his clothing his oily hair clung to his
equally oily skin like he was rubbed down by a Japanese prostitute but even
with his physical abnormalities there was something about digi that Nate just
found irresistible it wasn't his uncircumcised 7-inch penis it was his
uncircumcised 7-inch brain
it was nothing more than a professional appreciation Nate had insisted
nothing more I'm gay digi was one of Digi's personal names I try not to hold it
against you Nate replied but it was for naught Digi had become painfully
aware that he was not currently ingesting drugs and sought to remedy
this as soon as possible without another word did he marched back to his
work desk he started up his water-cooled desktop tower which also
functioned as a bong he took a long hit and invited Nate to come sit next to
him you want some of this did he asked politely Nate was hesitant to partake
in Digi Bo's debauchery but the long and uncomfortable flight had left his body
and mind withered it felt like he had just gotten hit by the wither in
Minecraft and it was now a scene from being withered like in the video game
Minecraft followed Digi's example and did the weed it took effect immediately
Nate was no stranger to weed but he should have known that Digi Bo's personal
tolerance would have been multiple times higher than his own pretty strong right
I brought it off the deep web did you explain and by that I mean I bought it
from a black guy never having actually met a black person Nate was having
trouble focusing on the computer screen it was consistently blocked by Digi
exhaling fat clouds of smoke and after a few more lips for himself Nate's
throat had become dry I'm gonna go grab a drink Nate announced rising from his
seat do you have any off-brand LaCroix did you bro never got the opportunity to
answer because once Nate stopped using his chairs of support he fell face
forward right into his friend and in their intoxicated states neither of them
were able to grasp what had exactly happened if they were sober both of them
would have noticed Nate's hand grasping Digi Bo's uncircumcised seven inch
penis there's Dr. Pepper pajama pants immediately as things were took me at a
good 30 seconds and even after that his brain failed to process the next
reasonable course of action Digi bro who tried to have his uncircumcised
seven inch penis touched at all times made no attempts to push Nate off it was
like that one scene in Evangelion except dumb and gay you're a big guy noted for
you did you answered well if you'd like to read the full unabridged version there
you go click the link in the description link in the description there's a link
not only to to the text version of that but the entire story of which that's
just an excerpt that I have not read the end of conclusion the music well done
was yeah favorite part for sure yeah yeah that's that's that's production
value that's quality no doubt no doubt he put work actually yes yesterday on the
stream he was like Nate why would you read my fanfiction and I just said
bro convert it to a voicemail and then if it's good I'll play it and that's what
he did I'm thinking voice grail voice grail for doing Coon what do you think
maybe if the story continues and to be entertaining then I mean to be fair he did
there's a complete something about Isis shows up I mean it's voice grail it's
voice grail not thick grail the voicemail was good what was presented
Isis already shows up in my story in the road to Radcon 4 well maybe that's why
maybe it's continuity hey you know I'm for it I say voice grail
value I want other people to be incentivized listen to the rest of the
road to Radcon 4 Nate I haven't I just haven't got around to listen to it I
want to live it now listen our epic face-off against Isis which Munchie
becomes leader of immediately you're telling me on that I'm gonna listen to
that very soon indeed indeed okay I'll give a full review I probably won't I'm
please check to make an analysis video about wait wait five is out before you
write a comprehensive analysis okay all right well that's it for the voice
males everybody quality stuff here by the way I think I just have forgotten to
update the voice grail in jail for the last like a month so just at me on
Twitter reminding me who I've forgotten that be appreciate keep is been keeping
track of yeah there's a word document I thought we just say it like randomly
because what like wherever the moment takes us I knew there was a word doc
but is it publicly visible anywhere I think it's in the description of every
video I'm pretty sure what is like down there somewhere in any case I'll go look
for an update it that tells you how serious we take the voice grail slash
yeah yeah the real value is the us saying that you're in it that that goes
that goes further okay anyway we're done if you want to leave a voice mail click
the speak pipe link down in the description by the way lol I got another
email from speak pipe and they're like um police procrastiners you're over your
account limit but please we're not gonna let you do any more and then multiple
more voice mails keep coming in what a bunch of simps just cut us off you
pussies I'm not gonna delete them they're definitely there they don't work
like web node the sea the site where I built my my website where I had gone
over the I went over the bandwidth limit like pretty quickly and for a few
days I was just dancing around doesn't even seem to matter and then the entire
website disappeared and I had to email support in order to get it back you're
like promising that I would pay lol that could happen to us with speak pipe but
lol fuck it I'm sure we'll be fine another one we'll just make another one
yeah what are they gonna do all right well that's it okay so patreon.com
the procrastiners support the show $5 for bonus episodes $1 for the patron
discord Radcon 4 is now the Kickstarter is over anyway so that shit's locked in
there will be a public meetup more details coming about that which gonna
be on March 3rd and Radcon starts in one week one week when you're hearing this
wait March 3rd Jesus Christ what oh sorry March 14th it starts March 6th
the meetup is on the 15th a lot closer than I thought for some reason I
convinced myself it started on like the 13th so incorrect no it's the 14th sorry
it's Saturday right yeah the 14th that's right the Saturday yeah okay okay
and and that's that and it's gonna be good and all kinds of good stuff coming
to you and oh by the way if you're a patron oh you know what now I guess it
maybe this might already be old news but like we need people to respond to the
back of rewards especially if you're a $200 up guy so that Ben can get your
art in the poster so if you're hearing this yeah I have like one or two days
left fuck I have to do that you have to do it okay yes correct
other there's like fucking character whatever and get your get your face in
I gotta add there's something like there's something like 30 people who have
responded already and that's out of a total of 47 people so that's most
already so that's that's good and so it's gonna be like 47 people then six
rad con boys and Vic and of course a G no other members so it's like 56 or
something I don't know you know taking up 60% of the entire screen yeah how fun
and I guess that's it oh follow us updates if you will get the channel back
sometime everything important is happening on the Twitter at TP crass
tenators so watch that for updates it's where you'll want to know anything
important happens that's where it'll be and that's it and that's it leave more
voicemails etc etc ever confused about when when the what channel the new
episodes on they're always on iTunes Google Play and Spotify there you go
that's right you won't go wrong if you just follow that business there you go
all right we'll see you next week everybody one week from when you hear
this till radcon a new episode will come out that day on that like 2 p.m. but like
hours after you hear the next radcon like we will be there and it'll start so
won't that be exciting probably all right that's it all right everyone vote
Bernie cuz I can't that's my log off message today all right everybody see
you soon