Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. You
are greeted by me, Besty Boyman. And who else is here? We've got Gibbontake.
Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way.
It's that time of year, everybody. We've got other reindeer pulling the sleigh, Tom Oliver.
Oh what fun it is to be super fucking gay, dab. As expected, there's Ben Saint.
That's me here.
Christmas, fuck. And Mage, our purple-nosed reindeer, leading the pack.
I wish you a Merry Christmas. This is actually a very funny song once you know all the lyrics.
Why's that?
Because they ask for figgy pudding, and I didn't know what figgy pudding is, and it just sounds so funny to me.
It sounds like baggy pudding, it does.
It's just pudding with figs in it.
But it sounds so funny when you say, like, oh give us some figgy pudding, oh give us some figgy pudding.
It is an amusing word.
Give us a break, give us a break, at our own like Christmas.
Break me off the piece of that Kit Kat bar.
Let me see, today, people will be hearing this on Friday the 13th, which is a fucking way.
This is the last time people are hearing me on the public podcast this year.
Are you going to go back to the North Pole and be Santa?
Yes, that is my plan.
You're going to be very busy.
When this comes out, shortly after this, I think on this day, we are doing a PCP Minecraft stream on this very channel, so you will see it here shortly after this episode goes live.
Maybe you're listening to this episode while playing in the Minecraft server with us right this moment.
I hope so, I hope so.
There's an event going on, people have to have like their little houses and they put in their wish lists for the Santa of the server and they might get some things from their wish list.
And the deadline is the 15th, so if you want to get some free goodies right off the bat, feel free to join.
How exciting.
I'm going to put the top of my wish list to be banned from the server.
If you want to join, go to athtrend.com slash PCP Minecraft everybody, go join the good times.
If you've been a good little boy or girl, then perhaps.
Who's going home for Crembus?
Me.
I will be going home for a few days.
I mean, I'm not going home, I'm going to my parents.
I am going.
I'm here, I'll be home, but it's not that far for me.
It's like an hour's train ride.
Right, right.
That'll be good.
Check in with the folks.
Christmas Eve will be a party time.
You know, Ben, we did a little shopping for you.
We have a gift that we have acquired that you shall receive in the near future.
The joke is you're going to be given the gift and then Nate is going to take it when he leaves.
And then I'll wear it on my feet and you'll see how you like it, Ben.
Okay, what is it?
No one knows.
It's a mystery.
Oh, okay.
Is it a toothbrush?
Someone said, here's a gift that you don't know what it is.
Purchase it.
And then, oh, actually, here's a brand new concept that I'm selling to everyone right
now.
It's you buy an item from me, you don't know what it is.
The person you're giving it to doesn't know what it is.
So when that person opens it, it's a surprise for everyone there.
Now that's fun.
That's double the fun.
You know what you should do?
You should go to a shop on the high street, close your eyes and just charge, run in some
random direction.
Charge the money held out in front of you.
The first thing you fucking smash into and fall over on, that's the present.
Keep your eyes closed, grab it with both hands.
We have only the moment of impact to determine what it is.
You just keep bumping into things until the amount of money you're holding out exceeds
the value.
So until you hear a shop keep yell sold and then you grab whatever you got, stuff it in
your pocket and run away.
It's a brand new fucking electric toothbrush.
We partner up with, I don't know, I'm picturing the setting at some cheap porn movie.
I don't know why, but that seems appropriate for it.
In the setting, it's like a panic room or one of those event rooms, escape room.
That's the word I'm looking for.
Kind of a porn has a panic room or escape room.
What kind of shit are you into, Nate?
That's where I go before I'm about to film my scene where everyone will see my
ween and how nervous that makes me.
He has this emergency coomer panic room.
I'm just wondering what about this is porn at all?
I'm just picturing like a shitty room.
That's all it is.
That's the only connection here.
There's shit on the walls as well.
What the fuck?
There's shit on the walls.
Oh yes.
The distinctive thing about porn is that they take place in rooms.
That's the main defining characteristic of most of the films I watch.
I've talked a lot more porn than I thought I did then.
Here's the deal.
This is a new product I'm going to be selling with my services.
You hire me, Nate, to find you a cheap porn room that's just been used to film porn.
In that room, on the casting couch, we sit down you and your whole extended family.
And on this casting couch, we're given a lump sum of money by you and your group beforehand.
We go out and we buy the gifts and we give them to everyone.
And then you people, you lowly creatures engaging in this voluntary exchange of goods and services,
get to open the gifts and nobody knows what they're getting.
We as the service providers get the gifts so everyone gets surprised things that hopefully are at least kind of nice.
I bet some people would be into that.
I bet someone would like that.
I know if there's any goods, but there's certainly a service being provided of dubious quality.
It is.
Well, I mean, hopefully we'll get some good Yelp reviews and then we'll work our way up the corporate ladder
and we'll be doing it for Steve Jobs next year.
Everybody in hell.
Everybody hates white elephants, but we all do.
We all do.
We do white elephant.
What's a white elephant?
I don't know what that is.
What?
It's the Yankee Swap.
Oh, okay.
I feel like more people know it is a white elephant, but we here in New England call it a Yankee Swap.
I've never heard the term white elephant ever.
Is that like a Republic or a Democrat thing?
No, it's a God.
It's the thing where everyone buys a gift and then you pool them all and then you draw a lotteries and then you see for Santa.
Not quite, but then you go around in the order that you drew the lots and then the next person picks one from the pile, opens it
and then gets to choose someone else who already opened one and they get to switch with them.
Right.
So the whole plan will be like one good gift that everyone keeps trading for usually.
It's basically the worst idea ever and I don't know if people do that.
It's just like how to guarantee yourself disappointment and a shitty gift.
It's kind of fun.
Is this a Nintendo 64 game?
It rattles the box.
I guess it's something to do for an hour.
You're thinking about this as like a game to win the best gift.
What it really is, is a game to spend the time that you're forced to be with your family and friends in some way that can be, you know, have a conversation about.
Win or lose, it sounds like evil corporations win by making us buy more useless shit that we don't actually even want.
Well, there's definitely that of the whole consumerism game.
Well, I think the concede is that if you weren't doing the Yankee swap, then...
You have to talk to them and...
You know, then you would have to pick out a gift for someone.
But you're not doing that.
We're sidestepping the need to do that.
You can find as generic a gift as possible.
You just get something and throw it into a pool.
It's like a monkey's paw thing.
You don't have to worry about picking a gift, but you don't get a good one either.
So it's like everybody loses.
One person gets a good gift, basically.
I got the best gifts for my immediate family, my brothers and my mom and dad.
They're going to be like, oh, nice.
And I'm going to be the cool guy.
I'm going to be the best son.
That is good.
I got gifts, sort of kind of as well.
I can't believe you fuckers got gifts. I don't have any gifts.
To be fair, I guess I'll have to get some, but like, whatever.
Michelle's the one who picked out the stuff that we got so far.
I have not done anything, including by anything for Michelle.
Actually, technically I did, but that was like a side thing.
So I'm still high and dry.
It is a nightmare.
I don't want to have to think about it, but I do.
And the date creeps ever closer that I'll have the gun in my hand soon.
What happened to our pact?
We used to get each other nothing as our mutual Christmas gift.
You could still get me nothing. I don't care.
Michelle took it upon herself to buy something.
Okay.
So blame her. Put the gun to her head.
I do.
Alright.
Fair enough.
My present is the one bullet.
Please give it back.
Oh, fancy that.
I rented you a gun.
Oh no.
Now neither of us have what we want this Christmas.
I sold all my ammunition to buy this ammunition.
I sold all my guns to buy this ammunition.
Now what are we going to do?
The tail is all this time.
What if I sold all my time to buy this pocket watch?
Oh, alas, no time is left, so it has no function.
Wait, isn't a watch?
No.
A watch is already part of the original story, Claude.
Well, shit.
Okay, I forgot.
What did the other guy sell in the watch?
The woman sells her hair to buy the guy a watch chain,
and the guy sells his watch to buy her combs for her hair.
And then he uses the chain to strangle her.
But just strangle to just shitty gift.
He used to strangle first himself and then his wife.
Yes.
Yeah, that's right.
As he fell, the chain wrapped around his throat.
That's a happy holiday ending.
They both said thank you, sir.
And then they fused together and became the super rat
that dominates the streets underneath
in the sewer system below Gotham City.
I believe that's what led to the creation of the superhero
known as The Rat Man.
That's my favorite villain.
He's got a deep floor.
Deep.
It runs deep.
Hey, you know, while we're on this tangential subject,
I have a public service announcement to make
because it's been quite entertaining for me to watch.
And this is a Michelle thing.
And it's that there have been quite a number of people.
It's been quite staggering to see
who have just been kind of assuming,
and this does relate to me,
that Michelle does not have a job
and is simply leaching off of me,
like as her whole lifestyle.
And look, we all know she gives off that vibe.
We're all very well aware
that Michelle certainly comes across that way.
Yeah, I think I saw this on Twitter.
I don't remember when it started,
but I've seen her get annoyed about it.
And this was partially used as an insult to me.
Nate, why don't you, what a loser,
stand up for your principles and blah, blah, blah,
and stop letting your girlfriend leech off you.
But I'm not gonna get into all the details
because whatever, it doesn't matter.
But Michelle financially more than pulls her weight
and has two jobs right now.
She definitely works, yeah.
And I mean, I hate to rush to this,
but it seems like a lot of people might think,
we got a pretty girl here,
we're just making some assumptions about,
no, she definitely doesn't work,
but she does is the thing.
So perhaps these people should perhaps check
their own assumptions before running away.
Maybe they should check their own no job privilege.
Actually, you know what was funny?
The person that Michelle was really fighting with on Twitter,
clearly was an unemployed person.
It's something along the lines of...
Was he trying to build no job solidarity with her?
No, no, it was like,
Michelle is such an asshole on Twitter,
which absolutely can be at times.
Their case was that Michelle's such an asshole,
of course no one would hire her for any job,
and it just calls into question this person's understanding
of the nature of employment itself.
So I just assume they don't have jobs.
Yeah, like a store would look up your Twitter profile.
They'd search your Twitter, like if you're a cashier,
they're going to be on your account.
Yes, I do, but like so many people don't give a shit.
Yeah.
Like the vast majority of jobs do not really care at all.
I mean, it's easy to pretend to be nice for like an hour
when you take a fucking job interview.
Of course, and like all our parents tell us as we're growing up,
like, oh, I mean, I remember this like,
Nate, there's a picture of you like at a party.
Do you really want that on your Facebook?
What if an employer looks there one day?
Oh my God.
I mean, sure mom, I suppose that's theoretically possible.
Remember when dad told us that we shouldn't swear on T-Bat?
I mean, based dad, right once again.
But you know.
He knew all those years ago that you're going to get demonetized
if you fucking did that shit.
We're at the very beginning.
We're not Compa compliant, dude.
No, we're not.
$46,000 video.
I hope that T-Bap, you know, a channel that's been dead for years,
technically a new video last year, that was this year, okay.
But I hope we get sued for every single video on T-Bap
and we owe, you know, millions all told for $42,000 each video.
One can only hope.
Slime and punishment to pay for it all.
You know, I think we were going to name our channel,
like the channel name is Two Best Brothers Bitch About Ponies.
Nobody gets it right.
Even everybody spells it.
That's shocking.
It is shocking because it's so easy and it's obvious
if you think for a fucking second about it,
but everybody spells it with two Bs.
Even people I would expect to understand.
It's true.
Three fucking Bs people.
Are you just learning this now that that's the meaning of T-Bap?
Yeah, I had no idea you guys bitched.
No.
Okay.
I thought for a second.
Because I've been shocked before by people that don't know.
It's on, like, it's on YouTube.
It's in words.
Like, I can read.
It's in, like, every video we say the name of the video.
I had trouble pronouncing it.
Not a single fucking comment on YouTube has ever spelled it right.
It is amazing.
I mean, I know three Bs.
You don't see it in words in English.
That's true, but this is an acronym and it means something.
I used to say T-Bap-Bap.
You did.
Which was one B short, frankly.
I remember that.
It should be T-Bap-Bap-Bap.
And while it's not how I personally chose.
T-Bap-Bap-Bap is correct.
Yeah, it's correct.
It's T-Bap-Bap.
And then back.
Yeah, it's T-Bap-Bap-Bap.
T-Bap-Bap-Bap.
Yeah, that's the right one.
Thought went into it.
Some.
Well, glad we cleared that up.
Guys, stop being misogynistic against Michelle.
It's, you know, it's important.
Stop being misogynistic against T-Bap as well.
That's my job, guys.
I give her enough of that at home.
I give that for, you know, for when it really counts.
That will really get it to her.
That'll be good.
Hey, while I'm speaking of domestic life, I'll spill my guts on my other thing I wanted
to bring up, which is just that perhaps you guys would be proud of me.
And it's that I've been a, call me a Britbong, because I've been a curry making fiend these
last several weeks and months.
Is curry a British thing?
I too have been playing Pokemon.
It's like an adopted British thing.
There's a lot of Indian people in England.
And it's become a national dish.
Did you culturally appropriate that?
I'm so mad about this culture.
I'm so disappointed that the fucking, that fucking the white, that the great replacement
took place and now British culture doesn't exist anymore.
It is unfortunate.
In the Pokemon game, I don't know if you've played it yet.
You make curry.
It's like the thing you do in, like instead of poffins, there's curry.
Yeah, it's kind of like how Chinese food in America is not the same as Chinese food
in China.
Like Indian food in England is not really right.
When I was in Germany, I remember I asked like, what's like some German food I should
try while I'm here?
And natives told me, how about curry worse?
And I was like, what curry?
Like the Indian stuff?
And they're like, yeah, but like on a worst.
Go get some.
I had some of that.
Sure.
Cool.
And it was fine.
I don't like curry.
I don't think.
At least not the ones.
That's too bad.
Yeah, I know.
I kind of, I want to like it, but it doesn't taste so good.
Whatever in the same area.
You should let me make curry.
Yeah, I was going to say it depends on the type because I've had Indian curry.
When you say curry, do you mean like the stew?
Basically that's like a curry stew with like potatoes and meat and stuff.
Okay.
Let me tell you.
So it's just, remember how I've talked about in the past, how about when I was in Japan,
I had curry and I love it and I miss it and I want all the time.
I made it.
I made it myself.
I found the solution because I'm not having an Indian curry, which is good, but not like
what I wanted.
I've been buying like a couple of types, but like golden curry, it's specifically the Japanese
curry brand and with that, what it is, it's still, I mean, okay, so you fry your meat.
You can get that stuff in, you can get that stuff in like, it comes in like, in like rectangles.
You can get it like Asian markets here.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
You can get some like other, you know, types or different flavor, but this like, this is
the flavor I've been seeking.
So let me just tell you what I put in this.
I've used pork on Thanksgiving.
I made turkey curry and it was fucking delicious.
We, what else do I use?
I like that.
Thinking outside of the box.
Right?
That's what we were doing.
Always after like Christmas, all the leftover meat gets turned into a big curry that is
used for weeks on end because it's so much usually.
It's so good.
I love it.
I mean, here's the X factor.
I bet you're going to get into this.
So we put potatoes and onions and all those delicious things in and what's the other one,
Michelle?
Like cabbage, but, but what we did on Thanksgiving and we've been doing a lot, we've been chopping
up sweet potatoes and putting sweet potatoes into the curry.
And boy, when you bite into these fucking sweet potatoes, I'm on the fucking moon.
It's, it's so delicious and I made it.
I'm so proud.
We put it over delicious white rice cooked in my white rice cooker.
Well, it's just a rice cooker, whatever.
And you, you pour your slop on there.
And you put rice into this.
God damn it.
It's so delicious and I've been making it, it is great.
It is.
And here's what you do.
I mean, in your rice cooker, you make it once, you've got rice to last you like a couple
days.
You make your big batch of curry.
You make like two batches at once and that'll last you several days, like several meals.
And we just sit down and we eat it at our little Japanese table, uh, you know, sitting
a fuck, uh, say is a style or whatever with our chopsticks in hand.
You sit on your knees.
And shovel it down.
I don't fucking tatami mats.
I try.
You can't do it for long.
I don't know how the fucking way to manage it.
Jesus Christ.
Michelle insisted she wanted a Japanese table, so I bought it for her for her birthday.
Do you have like the, do you have like the, what's it called, the, the mat, the, the,
the, no wait, not the mat, the, the, the cushions, it's the heater, the thing.
A futon.
We do not have a, uh, what's it called, the thing they sit under.
No, we don't have that.
Look, we're not that deep into this.
It's just a low table.
Okay.
Just sitting with your Japanese table, eating your Japanese curry.
Well, speak of the Japanese tongue and make videos about the Japanese anime and record
your Japanese podcast.
People have been mocking me lately for my less than fluent understanding of the Japanese
language.
And you know what?
Fair, fair.
I've, uh, you know, I'm not, not the best.
Uh, anyway, uh, just, I've been actually cooking.
It's been curry.
It's been the taste that I've been seeking in my life and I brought it back through my
own effort.
Yeah.
Thank you, Mage.
It feels great.
I've been cooking packs so I can keep making curry every damn day.
It's been a revolution.
Was this inspired by playing Pokemon or was this completely coincidental?
It was completely coincidental.
What is Pokemon?
And your Pokemon instead of puffins, they have curries.
You make curries to feed your Pokemon when you do camps.
So.
Oh, got it.
Indeed.
Yeah.
Hence Brit Bung thing.
You know, I'm trying to think, but I don't know exactly what inspired it or made me think
of it.
I guess we just had rice and I was like, what should I put in this rice?
Curry maybe?
I don't know.
Wow.
Got to be in that scene from Fully Cooley where they eat the really hot curry.
Oh yeah.
You know what?
Like Indian curry is like spicy.
This shit's not spicy at all.
I don't like spicy.
It's like cinnamon flavor.
Kind of.
What?
It's like sweet curry.
Interesting.
It's not.
It just has like elements of that.
It's still, I don't know, curry flavor, whatever that is.
Well, I know.
It's just got like no taste.
No, it's just like to tell them like.
I guess my brain immediately went sweet.
You said cinnamon for something.
I think it's American re-associated.
I think like cinnamon gets put with a lot of sweet things because it works.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Well, there you go.
Life update.
All right.
You're welcome.
Cooking more.
It feels good.
Well, I got a story for you this week.
I'm having a shit week so far.
I did some hard drugs.
Oh, no.
No, I didn't.
I did some real shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Was that a PCP?
No.
No, I did Molly.
Which one of us is going to do it first?
Someone has to.
At some point.
No.
No, I did.
What's Molly?
I did Molly and it sucked.
I believe you.
It's what they call a marrow wound.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Molly is slang for it.
Oh, God.
An illegal street drug.
Oh, yes.
Oh, no.
I guess it's MDMA.
A commonly known as.
Joe Rogan says I should do that daily or something.
So.
No, that's MMA.
Oops.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
Commonly known as ecstasy.
So I guess I did ecstasy.
It wasn't even good.
I didn't even like it.
Okay.
You want to describe the sensation?
I just made a fool of myself and embarrassed myself and felt bad about it.
So it was just a normal day.
Still do it.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Well, I went to a friend invited me out to a thing of just like a bunch of guys sitting
around someone's house just like fucking around drinking whatever, smoking weed, vaping.
I don't personally smoke weed.
So I didn't do that.
But whatever.
Just drank a bunch of hard seltzers, you know, like my man, baby Yoda.
You guys see that baby Yoda holding a white claw tattoo?
Yeah.
No, but I can imagine a tattoo of it.
What the fuck?
A tattoo of baby Yoda holding a white claw seltzer that is culture in a nutshell right
there.
Oh God, someone got that tattoo and then, oh fuck, it's one of the, shit, is it one
of the guys on Come Town or one of the guys on Chapo Trap House or some like Twitch streamer
collective, like one of them just like pretended it was his and like all his friends, people
that there's a big joke is like, oh yeah, this guy on this podcast, like he totally
got that.
He was so great with his new baby Yoda holding a white claw seltzer tattoo and the guy with
a real tattoo was like really mad that this guy is like stolen his thunder.
Now that's stolen valor right now.
He had a chance to dodge this bullet and he's not.
What a fool.
I could have pretended it never happened, but no.
Okay, but anyway, so we're there and then like one of these guys and this guy, he's
got long hair, he wears a beanie so you know he's a fucking, you know what, you know the
type, you know the type and I'm a few hard seltzers in at this point and he's just like
hey dudes, whoa or something, I forget what he says and he drops these two like bright
green pills on the table and I'm like what the fuck is that and he's like it's Molly
and I'm like and I think back and I lived in California, I lived with a guy and one
day him and his girlfriend did Molly and I saw them later and all it did, the guy was
just really, he was just really smiley, he just seemed like he was like super happy and
he just kept telling his girlfriend how cute her babies would be and I was like that seems
pretty fun.
Unrelated to him I assume.
Yeah, so I was like that seems fine and I was and I'm like okay guys, how much is this
gonna fuck me up and they're like okay just take half, if you've never done it before
just take half and I'm like okay great compromise, so I take half anyway shouldn't it done it.
It was a nightmare, what was bad about it is that I felt at all times like I was perfectly
in control of myself, I didn't feel, I mean I guess I felt kind of warm and tingly but
I didn't feel like I was high or fucked up but at the same time I could tell from the
reactions of people around me that that was absolutely not the case, I was being super
weird, I walked home, okay people told me a bunch of different things, people told me
that I kept asking the same questions over and over again, like I would get an answer
and then I would ask the same thing like a minute later.
Someone else told me that apparently like all night I was like stomping around the kitchen,
I was like stomping around the kitchen talking to myself, apparently I would walk to the
fridge, open the refrigerator, look inside, say vile and then like do it again on loop.
As a post food boy that's my general experience, I would believe you do, that sounds so me,
that sounds so me, none of this is keto, someone else told me that I like alternated between
cackling and weeping, which also sounds totally me but like in a very embarrassing and shitty
way, eventually one of my friends like fucking yelled at me like go fuck to bed, like fuck
you I have work in the morning and I'm sure even at the time I was like okay obviously
I'm acting like a fucking moron and I'm being obnoxious, I feel terrible but wait there
was one more thing, there was like one, oh okay the worst thing about it was in the middle
of it right, like four in the fucking morning, I am just like stomping around presumably
thinking like I'm a perfectly cogent actor at the moment and I'm like hey we live in
a neighborhood and I don't know my neighbors, why don't I introduce myself to my neighbor,
what time was this?
Like four in the morning, okay, so I just walk to the, and I'm zoning to say I'm possessed,
like the problems I keep at 300, I just walk to the neighbor's house and I just go up to
their porch and I just knock on their door and I'm just like standing there like yeah
I'm just gonna say hi, I'm Ben, nice to meet you, I live next door, what a great time,
but one of my roommates sees me from his window I think and he like comes out and gets me
and is like dude what the fuck are you doing, it was miserable, it was totally miserable.
That's one of those things that under normal circumstances, in a normal time of day is
a perfectly nice thing to do, but I've given this, I just didn't get it, I just didn't
understand and then the next day, so yesterday, they did actually, they came and they knocked
on my door and they were like well someone knocking on our door yesterday and I had to
be like I'm sorry, that was me, I was high and I thought it would make sense, I apologize
and won't do it again and there was a guy and a girl and the girl was just like making
a very concerned face like oh okay, but the guy behind it was like yeah man, I get it,
that's like our feet sweet, at least it always makes sense, we've all been there, so at least
one of them got it, so it's fine.
That's good, that's good.
And that's how I got to 50% of my neighbors to like me.
So that was my weekend.
Have you felt sense, like physically?
I was kind of hungover the next day, but I think it was just because of, and it wasn't
even that bad, I didn't even have a headache or anything, all told it was pretty, I mean
I just felt morally, I just felt morally bad, morally hungover.
Be careful man, the moral high grounds, all you have left at this stage of the game.
Just because I had annoyed and been a nuisance to all my roommates and shit, so that sucks.
I still have to apologize to a few of them.
Like you came on Discord, presumably right after.
Yeah, I saw that and I was like oh Jesus, why did I do that, I'm such a fucking loser.
What happened, what happened?
Well he just came on and explained that and I was there and I was talking to him and I
realized that he was still high.
Oh I was still high, I was still high as bald.
But like now I'm thinking about, you didn't mention, cause obviously you weren't like,
you didn't know all the facts at the time, but you may have been like standing out front
of the door like knocking repeatedly over and over again in a loop.
No, no, that was inside, I had already come inside at that point I think.
No I mean like afterwards, like you were talking on Discord, but like when you went to knock
on the neighbor's door, like if you were doing other things in a loop, maybe you knocked
on their door for like 10 minutes.
I might have done it multiple times, a lot of it is a blur.
Shit, fair enough.
So you know.
That's pretty epic by the way.
So the thing about it is like, what's annoying about it is that it was a shitty trip because
I didn't even realize I was high at the time, I didn't feel like I was doing anything weird,
it felt normal and like, what's the point of that?
What's the point if you feel normal?
It's all downsides to me.
Yeah, so I don't know, not the best, whatever.
Right, I mean now I suppose you know your neighbor and one of them at least thinks he's not really
worse.
It's like ignorance anyway.
They know that I'm a fucking weirdo.
Oh yeah, yeah, well that was inevitable I suppose, unless they just never met you.
It's like nothing ventured, nothing gained, right?
I guess so.
So you're known as the Molly Knocker.
I'm saying audience to Molly Knocker, I guess.
Ooh, yeah.
Catchy, catchy.
Not bad.
Urban legend.
Incredible.
This fucking, the legends tell of a guy who at four in the morning would be like, hey
I'm your neighbor, how's it going?
It sucks because lately I've been thinking like I should introduce myself to my neighbors,
maybe I should like get a pie, like bring a pie over or something, be like hi, what's
up?
Well now I fucking blown it.
You know, I don't think that's necessary.
I think where there's a will, like okay, is this a problem just theoretically to examine
if one could perhaps make any kind of way to be like positively know your neighbors?
Like is it potentially possible?
Yes.
Would it take perhaps more effort than it would have from the start?
That's possible.
Now it's going to take two pies.
It might take two.
It might be worried about what's in the pies at this point.
The store bought pie and still sealed up.
Have it sealed?
Yeah.
They'll notice a few syringe holes in the side as they're opening it up.
So that's my fucking weekend story.
What do they call it?
That like curve or whatever where there's a certain time when, like I just had a neighbor,
like one of the neighbors in the house I live in, he moved out recently.
I had had a handful of exchanges with that guy and the vast majority of them were as
I was moving in because I just was outside the most inevitably he like couldn't help
but interact with me a little bit as he went into his place or whatever.
I was moving my shit in like since then we've exchanged like maybe a dozen words.
And then after like over a year of living here, he moved away and he seemed like a pretty
cool guy.
I think it was like a military guy.
He was like Asian or something.
And frequently I would see him playing his computer.
I think World of Warcraft late into the evening and also so he wasn't a total loser.
I don't know, maybe like once a month or whatever.
He would bring like a bunch of friends into like this little like kind of glass, kind of
like a little, I don't know, like a little glassed in area that kind of stuck out of
his apartment, which was a nice area.
He would sit there with a bunch of friends and they would all play board games together.
And I thought many times, it is neat.
I thought I should just go down to that guy, knock his door, so like, hey, dude, you know,
couldn't help but notice you play games or something.
How would you feel about like me and Michelle bringing a pie and just hanging out?
Because I don't know.
Yeah, like I've seen our neighbors like through their way, like we see, we see him play Smash
Bros and stuff.
Yeah.
They just seem like dudes like of like similar age to like the people that live in this house.
We could probably hang out if we wanted to.
We just nobody does.
We're just all cowards these days and we're too stuck in our Amazon Prime machines.
We're too busy on our Samsung Galaxy and playing Pokemon Go.
I mean, on the one hand, like Calidus, but on the other hand, we can speak to people
through a wire, so we don't need to go outside to talk.
Like if we're lonely, we could just have a chat.
I think there are important things that you get through a face-to-face interaction that
cannot be replicated through a digital.
It is true.
The lessons.
It's hard.
It's hard to feel that.
It's like some reason for you to stay inside compared to us.
It's kind of like the same thing.
You don't need courage when you have fucking Molly.
Like courage, yeah.
So pop some pills and go say hi to your fellow man, I guess.
I think of these things and I would encourage others to think of it as well as like socialization
in general is very much like exercise.
It's something that doesn't exactly feel good to start to do, but once you've got going
and especially after you've done it, you feel really good about it and it's definitely
good for you.
So you know, I should do more for sure.
I should, exactly.
I mean, I should have done with that guy.
He moved away.
Whatever.
I guarantee there will be a million other chances in my life to say hi to a neighbor or something.
But I mean, I live in a really poor neighborhood right now, so he was kind of the only one
that I was even thinking of doing that with.
So I mean, I don't interact with the poor, as you know me.
No, no, no.
So I would never.
No value to extract there.
No, sir.
Yeah.
I wanted to talk a little bit about crochet.
Please do.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I saw you did the thing.
Oh, yes.
Talk about it.
So last year I was getting into crochet and I was crocheting a few things and it was it
was really nothing.
It was I had this Christmas gift from a while ago, which was like a Star Wars Yoda crochet
Christmas gift.
Baby Yoda.
Yeah.
No.
It was a pre baby Yoda, pre baby Groot.
And I didn't want to make a Yoda.
So I just used the yarn to make whatever and I discovered that I like crochet.
The book that it came with was too hard to follow.
So I looked at YouTube tutorials, obviously really, you know, much better and I learned
how to do a basic crochet and I made it like an arm bracelet, which I gave to Munchie, which
he still has.
And that's cool.
I asked for some yarn for for that Christmas and then I didn't use it.
It's just been sitting on my desk, but bullseye and I was like, finally, just decided to
start using it again.
And it's it's really fun.
I'm not really doing anything like I posted on Twitter.
I made a big rectangle, which is basically just a repetitive repetitive task, making
a crochet in a line and turning around and going the other way and just going this way
in that way.
And I made a rectangle and it was cool and I can use it to put pins on.
So now I have a place for my pin collection.
It's not it's the Puba.
It's Puba pin.
Yeah.
All on there.
Dude, speaking of pins, I think my fucking heart pins are due to arrive any day now.
Fuck fucking I'm fucking juiced.
What about the other pins?
Did you already have the book ones?
I already I already have the book pins and the Puba pins.
I've just I've got enough left over from the last one.
I didn't have to order anymore.
Oh, OK.
Miraculously.
And I'm thinking like the the the the stereotype is like grandma knitting like Christmas sweaters
for all of her grandkids and they hate you because they suck.
I'm not really into like knitting, you know, entire sweaters yet also take a while, but
I am thinking like I could maybe knit like this is really gay is really really gay, but
I'm thinking of knitting like clothes for like the brisker and punk plush that I have
like a little like a little like little mittens or something just as a like a little project.
He's kind of gay.
It is.
It's pretty sick.
No, it's precious.
Do it.
It's precious.
Like that's not that's not a good look.
That's not good.
Like for a man.
I get fucking crucified.
No, I mean, I mean, I'm I'm about results.
So like if knitting is the fastest and most efficient way to achieve whatever ends you're
looking for in this case, I guess to obtain highly specific cloth goods, then like I would
say absolutely go for it.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
I am thinking like eventually eventually I want to be I was like making this rectangle
and I was learning a few basic crochets like the crochet, the half double crochet, which
is cool, the double crochet, which is even cooler, and then the triple crochet, which
is a little bit a little bit too far.
And I was doing those and I was like, OK, this is pretty good.
I want to learn some new patterns.
I want to learn some something that isn't just a rectangle, something that's slightly
more complex.
And I looked on you on online, found a bunch of things.
But there was like this one blog, I mean, all the all these blogs, they're all very feminine,
very gay, very girly, very pink and very pointless.
There was so much of like stupid shit that no one would ever need.
Is it like, is it like how when you look up a recipe, every fucking recipe you find is
preceded by like 14 paragraphs of like some wine mom explaining about how she was struck
for inspiration for this thing, like while she was like hiking in the Alps or something.
White middle class wine mom crochet is like they've got the market corner.
There's no cool crochet guys.
I couldn't be the only man who don't crochet.
I want to like I want to like use the white yarn I have and make a skull, a 3D skull and
that's going to be really difficult.
But like there's no fucking plans like that I can blueprints for a skull I can find.
I can make like I can make like a mermaid dress for a baby, but I don't want to do that.
That's a stupid idea.
Babies want to eat stuff.
They want to put plastic in their mouths and throw it.
That's what they want.
You don't make them yarn while like your blanket would be nice.
It'd be cool to make the skull and then like have that like plan available to others who
were similarly predisposed to want that.
You can make little hats for babies if you want to make something for kids.
Fuck babies.
Nobody likes babies.
They should all die and burn and you know.
I don't know any babies' personalities and agree with it.
But yeah like the next step I guess is like finding baby clothes but just making them
like fit the plushies I have which is again really gay.
I don't want to stress that I know how gay this is.
I just like crocheting so I don't care.
Okay.
Well it makes sense to me.
That's like not gay at all.
That's the opposite of gay.
Like I'm just I'm going to do it fuck what everyone else thinks that's big dick energy.
Go for it.
Make it happen.
I think if you if you want the final product then it only makes sense.
Yeah.
It's totally totally reasonable to me eventually.
Eventually I may be at a point where like I like it enough and I'm good at it enough
to like be an Etsy boy dude like Etsy things.
Sure.
Like hey I'll make like obscure weird masculine things but in crochet form if you want instead
of like gay bears and and and smiley phases that everyone else does I'll make a skull
for you I'll I'll do that and ship it to you and you'll I'll make I'll make a skull cozy
for your Dan Ackeroids crystal skull I'll make a fucking coffin for you a coffin cozy
for my deceased baby who Nate aforementionedly was going to incinerate and you know providing
a service people need here mage well if you're going to incinerate it and earn cozy would
probably you know you're right much much simpler design yeah let's not be on the subject
of the masculinity of such activities it's I mean it sounds to me like at least part
of the inspiration here seems to be that like the sheer enjoyment of kind of having a repetitive
task is is kind of relaxing I don't I don't have that much time to do a lot of repetitive
tasks but you know because it's like I'm either drawing or I'm working I'm writing when I'm
listening to something that I could turn my brain off at right which is why I had to stop
yarn for a bit and I want to get back into it to do to do some sort of pen but it is
very nice it's like it takes a while which is kind of the the toughest thing about it
because you need you need time obviously there's loads of there's lots of content there's lots
of content and there's podcasts that I can listen to for that but it's like an issue
of like time in the day right you have to dedicate that time to doing that thing even
if you have plenty to listen to it's hard to like do any other like obviously you're both
your hands are being used up but I can't even really think of like my own projects because
that's like strenuous so I have to just sort of veg out and do yarn for a whole day and
it's I mean it kind of reminds me of I just think of like I mean I now I'm a capital
G gamer and there's nothing more masculine than that but after a hard gaming sesh I mean
what do I have to show for it you know only the sick trophies on your Xbox live yeah that's
the thing and there's nothing more masculine than that I'll make a PS4 cozy for you so
that it can warm up and overheat so it'll overheat yeah it's just like make a CPU cozy
for me so it can get way overheated and burn up while I'm playing burn out paradise overclocked
oh hey you know what oh yeah going on video games are you gonna talk about cross crisis
cringe cringe okay well you cross code this game I've been enjoying so much I mean I could
say yeah I talked about last time they still still going strong recommended for everybody
but that's that's it same for me with Divinity Originals in two also still playing still
fun I had to restart the game now instead of eight buckets I had 16 so there you go buckets
of blood yeah and I'm still going I'm I still gathered by because sadly I had to sell some
of them off because they were taking up inventory but I still keep gathering them now I mean
and you gave him playing your own big ol video yeah so I obsessively I've been like I finished
the yarn and then I immediately filled my time with some other bullshit which was a video
game called Nino Kuni 2 Revenant King he don't try and try not to spoil because I'm gonna
play it as soon as I'm done okay first one yeah that they are not related story wise
whatsoever as far as I understand so but I won't spoil any of the story but the the basic
gist of this is that it's like an RPG about a little boy prince who is overthrown his kingdom
his cat kingdom he's a cat boy and there are cat people there's a lot of furries in this game
they're all very nicely drawn and 3d rendered so it's not like gross or anything totally cool
yeah so it's totally cool they're all smooth there's no there's no like fur physics involved
it's great god this prince was like attacked his kingdom was attacked and he was thrown out
ready to run away and in it he he wants to try and get back his kingdom but he can't like you
know do anything by himself because he's on his own and so he has to try and build a kingdom
himself but with the intent of like because he's you know born to rule in it literally because he's
a prince and he's like I'm gonna be born to rule the world is I'm gonna be a 10,000 dead cops
right understood and your mission or your your quest is about building a kingdom and then
uniting the kingdoms together in peace and it's you know beyond that is a very basic RPG
cultural victory of civilization yes right okay and so it's it's it's a good game I'm
trying to think of I'll just talk about gameplay it's action RPG you run around and you you see
monsters in the field there's like the world map is your tiny chibi people and you run around you
see them and you see the monsters you run into them you can run away from them and then there's
in 3d whoa can you still recruit the monsters or did they get rid of that you can't recruit
monsters the the whole thing is the monsters are you know just monsters you kill them but you
recruit people in villages and towns for your kingdom that is its own like mini game large
part of the game but like mini game thing so it's a town building game where you have Kings
Guilders which is like currency for spending on building projects and fortifications and army
stuff and research on new technologies so that like if you get your if you want like a specific
character to have a really powerful ranged weapon you build your research ranged weapon stuff
upgrades in your armory weapon shop and then you can go shop there and you can buy it and it's all
it's it's it's real so you have to put in resources to research your thing and now and then you
don't even get it you have to buy you yeah yeah it makes sense it makes sense that's how
people should probably be aware as well it's by level five who made dark cloud and what not
yes yes I was speaking about this tonight a few days ago it's it's it feels a lot like dark cloud
three because there's the whole dungeon crawling or monster slashing action stuff what what is it
called it's like action RPG where you run and roll and dodge and you press the buttons in real time
I guess action RPG is the best one we got for that Dark Souls-esque perhaps it's it's like it's like
it's like Kingdom Hearts and Dark Souls and a little bit of Okami it's turn based isn't it
the Dark Souls of Kingdom Hearts it is it is it is real time action RPG you run around right like
the first one yeah you you kill you kill and you gain power and that's why I like to hear that's
all I needed to hear I mean yeah the thing the thing that I really like it's got the endorsement
there's all the different nations there's this ocean nation where everybody's a blue fish person
and a lot of the blue fish ladies also have red hair so undyne is in this game oh and you can
recruit a few undynes to add to your army and your kingdom and they all have different skills some
of them are good at you know spell stuff others are good at weapon things and there's loads of
different buildings you can get and then you upgrade your kingdom it starts as a like a little
sort of wooden sort of thank you a rustic wooden like Viking town hall thing yeah few tents and
then you upgrade it to level 2 and it's got walls and there are buildings with bricks and then the
music changes and it's more bombastic and now level 3 it's like a huge sprawling thing you've got a
shipyard you've got this and then that and then the music is even more bombastic and level 4 is
just around the corner so basically you lose your kingdom you make a new kingdom you make a new
kingdom and then I don't I don't I don't want to spoil but there's a really cool thing with what
happens with the guy who overthrows you because the choices are make peace with him or go to war
with him and it's like ooh what's gonna happen wait we're quite interesting Nino Kuni to Revenant
Kingdom yeah it's on it's sounds like a very satisfying gameplay loop it is a it is a very
satisfying gameplay loop I haven't explained it the best because I don't think some of these things
are hard to just know I want to look up some images so I can look at look at trailer footage
it that the thing that really got me into it was like why does it look like Ghibli it I think it's
a lot of Ghibli people the guy who does a lot of good reason why it looks like a fucking Ghibli
because Ghibli people are involved the guy yeah that the guy who does most of the Ghibli music
soundtracks does the soundtrack for this game and it's very nice the art direction is really good
and it has art direction which you can't say for every game every every some games they just want
to be like let's put a lens flare in there and I hate it turn it off this game has bright colors
beautiful designs of things the one thing I would say is that the story is a bit basic and
like baby's first RPG the bad guy is just bad and you go and kill and it's it's simple simplistic
there's not a lot of like hard questions being asked about the politics of like starting a kingdom
in a place and disposing like bandits who used to live there and and but you know is it is it
whimsical because I really love the first one because it was so whimsical and there's so many
puns and stuff and I love it I've heard well it is whimsical it's funny and cute and it's very
wholesome it's a very very wholesome feeling thing oh I'm glad um I have want to play it now I have
heard a little bit that there are maybe due to the scope of like the amount of people there's a
lot of side quests to get people in your kingdom um I don't know for what reason but people have
said that the first game has a lot of cutscenes and a lot of writing prowess there's a lot of
really in you know you really care about the characters a lot and the story is good sure
nino kuni two people say it sort of falters in the story department and the characterization
and a lot of there's not that many cutscenes there's one there's a few big ones at the
beginning and apparently some of the end I haven't eaten it yet but most of like the story stuff is
like characters standing around talking in text which I don't mind personally because like I'm
used to I'm used to old games where fully voice acted stuff was just not a thing so I still like
that right I mean these days a lot of that can be more trouble than it's worth and be more of a
downside than anything if it like stops you to try to watch a cutscene that's so good I don't know
so it depends I mean yeah it's it's not like a terrible thing like I didn't know that the first
game had better writing and I was perfectly satisfied with what I'd been experiencing so
it's it's a good good good time just just because something is supposedly better doesn't mean the
other thing is bad no I like this little I like this little Lisa Simpson ass bitch oh yeah I kept
calling him Lisa Simpson he's the king maker every every host and I don't know what you're
talking about every it's the cute animal sidekick is like a spiky-headed like yellow blowfish thing
and like a red robe and it looks it's it's literally Lisa it looks I believe you but yeah
paste it in the damn chat all right fine that guy that guy's called lofty and he is um the king
maker of young evan every king has to have a king maker in order to be recognized as such
and so there's like every kingdom has their king maker and a huge massive grandiose beasts and
then Evan gets this tiny little Lisa Simpson guy who has like a Welsh accent like a very strong
Welsh accent it's kind of it's kind of hard to like parse some of the text because they do a lot of
like um English accents in like phonetically written and his well stuff is a bit hard to
parse sometimes and there's these very up north like Manchester sort of characters who are um
like shipwrights and it's kind of impossible to tell what they're saying you have to really
go over it like okay you're just saying thanks you ever play you ever play poacher what's that
it's it's it's one of the games but that yatsi made and it's Ryan Ryan well it's the only one
that I have any interest in playing because it's a Metroidvania and not like some weird adventure
thing um and it's super good and it just reminds me like the the guy you play as is like this like
hunter guy who's from who's up north and like he speaks in like such a fucking thick ass accent
that like other people can't understand him but he's really funny that's a really fucking good
game by the way and it's free um it's free just what metacritic thinks of it yeah speaking of
accents and voice acting as if Divinity original sin and original sin too I haven't fully played
the first one I only played a little bit of it a better guy distracted by the fact that could be
a bush and I just walked around being a bush a while and then I became a rock and then a box
it's a good game I swear but like the thing about the games um they're very much voice acting even
even like the little animals that you might not be able to ever speak to ever if you don't take
the skill pet talk or something like that they all they're also fully voice acting and it's just
amazing how much work they put into this game and it doesn't feel like they had to restrict
themselves due to the fact that they had to voice act things uh the main character is mute so you
know main character isn't voice acted uh but other than that I think like every single thing has a
voice to it and it's really cool and it's very British accent te so neat that's pretty cool
that's pretty cool actually such a good game speaking of game development and and yacht this
just reminds me of one other thing I was going to mention this episode which is just so the the
game development pcp bonus episode came out uh beginning of the month or whatever so you should
go listen to that but now that a time period has elapsed uh because I put effort into this I want
to do this I uh one of the things we talked about that I brought up on that was this demo of this
game I made with my friend Jonos uh this music jumper demo featuring qt bass drop blah blah blah
etc etc um I'm just I was so proud that because while we were recording that I didn't have a
working demo and I tried to find it after that episode ended I went I found the code and I attempted
to get to work it didn't work I had to actually dig in and fix some broken things in order to get
an exported working executable for the game and I did that and I exported it and now like the one
level you can play actually works and I linked that in that episode and I was just so proud of
myself for figuring that out and getting it working it didn't take me long but I had to put
some effort in that uh I wanted everybody to play it and see the cute girl qt bass drop in there
so uh link in the description too to the extremely short demo of that game uh by me and my buddy
Jonos but hopefully you will enjoy you indeed very very proud very strong very powerful me curious
it's good speaking of the video games speaking of video games I've I've been playing or I played
briefly yesterday after seeing it on twitter a bunch of the time have you seen uh the talkings
about AI dungeon 2 nope no okay so uh AI dungeon 2 has been popping up all over like my game dev
twitter because that's the people I follow uh I guess so you guys are aware of you know uh text
rpgs you know that that old classic genre where you just type commands and you play the rpg
you know with no like uh I mean I know text-based adventure games or is it like that plus like hp
and stuff well just just like a text-based adventure game you know okay like that that
oft neglected genre yeah so some guy I guess decided I'm going to combine that style of game
with AI so you just it just randomly generates an adventure and it'll accept any command you
type in just in normal English and we'll parse it and try and continue the story based on it
and so it has like an infinite number of like scenarios and stuff and it just generates I assume
it uses AI to like figure out what you're saying and yes like your mileage perhaps may vary based
on the strengths and weaknesses okay I guess you like you can choose the genre of style adventure
you want from a couple options in the beginning okay it recommends fantasy I'm assuming probably
because that's the one that's it's the most competent in but you can also do like post apocalyptic
and things like that like a different or like a mystery I haven't dealt delved too deeply into it
but I was interested because it's like starting to address something I've always kind of dreamed
about about games because like one of the if you watch the uh the the video that I did a long time
ago on the pcp responding to ben about why dnd is so cool right the idea I was saying is that
tabletop allows you to do anything you know because you have another human being to listen
to what you're doing and I've always wondered when is technology going to get good enough
that video games will be able to do something similar no longer constrained by a particular
particular rule set and this is like that as well I just like your first step towards that is this
game like that's kind of a coward's pitch is that you can say whatever you want and uh so I played
a little bit of it yesterday uh before I went to bed this is called AI dungeons AI dungeon yeah um
two two so I can find a link for it I don't have it on hand because playing on my laptop and it works
to a degree I mean okay um I think it's probably because a lot of what I was doing I was trying
to like push the engine and see how far it works so instead of like typing good I'm glad you did
commands like because when you the situation I got I was talking to some guy outside of a bandit camp
and I was just speaking in English like in response to the queries as opposed to trying to talk
as you would in a traditional text adventure game and there were a couple like kind of like
assumptions it made about what I was saying but like the game continued regardless of whatever I
said uh so it's interesting and I definitely want to play around with it more I was thinking maybe
doing an iam games video on it just because I think the concept is so novel and like that's cool
people interested in it sadly so we cannot play at this every moment any uh any highlights from
your experience during it notable experiences I gave you or anything I guess I mean I didn't get
super far into it so I can't say like I have a breath of experience of the game but just the
fact that like it's so approachable you know like there's nothing to learn there's no like it's
just like you speak English and the game responds and it's it's it's still like a lot a lot to go I
guess to make it like truly natural but I think this will be an interesting starting off point
because like if you can get to a point where you can have an AI basically DM a game for you it opens
up a lot of possibilities uh even if it's just like a behind the scenes thing in a more traditional
game so uh yeah that's definitely true and I mean one of the one of the I mean I'm sure of course
you're aware but it's like uh the main issue of like when you can play a game with another human
they have like all their the the bind is a is a powerful machine for coming up with information
and stuff I mean I think humans are just robots but really advanced robots that do this stuff really
well and like we've got we've got definitely a long way to go before a machine is capable of
handling things to the same degree of flexibility that your human mind on average is able to
but uh yeah I mean any any step forward sounds like a cool one so I would be
fascinated to hear if other people have played as well with their experiences nobody's safe
from the robots taking over even DM right there's not even our video games the small window of time
in between where we are right now when the robots kill us all that we'll have perfect video games
I'll have to just like really enjoy that brief window I heard like there was a line I heard
something about perfect video games like perfect entertainment the other day I was like some dystopian
line about once we have like perfect video games there's no point in doing anything anymore
because I mean what is a perfect video game except like an infinite pleasure machine I guess basically
so uh yeah we're all fucked when we get there but in the meantime uh keep it keep it tight lads
keep going to the gym but by the way while I was googling AI dungeon 2 uh it brought me to
like a kotaku article about it and and this and then from there I saw linked another kotaku
article that I think you guys should definitely take a look at and uh I'm a little distrustful
of kotaku generally but I had heard about this elsewhere so I think this is accurate and okay
take a look at this the article title is vaping congressman who spent campaign funds on steam
games resigns okay so this guy this guy Ben I didn't know you were a member of congress oh
I thought vaping wasn't a crime what happened fuck this guy is a republican that's not okay he is a
republican from california and listen to this he so he misused apparently uh $250,000 in campaign funds
including out of that $1,528 spent on steam games now that's not a massive amount of money but it
is a sizable amount of money to spend on okay it is a massive amount to spend on steam games how
many yeah that's so many fucking games I mean the question is did he spend that during a steam sale
or no I mean that's less than one percent of the total amount that was misused it is uh see
that they're a little bit exaggerating like gamer guy but I mean he definitely isn't a video games
if you spent that much um there's there's like I'm curious where he spent the rest of it probably
in like I don't know houses and travel and who knows who knows but it is funny and he is vaping
in congress as we see well I'm mad that he's gonna cost us our our vape representation
damn it we had one at last apparently he was vaping during a transportation committee hearing
about whether to ban e-cigarettes on planes so okay you know what that may have been a deliberate
statement it sounds like like it sounds like it can't have been an accident no of course not he's
vaping pretty no he knows what he's doing look at that image look at how smart he looks he knows I
mean someone's probably going on about how like oh we don't know what they're doing as he just blows
a fat cloud in their face um and take that madame speaker or you know whatever the fuck he's clearly
doing it on purpose to try and undermine vapors everywhere unfortunately oh yeah well it's
succeeded and now I see some high jewel pods in massachusetts anymore I guess vaping is a crime
now legally I'm just curious okay no only buying them is a crime right no no sorry they're selling
them is a crime now I haven't looked into the details of this at all uh and like so okay miss
spent $250,000 it sounds like he resigned like surely you must go to jail when you miss spend
$250,000 of other people's money right yeah politicians don't uh they they make the laws
they don't live by them I guess it depends like how maybe he just like bought way too many like
reelect me signs for himself like if that's the issue I mean like okay I guess it doesn't
matter what you spend it on I don't know you know it okay surely it matters to some degree
like the steam games thing I mean that's in no way helping the people unless he's the game
a representative he's trying to get in touch with his constituents man in which case this
politician shit when are we gonna talk about the new jesus video game do you guys see that
I have seen that wait I saw Jim's video and like the the other game he talked about seemed way
more interesting Jim sterling Jim sterling uh tell me about the jesus game I guess I haven't
seen it it's just it looks this is weird I think it's a pre-rendered trailer there's no way the
game's gonna look like it's what it's called I am jesus christ and it's like a first person game
where you just bomb around as jesus jesus has a mana bar and you perform miracles or something
I did just see a gif of it and it looked like shit yeah yeah it's bizarre well but I can't believe
it's real it's gotta be made by like some kind of like I'm not sure if this is like a legitimate
like christian game or if it is a meme I haven't I haven't parsed it but the the pre simulator
looked a lot more funny and interesting like the satan just comes in and just right strangles you
which is funny it's all about the name on it's all in the name like I am just it gets the clicks
you know so mission successful I wonder how much money that will be uh converted into you know
probably not much but I was thinking about like the whole like oh dude you get to play as Jesus
being crucified
game of the year game of the year confirmed crucifixion or are you saying game I was I was
thinking about like the the fundamental problem with politicians always being led to corruption
because it's just sort of a fun like it always seems to happen no matter what system power corrupts
people find ways to because they're making the laws and they can break them because they're
making them essentially they can find loopholes because they make the loopholes for themselves
and for their friends and I just it really just comes down to the power of being in power
comes with a lot of money and I think if we put if some if some Jesus christ superstar man
got into power and then made a law that means that you have a like you only get minimum wage
if you're a politician mm-hmm like you can't get higher than minimum wage that's what you get
you don't get money for being in power because you already have power hey donald trump gave up
his whole salary as president that's why he's the best we've ever had right well he gets work the
system works but he gets his his like $200,000 salary is that's correct yeah he did I think he
donated it I don't know how generous it's kind of an impossible problem because like it is it is
well the reason there's no perfect system the people like
like politics doesn't necessarily mean you are corrupt if you're a politician there are people
trying to do good things it's just that mixed in with those people are so many other people who
just like the money and the power and if you take away like the incentive for those other people
you'll be left with only people who care about making their country better or whatever for sure
it's just it's just not possible to like it like make that change because the people who
stay in power are usually the people who are the most aggressive and like you in order to stay in
power you need to be focused on staying in power and not focused on I mean helping people who are
going to be the most motivated to stay in power are the people for whom is the thing that gets their
dick hard so you know it's going to be a bunch of fucking psychopaths well I mean it's it's like
this is the argument for term limits like this for at least here in the US for like congress and
stuff because like you have people who just like get paid a fuck ton of money they get tons of like
bribes and you know lobbying money and there's no term limit so they don't have to deal with the
consequences of their legislation and this is the argument for having term limits so if you have
like a two term limit like whatever fucked up shit you do you have to live by once your terms are up
but like the issue right now of course is just that like the people in the with the authority
to change society for the better are the ones benefiting from keeping it the way it is so no
one has any incentive or any means to change society which is why we have to murder everybody
makes sense time for a revolution time for a revolution boys vote burning
time for a 360 revolution no scope kill the president
dude if the person who kills you know the next president donald trump or whoever comes next
uh those like a 360 no scope then i think he should be allowed to not die i think he should
be allowed to go free in fact anyone who kills anyone with a 360 no scope in real life the person
who does the best 360 no scope is the next president that yeah dude 360 no scopes i've been
training for us my whole life i wonder if anyone has actually 360 no scope in real life like in
war you know i i wouldn't be i wouldn't be surprised if like some superman like some
gamer god played our like cola duty what got into army because of cola duty and then tried it
and then he got told off but he's like yeah he got fucking immediately like like court marshaled
because he likes spun around in his target with his sniper rifle does it count if you do it just
like at a range or something uh is that if you turn around in a range you'll probably hurt someone
like i don't think you're allowed to turn around with your gun what if you just if you're by yourself
i'm sure i'm sure people have done it at a range i'm talking about in a real
live in a live combat situation you'd have to be a fucking psycho you'd have to be a fucking
bad ass dude i mean you'd have to be like the coolest soldier out there to do that that is how
they kill the summer bin Laden so you know what you're right what was i think of course they just
got their kill ratio up so that like it's that cola duty achievement where you like unlock the dogs
to attach i think that's how they got what's his face recently remember that one hero dog that like
trump gave a medal yeah maybe the dog like the medal of pauner i believe it was called yeah like
maybe the dog 360 no scoped whoever like he 360 no scoped bit someone in the yeah like that like
he spun around perfectly still stationary like it's not as impressive for dogs though they have
like a great sense of smell and that's right on in the barbarian scent alone uh oh okay the the
hero dog who was injured during a raid which led to death of isis leader abu bhak bhakir al bagdadi
okay so i don't know if you bad doggy more like the only the only answer to a bad doggy is a good
doggy the only thing that stops a bad doggy with a gun is a good doggy with
man it's fucked up how how much we fucked up dogs like as a species like pug's eyes just fall out
and shit sure sure i mean there's no uh there's no way to fix this they love it though they love it
could we could we call this the first ever ethical we did we fucked them up so their eyeballs pop out
but we also bred them to fucking love it they yeah i mean that's true they cannot get enough of their
own eyeballs falling out they cannot get enough of barely being able to breathe at all times yeah
that's the modest the modest amount of air that they're able to get in is like just enough to keep
them fucking jazzed about life if you could create a life they're fucking high on like oxygen deprivation
24 7 you know what yeah constant auto erotic expixiation just that's that's just their
modus operandi brilliant brilliant maneuver all right i'm i'm tapped yeah i'm i'm dry of things to
say i want to say one thing uh that happened to me immediately almost immediately after we stopped
recording last week on sunday so uh before before the podcast i cooked myself some chicken and i ate
it and i thought to myself that tasted a little bit odd not like bad it just a little bit odd
and then after the podcast like i want to like i didn't immediately go to bed better that day
ish i went to bed and uh and i started getting chills and i started getting feeling really bad
and the chills got really violent and painful and and my fever rose to um 39 Celsius which i think is
102 Fahrenheit word uh and yeah and i thought i thought i because i kept getting chills i
thought is gonna get higher and my boyfriend was asleep so i just left him a message on discord
if i don't wake up call the ambulance
all right wait wait wait wait wait wait with the lifestyle oh god did you wake up on discord
I don't know did I but yeah I was I was scared because I didn't know at that
point that it was food poisoning I just I just started messaging people just
like hey I might not do the commission I'm sorry give me a few days if I might
never wake up in time to do the commission I didn't I didn't want to
alert people I just said like hey I'm a little bit not feeling too good not sure
what I'm gonna feel better but yeah I just I was panicking because I don't
remember the last time I hear it was so high and but yeah so like it did go down
eventually within the 24 hours and then like three days after I was in pretty
bad shape on the on the upside though I got to taste Jacobs crackers Jacobs is
a brand and crackers are really and and and they were really nice yeah they're
crackers are like like a like a cure-all for for feeling sick I have like a
whole packet when I'm just not not like I don't want to eat real food in case I
get like throw up right yeah if your stomach is upset you can eat crackers
and Jacobs crackers are really nice and toasty I like how lightly toasted they
are they're just so just so good very good crackers you know Michelle wasn't
feeling great the other day so I went out and got chicken soup crackers and
ginger ale I have enjoyed those myself with all leftovers and it has been
delicious I love them yeah so for three days afterward I had to be within close
proximity of a bathroom at all times and not good days not good days do you know
what it is that gave you the poison was it was it the chicken uncooked or
something I think I it wasn't cooked enough okay so like they're like
instructions on that chicken specific it's like after you open the packet 24
hours to eat them it had not been 24 hours but was getting close and I might
have taken them taken them out a bit too early and it just baffles me
because like they were supposed to cook for five more minutes afterwards so
those five minutes could have been like the difference between yeah food poison
and not food poison so cook your food people less than well learned and when
I've been when I've been making the curry recently like the way you cook it is you
you fry the vegetables and the and the meat at the beginning but you you're
only supposed to fry them for like five minutes so the meat is not fully cooked
at that point but then like you put into boiling water you're like cooking that
for longer and like I've been scared every time that like I'm not cooking it
as long as it needs to it hasn't been an issue so far and it's been perfect well
so long as you boil it properly like yeah yeah but I've been on I've been
scared that I'm going to under cook because it goes in just just boil it for
a little bit extra I have been I have been but now now that I've heard your
tale even even more so I spoke to everyone but yeah I survived
thankfully but God God that was such a big scare that is unfortunate being
not sure if she's going to die her first concern is I can't wake up my
boyfriend and my commissioners might be upset with me you know there's there's a
feeling I think in all of us that's like if I bother someone like at any moment
we might be dying if something I've got a little prick in my back maybe I just
got bit by a black widow I'm about to die and if I don't contact someone within
10 seconds like I'm going to you know die of that poison but maybe it's nothing
and I don't want to bother people in case it turns out to be nothing there's
like a certain amount of of of estimation you have to make there about how much
I don't like if I feel like I might die I'm not gonna worry about that's like
um it's the doubt it's the doubt that's that gets you out is it I mean this is
how I think about it I mean if I I don't really get too worried if I'm not
like actually feeling bad as well like if I'm feeling bad physically and it like
I might be sick and this might be a really bad sickness I don't think people
like I don't think of like my my like a worry in the moment as like that big of
a deal in the in hindsight like people aren't gonna worry about it but if it
was like if it was like I didn't feel anything but I just had some strange
idea that I was gonna die that would be weird I wouldn't I wouldn't bother people
that's for me for me it was kind of like my boyfriend already knew that I was
sort of ill because I went to bed and said like I'm feeling really cold and
I'm not feeling too good so he knew I was not good and the fever just hit me in
the middle of the night and I woke up because of the fever so I didn't want
to you know pester him because what is he gonna do I'm just gonna wake him up
and worry him just like there's it's not gonna it's not gonna matter like I just
asked him to like check up on me when he wakes up enough I'm like not
responsive then calling ambulance but I was too awake I didn't fall asleep that
night but yeah before that I didn't even know that it was sweet poisoning because
beforehand for like a whole month I was feeling ill like sore throat and then
like very small he was here and there because I always get sick around this
time of year so that threw me off and I didn't realize it was food poisoning up
until like much later but he was the one who suggested oh it could have been
food poisoning I was like nah it must be it must be just like the flu but no he
was right flu poisoning well glad you made it out the other side I suspect a
cold see now now that I'm thinking about sickness now I'm feeling like I'm oh am I
like hotter than I'm normally feel why am I so hot right now is this like a
fever coming on I get all I get all I you when fever comes on come on you
usually feel a chill rather than feeling hot what's what makes you feel hot like
cold or okay so for the chill comes on one that your fever is rising because
your muscles spasm and they're trying to combat the whatever is alien so to
speak so by the time you're feeling hot you feel the fever but the fever isn't
rising anymore so you're stable I think it's the flu the flu makes you feel hot
I think I thought just a cold makes you feel hot oh no I don't know it's like
uh I don't know oh no the screen all day doing work but I feel like a weird
thing in my head oh god it's my it's my disease is creeping back up it's Japanese
cold you know the the most deadly disease known from the Simpsons that's the
I remember that episode and I think I've got that Japanese they sneezed into a
box and they send it I guess it was a Chinese cold actually okay and then
what the fuck you're talking about but I'm talking about anime colds that lay
people low you know the anime cold that whenever someone says your name you
sneeze no matter where oh okay no yeah I get it like when when in an anime when
someone gets a cold they just like they they have to be hospitalized hit the
fucking floor yes that's right that's right instantly okay well anyway I'm
tapped a couple of voicemail I'm not tapped okay okay I got some things to say
for one say them imagine imagine me dear reader but on a good podcast that
happens no can you believe it it can't you guys know what you guys know the
sketchy people podcast okay I was on it I was on it this Friday I don't know
when the episode is coming out but link in the description I guess I was on it
with who was on it lemon tart sake it's ake a tattoo art of graph aka green
fleshy flowers Asha am I'm forgetting anyone I think that's it anyway it was
good it's a good show that's nice graph grafted um if you remember from the the
editor contest graph was the one who's entry was the two was the TVs all the
all the TVs and Lee he basically created that but different for there and it
looks really cool I'm glad it lives on because I really like that concept yeah
anyway we talk about art and fucking comics and shit and they asked me a
bunch of questions and I dab oh never paint is all so oh yeah never paint was
there you never paint was there and I think you know what yes but noodle bomb
was not on the episode I was on he isn't there sketchy people podcast good
yeah all okay so I did a thing I announced the thing for my patreon and
like it's probably just like not gonna do anything but I'm gonna say it here
anyway just in case so I said that like since I'm doing slime and punishment
and I'm putting in slime boys in as like background characters I said on
Twitter that like if you are my patron and you are a slime boy I will like
preff forgive you preferential tree I will I will put you will be on the short
list to be a background character but it's only for slime boys like if you if
you're not an endless war player like there's no point and I'm not gonna just
like put your OC and if your OC has if you don't play endless war and you're
not in there and you don't know what it is right sure so I announced this on
Twitter and like one guy it became a patron and it was someone who had
previously been a patron anyway so I think that probably maybe this just maybe
this doesn't make any difference maybe I just have already included all of the
hardcore slime boys anyway or enough of them that like maybe anyone who would
have maybe pledged for this for this quote-unquote for this honor this dubious
distinction I like has already gotten it and doesn't need it anymore but what I
think I think a lot of rewards like this like a lot of people kind of just
don't hear about them and aren't even aware it's something they could do I
feel that with some things I do so well I'm saying it here just so everyone
knows but it's not even like I mean I guess it is a reward for pledging but
like mm-hmm like as much as that it's just like I have to put some people in it
kind of to a certain extent it sort of doesn't matter who I put in as background
characters and I feel like if I'm gonna give someone that I might as well give
it to someone who's like supporting me on patreon so I said like if you're if
you're pledging me ten bucks you will be in just message me on patreon and I
will even even if I wouldn't have had another I will like add an extra page
just just to get you in there if you're pledging less than that then you know it'll
just be like basically the more you're pledging the higher up on the list you'll
be and I'll just go down and like priority list basically and message me on
patreon pledge me on patreon I've sort of been neglecting my patreon and I kind
of need to like not do that I too have been kind of trying to to do a couple
of things I've been doing this like my monthly podcast or ever I do just like
how things are going overall for this like I like a year of experimentation and
then I started doing like anybody who's pledging ten dollars I'll give like a
long answer to any questions but only like a couple of people have actually
taken me up on that so I I wonder how many are actually hearing about that
that feature so hey ten dollars I keep I keep thinking I should I should steal
hippo's idea steal your idea and just do a money spenders podcast sometimes I
think that I should just pull a Jesse and just like disappear and make patreon
the only way to contact me it seems to have worked pretty well for him I mean
I'm doing I'm doing a patron podcast since working out pretty well for me as
well yeah I mean that that's exactly what mine is to I think all of us are
kind of 30 something episodes so far five dollars get in on it if you're not
already shameless plug is shameless guess I might start thinking about that it's
fun to do I mean I just have I have I have two podcasts right now I have like
one where it's just like whatever strikes my fancy I'll just make them
whatever and $1 patrons get that and for $5 I have a suggestions channel on the
discord and then people can leave topic suggestions and I'll just at the end of
the week others everyone who dropped one in I'm like all right this is what you
want to talk about this week and then I'll just go off and half an hour of a
podcast it's great since I'm since like currently the reward on my $5 tier is
like access to speed draws I do have what I did I downloaded all the VODs of my
like twitch draw streams and I could and I started doing this but I didn't finish
it and I might do it at some point is like just fucking speed them up and
condense those down into speed draws and make those like some patrons only
content so that's the thing I should probably do I guess if everyone's doing
a fucking solo money spenders podcast I should probably do one too it doesn't
hurt it's simple enough to do for me to be justifying I think so yeah and I kind
of like it it forces me to sit down and like think about stuff which I kind of
like I hate to do it you hate to do it you hate to sit down and acknowledge the
realities of this you of this world indeed indeed I like doing the money
spenders podcast because it allows me to my favorite name to talk about the sort
of stuff that's going on in my life that only patrons would care about so it like
yeah that's one makes sense you know these people give a little bit of a shit
at least yeah nice to know yeah it might you know what I think would might would
maybe be the good thing about it is that then like it like since since I don't
like post a lot of content specifically to patreon I mostly interact with people
through Twitter but it would probably be good to have a thing that only patrons
are listening to and so only patrons are responding to and so I'm getting like
patron feedback like from my like the people from like specifically the
people supporting it hurt to have that dedicated avenue that you know is just
those people you know yeah just for comparison sake if nothing else yeah
maybe they could probably give some like yeah I felt some some insight coming
from that group commenting on on mine that's been I mean just knowing it's
people who are invested again like this that particular group has kind of its
own biases they might like like you too much or they might be like too invested
in stuff and not able to make the kind of cold-hearted decisions you need to as a
businessman or whatever but you know just having that data set has has been
useful I think right yeah okay well now I'm okay oh yeah actually you know what
all that reminded me that I did have one little announcement it's not a big
deal it's nothing crazy except that the heart gold Nuzlocke begins tomorrow
everybody if you're listening to this episode the new Nuzlocke I've decided
fuck it I don't care about waiting anymore whatever I'm gonna be streaming
twice a week from now on Tuesdays and Saturdays but starting the day you hear
this tomorrow on twitch.tv slash definitely best guy ever 7 p.m. now no
more this 30 stuff we don't need that anymore 7 p.m. on Saturday December
the 14th the first episode of the new Nuzlocke it's gonna be a whole new
thing heart gold very except best Pokemon game ever made it's gonna be
actually it's weird going from the the quality of life changes in sword and
shield like should have been there generations ago but going back to like
not happen anymore they took out follow Pokemon so game sucks zero my god I
forgot heart gold like has that that'll be totally all the reason to play
heart gold and soul silver it's up there pretty much playing through black
or I have white version actually but I'm playing to white cuz comments on the
I am games reader did on the first impressions for the new one it's like
that's the best one I have a lighter fucking sick and I'm playing it and it
is like you can just tell going through the towns and stuff all the little
details they add that they cared a lot more and there's just more like life to
everything not wrong like in one of the one of the first towns something that
was super fucking cool is like you you're just in the town and it's playing a
background music and then you go into this like room and there's like a piano
and something like as two people and they're playing instruments and you
talk to them and it just adds more to the music and then you go back outside
and now the music's like remixed I'm like yeah there's nothing like this in
those other games like the towns feel so empty compared to this but listen the
quality of life stuff of the new games is like yeah god what do you mean what
do you mean are you fucking kidding me single use TMS well my problem is that
like not getting XP for catching Pokemon makes me not want to ever catch
Pokemon ever oh yeah that like I have like a like almost 200 catches and that
is a new game that I just from my playthrough and I usually never break
50 on my first run of a poker game because I'm like why would I ever waste my
time catching Pokemon which serves me no purpose and I'll just save it for end
game who fucking cares your subject of like having things reminded me of a
brilliant thing I read I think this is on like a 4chan thread about about
something but I thought this was a very insightful commentary on like old game
good new game bad mindsets which is it's that so like when you compare like Sword
and Shield for example or really like any kind of like triple-a fancy game like
like your Final Fantasy 15 or something like that to like you could say Final
Fantasy 7 or like a sprite like Final Fantasy 6 something like that any of
that old stuff let's just do like a like a fancy 3d game versus like an old like
16-bit like Final Fantasy 6 for example it's that you know in the new game this
was this was something somebody was pointing out that like when you play
the new game it can feel kind of like empty and lifeless despite there being
so much more stuff and it's like why is that and this this person's point was
when if you got a game like Final Fantasy 6 it's it's sprite based right and you
walk around a town and like it's they don't have to think about the kind there's
not so much information that you need to fill this huge 3d space with stuff and
and we're hitting this this like intellectual wall or this like cognition
limit that we can't expect a company like does every fucking blade of grass in
in like Breath of the Wild like have meaning and purpose no no it does not
or like Final Fantasy 15 is an even better example absolutely not like the
vast majority of it is really just filling empty space because something
has to be in that space but in your average like town or even just like an
open wilderness in like a Chrono Trigger or Final Fantasy 6 like proportionately
speaking way more love and way more like kind of intelligence or purpose is
given to every like individual tile or something so it's like when you when you
look at a game like a Chrono Trigger you can kind of feel that like more thought
was put into every individual panel there versus something like Final Fantasy 15
where we just know it's mostly like filler content with a couple of waypoints in
this giant world that have like actual meaning by the developers and that
gulf is the soul versus soulless feeling I think everything in Chrono Trigger you
know was was put there by hand because the entire thing had to be handcrafted
but in Final Fantasy 15 all of the like the vast majority of the environment
stuff like the blades of grass that's all just like a shader or like just like
you know a a program that just like right populates with grass like none of
that was like hand placed and stuff and you know if anybody's gonna say
something like this is fair like Final Fantasy 6 or Chrono Trigger like they
use tile sets I mean okay that's true but like think of the proportions like so
many less tiles are used compared to like the vast gigantic open spaces of
like a Final Fantasy 15 or 13 or I don't know Assassin's Creed or something
like that not that I've played many of those so I think that this gulf is why
at least people like me get instantly more attracted to like sprite based games
because if it feels more like something thing especially considering a game
again RPG like Chrono Trigger or Final Fantasy is that like the level of
abstraction allows you to like you you kind of just subconsciously fill in the
gaps you know because yes you know like you're in a town and like there's like
five buildings in the town but because it's so abstract it's the idea of a town
and then your subconscious like fills in what isn't there but once you get like
in a 3d space that's more photorealistic it's just you know it's the
uncanny valley it's like well there's only like you know 20 people now that work
that was done by the player's imagination has to be done by the
developers and there's no way they can live up to that expectation that we've
had like from our youth and you know this is why realism is such a bane on
fucking video games like it's it's yeah all this empty work that serves no real
purpose it doesn't serve the game it's just like kind of dick wagging for no
no benefit for anybody it's just empty pointless soulless work to re-create
the trudgery of reality that I hate that's absolutely true that's exactly
that's exactly what I was gonna and like the only thing is I I do feel sympathy
for companies who feel and to an extent it's true that they like have to live up
to this standard that they feel is being set I mean companies like Square Enix
take it to the extreme and they do it like they think too much they have to live
up to this I thought I was still muted lol
I mean this was slightly unrelated I just made a post on Twitter this morning
I was just thinking about the Final Fantasy 7 remake wasn't exactly about this but
just like I do have sympathy for companies that I think these days like
standards just changed expectation of the audience change or at least companies
understanding of what they think the audience needs has changed and it's
just put such a burden on them and I have true sympathy for the for the trap
they've basically fallen into with this but I'm just gonna I mean I'm playing
crosscode right now it's like a 16-bit game and I'm loving it so much more than
like any RPG I've played in the last I don't know like RPG specifically in the
last probably like I don't know five to ten years you know I unmuted myself I
was eating lol but I'm muted myself because Nino Cooney has deals with this
problem of like things being like too too real for you to to on this like to get
that it's like everything you see mm-hmm you know probably have meaning or is it
like filler content like with a big no everything is is handcrafted but the
thing they the way they get around it it stylized and when you're in in world
map or in your kingdom mm-hmm you are like a tiny little chibi-ized version of
yourself and everything small and cute and it kind of looks like when you're
running around your kingdom upgrading things they have like timers so like
once you've spent a load of money there's like oh this will take like 12
minutes to research so then you go out into the field and you do stuff and you
come back you've got more income to spend and research is completed but it
looks like a mobile game which is is like it doesn't play like a mobile game
but it looks like a little more ball game if you imagine like I don't know
clash of guys my favorite where everything sort of like cutesy and
stylized and cartoony and they can make games in 3D that look good mm-hmm
is good I think you know Korea is a great example of like not letting
technology like rule you you know because the game stylized so it's not
it's probably not pushing technological boundaries the same way something
like Death Stranding is for example not but it still looks good because it's
it's it's art direction instead of raw polycast yeah that one Zelda game the
people hated when it came out but then started praising about how I think
yeah Wind Waker that's the one that there is a lot there is a very specific
Wind Waker feeling like the the the the the the sea town level which is like
kind of like a half submerged what's it's not called Athens what Atlantis so it's
like a sort of Greekish architecture with this a few of these like stone
walkways that are very like covered in water but like by one or two inches of
water and you splash through it and it's it's a really sunny town and it just is
the it just I love it so much I love the music I love being in that place and
it's it's you know it's a stylized location it's so wonderful that it
couldn't exist in real life because like the realistic lighting engine would make
the shadows so dark that they're black and walking into them would be like oh
you know like you know how in in like realistic games where they do that thing
where if you go from extreme shadow to extreme brightness the camera adjusts
its aperture or whatever to like adjust to the light and now like you can't see
anything that's in the shadow and when you're in the shadow the the light areas
are completely like so bright that you can't see anything I don't like that
about reality I would prefer being able to see the shadows and the light the
same time and you know I would I would prefer the worlds to be art directed
but the real world is annoying things such as you can't see like the human eye
is fallible I prefer video games where they they got around those problems and
then they are officially putting them back in so that people can imagine they're
outside of some stupid bullshit you know I like games past little colors bright
games like like story of seasons games are cute and nice looking and I love them
I mean I'm totally with you on the stylization thing being nice but I
mean you guys are you're talking more about graphics which which again is fine
and I agree with but like I meant it a little bit more like specifically like
gameplay wise I think maybe one good example is like for example you got a
game like Final Fantasy 12 where it's a big open 3d world you can walk around
but there are like set areas that you walk into but the problem I mean it's not
really a problem but like the kind of issue is that you can like look down a
path and you see that there's so much more city that you just can't access due
to like you know invisible walls and not even necessarily that but like the city
is structured in such a way that you can't get to like the vast majority of
it whereas if you compare that to something like Final Fantasy 9 for
example or even Final Fantasy 7 which is the same they both have like pre-rendered
backgrounds and stuff and like pathways that you're let along like a city like
Lindblum or something or Trino it's clearly bigger than the set few areas
you're like able to walk in relatively like how big the city looks but it feels
satisfying from a gameplay sense because like every area you walk through it's
not they're not like a breath of the wild where like it's a whole map full of shit
and then there's just a couple things in there to do or like a Final Fantasy 15
or something it's that like every alley in there is used for like some event
throughout the game so they all like feel meaningful like this is where I had
like that boss battle here's where like Freya joined my party and it feels like
every area for the most part not every single one but like more of it
proportionately feels like it had value and purpose behind it in terms of
gameplay and like I would say like Nino Kuni they have some really good level
designers because the towns in that game are one of the only places like
there are the towns castles like main areas hubs where you talk to people and
that's where your normal character model is they have designed these towns in
such a way that they they are actually very very small but they've made it like
they're just I don't know how they did it I would have to like see if there's an
analysis video analyzing the topography the geology of like Goldpaw which is
like a Chinese dog city where everyone's a dog and they go to the casino
and it's China and it's a really nice place but there's like all these alleyways
but it's not like all these alleyways it's like the entire city is there's no
like invisible wall and the rest of the city is over there it's like the whole
city is very small there's only a few buildings but it feels like it's a big
place because of the way they've structured you know the stairs and the
alleyways and the and and you know what you can see from each location I feel
like a lot of thought has been put into making a 3d environment like that like
feel bigger than it is and it's yeah I think I had the I had the similar sense
with Ding Dong Dell like the first city you go into the first Nino Kuni yeah
really good yeah not that I mentioned I didn't even think about it I like it well
perhaps hopefully we've been successful at articulating this nebulous game feel
issue but that's just a theory a game theory so let us know what you think I
guess you want to go to the voicemails now last I'm ready I'm ready for those
fucking voicemails okay we've only got three so we'll we'll get through them
pretty quick here oh there was an update I didn't feel the need to play it but
I think we had guessed last time that the voicemail God was was keyblade
spirit confirmed not keyblade spirit and the key but do you guys remember no
what was it the remember the unironic gang weed guy who had called in as the
Joker before that's another voice of the voice okay well I remember who could
ever forget that beloved character you know I actually just watched the was a
dark night the dark night like this morning as I was doing other work
excellent film it's kind of amazing how many legendary lines are like all from
that one movie unironically incredible filmmaking okay anyway doesn't matter
fuck you voicemail God no one will ever figure out who you are you made it too
hard dude you fucked up I did make it too hard like I don't want to be mean or
anything but it's a little bit unreasonable just like guess who I am guess
who I am and we have to wait a week only to hear nope guess again yeah I mean how
long are we gonna play this game out I mean like it's already annoying when
you're in real life next to the person and they say hey guess what I have or
something guess guess guess guess this thing and you guess once and you're
already done with it like you don't want to hear more so just just just come out
with it we're not gonna we're not gonna do this for months true true well okay so
that that all being out of the way we've got a voicemail called not surprised
just disappointed okay and let's play it one two three here we go a KPCP here's
a list of potential characters I'd rather get fucked in the ass by Ben
Saint Betty's real gentle Digi bro I'm not getting fucked by a little girl
endless Jess to Harry best guy ever yes sure why not so in conclusion your
all terrible homosexual lovers don't you ever be looking around here for work
again well okay you know I thought that was funnier the first time I heard it's
alright it's fine and you all appeared apparently I don't even understand the
premise it was that people I'd rather be fucked in the ass by but he objected to
most of them and then said he would I guess he's ranking he's ranking us he's
glitching out something like that well checked okay that embarrassment behind
us let's move on to the next one this is from Hiki Komori Rambo okay all right
here we go and play yeah so this one goes out to Ben Saint yeah I just started
a pretty normie office gig and I noticed in the break room on my first day
there was perched atop the refrigerator a box that stated slimfast keto peanut
butter cups and not only was this box perfectly at eye level with me but also
etched on the side and Sharpie it said please eat these and you know you really
can't ask for more of an open invitation so I decided to take the box down on
sheath one of the individual peanut butter cups and eat it and you know Ben you
get a lot of shit on the podcast whenever you talk about keto I don't really
know as much as I would expect I've had a pretty open mind so being able to
actually experience something keto certified like literally says on the box
this is keto mm-hmm I have to say completely you know bias free it was one
of the worst fucking things I've ever eaten in my entire life dude anyways my
question is why are you so good you fucking douchebag okay you want to
have something that's keto and great eat bacon there you go yeah eggs second of
all what he doesn't say what what was wrong with them did they taste bad cuz
I think that was his point I had sugar-free chocolate shit before and it
has given me ridiculous diarrhea because some because some like artificial
sweeteners can give you fucking crazy diarrhea yeah that happened is that the
problem did they just taste like shit what how do they taste like shit I've
never some could have given us more some people I don't know some people are
like really sensitive to the taste of like artificial sweeteners and can be
like oh like stevia has a weird aftertaste sucralose has a weird aftertaste
gross I pity those people I really do because to me there's like they're not
new types like Ben over here literally cannot tell the difference between
like something that's sweetened with sucralose and if you're doing if you're
doing keto correctly you shouldn't even be having artificial sweeteners
because they still trigger insulin and you don't you don't want to have an
insulin reaction just just eat fats and and proteins
fuck everything else well it sounded like it sounded like a rookie's first
attempt at pouring into the world of keto and it went catastrophically wrong
making making a rookie mistake is fine casting judgment on an entire
fucking uh mindset due to what you can do it as a vehicle
to dab on Ben I mean who's gonna turn that one I don't think honestly I think
this guy's arguing in bad faith he didn't he didn't lay out a
cocaine case for what was wrong what was wrong with the fucking peanut butter
we'll name one thing that was wrong with those fucking peanut butter cups
there wasn't enough p there wasn't enough nut I think too much nut not enough p in
my opinion that's gross fucking all right let's move on right along here we've
only got one left we only got one voicemail left oh my god yeah that's
right that's right and this is from uh Harlock Asnable who's written it I
think he oh I think I know what he's gonna say I think okay he's gonna remember
well I'll tell you I think this is probably about the fact that Harlock Asnable
who famously got a girlfriend at uh got an anime club oh that's right he told me
I think it was on twitch twitch.tv slash st comics with an x dab
that his brother also got a girlfriend for an anime club not the same anime club
a different anime club okay well let's let's let's see if I'm right and that's what this is about
all right Harlock uh three two one go yo update on anime club gfs um my little
brother went to an anime club at his high school and he also got a girlfriend so nice
this is really starting to be a threat to society you know what I mean yeah but uh
I'd also like to make it clear that I am making a bet with ben saint yeah if I'm not with
this anime club gf that I'm with right now till February uh I'll give him fat stacks on his
patreon but if I am and he was wrong he did make it to February I'm giving Nate bestman
now we're talking baby oh yeah that's the rules of the bet here we go February that's right
specifically Valentine's Day fucking be there be square why why does it make me why does it make
me so much more angry to imagine Nate getting money from me losing than it does to imagine just
just me not getting the money from all I can say to this is hashtag gamify your gf boys across the
world gamify your gf this is the right way to structure a relationship I have no doubt about
it make it so that it's a bet if you stay with this girl not based on like if you like her or
hey hey harlock hey harlock great great way great way to make make me win is tell her about these
voicemails okay consider that possibility if you wonder she knows I wonder if they know about
this I would be fascinated okay no because I think when the first called in I said we said like
Valentine's Day and I said oh they won't be together by valentine's day oh this motherfucker I think
statistically probably true well I don't know who knows yeah who can who the fuck knows I like
to think that our boy harlock is is gazing lovingly into his anime gf's eyes and he's like honey I'm
so happy to be with you I feel like we're gonna be together be together forever rolls over picks
up phone calls and what's up PCP I want to make a quick bet over here I think I'm gonna be with this
bitch forever just letting you know you know money flipping it around I mean no matter what this man
is losing money it's either going to Ben or to me based on the stakes of the game here that's why
I mean that's it's just fine with me relationship involved in this until now you know you gotta
have those fat stacks if you want to keep a woman in those fat stacks of pancakes you've got to be
given fat stacks to either ben saint or best guy ever on patreon if they're gonna be the only
glance your way it's the dichotomy of man uh really either one of these two it's the only way
well uh well best of luck it's spicy it is spicy well done I'll be eagerly awaiting now so uh what
is that wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait get your brother get your brother to call in I want
to make the same bet with him oh yeah that'd be great I want to double the same stakes let's take
his money as well as one of us or the other oh maybe me and Ben can make a secret bet uh to no
matter who wins we'll split the money 50 50 and uh I mean I guess then we there's just no there's
no edging our bets eh I like those odds okay well we make corruption aside
guaranteed corruption aside collusion that's yeah collusion yeah that's the end of the voicemails
everybody but leave us more at the speak pipe link down below somebody called in and was saying
like it's hard to leave a voicemail um to like get the audio quality in but we had a wasn't there
a solution that like oblivion had in order to get like a high quality audio upload yeah but who
remembers that I don't know how I know how to look back at past episodes if anybody remembers
like post in the comments or something and I will like add a little document to the description of
episodes if people want to do that because it seems useful to have just because some people care about
like the quality and there's some issues with that uh okay but nonetheless leave us your
fucking voicemails don't overthink it but also make it decent or you won't get played uh we're
culling as you can see on this episode um and that's it patreon.com slash the procrastinators
five dollars for bonus episodes game development one was recent that was a good one there's like
32 total episodes what a steal uh and at least one dollar getting the pcp patron lounge what a fun
time that is for all uh what else we got uh at tpcrastinators on twitter updates releases etc etc
send a shit there um and uh I think that'll about do it send more voicemails we need them
always happy to have them and that's it uh patreon.com slash pcp minecraft if you want to play
minecraft with us today as soon as you're done listening to this we're like about to start streaming
I think like right as you fucking hear this shit or maybe we already have so uh give us five dollars
and you can play with us for a month and then a month after that for another five dollars and so on
until the end of time peace be minecraft forever all right that's it we're done see you next week
everybody thanks for being here have a good time